[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
oh yeah wow yeah
oh
um
[Music]
mm-hmm
oh
[Music]
wow
junkers that's movie
ah
bye
okay so Chris is having a little bit of
a I want attention time
[Music]
um
boat engine
oh she's scratching the tree yes yes
give it a good scratch oh no that was
smoothie wow
[Music]
um
hello
[Music]
chunky wonky cute
how's it going guys
key
energy local
uh energy.com
[Music]
I'm going to unpack something now
because
I picked up something
from the post office
yeah
oh oh
um
it's not capturing though I I see it
oh I'll think about that later
I think it's my toaster
I think this is my toaster
out
pleasure
my toaster
[Laughter]
it's my toaster
it's so small
it's so small it's so cute okay I wanna
take a picture
[Music]
oh my God
treated myself to a toaster
yay first pizza Arc now toaster Ark no
no no no
[Music]
no
she's trying to get the cat hairs off of
my mat
I bought a new matte desk mats too but
that one's not here yet
okay
um
[Music]
and then I opened the toast
how many slices
you'll see oh it's so cute
it's so so cute
oh
my that is incredibly adorable
oh my God
wow
that is so cute
let's take a picture like this
toast
okay
the way I will get this onto the stream
is I sent the picture to jenma
[Music]
okay
it came with a USB cable
hooray toast or the USB cable is not
even that short okay
[Music]
um
oh okay oh
is it gonna light up I wasn't that
something with you charge it no is it
does it always have to be plug in the
power supply to activate the night light
full of charging
indicators light off and on
what
it's just me or was that not proper
English
plug in the power supply to activate the
night light yeah
full of charging indicators light often
on
hmm
so I assume when I charged it fully the
lights will be constantly on
or so I don't know what
can I find the opening of the USB slot
without looking yeah
if I did I think I did
oh
it's so tiny
how do I take a picture
there we go
oh
[Music]
now I wonder if I can really charge it
ah Jen my likes my toaster
okay okay reporting for Duty Hello I'm
just
you guys just currently have to imagine
me unboxing a toaster but let me show
you
I can show you my toaster
I showed you my toaster please answer
okay came in the cute box
um
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
and then you unpack
and it's so small
it's so small
yeah
okay it's kind of dirty don't don't look
I mean
that's why I'm getting a new mat okay I
mean I could wash it too but it's just
you know black black shows off the dirt
quite easily anyway cute
foreign
I have a real toaster too
[Laughter]
and then and then you know there's this
little little handle on the right side
it's the toasters
um love handle
it it gets pretty bright
even though it's so small
so cute I will keep it on my table
[Music]
yeah
okay it gets even like it doesn't look
so bright on the picture because you
know well it's it's still daytime as
well
you know
hi
okay so I have
a little snack sandwich for later
and I have my vitamin water that I still
trust and believe in
yeah
and I have chocolate for later in case
we need it but I don't wanna eat
chocolate I feel like I'm so unhealthy
right now
um
toast for later yeah if we want toast we
can just
you know make us some toast some fresh
toast
it's so cute my new friend hello toasty
toasty cute
killed
okay
I wanted to show you that my my new my
new desk buddy yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum
Yum Yum Yum Yum orange juice I like
orange juice maybe I should just go back
to orange juice
you trust in in orange juice but not in
vitamin water is that what you're saying
man
[Music]
why that's my
why does my thingy not show
oh there you go
[Music]
how long would that take I wonder
ah not so long
okay
well then let me take a sip
water
ah
foreign
not that I'll be playing the DLC
on stream
but
I guess
we should install this anyway maybe
so yeah how's it going guys
the DLC is pure suffering oh
oh
um you're doing fine
good for you
maybe at the end of the stream we can
talk about the Mario movie and then
really at the end of The Stream So that
we I say okay who hasn't watched it yet
please leave the stream now
early we're just gonna talk about the
Mario movie and then
um I'm gonna end the Stream
I'm watching it today so yesterday
building a desk today oh good luck
DLC is damn hard oof
might have to leave stream early to see
the movie with some friends oh okay
okay have fun
Anime Boston and watch Amara movie
oh oh thank you for the membership
hello no problem
I've not seen it but I'll still listen
no
my Star Wars remarks no I mean I only
said I didn't like it
I just felt bad uh to my viewers because
I know many of them like Star Wars
and and then I felt bad for not liking
it
[Laughter]
you also saw the extra credit scene nice
yeah without spoilering anything the
extra credit scene what appeared there
was something I feel like was lacking in
throughout the movie but if you think
about it that way
they I guess
didn't include
certain characters
um
anyway that you know people would have
been happy to see but I mean they also
included a lot of others
um
yeah
I mean I like I would have liked to see
I mean people know right that there is
no counterparts right of you know people
know why this is not really a spoiler
I mean a disappointing notice but
like you know ah [\h__\h] I should keep this
for the end
I should keep this for the end let's not
talk about it now remind me to talk
about it later hmm
let's talk about it later about the
Mario movie I want to talk about the
Mario movie
[Music]
I should not try it I should not I
should not have my new song
I should not hum my new song
[Music]
bail I am your
sister that's right
well even if I humid for a couple
seconds
instrumentals and all that and no lyrics
so like how I think it could really tell
you much about it
um
it's worth it even if I don't do the DLC
up there it will you will receive a set
of engaged weapon refining materials
when you enter the thumbnail after clear
in chapter four
and I can obtain bones content from the
Nintendo Esha for free what why don't
you just
but why don't you just give it what does
that mean why don't you just give it to
me now what
why do I have to go to the Nintendo
eShop
and enchanter and Mage cut on your
classes oh hey a new class ah but only
if you do the the new story hmm
what is this free content that I have to
go to the Nintendo eShop for
yeah I think the weapons from heroes are
free now about playing it
ah some people like to know ah okay
um Iron Man run I see
72 hours
let's go
[Music]
did you hear that bgm
what
crystals
and she's basically like
oh
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
and this is
for my engagements
what can't happen the song is so gone
loveier talk to me
mavier I'm curious what are some of your
favorite things
why would you wish to know he's gonna
start singing My Favorite Things he's a
token of my gratitude
a gift from the Divine Dragon for what
reasons
your veil's night yes Vale is alive
today because of your actions
she is my only sibling and I cannot
thank you enough
do you understand why I might want to
reward you for such service
I understand however knowing I have your
gratitude is reward enough only my
gratitude
I am pleased you value my efforts to Aid
I am not a good person as your former
enemy pardon me I am needed elsewhere
mavier you don't
okay
[Music]
sorry that wasn't so interesting
oh
there's so many
car too many
hey Ivy yes do you think I could be like
my mother someday I mean obviously I've
got her looks already but I'm not sure I
have her other qualities you know
I think you do you lost her when you
were seven correct
yes but you kept living in the castle
even without the benefit of her
protection you know what a Viper's den
of in-free that place is no ordinary
child could survive it but your charisma
made that possible
what are you getting at
your wit and charm when you allies in
the court and a safe place in the castle
sound familiar you thrived in the
academy as well you even skipped enough
grades to catch up to me and girls done
by virtue of your own Merit
do you see it yet
you said you hoped you could become like
your mother someday
but you already are
your light shines on everyone you touch
just as hers did
I I can't believe that's how you see me
thank you I should be thanking you your
example has given me courage more times
than I can count thank you for shining
your light on me Hortensia
oh I'm gonna do all I can to live up to
the image you have of me it was so hard
not to just despair and give up when we
were separated father was gone you were
gone I had no one why does this voice
actor not become a YouTuber
from now on she's incredible that better
be a promise her voice is so good
getting rid of me absolutely
we will never be separated again I
promise I am blessed then [\h__\h] with them
actual retencia
I will never willingly let that go good
both of them me neither well that didn't
mean Hortensia specifically
um
[Music]
Prince all Chris
we know you can hear me
Princess Hortensia please speaking to me
will only dampen your mood always a
bundle of joy you are
that's exactly what I want to talk to
talk to you listen I'm gonna help you
get some confidence just like you asked
what really oh thank you why did you
change your mind you seemed so strongly
opposed to it earlier that was a joke I
got carried away sorry I may not love
brodia but you're my friend and when a
friend's in trouble you help simple as
that princess Hortensia I
hi hey what's with all the tear actually
you're kind of cute when you get all
emotional oh anyway let's get started
shall we no don't come any closer
please don't look at me like this
huh
[Music]
you agreed to help me Princess Hortensia
you are without a shadow without a
wonderful person today is praise
Hortensia day it's a deeper Heights
almost went to despair what kind heart
shines too bright it reveals my heart
for the worm written filth that it is so
please don't come near me spare me I am
so so sorry
spare me or spare me that boy has
self-deprecation down to an art form
oh Chris please
don't be such a drama queen
princess Hortensia you're not busy all
right let's grab a cup of tea
I know I'm irresistant resistable but
I'm also a princess you shouldn't be
hitting on me not up to anything I
promise
exchange of ideas
the innocent if you want but even in
illusion we've heard what A Flirt you
are people talk about me all the way in
illusion I'm flattered you wouldn't be
if you heard what they said
why put stock in Gossip I want to have
tea and learn of each other's countries
that's all no thanks besides my sister
needs help today hey you're a prince
shouldn't you have a ton of work too
Psalm is a queendom so my sister is
first in line to the throne oh
so you just wasted the day away
wandering around and
learning patrolling oh okay Ben you
definitely got me there hey why are you
helping Princess Tamara ladies in
control
oh well if you happen to change your
mind and decide you like tea just tea
I'm around
oh my God why is everyone hitting on
Hortensia She's Mine
[Music]
stop
oh
Archer conversation
hey Prince Alquist quick question how
can I become an amazing Critter like you
why do you want to know about that well
I was thinking about our somewhat
abbreviated conversation the other day
you know how our situations are similar
but our personalities are and I thought
maybe the difference can be explained by
upbringers I see
broad details with you but be warned
it's not very interesting
that's totally fine I was born the
second Prince of brodia with a
significant age gap between my brother
and me as far back as I can remember
people have praised my older brother for
his skills one could not ask for a
better successor to the brodian throne
they would say but when it came to me
the thing I heard most often was
diamont would have done better
ouch so you always felt like second
fiddle
that's rough it's my own fault I'm a
lost cause you ever just snap and save
forget him look at me no never I would
never allow a thought like that to cross
my mind my brother is perfect that's the
plain truth
it's not his fault I can't compare at
the same time
I am aware that those truths form the
backbone of my gloomy personality so
instead of holding a grudge against him
you just accepted that you were inferior
kind person maybe that's why I like you
so much oh kind that makes him kind hmm
you're saying you like me
you're sucking He's Surely kind but I
wouldn't think that makes sense dragging
you down I have to go again I'm sorry
I'm sorry
oh
he gone okay I'll Chris
Jesus Christ
gold Mary I hear you are quite the chef
chef
I'm sorry to say to the Chagrin of all
lesser Cooks wait my talent in the
kitchen has no equal did she
recently made good food oh was she the
one who [\h__\h] up my food though was it
real does she really cook well I don't
remember we have others weighing heavily
on me
but I suppose that is the price of
greatness marvelous bad being such an
expert might you be willing to teach me
maybe no there was one more well it
might have been off screen to my great
shame I know nothing of The Culinary
Friends of the royal family I ought to
have yeah
don't you think naturally but giving you
my culinary Secrets would mean more
competition for me I assure you I do not
wish to steal your thunder all I want is
to please the boss if it's purely for
the Crown Princess all right
out of respect for your devotion I'll do
it I will gather up the ingredients
be ready to get started next time Wayne
thank you I will not forget this
kindness
[Music]
ah yeah that was me did you notice that
was me I'm such a good actress
easy
well look what we have here it is
Princess I trust you are well today
princess saline okay always brimming
with energy aren't you
naturally my spirits are constantly
Rising I have plenty of cheer to share
unfortunately I've just come from tea
time but I should be happy to take you
up on that offer at a later date that is
disappointing perhaps you will indulge
me in a round of mock combat then
exercise is always good just after tea
come now is that all they do up there
tea and mock combat
no other person
what a life one moment you invite me to
Tea and the next you challenge me to
Arms there's many who would behave that
way around a princess
will not get you anywhere I mean there's
also Dragon minigame but I'm the only
one playing it but the two of us must
sit and chat sometime of course
that is what friends do indeed it is
foreign
[Music]
a bit more
please bear with us
yunaka I heard a rumor that you're very
good at doing impressions is that true
does that be I do them from time to time
for a giggle want a demonstration here
goes oh I am emblem Corin I'll fight
with all I have oh how about I am Ivy
Crown Princess of illusia doesn't you
get the idea
I found you you were looking please
I need you to join me on stage bye H I
take it you mean the kind for you get in
front of people and sing and dance
exactly that kind I've been
choreographing a stage play and I am in
need of an actor
[Music]
what you're describing is
impossible
I swear I won't let this be a bad
experience for you
I can't make this performance happen
without you
you sound so sure if that's really how
you feel about it I guess I can give it
a try thank you just remember if it
turns out I'm terrible at this I did
warn you I promise you there won't be
any blame only gratitude I know what
I've just seen that Patrick Watson
Amelia
Channel whole life Ian
fake fake fake
imposter
princess saline may I ask you something
can't fool me are you aware of a hill
broadleaf tree stands alone broadleaf
tree none spring to mind why do you ask
I do not know if you are aware but I was
born in firenay throughout my childhood
my family would travel to that Hillside
the name of the region eludes me but I
will always remember the beauty of that
scenery I wish to visit that place again
if I can my goodness
had no idea that you hailed from
fiorinae but you've given me little to
go on when it comes to the sight in
question I apologize I realize now how
little information I have to offer for
the search I have wonderful memories of
my days there
sometimes I can almost smell the air you
carry a profound emotional attachment to
this
very well I cannot abandon the plight of
and I shall do what I can to help as
Princess Sofia thank you princess
okay
don't know what's more boring this or
the Star Wars movie
[Music]
but I have to say like yo like there's
so many characters and so many character
combinations
like damn respect that they make so many
dialogues right respect to that
thank you for Lending me your strengths
Lin
I've come to rely on your power a lot
thank you all Crest I've come to rely on
your power as well you're quite skilled
yeah I shouldn't make them I shouldn't I
shouldn't turned them against me
oh
nice
[Music]
in the world I come from my bracelet was
entrusted to the kingdom of Illusion
between us
wow okay friend zoned
[Music]
and yunaka with Korean
I wouldn't have guessed it by your usual
cheer but you're quite cool in
calculating in battle what me nah that
imagination's gotta be what makes you
such a clever fighter though
okay we did it
I want to do this off-screen
oh well
ah
um
so last time in case you don't remember
last time we got I think all of the
Rings back
and we managed to get Veil
on our side what are they all doing here
playing with the dogs I thought they
were items here
no oh
yeah I am I am a ring as well
or no I'm an emblem now okay
yay
I am the Fire Emblem
oh oh that's copper Veil
and bell and um
[Music]
I don't know
I can't see y'all
oh there's nothing that they both like
really
look at that
Veil and
[Music]
wait
they land Annette
okay they have some stuff they both like
um
but the specialty
oh
special they're not so
not so in sync there mm-hmm
let's see I want to find a better
matchup
is there any good matchup
see down
[Music]
oh wait they don't
oh come on
Vale and Alfred
really
neutral on that one
[Music]
wow okay maybe
can't help it
oh wait literally feel this like this
like
this girl girl who
why is she so picky
[Music]
check the well ah okay did I put
something in there
hmm
all right we're gonna go for
we're gonna go for on it
freaking controls
[Music]
can I
I'll just I'll do you how about this
no okay okay whatever whatever
I will choose you
grapes braised beef and grape sauce you
mean like wine sauce
hopefully
that could be very good
these utensils aren't weighted Ah that's
where the another win for Etsy
oh I don't want to do those though did
we eat it again
she liked it yeah I could get used to
this flavor
see oh that's not even so bad whoa look
at those stats
okay nice suit
what else do those items but it's also
just for the Santa loves our house
uh-huh
I see let me take a quick peek
what
is it gonna be a portal opening we have
been getting reports lately of a strange
presence coming from this well I have
not been able to find anything unusual
about it but perhaps you should
investigate
if you want
yeah but then I can't change it back
right
so I would have to do that like at the
very very end but
[Music]
um
I have to complete it all at once you
can return to the world the main story
between chapters if you like the Felix
analog also has a difficulty setting but
what is even the the story like is it
good is it important
it is DLC so it can't be that important
but
is it like worth doing
[Music]
nice addition
alternate realities
alternate universe type oh an alternate
reality
um
let me know well if I can help
feel cute
Vale
why are you looking at me like that
I just
are you really okay I really am
was strange
taking corrupted form and waking up from
that but I'm by now
and it's all thanks to you Vale I'm
relieved I
I also wanted to apologize for
everything I've done
everything I did in the past so many
people died
and it's because of me
I was too pretty sickening my fault
they're dead I know I can't be forgiven
not completely
but if you could even just a little
I'm so sorry oh fail it wasn't my fault
the fell Dragon was controlling you he's
to blame not you you could say you're
weak but it was your strength that freed
you from him
that's impressive thank you I'll get
stronger too
like I said before I want to be a dragon
like you ready to save the world and
I'll do everything in my power to make
that happen
I just hope
you'll help me absolutely that's what a
big sister is for and I can to help you
it's the least I can do to make up for
not being around don't worry I'm right
beside you Littles these are the only
important we can do this together
conversations we can
yes they can oh support levels see I
heard that
because she joined so late it's pretty
easy to get there
um
support level up apparently
[Music]
hello guys
lazy little shits
let's see
we need to
go
am I blind other
I thought oh my god
well let's go swimming with
Tamara and
um
when I do confirm does it confirm the
others too
thank you yeah we can continue with that
sure sure
why not
comes back
the results
[Music]
okay let's get the results
oh
for yourself even
more support conversations
[Music]
here you go Divine One enjoy did you uh
cook me something yeah and it's got
spices that'll keep you warm I also
gathered some healing herbs for you here
you go she loves me
thank you this is all great but
he love his name you said something that
opened my eyes
if I'm gonna be for real Charming I need
practice helping people I'm sorry for
the way I acted before
do you forgive me of course I was never
upset with you to begin with I'm glad to
hear that everyone loved my mother
because she was both charming and kind
I've got a long way to go to be like her
but thanks for helping me figure that
out
you're welcome
and for what it's worth I think you're
well on your way I have to wonder though
if I do become truly Charming inside and
out who Are You Gonna Keep pretending
you don't care about cuteness
I'll figure something out
I don't know about that
about that change your tune we'll see
foreign
look I always look like an emblem now
down here because oh my God
this is this is the emblem bonding thing
isn't it though
sword wielded by Emblem kiwawa
effective corrupted IA
so that's like as if I'm an emblem now
right
[Music]
what'd you do I thought I was going to
die I mean I'm pretty sure it did Die 2
why have you screamed so hard I lost my
voice at one point
so what'd you think of your first time
tearing it up on Wolf back oh it was
exciting pairing it up almost back
you're such a Kidder lady I'm not
kidding not even a little bit
the miracle I'm still alive in fact
I believe I am alive
takes your mind off everything though
right
couldn't you feel your worries just
float away
I guess you could say that good
you looked a little tense earlier I
thought this might be a good way to
unwind what I do sometimes wonder if
it's okay for me to be here for all of
you I hear ya but next time you start
feeling like that you let me know what
the [\h__\h] guys what are you thinking
about
okay I will huh and Tamara
thank you
honey bunk everyone in the chat you're
lucky but I
huh
what are you thinking that I was
thinking
you little shits
unbelievable
uh what else is there
um
[Music]
Engraving I think because like didn't
they give me materials for that is that
how that works
how how does it work
how does that work
exactly I'm going to
chat dot dot dot you
for real
okay oh
okay no need to [\h__\h]
did I get this last time surely someone
will use it right
no way
we're fine that's fine
[Music]
oh wait there's so much cool stuff
a legendary short sword so a dagger
oh no my materials
are looking hacking weak I need some
silver
is this one good
can they only carry that their weapon
rank is s for that I'll be here uh wait
I need to exchange
I need silver
[Music]
iron silver
yes
what 110 10 1
.
holy [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
what I don't even have that much iron
either
and put out some dogs in the farm you
mean kill them
or just bring them out I already I
constantly have dogs there
so we have dogs there though
all right so one more thing that I
upgrades because it looks strong I'll be
here
[Music]
y'all bit
um
[Music]
okay anyway we have
all the Rings maybe we should like
properly distribute them as well but
um
what was I gonna do oh yeah who am I
gonna give that sword to someone with
swords uh S rank yeah
so kagetsu could have it
oh I can't even have it
surely
only kagetsu could have that as rank
sword
instead of
which one
[Music]
maybe instead of
the old sword
even though it's plus two
[Music]
hmm
ah it's a smash weapon
ho
yeah
let's use on slow and tanky characters I
mean I'm not using Diamond though
[Music]
um
it isn't a smash weapon well wonderful
okay and then we have a dagger uh could
give dagger to yunaka
only unicorn I think
[Music]
honey
what's smashes smashes this is a smash
weapon it seems
okay
oh okay did we get any other special
weapons
oh I was I just want to look at that
point
[Music]
ah yeah we got like a what brionak
although I don't know maybe we got that
before [\h__\h] House menu
is it I think so
is it the same type
[Music]
okay besides that
do we need to buy some more
yeah maybe need some mending
stuff
[Music]
and
perhaps some elixirs because a lot of
those were only one left over I wish you
could just take the several one
like single singular
ones and then like put them together
until free
now thanks for the membership
pack
[\h__\h]
and
mean
I think
wouldn't that be amazing you could do
that in all the game
[Music]
I see
okay
a step in beautiful feeling magic
recovers vast amounts of an allies hpe
oh I mean I have plenty of money I thank
you
I shall Buy
I thank you both and then what what the
exclamation marks are gone
[Music]
foreign
do come again
I thank you ah thank you I thank you I
thank you
thank you too level 5 14 18. so he's
gonna be ready for seconds little soon
right
uh 1719 also soon
19 soon
[Music]
45.
she needs a second sale doesn't she but
she came like this
I think I have a second too do what
fell child
oh no yeah that's what she has I know I
have a 40.
I actually took it up to 40.
um foreign
[Music]
am I not understanding something here
40.
wait after you give them a second sale
of once
it goes up to 40 then or what does it go
from 20 to 40 or
on screen ah once the level ah okay
[Music]
oh oh no it's just okay
oh
Oh I thought they I thought it was 20.
hmm
[Music]
okay one more thing we do this and right
now almost forgot about it thanks for
the membership for anyone
[Music]
yo guys tomorrow I'll be an anime Boston
first first convention
this year I think
or is it that's my membership yay
thank you
[Music]
I am all Crest a prince of protea I hope
it goes well I am Lucia I've been told
about it
quick
oh crit
is there
[Music]
um
I haven't heard of anything
on that matter
have your second sealed Celine I'm not
sure but her exp bar wasn't green so
probably fine
ivy Crown Princess of Illusion
come on let's do this
oh
I suppose
win
[Music]
she is winning of course she is
that dude
can we go again
yeah celine's level one right now
oh we'll be here
am I gonna be bringing a movie air in
the future
maybe hello
[Music]
the crime that you've been hi Mom guy
this might be dangerous no no no never
mind her level is way too low
ah come on I'm still so weak this one's
most valuable
guy well you seem a little bit biased
could that be
hmm
foreign
[Music]
here
Cantor
net
and for more beer too I guess you must
be more powerful than I was
I am sigured you think to do on me
stronger
[Music]
and you're acts completely different
around the Divine Dragon hmm But he
better
sacred no one here blames you
sorry
[Music]
itchy nose
oh
we're like no no no no
panette is not my Oshi just because I
look like her this is just how I was
born okay excuse me
[Music]
prepare yourself maybe
again
never win against an emblem
congratulations
you accept me although I once oh
Selena your shame has no
your shame has no values
I think he's trying to say something
nice but that kind of sounds
questionable
like your feelings have no value in this
world
[Music]
okay halitos again
uh
uh uh go to Vale
go to manage skills
no uh
what
why so extract
[Music]
oh she actually had a good amount of SP
thank God
even though we just got her
Santa
[Music]
okay
this is the only thing that I know when
it comes to skills
like what skill everybody needs
don't know what other skills to give
anyone at all
but this one I know this is the one
thing I know
[Music]
I mean they have two more slots Maybe
is there something else that can inherit
or is it only cigarette stuff right now
[Music]
yeah only stickered yeah
um I don't know
I usually run avoid plus 10 in Canton on
everybody
plus 15 is good
[Music]
for boys
plus from Linda's good I would give Veil
draconic hex instead of Canter and stick
silicone's ring on her for
double four range forearm debuffs while
choosing gauge
sound like silica is do we have silicone
someone no
[Music]
no
how do I give him a ring again
oh
[Music]
silica
okay
[Music]
there she's empty nice okay you can have
her gladly
[Music]
thank you
wrong sorry for Vale is the way to go
but Soarin also works really well on
on Ivy right so
[Music]
corn on unicorn oh yeah let's let's sort
this stuff out
um put me Kyle
this is the endless discussion
uh
Celine Celine we have rings again please
take one
um
where it's raining for Celine
[Music]
um
look I'm a ring
I'm a fancy ring
bye love
Mark or Celica
bye bye love foreign
I'm ready bye love
uh
what ring
for kiwawa
can I put my own ring on myself
why am I not why can I not choose myself
[Music]
night of course I didn't see it
because I don't normally look
on my calendar I use Google Calendar
what where where is that
[Music]
wait what Jesse jst
ah no no no okay stupid man
[Music]
never mind
hi hi hi no problem then I bring it on
kiwawa
[Music]
thank you
it's a card ah
I just went with more for her okay let's
keep Marvin I like Eagle Garden Panetta
too
um
because they they look through around my
rings we have to go through all of them
sorry
ah no
[Music]
all when s what no no we're using an
emblem ring
ikaya hotels
of course
okay spring
I'll Chris
I say Lynn
gold Mary ring
[Music]
Lucina
Roy Lucina oh
[Music]
interesting Lucina ready
yeah interesting
I'm gonna
[Music]
um
okay too
currently has Hector
[Music]
we can put Hector on someone else
Lucina
okay we have Lucina free right now we
can do that okay go go go go go go go
Ivy I'll keep
seedel
[Music]
sit down who do we give to see now
Camilla what who is Camilla
I don't have Camilla
picky
you need to get Camilla
yes it doesn't need a ring yeah I feel
like any ring one ring I think Tiki is
fine
sticky
[Music]
uh Chloe
Chloe currently has
Chloe ring is it good
[Music]
okay Annette and little God of who's
fine Celine and bye love okay uh mavier
mavier I was thinking
Hector
sir Hector they look like each other
even
and we currently have Veronica and
fogado which is fun so why not
[Music]
yeah they sued each other
we ripped Mikaya off of her finger
ah thank you for Super Chat Corinth
pouring corn corn
ah Dragon vein yeah yeah yeah okay
Tamara
might still use her so let's give her
something I have I have Tiki empty what
the [\h__\h] wait what oh my God
[Music]
Erica
yeah
okay that's as far as I'll go but why do
we not have Tiki on someone in that case
I will give Tiki to see though
Tiki in case we need an extra life
somewhere
um
okay
uh let me save and then we'll go story
time
I think we're ready to go
Two Worlds Maps
no I'm not doing well stories on stream
sorry no send a logs
[Music]
oh look everything's so sparkly
over here do I go left or right oh
there's like circles
and squares so I'm guessing the circles
on her story
is that lava fields
what a parallel Garden Of Memories oh
[Music]
right is there I mean the marriage ring
oh
okay gotta do this one a mysterious ring
isn't shrined in a place that feels
similar to The lifo's Castle Gardens
well I hope it's not too difficult
please make a choice
is there some some dialogue then I will
have a bite in my sandwich
[Music]
paper noise
oh my
are my eyes lying to me
this is quite a surprise
it looks just like the lethos Castle
Gardens so I'm not the only one seeing
it it looks like the castle but feels
like it too the air the smells all of it
right you are
I've served in the castle for many years
yet this Vision fooled me at first I
know it isn't real yet
Garden
ours were in full bloom
like these I remember it well
alas after the attack that Garden has
been left in ruins it has hasn't it look
over there
I can see something glimmering
do you see it too
is that an altar and on it
there's a ring
I thought we'd gathered all the emblem
rings
and it'd be that there were more perhaps
an emblem we were unaware of let's go
have a look wait
I feel a presence
there are enemies nearby
they also want to get married
corrupted maybe I should leave it for
them like what else would they have in
their life let them take it that ring
might they need someone to love in their
life I fight beside you once more Divine
One
that ring
could it be
no bander you're not going to fight next
to me
[Music]
back to the bench
um
what
[Music]
foreign
putting both units in an Engaged State
without the need to sink
do they need to have like a
the charge thingy
the sync skill bomb for girl
increases the hit rate and the void rate
of the user and nearby synced or engaged
allies wow pretties
the engage weapon Lou Rush relation
increases all adjacent allies engage
meters by one when the wielder initiates
combat
and defeats are full
the engage skill attuned greatly
increases engage Partners stats when
they initiate combat and defeatable
mm-hmm
when the engaged attack Dragon Blast
launches both a sword and Magic attack
dealing heavy damage
put the foes with high depth and rests
okay I don't I need to see how that
works
unlike other emblems emblem Kiana's Bond
levels tied to the ls support level
instead of bond XP no support level
translates to bond Level One support
levels
okay oh small map
but we're separated
I think they didn't like force Vander
into my team right yeah no okay
[Music]
um
let me bring in Veil and
maybe no sidel for this round
oh it's a mirror because I don't think
I'll be using her much in the last
couple of fights
but I feel like CDL is unnecessary this
time around
um
may look like there aren't a lot of
enemies but there will be
oh okay what do we have
I put the altars right there
that's it why are we right on the side
there has to be a catch there's now
I can't just go straight up and kill him
can I
but I'm right there
is there gonna be like something
spawning that I can't I can't
I can I could
if I want a shortcut is that it well if
I want exp I should do all of this or
what oh no I have to go ah
I'll do that first and then I have to
escape here huh
ah
oh he took the ring didn't he ah he took
the ring okay
that's him who has to escape
[Music]
okay but even even if there's gonna be
more enemies I think
I think
um this side also looks
special boo
depending on We're not gonna send
everyone for the middle already
I feel like one team through the middle
and one through the side Maybe
and I don't know what happens with the
left side but
you can come and find me
[Music]
I use Corn's ring to freeze them and
kill them and turn to
I see
Corn's ring do I have corn with me
Lauren was a white hair on it
I don't have corn with me right now
don't hold on
I could use like a freeze
um stick
unicorn
[Music]
um
okay
she is pretty close now okay I think
whatever
foreign
[Music]
can I go with just one unit if I wanted
to
fight whatever
works
oh
whatever you need
[Music]
um
I can't read
yet
does she have to be right in front of
him for that skill I don't remember
I've got this
ah it's showing me this again I guess
adjacent to an ally and has full
engagement you can select engage plus to
engage with them
wait can she not even use Mark I don't
understand emblem Kiana engages with the
Ally and Kiara also enters an Engaged
state
um
while I'm Kiana and the engaged Ally
remain adjacent Dragon Blast becomes the
even more powerful Bomb Blast okay I
don't understand dude let's just do it
[Music]
um
should I should have brought my dancer
devoted to you
[Music]
[\h__\h] I didn't even uh switch out the
steps
[Music]
rescue Unico rescue
Oh you mean like go here
rescue brings her
close by oh
and uh yeah I can
[Music]
I'm in France with tarantula Roar
um
[Music]
kind of worried about oh you're not
being all alone there though
I've made myself
[Music]
oh
any attack
[Music]
turn
all right the rest really
just can't reach what about this side
[Music]
can you guys do anything at all
do we have we have a Lin I can lend him
protect you
[Music]
I don't know if it's worth it though
I mean where why not I mean
[Music]
why still both the strongest huh
amazing and you guys you guys make me
get rid of Steel weapons but they're
actually pretty decent
[Music]
by my head
the fact normal is going to be over
before you notice okay let's see what
happens if I don't put too much uh
brains and thought into my single every
moves
foreign
[Music]
oh wait we can actually reach them
foreign
[Music]
capital of enemy range and you'll be
fine it's Elegance
Capital what is that I don't know that
word
[Music]
[Applause]
no way we can maybe do something I know
because it's only hand ax
[Music]
oh well
oh yeah
[Music]
and now it's on fire
I sounded like a
like a rooster in the morning didn't it
yes
what a lovely scene
[Music]
Grace and skill
I'll put ER I'll bring some down this
path of the way we were splitting into
Free Will I regret that guys
these are the regrettable choice to
split into three
[Music]
yes
maybe yes yes oh no
oh my God what's up
I converged into one
converged yes yes okay
have you guys already all the rest of
the game or what
[Music]
what two I will split into two though
I don't know how many people I need on
the right side though
we all finished ages ago I finished the
value in Japan
man you guys don't say this as if it's
like
um
a given
but
[Music]
I mean
others are still like ah
I can't keep up with watching
[Music]
you're so far ahead
and but that's also just you know
because the archives are long I get it
foreign
[Music]
okay I shall wait
my destiny
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
my goodness how awful
oh
leave her alone
my God
[Music]
imagine
foreign
[Music]
but how much damage do this car get to
do oh
not much
not much okay there must be a better
option
[Music]
Ivy is always the better option
relax
quick chance also pretty high we could
get a crit out of this
I bring everyone to the center to gang
up on the ring corrupted worry about the
sword masses later
[Music]
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
um
there's work to do
foreign
bar down yes with the oh but first that
would take too much damage no
[Music]
I mean he does only have a 52 hit Jazz
but
oh
only if I heal her first she'll she
should be fine though
I just wanna
be efficient
coin flip
[Music]
I might wanna use her afterward after
the first HP virus so I can
break him
[Music]
okay well let's go with the killing Edge
okay I will bring
I don't know I guess I'll do some more
over here
[Music]
I'm not looking good
we should all killed this dude
[Music]
well
served you right
level up congrats
okay
I'm scared I'm I'm chickening out
I mean I feel like I can move on here
with some characters
but
okay no no no no shame and a little bit
of a retreat
right
you guys told me that
kind of want to restart the battle
chicken
chicken thickening the chicken
[Music]
it's kind of lame to go back now
should I should I just restart
[Laughter]
I'll bring everyone to the middle now
yeah it would have been fine yes I know
but I don't like it
this is the state of how right before I
started right
[Music]
should be fun
okay
[Music]
foreign
again
[Music]
here
Quick Change okay you guys have a phrase
with any attack so let's see if I can do
more damage
[Music]
does do decent damage
oh but no no no I do the torrential
award because otherwise I get so much
damage bag
I guess from afar
wait how much how much does wait
torrential War
50.
well
[Music]
nah nah in the end
it's still better to do this I think
[Music]
it's fun also it's fancy so you know
see
[Music]
okay
I'm ready
I will do the same with Lynn I think
[Music]
as before eat
how do I look
[Music]
my will is firm
I thought I only have cramps I'll do my
best
because Chihuahua could not decide
wait if I if I do this now after they
already moved it makes no sense right
they can't move again
if I do that
[Music]
right
okay
I am full of vigor oh yeah but we will
start next to each other in the next
round whatever you ask so get will be
interesting
[Music]
his eye tissue
guys who do you think I will be marrying
huh and Fire Emblem
[Music]
I think at this point it might be
obvious
yes
I think I'll marry Jose I'll [\h__\h]
hell bastard
[Music]
they're all surrounding me on you
yeah who would you guys marry in the
game
it's just a game
fire emblems is just a game I can't
complain I do the same oh
oh
toys
gold Mary ivy
Ali are Ivy Veil
kakitsu
a married wolf girl who's wolf girl
ah that girl
oh lots of lots of lappies what
huh
sir specific reason why
hmm
[Music]
wait I should have started with engage
Plus
I think I don't know Ivy didn't even
start next to them
dangerous
dangerous dangerous
so engage Plus
engages ivy too
wow okay and then
but wait I want to use uh
let me let me get that one HP bar first
[Music]
and they lived happily ever after
no one marry him over here
I think he's quite husband material
though
you gotta think most of the chat is into
girls I think
so I understand the choice
[Music]
anyone for Vander
nah not really interested in bander
to be honest
[Music]
IO
I am bottom
I think what what what sticks what
sticks does she have does she have a
physique
[Music]
oh yes
big help
[Music]
what smart thing could I do over there
yeah I can't design because I mean I
want this one to go down too but uh
I want some of the signed mobs also to
go away
[Music]
okay this will be one thing that I'll do
oh no no I will call doubles
to occupy these guys with although maybe
not here
I wonder if there will be more mobs
coming from the left because if I call
Four doubles here I can't move them
foreign
[Music]
here
I think that could be good
[Music]
that would grab the attention I think of
the left ones and the top ones right
[Music]
just a scratch
there's just just a box just a scratch
[Music]
one zero
well
okay
now let's focus
on
the sky
liberation
[Music]
hmm
maybe a crit
no Chris
[Music]
no I want to do engage blood
I was gonna do it
[Music]
did I do it
I feel like it does less damage
huh
[Music]
no not Chris that looks like a crit
because it was so fancy
engage with marf would kill oh well we
have plenty of
girls around here
[Music]
um
who gets the finishing hit for this HP
bar
I say
panette with the handex
that's how it might be stronger when I
use it while we're still adjacent
[Music]
really
okay next HP bar
[Music]
they got like Sakura
induced hair
[Music]
half Miss
yo I keep on seeing so many kfps on
Twitter announcing that they got a
ticket
I'm really really happy in the beginning
right after it happened I actually this
was after the Mario movie
me and the the friends that watch the
movie with me
I did the unthinkable they wanted to go
into like a do you call it a bar
you called at a bar
probably
and so I ordered a mocktail and I looked
on my Twitter and then I saw everybody
tweeting oh I didn't get a ticket my
life is over it was all so fast and
I'm like what
this I only see negative sads tweets
then this happened while I was in the
movie
yeah day two apparently went better or
or Twitter just first shared only the
negativity negativity with me thanks
winner
um
it was a bit concerned I was very
worried about you guys I felt so bad
even though I can't do anything but I
felt so bad that it was much better
preset was bad it too much better oh and
then I saw like so many of you guys got
like two tickets so now you're all
sharing it's sweet
sharing is caring
very good
[Music]
I feel like by default you guys were
beginning to take it because
there will definitely be plenty of kfp
who didn't get a ticket and want one
it's always safe if you have the chance
just get two tickets and then you know
sort it out later nice crit Pac-Man
ghetto
[Music]
mmm
yeah many of you guys got it for someone
else so I'm happy hmm
okay oh
no
wait I have to kill all the mobs right
that's what routes the enemy means right
reinforcements
[Music]
yeah will they come to the middle I'm
done I'm good
they really want that ring
[Music]
okay
wait
I wasn't even dumb but reset
my turn oh
oh is that good or Nah that might be bad
it's not kind of bad because
yeah
could have been better if I did that
killing last and killed the others first
but oh well at least I get my turn again
now um
okay let's go let's go let's go
I wanna kill
give me that kill
Brave swords
what do you mean there's no kill in this
one
let us become one
huh
wake wake
[Music]
social
that pisses me off we get soup I mean
there is a 13 crit chance but it's not
so much
[Music]
but I would trust
that one more
all right
wow wow wow
okay no Chris wonderful
oh cry I guess we'll leave them alive
with 2 Hp
and see him suffering bleeding
everything out wonderful
uh enemies no enemies here okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] one two oh my God oh my God
there's so many now oh my God they're
like everywhere they're like cockroaches
hmm
[Music]
um
flying one on that side flying on that
side oh
I'll crushed
can't reach
I want to reach
[Music]
um
okay chill kiwawa oh let's chill all is
good look here me too not done yet
so no one can beat me how long is this
game too long
I mean I think it's a streamer
it's a bit too long as you know if you
play privately then hell yeah you get so
much value out of the game
so much play time how much does it cost
60 bucks
and you get like you can you can even
drag it out even more and get like 150
or 200 hours out of it if you wanna
the other games which cost 60 Euro
they're you're done with them after 20
hours think about that think about that
hmm
yeah
that's that's huge value and yeah replay
value it does have to especially I would
say free houses though
free houses more replay value than this
game in my opinion
[Music]
he's my hero because of the different
houses
surprise surprise
how does it freeze them
is that the freezing thing
[Music]
strong on heavy armor as always but damn
bill
that is incredible
[Music]
stay here
they can come can try
[Music]
I wish I had an ax over here I do have
penet but you can only throw the
handbags
[Music]
foreign
how does that work
what is there then
[Music]
there's only I mean like generally for
other games too
you just start over
[Music]
wait what does New Game Plus typically
do
you say orbit with like the same
something
[Music]
new game
harder you keep your items or weapons or
levels yeah that's what I thought
[Music]
you carry yourself over
I wonder why they brought it into free
houses but then
let go of it later
[Music]
really
I was like no way ten percent no way
I wasn't hoping for that ha ha
it happens when you don't expect it when
you least expect it
wow
[Music]
the horsey over there is um
probably gonna oh hi I didn't know this
[\h__\h] I didn't notice these people
[Music]
let's try this one
wait first one is zero
one person let me check the other one
when Hellfire would kill though why
would I try the other one
how long does she stay like this
also for free turns oh
[Music]
and then is her Circle used up
afterwards
by the emblems
I'll go back I'll go back
oh [\h__\h] they all they're all looking at
me
all three of them what there's another
oh with several health bars oh yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
charging plates are like on the outside
even [\h__\h]
hmm
Chloe please it's just like Chloe do
something
[Music]
Chloe do nothing
do nothing I guess let's go go
white girl go
with flame lamps doesn't
not do much really nice
yeah flame lens is decent by flameless
[Music]
works from a distance
I really like the gold white girl go I
mean I think I know it's kind of a roast
but I I really like
um
I don't know
somehow I really like it
is that the one with the enter
[Music]
yeah
yeah it is
should I do that here
[Music]
I hear it now
I'm a funny bird
memes meme
isn't really even a meme
[Music]
should I do it
do you understand
oh white girl go
yeah okay
enduring
[Music]
silver gray ones not even that bad
why not
but I will say kfp I mean I think it
almost goes without asking
uh watch
the chant videos and I I think I'll make
some for like General
oh armor Slayer wow welcome back welcome
back
[Music]
for not
um yeah I'm gonna make some chant videos
for me
some other like General whole life
English songs hmm
[Music]
gotta practice for tomorrow
yeah tomorrow hot challenge I will spoil
only that
I mean it's just a little convention
panel so
oh man hmm
[Music]
okay well that was it let's go yeah bye
okay well if he goes for uh if he stands
right there
I thought he was gonna attack the other
one oh was he going to Magic Victory did
he just miss
ah I know nevermind it doesn't block
because he uh the path because he dies
anyway
good that we have the auto Slayer
equipped now oh
so this one was going for a smash weapon
yeah
definitely I was looking
I agree
[Music]
okay all the doubles are going down but
they were so worth it
[Music]
um
hmm
did you guys watch
that um
it wasn't it wasn't really a stream
because it was a Premiere video
oh okay
on the whole life English channels where
they had all those like questions and
polls
[Music]
wait what yeah
no
yeah the whole trials
be nice
well yeah there were a couple more
questions I think I answered every
question but sometimes I didn't use my
answer but they used my answer quite
often didn't they and then the girls
were like let's go with koalas all the
time
pressure that assumption that kiwawa is
always right torso
it says it just didn't sit right with me
no one one was like uh which video is oh
my God
the most viewed one on the whole life
English Channel and I mean of course for
all these questions you could have
cheated you could have just looked up
the answer but I was like I'm not gonna
do that of course not
but I just assumed you know because I
think
is it still the automatic automatically
playing one
[Music]
but I feel like it might be
I think so yeah
[Music]
oh wait is there anyone here
oh
[Music]
well yeah I mean that's more that she
could have done
otherwise
yeah so I knew that but then another one
was like what is
what is the word for
a change of clothes
at like the end of the season
I barely knew that one
uh but I got it right I was the right
answer
and another one ah no one was like what
sounds does a mouse or rat make right
they were
all a keyboard master and I'm like why
why I don't know I just oh in Japanese
still what is like the the words that
you would write to create the sound of a
rat why would I know I didn't know
why would I not no because I
because like squeaky sounds
just because of Casper but why would I
know like what how is this written in
Japanese I don't know
I don't even think they considered
Casper because I didn't mention Casper
holy [\h__\h] I didn't even mention Casper I
need sick
[Music]
emblem engage
how much does that do yep
[Music]
but then
I might as well do it over here
I mean the flame lens does a little bit
more damage on the back ones
a little bit
but the flame Lance wouldn't kill the
front one
I don't
sorry
[Music]
we're From Below
what
[Music]
what why
moment ah because you walk more uh yeah
okay
but still
I guess I should go
[Music]
The Writer's pain yeah
at least it kills the frontals
[Music]
oh Max up oh
congratulations we gotta give her a
second steal afterwards
okay
waiting here
and then oh my god oh this is
still now oh oh
into my chair
[Music]
we're following attack
two separate times
[Music]
focus on one side over the other
oh but they'll run after me oh
[Music]
name my target
foreign
[Music]
I think I should
heal
[Music]
like
could she could kill that one
ah well she has counters so they can
kill that mob and walk away don't get
healed
[Music]
I blew it
well okay
I'll back up
[Music]
What if I
yeah they're all bad they're all
terrible
what
[Music]
Mamma Mia
who made it from Hardwoods normal mode
wow I can't believe you are suggesting
that to me now when I'm so close to the
end
can't believe it that's
that's kind of
the word belittling
[Music]
you don't believe in me
you don't want me to thrive
[Music]
you don't want me to get good
okay I need to shoot you down
can I not get like um a Kill
eh
kill a ball oh Chris I trust in you
although even then would it be a kill
even with a crit how much can you crit
I mean it could be right it could be
[\h__\h]
is double [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay I'll ignore the top okay I'm gonna
ignore the top
hmm
but I can't really ignore Teespring
ah
[Music]
yeah
bye I can at least I cannot no can I I
can drag in vain at least
um somewhere
[Music]
dragonvane is like um
bye-bye I will definitely lose at least
one
[Music]
North here
you're dragging me here you mean
[Music]
and that could still hide some units
inside the dragon veins
because
so like uh here or more like here
[Music]
yeah
I have plenty of pulses left
like eight
[Music]
that's the only thing I know to do
I can at least get a kill here
a facila sword or this one same
[Music]
result
okay
every one hit kill is precious
[Music]
Celine
oh
[Music]
I think that's worth taking some damage
no wait wait what did that happen for
now wait how much percent but the egg no
no bye bye-bye goodbye
[Music]
feed some more dangerous than the fist
users yeah I think so too I think so too
should I wear wine for that
no
Griffin Knights
I mean this is the the one yeah buy a
wave after that they're still kind of
far away so
we'll manage let's just have to survive
this one wave
you never need all the okay
let's hope I don't need them today
either
I wanna
just take a little bit
[Music]
what can I do
okay
[Music]
yes
that triggers me that that can't be a
Kill
[Music]
fire neither
it's California
before on
PHP
and the correction so here here I have
an even higher Christian
[Music]
how like if I
was getting rid of him
had to stop you
yeah I should be dancing
where's the dancer
I mean my my bailiff
ah up there
[Music]
I think if I stand here there's a chance
she could reach Celine
I mean yeah not
[Music]
no she wouldn't but
I was also hoping to heal up Celine to
be honest
connect me sailing but I might just have
to do the the heal everybody
thing now
maybe I can dance some Hortensia too
we kind of was the healing one right
[Music]
okay but before well oh no Okay order
wise we do everyone what whatever they
can do as long as they don't die and the
Hortensia heals everybody then I try to
dance
but I I have to try to keep keep like a
position maybe like
in this form across like this
because here I can't put anyone above
her
this would be around someone effective I
could cook I could put penet to her
right side
and Veil to her top
side or Unico
and then Hortensia to her left side
something like that
[Music]
um
with that in mind
have I already tried and then rewinded
this I did didn't I I failed but is the
RNG reset now
[Music]
a little bit different
I mean I think 68 is in general not that
long
[Music]
um
Maria could do it too
[Music]
shreddinger you want me to fail
you want me to film
[Music]
yo yo look he looks insane
yo
[Music]
you say he should engage
well but do you mean you should use his
is attack thingy but it's just Storm's
eye
stated that but still
engaging how to just make some tank here
[Music]
um
you're no match for me
[Music]
okay
sandwich gone
Marvel the best book but he will be
healed back up
[Music]
and he's tanky as [\h__\h] now
um
penet I guess
wait let me just take a percentage let
me just say the percentage
60 50 55 54 okay nope
but won't you always be like that
won't it always be like that
I buy a sandwich sandwich defeated
um
[Music]
diagonally
is that how it works with them
okay
diagonally makes no big difference is it
and at least you can
take
I could feel that Hopper it works and
then how many steps after that how many
steps can I counter back
I don't know
[Music]
you can engage in one shot it
and I go here afterwards
I mean I could also
do it do the cross here
and have our crisp pennant
Celine Maybe
and you knock out your Veil here
it's four down here yeah but over here
here would work right
[Music]
engage 100
no no no no no no let's keep it still
let's keep it
although
uh emblem
[Music]
but then I have to use a combat
okay
um actually I might actually want to re
uh re-dance alcreased rabbit and Chloe
so I will stand here
well yeah after
falling star it is what where
to me it doesn't actually become 100
I got one guide
then if it's still just
if it's still just 60 then I only use my
attacks
attack bottom bus instead you can detect
fire after dance
[Music]
you mean you mean the sky
oh true
about it
um
[Music]
thank you lankies
sure okay okay
oh that's um
not a bad idea actually
that one HP bar
and then where do I want to stand here
for the owl crisp dance or here
for the Chloe dance I think I'll Chris
right said here too
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
then
oh wait we can re-dance Ivy if we make
her oh wait no yeah she could she could
reach that right
[Music]
yeah
proforen or throw an L fire
[Music]
foreign
stand here
if I stand here
if I just stand here
would you stand with me and
just
crits this bastard
gold Mary gold Mary gold Mary
a
can we not first
get the HP board down we'll be uh but I
want red
Vail how far can you go oh well
who will do more damage to this enemy
Vale or goldberry Veil right
so I should finish him off with gold
memory right
yeah we'll engage bail afterwards Maybe
[Music]
I mean now after the first stage people
this one is gone
yeah
7 800.
we're killing us doesn't matter although
silver sword okay
hair you'll get no sympathy from me
[Music]
last eight people are
we will Dragon vein
here
[Music]
I suppose because I or here I don't know
still not sure about the dragon vein
position
yeah but I think left left should be
fine yeah
hello
[Music]
this one or the bottom one
top one top one could
[Music]
hug from the top ones too
not on the pillar
[Music]
yeah
I agree can you tell that that's how I
understood it as well thanks for the
membership
[Music]
now with Veil I would like to
engage help me be right
oh oh pretty just she's pink carrot now
ah what her thing is the Ragnarok
wait I haven't done the Ragnarok in a
long time does that do damage to all of
these foes
[Music]
oh
it's not anyway okay just the one like
right next to her
[Music]
[\h__\h] she can't kill him
I thought maybe she could
but we're done we will be dancing
we'll be dancing
[Music]
hey cool
if I attack twice
39.
and we kind of get the same results in
the end
but I got two assist attacks
[Music]
15. 15 and 5.
versus
31 and five
[Music]
what crit chance
okay
Echo does four more damage okay
need help
[Music]
hmm okay
can't stand in the cross though in the
dancing cross
but
still no wait Celine is the one dancing
but we could bring we could you think
Hortensia reaches
here
[Music]
I could she do her engaging thing here
nah
without it then maybe we should dance
here no altruist then but
more efficient
she's not gonna make it
okay then we'll dance here
I say
okay sorry this turn is taking ages
when uh dance
[Music]
I I will why do I do why do I do my
healing or do I I should do the healing
after dancing Maybe
and just first get the ones that have
good HP uh to move again first
and then heal and then the ones who had
bad HP at point then they can move right
and then first
[Music]
grant me your strength
proper planning for once
all right
[Music]
okay
um
there we go Celine
[Music]
all right
back in action
playing real fire emblem expert yeah I
am a real fire blood expert totally
Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe
Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe what
are we doing you
Chloe
Chloe has many options now
well we can go through the whole field
yeah I definitely brought a lot of
Knowledge from My Fire Emblem free house
play through with me
[Music]
thank you
the left fly with momentum
because that one is that one is not
affected by the
stupid
stuff here
and wait but how
[Music]
I can only use the javelin or the flame
limbs
I wouldn't kill him thank you thank for
the memberships
it's all right thank you
I wish you guys much Gesundheit as well
go behind him ah you're behind him
[Music]
so can't kill him though sadly maybe
with the killer man
30.
30 81 30.
[Music]
hmm
do we believe
[Music]
brisk it for the biscuit
do you believe
is that what she thinks
before
[Music]
she has such a funny way of singing how
do you sing like that
do you
believe I don't know how
maybe uh
scared mommy help Chloe gonna die
[Music]
do you burn
yeah oh well
[Music]
oh
um
kill this fire or kill the left flyer or
kill this dude
could also do a veil though so not
necessary
[Music]
all right we have connect to connect
not just checking just checking don't
don't freak out guys
[Music]
54.
64.
I'm so lost
[Music]
and I was just checking
I'd kill the flashlight don't kill her
attention
[Music]
what about the boss this boss I mean
it's not much of a boss now
okay better than nothing is true good
argument
then
I suppose
revealed to kill the right one with
Ivory because the left one
[Music]
thank you to find one
they're the only ones who can hit
with good accuracy
okay and then
she's just chilling there
can reach
whale Camp why can't you not reach now
she could
that all she can I thought she couldn't
[Music]
Echo
13. comes to we'll leave one [\h__\h] HP
[Music]
ah no Ragnarok left something as well
look
why
leave them and clear out the bottom
let's see what can we do with the bottom
oh
[Music]
I might just kill the boss here
ah wait I can do
this one first and then a little bit
damage down there too
yeah whatever I don't want to think
anymore
[Music]
nice level up
okay
I'm out of here
now
time
to heal
uh
I think
the left ones those fifths
it says the
can reach but they wouldn't write she
would would she be safe here
I I can't interrupt the word oh yeah
[Music]
where should she go beside the central
pillar she only gets powered by one
enemy
yeah but she has one HP left after that
probably gonna die no matter what
[Music]
I think I'll stay here
I have hopes here
[Music]
Central pillar
okay maybe we can go underneath after I
don't know
I need healing I need healing you'll get
healing uh you've got healing
yay
okay here see if you should save here
okay
so our choices with you are finishing
off that anime probably pretty safely
71 percent
or going for the flyer
[Music]
60 percent
raging Storm
oh wait how much does the phone start
16.
how much is the other stuff also 16.
45.
60. what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay at least this gives us a little
preview of what is going to happen but I
will rewind I think
because
I was gonna check the engage attack
[Music]
looking pretty safe over there okay okay
oh okay
ah
[Music]
oh oh oh oh okay does the RNG change I
better pull back afterwards always
you're not gonna Dying For Real
it will okay
I mean she might still end up dead but
what the [\h__\h] I can't believe I
I am because I
just let her wait there
Annette will be in a dangerous place
what is the flyer going to do
I mean now the connect is gone
for okay they seem totally fine at the
bottom
they're totally handling it all down
there now Chris is becoming a dancer
second occupation
[Music]
wow
attacking the flyer and the flyer
already went and attacked that oh okay
okay did he do that or did he missed
I think he did some damage didn't he
because Annette started off with low HP
just there
oh oh Moby is fun
more people could go for more beer if it
were up to me
it was little
oh it's dangerous as my phone you want
to be
now that we've seen the future let's fix
my mistake
should I only fix the last mistake
because I think yunaka
we'll see
we'll see how that changes
the one that killed her is this bastard
dildo the one who killed from that do we
have a chance of killing him
[Music]
we do
we have to flyer ends up not doing so
much damage
I'll be only able to go back two steps
right
that's not good
but
let's do this and then walk back slowly
in style
yes it feels like such a waste
must stay focused
yes because it's already almost been
three hours and we're still at the ring
map
okay here we go again pray for you naka
[Music]
zero zero
was that worth it buddy
[Music]
oh
what he didn't get a crate out of his
seven down
little shits
[Music]
oh yeah she did unless he misses
birthday
with 30 hit chance we better pull back
sorry I'm out of here
we got worse
huh
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my God
this is
ridiculous at least they're all missing
on Chloe I think Chloe was completely
snorted
okay and panette is alive
what the [\h__\h] okay
yunaka is dead either way so
I'll just keep it this way at least we
don't have two dead people
yet
[Music]
of course you hit as well
on my precious precious Veil
had to stop you orangey
oh no
I blew it I can't believe I lost
[Music]
maybe I should just say [\h__\h] marriage
I don't believe in marriage anymore just
quit this map right now
it's looking dire
God
if I die I die I guess
foreign
[Music]
use these stupid plates
eh
all the next story Maps gonna be like
this really really right away
[Music]
oh man and okay there's no more flyers
say where he got killed
oh my God
[Music]
oh
yeah man I don't even know what to do
we'll survive somehow I mean even if we
lose all our units are standing at the
end with one unit
we will survive surely
all right right
and what is it do they have
why don't they they're surely weak right
but like they don't seem to take damage
from me
at least not much
[Music]
okay I will kill this one first
thing
[Music]
I have to engage everyone now
yeah I think so too
I can't imagine
this one because
this is terrible
[Music]
okay okay
one down
[Music]
and where are our healers so we can heal
clogging Hill right
I'm getting hungry let me get out of
here I'll go don't we kind of want to
hurt damage too I don't know
she can't do that much
what's her stuff I'm mending okay
men's
or Hortense is still alive
I would say I meant Veil for now
I'm a glow
[Music]
yeah if I make it for this wave somehow
Mamma Mia
fail
whale which one do you want to kill
also use warp Stone
foreign
[Music]
what the hell
what what is it with these ones why
don't they take damage
[Music]
I I I need to do something else first
because I don't think I am
I don't
know
they have Queen adoption
I got the monks first
look these first ones
ah
[Music]
these ones down here are pretty
dangerous too though I don't know who to
prioritize
[Music]
I mean I know what the pillar does but
but why does he need to be on the pillar
right now
[Music]
the gold Mary first
um
gold Mary
doesn't really get her time to shine on
this turn
so I guess I'll
maybe in combination with Veil we can do
something here
[Music]
do some starter damage
is what I'm thinking
promise that even with Echo it's still
not enough to kill both of them
[Music]
oh well
right
I trust in you
[Music]
has 17 Crips
I believe
oh I was I was
disappointed okay
it was I mean a good
[Music]
chance a good amount of percentage
um
foreign
[Music]
flying
fortified ah
Ellie Hill hmm
[Music]
thank God I brought four to five
I mean maybe I should have done it a bit
later actually oh well
well well well I wanted to decide on
what to do now
[Music]
oh
you're in cup won on vacation
I
Capone I like couple when I've been
there a couple times for um medieval
festivals
that was one of the places
Cliffs um
pretty good Medieval Festival that we
went to
a lot
but I guess it's also good for skiing
hmm
[Music]
you didn't I missed that well it's good
times when I was younger a young young
young teenager or more like a child
mommy took me to many many medieval
festivals
it was fun I mean it was also partially
a little bit creepy here and there there
were some things that were questionable
[Music]
um
but also had good fun
and good food
very good food there
[Music]
would love to go to one
they were everywhere aren't they
[Music]
uh
I know but I don't know about
elaborating
[Music]
um
I should take the ones out that I can
kill don't you think
[Music]
You Are My Hope my light my everything
oh wow
I can kill that dude completely and he
can't do [\h__\h]
actually I should because otherwise he
gets really dangerous for Ivan
knit
[Music]
sexy damage him we had to stop you
cool
no Ivy she still has Soarin
uh
what's AOE man that's AOE just this one
there
[Music]
wait how does it it when I
I can kill the bottom tool of the old
[Music]
like these
signed decline Maybe
doesn't kill the right
[Music]
wait here I heal three times
wait oh sorry uh why
why is that
because ah he dies already in the first
one
but here I can continue healing
there's a kill when standing next week
[Music]
I can't
me
[Music]
well well
let's do it
from safe distance all right
wait why does it now show us a square
when I stand there but it shows us uh
as a cross when I stand here I don't get
it
who can one damage the other finishers
from over here
ah
[Music]
but in this case it doesn't really help
us so
no one else there
this is smart because we can heal Ivy up
even I wasn't even that low but you know
better than nothing could always
uh save our butt
look how they're like cornering me
unbelievable
[Music]
thank you
hi Raiders I am fight our way through in
a problematic situation
I think I want to offer mobile
putting him closer and then hoping
they'll go go for him
[Music]
there will be devs there's no way there
won't be
apparently
[Music]
who would have known
and he's my scapegoat
s
I won't be much use in the state I bet
it's true
bye bye Chloe
oh this one stands on the pillow 15 I
only have fifty percent no no no
[Music]
no
sorry
fail I'm falling back
pain doesn't matter
to rest so I can fight to the end how do
I undo that
Maybe by uh putting movie around the
pillar
instead
was he able to reach the pillar he
definitely was right
I will put in there
[Music]
how many units will I have left after
this
I saw the brought the dancer not because
of the dancing necessarily but for Tiki
so I have Tiki on him
helped me
oh but nice nice going over there one
two three four five six seven that's not
too bad
seven units
[Music]
you could restart keep takes me
yeah well
what about ivy
guys
is there a better position to be
where he wouldn't die
[Music]
wanna check
and she
is safer here
okay
emblem
[Music]
yeah
she won't heal up completely but she
would be safer you know
ah
there's an arch ah is that what killed
her
[Music]
he's in the tree I didn't see him
so I should have killed her
um
the other positions aren't much better
the question is just who will all these
people go for
[Music]
well
actually
if I will have to have mavier to help
out anyway down there to kill both of
them then why waste by cataclysm
and not just do it this way kill the
left one with more of the air because he
obviously can and then just kill the
other one Ivy decoy mavier yeah but then
I'll have to live a life that sword guy
[Music]
no I don't think I want to decoy now but
I want to fix this thing I mean I could
can I not
I can kill the other one
you won't leave me with one HP will you
no he I he will okay
never mind never mind
[Music]
yeah but where did I go
where did I stand I stood in an Archer
range you know so instead
cute dead
[Music]
she has high resistance to Magic right
so if I put that is another Archer
here
isn't that where I saw before
did that isn't it this actually that
killed me
[Music]
it's just one above before okay so it's
the top Archer that killed me
then if I stand here I'll be fine
[Music]
the bottom arches
no I want to put malviere on the pillar
he'll attack that bastard anyway and you
know
[Music]
here
hmm
[Music]
and mavia will just stay on the pillar
let's see how everything changes
[Music]
we had seven units at the end originally
hungry for more
does this change the state's the same
okay
I guess oh is the RNG the same
huh
[Music]
he's so far so far it's the same
it won't be much use
for Chloe hmm
Veil Bale no
no
[Applause]
she took the chair to crit his ass oh my
God thank God that might leave us with
one more unit alive
oh my God
oh Archer Prevail okay bye Veil sorry
um
[Music]
no more MVP a dead person can't be MVP
can they
okay okay see those are weak those are
weak as [\h__\h] so we don't need to worry
about them
12 12.
the last two units so far
this would absolutely wreck me if I
played on classic
12 12 again wait
I'm sorry device
[Music]
I must retreat
oh you said your relative
say it's a really sophisticated language
one two three four five six seven same
outcome
thing
same outcome but different enemies are
dead now I think
um
[Music]
you're cool
do we
do we wanna
go back one more time and try the decoy
actually
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
and then put him on the pillar anyway
though
uh Ivy does she have to stand right next
to someone to do that next one looks
like it
looks like it
[Music]
but then you can attack this one and
then move over here
and she can go there and make him
be close
[Music]
to
Storm's eye if he's the decoy
stance that always follows up those
cannot follow up
no
[Music]
crit
just need corn and grape on obviously
and give her the store and bracelet
it costs 20 hp
[Music]
no it doesn't Okay one guy
if I do that can I still move afterwards
I don't think I can
I
I'll just do it here
that's what I thought
ah
[Music]
sorry mother but you'll do it with honor
won't you
Chloe we already this is like read zero
we only already saw your face
have we seen this before okay
it's all been lost
Celine the fight for
new orangey now huh
I would have preferred to have Celine
alive okay okay okay okay okay no chance
[Music]
no chance
real life
[Music]
that guy that we kept alive is rough the
pink
okay two units dead
what is it
yeah
no chance
[Music]
Archer is fine
and fine
this is fine
this is fine this is fine
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
huh
one two three four five six
one two three four five six seven eight
one more
put here with one more unit stand before
okay
[Music]
be smart
let's be smart
[Music]
um fortify okay I might use four to five
again
[Music]
ah
where's that ax bastard was this one
um
[Music]
I don't even know I hate this map so
much
I hate it
[Music]
I feel like the kuya depths are still
kind of not dangerous
these boys are more dangerous
[Music]
killing the bottom enemies oh can I do
it again
I spent a whole map at the top and was
very manageable
yeah I didn't
I mean I I restarted once in the
beginning to fix one of my mistakes but
you know
[Music]
we'll keep trying to keep her down here
I don't know I'll keep her here
[Music]
she can tank him in the middle you get
sandwiched can you even call this a
sandwich sandwich gets sandwiched from
Tucson I'm getting sandwiched from four
signs
that's like
40 chess sandwich a slight injury
um
interesting
[Music]
I need a [\h__\h]
I'm listening
wait she has a charge so she's one more
charge
hmm
[Music]
um
Chloe I don't think I'll ever bring you
again because
not gonna lie you're kind of weak
I don't know
[Music]
but take down someone
Grant
[Music]
uh
what next was it next to Hector when I
get the big one yeah
well then let's move her
welcome with her so that I can do it so
I can get all this free maybe
thank you
which she could go like here
kill
the silver ax sky
I see
[Music]
I know I don't know what my clothes that
week oh man
[Music]
I don't know if that's wasted potential
in Gold Mary in terms of how much damage
you can do right now but
cataclysm
Oh that's
oh here here's fine okay
um
[Music]
are you ready to die
no decoy then that's what we're giving
up on
[Music]
but decent AOE damage
okay we'll survive I think we'll survive
I think
[Music]
gotta take the Archer down
maybe no need for
Fortify maybe go full damage this turn
[Music]
okay mavia can kill all three of these
you
are
what about the feet the feet is kind of
strong too
also we gotta we gotta stay on the
pillars
preferably at least afterwards you can
survive if the Mage dies
okay I shall kill the mage
[Music]
I'll apologize later
she got stat screwed maybe she did if
you say so then it's probably true oh by
the way I completely forgot I wanted to
finish talking about that topic from
that
from that video
[Music]
um
a bit
about
apparently I am Number Two mommy of
whole life English
I was
oh surprised
but then again it depends on how you see
the term Mommy because I I guess people
see fauna as
well modern nature but also kind of a
little bit
but not really she's a sweet adult
I don't know
is that why they voted for why did
people vote for is it the mother nature
thing or is it something else
I'm not sure
as American yeah I think that the whole
like image of her doing ASMR and
yeah yeah
I think it's yeah
sweet caring Aura and then for me
why did they choose it for me
is there anyone
here for Mommy
[Music]
I guess the whole mom and dad was me and
Callie and then
I I don't think people really think
about it that way when they voted for me
but the fact that I do have my chickens
um [\h__\h] I should have killed him from
here
[Music]
I do have my chickens
I drove my chickens don't I
um
[Music]
that I hatched and raised but I'm more
of a boss yeah
[Music]
I don't really see myself as like the
mommy type like the mommy type that you
think of when you hear about the mommy
type YouTuber
that's not really me
[Music]
foreign
was it who do you do you your mommy
[Music]
said it wasn't the boy's [\h__\h] the mom of
Halloween
[Music]
who do you want your to be your mom I
think I'll rewind this because then I
can also make somebody like cockatoo
stand on the pillar
uh
[Music]
oh yeah the fact that I cook so much
though
I guess could give you mommy or
girlfriend waifu vibes
oh kagitsu getting that unnecessary
magic that thanks
[Music]
thanks thanks well Chloe's still alive
damn
[Music]
and I was shocked that I was voted
number one
for
best
the one who would be the best at uh
making date plans that was the thing I
think
I was surprised about that
[Music]
the whole thing about me doing me
planning collabs and all that
um but that's not really date planning
though
oh well I do think that um
I can come up with good date plans
but I really wanted Cali to win that one
because she all the time when we when we
come to Japan or even without that like
you know how she would visit crony and
so on and me but okay when she came to
me I made the date plans I I made the
the plans of what to check out in the
city Etc
um but like when people visit Japan Cali
is like she gets so excited she's like
the whole time she's like oh I want to
do this so you guys I want to bring you
here I want to bring you this on so I
want to bring you to this restaurant I
want to bring you to this Yakiniku place
that but it's mostly about food but
she gets so excited
you think I can get a hit this time
maybe I should hit with this one
yeah she really wants to show off
uh what she knows and what she
what she can show off
she's really proud
of that and yeah she just wants her
gently to have a good time
to give them a good time
[Music]
so I will
not
uh wait hotel is a flying unit though
but I will keep I will occupy the pillar
nonetheless holy [\h__\h]
dagger my God wait how much percentage
.
wait is she my last unit
maybe [\h__\h] the pillar and go somewhere
else
that dagger boy might take me down
[Music]
maybe I'll go away but I don't want to
waste her potential either
maybe attack at least the queen adapt
from here and then [\h__\h] off a little bit
[Music]
I can't [\h__\h] off that much
I want that damage
[Music]
practical retreating style is best
I mean we're almost at the end of this
but uh there's still a couple more
coming from the top hmm
I shouldn't even Retreat to the self
because all the all the thingies are out
there
so sad
can't get to greedy
okay
do we have a physic so
and I'll hear Mommy here I think
[Music]
Javier he's kind of my big hope
at least feeling important
but anyway the quiz was interesting to
see what people think
like non-kfps as well what people think
of the other Ians
[Music]
although I think there are definitely
some
not so accurate Impressions that people
have
I also see that
uh in in those random polls that show up
on YouTube suggested even when you're
not subscribed to them
show up these four Halloween members is
this and that
some of the questions are like
hypothetical questions
but like
questions like who do you think is
something something and other questions
are like asking about facts that if you
watch streams you there's there is only
one answer and I what I mean is others
are just like opinions like
facts and opinions
but then even with the opinion one some
with the fat one some people still get
it wrong
[Music]
even though it's so obvious sometimes
okay no one died
no one died
[Music]
we are still a little bit outnumbered
though
[Music]
hmm
kogetsu still has uh engagement attack
right
no
no no cockatoo doesn't have engagement
um
all right
how we gonna play this
I can do decent damage on this wolf guy
[Music]
well I'll get decent damage back
I think I'll do my best call doubles on
it
with who
does that again
[Music]
I can't can I I can oh yes I can I can
engage again
oh
all right I'll do it on on the pillar
the cockatoo standing on that thing
[Music]
the wood owl is kind of falling behind
in terms of damage and all that damn
oh
kill the thief
this one you mean I'm trying to I'm
trying
[Music]
damaged one oh
I'll get there
lavier reporting
[Music]
why is this taking so long
a stupid queer that's I don't care about
them
go away go away
kill this one
try to come okay
nice
[Music]
he only has 11 hit chance
watch him hitch
this ends now oh
yeah
and I can go on the pillar okay
also engage again after this
okay thank God
thank God Hallelujah ivy
Ivy could assigned decoy
again
and we have the double decoys
and the more the air decoy
[Music]
or she can kill this [\h__\h] face
down here
I signed decline
Coin Attack for Ivy so she heals huh
yeah I mean the bottom unit
[Music]
Mamma Mia
what gold Mary why can you not do
anything
[Music]
fortify can reach allcrest if you use it
on the bottom tile of movia
[Music]
Below movie are you mean
one two three four five
okay okay
I benched her early so sad
[Music]
okay if we heal then we
um
sorry guys this is taking endlessly long
hmm
oh Javelin let's go down the queen adapt
what's the range of the flame lens 201
[Music]
cool
I mean two or three
that's that's what I meant
no oh
no no no no what the [\h__\h] I have to take
that fifth down otherwise he'll kill
anyone anyway
yeah you should go for the for mommy
yeah right
[Music]
rough
freaking rough
[Music]
I don't think I can do much more Chloe
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah let's kill a beef
oh
this is fine right
[Music]
[Applause]
we have to keep Ivy alive at all costs
are the queen adapts dangerous to her
[Music]
oh my God
nice
I see a light at the end of the tunnel
no whatever
it's okay because all the top ones will
go for the uh other decoys and the
bottom ones the queer depths are in no
nothing scary to me
yeah it'll be fine also I can still heal
down here so
okay and then the cold Mary we'll just
do some
a little bit of damage here
huh
zero okay yeah they don't scare me they
don't scare me no more
[Music]
that's the last move Frank
okay 45.
[Music]
huh
okay ah wait does someone left I am over
here oh
[Music]
yeah can you can you
77.
[Music]
have I made a difference
pillar kind of looking empty now though
[Music]
where should I stand
if I stand here I feel like the queen of
death will stand on the pillar and
attack mulvira but I guess he won't even
done he won't really do much
[Music]
okay let's end this [\h__\h] come on
Dodge Dodge no
Dodge
no
[Music]
oh man okay but at least after space
stranger danger stranger danger
oh I'm Chloe them
ridiculous
that is indeed ridiculous
huh
[Music]
okay
oh we're done with the jokes now
[Music]
my oranges pretty fast today
oh kind of disappointing but maybe I'm
keeping all the RNG for later
[Music]
where would it be helpful for me to
stand
let me just here
Mamma Mia
[Music]
does she still have no Cantor I just
realized I think she was still out of um
SP
Ivey
maybe let's do something cool
[Music]
most wanted it
hmm
[Music]
oh my mommy
decline
[Music]
I won't wait about that I'm not sure
about that one yet I am fine
[Music]
I won't fall
Chloe
what can you even do
ripples kills yeah it kills me
[Music]
I'll go 48 on this oh wait
hmm
who's left to heal
or tencia is gone
[Music]
right
me yeah yeah
who else
wait I can call more doubles what
what kind of questions
what are we even thinking about no no no
no no no no it's good it's okay
how many Revenge do I have
I can make it with French I'll test
oh 48 that's pretty high
[Music]
Maybe
no
[Music]
foreign
guess that's just hopeless
but I can at least take this one down
can I do it with Chloe
before she did or no
no
not like this
maybe like this
wait wait wait I know I know don't don't
scream at me
yes
she will die
after this turn
what sacrifices will be made once again
[Music]
maybe she won't who knows maybe they'll
go from over here and all the doubles
that would be nice
that will be most preferable
[Music]
one more and it made down I think that's
the smartest step to do here
I believe I am in the right
I believe so too
[Music]
uh no more enemies at the bottom on the
free left only for
foreign
[Music]
maybe this is just you know supposed to
show you
you shouldn't go into marriage
so recklessly and you should know that
marriage comes with its ups and downs
and challenges
that you have to overcome I will endure
is that what we're learning I think so
probably I haven't so deep it's
symbolism and that's exactly what they
wanted me to learn from this
before I go into a very
very important
new La chapter in life with Hortensia
who I
left dead on the battlefield
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's like don't worry she's not really
dead it's like Romeo and Juliet she
seems dead but she's not
but I'll fix my mistakes and you know it
will be fine
[Music]
a couple times in the beginning no
no
[Music]
um
they're not gonna force me to do
one more round I think for one enemy or
so
[Music]
maybe they will
ah can she reach with the spear
yes
sorry if that was too much
okay at least this was a good grind
good exp Source because they've forced
me to kill every single one of them I
cannot reach of kagetsu but that's okay
here we
are fighting our debt after
four hours of suffering although not all
of those four hours was this battle
maybe three and a half
only nine turns
the ring safely but it doesn't work
at what cost
is it but a normal ring
it seems so
when I hold their
older what is it that you have surmised
Factory
it belongs to and holds the hour of
divine Dragon Monarch Lumera
you know about this pack
Lumera once said that Divine dragons
will give a special ring to someone they
truly trust the ring strengthens the
bond between the two and brings them
closer together it grants special powers
to the Divine dragon and anyone they
make a pact with of any sort so mother
once gave this ring to someone she
trusted and had a special connection
with that's what I guess too
but she lost her friends and allies in
the war so who she gave the ring to or
if she gave it at all
there's just no way to know mother but
we know that as long as she lived the
most important person to her was you you
just kind of thing be documented a
marriage certificate I'll think long and
hard before I decide who's worthy to
wear especially if someone is important
as the Divine Dragon arrived at this
place
is my own
I must be strong the vine dragon is even
more important
there is much work to do anyway how do
we marry
[Music]
if you reached support level a with an
ally you can give that Ally The Pact
ring to strengthen your bond even
further you can find a ring in the
Memento trial in your room if you cannot
find your chosen Ally on this thumbnail
try resting in bed a while
oh
you can only give the pattern to one of
yalas choose a recipient carefully hmm
there is only one that has a rank with
me now I think
and it's exactly the one that I want to
give it to
[Music]
Embrace being a Targaryen Kiara give it
to Veil
can you
in three houses there were
[Music]
Nani saiso congratulations
foreign
[Music]
lost my train of thought
no need for cat I think it's quite a
nice place to be for a cat
and then three houses
they were quite a lot of restrictions
in who I can marry
is that not the case in this game
there's only cats here hmm
[Music]
not marrying stuff it was your biggest
one guy moment eh what did someone say I
can't marry sofas and then only one
person said it but it wasn't true and I
believed them
is that what you're saying
yes no
I think so
you can marry whoever
but a lot of the English dialogue is
censored uh you mean in this game or
I was trying to tell you otherwise no
way no way
stuff is just great Advocate you can
actually cook
what
[Music]
what can I time Crystal back to that
time right now IRL
[Music]
and correct my mistake
how could that have happened
[Music]
no
no my beloved who did I marry in the end
or is this food here
I ate my own ill guard wall
I mean
apparently I was never really that much
into her
and I think I remember now
um
well but
at least she's like one of the main
characters
and
it doesn't make no sense to marry
Mary Mary
doesn't surface
marriage require one complete of
playthrough
says someone
maybe that's how it is
and you guys looked up can you memories
office and it says yes but but and you
didn't read the butt
well actually you have to play for the
game once don't get one guy again though
oh remember Hortensia is with the dogs
right now
in case we need to go to her in person
and go on my knees
nice silver
and some more steel okay
[Music]
oh
she's under it so they censor her
marriage lines in the end
[Music]
only in Ian what about German
game
is there a voice acting for it at all
because in German it would probably
still be I could choose probably between
Japanese and English dub
but yeah we can change from Japanese
just for that
I think that's it then
uh
[Music]
all Crest do you have a moment
I do Define one what is it uh why are
you standing like that are you okay I'm
preparing to bow
and why are you doing that I want to be
ready in case I need to apologize for
something
For the Love of and there's no need for
that I just wanted to discuss that well
Chris oh what about it I need you to
understand something about me and about
you
I'm not higher he's unfixable we share
the same footing
to think or when you marry him maybe he
is I wish
I just don't believe it hey come on
why is it so hard for you to accept that
I'm very sorry for him guys
I guess it can't be helped
I worry but you do get results
keep handling things your own way
don't say that it'll make it even worse
I often bring the mood down around
others he'll feel so bad he won't go to
battle with me anymore now we're near as
confident as my brother so I'm sure my
hesitation frustrates people despite all
of that
you really think it's okay for me to
keep handling things my own way no I do
no I hope that someday you'll take what
I've been for a position of blame and
sad at all times thank you for your
advice Define one and one guy put it I
shouldn't get one guy though should I
[Music]
I would not believe that
dragon's face
gold Mary are you okay
oh to find one
did the sound of my soul in anguish
finally get your attention I'm so glad
what's wrong
talk to me I'm here to help
[Music]
possibly
be more Charming
wow everyone always says I'm the most
popular woman in the world but if you're
immune to my charms I know that can't be
true
confidence is shattered I'm still here
stand
my tears flowing freely like two hours
of cluttering diamond gold mirror oh
look I'm sorry if you're trying to
change my mind in terms of marriage you
didn't mean to no please don't apologize
only tell me what I can do to earn your
affection
I already think you're quite Charming
you do
laughs
you think I'm Charming of course and
it's not just me does crony still keep
that whole Perfection thing up don't
feel like you have to push yourself so
hard okay
if yes and respect
that's a token of my appreciation
you may admire my perfect tears a little
bit longer
okay I wonder because coron you played
this game
um
pretty much the end I wonder if she ever
saw this support conversation and what
she was thinking
I'm like oh that's me
[Music]
ivy do you think maybe it's time we
talked whatever you're feeling toward me
I'm prepared to listen
allies did they end up playing Uno
very well I am rather more comfortable
around you now so I don't know I was
sleeping did they manage to play it I'm
glad to hear that let me start with why
you seem to have such a anger toward me
good for them I love you huh I love you
divine one who destroyed them my
feelings began long before I met you I
understand I do not mean romantically oh
okay I adore you as a worshiper adores a
deity
when you were staring at me before my
deity was standing Before Me In the
Flesh
I was nervous
do you understand now
um
thank you for sharing that in Japanese
she loves her for real really like you
as well
may I be excused oh yes yes of course
fun and God is so I'm sorry we'll speak
again later these conversations are
indeed weird if you think about it maybe
you don't even have to think about it
they are weird
foreign
[Music]
go to a before I marry her
encia
I wanted to tell you that I
so
I wonder if we I have nothing to say to
you wow my father is dead because of you
oh yeah why would I want to be friends
it doesn't matter to me if you were
controlled or whatever and now you're
back to normal I'll never forget the
sight of you laughing as you watched my
father die oh please
just leave me alone
I've wanted so badly to apologize for
that illusia should never have allowed
worship of the fell Dragon his power
though much as I hate to admit it I do
envy that if I'd been born with what he
has
what you have my father would still be
alive be glad you weren't born a fell
dragon
it's a light full of fear pain and
persecution I wish I had been born human
to me that life seems so much more
bearable
yeah I'm sure it's terrible poor thing
oh my friends fail goodbye let's go
Hortensia wow oh
yeah oh your life must be so bad little
veil being one of the main characters
and being so important and uh
being so powerful
oh
damn more dense yeah don't worry guys
I'll calm her down
oh man okay I want to marry her first
not that they turn into a rank and then
marry themselves
and that probably wouldn't happen but
still
um
to go to my room
[Laughter]
biased opinions about hortension now
hey I you have to understand her point
of view as well okay
what's this A flowers
[Music]
no no I know where to go
I know where to go
[Music]
[Applause]
ah okay
Japanese dub
it's gonna be a bit weird for the first
time in a long time to hear the
Japanese dub when we're actually quite
used now tutu
English one
nihongi
climasu
is even closer to me now she's awaiting
me
[Music]
do I have to go out the game once
ah
okay
foreign
might not have been there yet
boys
Japanese
I never heard her oh so on my wedding
day I'm Gonna Hear My bride's other
voice for the first time
foreign
the translation of the Japanese voice
accurate right to what she says in
Japanese oh oh no they do censor the
text okay
okay I shall Translate
no wait let me hear you a bit more
before we marry here's a pretty pebble
[Music]
d
on
psyche mode
[Music]
okay I'll I also forgot alaya's voice
wait
she sounds even younger
in Japanese and also she sounds might be
the same voice actress she sounds like
the from that movie that I watched with
coyote and Canada
tastes like this this evil cat
who uh has like a childish very childish
voice
and it sounds pretty much like this
is it the same voice actor maybe it is
Superman wait let me let me see
this is a mad cat voice actress
does it will it show me hey what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
voice actress cut
um
where's the cut
ting
[Music]
and yeah
and then um
uh
Hortensia Japanese
CA
no it's a different one
um
[Music]
foreign
so
so tacky
business
[Music]
yes
don't give it to Celine
because you're
turning a rank with her
foreign
[Music]
come on
she's saying You're Beautiful on the
inside and on the outside
you've been always beautiful on the
inside and outside
[Music]
foreign
you're the one that I fell in love with
so you better have confidence from now
until I will love you
[Music]
kind of part of Ivy I love you and I
will take you to battle no matter what
oh God
[Music]
oh
hey I have a little bit teary eyes
she's a good healer yeah
[Music]
why not listen a little bit more to her
voice in this dialogue
[Music]
bring me
soon
[Music]
mascara
oh I'm listening
I just married you
know
foreign
[Music]
because if I didn't then maybe I would
have changed my mind because I would
have felt betrayed
what the hell
Japanese voice
[Music]
well I just realized is this an emblem
thing her right eye
compared to her left eye
is different
the inside is this an emblem it's a
Lucina thing
oh
oh it's freaking me out
[Music]
no no what I never noticed until now
should we change back to English but I
feel like damn the Smith went and once
again makes me feel like
tacky
tacky dialogue
on cute anime characters just works so
much better in Japanese doesn't it
hmm
it's less cringe when it's in Japanese
for some reason
maybe maybe if we're interested a little
bit we can have it be Japanese because
there's some voices I haven't heard yet
I think
like a veil happy heart Valen England
and Japanese I think maybe not
[Music]
very interesting for sure and hey we're
married now that's all
that's not
it's not what it looks like surely
that's what she will surely tell me tell
me
let's
let's have a conversation with Hortensia
while having dinner
[Music]
nope never mind
portancia and okay let's clear it up
while having Celine there as well
hmm
doesn't really matter if they like it
this is maybe worth more to just go for
something they're good at
magic rest step
strength of speed
[Music]
oh I don't have to support you know true
but I need to talk to her about this
[Music]
eh I can only marry one person right
why is our support so [\h__\h] damn
okay maybe this one
[Music]
cabbage beans and another vegetable what
is this bean and veggie console man okay
[Music]
no I don't really believe in that when
it's
when it comes to love
this is an a-rank Maybe
yo good job
chef
oh tomorrow's Sports was cute too
maybe a little bit too cute
where's she from
she's not from brodia right
I don't have anything from her country
sadly hmm
we can disappoint right here
talk to me Tamara
I prefer her English voice
[Music]
foreign
is not bad though
just after hearing the English one
I can definitely say English one is more
fitting of her personality
more energetic sounding and a bit more
mature this one sounds a bit too young
Maybe
cheers baby
both are okay
point one for English yeah surprisingly
[Music]
foreign
that's pretty good though
[Music]
Japanese like real name
it's her real name
[Music]
no this is
and nah
[Music]
foreign
you mean a voice actors that's actually
called akarikito okay because I just
looked up akani Community is voiced by
shiori mikami
[Music]
second uh
what's it called
[Music]
in Japanese
it doesn't translate
well into English
foreign
[Music]
respectful friendly protect us
to all these other girls they're trying
to get into my panties
[Music]
you're the best
on me you know
um
[Music]
and ah yeah yeah I think um for the
upcoming chapter I'll keep the Japanese
ones so we hear a little bit more
[Music]
um
I wanted to do this
this was green you're green
from
blah blah blah blah
do the same thing again
[Music]
yeah sorry podcast gang just this one
why override safe and why not
Chris don't start from zero again once
again
do I have another second sale
Griffin Knight to
riponite
you know the story by now
I can't imagine
[Music]
ah to check different marriage scenes if
I really wanted to see that I can go on
YouTube
I don't care
and that's
that's it for now
huh
now
let's go into the arena
never miss out on those yummy EXP
o in your conversation before attention
that's because your part isn't
translated yeah I mean why not you could
say I like you that's not illegal to
like me
[Music]
foreign
I mean you know the words you choose are
fine for me to be Ojo style but the
voice
for me
[Music]
I think I like her English one quite a
lot
actually
[Music]
girl
oh
[Laughter]
took out that old man so well oh man her
voice is good in both English and
Japanese
um
okay
[Music]
gold Mary needs EXP
enses
[Music]
gold mirror very good too oh
um
[Music]
I wanna
look
skills like for example why do you not
have anything let's write it down we
need something for Al Chris
we need something gold Mary she still
doesn't have cancer
you need something for Ivy
and for more beer or density oh my God
write it down write it down
you write it down bail almost everybody
but um
[Music]
okay
have you written a dance
you wrote this
Vantage could work on
on Annette and gold Mary
Advantage is from who
we've got something Advantage from
thanks ah Georgie is that like a new
thing when I sneeze you send a
membership
oh
advantage what is Vantage do
will put me uh
on the not disadvantage
[Music]
it's already on free but I have to do
five right in order to inherit that yeah
[Music]
is your countertops before the enemy
does oh
need HP requirements low HP attack
shirts whenever
in case I have low HP I encounter first
so that I don't die cool
oh sorry live sorry
[Music]
I under 25 cool cool cool
uh for gold maybe two I suppose that's
fine I really why not
[Music]
go to the mighty death
could I say
is
[Music]
yes
say that name correctly
sounds kind of weird in Japanese reading
foreign
[Music]
okay
um what else like for example we wanted
something for
who for alcres probably I needed one
[Music]
what do I want for our Chris can we get
something interesting somewhere
and his bond level is LIN is Max
[Music]
yeah okay maybe maybe something here
what's alacrity if you look initiate
combat with a speed advantage of nine or
more you let's follow up if possible
occurs before fall all right that's like
that isn't that kind of the same thing
but not with um HP
it's good okay
[Music]
okay
um
gold Mary
gets the Vantage and
who should be able to afford
the Canter as well
hey
okay
[Music]
still has geosphere already so whatever
ivy can you get something
[Music]
wait if I if I get this I can assign
decoy like even without Soarin what
[Music]
well acros already has it because she's
using Lin hmm
okay I'll see if I can find something
else
but she's your attacker no
oh plus one
what's this I'm using tomes unit
inflicts death minus three
with fire let's go for somebody else do
we have something else I have some
Secret
[Music]
some Lin
is is is Ivy fast
[Music]
um
no so we want more speed
I can give her speed plus free
or we can find something better speed
taker
attack
[Music]
okay that means I have to
get more
bonding with her
and we're at Max how do I get speed
taker
ah it's just because it grows great out
because I don't have the money huh the
SP okay and then we'll wait with Ivy I
guess
[Music]
ah it's people I forgot about those
uh
and how uh got the ivy
finish items
yeah
300 you guys say
[Music]
100 100
500 okay let's get three of the novice
books
[Music]
I can use them from the storage so it's
their fault for making this a weird not
my fault
thank you
don't worry I'll get it back
[Music]
or I'll take the recover
I don't know should I get the rescue gun
or a ringworm
a rescue Ice Cube
[Music]
it's time to use the boards
okay
[Music]
um
manage skills
uh
inherent skills called Ivy photo
[Music]
okay
and then
let me equip some of these things
actively
get something oh yeah we got a lot I
like pretty but we want something else
for him now
how much points does he have left
[Music]
huh nothing
okay let's find the way he is
he's plenty strong
he doesn't need anything
for now
uh gold Mary
Panther Vantage
[Music]
huh
itika
[Music]
currently have cigarette on her
so she gets cancer anyway
she also I also gave her avoids at some
point
which seems okay
[Music]
it doesn't have anything else okay let's
do more of the year and Hortensia and
bail
[Music]
thank you
um
more beer
he's pretty new Phil doesn't really have
anything
you could get one of the cigarettes
skills
that's momentum
attack was once we first attacked during
combat for each Space Unit moved before
attack oh ah
a horse so he does move quite a bit
give a momentum
what do you think
my name is
[Music]
might be worth it
which is it will help with his damage
okay
[Music]
look at that what about Hortensia I
don't mind like teaching her like
getting her bond up with someone
because we have bile of stuff
they're all kind of cheap then
may turn the Mist attack into it oh she
never misses wrong
[Music]
no no she she needs to I think we need
to
get her bond up with someone
mentorship is good the XP one
[Music]
Divine pulse is great for stage like
freeze or in trout
[Music]
I never use those
give her draconic hacks
is that from Tiki
no where's it from
[Music]
corn
two thousand okay then she needs a few
SP as well
[Music]
okay why not
level eight
[Music]
should we do the same for Veil what was
this thing somebody said I need for Veil
[Music]
eh I'm getting it because that's what
you guys recommended
If You're Gonna Keep silica unveiled and
she should inherit or connect hex from
corn
on the table
[Music]
you're sorry
no no
[Music]
who do I give to Ivy yeah
that's good
[Music]
um
I mean they're like pretty much the same
to me
I work with Lynn Soren or Veronica best
okay
[Music]
I can't inherit this feeling right we
need to be eight
[Music]
I have to take so much time guys
takes so much time
[Music]
foreign
I see
S rank ring now I want to give them the
engage rings
but thanks for your
input at least what oh yeah okay now I
need how many points 200 on Hortensia
[Music]
um
oh
I hate all the system stuff
um I guess
[Music]
I guess I'll have you ever one of the
500s
500 points ones
and then we have two
maybe just give her the novice one and
hope she gets some points on her own
machine
[Music]
huh
okay but you guys say put Sauron
on Veil as a ring right and
um
then what in terms of skills I should
just
you want
avail
[Music]
Vantage and hold up okay
thank you
uh
I assume I need to level her with
someone
bandage was slave right
[Music]
um
I'm 80 into unlocking a very
game-breaking
where's the other twenty percent
[Music]
well I guess 80 is fine on its own
ah Engravings okay okay
[Music]
hold up
who has called out
[Music]
Roy
and what level
[Music]
very expensive
it's okay I'll spend it on Veil Bale
will be worth it surely
right
now
[Music]
yeah I need to use the books
okay and then and then and then and then
don't kick me out of the menu
I want to continue
level eight
[Music]
foreign
okay she needs 900 points I'll give her
one of those with thousands
and she'll be just fine
can she use staves no she should be able
to use this
[Music]
it's fine
use but I don't know what else could I
give her
[Music]
a tiramy storm
why not
[Music]
book enough oh yeah right daggers work
too
oh well uh inherit
or Veil
[Music]
uh the hold out
okay
[Music]
step by step
equipped
oh we're getting rid of cancer on her
then
damn she'll be fine hopefully
okay
um
I already gave Celine something else
okay then you keep it
okay
and Annette
what do we give to panette
thank you guys
uh didn't we already like
train her with someone though
[Music]
I forgot
she can learn momentum
or advantage
[Music]
or one of these
result what's this 25 or less
[Music]
huh
Ralph
[Music]
wrap
and the German prize of Vantage then no
rap
I mean no control
[Music]
beyond my reach now okay ah only has RAF
post parallel
[Music]
okay okay
so
Vantage or reprisals oh yeah right you
said that Vantage would be good okay
okay one more thing
we have put so many characters on yunaka
before I think are so many emblems
[Music]
no not that many
what's this
I shouldn't give her a Mikaya thing
though right because she's already with
Mikaya usually
or with Karen
speed take on you know guys good
[Music]
takea
2 000 points
thank you
[Music]
okay
hopefully we'll be done soon
[Music]
koi does not
but that's your identity
[Music]
oh she always double anyway
should we not do it
um
skill and Heritage recommend
[Music]
and what the [\h__\h]
why does sometimes when I type into the
Google search bar it defaults to Yahoo
and then tells me sorry you can't use
Yahoo because you're overseas
[\h__\h] you no Japanese Yahoo
why I don't want to be I want to be a
Google
[Music]
yeah that's so weird
Fire Emblem
skill in hair red
[Music]
they recommend
Canter draconic hacks avoid plus 10
electricity or speedteker electricity
we can afford the alacrity at least
maybe I'll just take that one because
there were doubters about to be taker
I suppose
uh
this is making my brain really mushy
I know where you guys but the back and
forth between the menus oh my God
same
[Music]
guy says do this and I believe guide as
well
uh uh inventory inventory inventory even
though it makes no sense
of skills
okay
um
yeah let's do Tamara sit down and maybe
forgado
[Music]
they're the same guy for Tamara
Tamara
hey why does it default to Yahoo how do
I turn that [\h__\h] off
[Music]
tomorrow
forgot she was still on the team
um
see them see that Fire Emblem build
[Music]
uh skills
avoid plus 30 Maybe
[Music]
star sphere
I didn't set Yahoo once my default doll
um normally it always goes to Google
weird
recommended skills dual support
grants a bonus to avoid
that increases with unit support level
of interesting allies
quality time on yielding plus plus
HP is 40 less restores 40 of humans
magazine free
or avoid plus voting
[Music]
um
like whatever
[Music]
I'll do unyielding because it sounds fun
I want to see that in action
surprise heel
has Mega app installed maybe I do I
might do indeed
I might have that installed
I guess my will
[Music]
oh
hi hi
I don't have time
[Music]
loss
sad
[Music]
apparently we need to get up to level 18
for unyielding or 19 for avoid Plus 30.
[Music]
damn and they keep on kicking me out of
this menu so that's not very nice
[Music]
oh wait
what
no unyielding plus plus yeah and
yielding already shows up here but we
want a yielding plus I have plenty
fragments it just depends on how
expensive that is it can't be more than
two thousand right
Body candles 2000 seems like the maximum
add too much SP anyway really
let me see let me see we gotta check how
much SP they want from me
[Music]
avoid plus 20 is already involved for
decent
inherent skills
[Music]
oh
I can't see the prices for the other yet
but avoid was 20 2500 and yielding
normal is 100.
mmm
I'll go up to plus plus shouldn't or or
at least Plus
[Music]
ah wait is that what do you mean it's
Max how do I get higher than this
[Music]
ah because of Marv's parallelog
oh okay
oh and that case
[Music]
I don't want to spend those books all
those books on him because even then I
don't think he has enough
[Music]
also Seattle like never gets hit because
he's always so far behind
really they don't have anything really
interesting
ah quality time would actually be nice
maybe after unit act awaits
restores 10 HP to adjacent allies and
slightly increase the support with them
Link at least that gives the other
something
[Music]
but then I also have to go to level 18.
record
which ah I guess I can't get to either
well all of this
stupid stupid
to take avoid Plus 10.
I suppose
what about polgado if we're still taking
him
[Music]
what what's up with my browser
my brows was broken mine's broken
[Music]
normal qualities I'm already available
with Plus
this is 10 HP them normal is probably
just 5 HP or so
yeah well I'll check my browser later
don't worry don't worry
what happened to Jade
who's Jade I will know
[Music]
in my hands please maybe something with
Lynn
[Music]
I know
I have to Google for recommend bills
we've come to such a sad point
Mississippi
laughs
[Music]
that's sorrow I'm so alone forever
I'm at work but you shouldn't be you
should be here helping people
do I not matter to you anymore
[Music]
your name's literally a fireball
character
you should be on call
okay uh
two thousand
[Music]
can I even scratch together two thousand
I don't think I can
[Music]
I
can is that perfect Unforgettable
[Music]
is that weapon
yeah
just gonna give him some bow agility
I'm gonna use all of my books on him
I know I don't use them much otherwise
but still
[Music]
although speed plus three would have
been nice
oh well whatever
[Music]
this I think we can go
continue the story AKA into one map and
and then
it's over again uh
all right
did I not equipped something
indeed the knots
did I get something for you to mirror
no
come on tomorrow deserves something
let's get to remember something
[Music]
she has about the same chance of me
using her
almost
[Music]
how about Lance
proficiency stuff
we're already quite high with cigarette
anyway
[Music]
s
you know what she gets momentum
don't ask
why but it just so happens that she got
the momentum
and she will make it work if I if I get
her into the game again
okay
one more quick check to the plaza
thank you thank you I made independent
decisions some some independent
decisions and some decisions with a
guide online
thanks for trying to help though
finally framed free from the confines of
the Arena yeah get out of here it was
kind of a magical void I don't want to
see that anymore it's depressing
ah but we wanted to engrave
veils weapons with whom was it again
please help me
um
something is more correct which one
probably someone that I already used huh
Korean or any plus crit
Curren
looks like nowhere to sampling
I think that's cool
[Music]
would it say if I
have it on someone else already
oh yeah my killer ax on Pinette
anything else that has crit
uh this one
[Music]
but wait what else did I do I didn't
check [\h__\h]
is it okay to use this one
what did I give
it's gone now what
the hit and avoid did she get rid of
something that we don't want this is
decent
is it decent
maybe not mess it up
oh
I'm seasoned grape I gave it koala
Engraving
blazing lemon butter
[Music]
but she's also taken I think
whatever it's fine she's strong enough
already
she has too much power she will lose her
mind and turn into evil Veil again do we
want that huh you know what power does
to her
only bad things we need to keep her in
check
we need to control her properly at least
for a while and see you know step by
step if she can handle it
can't go too fast she'll be overwhelmed
by the power
um
I can give her a plus two
got some silver here so thank you
thank you on my latest marriage
thank you
oh I actually let me tell you about an
idea that I have
dad I wasn't sure if I should tell you
about first I have this stream idea
um
[Music]
um I want to hire
a professional marriage counselor
to like of course they I would explain
them that you know it's a joke and it's
that and this does happen before with me
and Elena and to a one-on-one stream of
brainer with the marriage counselor
um where we like grammatically
emotionally exaggerately
uh discuss our problems such as why
shouldn't tell me that she was gonna go
to Japan when I was there already
stuff like that and why this and dance
and then have the marriage counselor
help us and comments down and try to
explain you know what our issues are and
how do we improve our our relationship
I thought that would be so funny
and Lena would like be like totally up
for it I think but no I want a
professional like legit a professional
but hopefully someone who is also funny
and
can joke with us
I just need to find someone somehow
um
no the plan didn't fall through I didn't
even tell you right now about it yet
[Music]
are there any marriage counselors Among
Us by the chance
I was gonna just like look online for
marriage counselors that I could hire
and I'm like hey I have a really weird
request for you but it does pay I will
pay you like your normal marriage
counselor fees and you can even
advertise your marriage counseling
service in front of a couple thousands
of viewers
[Applause]
yeah married to a relationship
counseling yeah yeah
isn't that a fun idea I just wanna I
wanted to make something new and I was
thinking of what's what's what hasn't
been done yet somehow I got this idea
when I was thinking of like
like bringing some professional into the
Stream
to do something and then I got this idea
you don't have to actually have use for
marriage counsel guys we just have to
make the marriage counselor think that
there is potential customers within our
audience let's just make them think this
management even okay with that we'll
make them okay of course we work with
people that we like get under an NDA all
the time so we can get the marriage
counselor on an NDA of course I don't
see any issue hmm
no no we'll pay him with actual money
too but I I wanted to be a female
marriage counselor uh did I get food yet
kind of did you cook for me no not you
but I need to get food
okay I think we've done plenty of
preparation
did we we just haven't one thing one
more thing I'm sorry I'm sorry I need to
do something one more thing
wait why does alcress only have
yeah because I said he's too strong
already
um
one more thing the one more thing is
checking
if everyone's okay
[Music]
why does she why does she have a physic
Ally
he can use physic
oh yeah what
[Music]
I didn't like consider that as an option
at all before hmm
[Music]
oh you can keep it
um
[Music]
pulmonary is taking up space man
uh yeah you definitely need to switch
out some things
fortifies on one
[Music]
take the new fortify
take a recover
and keep the physics
[Music]
do I have any extra daggers oh
make her more powerful
all right
[Music]
why can't she not use the speed Wing she
can use
[Music]
it I'm gonna use up these items now
that's right kiwan was finally doing it
not ignoring these items in her
inventory
who needs
luck
[Music]
that's it that's it
that's it I didn't even have that many
okay
Sarah Alex here
physic frame
[Music]
um
Alex here
I'm sorry this is like a really boring
episode at this point
archive I hope you're watching it and
two times
[Music]
but we're in last spurt and
to be careful
do not get too cocky you know
[Music]
thank you
my power level must be increased
so but now I think
I'm ready
on two more
story continues we have had our marriage
and now we continue the war
yeah especially after that
fight that we just had uh where we
struggle a lot but mostly because of the
position I would say but still I think
it taught us that we should prepare
what we can insomnia
um
[Music]
engage is much quicker than free houses
was is what people say really
[Music]
Middle Island looks like
begin chapter
[Music]
where were we oh now it's nihongo
the four Hounds in nihongo
[Music]
of course who else
was gonna be great isn't it gonna be
really
Vader
a
is
[Music]
please talk
to us
oh
another foreign
[Music]
I mean
I live [\h__\h]
ES
[Music]
kind of cheese
they're all a little bit too nice to
each other I think
foreign
[Music]
okay
foreign foreign
[Music]
we'll kill them for the millionth time
will we really kill them this time that
is the question or will they come back
again to protect some bran again
who knows
yeah I want their heads as trophies and
put them on the spike
all right what do we have oh dear uh
it doesn't look like too many units but
um
can we
go through here
we have to break it
oh
[Music]
they're on the horse oh okay
we have a worm
oh they're next to each other next to a
weird
big Shard okay
[Music]
it's broken eventually
hey Griffins
many dragons many Griffins around here
I think
um
maybe bring fogado as well as our crest
not sure
let's see
we can do this
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I know I'm already happy just need to
check the spaces
[Music]
like if this team
goes up here
and this team up there
there's a worm right there so we need
panette over here
and I'll crisp
as well as folgado
I would say on the left
on a strong Bale I keep on the right
oh no there's already Ivy and kiwala hmm
and then
[Music]
maybe like this
radiant bull he should have it or I gave
it to someone else like alcres
I feel like I gave him the radiant pill
before
yeah
when that happened last episode uh last
stream last stream I got Veil
on my team I wonder if those spawn some
flyers over here
when the game starts or so
[Music]
ah
we tried it on forgot it didn't change
much if I remember correctly oh really
okay
[Music]
I think something like this is fine just
not sure is this really just on like one
path
one tile path for real for real
what about here
[Music]
and they
also here how does this work we'll have
to destroy it probably
hmm
there's a gimmick okay
well let's just start let's see what
happens
thanks
well they really only helped me
[Music]
well I know where they will hit
to destroy the fell during The Shard you
must defeat its attendance Zephyr and
Grace Sophia and griss will use the
short power to unleash devastating
volcanic bombs yes the game will tell me
volcanic bombs will strike every few
turns the bombs destroy Boulders and
deal heavy damage to Alice hit by them
the warning will indicate where the
bombs will fall so take care to move out
of the way okay
thank you
all right let's go go go go go go go
[Music]
more more Soul War
first of all
doing split like completely
this group up and left
or can we all can we send everybody to
the left up
but that seems to be
easy but there must be a catch
I mean there's a lot of like one tile
paths but they'll surely destroy those
anyway focusing laps is good okay good I
mean maybe people do the right path if
they want a lot of exp but if I don't
have to then I Don't Wanna Know
[Music]
we will dance me
[\h__\h] I don't have the dancer here
God damn it
yeah
[Music]
go up and then left
at least we can attack a little bit
although 35 that's not [\h__\h] worth it
I think
restart
face palm moment
no I brought the dancer but he's on the
right side I want him on the left side
now
I changed my mind
it's better than I do it now in the
beginning at least
come on over
right
here
because the Flyers you know
they'll be fine
okay
because I want the net to hit that worm
like run away
hi
as strong as she can go go open It Go
[Music]
ES
hey
[Music]
yeah that's always the thing like I can
hit him in one turn but I do also get a
lot of damage from it it is inevitable
unless it was the killer ax I get a crit
right away let's see
[Music]
often I get I get the crates on the
second hit and then it's too late
you're the best I can attest
now
good job
[Music]
should I troll them
should I shoot them already
I wonder are they gonna they don't have
an emblem ring so what can they really
do up there
I can't do [\h__\h]
especially
flyer you won't like that bow will you
although it does the same damage on both
of them
watch out
oh is it a shooting star oh no shots
all right all right
[Music]
all right uh over here
I guess we can just pass
up and then left
should we go straight left straight
completely straight
as straight as it gets
those will go after me though I think
right that's good
okay they can come for me then
I do I do one little one little hit and
then I walk away okay
yeah just a little a little bit
[Music]
nine percent hit chance on him
try me try to kill Chihuahua
you're welcome to give it a try
[Music]
several great lens six or six percent
only though
[Music]
now
I'll go with the same choice
oh we can finish off
with kage to
or ADD
the start of this map already looking
pretty fine also are they not gonna like
shoot after this turn
with uh
they're
shard
because I don't see any pink areas oh my
gosh
oh oh
this one too
yay I left just enough uh units
over here to clear that round
[Music]
let's go although all these free will go
for kiwama one day oh I'm gonna break
that thing
oh no oh you did something on mobile
is that only for one round hopefully
fortified
ah
well what would he have done if he
didn't have to heal
her he they would both it seems like
they make their way over
to us
so maybe good to because like she moved
a few steps ahead
love is frozen oh
[Music]
surprisingly they all go for Mom
and one goes oh yeah 41 damage
oh [\h__\h] out
for one turn he can't move
I get I do have like a warp though don't
I
oh why did I
Fidel you okay you're back
goodbye
foreign
[Music]
their aim is getting better but they
don't know I'll be gone by the time they
reach
will this hit when
like after I move
before the enemies move
or
after I move and after the enemies move
oh [\h__\h] yeah I'm over here
before the enemies move okay so rip
enemies but also rip moviere
after you end your turn okay
[Music]
um
how does the whipping stick work again
it has the person has to be right next
to me huh okay
but then I can I move after using it
we just want to get him out of here but
after he attacks them
right
if I I can count it right with ivy
oh
maybe heal him first with hortension
he has a physical thing
[Music]
to be honest
is that um Shard thingy bump
hits them will it kill them how much
damage does that end up doing
it can't kill them oh oh it's like fire
all right let me deal with the left side
first
[Music]
I don't know maybe I want to dance
Celine
[Music]
yeah yeah I know either Celine or I mean
we can also dance Veil for example
let's see what her obscurity can do
[Laughter]
how many hours does Kayla played this
game 77 hours
incredible right
there's some hopefully many cribs yeah
but I mean I didn't think
I think her crit percentage was that
high just now but damn
it's this convinced
definitely
where's Al Chris
is he on the other side
I don't see him
I'm blind
juice is all Chris
attacked that he looks so different man
[Music]
oh really now Chris really
sound [\h__\h] yo
I'm joking
you just want to give some exp to our
buddy fogado right but he only has a low
chance ah 73 is fun
okay
I'm not gonna break the crates
nah sometimes but not I mean what's more
important to me is that it hits it all
unless I'm when I'm in a really dire
situation the crit really should have
happened
well then maybe
we'll move again let's kill the ax guy
behind her
that's Chris
didn't need it but thanks
sadly I can't move on maybe peanut can
throw hand ax
oh yeah oh that's pretty good actually
wow
damage wise again
oh [\h__\h] wait we need to get out of here
I forgot about the pink area
um I'll stand here
so maybe someone can go here
y'all
optimal optimal optimize
oh you're not cute
you're not gonna cut this now
all right
flowy catching up
gold Mary coming also
optimal it sounds weird in English
sounds like it should be a German word
it is
optimal
what are we gonna do here ask
I can warp him away but if he won't die
yeah
anyway I could also focus on
killing these free mobs
[Music]
just kill the great knife
and hit just keep this HP okay
[Music]
let me see
and even engage first
partner well
wait what
the camera here look at him
what is that you Fabian
CA
um
it looks so different
oh
yeah am I wow
he looks funny in these colors it looks
good though
oh my God I'm rocking this so far
you can't do it oh fine then also you
playing the new DLC because it comes out
of the story I heard it has like an
alternative storyline timeline whatever
but I won't be playing it on stream to
be honest I really want to move on as
much as I enjoyed this
I want to move on from Fire Emblem
because
you know
it's been a long time many streams
and I think my viewers also want to
break from it
I'm kind of sick of long flavors now as
well
this one especially everything takes so
long and we can't it feels like I'm not
doing much progress
the whole time
did it
didn't meteorite already hit
because it didn't really do much damage
I think
I don't even feel it on him
I mean maybe I'm playing privately
but you know it didn't hurt him not even
yeah hold meteor bounced off of him
maybe partially because he's uh engaged
but
oh
you're kind of far why are you so far
did you even move
why is it so easy right now what the
hell why is it so easy there must be a
catch let's what's the catch what's the
catch I'm getting suspicious
[Music]
none
what
uh he's still stuck wait two turns
two turn stuck
I might just kind of stay in this area
almost there
this is easy man oh
okay
because marriage is the most painful
it's unironically so yeah
damn it
is
[Music]
annoying makes me wait
I'll move the group a little bit to the
left but I won't go higher yet
Gotta Wait for more of you more beers
no wait Novia can move
seedel can't yet okay
[Music]
HP
I need more like 20. no I guess I'll use
it
huh
all right
[Music]
hmm
sweetie send me some enemies why is
there only one here and I can't even
reach that one I think
it's gonna run out but I didn't even
call doubles
I guess I'll call doubles but they might
just be stuck here forever alone
[Music]
sad
sad life
but maybe the flyer will go for the
double
um
should
anything
[Music]
that was the one I should have used
Lin's ulti on
if he doesn't want to come he doesn't he
won't I don't care stay there if you
want
unless
fight fight me fight me
[Music]
book of Worlds what's that
yeah I don't want to move too far so uh
dragon veins
[Music]
um
you mean the book I thought you meant I
should go
[Music]
build her engage skill
mmm
[Music]
no
Which chapter is this oh chat will tell
you because I don't know
[Music]
she'll Gambit on the illusory doubles
okay
what are we gonna do a villain
can't even dance what kind of dancer are
you
[Music]
can I do something smart
cute veiled with green hair kind of cute
that's not even much damage
[Music]
I just
bring Bale here
um
[Music]
because I would give him I would like
um
engage them now and give someone the
Eternal claw that was it or the live
thingy but
I think it only works with adjacent
units right
[Music]
ah divine blessing yeah
what was that
whoa what that we are already here
what is she doing here already
he's greedy
please please I need to be entertained
all right
[Music]
no chance
oh is it because I attacked her so she
already Ah that's good that's good
oh
all right yeah it's actually really good
dragging her out of her little cave oh
but this
is kind of rough place because it's
really
narrow here okay uh
illusory doubles are gone but it was
actually really worth it doing that I
think
I think we're gonna one turn the piano
[Music]
where am I
or all of my alcreased okay I need you
I need you I need you
which one in terms of range
Can dancer come over here
you can go here
all right one of them is here now
hmm
oh
could also
do this and that but I will do these I
wish I could dance ah I can I can Violet
but yeah
I'm kind of wasteful we'll see maybe
it's not the end of the turn I feel like
I need a bit more horsepower I might
dance
some peeps
with Viola
ah yeah count it back true true true
yeah that's close enough oh
102 critical
[Music]
hmm
then dance him
I want to buy tickets but if it is too
scary awesome is a scary City
yeah
you live in an area but
I think this
if you live in an area but you say
bosses was scaring really is that so
[Music]
it can be sure can be
fly
just America things
is it just a miracle thing
big city
awesome there's no scary I've been there
fixed anything every city can be scary
and go to bad area
yeah but even like Austria's
big cities okay there's maybe only one
big city even then it's in shambles
compared to America's big cities but
um
uh even in the worst areas
I don't even know what's the worst area
it really depends on what kind of
trouble you get yourself into
I feel like the most danger that can
get to you if you go to like a club
and then someone drugs you that's then
you're absolutely [\h__\h]
with something in your drink right I
hear about that a lot
um
say Berlin what no but that's fine I
think no no it's not
there's certainly a special dialogue
with Veil isn't there oh so he's also in
reach
maybe I can do both
wait
I could speed run this
nah the rest of the team is a little bit
too far
I don't know what I want to focus on
though
[Music]
foreign
do I do like a lot more damage with this
that much
maybe not necessary now
yo 86 10 credit oh
you know more crit is not always
better
as we've seen
although 86 is convincing
what is
and we will shut her up
no I will not even let her talk no no no
no no no no no
tell her
tell everybody you'll get angry
don't don't even listen to her [\h__\h] her
up okay
[Music]
so many changes
you wanna fight let's fight
[Music]
yum yum
I wonder how strong these flyers are if
I keep them alive
who they'll go for
come on end up dancing maybe because
kind of crowded over here
mommy yeah
let's do this
yeah yeah next turn I'll finish it
oh sorry
oh [\h__\h] sorry I'm over here right you're
like kind of involved with her
oh really
cotton candy
did you
go
this one's so short then but the the one
after is truly not that short is it
wonder if there's something short we can
do after
probably not
yeah but honestly I think I was hoping
for ending it today a bit early
on the earlier side
because
I'm nervous about tomorrow
41 [\h__\h] what
50 of them
come on just poison her first because
you're making it a bit difficult
well thanks so much
I don't think so much
oh what
Brave ex what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's just a minute
I'll shoot it
and because one of them
one of the thing is missed you know what
I will
uh go back in time
one of the chain attacks missed
um
[Music]
if I could do that
dark hair
a really suits her with that edgy makeup
um
one more HP bar
um who wants to do it
[Music]
I want foreign
yeah he never joined the Light Side
unfortunately
foreign
[Music]
maybe right before the end I turn evil
after all
and I will have to fix her oh no
oh no
is she dead now for real
that was kind of
anti-climatic the way we took her down
now
I am the final boss oh
Georgia's gorgeous
Legendary Blade that smashes spells ah
smashing weapons hmm
okay
my dear Grace
could
dance a couple
huh
yeah I could force it probably but yeah
yeah no
let's just try to take care of this uh
flying Griffin now
[Music]
I'll go here
we have a javelin
foreign wind works well
physical attackers will rip Grace to
shreds
I'm looking forward to it
he deserves
it's the most
but he'll also enjoy it so actually
maybe we shouldn't do it
Tim to marry the love of his life and
live a happy life somewhere in a house
uh in in the suburbs with a picket fence
a white ticket fence
and and he'll be forced to have a child
and and bring his child to school every
day and feel the the pure happiness from
it the pure innocent happiness
that'll be the kind of portrait that's
actually important for him
and maybe by that he'll also end up
being fixed
he will become a better person
and then damn
we improved the world once again
genius
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] I forgot I could use some
healing
it's bulmery
okay that
I don't even care about these dragons
right now should I should I care
I feel like closet still couldn't take
if if marvier can take one hit from a
meteor then I feel like I could
I think
YOLO oh
number two and number three
Seventeen that's all right that's
perfectly fine
huh
oh did you guys see him we're doing
something like hologram but not really
now did you see
they uploaded it yesterday the first fit
one is with me
the famous showing each other the middle
finger scene
where really I'm only
the side character it's about Gouda
Annette
yeah
reenacting oh no connect oh that's
unfortunate oh well
they need to make them longer they will
be more of course a little bit more um
I took a peek at a list of what's coming
up next
there's a couple orange Alex
not too many I wonder maybe you guys can
make suggestions to me and I can send
them over
because from the upcoming ones there was
not a single one with me involved
but if you guys have
and some suggestions you guys have
better memory of good moments I think
a one to five yeah
I mean that looks kind of like
overdone don't you think but
I'll write it down
uh suggestions for arena
[Music]
um
videos with Chihuahua
one two five ah I'm wrestling uh
in USA 2022 that's a good one yeah
me and me and Cali have a bunch but
which one
um maybe
Ahmed and Piada we would have to cut it
a little bit but I'm in Kiara first
chess devastation
cut it a bit
[Music]
indirect kiss offer
add Pop-Tart stream
ah good uh Piada
um jelly beans
throwing up moments
it was a couple good ones yeah
Kelly popped into rise's dream oh I
wonder if like you know when it comes to
streams where games were involved
we can even show those
[Music]
Cali
what the hell
you know I want to do some things like
the Maldives or or the Onsen with Cali
trip and so on but those things like we
just talked about it on stream
and we just talk about it it's maybe a
bit more difficult to reenact but oh
how about
Kiana sees
Cali
changing in the window
a hotel I don't know
Minecraft
um
whole
mystery
compilation of people falling into it
Maybe
ah Halloween frog dance
but properly animated and not in frog
form
Maybe
they need to be funny no I don't think
so
funny is probably preferred by yourself
you sustained frog no I think better
without bra because if
it makes no sense
then we need brights for the Frog
costume and and then it makes no sense
to reenact it
with our 3D thingies
door race that's another one where it's
like I'm just retelling it on Stream So
hmm
ah wait
um uh Kiana goes while Amber and gonna
run around fighting
now here again I think amen good as the
focus but
keep keep kiwawa in it please we're
being confused
in a manga's kebab
that one was funny
he had a POV made it better yeah it was
just perfectly timed
that's with idea
if ID can be involved
um
Kiana stealing only controller in Mario
Party collab
yeah I wouldn't put the Kobo fighting
one in though because that's really just
Kobo in the focus and that should be if
anything on the ID channel
touching channels back stuff like that
or
or even the the floaty flying away story
but those are I don't know
how they would do it
because it didn't happen on stream just
reenacting it uh or retelling the story
okay for now
for now let's just keep these
let me send it
okay I sent it yeah
yeah this one was uh the first one was
kind of cute I wonder when the next one
will be released
on that what pace maybe weekly and how
long if they'll actually manage to keep
it up properly
we'll say we'll see
because then they start like flips
shorts or so and then then continue with
them
it was
it yeah
a bit more exaggerated
maybe give them that kind of feedback in
the comment section
or on Twitter also has a reply
both Maybe
foreign
[Music]
it needs quite a bit of budget and oh
more staff so I don't know if that's
possible anytime soon
[Music]
I don't know where to go
hey baby
where's my dancer
we left him with
a lame amount of HP
let me fix that
took a while for the stars to get there
on oh yeah right they have Holy Ground
right
um
okay he's poisoned now at least that's
kind of cool
let's go all out baby
want these people real for real
but 76 crits
how cute
[Music]
okay shut up Chris
can I call him Chris just now
Christopher maybe that's his real name
[Music]
cool sounding name
so he changed it to Chris
I've seen your passport
I know what your real name is
Christopher
banana llama
I know it's embarrassing
oh there's the crit that we need
thank you
[Music]
okay he has one other people are left
um I want to get some HP from the others
though
foreign
all these enemies that are around me now
I Wanna Get rid of those two right
but yeah that might be my last
thing to do no he can't even reach her
unfortunately
oh man
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
if we really want to dance here
we can do that
[Music]
this isn't choices
what
[\h__\h] even Chloe does a lot of damage on
Grizz
[Music]
ly
whoa
please don't accidentally kill him
please don't get the crits please don't
get the crits
foreign
look look at all that wasted experience
I would almost rewind if it doesn't if
it didn't automatically end the battle I
would rewind right now
man know what time is really good who
should we give it to
and I wasn't really that bad I was
really short
ha ha ha
we start whole map
I am she has more space still in her
inventory
thank God you aggro Cynthia could have
been really long really smart
they're really dead now let's go
I'll dance on their bodies
foreign
[Music]
foreign Little Summer Corrections
that is dramatizing so you look at it
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
dialogue and then we kept it because I
want to hear
some of the voices I haven't heard yet
Sony
um
nice
sweet I miss you
yeah yeah let's go
as soon
I mean maybe we should make sure because
the amount of times they seem to die and
then come back again
I can't trust them
she'll recover Chris seems completely
dead though but his clothes are floating
up in the air
[Music]
well well well
arigato
if it isn't the consequences of her own
actions
Chris just he was sleeping
happily ever after
all right uh how many chapters are left
guys two
so like two more fives or so
or maybe there's like a
something free
how long do you reckon it'll take
if we do next stream
a little bit longer than this one nine
hours or so we can do it right
okay
easy one is short second medium Final
Long
that'll be fine
I'll be fine
I'll make sure I have plenty of time
we'll start at 3 P.M my time again like
today
um
I get like a
frozen pizza for afterwards
yeah when should we do it should we do
it uh actually I think I have like plans
on the upcoming weekend
like streaming plans
one will be will it be Hotel no not yet
I'll talk about the week after but still
um maybe on Sunday but then there's so
much time in between
can we keep Japanese list yeah
I know I love it although the last
episode you shouldn't be watching in
podcast mode anywhere because you should
be paying attention
this is where it gets really interesting
in the end
but yeah whole talk is basically
scheduled
um
we have a date we just don't have a time
yet but
maybe out of loyalty to the end up
because it wasn't so bad I might go back
to it yeah
I'm so used to them
would be weird to suddenly oh yeah
oh
mother
[Applause]
I told you
oh no he is dying
okay that feels dying but he isn't
I'm sorry
the way she's lying on the ground is so
so good
evil people do evil things
foreign
[Music]
they had cool designs
that's for sure
he's like a joker not really just
because you enjoy suffering
crazy good
[Music]
oh
yeah right because
he sees her as a mommy
interesting
[Music]
killed sepia
okay oh he will die okay
[Music]
foreign
I appreciate the scene I thought they
would just like move on
oh
that's kind of a nice ending for them
like
story-wise I appreciate that
[Music]
um
and thankfully he doesn't survive and go
after us again
yeah I guess so a little bit more
elaboration on their backstores could
have been nice
they only
gave us like some explanation now on
zephia
I don't remember much on Grace
nothing hurts me anymore it's such a raw
death quote
yeah I guess in the end you don't you
feel nothing anymore is that how it
works I guess I should no
yeah okay I mean the whole marriage map
was annoying
but this one was quick and made up for
all that time we spent today messing
around
going crazy
that was 70 of the stream for real for
real
uh what the hell
yeah marriage just doesn't come that
easy right I think that's really the
game really wanted to let us know that
don't take it for granted don't think at
all
happens so easily
more of the stream marriage is hard yep
up
think it through
big time
[Music]
yeah yeah
but besides that I mean it was a normal
stream I'll read some super chats I'm
called up so it shouldn't take too long
[Music]
let me pick up all the items because why
not
I'm married to Elena more or less
and maybe also too sadly
[Music]
then there's my wife
are you married Thomas no in my dreams
man in my dreams
for me an unreachable
um
Miracle dream
so unreachable that I don't even think
about marrying her but I I love her
as a friend I value her as a friend as a
gen mate as a colleague
and
I kind of like respect her a lot as a
streamer
and see her as
like someone really talented when I look
up to
an Admire and genuinely if I wasn't
part of whole life I think if I stumbled
upon her I would actually still enjoy
watching her
might be a genuine fan like I was a no
saggy
no
I don't want people to think like that's
why I really don't didn't like when
people thought that I'm like trying to
do this whole takamuri thing with Cali
with amen it made no sense to me because
I was just generally showing
appreciation to Ahmed in my mind
because she deserves it and it pissed me
off that people try it to be pissed off
about it
like oh why are you doing this try stop
trying to push your ship and so I'm not
at all it's like really not what I'm
trying to do like in the least
it's why can't we just be appreciative
of each other and be friends and you
know
praise each other
and try to make each other feel better
you know I want I wanted to know because
I I I know I miss
like
I don't know I feel like she deserves to
hear as much praise as possible
um
even if she has maybe a hard time
reacting to it I think
she needs it and and it helps her and
you know
[Music]
so
that's why I like to be very clear and
open
with my appreciation to her
she maybe doesn't show
that you know she would appreciate
something like that like a really open
clear direct thank you you're amazing I
love you
but I think when she gets it
even
if she doesn't like
know how to react to it
I mean honestly this applies to anyone
in general
oh [\h__\h]
what
even more so to people like Ahmed
we have a hard time
showing their feelings sometimes Maybe
[Music]
and with the amount of help that she has
provided to hollow Ian
over the years
I think that
she hasn't been even getting
close to enough appreciation for it
anyway
the more the merrier
I just wanted to know that there's
someone there
who really appreciates her efforts and
her support you know
yeah that doesn't have anything to do
with me trying to
you know start a couple thing or
whatever or not at all that's the least
thing that I'm planning that I have in
my mind not at all
and even if I was like these things are
all just jokes you know
but it's when it turns into something
like me wanting to do marriage
counseling in with Dana obviously that's
a joke
come on
of course it is
I mean but I still want to do it but
like you know there's not we're not
actually married we're not actually
dating
we're just having fun
it's
joking she doesn't need counseling
[Music]
but friends can be lovey-dovey hmm
just too homie sleeping on the bed with
roses yeah yeah and bathing in a bathtub
with roses with bubbles yeah yeah
but Swizzles we are wearing swimsuits
right I knew that hey
okay let's go office office time
[Music]
again
boom boom
gonna Read Super chats
[Music]
every time
you lost all your professionalism
unbelievable
time
thanks for the stream thank you good
progress decision let's hope the smooth
progress continues so you can finish the
game in the next
or two months no next no next next one
um
I saved right I'm pretty sure I did but
double safe better
maybe if I can maybe I'll squeeze in
another parallelogram in my private time
I'll see what I can do
probably better than watching
murder investigation documentaries
probably also less traumatizing
with you
can you hear that
both at the same time I guess so no
but then I think I can do it but then I
can't because I'm not really paying
attention to either thing I can only pay
attention to one thing
any interesting cases
yeah I think
the one thing I watched like yesterday
was like the most [\h__\h] up thing I
think so far
I've watched like maybe 30 cases until
now the one I watched yesterday was the
most [\h__\h] up one
I'll say one word maybe you know
pigs
Jesus [\h__\h] Christ
the most the most like unreasonable like
stupid
no
yeah yeah unverton Birds basically that
okay so super tattoo
Jacob 47 I'll thank you soon
you're hearing the bgm right
are you watching Criminal Minds all week
what's that
my oceans are all into crime stuff
lately
aren't we all
yeah okay okay
I recently got a new job oh oh so I'll
most likely you have to be vlogging
during the week oh no but I'll still be
here live on the weekend I just want to
thank you for being a huge source of
motivation inspiration all damn but then
you don't have so much time to watch the
Vlogs either do you because you need to
sleep and you need to work or maybe your
job gives you some
some time to watch maybe sometimes you
can watch while you're working like
others basically as a kfp if you're on
the lookout for a job you need to find a
job that lets you
watch my streams on the side hopefully
when are you starting
[Music]
don't forget about me
oh
but like I am actively trying
to keep my long therapy streams on the
weekend now
considering people like you
who won't be able to watch it otherwise
I wanna
Focus to have them on the weekend
if I can
worst case maybe a Friday
some people end their job earlier on
Fridays or
you know maybe your sea so it's already
Saturday and so on
you're the best boss
forget about me
so when it does the same yeah yeah yeah
I was thinking so because of that seems
to work for her so
but I mean I still might have to
I might be forced to still do longer
streams during the week as well every
once in a while
may not even be jrpgs but
um
Yeah because sometimes I have to do
things on the weekend like Holo talk
it will be like that
but um congratulations on your new job
I hope it goes well I hope you feel
like welcome there and comfortable hope
it goes nicely smoothly everything
um
good luck bye
[Music]
five chickens in a trench called thank
you for the pinky we only managed to
snack one ticket for the concert between
all of us but I think we have come up
with a full proof plan to get in and
wish us luck yeah I guess it's in your
in your name make I think that will work
surely that will work
cute
when buying the ticket come on
beginner's mistake ah you actually still
have the name on the chat
thank you the chickens there they are
five chickens in the trench Club so cute
man
so adorable I love that thought
such a minion thing to do
yeah good luck
but maybe in reality this means you are
one person and you got one ticket and
you're going and then congratulations in
that case yay
foreign
[Music]
Opposite Day
you can get new characters but to be
honest it's not that worth it you can do
it off screen oh okay if I do a paralog
off screen should I be doing this one or
any other one
maybe it takes much longer than just
doing one parallel this DLC story
um
emblem one what's the emblem one
other than the another DLC bracelet
Camila
would we use her if we get Camilla
she's another like magic type isn't she
it doesn't reward you until the end well
then [\h__\h] it
I won't do that one before then
EK for rap like for Raph
a
Camille lets you fly
Oh you mean like the person who gets it
once they're engaged they're a flying
unit or what
because analog is super long
it turns anyone into a flyer oh
okay why for an ax oh okay
yeah maybe I'll do her
okay okay
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this was still during the marriage one
right and then she ended up dying and
the other one too unnecessarily
I was like whatever we're done in the
next turn anyway but you're actually
kind of right even though I was gonna
say like wrong wrong how can you say
such a thing you must back it up you
must back up your claim for proof but it
might be right actually
because today was definitely correct
[\h__\h]
but she's also like
like bringing so much damage with her
that her death is always worth it you
know
and then then I worry though damn it all
the damage I put gone now
I don't think that's really on you I
agree
thank you soon
um
soon
thank you I did that
um
[Music]
sincerely you're a housewife
hello my sweet alpacao
I love my new blanket thank you so much
and thank you soon for the help looking
for the top donations
thank you
game 8910 thank you
super SSG thank you
uh
I'm sick but before I go back to bed I
want to congratulate you on your latest
parents
Isn't it nice you all all of you you
were invited to my marriage and you were
there when it happened
not everybody can say that the others
will just watch a vault of it basically
like a DVD that I sent to people who
weren't able to come but you were there
you were there when it was most
important on my special day thank you
French bone vintage bones thank you soon
um
thank you
today's my birthday and it was great
spending the afternoon with you and the
rest of kfb because I got a happy
birthday of course
thank you for spending your precious
special day with me thank you I hope you
still like I don't know go out and do
something to enjoy the rest of your day
because you donated in Euro so I assume
it's like evening for you now as well or
like late evening
go go go go meet some friends go to a
bar or so I suppose
wait I had like a
really really yummy strawberry mocktail
that literally tasted like strawberry
ice cream
mmm
my best friend
she was supposed to come and join us but
she arrived so late
I just wanted home because it was so
late
and I knew I had the
Korean study stream the next day
so I didn't want to stay for too long
and I felt like super awkward the moment
I walked into it
it was like a bar that I've been into
before I don't know is it maybe more of
a pup I'm really not sure where's the
difference
something like a pub something like a
bar they have like
um some stuff like you can play darts
and so on there as well
and and a pool
what do you call it in English
oh yeah apparently my friends told me
they have good bar food yeah
but the mocktails and Cocktails are
really good there apparently so yeah
I've been there before and I haven't
been there for a long long long long
long time maybe like two years or three
years even so I walk in and oh my God I
felt so awkward
felt like for real like this is not my
kind of place I don't belong here
it was like really packed and uh
I felt so nerdy and
when I walked in the others all seemed
so like normal and cool you know
I was like I don't want to be here
[Music]
we'll have to wait for my BFF because
she was kind of on the way
so I just sipped my cute strawberry
mocktail
while watching you guys despair about
the tickets on Twitter
uh
hoping for my friend to come soon
um
[Music]
teaching my other friend about croissant
and
stuff like that
the bigger problems
and a Gutenberg would feel maybe more
comfortable maybe yeah
outside seat okay
oh that's nice I can imagine yeah
okay okay
[Music]
so yeah
um
please hold a message
hey come on
it was fun it was fun wasn't it
finally some time to watch wow random
but I opened the stream and my mom heard
your voice is that the animal girl you
were watching last time too who sang the
cool song Good Luck goodbye goodbye
declaration yes I had to leave the
stream again because she wanted to
listen to it again
oh well how does it go again
da da
that's not goodbye declaration
[Music]
uh
that's the only thing I can remember
[Music]
my pajamas in the video I don't remember
those either
[Music]
it was definitely such a good cover and
video and I was so happy by Dan and I
did so well with you guys
um
he's dancing too
I remember my vacation back then
got scammed a little bit with my hotel
room because we didn't get the thing
that was on the picture
but besides that
was a nice vacation with my rmt
is your most popular video still really
how about my other musical Adventures
are doing quite well too I would say
I'm quite happy yeah
thank you
I have to listen to but like goodbye
can't [\h__\h] say it anymore goodbye
declaration again have to listen to it
you didn't bring a wedding gift it's
okay I'll take the money
and then let's stop it here any super
chat so come in now or afterwards I
won't read anymore
uh let me read the genma ones
I need to close them
I also went close this window
you cut off
okay buy smart super chats
eight boxes was a little bit too much
but without the eight boxes we may not
have gotten an energy card
but time wise
it got so repetitive after a point
took so much more time than I thought it
would damn
bamboozled
okay here we go
um
I didn't
think guys
Cruz Jones
thank you for two pinkies I personally
think every kfb should have their own
dignity like me I'm very dignified but I
would never do such a thing as butt kiss
oh greatest and beautiful and awesome
and intelligent leader Mighty well can
you tell me what is the meaning of is it
type horror games
do you really not know I actually I I
have troubles finding the best video to
introduce someone to croissant
because when I look it up on YouTube the
one that's the most recommended and
viewed one is that like
drawn cartoon video but I don't even
know if that's the OG I feel like the
other videos are funnier but
hmm I never know which one is the best
one
because I wanted to show my my friend
the one with me and Elena somebody made
one with me and Elena
but
it does it didn't come across as well
either I think it's like what is this
they don't get it they won't get it
huh
[Music]
well
is the answer to all your questions let
me tell you that
[Music]
see for the pinky let's hope Gemma pulls
some good ones she did
it was like really funny how
she pulled the first one was The Shining
energy then she pulls a shiny Chihuahua
and then at the very end the one side
one that we get is an entity
and we got all the hold of Tony ones the
nice ones except for mume
that's my only regret
um yes croissant is better than 42.
thank you thank you thank you jenma for
doing that for me
I hope she got some sleep afterwards
just like never sleeping man
Chester United Sky thanks for the pinky
you're always my you always will be my
true Oshi thank you for helping orange
color hair girl a lot you're the best
ah
you little shits I will not this will
not hurt me you guys cannot hurt me with
these words
I'm stronger than that I've grown you
cannot fool me anymore I know you love
me the most
you don't love 10 more than me but
honestly I mean I think she's always
flattered when you guys say things like
this so it's cute it's funny so no
problem
after all those years I'm so happy to
see your debuting on live
thank you for all your hardworking and
helping our Cute Mama I love you Jenna
you'll always be my question
it wasn't the proper debut as long as
she doesn't talk in it you can't even
call it a w she's not a YouTuber
she's not a YouTuber
hmm
communicated me a little bit
it's my manager okay
it'll make her into something she's not
thank you Alice
you guys so funny being so hyped about
my manager being on stream
our tease values
she's a hand tuber
I guess so
another new term was coined is
oh my God
even you
gosh
wow
wait I guess I shouldn't even be giving
you kisses because if you send this so
directly to Jenna you better hope that
she's gonna give you kisses but she
won't so
so what are you gonna do with that kiss
withdrawal huh
it's not gonna feel good
Unwritten bird thank you sir
Merlin Center
Chemical Romance
thank you you didn't write anything so I
assume this is for me right it's not for
General right Tai Chi you're not also a
general
supporter right she's not your true
kameoshi um
well I assume that's a yes
oh you sent the same Super Chat three
times
the same text
oh no you know you didn't
just the first sentence Oh
first and second
and the third
after the first sentence
it was all the same you probably thought
it didn't send huh
if I didn't go through
and then YouTube
[\h__\h] you over man
too bad
sorry YouTube is confusing
Jeep 636
uh
Patsy duncast
thank you for the pinky I was just
catching up on yesterday's Super Chat
stream and wanted to assure you that it
was a silly April Fool's joke I paid for
super chats with my own money
that is very relieving I'm glad
yeah I should have known I kind of knew
more or less well there was a little bit
doubt just you know
for your own
safety and all that
thank you monsters
[Music]
thank you
no
coming out to anyone Junction
check out for the seven alterations
as expected of Gemma she pulls a science
letter yeah it couldn't have been any
better
that's perfect I guess now I don't need
to give you my extra one from the first
set oh if I ever want to meet and greet
and could give a gift like people God to
Affordable me oh
randomly forever yeah thank you
yeah well the problem is
most conventions don't uh
uh you know
you know feel like it's necessary to
invite us in person as well but I mean
most of the time it isn't necessary and
if I would have to fly to America for
like one day of convention it would be
kind of a waste of time
um I don't know if I would even do that
no maybe I would because it could be fun
extending my stay a little bit
because I haven't been in America much
and could check out some places
but yeah it's a big time and money
investment
for both parties because even if they
pay for the flight in the hotel
with these kind of things you always end
up spending a lot of money on your own
anyway in the end
so huh
it's not really free
but yeah it would be nice if some
convention would invite me not only
virtually again but in person again
New England or North NorCal North
Carolina or what
or north California
what's North California
foreign
they don't invite me I don't know why
I'm right here
oh yeah Florida would be nice go to
Disneyland there yeah
I tried to get the big Colorado
Convention to invite you thank you for
trying I appreciate that
North Cal is North oh it really is oh
it is north California
San Francisco it's not California ah
I've been to San Francisco
I want to see it again
long time ago
say it again it was quite nice
oh that was nice you should go but
there's alligators
oh it will have its own Super Nintendo
World location eventually
I'll go when it has that
they better hurry
okay I'm done reading guys
I'm done
I am [\h__\h] nervous about the flow of
tomorrow
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] is
we are doing
I think I make a thumbnail after I wake
up
and
yeah
I can't even test it out yet I think
because it's not really
set up just yet but
it will be a bit gitty-gitty after all
I think
from what I saw in my Discord
the world is finished now
or like the world update but
now they're just starting now to program
like the games and stuff
well at least one of the games is kind
of using something as a template that
we've had before
I mean time wise it should be fine it's
just kind of getting engaging in terms
of testing it but
let's pray lucky kiwawa to make
an appearance again where everything
will go smoothly huh
and I will probably be in desktop mode
so maybe I can even have yeah another
good thing about being in decimal is
number one I can see the comments all
the time
um in terms of like audio check and so
on I can see if you guys say something's
bad and then also I could have a script
open to tell me what's next to do and I
always have a clear vision of
when to do the next thing and because
what I can see what time it is
and when to move on to the next thing
yeah yeah yeah
desktop mode definitely the way to go
this time hmm
yeah yeah
yeah yeah I have to be organized have to
stay on top of things
in the artist I'm sorry
are we sorry maybe another time
okay guys
then thanks for watching we'll finish
five of them next week guys
yeah
and then Claire will be an anime Boston
tomorrow I'll see you there bring your
towel and maybe pen lights
and yeah bring your good mood alright
hmm
and wear orange yeah
thank you bye bye love you guys see you
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]