oh
[Music]
welcome
but now we have council so it's the
first almost full collaboration
and
[Music]
[Applause]
probably watching this
the discord support today and hopefully
also the viewers support today because
uh today will be a very very passionate
and dangerous and fun and exciting
events yay it's race day
[Music]
i may be uh bad driver but i'll drive
you guys nuts
[Laughter]
i think we shall oh my god some
introductions of each member uh now
let's start with
from whole live indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
anya melvisa from hello life i second
generation
thank you everyone i can't wait what's
your what's your goal
what's my ikigomi um to not be on the
last last place at least
[Music]
okay
what about
senpai
oh
hello oh
obviously
i'm from
poland i read generation one
so my motivation
tonight is um to show you my practice i
guess
[Music]
oh show me what you got
next up how about rainey
hi
attention please i'm pavilio rainey from
whole life id generation 2. my goal
today is to be
number one in your heart and also not
that loud
oh yeah
yeah i thought you were good you and
iris have heard good
good news about you we had a good
practice yesterday right right yeah
nice
[Music]
next up how
nice to meet you
[Music]
what's your motivation for today
oh well
i i want to be at least not on the last
okay
[Music]
the last and the last in someone's heart
is that such a good thing
does it sound like a good thing
yeah okay next up
[Music]
hi
hello hello everyone
from whole life indonesia and thank you
so much for inviting me to this collab
i'm so happy though i'm so excited they
go
yes
[Music]
my motivation for today is that i would
like to have fun though although yes i'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
it will be fine
as long as we all have fun it's all
[Music]
hi guys
motivation i plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms what is my
motivation for today
[Laughter]
ooh
okay it seems jokes on you we're already
here
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
thank you
and i think wait did i get
all the introductions from id i think i
did
[Music]
back yeah introduce the inside let's
start with irise
oh yeah hi russ it's iris hololive
english project hope v singer here um my
goal today is to get first place
victorious
thank you amy for participating and
looking forward to your driving skills
thank you so much for having me here so
i heard that you waited for
yeah
for me to come online
you were literally the last thing that i
needed because before you it was there
were elf elf
that was german we were 11 people
do you not understand germany
12 12 12 is
[Music]
yeah thank you next up how about
hello amelia
number one hello i'm detective
today i'm gonna win probably okay
i heard you only played mario kart so
far in a member's only stream but that's
about it
yeah i won and that one too oh oh oh
okay
i see
oh then you might be the hidden
um winning choice that the one
horse
dark horse
[Music]
english um
um i'll do my best i think we have a we
have a fiercer competition to be not
last and to be first so i'll do my best
[Music]
yeah i was also
taking this very seriously in her
practice round so a bit scared of inna
no i don't know
i'm still falling off maps it's fine oh
yeah it happens oh kelly joined
yesterday nice thanksgiving
thank you there's a door around here
nice
let's continue with the uh introduction
from cal iop
maureen hello everyone my name is
callipe my parents are still asleep and
probably can't watch the news this
morning maury nice to meet you i'm gonna
be talking a bit low because it's a bit
early uh so excuse me for that guys but
i'm very excited just to be here i
really didn't think this was going to
work but it's working i love it
[Music]
thank you kelly for joining even though
it's such an early time and kind of
troublesome with some setups and all
that i'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good uh thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
oh
[Laughter]
english and i'm kind of sick today and
if you're watching on my site i just
need to say this now
i've had some technical difficulties
very suddenly so i am made of cardboard
i'm sorry please bring well i it was not
my fault it's out of my control right
now so anyways
i'm png tuber domo somebody does a png
tuber let's race today baby i'm the wild
card today
[Applause]
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so i think it's fine
i'm curious of course they want to look
at me right guys
[Music]
i wanted to do this tournament for a
long long time i i think my viewers have
heard me talk about it since months ago
and finally it's happening uh and i'm
very glad to have all these lovely girls
here together it's the first time we're
doing a tournament like this so i i
don't think anyone has to feel bad about
you know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some uh more often in
the future so please don't stress
yourself out let's just have fun today
[Music]
i think we will go to the roof but
before that let me say thank you uh the
hats and the cards are sponsored by
minomai inanis
[Music]
so cute all right let's uh everyone
switch to the rules image please thank
you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically uh all characters
all courses are allowed however
uh if you choose uh please do not choose
random courses please choose a certain
course that you want to actually erase
but if that course has been used before
like if it has actually been chosen
before please do not choose the same
course again
already understandable
[Music]
and
number two items are allowed number
three uh we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistant i think you
can check by pressing y
all right i think i've turned it off now
okay
yeah
if uh wait a second it's if you press y
and select your character at the point
where you select the card you can press
on uh plus
the plus button
and that way you see the the three
options on the right side if you press l
uh if if there's a
if there's a
sign that says no
then it's uh
auto steering off that's how it's
supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the other ones you can ignore
oh
okay okay okay
okay
uh-oh
i also want to quickly let you guys know
yes i'm on i'm going to be on like auto
mute this whole time so unless i have
something to say i'm going to be muted
don't worry if i'm a little quiet i'm
still here with you guys in spirit
yeah okay no problem no problem
and next row uh oh yeah then there's no
more rules let's look at just the system
we're doing the first cup all versus all
big mixer four races each and then we
get uh we mute each other by the way
during the race and just to focus
everyone on what we're driving and then
we get back together and discord talk a
little bit then we go to the second cup
which is en versus id six versus classic
yes yes yes gently we will separate each
other in uh the voice channels by team
this one and this one we will actually
talk with one another if you wanna and
then we uh
give some comments together again and
when we get all back together in the
same channel and then we do the third
cup with random randomly thrown together
teams no ian vs id but like all mixed
together naturally beautiful yeah
it's random
random random we will just like i'll
i'll count down and
and then everyone joins eva voice chat
room zero or voice chat room one is
[Music]
just so you know the the those like team
cups would basically be
um
like the same
as all versus all the difference is just
basically like if you throw items like
red tails or whatever and there is a
teammate in front of you it will not go
to the teammate obviously it will go
directly to the closest opponent driver
that's around you so yeah that's how
that team system works i think
okay
who's that random dude
is
[Music]
then everyone who is ready mute yourself
on discord if someone's not ready then i
will ask you why you're not ready
wait guys how do you wait guys uh how do
you go forward in the game
you push the
a button you can't go
right now yeah
world right now okay that's what you
mean gotcha all right understood thank
you thanks guys love you okay love you
too
okay all right so
hey
all right i muted myself okay and i'm
i'm quite nervous right now
and and cali sounds hot not gonna lie i
love it
i'm turning i'm turning down the the
game volume a little bit all right
okay let's go a first race
are you so so cali scally's voice is
like my mood booster right now so let's
go
i like this one
cali be like oh yeah i'm dead oh yeah
i love it
and also i'm really happy that i could
actually uh what is it i can actually
like legit collab this is uh with
everyone else again also this is my
first time collabing with iris she's a
very sweet girl we've talked before like
when we prepare
so yes it's it's really amazing i love
it i love everyone everyone's nice
and let's just let's just do it all
right
i've been practicing but
let's go
today
i i i
wow wow wow
okay let's let's focus and let's think
that everyone is npc alright
let's go
oh my god
hey
oh so i watched i wants uh corona
senpai's uh what is it uh practice
practice stream
that uh that she
like if she if she got like below eight
at the stream end and everyone's been
bullying her okay like
[Music]
it's so cute
ouch
teamed myself i don't want to get
bullied
but i think i played better though like
than the last time i played although i'm
still 11 though
i can do drift though which is nice
woof
ah done then
[Music]
all right
oh my god rainey is like the first oh my
god
let's go
i
wait where was us again
so where was us again i mean it's okay
for me to pick twisted mansion right
is it okay
is it still allowed because i forgot
what was our last
uh our last stage what was before what
is the name again
so yeah i forgot
okay i'm okay now all right all right
oh what is that oh what is that name
what is what is that oh cheap cheap
beach
[Music]
all right okay i forgot alright
let's go
second race
[Music]
ah i lost this
water
what is this water what is this banana
hey hey hey hey hey do not
[Music]
oh my god
ouch
[Music]
stop
i'm getting faster i'm scared
and
what's around to last
oh
[Music]
wow
let's go
crab
[Music]
okay and please everyone do not use
cheap cheap beach or uh mario kart
stadium anymore for your
collection thank you i'm gonna try and
remember that but i don't know
okay nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life
race
but isn't there multiple beach
uh yes but the cheap cheap beach the one
that we just did from the ds version not
anything yeah okay okay
okay are we doing team wait when are we
doing teams
uh we still have two races to go before
all this is all bye bye bye okay
oh sorry okay
[Music]
okay i'm already muted yeah
what is that
tow the harbor
towed
harbor
okay
[Music]
hmm
[Applause]
[Music]
oh there's a shortcut i didn't see it
oh no there's a shortcut
oh my god
[Music]
wow
she
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i'm definitely not not going to go there
[Applause]
[Laughter]
uh i lost it i i lost it i lost that one
all right okay
[Music]
i didn't
oh my god
oh my god oh
hey
bud
let's go
[Music]
oh my god
inna and iris is like so great right
okay one one more one more one more last
okay let me let me let's pick animal
crossing
all right
god it is amazing
don't worry now
no i think i'm improving so that's
that's
that's fine it doesn't matter
it's actually really fun playing with
everyone probably probably let's let's
play uh
let's play uh mario kart with with
everyone next time probably i can
i don't know if i can play it on
membership though but let's let's play
it
too like
like me and you guys so yeah
[Music]
hmm what is this what is this place
oh
confusing
i've never i've never played this stage
before
what
oh my god
oh goodness
oh goodness oh my god
out out out turn
out hey
[Music]
oh what is this ew trickle trickle
oh oh no
no i don't i don't i don't
wow somebody's actually up there
guys i got disconnected
oh no
i think i think i think we'll have to
like uh finish this because this is like
last round all right because if you get
disconnected uh uh uh cpu i like
computer computer will take care
will take care of your race
so
yes
computer unit
kind of thing we'll take care of your
your your race
what is this this is actually
[Music]
this is actually trippy
i will make everyone blind
okay about the disconnection i'm
i'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well the like disqualification like last
spot if you
uh oh
if you are oh wow
uh congratulations or everyone cannot
mute themselves now
oh yeah
[Music]
so
i think that's just how we're going to
take it it is what it is yeah maybe
[Music]
so uh
let me let me just uh ena was number one
right
number one
[Music]
i i saw you kept on selecting rainbow
road why do
rainbow
yeah yeah she practiced on that one a
lot i think that's what she was talking
about
you guys better be ready
there's no chance i will get it
oh okay someone has to
uh yeah
wait who was number one
okay
no problem who was number two though
iris is
how did you how did you manage to get
number two today
i i did bad on the first race so that
really pulled me back but yeah ina
senpai was very quick uh
but i did my best i did my best
you were amazing both of you
oh and me and elena were third ah we
tied up oh
third
job good job i wait wait are we complete
in the
lobby right now one two three i am in
the lobby
okay well then shall we continue uh what
muna senpai is currently unavailable
yeah she's checking something out oh oh
she's that low battery but i don't know
my my battery is 100 but it's a low
battery so i don't know which one is low
battery oh oh
[Music]
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time i i think i think it
should be fine
okay
sorry we're making coffee right now
i have the caffeine shakes already so
i'm banned from coffee
i was actually really surprised about
amma's driving too like i thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see her
playing the game and then talking with
him a lot so i was like i'm really close
to most of the races until the end when
i got silver
screwed over
i saw you go off the edge though watson
it was pretty good the gaming tactic as
planned right it's all part of the
planet
yeah whatever yeah no it would have been
a waste if you would have shout casted
how you uh suggested uh amer because
you're such a good driver we need you we
need you
all right then let's uh
oh okay ollie okay okay ollie is going
to be picking teams are we picking teams
like dodge ball no
no that gives me really bad flashbacks i
don't like that
[Laughter]
and i don't want that i'm gonna go at my
full power now because now i'm fighting
for the en ladies
i was just warm up now let's do that
yeah
this is good because inna and iris the
two of the strongest ones aren't ian
wait me too no
i got this in the bag
at not getting last place so that's good
news yes
morrison is a good asset to have i want
her on our team hell yeah
guys
[Music]
after all this i'll be good all right
oh i hope you don't get this connected
on the break right now
everyone uh please split into teams by
uh i think let's just um ian go to uh
voice channel 01 thank you okay
um i guess so we're going to abayo i
think i think we're staying yeah we're
staying
i guess
and then it's on this morning and this
isn't ellis can we watch
our team
i think kelly sampras secretly wants
gangsters
moms here are famous for like their
super reckless way of driving yes
supremacy
all right
the auntie very dangerous
i'm a very dangerous indeed
did you know
yes
uh there's a problem with my night
nintendo what's up what should we do
uh
[Music]
because like i thought uh
yeah you know
uh
open i just opened the room
okay
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again i think it's closed once you
can join again now yeah yeah thank you
sorry
all right
[Music]
all right i think i think that i think
that we actually need to buy separate uh
what is it controller did you get a
controller another
one controller yeah controller young
controller ps italia
[Music]
i was using the uh the normal controller
for the longest time and it had never
had problems mine is good though
yeah
it happened to me once
[Music]
and the worst thing is that my
controller actually died so
you might want to be careful with it um
okay now i think they say they're full
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm trying to not get the last place and
i i did okay i i
i yes
[Music]
ring
oh
[Music]
a
i hate this i have no idea who's in
front of us
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
like mario kart you know
where we where we play
[Music]
i think you have to be at least good at
mario kart because this kind of
tournament is gonna like happen in the
future yeah
like let's let's go let's go make it for
ourselves
[Music]
oh my god i bought the wheels for that
huh
[Music]
but it's not arrived sadly
i don't know i'm just using isn't it
[Music]
music man
where am i supposed to
should have worn
[Applause]
it's lava but i'm not born
[Music]
moment
[Applause]
i'm doing good okay somebody just like
stole my eyes
definitely it was not me
oh my gosh somebody somebody has like
kills
it's okay final laugh guys
[Music]
i really have a problem in this map
where is this
i'm i'm i'm lost
i'm dying
this is
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know
it doesn't matter honestly
see is land what
god why did they pick that place oh my
god rainy day remember
rainbow because it's all sunshine and
rain
[Music]
when i saw it i please cheeseland
gotta get that cheddar delicious
[Music]
we just like randomly screaming at each
other at this point right
yes
oh a lot of cheese
cheeses
[Music]
i think it's okay i i i did hope it's
okay though and i fall okay
that was for you
[Music]
and everybody
wow
i kept trying to cheating by flying you
know but i think out of it
how do
well you are an alien so you can't touch
the sky basically
[Music]
blue shell is the scariest thing and you
know
yes
the show's bad
oh no i gotta drive honest here
i'm not liking this i gotta drive on us
here
[Music]
that's dirty that's so dirty
oh my god
ah
let's try popping top five on all of us
i'll i'll i'll do my best
please
[Music]
okay we got cheese land so uh oh i'm
hacked
okay let's do the airplane stage
airplane airplane
airport
[Music]
sunshine
oh it's gonna be a rainbow road oh
yeah
especially this one this one is
especially hard
really
that one's easy but this one is
[Music]
so i wouldn't drive
oh
[Music]
oh my god
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
and i kept falling again
oh
[Music]
i almost fell
you know how to stop the car like kind
of like that
um
i guess
[Music]
yeah i guess your thumb um
oh no i fell
i hear the music like it's mocking me so
much
wait i'm not supposed to curse sorry
oh no i feel like
it's just loud it's loud
it's so because of our id
what does that mean
[Music]
like if it's indonesia yes let's go
okay let's go away so which one is not
okay english indonesia no english is
english is not good because youtube
youtube ai is bad bad right
awesome
but cursing
is okay
[Laughter]
it's okay we can do it guys
next time we did our best
we did our best yes
i expected guys
[Music]
in the next race because yeah
what was their reasoning behind choosing
uh the cheese one and the baby road
i like cheese
because like it's gotta be a road where
reina knows the shortcuts and stuff yeah
yeah
[Music]
well
i wasn't the one choosing it
what uh do we have uh
some
uh comments from the winner ina it was
number one i think
uh yes uh i would like to thank pajamas
um
academy
[Laughter]
for this
opportunity because because of you yago
i was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay
[Laughter]
okay so we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
um oh can you even if you have yes
what
what did we choose
i forgot what did i just
oh i mean well even if you accidentally
choose one that has been uh chosen
before don't worry it will probably not
be
i like that so let's just let's just try
to not choose the ones that we have uh
raced before then i will do the random
teams now actually there is uh we don't
have to do the voice chat thing because
there is actually uh a way to do it here
and then once the teams are selected
oh there it is okay so
uh in voice chat zero
uh zero zero one we want uh gouda
aina
anya
guys
all right
we still have home
[Laughter]
i'm not really confident in winning
against eno right now what's your
favorite map
my favorite map has to be uh probably uh
the airport right now oh okay airport
airport sunshine airport school airport
yeah airport airport all right okay then
how will we choose the iphone all right
we have to clean it one right yeah
what is it on
oh
well
uh aren't this like the the the you know
the the
the top 10 from the back
yeah the other team is is packed with
like the really strong ones
there's like
at least our top 10 right
let's go
yes also i'd like to apologize to you
personally because i kept bullying you
in the previous round i got karma
we got this
we believe
together darkness will fade
[Music]
wait i hate this map so much this one
particularly hard for me
i never win
uh
least i don't know
wait we can do it guys don't worry i
don't know
but we could do it what did i do
did i just
beat you what
yeah ollie's in front okay good good
[Music]
all right
no no please please please please
[Music]
okay
we're doing good
what oh
oh my god
oh no no oh no
this is bad
like even the song is
[Music]
this one feels like a toy story really
it does look like toy story isn't it
no come on please stop
oh yeah oh we stopped
[Music]
oh no wait who's in front of me right
now
arena yeah
okay i'm third
but i'm not confident okay i'm following
there are nobody in here i'm so far
waiting yeah
we didn't get all of the items
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
oh that was close that was very close
okay uh
second
[Music]
yeah
okay it could be worse
yeah yeah
yeah we're still we're still in the race
i don't like that we can hit our friends
that annoys me yeah
yeah
yeah the airport the items are important
airport
airport please
airplane okay
airport sunshine
okay
guys
i'm still okay
i just gotta beat nina she's gonna be
ena
you could do much practice today yeah
yeah
you are our hope how are you so strong
amelia's invite can't you rewind time so
that we can like redo that and win
isn't that crony's job oh yeah
but wait for everyone just me
amelia's the one with the watch right so
yeah she can go back in time and
practice a lot yes
yes
ah what is this
oh what is this
big blue big blue i don't know if i've
ever played this one before what is this
oh this one is like futuristic water
parkish oh
[Music]
ah
what i don't like is that the npcs keep
harassing me
all the ones in the map
in the way yeah
[Music]
oh i love this music though oh yes
it's a bop
[Music]
oh
oh iris
okay yeah i'm in the front right now but
this is very early game oh my god it's
not jinx
yes
oh my god
[Music]
oh there's somebody's actually flying
with bananas
well that's me
[Music]
really destroys my face ah okay
i don't see it
come on come on i want to see ina i
don't like him
i see right now
[Music]
legit like
if i know any shortcuts
i did not make it ah
i should have studied more
it's alright
sorry
[Music]
i don't think i've ever played this map
been yeah i didn't get lost again lucky
number seven baby i'm i'm getting really
healthy right now i'm being very salty
right now guys oh no oh no
piling up
the yeah will do us justice will ascend
it'd be embarrassing though if you get
airport and i still do bad at it
okay
i believe
let's believe
believe it
[Music]
oh everyone's choosing airport oh my god
are you really sorry
i hope you got it
wait is this the third race or the last
race is this
third
it's turned oh we got it yes okay we got
this we got this okay
no
don't shine airborne
let's just hope that ina doesn't really
know this map but i probably she
probably does i think she does
hi yeah
we can do myself to not use the items
that we got
[Music]
like what do you mean by lose as in uh
from like thunder and stuff there's no
way to really prevent that
no no no i mean like if we got something
but we don't want to use it how can we
you know
move it
to the trash
there is some of the item that i don't
really like to use
come on
[Music]
i don't really get how this music i have
this like speaker looking thing i don't
really know how i'm supposed to use it
oh it's like if there are like a lot of
people around you you can just like honk
it
and everyone's just like you know what
i'm just gonna honk it
let's just use it
i have a bad habit of holding on to
items
yes ollie go ollie okay
okay
[Music]
you're good
we're doing good so far okay
oops i'm sorry
that was close
okay we got
[Music]
it's okay we're in the same team okay
just gotta make sure it's not enough
okay
oh my god
[Applause]
[Music]
oh you got third
okay ah i wonder how this looks right
now
[Music]
you know what i kind of like being right
in the middle
does anyone have anything that they're
confident in
music i'm very confident
[Music]
okay yeah
oh no can i can i join before it is ah
yeah you can join oh oh i'll tell you
i'll tell first sorry
run for
um
[Music]
oh no
oh my god
uh okay i'm back now every point counts
ladies let's do this not not the clock
not the clock i don't like they still on
the same team though
i hope so
okay
oh yeah okay
this one has a lot of drifting so
whenever you guys
did just get ready for a lot of do you
know the shortcuts for this okay there
there are a few shortcuts but they're
actually pretty tricky so i wouldn't
recommend them
okay yeah all right let's let's do this
i don't really recognize this place but
let's go
i'm gonna win this
ah
oh no i just passed
up on the beginning okay over here the
piano dress
okay
[Music]
then let's go
and then another one
[Music]
yeah this is a lot of dripping okay
yeah this place is kind of tricky so
please be careful
okay there's a shortcut over here but
it's really really tricky
shoot
okay wait uh
who's first right now i see inaudible
how can we know who's the first
because i saw them
oh god
i don't like this map
oh no guru is in front of me
oh you're our last hope right now i'm
i'm doing really bad i'm a zombie how am
i my host
that's okay
i got inaudible
[Music]
hope has consumed zombie meat a lot so
we're good
oh no i see so many people here
[Music]
good job
what's the piano
okay okay
[Music]
oops
did i accidentally hit someone
nope okay be careful
oh no
good
sorry i'll go watch one of your
one of your
perspectives to see what's going on
so when i ate okay i'm last so when i
got oh
[Music]
well it was a valiant effort ladies and
one four four hey that's two fours in
there four's a good number i like it i
can't say i'm unhappy
[Music]
i forget
okay so we uh we had a great i got
clicked out of the room uh
yeah
[Music]
and we had two disconnections so it kind
of doesn't count
yeah i guess connected it really doesn't
count and when i rejoin like my points
are
all reset
[Music]
yeah
we got disconnected
i got disconnected like right before the
last lap
oh no that was me my shark friends after
the wi-fi cables
[Music]
that probably means that you know the
last round if if liso you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round uh final
result is not really accurate um
but that's okay let's just say the last
round was an extra encore for fun
and yeah and i would like to give out
some golden yogurts
we all want a golden yagu right so okay
they're not showing up on your stream
but i'd like i would like to give one a
golden juggle to ina for winning almost
everything
yeah
good job
[Music]
and i would like to give
another uh golden yago um as a to iris
for also being absolutely
amazing golden yaga
another golden juggle goes to
dana for being i guess the strongest in
the id team holy molly
[Music]
goes to gura for being absolutely the
speediest shark i've ever seen
[Music]
[Laughter]
big surprising uh what do you call that
oh
wild card
[Music]
[Applause]
goes to muna for being amazing
[Music]
i didn't see you that much on the race
but i think you were still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
and now the golden yellow goes to ali
for being also surprisingly damn good
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
and another golden yago goes to cali for
actually really you know i don't
you surprised me you surprised me callie
i was i was looking at you driving there
and i was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arcs is
she's so good maybe
[Laughter]
didn't i didn't get last place even once
guys that was my goal
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you we love you moving don't mind
me uh chat i'm not gonna be able to fix
that now i think one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven
uh
wait who did i not give up
you were surprising me too sometimes i
have i had an eye on you thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah you very much everyone um i hope
you all had fun um can we get like uh
last comment from everyone let's start
with uh anya
oh me
okay um that was so much fun but i have
to practice more it's gonna be next time
i don't know maybe
maybe there's gonna be it will
definitely be a next time yeah
there's always room for improvement
[Music]
kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff ina as well for
helping with the assets but like
oh my goodness you organized the whole
thing and it was a blast and i just
wanted to have fun with my friends and i
was able to do that because you
organized this amazing thing just thank
you so much for for working so hard on
it because it was a blast
thank you i'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you
[Music]
thank you i want to say thank you also
to ina and kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and i'm very i'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as i thought it
would and i would like to uh say that it
was probably because i fixed my switched
leg so i didn't have any lag let's go
gamers let's go
no
nice
now excuse me i'm sorry i watched and i
won though i can you said excuse
[Music]
even though i me played the game in a
long time i think yeah no practice baby
let's go raw talent let's go rob allen
shark that's cool
well
uh you know i'm coming from last place
yes so i'm just uh thank you for uh
organizing this i know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles
but yes thank you for this golden yeah i
will cherish it and talk to you
[Music]
okay i've completely disappeared i'm
sorry guys
okay i raise clothes in common please
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament kiara and
thank you so much ina for the very very
cute assets
and
yes i will practice more so that
we can i can get go against ena
yeah yeah my goal is
my goal is you know
yeah
i'm excited to do this again hopefully
one
day thank you i hope yeah one day i want
to win against
inaudible that would be a big
accomplishment it's not that big of a
goal
not the confidence
i'm so glad i'm so glad you joined holo
ian because that's what made this uh
tournament possible
yeah i'm really glad to be able to join
this wonderful tournament being part of
the cool kids
okay i'd like to say a very very big
thank you to kiara senpai for organizing
this i've organized it once and it was
really hectic so i can't really imagine
the links that you go through
for like long logos and stuff and even
the thumbnails those must have been hard
and also for innocent wife are making
all of those assets so quickly like you
guys really um how do i say it i really
appreciate it a lot and i'm sure all of
us do so thank you so much for your hard
work it was really fun playing with
everyone and um i may have not popped
everyone but one way or another you guys
will all be young
i forgot about that goal yeah
you'll get them someday only you'll get
them
thank you
thank you all right
stand by closing completely
um first of all i'm thank you for you
kiara for organizing this thing and
you guys can stop thanking me
stop
i mean
i i don't think without without you
organizing we wouldn't be like this
i mean it's it's it's rare to
gather all the whole life indonesian
together that's true yeah so i'm so
thankful for that
and also
um
big thanks to inna 2 for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and i hope uh in the future we can
be like this again yes
yes yes yes i hope so too definitely i
was thinking like maybe on on
like around christmas or new year's eve
yes
okay
closing comments please yeah i'd like to
say a big thank you to
kiara for organizing it of course i know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and
like schedules is really really
difficult but you really put a lot of
effort into organizing it commissioning
like the logo and everything really
thankful um and everyone feel free to
use your hats and cards like in your
meyer card streams in the future too
[Music]
yeah thank you everyone for joining us
today like it was so much fun like
playing with everyone and i hope we can
do it again definitely
it's been a pleasure big
operation this was a great cooperation
between uh kfb and taco taco bell taco
eats definitely
yeah
[Music]
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speed because we're
fast
okay all right
closing comments please okay i know you
said stop but thank you kiara
thanks for everything
and
also inna senpai uh thank you so much
and i had a lot of fun oh there was a
little mishap there there was a little
disconnection issue but overall i had a
lot of fun and i would love to have this
kind of tournament again in the future
let's do it you were so good yeah yeah
thank you
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay so it doesn't end there i would
like to say thank you
again
to to everyone here also especially uh
kiara and ina like it is
amazing and also okay uh i'm really
happy because i can actually uh gather
and play with all of you guys here
because
yes like well uh i'd appreciate more
more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
i
i'd love to and i would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much i
love you guys
[Music]
ah
well first uh i'd like to apologize
if i was salty if i cursed that you guys
uh
[Music]
yeah thank you kiara and and ina you
guys worked really hard thank you guys
and thank you everybody for
participating it's really fun i know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules thank you and i had
a lot of fun thank you
you know now that we have uh now that we
have holy council we can like we don't
have to relay on these exact 12 members
anymore so next time if you want you can
do shout casting
thank you
thank you everyone for participating
today um i hope i hope everyone had a
great time even if you know maybe you
were not number one number two number
three that's fine i think today was
really just about getting together
putting um two communities two fan
communities of hello ian and hello id
together and just feeling united
definitely and i am always glad to um do
stuff like this again so i will gladly
invite you guys again whenever you have
time for it and want to join and i'm
sorry that you know because since it's
such an international collaboration um
it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so i'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like six seven a.m
or something like that i'm so sorry i
know it's tough i it's no problem it was
fun
i hope your mom enjoyed the tournament
i think she did i think that she should
as well
hey
[Music]
i would like to officially close to holo
ian hall id mario kart tournament
everyone
take care of your golden yagos polish
him every day he wants to be shiny and
sparkly
and yeah i'll see you guys soon
[Applause]
[Music]
bye everyone
this