wow
let's test everyone's volume everyone
say things yeah
how are you doing good
everyone say something say something
something next
[Laughter]
seems fine no one's complaining on my
side are you good i think everything's
good
oh
is is everyone already in the holiday
mood
jingle jangle bengal bangla
[Music]
in the middle at the port can we all
meet up at the portal
everyone at the portal
[Music]
the voice is definitely peeking okay
that's fine that's funny
okay maybe this is okay
[Music]
someone going back and forth in the
portal i keep hearing it now is that 200
volume
hold up let me just
[Music]
i gotta go drop my cat off at the house
so he stays
safe oh yeah i've got like i have like
12 i think i have too many
but then again there's never such thing
as too many cats okay
your house is looking good now thank you
amelia added a nice touch on top i don't
really know what it is
it looks better wow yeah that looks
better what do you say
yeah i think i definitely made a big
contribution like can you get rid of my
chickens
a long finger oh it's a finger is it a
middle finger
yeah you could say middle you can say
that i think the answer is clear if you
have to uh
ask
[Music]
flying out of the wall i don't really
know how he did it
don't you think someone else's cat maybe
uh no
they shouldn't have a car yeah there's
water entrance to your house
why is it that when gooda walks all this
dirt comes up
cause i'm dirty
[Laughter]
smells sad
i didn't come here to be bullied man
you didn't come here too but that
doesn't mean you're not going to be
telling me the christmas tree is this
your christmas tree
oh yeah let's go see the christmas tree
over here
[Music]
yeah i built this earlier
it's the dinner bell i'm hungry
[Music]
if you look inside this chest yeah if
you look in the box there's like a bunch
of different decorations and shears
so you guys can make your snowmen and
they'll be alive
truly do you guys want to build a
snowman oh my god
you come on let's go and play you see
these
these pillars here that have snow and
they have the pumpkin if you grab a
sheer from the chest
and you uh use the shear on the pumpkin
then
now you have a snowman you can take off
the pumpkin
wait what what how do i get
in here
[Music]
and then you can take the pumpkin off if
you want to or you can leave it
oh my god they always try escaping i
have to put a fence here
that's so cute is that a mod or is it
actually in-game a feature
that's not in game chat
[Music]
and what else do i want they're trying
to
[Music]
i'll trap them hold on i killed my
snowman and only left me was these
snowballs
what do i do with them uh you can throw
them at people
can i build another snowman i messed up
yes how do you build a snowman how do
you do it again
right click with the sheer on the on the
pumpkin top
oh yeah you you just need like a few
snowballs and you can make a snow block
you don't need like a
a crafting table to do it and then you
can
put two down and put a pumpkin on top
[Music]
i know you already prepared a lot of uh
decorations on it but
i also prepared about the pumpkin so
that i can also contribute so i want to
put some pumpkins on the tree yeah yes
whatever you want i just picked some
extra stuff that closed these snowmans
and if i do
but it's gonna be hard to decorate on
the other side when there is literally a
cliff there
um that's how we have a scaffolding look
you see all the scaffolding i took half
of it i never used that before
yeah scaffolding scaffolding is nice
because you can just click on the ground
and it just spills itself
you can build really hot yay
with like one one hit like like
and then breaks all down it's really
good yeah oh they hit spacebar and it
goes up
look at that on top of it when i use the
snowball it just uh it
just makes me throw it yeah yeah you
gotta make it in the in the blocks
[Laughter]
you have a shovel you can also uh you
can dig these
the snow on the ground what happens if i
put a torch as a light on on the tree
does the tree burn
oh the point so oh we have like these
glowy i can't put it on there anyway
but yeah we need to lighten the tree up
as well no don't set it on fire
that's not no don't worry i'm not going
to set it on fire
scheme we're going for or is it just red
ah
whatever you want whatever color i think
it works yeah
why are we putting some wool over the
lights
i'll bring some color i've colored all
over you put them wherever you want
to climb up this elevator thingy daisy
should we build a star on top yeah yeah
yeah how do we build redstone lamps or i
have these shroom
shroom lights either work it's growing
so pretty
damn can you not put the scaffolding on
a bush
oh
[Music]
does anyone here already have a tree in
their home
i forgot
you got to put it on sideways stuff like
uh on the wall like this oh
[Laughter]
what are you guys doing
crimson roots wait who are they throwing
snowballs at
what a shame oh they're zombies oh
can
[Laughter]
right at my arrow
[Music]
the words come in handy the ones i
taught you oh yes delicious
you go where'd you go oh boy
where did you come from where'd you go
where'd you come from cotton nigel
huh
thirsty i see i need to bring some
stronger weapons
tara hasn't spotted her yet
she's going she's going to get more
weapons
this is what christmas is all about
right fighting
fighting we're fighting around the
christmas tree
called christmas girl oh dead
oh no i need to get something oh no oh
no
you need some steak did you make a
mistake
no real for real they need some steak oh
that might be nice
actually maybe i can at least put some
bones oh wait no
oh no now all these weird rocks are in
front of our tree
because i tried to make a big tower so i
could i could put the star on the top
to just be able to like jump around like
if you come this way kelly
yeah follow me i think we can get to the
top like this
you just jump on the blocks yes oh okay
maneuver around the tree
it should be like a little stairway okay
did you call a uh taco
dolly yeah yeah oh
yeah how does it work where did you get
what is what is she plotting now
i was just setting something on fire but
don't worry it won't be the christmas
i just want to tree this bone somewhere
i can't all the things that i want to
put down i can't put down
when you press e and you you click on
your inventory you can drag it out
and then just oh drop it just drop it
somewhere okay cool yep
to make the star with glowstone's like
glows
oh yeah yeah well there's also the
there's also redstone light but i don't
i'm not sure how to make it
oh it's still right that sounds pretty
hmm
i don't realize how much torches are
around our town until now
some bones there they're just kind of
floating well they disappear i wonder
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
hi
they look like them
[Music]
we're safe okay scaffolding
here's zombie why are so many chickens
i don't know why you tell me why ma'am
[Laughter]
i mean they do eat a lot of kfc in uh
japan for christmas
yeah they do i don't know what so
why on christmas but i eat fried
chicken nuggets every day hello girl is
the star
girl is the star on top of the tree oh
[\h__\h]
star should we do like wait i have an
idea i have an idea
will you get close don't hold on let me
get it i have like
i have some glowstone i have 28. i took
a bit of it
if anybody has redstone dust i can try
making a redstone lamp
okay gonna think
now i'm reading your house for redstone
dust okay
i forgot where i put it but it's in
there somewhere
um
[Music]
bringing out the battle accent if that's
how you want to play
now ladies let's not play fair thank you
we're gonna be nakaya takayoshi
impromptu star ready
oh another man is here i heard enderman
no oh there you go with us
is it the andaman from the uh the
railway
endermen okay
okay uh miss calliope
yeah could you take a backstab just
knock towards the cliff
oh towards the cliff
i need a i need a little bit of room for
the star thank you guys
[Music]
have you ever thought of the theory that
enderman might just be
enma song our manager
uh
that would be quite a twist
what's your building i don't know
[Music]
all the different types of lines yeah
look
this looks so nice a little more sense
in my head
but that's breaking here
it's gonna be a scuffed scar i want to
see how it looks from the fly
we need a little bit more yellow here
looks good looking good wait let me see
how that star is looking
quite nice it might not be very storage
but
it's good either yes i just can't put
them anywhere else i wonder if we could
have like
a few more color variations in the
decoration although it looks kind of
cluttered now so i mean
should we add more hmm i think a few
more colors would be nice though
maybe like some wool yeah i think that'd
be good
i'll put mushrooms on it pink and green
let's see what colors i have ah
see how this looks i can't tell
i i'm gonna think it's upside down i'm
gonna put
some of my fancy white glazed terracotta
on it but can i have it back when the
tree is gone
maybe maybe not because i got them from
far away lands okay i don't want to lose
them
next week we could blow it up with tnt
oh they're really fancy
that's a nice idea we can make lots of
tnt we can make fireworks and we can
send off the fireworks yeah
i
okay this is easy i can do blocks the
roots i can't understand
i can't make them work i tried very hard
it's not working
they don't want to go anywhere the style
looks good
it's a little skunk but we can improve
it later
it's nice i can't get up the scaffolding
ow
who pushed me it was a you you little
wasn't me
what's the chicken what does it say it's
a chicken no no no
no no i'll eat you don't blame me down
my employees
[Laughter]
innocent nothing
yes of course yes
is the tree lopsided or is it just me
i don't remember being like that but
it's possible that
i may have forgotten one side
i can't make progress how do you get up
there
oh god uh hold on oh man
i can fix this what did you guys want
for christmas
oh what did you ask me
well you have to ask but what about
everyone else
[Laughter]
i want sleep
look
oh wait do you need leaves i have like
like i wanted
oh yeah leaves yeah you have leaves yeah
i do hold on
i need them we can't make the tree even
bigger you won't believe how many leaves
i have
[Music]
i have birch and uh oak and i have a lot
of spruce
are
oh i'll come to you my house
we're gonna have a very mixed
treat yeah this is fine
do you guys like when trees have like
themed ornaments or do you like when
it's uh
like a bunch of handmade different
colors oh
i like colors lots of colors colors and
that's like a more
personal flair to the trees i think
um
are you are you guys even gonna get a
tree this year
i'm probably not getting one because uh
i i don't want to get rid of it it's
kind of annoying in here
and in japan you have to vacuum after
the trees a lot so it's easier to get a
fake one
especially and where are you
you know what fun when you have cats and
a christmas tree that's fun
yeah i had some kittens that were hiding
in the dream christmas it was very
nice
cute okay nice
i think something even where's the door
oh it was up
thank you thank you
[Music]
if i make the star a little better it's
going to be like bigger than the tree
has to be bigger from afar
i can't wait to see oh wait it's
glowstone that means it's going to glow
i'm so excited to see this glow how are
you guys
yeah good point
this could be so much fun
[Music]
i wish we could make like different
colored lights
can you use one glossy oh we can make a
we can make stained glass
stained glass nice idea go bring some
[Music]
ah my trees
i'm trying to make it uh a bit more
spacier
we can put even more in it looks so good
from afar
it's so cute
wow goddammit
they're not always perfect okay yes
exactly
that's but them being individually
beautiful that's what makes them special
oh
i literally have no idea what i was just
saying but okay i'm glad that's a lie
well it sounded good um
i mean i brought some stained glass
i'll put it in the chest thank you
[Music]
i only brought like two of each because
that's all i had left over but if you
need more i have more
how do we light up the stained glass
still can you light it up
i guess you can put it like in front of
a glowstone the light so if you look
from the front it looks like different
color maybe
huh what if we put torches on the tree
will it catch on fire
[Laughter]
they don't even place on the on the
leaves um oh i guess you'd have to have
a block
what does it have somehow um what if you
put it on an ornament
is it getting too much now how does it
look still
that could probably put torches on like
the pumpkin or the terracotta
oh yeah it's missing a bit of clothes
over there okay it doesn't burn the tree
it'll be fine
and the sun is setting almost time okay
should we put something under the tree
like a carpeting or
something like a carpet sounds nice
right
maybe i can all right
the tree looks so yummy forbidden snack
trees
what color should it go under the tree
guys red
oh red would be nice
i'm sorry i'm trying to move
are you okay are you okay are you okay
it's okay she's she's not that's itself
she can't
she can't tell it right yeah tr true
facts
she looks so cute from over here it
looks so
good oh i want to see
oh that is so cute
oh my heart
there's like a perfect spot for a
photograph
can i make the decoration for the tree
as well i want to stay on here
oh my god
oh you want me to be there naked okay
that's what i like to see as well i see
our tastes are very similar
that's why we are both business owners
taco bell and kfb hell yeah exactly
oh i think we could use one more
we can make a christmas card and then we
can sign it and then we can post it
yeah it looks really pretty it's a great
idea i like that
let's do it then happy holidays
from halloween to you
[Music]
are you looking at huh
while i eat these potato chips i will
provide a view of the christmas tree for
everything you eat anything besides
potato chips
is there a reason to and bread
that's that's your favorite food i'm
gonna order some vegetables water for
lunch i wonder what i should have
wow
i mean potato is a vegetable right yes
yes yeah yeah before potato chip is
vegetable
yes agree
i also agree that this fried chicken is
healthy and pizza is healthy
oh oh we gotta sleep we gotta sleep oh
god it's like
i'll shoot him down guys don't worry
one day's in there
come back down fight me like a real
fandom
that's what i thought yeah wait nice
nice no i shot shot
shots
is there only one i think it's only like
only
one the skies are safe another day yes
i feel bad i wish i was there to help i
tried to go to sleep
you guys remember the first minecraft
collab where we all just got at the
start
the perfect time how times have changed
how they have there's a party going on
in my chat right now
party did someone bring the police
[Music]
i'm ready for battle maybe we should
sleep they what if they destroy our tree
there's three they just destroy our
lives
that's okay that's expendable we can
take them
thank you kfb thank you i love you guys
oh sweet where is it
i see it enemy spotted he's going
to sleep he's hissing oh he's sitting at
the cat i don't think he likes the cat
oh wow
are you sleeping or not i'm gonna go to
sleep i gotta sleep
okay sometimes the best option in a
battle is just to sleep
i will also sleep i'm sleeping on your
cat's bed
okay are you sure you can because the
phantom's around
i think so i'm gonna sleep to the the
calming sounds of their hissing
let's pretend they're just pretend
they're um
in front
thank you everyone oh my god they're
still partying
party party party oh they're gonna burn
to
they look like phoenixes except they're
dying instead of coming back alive
oh my god those are so infertile
they're gone you're cute
necronomicon second edition yes
what
[Laughter]
there was actually a cat that looked
just like the first edition i think
those girls
girls can huh oh yeah
it's like the uh the three different
colored ones
oh yeah yeah yeah i have a lot of cats
now i can't really remember what they
all
look like i think we're gonna have more
and more cats because of the
iron i mean i'm fine with that they're
still killed
right yeah more i only have one but i
want i would millions of cats in my home
soon yes wait what is this can i ask
what this is
is this like it's the uh
the photo zone for i don't know the
viewing platform
yeah the photo zone
temporarily i'll just think oh so cute
tree's looking good it actually looks
really
really really good i'm really happy with
it
oh terrible it's really good it's a
little more red oh
it's just a little more red in my
opinion more red or
just a little more red like bright red
like this kind of thing
you know like red flame red red red
red red red red
[Music]
we should make like a red carpet that
goes to like the entrance
oh good idea i have some red if you
would like to do it do you want to do it
yes please oopsie give me some red there
you go
wait hey go like
so our elevators are gone huh oh do you
need some you can build oh it's okay no
worries
oh good in the hood i think i'll just
climb it the old-fashioned way oh here
there's some skype in here
who doesn't have to shoot me while i'm
partying with my employees
[Music]
you're having an intimate moment do you
really think i
would do that i'll watch the archive
i'll see
what happened there okay guys this is
unarchived
suddenly it becomes unarchived quick get
rid of the evidence
like scrub it
it's okay it's okay um it's okay
excuse me thank you it feels good yeah
she's used to dying
i like pain i'm a mess against
[Music]
i tried so hard because they're vines
didn't work out
yeah oh i kept destroying those my bed i
thought they were like
what i thought they could actually go
get the uh
you can find separately oh low power i
don't think you can
what i have vines that i can bring i'll
bring him
i'll go get him you want wine
the game has stuff like that what mm-hmm
not it's not a tinsel are you talking
about like tinsel that you wrap around
the tree
you know something like yeah oh it just
hangs down
but we can yeah oh but that's cool
yeah i don't hear a zombie um is there
anything you don't have
i'm telling you guys there's zombies
everywhere
i keep hearing them just like there's no
there's no caves
careful they got arrows too they'll
shoot you you sure don't get you
what's for christmas dinner by the way
oh
yum chicken and christmas cake of course
hey
christmas cake i'm gonna steal your
snowflake
no you're not
oh my god the sound of
the sound of snow when you walk on it
isn't it amazing
crunch crunch crunch
they have to tell you something from a
distance
oh no from uh
you look beautiful
thank you
would do some damage so we can have like
an actual snowball fight
maybe we could throw we can throw some
arrows at each other oh yeah almost
until we die
maybe we should build that we should
build a coliseum
yeah oh and we can fight to the dead
what are you gonna build a ring yes i
did
like a you bought like a fighting ring a
boxing ring
yeah yeah it's over to my house do we
want to have a
battle christmas battle i'd like a
christmas batter
forget the christmas dinner it's time
for the christmas battle
yes the christmas battle that's what i'm
concerned about if we need to
tell you i'll just bring us back kfc and
yeah exactly i'll just bring you well
actually that's not really my job it's
kind of my job to keep you from coming
back but uh you can
[Music]
12 deaths of christmas no i'm really
lagging
watson is suspiciously quiet has anybody
seen watson ah
i'm in the tunnel why are you in the
tunnel
now i'm going to get vines and i'll be
i'll be back in like
four minutes i thought vines only take
six seconds
okay oh my goodness
okay that was good i'll give that to you
that was a good one that was really good
oh my god i'm so proud of myself
it took like a sec half a second and i
was like
that was really nice
oh my god a comedian
kiara you are on fire tonight
he's always on fire
yeah i like it
uh i can't do it did somebody say
possible
oh were you going to make an attempt on
my life no no you were going to make an
attempt on my life because you don't
have a life if you're
you're deaf exactly that's the point
which is why it wouldn't work
i don't know why i feel like battling
good albums i mean
oh so you're attempting i'll hurt both
of you i'll hurt both of you
it doesn't hurt though it doesn't hurt
at all though
let me throw cannonballs i can pretend
it is
this looks so good i really like it
i'm adding a little snow to the top
a frosted christmas tree frosted tips
like guy theory i like yeah yeah that's
right
like that guy tasting around the
christmas tree
all right coming back
[Music]
snowman do your thing oh you gave him a
life
yes i saved him from
i
[Music]
on the it's like a what is it not a
snowball
right now you take the snowballs and you
go in your inventory and you line them
up in a straight line i think
that's how you make them meanwhile yeah
you just fill
your uh crafting slots with no balls
and then you get snowblocks or you can
get you can get like the little
little snow thingies like the flat one
yeah snow thingies oh yes
yeah there's no thingies
what would you call them they're like
platforms i don't know there's a snow
sheet yeah yeah yeah
like this
wait wait wait some ornaments too the
torches remove the snow oh
no a snow carpet and
an effort was made
if we put lanterns i don't think it will
melt them uh
i think all the snowman just fell down
anyways oh
can you put the snowman on a lead
oh that's a good question can we put a
saddle on him
can we can we make a snow horse
hi he's so cute though he's so cute
very merry
well at least there's still more and
more snowman just jumping up and down
[Music]
i got an idea and we should get the
those red bushes
they're like holly we can put a holly
can we make a mistletoe
yeah yeah yeah
i want a mistletoe
[Laughter]
i'll make it here to be fine
[Music]
are you making an igloo yeah
i'm making a cake
oh my god i love it yes can i help you
anything
you're not um
[Music]
should we make landers for the well i
thought the torches look like candles
but like
i was wondering if we could make like
bigger candles with like
uh oh yeah yeah yeah um
this idea here and this
glass
[Music]
your sniping skills
do your worst phantom oh my gosh
all right you're fighting them all right
nice nice nice
provoke them i've got five shots today
today everybody uh
drop something good it'd be nice i
didn't even drop
anything cute box in here
hello
and the tree looks so good from the
distance too doesn't it it's
so colorful so pretty
christmas cake that's gonna be a cake
[Music]
yes shouldn't the ground layer be
i mean okay it's all going to be out of
cream okay
again why not but we could have it later
a layer came good like a like yellow and
white
oh with cream on top with strawberry
yeah
yeah and then you can have the sides
showing so you can see the strawberry
peeking out that's the plate
the plan yes now it can build on top of
it okay
you have yellow for cake oh this is the
i mean i have buckets
while i'm sleeping does that look like
from the side like it could be
what we want it to be but do you have a
layer of
yeah just a visual
this is so not symmetrical
you see this vine here yeah i guess
it'll blend in
i don't know it would hang you can hang
it off of stuff
let's get on with it okay let's see what
happens
go get him tiger cool it makes an
interesting
it looks interesting oh that's i see
they're only in green
uh yeah except for the ones from another
but i guess you can't put those on the
tree for some reason or maybe i grab the
wrong ones
oh oh the save
you tina
the mmc please
um let's see i'll put some on the
glowstone that'll look neat
no i forget how hot i heard this oh
there's it there come on
oh
[Music]
okay
one
stop [\h__\h]
doesn't even care about us it's just
it's just chewing
all the more reason to have lots more
cats
this is it
yeah that's good
okay uh hey buddy move dirt for the cake
damn it i brought yellow does this look
okay
oh is that too yellow yeah i can do that
you can do that
okay yeah
nice
membrane what is that oh what does it
make
do you want it i mean you kind of killed
it no it wasn't really me
you did it yeah i don't know what that
is i don't want it sounds gross
[Laughter]
oh you can do that membrane
oh it's used to repair elytras
oh that's useful for later
[Music]
does anyone have an uh elytra yet no
that's an electron we have to we have to
beat the dragon and then
we can fly with those
[Music]
that she got for free but then she
wanted to swim in the lava
oh hey i didn't want to
now listen oh god they're here
they're trying to destroy our tree our
tree
oh no get away from the tree everyone we
lead them away
kill it let's fight we will not do such
a thing
go away i'll try and drag them away oh
can we can we
kill them with snowballs or stuff it's
fine it's almost morning we just need to
keep them destroyed
snowman's fighting oh yeah i was like
what's the flying like
right like round things yeah
missing everything what's this guy doing
he's going the wrong way man the battle
is this way what are you doing over here
thanks guys for helping you nice snowy
dudes
big snowballs put down the base
where we start how many blocks in the
chef
uh start like right right here here's
like where i'm standing one more
yeah do it so that there's like one one
um yeah yeah i had one one white block
on the very edge i think that i'll do
you got it no that doesn't work
do you wanna do you want to come up here
for a second
for what just to see it look at the
thingy
anymore
um
[Music]
i think we need one more here
and then one more here yes
[Music]
yes beautiful oh yeah i see
okay beautiful i have i have these red
these red things here that we can put we
can use them as
as uh as strawberries
a really nice bright strawberry and it's
got dots on it too like a strawberry
yeah
yeah it sure does oh let's use those the
strawberries i'm healthy
are we done with the tree itself it
looks done
christmas cake no i will not burn
everything dude where's the pizza sama
[Laughter]
dude
no danny devito i will not burn our
christmas tree
excuse me
that's the phoenix right exactly
oh i should put the scaffolding closer i
have a little addiction when it comes to
fire
i enjoy a little bit too much techniques
do another cake layer
yes wait past the open in that glass two
layers
i'm curious you guys sure do a lot of
things in this game huh
but they're all blogging with you will
you burn it for 10
no no amount of money you're just going
to be wasting your money deadbeats are
you wasting your money
any more cake look at me ow
hey exactly i thought that
was a chicken leg that i was hitting you
with zach
are you guys hurting each other no we're
playful
we're playful uh having fun it looks
like yeah
we're high-fiving each other yeah yeah
we're being good buddies and good
buddies like to touch each other
every once in a while huh what what
what what's bad about touching what's
battle touching come on
i mean i can't focus somebody's making
the
cake baking station hostile i can't
focus
now we need we need more cream it looks
really good from the dishwasher
i got the i got the i got the whipped
cream
[Music]
what's going on
there's nothing wrong about that oh dude
you burn it down for a scooby snack no
would you do it for two
scooby snacks
she's supposed to make it through yeah
she's concerning
we're good for this job right now oh you
got to do it like a like yeah like a
clock right like
think
i didn't take screenshots again it's
tasty
oh wait f2 f2
ah oh yeah
gotta get some making off photos here
what
i'm leaving this area i even i don't
know if i hurt myself
what the hell what no no photos like
that
what i'm just taking you know off the
progress what the hell
wait do we only have two strawberries
later on
don't you do that to me cuz that's
already there's more
i'll check the thing i should have more
i think
you said making out photos no mapping
[Laughter]
wait this isn't gonna work uh
you gotta improvise yeah i got some more
strawberries honey
we're still one right right here they
really look like strawberries
yummy like huge
wait how do i like we got one for each
member one
should we i know this is not a birthday
cake but should we put candles on top of
the
strawberries oh that's gonna be a good
thing the strawberry looks a little
weird
do you think
[Laughter]
hand holding with kiara what the [\h__\h] is
wrong
what i'm going to cut down this tree any
objections
no put your mind sorry
no christmas kisses no christmas kisses
i put those trees there because i was to
hide anvils at the top so when you guys
cut them down they would fall on you but
it didn't work out
so yeah you can cut the trees that's
horrible that would have been funny
though come on think of the content
for the content yes let
got a very special block i can light on
fire
ooh uh i forgot where i put it though
oh there you go second crib if i made a
second christmas tree and burned that
one down make for a cozy fire
just make a bonfire
[Music]
can i hide inside of the cake yes
like a chicken dinner uh-huh
[Music]
ah it's a soul fire yeah yes
soul fire that sounds interesting i want
to see
hold on it's nice in here
outside the cave
it's like the uh you know when you make
like a marriage proposal and then
you cut the kill with me
it's your it's your it's your
[Music]
don't ask me questions kiss my quote
unquote
fine i don't answer wait why is there
who ate the cake i didn't cut it
what are you talking about
i fixed it i spit it back out and i put
it back on the cake it's fine
a little bit that's that's gonna be your
slice
well you guys are scared of some shark
cooties is that what it is huh
that sounds so weird
what else can we build as christmasy um
what are you doing to my candle there in
the tree
yeah that could be fun if we put one of
these just to put some cats on the tree
like as little decorations that want it
yeah you know you have a ton of cats
right can you go grab some put them on
i know we can do it we can get both
sides of the time
we can go sledding he's sliding
yeah on the on the ice there's an ice
biome at the end of ppp or somewhere
close let's do bumper sliding on ice
someone said we can build a giant candy
cane we can make a skating rink
i have a bunch of ice i can't bring it
hold on i'll go get the ice
skating green we can transform the
fighting ring
into a skating ring
i gotta spend it a
[Music]
oh no yeah kiara will you give me
permission to build a giant chicken on
top of your uh
i mean we can build it together because
that's what i wanted to do anyway
um it was a blueprint for it before oh
yeah oh yeah please
yes i got a lot of will uh wool as well
so mm-hmm let's do it again majestic
yeah majestic chicken i'm gonna make the
ice glue
we gotta make it look like a little bit
like a phoenix so that
my my employees don't misunderstand what
it actually
and what we actually sell but it's laser
chicken
i just realized the christmas tree is
right above my head
right on top of my cave eyes you'll
never lose your way this time
do you still not have a proper home let
me check it out
i mean i worked you can come see some of
it i worked
yeah want to see you next time you're in
your house yet you can come take a look
i still don't have a proper door but you
know oh
still here zombies yeah you don't have
to do you want a door
no i don't know how to make one hold on
oh my god
i got super lucky i picked it up as a
gotcha oh my goodness
oh there's a zombie and then there's a
[\h__\h] in kitchen up here i'm still
working on it but bitching
is this your pet or chemical
[Laughter]
color and they all have colors hot color
colors baby dolls yeah yeah when you
tame them
yeah it got so i have your shade thank
you i have your salmon buddy hold on
let me get it your cave has potential
and cali you're gonna have to light up
this place otherwise you're gonna have a
lot of friends give me one a name
she was told that before but she didn't
believe it i
didn't one i listen i just didn't want
to do it because they told me to do it
listen she doesn't want to be told what
to do she's a rebellious teenager
um
oh i'm getting ice but i already have a
bunch of eyes so i'm just picking it up
and then i'll be back in like
four minutes okay okay ice baby
yes callie i got the perfect door for
you
punching bag really loved that salmon
hot shut up
punching bag listen i don't know how
buttons work in this game
so on occasion when i try to feed my cat
the sam and i end up hitting the cow
with the salmon instead of getting
no i just don't play this planet often
there's only two bubbles to clean the
door now
i do you know
it's a nice color too thank you nice
nice a real door hooray thank you so
much just say it's uh
adorable how's everyone doing
it's raining sharks and squids
oh cool can i fight can i go kill some
more fish i need more food for my kitty
need more employees here
not enough people working at kfb why did
everyone quit their jobs what the hell
oh i think you need to look at yourself
mad in that respect
why did they live by watching are you
looking good i don't know i've heard
some stories
and zombies love me and i have to drink
your
tortured every now and then they'll love
me they will never leave me
was it me or did the zombie not have a
face
that would never leave i think that was
just you because you had a face for me
it was through the back of their head i
couldn't tell
it was looking at me maybe i think
you're going in from the
side of it yeah yeah
look how good this looks it's so good
i have some ink sets oh
i have some anvils nice
your house has a nice tattoo on this
tree and maybe the cats will come to it
do you like it i've been told it's a
finger apparently
it's a very interesting hat yeah maybe
maybe that's how they say hello to each
other
uh where am is from oh where are you
from again
uh the uk is that how they say
[Music]
i will not let them be hurt by a stupid
zombie
what's that
need this one
it's not hello hello hello
okay anyone sing everyone's hairy all
night
oh god hello
hello
kill me i hate it i gotta stop they'll
they're gonna kill me
they're gonna kill me people from the uk
i'm sorry i don't mean any disrespect
you don't do that the aussie
there you go you've got it i got the
cowboy covered though
oh with my silky wall
british people be like subscribe to my
youtube
channel oh my god
i love youtubers
actually bye bye
you guys sound legit
amazing all right anyway how's that ice
coming along honey
oh yeah i'm almost back i'm in the
tunnel on the way back
i have 52 ice wait
maybe we can make a long slide or
something instead
a lot he's got an egg yeah maybe he's
gonna
make us breakfast oh wow i don't want
that that would probably taste really
bad
zombie breakfast
just the side of brains mmm delicious
zombie
no i need i want to see if i can uh oh
this shimmer
house is so cool wait that's
good wow oh
[Music]
i like collecting that
admiring your beauty when the sun is
coming up
you shine even more beautifully than
ever oh my thank you
cutie well we know nothing's as
beautiful as you right
oh okay
where the tree the cake is almost bigger
than the tree though
i think it looks really nice wrong with
thick cake
yeah it's enough for everybody exactly
oh yeah let's probably get rid of this
uh cake he's good
i mean you knew people thank you new
audience
do you see our delicious cake and our
beautiful treat
mmm yummy and where do you guys think we
should build i have all the ice but
where should we put like an ice
maybe an ice slide because if you go
really fast on the boat
52 won't make that big of a square but
now
wait who is building something on the
mountain
from the mountain down down there yeah
nice idea can you go down ice like that
is it so slippery oh you're right ina
it's a cutting board just
oh thank you thank you
[Music]
all right i'll i'll put stairs let's go
up there
okay heading on the spider
what's happening why are you coming
after me
[Music]
oh what is that there's a pig
what
that's way faster we'll just use this
okay spiders have eight legs right
[Music]
okay why else has eight legs
because i called him an eight-legged
freak and i'd like to be correct when i
insult him
all right that's good i wish i didn't
answer that question
i like the view from here nice the tree
looked also nice from here
hi oh yeah
you know oh the tree on top of your
house
looks very weird
something else looks weird
what is it what looks weird huh
[Laughter]
i have the same thing we all have the
same thing all right everybody
man no i'm i'm getting one i'm getting
one and i'm getting
the same mic as several of you
[Music]
somebody do like this side with blocks
like a dirt or concrete on the other
side and then
uh we won't fall off when we when we go
really fast
oh you mean like um i feel like we're
gonna need a little
uh fence to make sure we don't
oh god wait that might be the fun part
who gets the furthest without dying yeah
it's like curling yeah but with bodies
we'll do it over this uh this ditch here
you know so you guys
it's more fun that way they should
probably put make a little pool of water
at the bottom
so we can like wee into it ah
yeah um or maybe it should maybe i
should
it's a it's an icy diving board of death
walk the plank
i'm gonna put a sharp turn here oh
it's like rainbow road
i the leap of faith i'm dropping i'm
dropping a bunch of boats if anybody
wants to pick up a boat
you don't want to like you don't want to
like put us put a
put some stuff on the side so we don't
fall off easily
yeah i'm bringing some dirt now though
but
that's the fun part
[Laughter]
wait i'm gonna put away my diamonds
somewhere
i brought
off i'll get some water yeah
i'll make some what
i like blue yeah your color is better
glue is very nice good choice we're
gonna make this longer or will it end
there
i don't have any more ice cream
apparently there's no fault in it
oh so we can't we can do it without the
walnut whoever falls off first is a
loser
whoever falls off versus a stinky
stinker stinkerton
mm-hmm i don't give a ride oh
[Music]
oh really i just found out
what i don't like the curve here the
curve kind of slows down
anything i'm going to leave this boat i
don't want it anymore
[Music]
no more scaffolding all right wait
more more more more it's actually kind
of fun
unfortunately your boy actually has to
dip out
i thought it would only be an hour 30
minutes for this okay okay that's fine
like uh like straight so we can go zoom
in and just fly oh
awesome nevermind if it was here i was
gonna
accidentally break the ice block that
she was standing on top
don't worry about it okay let's go uh
take a picture yeah screenshot
screenshot time
okay all of us are here we go down to
the tree
yes this is and we have the tree and the
cake on the
picture oh we can probably find an angle
we can do
that i'm coming
i'll go too hold on hi picture time
picture time yay time to take chelsea
oh it looks kind of prettier during the
night should we wait until it's night
oh i think it's on the setting right now
isn't it yeah he's staying with me like
a minute yeah let's go on top of here
it won't get both on it but let's at
least cut the tree and we can get two
yeah
f5 f5 there you go
f5 is the change thing
you can yeah yeah to get rid of the uh
hud you want to take off your
your uh uh that's my equipment good idea
ready oops
i'm here i'm coming
oh you dropped it should i what should i
do go get it
no if you want just get it it's fine
no worries hello oh it's all dead four
oh how could i have forgotten
maybe we can all uh crouch
how do you crouch shift
yes yes yeah
cool crouching in front of the christmas
tree it's perfect
and maybe one more should maybe one more
person should be uh
hold on let me go shorty's in the front
wait that's so confusing
all right down you go girl okay wait
wait wait wait
okay okay oh it's perfect right now
it's like not too dark
[Music]
how can i get rid of the ui f1
oh you know do you want to crouch again
what's the screenshot again f3 up two
enough room for both of you up here
do we want to be on the cake
oh it's so easy let's just sit here
sounds good ready
[Laughter]
[Music]
yay
[Applause]
you guys have fun okay enjoy the rest of
your time together
[Music]
i think we're all on the end yeah
i would suggest that we leave the
christmas tree forever
yeah i always keep it till next
christmas
[Music]
happy holidays
oh no they're killing me they're killing
[Music]
them
happy holidays goodbye
you