[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
no
la
[Music]
oh ah
K yeah yeah under five minute loading
screen take that stupid stupid game
capture card everything worked uh in
German we say of unhe just like that
today everything just work like that
just like that okay not first try I had
to open the program twice but I didn't
have to restart my PC
so that's
[Music]
amazing flag
them my flum I should be selling it
[Laughter]
[Music]
new highlight ah yeah the
Highlight oh somebody in the chat during
the loading screen wrote oh never heard
this bgm before I guess I'm a I'm a
casual or something like that don't
worry about it first of all uh even if
you are doesn't matter thank you for
being here and at the same time
the bgm I used it yesterday as the
loading screen bgm for the first time
today the second time and it's not
really my loading screen bgm I just kind
of all the loading screen bgms that I
had in the OBS I think I recently like
cleaned up my data that I have had in
the download
folder um and moved it over to like
resources and whatever I have a resource
follow and uh now it's like you
know now it's it doesn't work anymore in
OBS because it's like hey hey this file
isn't where it should
be and then I was scrambling like uh
what else do I use yesterday just
like uh at the moment really stressed
out so I just threw that one in I
thought everybody likes Jazz like can't
go wrong with
jazz what happened with the one where
you tap your shoes oh that one that one
I used as an end ending screen sometimes
I still have that somewhere like you
know all these things are somewhere but
today I finally in detail uh typed out
what I want for a new loading screen and
ending screen to the person I am it's
not clean no probably not to your
standards I just I cleaned my my
download folder excuse me not
OBS my OBS is clean enough
you guys have no idea these things are
necessary they're all necessary but yeah
uh I don't know how long it will take
because uh it might be a pretty
intricate um piece that I
[Music]
commission
yeah response is a pretty big tail hey
shut sh up usual room is still existing
I can still send you there
mhm looking forward to it yeah yeah I
saw something like on my Twitter
timeline a while ago before my break and
I was like oh I want a loading screen
like
that yeah yeah yeah okay now I have
green tea
antioxidative whatever that means and
and I have a nandom
Paca for my throat one cup of that and a
big jug of green tea hot in my
Theros
antioxidative what does that do how
how's that help me tell me what does
that do does that get like the sickness
out of my
body tell me tell me I don't want to
Google it removes free radicals what
they're good for my immune system uhhuh
prevents cells from aging I need to
drink more
more help more green tea they're good
for my immune system okay but what about
my cells what about my aging cells
that's a
myth well I am a myth
myself
oh I have to learn Korean
again oh my God help Lord save
me not a myth it helps protect cells
let's go wo wao you know that anime with
the
cells I didn't watch it I'm just I'm
just bringing it up randomly I'm just
bringing it up cuz you guys like it when
I know
anime and I don't I don't know
much yeah celles at work yeah yeah yeah
yeah was so cute when that was popular
there were so many sales at work
cosplayers out in out and about in Japan
too wait wait CH what's going on oh oh
okay
okay then today is another day of long
stream are you guys ready are you
guys ready for a long stream do you have
snacks do you have something to drink
did you go to the idol
meeting are you strapped in yeah do you
have maybe a blanket maybe your cats or
your dog over
around yes okay checklist do you have uh
if you're on your phone do you have it
charged or do you need to charge it now
if you're on your
PC um I don't
know is is uh is is your internet
connection stable actually I'm curious I
want to I want to I mean I actually I
most likely have an analytics for this
I'm going to ask you guys anyway I make
a poll let's make a poll an a polling
pole
what's your way of watching
Wawa PC ah uh tablet or t
TV or phone I don't know if there's
another popular
option no right now I mean right now
today what what is your choice
today oh
wow I feel like maybe va va va Watchers
might choose different devices cuz for
me like I feel like I
watch like you know BS a lot on my
tablet uh in the kitchen when I'm eating
breakfast or dinner okay I don't really
watch BS generally I'm not a stream
Watcher but generally like yeah I guess
B just any
videos v such a funny word
[Music]
v
I think I think the TV gang is
like is more powerful than you think TV
gang is
like TV gang is adult and appreciates
high quality
and is
maybe
maybe rich or one day will be
rich
and I
am I am I am
illusioned TV can vote on a poll oh yeah
well you okay so what I do often when I
want to participate in the chat I open
it on my phone while watching on the TV
so I have the stream open with two
devices there was a Japanese bro who
said he's watching right now on the TV
same same same yeah I mean how else are
you going to do it I don't think there's
any option to
comment that's what you got to do if you
got to do the do then you got to do it
like
that that's exactly what I do oh my God
yeah I mean everybody's like saying like
oh my God we're so the same but it's
like what else would you do that's
that's the only
way it's just because cuz there's no
other
choice what
else yeah yeah you can you can just uh
um I used to do this but somehow I
[\h__\h] up something so now it doesn't
connect anymore but uh I rather than
going on YouTube on the smart TV and
then typing stuff in because I'm not
logged in and I'm I'm too lazy to log
myself in on the TV on my YouTube
account I get ads and like [\h__\h] and all
that so what I do is I go on the phone I
choose the video I want to watch and
then I remote I play it on the TV
through the phone right yeah the casting
from the phone now I can't do it anymore
because somehow somehow it's not even
though I'm in the same internet Network
now it's not working ever since I got
the internet working now that is not
working yeah but then you have it
running and then you can comment on your
phone comfy while lying down wow high
tech we've come so far with Humanity
we've come so
[Music]
far humanity is amazing every now and
then you have to remind yourself of
amazing Humanity we are amazing
man 100 years ago who would have thought
who would have thought that there would
be vtubers that there would be like face
recogn
izing
stuff on iPhones and [\h__\h] and now who
would the f [\h__\h] AI is taking over
and cloning everything to the point that
you have to be worried about people
making videos of
you uh
anyway so what are we going to be able
to do in 100 years huh that's an
interesting conversation maybe we should
do a whole stream about that putting on
our tin foil hats and discussing what
could be in 100
years that might be interesting I mean
we're not going to be alive
but
but it's still it's still close enough
to think about
it we might not be alive but that that
stream will most likely still be
watchable in 100 years do you think
YouTube will still be thing in 100
years there's certain websites that just
survive forever and ever and ever and
ever and ever and I think YouTube is one
of those Twitter will be [\h__\h]
dead sad to say Twitter's already kind
of
dead my cousin the
bluebird it's my cousin by the way I
didn't I never told
you extended family yeah
yeah uh
anyway enough of
that where are we what are we
doing what what was I doing where where
did we we just got our jobs and then I
was told I should give everybody jobs
because they'll get the skills and this
and that uh do I ask this thing IO
happy and um so K doesn't have a job
right now let's give him aquanut oh
especially cuz he looks freaking dope
with that blonde hair again he So Fresh
So
Young this
one
happy and wait do they they need
different weapons for that right I do
have some stuff I think and then we're
going to like fight a few like random
red enemies to get our class up I think
it levels really fast wooden board oh
they wait they got it
automatically do they get it like as a
free
present H okay grass cut I don't have
anything
better ah the one I have another wooden
board that's better and oh no oh it's
the one that c go ah [\h__\h] didn't I sell
one I had two and I think I sold
one a damn it cuz I thought oh who needs
that that's
trash Oh armored chicken oh my God
congratulations you did it thank you for
staying with the Wabble for so
long uh oh well okay let's let's get
uh let's fight some
people
I don't have what if I have what what am
I supposed to do it's not going to stay
like this forever it's just like you
know blue what was it blue you guys told
me like go up to the blue
ones what L2 smack what does that
mean oh wait L2
[\h__\h] why the [\h__\h] did you ah cuz it's
automatic now I should have pressed it
earlier right you [\h__\h]
[Music]
a who what the [\h__\h] flipper to the
Lipper cring colid trippy flippy
Ripper flipper to the Ripper treat a
hoad to a visit to the surf and the
taste of
rubber he's also a surfer maybe we can
learn some stuff from
him show
me
wow he even got the
he even got the feet thingies
o wait oh his skills fire spinning
ancient Paka bewitching Hast and Soul
Capture enemy
area let's try the fire spinning anyone
who's sensitive no look
at she's just constantly dancing wow
wow she's so into it
she's giving it her best 24/7 look look
at her look at her oh she has so many
variations oh [\h__\h] I only got two the
first time I saw it but that's good
damage
wow wow wait did we start the class on
level Z on level
one
oh not going to be alive in 100 years
makes me grateful I'm alive in able to
joy YouTube and meters as such as
yourself for real like it's such a deep
thought to think like damn if you
weren't born at this time you wouldn't
experience any of these things but you
would surely experience other cool
things but you
know living in this time of like
internet and all that you get to meet so
many more people that otherwise maybe
you wouldn't be
meeting because okay like before
internet yeah people interacted more IRL
but you it wasn't so easy to meet people
people from all over the
world from Over the
globe the people you could potentially
meet were definitely like much less you
know now the world is open to you so
many possibilities
y okay
look at those Pokemon
goers damn Pokemon go in Hawaii must
have been
great okay
L2 I press it so
fast it's
happening is that just a really fast way
of leveling cuz they're too low
levels only ranked
two even level fast as they
f for 70% of the EXP uhhuh so it's just
like a strength test you only attack
once and if you're the stronger one then
it's like immediately winning I
guess yeah yeah oh cute can I jump in on
wait can I I
can ah cute they arve it stops
periodically and you wait at one to pass
time until it appears once the board had
to the exit door was stopped to
disembark you can also talk to the
driver to get the
next n I'm good actually but that's so
cute that you can
enter would be cool if you could like
seamlessly just walk in on the
stairs or maybe you can and I just got
the prompt cuz it was the first
time Su want snap ah what what
n Shake Shake Shake give me those
pineapples it's all coconut I don't like
coconuts
coconut I like to cook with coconut oil
though
sometimes going to cry no was going to
have a conversation
withy all
right oh I right I didn't see her skills
yet hululu hips a tropical hip drop
which deals magic damage to an enemy and
may low lower their willpower coconut
shower sprinkle of coconut water uhuh k
kick kick any
kick kick is better strikes an enemy
with magic damage applying your weapons
attributes May boost your evasion and
harmonious
hoola and nearby allies magic with the
traditional
dance
cute I mean we could just not use skills
but I just want to see
them
oh the flowers are so
pretty he
lik
hi
Edward friends friendship he wants his
own coffee shop oh I think you can do
that totally for over your
[Music]
C I love how he said that so
motivated so at what point what level
should my rank be so that I actually get
to inherit the skills flooring mob oh oh
isn't there a cleaning job a ma job I
think Al
oh this this one's interesting they're
protecting a chest let's go yeah there's
a m
right when I was when I was looking for
like materials to use for the thumbnails
I saw like some jobs going
Cy damn dude SW
swad
oh wait these are nah these are also
weak these are
weak
[\h__\h] from the bond level not drop
R continue to C
what flipper to the Lipper or CR and
collider let's do CR and collider like
this surf
time noise the wave wave was amazing it
almost ate me up but I fought it I
fought it with no
mercy the wave is
mine I feel
it okay why are you walking like a
goblin by the way
Tommy the wobbly wave oh no oh he's weak
to fire let's
go
but he didn't die the person behind him
died from it what okay I guess he's like
the boss
here whoa honestly those weights that
you're carrying the way that you're
moving them it looks like they're just
plastic like no
weight no weight in it I don't believe
it I don't believe
it look at him look at
him wow
what are
those those
Springs what is your outfit supposed to
do let's just do a normal
one hey
rude that poor hola lady what what why
would you do that to
her red Super Chat thank you T attack
employing infinite copies of myself for
maintenance of the infinite copies of
the usual room for seeds what are you
talking about we've encountered Taco
dges in the void they claim they are
containing aan we will monitor them as
well glory to
kfp were you always such a
lper thank you for the re
chance Mah m
but you trying your best to
protect glory to
KF I respect that I appreciate that
you're you're a
hero a health booster okay kind of
random not even even a weapon or
accessory there is supposed to force you
to use the strength to be able to do
even simple movements
ah no I'm not going to get into
that that's too
much look let me go h oh wait I got I
got a message from a
girl that's not in whole
[Music]
life girl just told me it's her
birthday
she wants she wants me to congratulate
her damn it damn it it's not so hot
anymore should have drunken it earlier
drunken
drunk autum
burglar cute
name kicking your
butt woo woohoo
Kirkwood that's his name
Kirkwood not very Hawaiian of you you
tourist eh are you [\h__\h] tourist
you're tourist and you're you're
stealing cars you suck you lost in
life what you're so
threatening you're always so threatening
you always the first to post the
threatening Emoji have you
noticed oh m oh that's a photo spot took
about the hell was I supposed to do that
go to
to
uh not sure what the button
was
uh
[Music]
dead no surf no life
okay nice I found the
spot what's our actual next goal right
now guys what do it
say almost time to meet with colum I'll
head over to Aloha Beach for the track a
the trash clean
up guys let me clean trash please check
the trash get proper jobs and what do
you mean proper jobs
what you mean our original
job
[Music]
what aquan not optimal okay well we can
bring K back to his OG
job
can you unlock any more jobs H probably
could yeah Mr Min winner it's him again
your bond levels aren't high enough for
many
inheritance okay hope we see y today I
thought we were done with him so I can't
promise unless you know something that I
don't yeah I need more
money
[Music]
no
[\h__\h] makes me so mad when they hit
me her movement is just the
best look at
her look at her [\h__\h]
go why
for speaking like a Japanese
uh what
call what do you call a what was that
wait no what what what do you call
talking like
this like
this help me out here please what are
you yeah Valley Girl Japanese valy girl
be
like it's like kind of like G
yeah not necessarily but
[Music]
yeah I just love running around and
picking up items everywhere
I could do that all
day it's like a
yak yeah yeah yeah
yeah now you may be wondering what is
that W what is
wow wow if only you studied German
properly we've been together for 3 and a
half years guys how come you have not
learned my language yet are you not
dedicated to our
relationship you don't care how as long
as I speak
English that's good enough for you huh
that I make the effort that I put the
effort in to our
relationship it's always me right you
never want to give me the opportunity to
speak my my mother tongue so I can feel
comfortable you know you know I would
sound much more intelligent if I could
speak my my mother
tongue yeah this whole time I have to
accept the fact that I sound and seem
stupid why I'm not I'm
not we could be so much more connected
if you tried a little
bit just
[Laughter]
kidding play along
guys the [\h__\h] wait the [\h__\h] are
you probably got fired from his Alo
happy job uh-oh coconut job coconut
coconut
job all right he's a special
monster you never encountered him did
you shake the trees did
you does K get it
too I can't see yeah everybody got it
no I'm not drunk it's uh currently not
tired that's that's what a not tired wa
sounds
like damage is an enemy with a Chance of
reducing your attack or defense he heavy
power
heavy
[\h__\h] I missed but his defense is
lower o flip it to the lip I he resist
it
how dare you
[Music]
SC kind of late alexanda what's wrong
what were you
doing
blinding so damage enemy absorbs HP
applying your weapons absorbs so he gets
it absorbing HP
skill yes
oh those are the best
skills life steal life steal let's
go oh my
god Tommy needs it he needs
it this coconut three oh my God it's so
funny it's so funny
that's the normal
attack almost
dead he's a bit
silly honestly I can imagine um some FR
[\h__\h] spring break
dude a
bro
uh dressing up like
this I I can totally see
it membership still going strong thank
you are T I need to commission you
H we need to keep you alive was Callie
not paying you enough do I need to have
a talk of
cie I'll have a talk with Callie
we can't lose
you turmeric tablets
taet Spin to
Win oh
sua oh my
God there's fed
banners but what the [\h__\h] they cost
5,000 per pole oh the this is 100
Pur I don't know if I how much money do
I
have 1,000 I don't have the money for
this right
now I need to save oh Toco I have
something for
[Music]
you bow B his name is
bow you had your a sh oh yeah they're
they're they can be pretty
good interesting kind of sweet uh
pastry you looking for a beating oh yeah
yeah I'm looking for a beating your face
PES I'm looking to beat you beat your
[Music]
ass oh yeah speaking of B bow
I I heard they announced that they're
moving to
Japan I get it like I used to
be really like man living in Japan is
the
dream Japan is the
goal what the that lady is getting
pushed now it's like you know I still
like being in Japan I
still
[Music]
um I still feel like living in Japan
would probably give me more
opportunities and
possibilities and make it easier to
bond with Japanese members and off
collabs and this and that so I do feel
like
yeah it'll probably be good for me too
but at the same time I'm happy where I
am
and I I can't even if I wanted even if I
was like okay I I can't I can't take the
fomo anymore I need to move to to Japan
I don't really have that option now
anymore and I've lived in Japan at the
beginning of my whole
lifetime and man I I wish we could have
already gotten 3D back
then but in the end it it was of no use
to me to be in
Japan didn't even meet that many people
that many whole life members I I met way
more on the trips that I go on every now
and then than I did in that half year of
living in Japan while being in
Holo
faster every year yeah so what let me
repeat some some stories let me repeat
some topics especially right now it's on
topic what are you staring at a FAL gold
and I wish them the best of luck I know
that you know they've lived in Japan
before and that
they they
are very excited to live there
again yeah but so many members are
moving
there and yeah seeing so many members
move over it does give me huge
fomo but I'm going to stay
strong and uh try my best where I
am yeah
well I'm counting Iris and Callie as
well who are already there and
I I may have heard that there's
possibilities of maybe some
more people maybe
maybe
yeah H maybe I don't know
I don't know nothing certain but like
yeah girls are interested and it's like
uh being in h life makes it easy now cuz
they provide a Visa and like it's a it's
a rare chance and you know I lived in
Japan I experienced it but people who
haven't then for them it's like oh my
[\h__\h] god let's go that's a chance
that you don't want to say no
to like for me for me it's like like
okay I experienced it all I've been
there done that
I I I love I love Japan still but uh I
have
built a family with my cats
here
so I'm staying where I
am
for babies first yeah it's not just that
just like even if it wasn't for the cats
if it wasn't for the cats I would
probably move there I guess for the time
that I'm working here but it's not like
I really feel a big desire to be there
just for the sake of being in Japan it
would really be for this just for the
job
but I don't know it's
like I think I just feel comfortable in
my own country right
now
yeah yeah the flying flying around so
much is yeah it's
annoying but
oh I don't know um I I I I want to tell
myself I'm fine where I am I I I'm
pretty convinced I'm fine where I am I'm
I'm happy I'm comfortable my my family
can see me here I can see
them I'm not like a a huge family person
uh I don't like go out of my way to see
my family like every week or so no not
at all uh we're all kind of like doing
our own
thing um but yeah still like you
know but I would be lying if if I said I
wasn't concerned
about you know maybe not getting
official program 3D opportunities or
like not bonding with members as much or
whatever but it's okay whenever I fly to
Japan and that's many times times a year
I'll I'll as always do as many off
collabs and stuff as possible that's a
legit concern right and I brought it up
and I was kind of told like that's
that's not like they don't choose by who
is in Japan when it comes to bringing in
whole life English
members
um so that shouldn't be my
concern like I I shouldn't be worried
about it I was told so but like still
I'm like n I don't know about
that we'll see about
[Music]
it yeah and then I said maybe maybe just
to make the studio people aware if
they're planning these programs maybe
the people who don't live in Japan
should just like uh if they have a plan
to go to Japan anytime soon uh we should
like report it to them so that they know
oh hey this person is coming to Japan
maybe we can plan them into one of our
our programs because they don't get you
know the chance to be in these often so
when they're here for once you know
let's have an eye out for that and and
involve them I said like I would like to
you know make them aware of these
things yeah
yeah hi drama clip Watchers oh no oh
no oh
no yeah it is it is what it is in the
end it's my choice and uh
um yeah I'm all alone here in
Europe I'm all
alone but but I have my Monopoly I rule
this place this is Wawa's area this is
the Wawa
[Music]
Zone one day K it's okay I'm back in
Japan soon uh for a little
trip for Fest and and I can interact
with people
[Music]
then W need more life in
EU
yeah there you step into the woward Zone
please come visit the wow
Zone come here you have us European
Watchers thank you queen of EU queen of
EU you that's
me I am the the co coin the queen
we love to have you here in e thank you
so much I appreciate that anyway this
woman what do you
want side quest huh oh it's about the
trash that you have did you find it in
the
ocean uh yeah I guess I did I figured
I'd throw it away instead of leaving it
is that a
problem no no that's fantastic you're
great really awesome well done afro
calling someone by their
hairstyle I guess it's like calling
someone Blondie
but that's weird calling someone Blondie
is weird too unless I don't know maybe
you're really good good good good
friends but if it's like a stranger I
think it's
weird so so sorry what's going on here
I'm just saying throwing away trash in
trash cans is great but there's an even
more wonderful spot to bring any you
find
what's that hey
ponytail hey
uh what do you call the the hairstyle
that's like spiky like your sides are
shaved but the top is like a
spiky spiky
thing a mohawk yeah hey
Mohawk me what you want me to throw the
trash at
you my name's yokoo
no I'm researching environmental issues
to help keep the ocean clean I'm from
Japan originally but I came to Hawaii on
a study
abroad and as me that's admirable while
going but what does that have to do with
picking up trash are you just trying to
clean up the ocean piece by piece not
exactly see I'm trying to solve this
issue with a different approach I'm
working with several different
manufacturers to recycle any trash that
washes up here and turn it into
something
nice and for that I need tons of tach to
use as samples thing is the other day I
slipped on an inconveniently placed SE
kill Comber and twisted my leg I can't
do much trash recovery
now I get it so you want me to give you
the trash now there's a smart trash
cookie of course I won't ask you to give
me anything for free although I haven't
got much money P
h i I guess I'd give it to you for free
even though I could sell it in the
store I de I'd like to implement some
kind of like um point system to
encourage more people to have fun
picking up
trash trash like you did I say that yet
no right don't please can't I persuade
you to give me a hand supplying me with
garbage like garbage like
you m okay what you mean by point system
I could award you points for trash and
you could exchange them for items I've
recycled from the trash how about that
huh it's like a beautiful circle of
trash wow amazing I've got some pretty
stuff sweet stuff so that's not such a
bad deal for you right my research
progress the ocean gets cleaner and you
receive press it's a win-win win
system
genius look at that
okay hooray may this be a wonderfully
trashy adventure for us both afro I keep
on calling you D if that's okay cuz
that's all I see when I look at
you mhm okay cans spicy BS magazines
glass bottles
okay well done it's not a mini game
right it's
just
coconuts a
watermelon sorry hello
sorry
uh wait this
way do I want to know wait isn't this
the quest people anyway what are what
the what maybe they're Ault after
all
uh
okay okay
[Music]
okay the
Sun
[Music]
o
for are you you're
still 39 months that's
[Music]
cool
pineapple
pineapple Apple
p
[Music]
for ah
for
[Music]
spee if we ever find
her
yes let's do
it oh oh we didn't even have to do
anything I thought I would actually be
picking up
trash nice nice as if the Honolulu Beach
would be ever this empty especially at
this time when it's so
beautiful as
if
no it's also way dirty now yeah cuz they
don't have each CLE cleaning it
up so
[Music]
fore
I get that but like he's been for some
[\h__\h] so it's not easy to be ichan
[Music]
either
fore
[Music]
a
for no no no when he proposed it sounds
[Music]
different
Doe
[Music]
she crashing on
him
maybe not really crushing but like
thinking like damn he's a great
guy and
like not like a love interest but
like hard you say I I feel like she has
like um not a crush but like this
feeling of it would be great if I
had a relationship with this guy but
it's still not really she doesn't see it
as a possibility
[Music]
maybe because she loves Tommy
zawa not add me RAC NE hry crab hry crab
Bonk B
C
for maybe the dog
knows
[Music]
fore
yeah she is always like
this
Al let me just pour
some
okay I'm so
weak and some
honey you need a hand no not
anymore wait I can't I want to open this
bottle of Honey
normally
this this this um f Lo sucks it's
terrible all right I have a scissor here
[Music]
nice okay finally I was able to yawn
fully let's go what the [\h__\h]
what the
[\h__\h]
ouch here we go it's honey time
oh I was like damn nothing's coming out
it's like barely and then suddenly bam a
huge chunk of
Honey flew out all right
okay honey honey honey
[Music]
can you put it in the fridge no I never
put honey in the
fridge all
right
oh
rainbow guys you have no idea about the
hermit cra drama out
there the Shell's probably a rent
say what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about yeah you guys told me
to I guess before I go deeper I should
um change K's class
again but what about the others I can
keep that
way that was a lot of b m
rank
five oh I can catch
him n don't want he's weak his OG class
is the best for k for everybody you
mean you're in for a
world keep it until you get the
[Music]
other month
what I don't know what you mean but send
me that then I'll then I'll maybe
understand other characters you can run
make it work don't
you
okay glasses are mostly preference I
think I finished this game and never
changed OG classes yeah but that's like
like kind of a waste the classes are
so cute and fun and
quirky I feel
like trying some out
definitely is a good idea yeah you can
also just go with the OG that you're
probably going to
be fine and
Powerful yeah I mean look at these
outfits look what you're missing out
on give it your
best
[Music]
yeah keep it in
mind oh did you see
it did anyone watch sub senpai's
birthday live
today oh not birthday uh uh
anniversary what are you looking at not
yet really pissing me
off Senpai wrote to me like two days
ago I think two days ago
like can you can you record a little
video for me that says
like so I'm like Yeah by any
chance did you did you realize that you
need to stall and fill some time and she
was she was like yeah and I'm like oh
yeah don't worry like I feel like a lot
of members are having this uh problem
recently somehow all the lives these
days end up being like 45 minutes or so
and it's not not
because like we have like I had 2 days
of studio time I recorded so many
songs but I feel like in hindsight uh
maybe I should have like postered it up
with a bit more uh MC's maybe I don't
know what are you looking at
yeah it's uh an interesting phenomenon
right now cuz I don't think we are
performing generally less songs than
before when it hits 1 hour more
often I think it's
just one
song recording dude it's like it's I in
those two days of recording I recorded I
mean I also recorded members only
content me only like
oncore if I would have added that to the
main part yeah it would have been an
hour I guess yeah
but yeah even with what I did record for
an hour like it's not less songs than
usual yeah I don't know man more MC's is
my the lesson that I learn for next time
anyway here's a
chicken sasam
me chicken I give you bird food you're
welcome come back to
KFC soon okay I'm waiting for
you sweet
chin
a
a a show
how you
doing he's on vacation that's
unrealistic K he doesn't get
vacation he must be working in the
Hawaii
branch is the bridge far am I stupid for
running there no isn't it right over
therey
so much rainstorms oh
damn why why all the tropical places
have so many
rainstorms
well you
you have to work somebody's got to
work to his
talk why are you interrupting us
rude that's what you
get yeah thank
you I like music but Music Festival I
don't like that atmosphere drunk people
and high
people young people they
scary really scary
SC I mean some can be chill too but I I
don't
[Music]
know oh you need
help we help
hi
dance wait I just passed them all I
could change my class St again right
[Music]
yeah they're at different
locations
the only one I know though is in the
mall the only one I'm aware
of I wi CH
I okay I guess I'll change cu's
claw as you guys told me to Dr
food uh wait that's a mall
no no
that's the mall and that's the Aloha
brid ah damn
it
then although let's see this is the this
is the mark for that is there one over
here no ah there's one
here in there I should be able to change
my
job what are you looking at we can give
him a different job once you've unlocked
more Hawai drivers
crazy you want to fight just go what
what do you mean what I'm I was going to
pick up an item is she behind the
tree reward 30
bucks
uh should
I reserve
members wait he's level 10 took them up
there
the colors the colors matter right so
I'll I'll keep
um these in the
reserve so we don't have two
blue well on yeah let's do it
on where is this
person
oh should be easy they're level
five
oh
mhm you got this i got
this
K one
down uh so are they going to bring in
their Reserve no yes sir he's becoming a
ball friend shaped very friend
[Music]
shaped the the dark was that good I'm
not sure or is that just because he's
his element so to say dark is bad oh
okay let's do this
one that seemed a bit better yeah type
disadvantage I
guess it doesn't seem like they're
bringing in the
reserve why
[Music]
not friend yeah like
you not quite perfectly round but uh
pretty
[Music]
round ooh he joined the
team nice of him you're the worst I had
no chance against you so where the [\h__\h]
were
you I just wanted to pick that
up
okay no no no no no no your
hand okay I was where the [\h__\h] was I
going hey my route is
gone I'm going to get
lost hi hey does do you always need the
food I only have one left I want to get
to know more chickens that I don't know
yet so I'll keep it for another
[Music]
one you had food
already what are you looking at time to
teach you a lesson I herbs too yeah I
guess so but the herbs the herbs
actually that um tea that we made out of
it it's pretty amazing
so besties let's go
Roberto you
too you too come on did that already do
it so and oh you guys said also I should
upgrade my gear is that really urgent
you
think need to find the the girl Julie
again I even remember her name though
wow not
really this might be the
best can I not inherit anything
now
uh ahuh
okay check new
[Music]
jobs
huh oh done done
done which ones are new uh you mean
there's actually new
ones or just means something I didn't do
yet Keo had the first one available
oh I can do par
sailing
um I could do dutyfree
shopping Tomy and Keo both have a SL
okay maybe maybe par
sailing
sorry wait oh I lacked the
personality
oh
[Music]
oh okay then I did everything I I could
do I think
yeah too
bad okay ah you does have something no
wait wait wait wait what what what what
I don't get
it I don't get it how does this
work do I have to
changed her class back to
normal wait here this one works this
one's locked I think it this one is
locked tell me is how it works
though you can keep the current class
and then take one of these with
him or all of
them ah one per Bond level
which one should I
do I
[Music]
like I like all of
these Tire
tumbler
[Music]
sure
okay oh
[Music]
okay did he take the gear again that I
gave him originally I mean I guess he's
just barehanded is he really going to be
barehanded this whole
time any better
hats
uh
okay
then I will
go to the
bridge saes you from having to upgr
weapons yeah I
guess
okay going to Aloha Bridge a
I did I did play on
[Music]
zero I guess he was using his fists back
then too but you
know could at least have like like these
what do you call them brass
knuckles something like
that what are you looking at
Get
[Music]
Wrecked weon would do less damage I
guess it it must at least mean that his
basic attacks are
boosted
for the fact that he can't
use uh weapons that boost his attack
normally hi hiy what's up everybody
loves me woo
sometimes it doesn't
work
now need to position yourself
better here we
are or oh maybe maybe I can buy
something should I buy something Al do I
need
[Music]
something
nah thank
you you would have ignored him to I was
looking at that
direction I would say so I would claim
so
oh are you
Romero yeah take it your kasuga col told
me all about you he said you were
helping with the TR that's the plan
anything specific you like us to do well
we've got a pretty big area to cover so
we should split uh into grips how about
you and your team Patrol along the river
we'll take care of the other
spots okay River sounds good anything we
need to watch out
for we should probably know about the
Labyrinth the Labyrinth well like a
dungeon oh it's a it's a building though
was never finished lands fell through
during construction and it's been
abandoned ever since well I say
abandoned but actually a bunch of crazy
people started living there sometimes
you even hear about locals walking by
and going missing so I'd still clear if
I were you
uhoh of course we're going
in for sure better not take any risks
anyway after we're done with Patrol
let's meet up back here I'll see you
soon so we got a labyrinths filled with
crazies here in Hawaii better stay on
alert while we're in Portal it sounds
sounds
Exquisite uh over there
okay then get rid of this how do
I uh there we
go they really just look like groups
that came together to play Pokmon
go
o
chest give me something
good okay I'll take it
[Music]
oh perent
prominent they're
prominent not was in
[Music]
battle
for
T A Sinner's height there in he talks
nicely
is he
British Fowler details I know not for I
am Mia Watchman take heed of my
warnings
what
Sav is a great place to farm and
grind a dollar for
my
yeah
$1 yeah you get exactly $1 cuz that's
what you asked
for so matter you are just the game
character but
sure oh it reminds me of that place from
like a dragon one I
think is the perfect word for it it's
like a video game
dungeon someone help me who's there came
from up ahead let's
go yeah like the there was like yeah the
battle
tower this is like a labyrinth version
of that dungeon diving dungeons are
Lawless zones what Lawless zones r with
adversaries their layouts change every
time you enter and Dennison grow
stronger as you progress okay it's like
that losing a balance at a dungeon will
transport you back to its entrance mhm
mhm within the dungeons you might
stumble upon some innocent missing
persons who are stuck in dangerous
situations be sure to lend a helping
hand if you happen to find them you'll
be able to gather a number of unique
items as you explore in fact some of
these items can be only found within so
it pays to be thorough yeah I know how
to pronounce that let's go deliver these
to recipients waiting back at the
entrance for helpful Rewards
okay guess we got to go where we found
the scream or where we heard the
[Music]
scream hey you
there I have no mp on
ichan oh yeah so wait these are
permanent you
say
the musle increases
attack give it to myself ich gotab be
ichan and the
defense oh and then yeah ah the this is
good this is
good let's give it to the ones who got
some new
classes that I probably want
them
okay technical manual that increases
your job as a geod Dancer by one geod
danc is so
specific
y okay and MP
and that's
[Music]
HP you can avoid enemies if you Circle
them
oh this will be a good it's okay we can
fight
ooh that's new
Shaman shamman Shan sham
sh they look
nice and they got pineapples around here
must be good people with good
taste slipper to the
lier [\h__\h]
kick him while he's
down are you
scared good he got his pineapple
Colors oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
damn
okay yes yes sh is German for
black so there you did your German reps
so proud of you oh we can go this way or
that way
[Music]
oh oh the other way has a ladder on the
map so maybe that would go
up [\h__\h] it's really a maze I don't like
it no
what's in
[Music]
here oh okay dead end no not a dead end
it connects
oh power tool and pest
uncontrol oh he spreads the pest that's
new
or he
is ah [\h__\h] I should have chosen the one
in the back damn I'm so
[Music]
stupid Lord
small
hey how are you not dead no not the
chainsaw oh I guard it it's always
protecting K it's my number one
priority he's
resisting although he does
look you do be looking
cold
nice nice
[Music]
nice yes okay so that connects to here
okay and then I want to also see what's
over there it feels like that could be a
dead
end it is
not it is it is it is it is not what is
this cool
place maybe there is no dead end maybe
all paths are
connected oh no hey it's a dead
end nothing in here not even an item
[Music]
H H okay
that's not very
nice not very
motivating uh right this
way
uhhuh this dead end has got some
stuff Robo disc time 20 wait I should
have read what that is now I have no no
idea
okay Cola zero Coca-Cola zero let's
go proceed to next
FL you get more okay oh floppy disc that
someone dropped can be exchanged for
rewards ah okay okay oh no oh no a
floppy disc I don't know how to use it
oh
no
M
uhhuh the middle part where the flag was
probably has um safe point
and uh healing spot I would
assume oh what's the matter oh
hi oh hi oh hi did you see movies you oh
this so like every movement outfit it's
just a banger like her sense
and her artist's way of recreating her
ideas and putting them into
art oh it's just so
perfect a so
cute the messy twin
Tails okay stop moving
now
I should have chosen the other one as a
tget
May yeah fun is
next new outfit hi
P oh he went all in on him interesting
who turned out the
light
are you scared new Alit always
have mine's still going to take a
while those moonman fall outfits there I
think 2023 out uh outfits
so we're all behind on
[Music]
time we have a new one there's always
one in the works always it just Tak
ages I should be planning the one for
this year simultaneously but like my
brain cannot handle it also I can't
decide yet I know we had a talk about it
but I can't
[Music]
decide giant chicken costume
no no no no
no I will not do that I don't want
to
connection
okay
nice and a dead end oh it's a
cater this one's
metal and the drunker they're just
chilling here oh he resists
this is high exp enemy
[Music]
okay ah he resisted though did he just
resist
[Applause]
everything oh well we get both that's
good a shiny B didn't put because he run
away he he'll run
away oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no
oh
[Music]
no this
everything I'll just I'll just go with
whatever oh man oh R2 let's go okay
strongest I can do
probably
please will he run away next don't use
those skills near the enemy
what he sells in for
nap that does that he a that healed so
much
no
no okay but then he didn't run away this
turn what
this guy doesn't want
to she has no MP should I give her
[Music]
MP I I guess I
will
um oh yeah I should throw a grenade or
so they get typically give a lot of time
to kill okay okay
okay okay that's good
damage that's pretty
good oh okay I can take him down this
round
easy
okay I was so
worried I was so concerned but my
controller
fell
no
okay job rank up for
everybody woohoo
[Music]
yes did she just she doesn't uh wear the
right color in that picture she should
be wearing the red version of the outfit
but now it was
blue
why this is always like
that careful of your HP no
o
another another uh
seing area
[Music]
interesting
oh let's go
treasure
monster what the [\h__\h] going to cry for
my
ah you
again all right bring it on Mr
swole you want revenge
huh Revenge you
Sur I got to say respect respect on on
the
muscles they do be pretty
impressive
pudding pudding is
here
huh I'll
try this
[Music]
one every
time it's difficult to catch that one
even though I knew it was the one that
suddenly appears so fast I knew it o we
to
fire my orange is still in C me I can
come watch your Origins you saying that
already makes me
sad sounds
like sounds
like you don't like your Orin anymore
the
oranges what's wrong with the oranges
huh hey yeah K got a new
[Music]
skill I recently saw another one of our
old kfp
Clippers
um got hired by I mean they probably
were hired for a while now um by by some
other like
company that's where they all go I'm
like where did they go they just
suddenly stopped clipping I wonder what
happened and then later I find out oh
okay yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
M they don't even say fire to
me they're just
gone are they still around at least no
no not
really pudding pudding surprisingly has
been showing up so I guess it doesn't
apply
to congrats yeah yeah good for good for
[Music]
them
again he can't get enough of us he wants
to join our team our
lineup I don't know what that has to do
with anything
[Music]
Pride if they say goodbye it'll be
S I don't know it it would be nice to
like know where they're going why
they're
leaving but no no no obligation so it's
cool it's fine I don't
care actually what am I doing I
should once I say goodbye and you said
[Music]
no uh
yeah
well
yeah cuz
no don't
go there any fresh Clippers in chat who
want to get started what are you
offering
a course maybe a Clipper
course CER and thumnail
course ooh level
up so many level UPS let's go
yes you should as La you should uh you
should teach people we need more
Clippers should make a
course new skill yay
I see I see a few kfps at least like uh
putting up like Clips on on Twitter in
the hashtag of moments they like but
it's just like not edited just the
moment not saying that you need to do
anything guys you you don't have to like
become
Clippers that's not something that
I I'm like I want you guys to feel like
you have to do only if you want to H if
you feel
like giving a try if you're interested
in
it I'd pick up clipping again if I
didn't have a job now o life gets in the
way it to be like
that cing you don't need a
course
if someone hires you for clipping then I
don't think you need a
course sector
one
B oh hey there's a safe Point here oh
and I can oh I can already heal here I
thought it would have to be like in the
middle
nice
oh boss fight there all right let's go
no
problem oh there it is there he is help
me what done already you're
pathetic hey you okay the hell who are
all of you you after the treasure in
here n we're here to
rescue people we don't care about the
treasure right no not at all it's not
the material
things stress relief or so my doctor
calls it little lost LS wandering here I
have fun with them keeps my blood
pressure
down
okay of course this bottle of chicken
[\h__\h] had no fight in him I'm thinking I
still got stress to spare how about you
guys when I help me cool off of
course play with me
chicken that's basically
K Wow freaking horror clown up
[Music]
here wonder how strong they are maybe uh
if you guys weren't standing so far away
I could help you here oh yeah come
closer maybe this can get them
all cute yes I got everybody better
focus willpower and evasion
race now we can get starting what is
this a classic polar maneuver which
damages enemies and has a slight chance
of lowering their
attack lots of MP though so maybe
instead I'll do the CI sticks
[Music]
or I pick of the CI
sticks more
[Music]
debuffs
got all of
them oh he got inor to the blinker get
Gnarly with a squid bro doing magic
damage to some wave hog and and any
around him with a Chance of blind that
fool these
descriptions are
amazing but I think I'm going to do the
cresting
Collider at like from
[Music]
here but what does that mean that attack
gains
momentum does it get stronger if I use
it
[Music]
again
what's maybe
this oh perfect I think I will get them
all Darkness
andow ah except for the boss cuz I guess
he's immune Darkness engulf me Darkness
engulf
me it gets WR cuz I was far enough oh
okay okay
okay I
see
she daddy long legs
think you can stand after
this they didn't Skip Leg
Day I skip leg day a
[Music]
lot damn it I missed
itoc you want to hear a whol wholesome
story
[Music]
guys
what you in the area oh there it
is okay so in a in a supermarket that
I'm really close
to that I go to the
most okay not the most but a supermarket
I go to quite a
bit
um there's there's a lady that once I
saw her for the first
time she was like really nice to me and
I was nice to her and I don't know like
uh the more I kept seeing her I noticed
she was really happy to see me and I was
always really happy to see her we smiled
at each other so so
brightly like I could tell she was is
really delighted to see me every time
and
[Music]
uh and we would like ask each other how
are you how are you what are you doing
this and that and then at some point our
conversations would get a little bit
deeper and so she uh told me because I
told her that I was having issues oh
iron balls I was having these issues
with Dam it with the internet right and
then she told me that she once worked
for uh that internet
provider fck how you block us and know
it's funny then we talked a little bit
about you know she she could relate even
more to my troubles with the provider
with the internet provider
mhm yeah
yeah so we're having some nice
conversations every now and then every
time I I came by and I I I came by quite
often because I you know I get I like to
get like fresh
qu and
[Music]
then I really like her like I'm Legit so
happy to see her when she's not working
and I don't see her it's a sad day so we
were having this like
interesting relationship I really think
she was happy to see me because like
mostly like the people I guess if you
work at a supermarket or any any store
like that the people that come to buy
stuff you don't really build a
connection with
them but in this case I feel like we did
you know we
did yeah
and so the other day you know when I
went to the doctor and I was like really
down
I
um I was crying so much right after the
doctor I was crying while eating cake
and it was really really a
sad sad morning for
me and I was like I just want to hug I
want to go home and hug my cats but in
reality I wish I could get a hug from a
human but I don't I don't have anyone
who I could you
know ask for
hug and then I was like would would it
be super pathetic to to see if she's
working right now on my way back and and
ask if she wants to hug me would it be
super pathetic and I was like thinking
to myself if I should do it or not if I
should do not I was contemplating it and
I was like no I shouldn't do it that's
too prophetic I can't go in and ask for
a
hug I mean I'm I'm sure she likes me but
maybe that goes too far and she'll be
like in a in a position where she's kind
of forced to do it because she doesn't
want to be rude but at the same time
maybe she'll be thinking like what the
[\h__\h] what a weirdo here I go what a
loser so I wasn't going to do it but
then I I was like passing the store and
I was like ah I'm going to go in and
just see if she's there and maybe I'll
buy
something [\h__\h] and so I walk in and I
see I see she's working and I'm like oh
what do I do I was like
nervous you and so it was like really
empty and
she as like like sneaking through the
store
slowly and like
walking like
these and then I see and then she sees
me and she's like oh hey how you doing
and I'm
like uh I'm like emotional so I can't
really say anything cuz I know the
moment I start talking I'll start
crying you know how that
feels so I I'm like not saying anything
but I'm like like sneaking wobbling
around and she's like why are you
sneaking for the stor Dad I'm
[Music]
like
yeah wait let me try this
one okay
nice she's like oh what's what's
wrong and I just can't get myself to
answer and and she asks again like
what's wrong how are you and I'm like um
and then I quietly
say can I I I asked oh how much how much
is a hug and she's like what did she say
she didn't hear me and then with even
more pen and uh first I couldn't say it
the second time cuz saying it without
crying in that moment took me so much
willpower H up to hold back the tears
and she made me say it again and say
made it
louder and and then I said it and I
broke out in tears no no the moment
before I even said it I was like I was
tearing up and I was hiding behind um
the the uh the paper dead the doctor
gave me she's like what's wrong what say
something and I'm like how how much is a
hug and then I cry and she's like oh
nothing and she walks around around the
counter and she gives me a hug and she's
like what's wrong what's wrong you can
talk to me it's okay I'm here and she
was so sweet I love her I love
[Music]
her I really love
her she's so
nice she has like a a sweet mommy area
she looks she looks
hugable She's a little bit Frenchy
Focus goodbye cool and yeah I just like
gave her a rough
explanation of the doctor thing she
really wanted to know what's
wrong like yeah that's frustrating but
then then suddenly even though it was
calm until then suddenly we kept on
getting interrupted by customers and um
I don't know I felt awkward waiting
there So eventually I I was happy I got
my hug and then I I
left but when I came back again she was
like oh oh when I left she also said
like I'm here I'm here all the time you
can come whenever you want to talk I'm
always
here so
[Music]
sweet why so
nice
yeah you better focus she's a sweet lady
yeah live and you get a prize
wa live and you get a
prize she seems very crun she is when
are you taking her to the
W she deserves
it not many people are that nice to say
I also just feel like like it's hard to
make a connection like that with like a
like a
supermarket worker or something like
that cuz like you don't interact much
like there's no time especially if
they're
busy the more than oh how are you is not
really possible most of the time but
even with just the checking up like how
are you how are you even with that I
feel like she was so happy to to to just
have a a pleasant customer to talk to
for a
[Music]
moment dad you connect with such a great
person at the supermarket for real she's
so sweet there's another person working
there who's like the opposite like I'm
so unhappy to see that person
there sorry because I'm tanging I can't
focus on
fight um CU that person is like
constantly
ranting and venting
about their
co-workers and how everything is [\h__\h]
and sucks they're so stupid my Co CU are
such
idiots and I'm like okay why are you
telling me that even the first time
I like talk to
them that was already the F the first
time and they're like already like like
venting out in the
open about their coworkers like right
there like oh I work with such idiots
such [\h__\h] idiots I'm surrounded by
only
idiots I'm like oh my god wow okay and I
like I I I uh smile and I nod and Nod
I'm like
okay and they're like that every
time every [\h__\h] time they failed the
vibe check for
real my
God how can you always be in such a bad
mood and then you let it out to
customers even when I go there and I see
like other people standing uh at the
cashier that are surely first timers
strangers like okay I go there more
often so okay whatever you feel like you
can rant at me sure but like first
timers I'll see I'll see it every time
it's every time the same
thing always in a bad mood always
spreading the worst kind of
energy yeah I don't get it like don't do
that to C customers oh my God like maybe
if they ask you but this person just
does it on their own out of nowhere just
yelling profanities and complaining
about their co-workers how they're so
[\h__\h] and how they're so much
better I've seen that so many times here
really it's awkward to me too like I I
would love to say
like you're an idiot but if I if I'm
going to go to the store more often then
I don't uh I don't feel like I want to
ruin this for
me yeah bad bad employee and and that's
even more so why I love seeing that lady
and I think she also loves seeing me
because especially when she's in a shift
with that with that person I'm sure
she's like oh my God please please just
talk to
me because I I just don't want to talk
to my
coworker yeah to very to people very
different perspectives and moods and
motivations have you asked her to hang
out yet no but I feel like maybe one day
I feel like we might become
friends h
any retail employee understands the
value of a customer that's what I'm
thinking yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm seeing
you as a human being
yeah no everybody everybody has been
nice except for that one that one
dude so rude but I feel
like I feel
like
uh because I keep on like smiling and
and nodding and
listening I think that taken as oh
she she doesn't mind and maybe she even
agrees with
me she's cool I like
her that's that's not it buddy that's
not it though it's
so it's so what's the
word up
up
up I don't know I can't I I can't find
the word like
[Music]
yeah abre
what
abre offputting yeah I think that's what
I want to say it's so offputting
especially if you do it to
strangers yeah anyway sorry for the
tangent oh I don't know what this
treasure is all about but nothing's
worth more than your life stay away from
this place from now on yeah wise words
those here take this at least for saving
me jet surfboat whoa
[\h__\h] oh my God
damn do you know if there are any more
people trapped here I'm afraid so I
could hear them calling for help from
further down some of us wandered in out
of sheer curiosity had no idea when we
were getting into into even more came
looking for the treasure and it seems
the lower flows are home to truly
Dreadful characters you all seem strong
enough but I'd still advice an abundance
of caution venturing any deeper you
would what oh dear
ambulance he's really beaten up let's
get him back to safety we're all pretty
worn out too yeah not a good idea to
keep going around I would go more but
okay if the story doesn't work be
too yeah a good place to level up if I
feel like I need to level up before I
stream sometime uh because we've been
like weak then I'll do it
yeah anyway end the
[Music]
PO
although that surfboard is pretty
dope the design looks crazy too a real
life Labyrinth H I'll conquer you just
wait perhaps we
will We grinded for like 5 hours
oh yeah I did didn't
I the final BL gives an ultimate armor
for each one
oo damn okay
um uh
gear whoa what the
[\h__\h] you can't surf with that that's not
a surfboard
that's
rad isn't
this that is just
rad is he fishing would he teach me
fishing if I talk to
him I didn't come here to
fish I came here to improve the world
Jasper what do you
need I got to find materials to build a
new one I wonder if there's any junk oh
[Music]
okay I got a lot
of iron fragments or lava fragments
let's give you lava fragments just one
right you're
welcome God I want to kill
you one stinky
towel better than no
towel if you want a stinky
towel how do I turn this into a m joke m
is not
stinky can't make a m can
I yo dude I did
it was nice was
fun m
another area the art
walls okay the art
walls is it
far ooh it is we've never been in that
area let me bring out my
[Music]
sco
Ain a I'm
[Music]
scoter
what did
[Music]
you give me that first aid
ooh St wi
suckers where are we going how far is
this oh now we're entering the area
where we haven't been at all
[Music]
oh I can charge
here let me
charge might as well right now 55
bucks
okay I guess cuz I'm charging all of
these scooters is this really so
expensive charging a scooter like in
real life you can charge it at home
right like with your own
electricity I guess there's no
equivalent
[Music]
IRL but I guess like rental
scooters you wouldn't have to charge
them yourself but just renting them and
using them
probably ends up being a good
amount did I get any new gear like this
thing that I just saw for
example that accessory you have a power
ring oh 10 up 10
down ankle we got some more ankle
weights and we got the Hibiscus hair
band which greatly increases drob exp
obtained from Battle
[Music]
H should I give this to her I'll give it
to
her
it costs me $2 in electricity to charge
my car oh you have an electric car it
costs only $2 oh that's pretty cheap
wait that's so much cheaper than paying
for
gas what the
[\h__\h] that is a the future a good reason
to get an electric car that's absolutely
not true
oh but I guess it's generally still
cheaper than gas
right cars are more expensive at the
purchase point and it's complicated okay
okay
yeah oh yeah
Sol
good
ide pineapp on the right
side I'm going to guess this exists
irl2 pretty
cool
bra please
stop I'm I'm begging you this place is
my livelihood your livelihood huh did no
one tell you we're the new
owners what's wrong is there some sort
of
trouble who the hell are you now who the
hell are you we're with pico saying
you're owners now poor oh thank goodness
please you have to listen I've been
running this Cafe for 30 years now and I
never once have endured such violence
yeah quit bitching if you'd have paid
your debt we wouldn't be here but I even
B Money from you oh we know who you
borrowed from thing is this morning we
bought that lender out so as of now your
Deb
is ours finally even so you can't just
budge in here like this the previous
lender agreed I could pay off my loan
and installments we had a
deal you're a native Hawaiian aren't you
what difference does that make H well
cheer up we're turning this place into a
boba shop and your can run the register
no need for more Boba shops please eat
that [\h__\h] up even like
B oh that that's
enough aren't you polyana people
supposed to be
volunteers volunteers should stay the
[\h__\h] out of
business strong arming helpless
shopkeepers is hardly what I call like
now yeah I like it without the Boba
without the bubbles you'll be hearing
from our lawyers
anything oh yeah how about you scram or
you'll be hearing out your
[\h__\h] I'm staying right here not
really you sure then maybe we ought to
tear you up first huh too much sugar me
all you want I'll never
budge he get a little guy here he thinks
he could stand up to
us all right let's see if you're still
standing after that
[\h__\h] that the fact that he would
actually do
this and the guy would actually stand
there and take the [\h__\h] hammer in his
face what the you another poly kind of
prick
God damn mang or pineapple
chunks
oh boys we're wrecking these bastards I
would prefer that
too fight fight fight my [\h__\h]
Sur oh my God
surfing in
space are they strong I
wonder kind of a on as
far then I'll do the Honolulu hips on
him
you heard some Chinese I didn't hear any
who's speaking
Chinese o uh this is the one that makes
some blind maybe I'll use
[Music]
that could get all three of
them oh [\h__\h] wait did we do this before
I don't think we did this was new to me
unless I didn't pay attention last time
we used it oh my
God oh my
God oh wait is
that no I'll just do I'll
do ah
oh we love to see it
nice
combo oh my
God
okay why didn't the C show them speaking
Chinese instead of English hm
H I guess because like they were in the
middle of a conversation with the
Hawaiian so they would speak English but
within the group they speak
Chinese especially the the small fry
maybe just speak more
[Music]
Chinese is that even fluent Chinese it
somehow sounds off to
me huh H I stole your
soul you were already soulless before
that
apparently sound sound ping
a
little bit
Overkill he wait isn't this new why is
fire
now oh wait it's because of maybe the
yeah applying your boards
attributes nice so now we have a fire
move oh he's weak to water let's
go
mhm he's so far the main
boss come over here Mr
Jin let me steal your soul
too
I got to catch them
all
okay now only the boss left why are they
all mysterious oh they're not really
mysterious to
me nothing mysterious about you I guess
the mysterious thing is we don't know
who they belong to but since they're
speaking Chinese it's I guess it's like
new group of
antagonists damn he does a lot of damage
with his little Hammer it's about the
size as my little Barbie
hammer that everybody who sees it makes
fun of but it's such a cool it's not
really from Barbie but just's like
really cute and colorful small Hammer
but did I tell you guys I recently when
I was building that furniture I realized
one thing that my hammer was more than
just a hammer my hammer should never be
disrespected ever
again cuz like hammering a lot of things
I was like noticing that it was getting
loose the the handle was getting loose
I'm like why and I eventually noticed
that when you
like uh open up the back of the handle
there's like
screwdrivers in there screwdriver and
and like you know there's the the flat
one and the starshaped one and so on
it's like a
matrioska of a hammer and and other
tools yeah like bits
mhm a multitool yeah but like so cute I
need to show you a photo I guess I never
showed you right never showed you what
it looks
like it's it's just
fabulous a tool in a tool in a tool in a
tool if there was a smaller Hammer
there's not a smaller hammer in there no
it's already small enough trust
me
huh h
still long
Li you know what I I'll use this we'll
get probably rid of all my mp
yeah
cute how much how much does that recover
plus 44 ooh that's good dot
recovery
[Music]
for
oh nice nice
cooperation good music Reviving are you
guys
vibing I can't decide
man one probably
happy let's do
this merciless
[Music]
me witness the power of a Chio through
and
through okay you're out of
MP the fight could still be relatively
long so let me give him some
[Music]
MP probably a big
one okay that was actually too much his
maximum HP U MP is 100
oopsies that was a little bit Overkill
then D
witness who is that again who's doing
the a witness witness me
intro who was
that I was like that sounds familiar who
was that again I just saw it recently
[Music]
I miss a I can't miss this one why do I
keep on doing
[Music]
this
Jun he's playing y one yeah I wonder
when she'll play this one maybe
immediately after she's done did she say
anything
about her
plans oh good damage yo holy
[\h__\h] that was really
good just going through it all she's
playing them in order what release
order or story
order
huh release release
yeah wait she didn't even play like a
dragon one yet right so of course she's
not going to play this one
yet makes
sense yeah it's going to take a long
time
finish started earlier than
me yo double guard [\h__\h]
yeah o tag team yeah I mean you're a
boss I should use it on a boss even
though we're almost
done if not now then
when you don't you don't think she's
enjoying
Bae is pulling off your streams when she
what does that
mean what does that mean she's pulling
off my
streams she's loving ke on me
okay oh you mean ah you means just
pulling up like the same
hours ba always had the potential of
being a long
streamer unlocked that potential
I was sleeping
inside she always had it in
her [\h__\h] son of a
Bach fre look
you yeah I gave him the finishing blow
that does it you should have listened
while you had the chance no no no no no
you got your first anniversary
mag which
the to and the the bird in the back
what's wrong with goddamn trigger
stuck say this
once Madame n you see for this the use
of fire in human
conflicts why can't he who the [\h__\h] are
you English he looks like good H me the
G white as [\h__\h] temp sh will only make
things worse for you friend get the hell
away from
me
[\h__\h]
backfire the IR to you your wounds get
the [\h__\h] away did it [\h__\h] back he's a
monster I swear he's a goddamn
monster ho
[\h__\h] if a if a gun is jammed does that
happen
for
damn yo it is a cult I mean a
miracle good grace is a
miracle Rejoice for Madame Lele has
extended her Divine protection to you
and your humble
establishment
okay
yeah I guess they didn't have the second
voice actor for this
one
[Music]
for
uhhuh you guys recognize
[Music]
him somebody keeps on sending hearts in
the chat guess what I help make dinner
this evening you did spamming those
hearts I see you I see you
spamming how much would you like well
I'm supposed to be on a
diet but today is a
special one big helping
priest yes sir I feel like if your if
your English is
on that level then you don't have the
vocabulary like one big helping I would
never say that like even even I would
never say it that way one big helping
that sounds like the choice of
vocabulary of a fluent person but like
when he has a an accent like that you
know it just doesn't match you know what
I mean from my point of view of
Foreigner learning English you kind of
pick up vocabulary that fits your skill
and you use it according to your skill
yeah I mean not blaming him for not like
they chose him as a voice actor for this
character so if that guy can't speak
English too well that's not his fault
but then they should adjust the the
script and the The Chosen vocabulary a
little bit but you know it is what it is
he has an English voice actor too I
guess you mean if I chose the English
uh wait if I had the English voice over
right
now this is so confusing cuz like
sometimes he speaks English and
sometimes he speaks Japanese in the
Japanese voice over and now if this was
the English voiceover would he he would
talk English to the to the kids and
English to the enemies probably but then
to us he would also speak English right
he just speaks English the whole time
but he would speak it fluently like
there's an actual fluent person talking
it right that would being whole time
this is
yeah
H and ichan too then you don't get like
this this switch of languag is That's
supposed to happen sometimes I don't
know what's the right way to play this
game
oopsie
[Music]
foree
for they got
nice I like their
walls I want walls like
that like these
decorations no crack I
failed
nice walls
[Music]
man what the [\h__\h] how don't we notice
this she just
leaves
CH it's dinner
time not blaming the kid though like
he's not supposed to be fluent in
[Music]
Japanese what is she still doing behind
her
backs
she's still working for someone else
ratting us
out misgivings oh chapter chapter
done how many chapters were there again
guys we're at chapter 6 now I
guess 14 almost halfway through
almost almost we're like 40%
35% 40 let's say
40 puppet honor string chapter
6 now the long chapter start okay I'll
take
for wait who are we talking
to
[Music]
peoplee
fore
[Music]
foree
okay uh yeah I guess I don't know much
about that mhm but I'm assuming it was
his his his lady and she died I guess
but don't tell me too much it's just my
assumption no I didn't stack not
yet
my
beloved
po pie po
p nice pot pie is that like a pie with
like some stew inside is that what that
was
M oh
Pine in the
P pretty much y y Yum Yum
Yum it's gotten late ready to call in
the night uh yeah I
[Music]
guess
really making me yawn over
here nice
view h
oh she wants to plaster his face all
over
why want the
posters
yeah maybe now she went to Japan
or some other
country maybe she's not even here
anymore
advertisement
uh
for that's
Japan a different kind of
Internet different audience different
[Music]
language
did we can I just say look at the
reflections of the glasses of Tomy
zaa
beautiful these cutscenes have really
good quality
man
you have such
look beautiful Reflections
wow
okay okay
me
R You' be so lucky if you get so many
views on like your first video on a new
channel
that's kind of
worse I'm dying not old dying is
worse okay what would that be
he's the mic Man sound engineer
[Music]
whatever yeah shotgun mic is it a
road he said it in such an edgy way
I was like for the actually this is a
good moment um I was looking for a new
mic
foring streams right not
sure if I should
[Music]
get if I should get an on camera
mic
or just a separate
[Music]
one found a nice one for on
camera but then it's kind
of
use on the PC too though
it's h
it can be used differently
too it's not it's not a like ASMR
microphone by the way I'm not going to
buy like one of those
heads but uh it seems to do the trick
you don't really need a like a hardcore
ASMR microne it's not going to be
binaural I think but that's fine right I
I don't I personally I just want nice
cutting
sounds
I don't think it's not asmi if it's not
Boral I wouldn't agree with that
no I look a little bit more into it
but I feel like uh Boral microphones
maybe the ones that I know you got to
like be really close to them or like
they they take up a lot of space or you
know I'll think about it okay there's
some people who really want the Bol
[Music]
roll just two inputs can do by nor but
it's most transparent to List's brain
the more head
shaped
interesting
over
yeah cuz the cooking ones that I watched
they weren't B binaural either and they
still were amazing
soothing I'll check around a bit more
maybe I'll
ask some
ASMR
genius
Shake tattoo that's
[Music]
R didn't he say say that more often like
that's rad or was that someone
else he's not saying it anymore these
[Music]
days
likee
fore he didn't say he
down ah there it is from the first
thumbnail the way he talks Japanese
is barely translate in
English
VI oh
[\h__\h] he's dragging him into
it story
time
[Music]
for so
extra
spe
[Music]
yeah he was a theat
kid
okay
damn well the thing is all of this is
great they're doing a good job but we
need someone who's good at editing
too
to make a video that can actually go
viral who's going to do that you guys
don't know how to edit a video do
you
hey let's
hireing or
else carrot I'm sure car would love to
help NOP says
no how dare you why won't you help them
out they pay an
exposure they would probably
pay this is totally going to go viral
trust me
bro first time video but I promise I can
give you
exposure you turning it down cuz you k
ofp you learned the script
properly studied it
she CH said the video is going to be a
bit guess I'll take a dip yo let's go
[Music]
swimming living the Hawaii
lifestyle oh
T small t
house damn the poor
Turtle no you're not going to sell that
baby
no
[Music]
poor no it belongs to the
ocean
try calling it let's see if it will
react protected
by of course we're going to
fight it reminds me of my snorkling
adventurers it's so so cool to see it
with your own eyes to see animals sea
animals in the water with your own
eyes let's get
him
Justice huh no I didn't I didn't fight
anyone but but it's so fascinating I
want to more snowling these are times
why I wish I didn't live in Austria
because you we don't have an ocean
man that reminds
me I I need to
go uh skiing still this year before the
season is completely over cuz my my
best is like even if it's just for one
day we should go we should go ski and
I'm like no I'm so I'm still traumatized
I swear I still have PTSD from
skiing I'm still so scared of it but I
have all this skiing equipment that was
really
expensive
so I should really make use of it but I
don't think I can use the skis yet
actually cuz they are way too
long I'm still such a beginner I can't
really control
them for people who don't know if you're
still a beginner you should get like
small skis short ones and the better you
get the longer skis you should
get the trip of RT went well for the
most
part I was still like oh but if it's
just for a day I guess I'll go with my
friends I got to hit her up I got to
tell her yo yo yo it's February but I
think I
thinking season let me check
it's
talking
oh don't we know this one from the
previous game
[Music]
too Kaa is it a
Kaa I don't know what the [\h__\h] it is
October until
May May is kind of [\h__\h]
mate
like beginning of May but okay I still
got time doesn't even have to be in
February he looks cute
Puppy Playtime
reject I love
it it's so cute it's very
hugable they have open time available
it's not a trip it would be a day day
trip just one day of uh
skiing not going
anywhere n
oh yeah the text box is different what
the hell is
this look at the aura in the
back
oh oh my God I should put these on my
thumpnail
[Music]
cute he's got goly
eyes are they real that's why gapin
looks familiar then
okay and where have you abducted me
[Music]
to it just looks like a trash island I'm
sorry
[Music]
but
the real game starts
now kids love you I can
imagine the [\h__\h] goggly eyes are so
cute so
funny
yeah
yeah you can't have a turtle on a trash
island it will get stuck in the trash
and will [\h__\h]
die ha population 90%
Japanese in Grand
blue
[Music]
fu
yeah that sucks
[Music]
though
cry going to cry
to
relatable
taimo I want to get good at it though
again because I used to enjoy it as a
kid that one week that I went skiing
with my
class was really
[Music]
fun but now I have so much
PT
no I'll clean up you stupid island then
leave it to
[Music]
me I'm the guy for
everything you can stop crying
[Music]
now yeah let's not be Al sad let's be Al
happy
you got Mr Yolo's number dude he was so
old already at that point you saw what
he looked like right I showed you the
video who knows if he's you know not on
wood but who knows
know he even you
know I mean he was really healthy
though healthy seemingly healthy
remember what I told you about like his
intake of
food he had all these like
smoothies I think all he drank was these
movies so
healthy yeah Mr
Yodo and and he was like like fin as in
like fit fit type of fin so I'm sure he
can live for a long time but damn
D also like I don't know he was a great
teacher but at the same time because of
my PTSD I felt like too
pushed too pushed to like go over these
um more difficult um
Hills on the
mountain it's really scary it took 8
years to be good at Snowboard what
really I feel like
generally you can get good really
fast at skiing and
snowboarding wonder why it took you so
long sorry it's not supposed to be a
roast but I got good at skiing in a week
with my class can you start on easier
routs of course but I feel
[Music]
like I don't know there's just I have
this blockage now ever since that
accident that was crazy man I almost
probably broke something that's actually
a miracle that I didn't break anything
and in hindsight I wish I would have
broken something that would have been
finally the first time in my life that I
broke something that was the one time
opportunity for me to break a bone in my
body and I didn't I
didn't I just had this really crazy
accident yeah had the one of
Cali really crazy accident that was
terrifying and gave me PTSD for my
[\h__\h] life with skiing
I don't even break a bone but it sure
felt like I
did you don't get it guys you don't get
it y'all are saying that because you
probably broke a bone before but I'm
like I never broke a bone I never had a
cast before I want
that no that it would probably hurt so
much and I would regret what I'm saying
but but but but that would have been a
great moment to break something that's
what I'm that's just what I'm saying
like you know if if if if any time I was
already hurting myself in that moment
why not just break
something might as well you
know excuse me for my craziness
un seen so many people being airlifted
at this slob airlifted Oh you mean like
people who had crashes and all that yeah
that's crazy that's sad at least I had
my crash at the very bottom of the
slope I just zoomed down the slope and I
crashed at the very bottom into a
fence and Z
SW swoosh I went by swoosh I took the
fence with me and all my equipment flew
in different
directions my sticks and my skis and my
hat helmet everything just whoosh whoosh
whoosh whoosh in every [\h__\h] Direction
like a
tornado nice
prefense I was like what the
[\h__\h] and then the Japanese people come
over and they're like oh with this G I'm
like like I understand Japanese but they
thought I didn't because in that moment
I couldn't even answer I was like wo
wo wo W
wo I was like wo wo wo wo
ouch yeah I was in a big shock and and
yeah it did hurt but the the pain went
away R quickly I really I really just
I'm too lucky man I'm too lucky how can
I have this insane accident and go away
from it
unscathed or maybe I didn't maybe I died
in that moment and as I am the Phoenix I
revived at the same moment
immediately
H do you want to lose your Phoenix like
above do you want to
De I'm just saying like I don't want to
go out of my way now to break a bone but
I'm just saying in that moment when I
was already in an accident already in
pain I might as well could have broken a
bone or
two
you know what I
[Music]
[Laughter]
mean it's like you know what a deal like
a package
deal you don't get
it you can you
imagine can you imagine because I was in
I was going to be in Hokkaido for a bit
longer after that with cie and she would
have treated me like a nurse she would
have been my caretaker
she would have made me soup and brought
the soup to me she have tucked me into
bed she' have held my hand in the
hospital
oh oh it's morning here
huh I didn't see cuz I was fast I was U
imagining what oh there why are you
manifesting broken bones cuz I never
broke a bone before and oh I don't know
having a cast one I don't even know
anymore I've been I've been saying this
[\h__\h] for years now and I don't even know
what's wrong with me right now right now
I'm actually questioning myself but I
still think I could have gotten a
package deal on that
day like that was weird like kind of
lame not break a bone but okay you guys
just don't get
it
you don't get
it I'm killing
you hey why why am I able to kill you
but not even break a bone of my
own neither have I damn Moy let's break
some bones sticks and
stones and chains and whips excite me
what
fix there's nothing e well I don't
know I just went to a Rihanna
song I don't know what
happened you can just get a cast should
I fake
it imagine oh I could make a I could
pull a prank I could put on a cast next
time I go like to a studio or or maybe
to the
Fest let's say I'll go to the Festival
rehearsal in a fake cast and I'll record
secretly on my phone I get their
permission afterwards but I'll record
secretly on my phone their
[Music]
reactions and I'll walk around with
jenma supporting me and with with some
um what do you call those sticks and the
cast on my leg or
so and they'll be
like over I need to come up with a story
though crutches yeah
crutches and I I'll be like sorry I
can't perform tomorrow or so whenever it
will be I'm sorry guys and they're like
oh [\h__\h]
Ki
no [\h__\h] oh it's what the [\h__\h] do we
[Laughter]
do is it a bad idea
yes I'll say I went
skydiving hardcore
hardcore go away from the
St prank I want to
prank it's it's j it's
j what's wrong with my ideas why you
guys you guys always approve of my ideas
yes now you don't what happened between
our
bond
huh
okay oh hey itan what's up CH I'm sorry
a lot this happens long story is short
I'm over at the resort called Dondo
Island d d what you're not making sense
I know I just want to give your heads up
that it's going to take me some time to
get
back how to never get any St time again
hey no no no no I I would just be
pranking the talents not the not the
staff I would tell the staff
beforehand
ah okay no worries I'm going to need a
few more days myself to finish editing
the video
[Music]
okay why suddenly
nongo
nongo I mean we want this video to take
over the internet right so we're going
to need some damn good editing to Spruce
it up and really sell it anyway don't
feel bad about taking this time to kick
back and relax on uh what was it don't
look Island I'll reach out once I'm done
okay
guess she won't be finished for a few
more days so I'll just take uh an easy
and look around this island for now
okay are there any newcomers newcomers
new kfp M who didn't know the skiing
crash
story oh my God how did I clean this
up
me really
oh I knew it was a classic I don't know
but it sounds
bad I didn't hear about it I didn't know
until today I don't think I've heard oh
my god oh wow well it it was while I
still lived in Jaan
right it was whyless to live there so
the first half year so you would have
really had to be here for a while or
just watch all the clips that exist M
mhm 3 years
ago long time ago me and Cali went to
Hokkaido on a trip to first we were in
sapo for like two days and then we went
spontaneously to the closest skiing uh
region that's the closest to Sao and
then went skiing there we we rented all
the equipment uh and then I had an
accident at the end of the day anyway uh
and then on the next days we went to the
Onan together which was like in in like
far away from the city in the
mountains it was a really nice place man
yeah yeah yeah but the accident it was
fine I recovered really fast it was more
like the shock from it that I still
after 3 years I still have this shock
this PTSD which is really bad for an
Austrian cuz in Austria like it's like
our national sport you know to go skiing
we have no ocean but we have a [\h__\h] ton
of beautiful mountains and and our
schools teach is skiing and snowboarding
and it's like you just every freaking
Austrian is like supposed to know how to
ski and we go to the Olympics a lot with
that like there's nothing else we're
good at really much but winter sports
we're good
at yeah
G around young kfp let me tell
you let me tell you the
story same here in Canada oh really
wow but you know I feel our mountains
must be superior never heard about
Canadian
mountains I'm sure you got some good m
mountains but you know we got the Alps
we got the
Alps
no so okay
ooh old
bad fighting words got to start a fight
of crony with Quon oh I'm scared I don't
want to fight with Quon she's been
intimidating all the all the clips
recently too of quason show that she's
ready to fight
KAS got a cleanup hitter okay just
hitting it is not going to make the
trash go away you're just like
scattering it all over again actually
the original state would have been
better when it's like you know all put
together in one little you know Hill of
trash this is not the way
kasuga
oh [\h__\h] I didn't properly read that
destroy 10 junk piles with your
bat there's not even a
timer what is the challenge here there's
no
[Music]
timer
I can do more that was too
[Music]
easy good
question ah that that was um
Japanese and
Japanese comedian impersonation that he
just did why there's a guy that does
that it's his cat's phace I said that
sometimes too in the
[Music]
past oh damn what's what's with all
those scars
dude [\h__\h] did you date a cat girl in the
past Pirates
in Japanese they called them the cream
[Music]
Pirates average Catgirl
enjoyer fight fight
fight the only hole I see is your mouth
oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh taking out the trash after equipping
a bad press square to attack the wash
bucklers what the [\h__\h] what's wash
bucklers enemy attacks can be dodged by
pressing R2 holding Square to perform a
sweeping strike which will be useful
when battling multiple enemies at once
okay use everything you can to drive
away those okay so it's not like a
normal fight okay
oh oh we have hearts pixel
Hearts suddenly different different
battle system are they dead yet or what
oh they
are on this island yeah we have a
different genre of
game it's a different
dimension
no Bring it on Bring more bring more to
the
[Music]
shore yeah for the people who miss the
old non turn based
comat night thank
you than nice profile picture
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore you will ban me
forever
[Music]
that was sensitive
content all right so I did say I had
help Serv place so you guys got some
kind of goal in mind go you yeah I think
uh it would be easier to go about things
if you guys had a clear-cut vision you
know rather than trying to restore
things all well and
E actually there's this old dream of
huh what about
[Music]
this that smirk oh ultimate
Challenge short punish guys get funding
to build a five star resort of your
dreams what's all this
about see your government back group
called The Resorts and tourism
Association is running this here
campaign what long as
you meet your criteria the association
will grant us some
funding that's basically what you need
right now isn't it so what we got to
good do well quite a few things actually
but the two main criteria are popularity
and
satisfaction what's that mean for us
popularity is pretty
straightforward wait is this like Animal
Crossing we got to get our Island to
Five Star Island by cleaning it and
stuff oh my my
God Yakuza keeps on stealing Concepts
from other
games I'm not going to read all of that
basically just clean it up
[Music]
mm zero Stars
okay okay clear out the entrance clear
clear out the gr tree
[Music]
okay
so but from here on out is this actually
optional
[Music]
or this part does over stay it's
welcome oh interesting trees so purple
and so
straight oh these ones I can
chop oh the stones and the trees okay
and now we make some DIY oh
no find me a girlfriend while you're at
it where maybe try and see what's
underneath those suits of these mascots
maybe there's a girl
underneath who knows who
knows
okay Survival game animal
crossing
wait oh there you
go
this is I can't get off of the island
now though if I wanted to right I to do
this for a while
huh suddenly I can roll wait I wasn't
able
to the [\h__\h] is that leech
why can't I pick it up or Jelly Bean or
whatever the [\h__\h] that
is it's just like Dark
Souls I spent so much time on this D
Place e why oh there's a green one over
there I'm sure you can collect them
later
maybe Bon
it what's on the
floor I don't think I can Bonk it right
now maybe I can roll over it
nope I need a net oh my
[Music]
God a [\h__\h]
workbench the house looks like out of
rust
though um building town blah blah blah
we'll figure it
out a
toilet floor cushion and a low dining
table okay okay did he say what he wants
me to
make uh maybe all of
[Music]
them toilet I'll make a toilet too o
nice nice
nice nice craft if I could do that on my
own that would be
amazing m
not a wor where to put it
okay why are we doing this oh my
God oh my
God
what what is this part of the
[Music]
game place
path
oh no oh
[Music]
no which one is the
same probably not this one
but please make more space between
what what ah
ah oh
no
okay I don't really know where I'm going
with this though let me tell you this
this mini game broke me you discovered
the real game the tery tery Side Story
was really long wasn't it playing Sims
again
yay
oh I can't start like in the middle
here okay I wanted to like you
know oh
[Music]
wow clearing out an area means to clear
out the area let's do
it 10,000 toal bucks
okay daily clearance
section New Deal mat Yoshi has Don
Island's very own General Store here you
can buy Furnishing and sell specialty
items to the shop
[Music]
owner what do I get if I make it five
stars if it is not not even worth it
putting so much work into
this I don't know
man money you'd be impressed maybe
that's an offscreen kind of thing make
any transaction on Dondo Island you'll
need the Island's currency doco bucks
are missions that update every
day
okay yeah
[Music]
cool mushroom shellfish even fish and
insects they can all be sold in exchange
for Dole
box oh the water is so
clear
oh a really good skill for
ichun don't be a hater okay I'm not I
mean you can finish the game before
getting five stars well but then then I
don't need it
anymore this is where the infinite
wealth is you get a huge amount of money
and a pretty decent ability but you can
also get lots of money from doing the
dungeons if you would prefer that I
don't
know is this like like in the first like
a dragon we had uh like a job with a
company right do we not have this or was
that Yakuza zero I keep on mixing them
up do we not have something like this
here and this is like maybe the
equivalent to make
money aha I yeah ichang Confections yeah
so oh okay that's like the
equivalent oh and zero had the
Cabaret it's not as good for making
money
okay we got the bugn net and the
[Music]
Harpoon
okay okay we'll just do it as long as we
have to for
now
let me get rid of the trash
here
amazing so good for the environment my
existence is good for the
environment I will
fix all the problems that Earth
has
enough trash has been demolished to
reduce the cost of side what side what
disappeared okay it said like get rid of
the entrance trash and another one I
don't know which
one do it say
here no that's not what
okay but we have to meet the criteria to
make it a onear
resort okay let's try
this
[Music]
ew that looks
disgusting
ah silver flutter it was red though in
reality what a
scam a shame Ki didn't really have a
mini game like
zero I'm I'm um generally I I don't
think um why are you not
running is he not running how do I run
now that
the why is he not
running
[Music]
oh now he's running never
mind oh okay it's x what was I saying ah
I I may sound like I'm like annoyed by
this and all that but I feel like
um if I wasn't streaming it I would mind
less it's not a bad thing that Yakuza
has all this variety it's a good thing
um but I guess I just like I see all
these mini games I'm like ah this is
making the game and the the the whole
series even longer this is adding
another 10 hours to my
playthrough but yeah generally like it's
adding variety a little bit um but this
is not it doesn't even have story though
if it at least had story
man I'm freeing the bucket Yay good for
you spread your wings and flap flap flap
flap bu
Bridge there is story it does a
story yeah just don't misunderstand like
this is not hate towards the game I
just uh I'm dreading the amount of hours
it's going to take
me to finish this
game you skipped it out no I mean I get
the gist
I get the gist of it it's just not main
story that's what I mean we're not
getting any further in the main
story I mean we do because we have to do
this otherwise we're not going to get
further but it's not in really
invol I'm not going to find out where my
mom
is but being able to collect things you
know is really addic thing I already do
that a lot on the main island anyway I
love
that back on my Animal Crossing Island
things have changed a
lot okay how does this fishing
Work O we're Haroon
fishing
sick
oh
[Music]
oo nice on the second try and why is it
still zooming why the [\h__\h] is it still
zooming does it need two
harpoons
unrealistic there we
go [\h__\h] my hits my
aim I
D
scler okay never heard of you buddy oh
so far what the
hell don't
scler
whoever yes
flounder lers look so
funny like their faces upside down is it
upside
down
nice got all the fish in the
sea I am actually bad for the
environment I take it
back
okay so talk to ging talk to L Place one
Furnishing outside craft one okay we're
crafting
toilet will I be able to make a walls
too and like a
[Music]
house could make some nice
chairs ah damn it man they
they they do
be putting us through quite
[Laughter]
something the parasol would be
nice I can actually build
it
oh
that was nice
though I like that um um the
[Music]
table okay how how do I
uh edit mode
okay I
made this floor cushion cuz this table
is really low oh but I can't place it
close enough the
[\h__\h] that triggers
me why is it so wow the
graphics I can't put the shade where it
should be I want it to be
closer okay here it here it is
then and the
toilet toilet in the corner
I would not use this kind of toilet
though I don't like it like even if
that's the only choice I have I I
wouldn't use
it I'd hold it in I don't like these
toilets like I feel like as a
woman you have to squat over it and like
the floor like you get so close to the
floor and usually for these toilets
they're public toilets and so the
surroundings are like like the floor is
like dirty and wet and you don't know
why it's wet and I feel like as a guy
it's easier usually cuz you can just be
quite distant from it but as a
woman no no thank
you yeah cuz people Miss yeah please
guys try to not miss so much cuz you're
you're making it difficult for women if
you miss so
much and then you don't even clean it up
you don't even clean it
up
skill issue now try a bit harder guys
please please for the sake of the women
if it's a mixed
toilet like in an airplane or whatever
in a train or in a bus or in a festival
whatever same
feeling I don't
miss
ew
e the trick is to do it in the dark for
maximum
practice well then do it at home if
you're going to do it in the dark I hope
you're saying you're doing it in the
darkness of your own
home I always sit on a normal Western
toilet
okay
no sorry I'm joking I'm talking while
drinking why am I doing
this I'm drinking a Capri Sun so it's
kind of weird right now we're drinking
like from a new cat person that has like
not the not the straw like a a different
thing what flavor M grenade apple and
cherry it's so
yummy by the way I think I need to go to
an idle
meeting while we're on the topic I'm
going to go
now
stretch stretch stretch don't miss I
don't miss I don't miss my chances are
missing a way lower than yours goodbye
sir
for
I'm back with
[Music]
smooy oh oh she to
go okay bye
bye you know my window's kind of broken
right
now my window is broken
it's just always open I can only lean it
to close right
now yeah I don't know how to like
something's wrong with like there's like
a lock on the handle
and I
think at one
point um wasn't even me uh it was
actually the like a the a technician
from the uh
provider and he just touched the window
and he closed it
and
then something got [\h__\h] up
internally I know it's weird and then I
wasn't able to open it at all
anymore
[Music]
um and then I had a friend check it out
cuz there's like a key for that lock my
friend was like experim in with it and
now it at least opens but it also
doesn't properly close
anymore that's weird oh I no don't worry
I won't get like robbed through the
window I don't really have that
concern I'm not I don't live in like New
York or something like
[Music]
that
did I just see a [\h__\h] mountain of
trash in the
background it's insane
huh what he's preparing something for
me New York City
slander am I wrong or am I wrong right
yeah should give you two different
options
Nan a house was that not here
before oh you're gifting it to me thank
you wow that's nice cuz I actually don't
have a home in Hawaii right now
obviously not even a temporary one just
kous
Place completely EMP feel okay then I'll
place the toilet in
here if I can still move
it um there's been some trouble
arranging you a way back to Hawaii
preparation won't be ready until the
morning after tomorrow
oh
okay I don't mind staying not much we
can do about it now so I don't have to
get it up to one
star maybe I already
did I maybe I already
did a nightl wow cute a light to help
you explore at Night Don't Islands full
of nature which means it gets dark very
quickly this will help you light your
path only a bit
sweet if you get to one side you get a
good reward okay I I'll get to one star
I don't mind this isn't too difficult I
think
hi wow that's a big house that we just
get for
free I mean exchange for working oh my
God inside it's actually I thought it
would be really shabby broken down look
at that
flooring impeccable
flooring okay Animal
Crossing finishing the inside of
kasuga's home will improve its liability
uh so will kasuga's help making it
harder for enemies to defeat him the
greater the life ability the better
shape kasuga will be in the next day as
well when kasuka is in tiptop farm he
will be able to gather more resources
note that once his HP reaches zero it
will cause doal books to get him patched
up back back
ooh damn we can re I can recreate kfp
office maybe I will maybe I
will really turning into the Sims it's
more like Animal Crossing than the Sims
and Sims you don't have to collect
resources and materials and trees and
all
that end your day by checking out the
calendar
okay
uhuh let me talk to the mascot
wherever they
are where are
they where are
they where would they
be he's in
here ah aha I found
muku
oopsie
okay why why would I talk to
you just just look at the GI tree isn't
it impressive you can find a merad of
insects as well here you know thank
you I'll take that advice and
Cat I mean cat this beautiful blue
butterfly uh where's
cin
he's green so he's possibly blending
Into the Night Life the
wildli same thing same
thing too
close I
can't will it Fly
Away golden Great Horn ain't that easy
to catch that in uh Animal Crossing
oh now something flew
away damn
it
oh
good give you T
enery I'm sure she doesn't have a golden
one
yet he kacha the [\h__\h] where is
he
kachaa
[Music]
K
got
speeda oh modern chair
[Music]
recipe
oh what the
[\h__\h] poison
Gat
[\h__\h]
interesting it's good that we captured
that don't want SC upin to get poisoned
and die right right that would be too
bad Mo let's go I I like him when
they're not eating my
jeans don't look a
mushroom wo wo wo wo wo gold
cockal
go is there oh there's a there's there's
one
here silver
Venture still blaming the most yeah yes
I am yes I am because they were really a
big issue I really had a big problem
with
them you want to play the game because
of this just play Animal Crossing
man man I wish I was already part of
whole life when the newest animal
crossing was the flavor of the month CU
I was I was watching the streams back
then and around that time I think
uh well soon after was audition
time but it looked like so much fun and
I got Animal Crossing on my own and I
was like playing I was playing um
privately and then I was hoping that
when I get in I can play some Animal
Crossing but by the time the flavor of
the month game was dead nobody played
Animal Crossing
anymore
mhm yeah we still played it but it
wasn't as um active
anymore there you are
gotta you want to invite
people new Resident oh
hello
Kon K I heard you left this island for
some other place I'm so happy you're
here who's this why only one of the best
Craftsmen in the world canas s's got
experience he makes carpets let's
go uhuh uhh uhhuh huh a
handyman one day you'll be on time for
the flavor of the
M yeah I miss it so
often I was thinking maybe playing pal
world next week could be a good
idea
ah okay blah blah the contaminated
areas if you destroy the trash and clear
the area a bit by day by day a little
less work for cancer and that will lower
the cost for him to clear deci side a
that's what that was about just use your
best judgment to decide when's the best
time to clear the area based of your
current budget
[Music]
okay ah
huh so basically I should save up my
money and destroy the trash until I get
to a point where I can ask Ken on the C
area for
me at the sign okay
that talk to Kel m yosia if you're
looking to upgrade your tools if you
want to expand your home or purchase
additional lodgings then work on your
home's liveability because if you
improve liability then Kenza will
approach you about home
expans home expansions
huh and no I'm not anymore the queen of
flavor the month when it comes to Ho
Early Access because now now I'm not the
only one anymore who gets it so it's not
special
anymore
Dawn trial ah you mean a DLC what ff14
no I don't think I'll play
it
okay I hope K pin stays there so I can
talk to
him begin
begin begin what the
day okay
now he's
gone well he's still there guys do you
know where he would
be ah never mind found
him found
him what don't what what you didn't say
much
there damn we're good
sure that was
you um
then uh which area did I this this
one
ahuh don't even have enough of those
bucks anyway for that
one
level
10 uhhuh okay no worries uh wait that
was that was dailies
anyway wait what is the how do I get it
to to level one oops it how do I get it
to level one
anyway
uh
aha uh
popularity 300 more satisfaction is very
low though clear the entrance and clear
the G great tree okay we cleared out the
entrance right oh but we didn't pay for
it yet I
guess so it's not officially cleared out
I guess and then the great tree is it
that thing over there yeah oh the oh
great
tree this
area until this
to but it gets cheaper as you get the
lther let ranking higher from claiming
it every
day claiming it every day you mean the
trash comes
back does the trash come back oh that's
why confused me cuz it didn't look like
the place that I cleaned before was
clean
ah
damn so much trash production really
makes you
think okay we can get this
rank up can't we a b c d d d
right there we go now it's an
e m
right yeah the price reduces I get
that um and this one and then we'll
clear out the other one that we cleared
out before which hopefully is also
already at rank
e is this area
inside so now it's e and it costs 5,000
right and no uh it needs level five of
building talent and
27,000 okay I'll do my best today I'll
do some of this and then the rest if I
ever touch it again I'm I'm do going to
do my best to do things off
screen I don't mind doing a little bit
of this off screen you know I don't mind
we completed one suggestion
nice gives us extra money wait we're at
20 W that gave me a lot of money though
and I'm at rank D now so it's even
cheaper but we can afford it probably
know we could but what if I don't what
if I don't waste all this money what if
I wait one more
day maybe I'll just wait one more
day then let's try to do some daily
craft one type of Furnishing by DIY
Place one Furnishing outside and catch
free bugs
easy M I got to do my daili I sound like
a gacha game
player m M so this whatever I craft I
can place either outside or inside too
right let's crab the
bookshelf and we'll put it in the
house am I really going to recre I don't
know yet if I'm really
going to be able to recreate
kfp we'll see we'll
see
okay oh uh
aha
ahuh yeah there is a good variety and uh
the kfp office generally is just like
you know wooden nice wooden
stuff so it looks like we could have
most of the things necessary even the
preview kind of reminded me
of kfp
office oh but they want me to place one
outside
too o
okay what could we put
outside what what do we want that place
to
be maybe just you know make
um like an outside Lounge
area I want to make a couple of
these oh I'm going to make
more just to imagine the future this
island will be what do you call it
buzzing buzzling buzz buzz buzz buzzing
with
people fitting chair I don't feel feel
like we have a fitting chair yet maybe
later on
bustling yes if only we could place the
chair uh the the table directly
under
this
umbrella I don't think we can no why
don't doesn't have to be so far
away I want to take this back can I take
it
back how do I ah
R1 taking this back and a toilet
too I'll put it
inside
[Music]
um I don't like this toilet and I don't
want to have it in the same room either
but I
mean it's not going to be
outside oh and I already have this
one okay second
one that's so stupid that pillow is
literally made to be used to that
table why is it got to be so far but hey
look at that big change
wow what a great place to live
in his PE
corner it's I hope your aim is good
don't mess it up the that flooring
it's very
sensitive
oh mushrooms too
exciting toxic
shroom I don't like any mushrooms
though so you guys will have to eat them
for
me
Tas tasar
guys what am I doing anyway I got all my
dailies so what now should I sleep one
night can I sleep yet
I just want to clear up that area again
make it
cheaper let me talk to the guy and see
like what he sells just out of
Interest stop
walking upgrade tools how much is
it
50,000 [\h__\h] no
oh do I look like I have the
money goodbye we won't be talking for a
while oh yeah want
use W paper and flooring oh wow and a
beautiful Japanese style
light
okay oh oh
ooh the window could be nice we don't
have Windows right now right but it's
expensive
too okay let's not do
that I guess let's clear out some more
areas while it's still the same day does
this count as the great tree or just a
no this is just a random area
right
Let's find let's find another area but
this this area this big
one on the map it's pretty big but I
can't where would I enter that one
from you can also sell
Stu this area I
cleaned
oh there I can't really
go need to clear the tree first oh
okay a
tree a tree this you
means
tree great tree the tree
itself oh I don't think I can it would
be a shame
too oh mean you mean the area okay so I
can't like work on them all right now
okay okay that's
fine ah wait so how much is it to build
a bridge probably way too much
money a okay and my Resort rank is not
high enough oh guys so this is really
all I can
do I could try to catch some more
fish
keep building stuff
H
okay ah
but I'll get the fish too shut the
mother was dead bondage
chair why would we need
that I have no use for
this I didn't even know a Bonet chair
looks like that I didn't even know that
was a
thing B
chair and
going to get the big fish I'm going to
get
you a
pro
salmon nice also the fish it says that
we can sell them but are they not good
for anything but selling are they just
like a moneymaking
machine
salmon I like
salmon pretty much oh you have to leave
there's a storm outside be
careful pretty much okay okay
okay oh it's time to go to sleep
apparently we don't have our a choice of
when we want to
sleep we're being forced like a
child
damn
[Music]
I'm where'd you get that
from did that come across from the
ocean this is a oh you bought it a
Tanuki statue
[Laughter]
cute we'll find a place for it
maybe know we can begin right
away satisfaction is still so low oh
guys so
sad well guys there's
trouble those
the can we can we fight again I want to
fight are they here
yeah the cat girl's ex boy
friend damn holy
[\h__\h]
this is what you get if you really want
to date a catg girl think twice about
it or cat
boy this here's this here Rocks Our dump
and you lot are putting in too much
effort to restore it to the way it once
was that's getting to be a pain in our
ass because of this Island's cleared up
where on Earth are we going to dispose
of our waste then recycle it ever heard
of
that
recycle mhm
mhm you cannot handle the SCS then you
don't deserve your catg girl
exactly he's even proudly showing them
off if you keep up the good the hard
work maybe this trash he really be
restored to its former Resort Glory but
not while I'm around oh oh
what what why would you do that that's
so mean that's so
[Music]
unnecessary
man if you want to get rid of our trash
ship then we'll just have to get rid of
you I will
get I'll steal your Catgirl
girlfriend oh we didn't even get to
fight this this
time
lame I'll protect this
island I'm with you there we can't keep
letting them get away with this if
they're going to keep shipping their men
our way then we'll just have to send
them
pack how are we going to do that let's
just say there's more my area of
expertise and DIY anyway leave it to me
I'll take care of them for you if you
see them anywhere on the island get give
me a shot all right okay
okay hot glue will fix the Tanuki statue
don't
worry oh are they just going to be
randomly on the island now oh they will
now attack Don Island while you battle
them some functions will become unusable
such as edit mode once you drive them
away with your trusty bat the watch
buckles will drop tole box in their W so
it's best to deal with them uh on the
double
okay
h Huh dolphin's back what who's dolphin
oh it's a
person glue
Gan my trusty tool of
greatness Miss dolphine are you Dolph
In
oh God oh God the eyes of a killer whale
I'm so scared oh damn an actual dolphin
this sweet lady's dolphine that's right
lately she's been traveling the scas but
now that she's finally home you can take
her for a ride back to Hawai ah
okay oh is that where that screenshot
comes from when he's on the
dolphin riding and
jumping oh much faster than our average
boat
damn I get myself a
[Music]
dolphin
wow so this if we return we continue the
main story
[Music]
maybe maybe that
is
MHM okay I'm going to do like this one
more
day
stop
[\h__\h] yeah the silver spinner is the fast
boy
okay oh they're in
here okay I can treat you the same way
as the trash then that would be fun
ow
[Music]
just business every
day all
normal yes Yakuza
Crossing this game has got it
all you want to play turn based RPG we
got you you want to play play jump and
run we got you
in some way or another you want to
play you want to play dating game we got
you want to play Koka ribm game we got
you you want to
play Animal Crossing we got you want to
play a survival game we got you want to
play
P okay man we got
you want to play the old battle system
action RPG we got you we got
you fore for
for
nice and AR Souls
yeah
oh there's more dudes over
there we're in rank D
now oh hi I'm not there I'm not the
car what did the car ever do to
you the car has always been nice driving
you
around and yet you treat it like
trash oh
hi almost
clean hard work
man but I am ready to go back to the
main story
soon
okay uh this one wasn't it rank B even
already rank C
21,000 I could do it but I don't even
have the talent okay just a m let's
build some
things H let's just build
[Music]
whatever
uh what the [\h__\h] is this an antenna
uh-huh I don't know I want to build nice
thing things
but okay let's build this for my
office actually let me look at my let me
look at my office for a moment I have a
screenshot we
need not all is there a nice office
table that we could use not yet these
don't look so nice the one's too low
yeah was that dining T no it's probably
not probably not ideal the chair we
have uh some plants I the the plants I
can make I need
two want everything right now to raise
your
talent you cooked up a new public
bathroom what how is this what oh it's
like really big it's like an actual
building
oh I wouldn't mind buing that if I have
the materials also we got some cool new
stuff
105 uh 110 30 ah we almost got
[Music]
it oh where's the other stuff ah the
basket and this lamp the lamp would
lamps would be nice
outside okay I'm going to go chop some
trees and catch those fish and gather
mushrooms I guess do this and that
gather for some materials
too too fun you like
it oh you say got
H for the things placed outside to have
an effect they need to be pulled exactly
next to your
road what do you mean to have an effect
you mean the things I currently place
they don't have an effect because oh
because like they wouldn't be accessible
or so that's kind of
lame but I can also place things on top
of what are you doing on top of uh the
road right so what if I just make the
whole thing a
road that would work too
right what are you
doing golden super
NOA yeah he's being emotional
just's happy someone's finally helping
him with this
island
oops
there something we could talk
about I actually have a
topic
that let's try if
I should talk about it I want to talk
about it
though
oh
[Music]
um I'll just I'll just just stop me when
I get to
deep I don't want to go too
deep
okay
so it's probably going to get clipped
but uh yesterday I was just like going
through my channel looking at BS and
stuff and and I went to my shorts and I
saw um you know generally the shorts
that I uploaded on my break uh the
algorithm wasn't too nice to them
but that's okay the most latest one
however has
280,000
views the one with the gotcha and I was
like H I wonder why that one I guess the
algorithm just randomly blessed and I
think that's it
really um and I guess also like the
important thing with shorts is
that you can't choose the thumbnails
still they still haven't implemented you
know the ability to choose thumbnails so
right now you just got to get lucky or
you you can kind of plan it out I guess
if you know at what time of the 60
seconds the fil gets
chosen yeah mysterious but
um where are the
mushrooms uh that one kind of did really
well and uh I'm I'm happy about that but
I was wondering H I wonder if cuz I
didn't pay attention the past two weeks
if like
um any any video was doing better than
the others I didn't know if this was
like a a recent spurt in views or if it
was a constant achievement over time so
I wanted to see so check the comments to
get any hints if all the comments are
recent or something but no the comments
were like all like scattered over the
past two weeks and then I noticed when
I'm scrolling for the comments there's a
lot a lot of comments who are in a
weirdly aggressive and unnecessarily
obsessive
way uh complaining about the
censorship I just want to quote so you
understand how unnecessarily obsessed
these people are with the censorship I
quote this is the first time I've ever
seen a video blurring hats that just
seems so unnecessary and
silly why even blur the hands very
unnecessary why censor your hand
everyone knows you're white and everyone
has white what does that even
mean so there were like a lot of these
kind of
comments and they seem like people who
don't watch my streams a lot uh but that
doesn't matter I think they watch
YouTubers probably every now and then I
would think or they really just found
the the um short random
but um I think generally even when it's
not in an aggressive way uh
because I I get it I partially totally
get it I get both
sides
um like the reasoning of why why are we
doing this so generally I want to make
one thing clear I'm just following the
rules of my
company
um and I'm fine with whatever because I
generally I'm not really the type of
YouTuber who keeps thing things very
immersive am I right but others do
others want to do that and
so I will admit it's not very immersive
to show a life to the avatar on on the
screen and then show like a real
hand uh no wait I have to sell
something um it's not really immersive
I'm definitely breaking a lot of walls
all the time
time
yeah but that's that's that in itself
like breaking walls is not against our
rules but like I guess there's like
certain uh certainly certain
boundaries and uh I want to I want to
like just this is just a friendly like
explanation of what you could consider
and what makes it maybe more
understandable
of why we
uh don't show our hands or so um imagine
let's
say yeah I'm I'm white I'm white so it's
not a big surprise that I'm white we all
know I'm white but let's imagine someone
maybe doesn't have a skin tone that
matches too well with their Avatar and
let's say showing using gloves wasn't so
normal here whole life let's say it
would become more and more uh expected
to show your hands and then maybe that
maybe one person who doesn't have that
skin tone would be pressured and
wouldn't be able to show it that the way
that others would do and then you kind
of put in a different in a difficult
situation yeah for me it doesn't matter
I guess cuz pretty matching but for
others it might not be so matching and
uh of course it also has to do with like
safety uh I it may sound crazy but there
are a lot of really obsessed people out
there who will look at the hands and try
to like count moles or
whatever uh people go overboard you know
uh so it is a thing it has to do with
safety too
um and yeah so that's some reasons and
then actually I guess people perceive it
as my hand but the hand that was pulling
all the gcha was not my hand it was
actually in this case the manager's hand
and it doesn't let's put my safety my
privacy my whatever all aside okay you
may wonder she's not a vtuber why do you
need to hide the hand of the manager and
I questioned that too but but um who am
I to endanger the safety and privacy of
my manager um who's helping me who's
going out of the way to help me with my
video you know um yeah maybe it's like
an unnecessary amount of censoring but
in the end like you know she's a she's a
manager she's Anonymous she's a private
person she's not a public person like me
so let's keep her safe uh and
yeah it's for our privacy and for for
and for our safety you have no idea how
crazy some people out there are they
will they could also like look at the
codes so I was trying to keep um in
another video in the in the crap video
as well it was also both of us and I U
my code my own hand was visible and my
code was visible and I was trying to get
that sensor too because codes definitely
are
uh probably like that that would be a a
way of finding someone you
know so you know and in the end I still
also totally get the argument of like
let's not break the immersion I think
that's an important Point like it's kind
of weird to show a real hand not that
the glove makes it any better
though that doesn't make it any better
and it is kind of like restraining me in
creativity uh sometimes and like the
streams I can do because with gloves I
can't do certain things I want to do a
uh Tua stream what's that called what's
tun in English again H yeah nail
polishing is kind of dead Pottery yeah I
want to do Pottery I want to do a
pottery stream but I don't think I can
do it with
gloves cuz you got to feel you got to
feel the
wet material
yeah anyway I just I don't know I was
readed out by those comments um like
obsessing so hard over the censoring
when that's really not the point of the
video why are you making such a big deal
out of it but if you want an explanation
here are several reasons why we do this
there you go you're
welcome I mean it's mostly
a thing with
like whole life and Japanese YouTubers
like on the Indie side and on the
western side I think people don't care
so
much and I'm really I understand both
sides you know I I wish for the
creativity sake I could um have more
freedom with that but it's fine you know
would painted on gloves work I don't
know but I was thinking once I get
started with the pottery my hands will
be so like covered in the pottery stuff
that you won't see the skin anymore it's
basically a glove
right
maybe
maybe yeah covered in clay oh maybe that
maybe the clay will work as censorship
yeah I'll coat my hands and Clay right
off the bat how about that I don't
know or or weart the Stream blurry and
then once I get my hands full with Clay
then we can release the blurriness and
start pottering
seriously I'll think about it cuz I
really want to do that I've been
thinking about it for a long time now
what are we going to sell I I guess
we're going to sell fish or so they just
want me to sell anything really I guess
let's
sell
maybe a flounder a flounder or two
flounders you would get your keyboard
all
dirty yeah might need an assistant for a
pottery
stream okay I did all the
goals all the dailies y are they going
to ask me to sleep
yet smovie and
dark or maybe my mom cuz I think she
must have done Pottery many times in her
life and would
know she would know a thing or
two about
it my mommy also used to make paper did
I tell you that before and I I used to
help her when I was young I was really
young I was so
small must I must have been like seven
or eight or
so yeah we made
paper paper self-made paper it wasn't
like smooth and thin it was pretty thick
but it was kind of cool
oh self-made
paper my mom also used to make so much
soap we had so much soap and so much uh
like Shia
butter like creamy stuff that you yeah
use as like body lotion
basically why she Mak some much soap I
don't know she just had fun making soap
when you start making soap you can stop
you just can't
stop she used to do a lot of things like
crafting I mean she still does she still
cra craft a lot of
things she literally like you know has
her whole garden which is this whole
crafting Quest that she has taken upon
herself Fight
Club you don't talk about the fight club
dude leave this island now
does she make handles too maybe she made
one before but no that's not not her
thing she makes like a lot of food stuff
now like jam oh she made a jam she made
a raspberry jam that she gave to me that
I've been eating re recently which is so
yummy so good and then she'll make
like um like she will have like a huge
uh tomato Harvest and make like lots of
tomato soup and give tomato sauce and
give it to us me and my
[Music]
brother all kinds of
things like she she once had this walnut
tree which dropped like millions of
walnuts and made Walnut pesto out of it
and other other things but mostly I
think she mostly made Walnut
p and I love
pesto love pesto
man but she got sick of the walnuts cuz
that was just way too many
walnuts so I think she swore to herself
to never have walnuts
again she still makes a pistol out of
other things
whatever you can make pesto out of so
many
things not just the most common ones
like
basil
but a bonk and a bonk and a bonk and a
B classic basil is so yummy yeah I
freaking love basil pesto so
good I love all the pesto of the
world what of my daili destroy free
rocks catch free bugs s an item craft
one time collect free special D
Treasures didn't I say I would leave
this
island maybe I'll leave today but we're
at be now how expensive is it
now1
18,000 h
hm oh but okay I still don't have the
what's my rank what the
hell just one more trash
pile I get it you get into a flow
honestly I felt the same flow in pal
World although in pal world it was a bit
stronger cuz I didn't have anything else
that I felt like I should be
doing
um do you later get the the opportunity
to paint uh things like Furniture can I
make it black for example cuz my office
chair is
black this shelf kind of looks like it
would fit somewhere in but I don't have
a vase in my
[Music]
office but I should just I should just
build whatever and yeah just you know
I'm going to build this
well that oh that got my level up a lot
oh and I cooked up a new market so oh
that's fun oh cute Cypress chair bust up
bench what a whole [\h__\h]
building the
[\h__\h] take out sushi a car sign fire
hydrant vending machine
yo it doesn't even take that many
materials that's like a a free story
building I don't think that's realistic
for me to
build crazy
[\h__\h] this one I can f make let's make
this one
too it can
yeah
okay let me play some
things how big is
this who whoa whoa whoa whoo whoa whoa
whoo whoo it takes up like the whole
lot oh there we
go H I think I it should be like in the
back
oh Mommy was
listening I thought you didn't like
Yakuza but she likes Animal Crossing I
think or or stuff like that similar
stuff this is her kind of game finally
Yakuza has become more to her liking
wait I can use this space too I
forgot oh and now it would be by the
road so satisfaction up
uhhuh should it be like this or like
this oh yeah that makes sense maybe like
[Music]
here
okay
nice do the lamps also have to be there
no doesn't say anything about
satisfaction does it even help at all to
put lamps down I wanted to put them like
on the side of the
[Music]
road I know I'm not
counting but it's it's
fine the lights light up at the path at
night though okay they look
nice it almost looks like I counted how
many how much space is in
between let's see what did my Mommy say
though oh she says it's funny yeah
Yakuza always was
funny uh let's see about the path I
guess we could you know does it it
doesn't even cost money
right what if I make it like decorative
like
this
H it doesn't
work
why oh this
works does cost
money table in way so I can't put it on
top
no and how do I get rid of
it
[Music]
oh oh
okay I
see
H
H oh oh no that helps for the
satisfaction
right plus
69 uh yeah
okay oh I think I know what I'm going to
do going to put one more of these like
here and
here too bad it's all got to be like on
the
road but now we have 610 and 741 how was
how much was I supposed to
get
uh
uh uh uh
here uhhuh popularity is almost there
satisfaction is getting there too
I just want to get it to level one and
then we can leave
so I just need more stuff I just need
more stuff but I also need more
materials a more trees more
Stones fre the space
first oh yeah I guess
so
[Music]
uh go to the
sign
yes does it happen right
away oh we get a cut
scene woohoo you freaking did it savior
of our Island
canel small building
[Music]
m
y recycling area oh they made a
recycling area that should be the same
amount of resources as you would have
collected yourself before the land was
cleared uh if not more convenient right
worth checking every day okay you can
retrieve resources from The Collection
Point next to mosia the amount of
resources you can obtain will increase
as you clear out areas they can only be
Conn collected once a day though so
don't forget to swing by
okay it's like the the trash the Lost
items section in Animal
Crossing oo okay now we got to clear out
the great tree I probably still have
enough money for it
um I feel like it's a little bit of a
waste you know wait there's still some
trash I don't
think just
one I can't get up to be not
today but I want to wait for this one
I'll wait until be yeah I want to wait
oh oh but there's no barriers at all now
I thought
oh then we got them make some paths
oopsie
[Music]
uh wow you can zoom out so much okay
um which one did I use
there this
one not
sure okay let's make something
[Music]
maybe a smaller strip of
land
here
oops
and for the sake of consistency or
whatever we make one up the here too it
it really bothers me that I can't use
the same path as the one that's here by
default yeah you can change if you need
later yeah and then I'll make one more
here it's really like a city Builder
now crazy
uh how about one
here
perfect it's pretty
good
okay
wow look at that City scaping almost
looks like it was done by a professional
fre rocks
done oh
wow my paing already better than yours
at Five Star Island okay wow thank you
for the compliment wow I'm
flattered I'm FL did you just randomly
Place
everything oh DIY AB
[Music]
blueprint stick out your for
nla you're so bow bow you're so
BX I just want want to be
youri I forgot the
rest I never sag it
fully skiy zmer
skiy you you can't blame me though cuz
English isn't my first language and I'm
just trying to learn the language and if
my colleagues learn teach me this kind
of English then it's not my fault I'm
just like a baby picking up
words those English speaking Naturals
you can blame them not
me Advent and
their their Zoomer language
man Babble T to picks up whatever comes
your
way BBD Golden Crown
wow but bibo speaks it like it's her
natural uh uh her first language does
she ever struggle with English you're
saying it's not her first language but
does
she like even if it's not your first
language sometimes you just get raised
by two
languages
it is her oh okay who who wrote that it
wasn't English is her main okay there
you go there you go she definitely seems
to me like
a not natural what's the
word
huh native thank you so
much I'm definitely not a native I'm
just the Mo speaker of
end you sound native to me thank you I
mean I'm definitely you know FL enough
oo nice in English to communicate every
pretty much everything I want to say and
Stream in that
language
Japanese
too makes me pretty op I got to
say
n
n you're native and you're 50% briish
well if you say it then it must be
true
speed popularity let's go okay I think
tomorrow we can reach the level of
satisfaction oh inventory full and um
yeah all the goals for getting to level
one no let me just sell an item
oh yeah right inventory full never
mind what is it SE yeah cuz it does
Animal Crossing for real man it's it's a
mystery it's a
riddle that I like to fiddle with period
oh what was I going to do i
s um you can have
this yeah Daily's done oo the Sun is
setting so
nicely
oh not hold is
this I guess it's a cuz I don't have
anything else I guess it's a shared
toilet
okay um if I craft things does that also
count as things in my
[Music]
inventory yeah hey I can build this
[\h__\h] free story
building oh my God what the
hell it doesn't really look that nice
though o but it gives me so much EXP be
cream armchair
M nice nice flowers white coffee truck I
want to make that oh and that pool table
I want to put in my office even though I
officially don't have one oo that's nice
we're not office complex flammable oil
drum commercial kit commercial if we get
another room we can make the
kitchen oh that's good that's good I
just I couldn't F okay oh
okay okay
[Music]
okay I'm guessing uh these buildings
they bring a lot
of like satisfaction or whatever it
is I want to make the food truck for
sure oh but I don't have the materials I
need yeah I need a lot of stuff now I
use it all
up
took them up there can I take it from my
storage what I just
built oops
uh
no ah come on that's
annoying damn it okay whatever we'll
just
sleep we'll just
sleep good kids go to sleep at
night when it gets
dark wrapping things up yep yep y yep y
yep yep yep you can store your items
mhm
is this my
storage yeah okay
uh where's the building ah ah over
here does this
work do I have to switch
something how do I
take
here uh uhuh okay
uhhuh uh you can
have
cheeseburger uh these
okay wow this looks
amazing okay I should be I should be a
city
Builder we should play some City
I want to like
these although yeah let's put it here it
will cover like some nice view though oh
it doesn't even
work oh oh oh
oh
oh eh
okay I feel like it makes more sense on
this path if it was looking to the left
cuz that's kind of like the main PA but
okay we'll put it here that's visible
from this view it's kind of
nice and a vending
machine next to the toilets give the
toilets or maybe in front of
it but no the guest laser put it here
and I can still move this right grab it
and put it more in the
front
wonderful woohoo oh y now we only got to
clear out the great
[Music]
tree good morning sunshine it's a
beautiful morning it's a beautiful day
to get some trash out of the
way
I couldn't think of a better day than
today 20 membership gifts thank you so
much
ouch thank
you so many new
eggs or also I guess those are also
given to membership renewals right
members that were members before and
then continue their job at
kfp nice nice nice nice okay the economy
growing
stuns stronger than ever with so many
streaming
hours kfps
economy and work ethic everything is
growing
blooming like like a flower field in
Spring
well we're already at B I doubt that we
can go to a yeah unless we waiting that
with day that's okay I have the
money oh level 10 oh
okay nowh oh what' you come
from oh [\h__\h] oh sh oh [\h__\h]
okay lots of money don't forgot to check
to rec ah
true wonder what they
have oh ah it's just like General
materials I thought it would be like
actual
items but this is fine
too makes sense uh oh yeah
um I wanted more but I don't know I
guess I don't give that much exp but it
doesn't matter I wanted more of the
parasols where is it
ah oh materials
do we're almost level 10
though I need I need more more stuff I
need more
[Music]
stuff I already cleared out everything
so those um like paper materials I can't
get much more oh I guess they are in
other places
too but it's just plus
one for one trash
bag you can build something else I know
but that's not what I want to build I'm
picky I don't want to just
randomly build [\h__\h] I want things with a
purpose got to keep things organized you
know that's the W
way motorcycle
recipe
[Music]
oh a a
suitable vehicle for aumer like me I am
a believe believe it you better believe
it they don't
believe you don't seem to
believe this is such a different stream
right now man this is I'm enjoying it
right now I'm kind of vibing I'm
chilling it's relaxing but it's such a
different
game 10 what I got
10,000 wa from that
bottle hey yo that
bottle that was that was some crazy cash
in
there St one more
day well if it's your Island it start
motivating you with all these all these
possibilities and once you get started
cleaning it's just like in real life I
can't stop I can't stop it's nice to see
everything become
pretty in the beginning I was just like
M because they were talking so much just
shut up and let me do the thing I don't
need so much explanation I know what
there's to do I played many of these
games I am a
gamer
where are
you golden
flutter can you use the butterflies for
crafting something or should I sell them
too you win quid let's
go ooh large Japanese
rug
why are some rugs so expensive
guys sometimes I see rug stores like
carpet stores they're so expensive but
they're always like these specific
rugs I'm guessing they're
handmade that's probably it but I'm not
going to spend
3,000 bucks on the
carpet
when I don't even like the
pattern I don't like any of
those they look usually they look like
so
Oriental maybe now you get an idea of
what I'm talking
about I really don't like them they
don't fit the style that I'm trying to
achieve which is The Great
Gatsby I want to live in the The Great
Gatsby
apartment house room
whatever we carpet should I make one
I've done a blanket I've done a uh a
towel Next Step carpet but honestly I
feel like like a bath mat or so is
possible
uh oh
wait I have the cutest
idea what about an uh what do you call
those entrance
mats don't worry I won't put a fullon
anime face on it
but what if the entrance mat says like
kfp or something has the kfp logo or
yeah doorm yeah door
M that's so
cute
chicken
D that would be again a
first as always wa the trend Setter uh
let me catch some fish actually really
quick so I can do the da what other
daily is even giving me
nothing well like completing them is it
giving me something I haven't noticed
I'm not I don't want to step on you guys
it's just you know you got to mark your
[Music]
territory a
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] wa
squid let's let's go I can take that
with me to Hawaii and use it for my
squid Blaster
attack i
w the mailman will know where to deliver
the merch
to oh yeah this is the this is the house
of that whole life
fan the vtuber
fan no I I would make it something
that's like not too crazy looking so you
can actually use it and not feel
embarrassed my mailman already
knows did he look inside your
packages he shouldn't be doing
that wait did you guys say something
about the butterflies and did you say
something about the
dailies I'll look now I I'm I'm watching
I'm watching the coms did you say
butterfly
sell they's get money
okay fly like a
butterfly
okay said sell on items so we'll do
that what about these corals as well
this water stuff sell those
two I guess the crafting stuff really
only uses those items that you see on
the bottom
right okay really oh then
oh like this brings a lot of money and
this damn okay if I sell all that that
really I can sell all of this without
concern
golden
flutter really okay yeah welcome mats is
kind of a cute
[Music]
idea infinite
money just some items are useful later
on like pearls
okay
uh Don staff is good to keep oh okay the
Don scuttler D Mosk and so on oh my
voice I need to drink the
tea golden Great Horn
10,000 man I should go out and collect
some
bugs
[Music]
Dam damn golden
Supernova Golden Crown
butterfly salmon The Flounder all right
yo wait can I convert the doo box to
real money
though otherwise it's not a good
equivalent to those other ways of making
money yeah is it a one to one
conversion and talk to m m where are you
before they sent me to sleep m m m
m
m wasn't he usually at the
tree
yes we can talk to the Dolph okay okay
okay
uh M I love
you got to tell muku every day you love
him so that he knows he must be
reassured of his
Beauty ah shut
up
no I wonder if you can get different
insects at
night he saying he's a he's from my
imagination he'll
disappear I have to think about him
every day otherwise he disappears yeah
yeah
there are fireflies different fish
definitely really
really
[Music]
okay day
six okay now we'll clear the other area
[Music]
also are we not level one
yet let me check
that unrated what are we missing the
great tree okay okay
fine let's
[Music]
go can we get to a can we make it extra
cheap why didn't I it was already B
yesterday why did I not end up cleaning
it
up oh
well what's another
day of grinding on this
island just another extra stream
probably tapped onto my
playr 3 months later we'll still be
playing this
game this is the
game for me like you can get so lost in
this cuz like the the business for
example the the confector or whatever
that was that it's just a menu but this
is like a whole island you can run
around in you can build things and all
that so it really feels like a separate
game especially the more time you spend
on it without going back to the main St
you kind of forget that you were playing
a different game
originally it's weird
you like the side management
quests I mean I like this too but it's
like what what was I actually here
for oh yeah right I needed level 10
that's why I didn't do it okay I'll
craft them up now I have some materials
again oh wait we should pick up
the this stuff
too
got
okay
I played so much baseball and baseball
was the
thing
interesting okay actually if as much
money as I have now it might be worth to
upgrade the bat it was like 50 bucks
right at
50,000 now I have so much money I feel
like yell did you see the materials on
the other side that I can't reach yet
man
Dam
okay yeah the other things don't seem as
necessary how much is the next level
150,000
H okay I would do it if I didn't need
to clear out the
area over there that's still costing
some money I don't know how much I
didn't look
but I got to save some so
now can we build another huge thing
although we don't have to we're almost
level 10 can I build this now the white
coffee
truck no I can't
[\h__\h] I can build another Public public
bathroom I could build nope I
can't it doesn't have to be for in
outside we can build the pool table that
I will probably use
eventually might not place it yet but
made mannequin Fountain white scooter
telephone box the telephone box would be
cute
box I mean who uses this nowadays but
it's still nice to see on the
streets still nice to see
it oh okay we're level
10 build a house of maim what there's
muchim my
house uh let's put it here if I can oh I
can where's the this is the the
front
nice
okay it's time
to clear out that area forever no more
returning
trash
25,000 very cheap very cheap Oh What A
Deal am I right we love a good deal and
we love to go to The Next Star level one
woohoo guys it's already been 5 and half
hours
uh we just need mother to contact the
resort review board I better talk to him
about it okay
battle I'm faster I'm so much faster
woo still no aim
though wow oh it looks so much nicer
that's that's really
nice the before after is pretty
[Music]
amazing almost feels like a different
Island I just got here oh welcome good
morning sunshine nice to nice to see who
finally made your way here too nice to
see you decided to come over today h
just kidding were we able to go over
here before I don't think
so oh look who decided to show
[Music]
up how to fish how to
fish how to
fish it's literally right there let me
fish maybe I need to be up there hey y
wa what is that what's that golden
trash
Oh that was some rare stuff
oh oh there's a lot of golden stuff here
damn real glass yeah the glass is
amazing we don't have much glass and
that like weird technical stuff we don't
have a lot of that either only
two yeah I kind of can see myself doing
this a lot uh off screen I might
actually enjoy
it but in my brain it like totally
overlaps of pal
world I don't know if I can do
both I wanted
both okay
hi let's do this forget power
world obviously the the Gathering
materials and the building and there's
some fighting that the only thing that's
missing is
catching uh pal
[Music]
H it's a mix it's a mix of not only Both
Worlds but like all the
[Music]
worlds
t
we can build a giant skyscraper or
Cabaret Club we're not building a
cabaret Club on my resort island okay we
are a pure innocent
Island only for the say so ones
oh look at
him what that is that a fedora that I
see you didn't even tip
it a cat
cafe I want to can we make it a cat
Island can we craft cats and then place
them all
over check it out check this out check
this out hey yo
whoa not bad right am I right or am I
right
mhm
yep
the size of the main plaza the
cleanliness and the level of
satisfaction all seem to meet standards
excellent truly excellent I hereby
acknowledge dle Island as a onear
res let's
go
certified the item offerings at Mat
yosia have expanded new exclusive M
yosia furnit are available place the
island will increase the amount of
resources at the collection point the
next day oh thanks for the rain thank
you small burnable waste small non
burnable wood working area okay this is
woohoo still got ways to go before we're
at five stars let's keep at it and here
are the promised funds from the resort
review board please put it to good use
oh we get money from that
too to be recognized as a two star
resort here the conditions you must
fulfill please make these your next goal
M clear the light house clear out the
hills and 5,000 2,000
okay seems very
manable
yeah oh another 10,000 okay thank you
oh ah it's actually real
money I'd rather you use this money
however you want the more prosperous
this island becomes the more I can repay
you it would mean a lot to me if you
could accept this much for now do okay
okay
oh all right if we want to be a two star
resort we're going to need to open up
the hills and the lighthouse I recommend
starting with The Hills first since the
closer and relatively affordable to
clear I couldn't get to the hills up
until now because of all the garbage in
the way but it looks like Kon took care
of it now
a
[Music]
okay my my fingers are shivering I want
to clean the island
up I'm
shaking I want to I want to throw the
trash away I want to punch it I want to
clean the island I want to make paths I
want to build
stuff got so excited I have to spit out
some
fum wonderful
wonderful oh boy and dealing all this
garbage is so going to be
R me too me too I feel the
same are you again you want to fight
let's have a real fight don't always
send your little
boys this ain't no playground for kids
you know we're an all adult resort but
say so
adults okay yeah yeah that's fine that's
fine let's fight fight me fight me fight
me what do you want huh huh what do you
want what do you want Try Me Try Me
Oh uhuh he's leaving again
okay
oh I'm ready for elen the ring
DLC
oh [\h__\h] I actually
[Music]
am I didn't get hit and I dodged in the
right moments even though you have to
like you have to kind of like do it all
earlier cuz the the movements are so
delayed both the dodging and the hitting
is so delayed and it takes so much
time
goodbye goodbye
man with the catg
girl
girlfriend Fight for Your Land some
areas on dondoka island are currently
occupied by the wasb CL in order to
reclaim the land you'll have to defeat
them in battle if your health gets
reduced to zero then you'll be sent home
but you can challenge them as many times
as you want by reentering there oh
they're no biggie for me I don't think
I'll ever
fail the hill s are alive with the sound
of
[Music]
garbage yeah oh hippity hop hippity
hoppity you are now my
property silver Hopper
[Music]
cute they they censored the
Cockroach
OMG ooh really be
or the
grasshopper you a scorpion yeah we got
to collect those we don't want
our our
Resort guests step on the Scorpions
wait I'm supposed to leave this island
now but let me just clear this up one
time just one
time just this
once cuz it's like you know it would be
a waste to leave now without having it
cleaned
up and then I'm looking forward to more
story I'm looking forward to the yapping
Bring It
On rank
e this is such a nice
area would be good to place like some
little Villas here and and look at that
that's what I saw before holy [\h__\h] that
mountain of trash is all purple it's
like a volcano of
trash
so like
a like a trash dungeon is in there and
the boss fight will be a trash
monster a trash Cano and maybe that's
really what it's supposed to
be that's why all the trash is coming
back each day on in the night time the
trash volcano spits out the trash and it
flies all over okay that's actually a
nice
explanation not realistic but uh in this
world totally realistic not IRL just in
this world it's realistic makes
sense
goofy
goofy goofy what does goopy sound
like actually have the daili even done
if I sell something to
matoshi matoshi
hey what's
up I can't can't recreate that if you
guys write it down like that I I
wouldn't know how to say
it oh wait the bugs should I keep the
dondle bugs too and the what about the
Ruby
or Y
pil
fosil sell the bgs keep the keep the ore
okay that's what I
F oh my God all the money we can upgrade
one more time on on the
bat
okay okay okay okay I'm going to I'm
going to leave this island I'm going to
leave this island now and I'll never
come back just kidding I
will what if I leave now and I come back
like basically like does it continue
exactly where I left off like here now
at this time with these daily is
completed or time freezes okay okay okay
okay
perfect that's all I needed to
know just this one thing before I forget
it o right about
here wow oh wow it's coming
together it's just one thing
just one
thing where
going okay I'm leaving to
Hawai
o we could convert them but we also kind
of need the money here on the island too
also
10,000 no wait what why is it why is
there yen
conversion why is there a y conversion
the doco Box 10,000 doco Buck $100 is
what this is saying right 10,000 to BU
that's really not
much yeah it's a bad rate we ever get a
better
rate
oh you think because it might we go to
Japan again too that makes
sense sorry guys I know I was gone for
like a whole freaking week but I hope
the video turned out good do we get to
watch it oh oh maybe we'll get to watch
it at
revolve find dolphin at the beach and
she whiskey away to D okay oh God this
is so weird this is so weird being
back this so weird feel so wrong like
what am I doing here who am I what is
this
place
let's see revolve was here let's take a
taxi try making a party healing fruit
salad
[Music]
okay
I'm going to be snacking for the first
time
today I'm having kit
cat
fore fore
fore
fore foreign
speech
speeech a
oh that would be nice to see him
again
[Music]
foree
foree foreign
fore fore
foreign
[Music]
yumy yeah I'm going to make the fruit
salad oh hi
K with
you oh with
her thank you free sample let's go
mm
mhm
mhm oh yummy kit cat it's a normal basic
one by the
way I just prefer the basic chocolate
not the special flavors mostly
mhm it's so
good okay so my fruit and I saw that the
fruit was also usable for um some stuff
over there where we made the
tea but if this fruit salad is so famous
then we shall use it here do I have
enough fruit though ah he can make the
tea
too
M okay but yeah I I don't have
I can't find so much fruit oh he needs
passion fruit where the hell would I
find passion
fruit well he needs so much coconut more
coconut and a passion
fruit mysterious
fruit also in the palm
[Music]
trees oh
okay where the bananas also from
there
and ah wait how do I gift it probably
just said how but
yes uh here have um this
beautiful plumia bouquet flowers you
love flowers don't you you're
welcome Tomy I'll give you some flowers
too cuz that's all I
got oh he likes
it they're often used in Lay but they
also look nice and a bouquet flowers
really do LIF Spirits
a I'm glad he appreciates it and Isn't
it nice how cutie is chilling at the bar
with
her they must have done that
purposefully do you like flowers you oh
he didn't like it much I don't his his
rank barely
improved these two like it let's
remember
that uh so can
I
small that was it that was the small
talk that was very small that small talk
was very
[Music]
small I'm not to you K
to it's not working okay ah they want to
do stuff hi
ah did you know you can make friends and
other and way other than saying hi just
the other day I gave some coffee to this
sleep sleep his security guard and we
became Aloha
link doing little
favors if you ordered more food here
thank you and I might get along
better so
difficult H you're hell of a saleswoman
here this one's on the house for our
friendship I love this
stuff who thank
you fighter fighing that's an upgrade to
my current
one
yo what a Chad what a Chad
move
yeah
nice
[Music]
Tas okay but like what about links they
just happen on its own when I'm here or
do I have to sleep or how do these
conversations
happen these proper
conversations I don't
remember once you reach certain levels
[Music]
okay where we go
oh the bond Bingle by going around oh
okay okay okay Bond Bingle oh someone
got himself 15 friends yeah Yahoo it
you're linking up a storm huh we should
go CH again and Revol when you got time
how's kute you
[Music]
son that's probably the only reason
you're messaging me be
real
uh is Julie close
by where's uh how's Julie's place marked
is it this no that's Fortune
[Music]
exchange oh this
one I'll go there and see if I can
afford anything
new let's
go
D [\h__\h]
yeah once ordered the wrong size once
W oh wait that's a photo
[Music]
spot no stamp rally is being filled
up wait that was a free magazine wasn't
[Music]
it let have this
guy
gained 15 kg by going to the US you
could have also eaten less but I guess I
hear all the time that there the
ingredients are also just not very
healthy nice did you see
that like we're playing domino
for real same reaction
[Music]
man mandated
cor known as The Freshman 15 that
students gain weight in their first year
of
University
why why does it happen when you go to
university
though how come my father's a uni
student you don't have any money cuz
America takes so much [\h__\h] money for
education so you don't have enough food
for food uh money for
food where you got all that money for
food huh where you got that from
huh
stress don't remind
eating junk food ah yeah cuz yeah the
thing is like junk food is like one of
the healthiest foods you can get and
then you just keep on eating [\h__\h]
junk
food it's like so so so bad such a
endless cycle of Hell
E I could do it if I knew about it but
if I don't know about it then how can I
do it what a question huh
what I never St or went to school for
any of this I just taught myself how
little by little over time I could do
more than I
couldn't but that still leaves me with
gaps in my knowledge no matter how
skilled I am there are some jobs I just
can't figure out because I don't have
the right
education because in
America never mind but the last thing I
want to go want to to do is go back to
school I'm not AF with people it didn't
work out well before I have to keep
learning though I need to know
everything there is about engineering
and craftsmanship there are books but
they're expensive
well hold on does that mean all you need
is a little money and you could make
even more stuff kasuga no kasuga stop
you have to learn to not support
everybody financially and
physically people are also capable to do
things on their own you shouldn't spoil
everybody and fund their [\h__\h]
education and life and Resort
Islands kasuga no no bad kasuga bad
I could definitely improve if you gave
me a little money or big money oh all
right let's go I'm a sucker for helping
people no I'll give you the funds you
study up and buy whatever else you need
to expand it's a win-win wi what no I
don't feel right about that listen your
tuneups and on our weapons have saved
our asses out there I wouldn't think
twice about investing in your talents
what do you say I won't force you to do
anything just consider it are you really
sure yeah don't think of it as a gift I
see how good you are at this stuff and I
want to double down okay thanks that's
really interesting of you I promise I'll
make sure you get more than your money's
worth yeah but like if I fund her
education she should at least like make
all those weapons for
free
man first I need a basic lineup of
textbooks do you think you could cover
that
text
books why do I get
them if you have cash to spare disc oh I
just give her the money and she buys
them 90% discount 90% discount I I would
accept
oh
wooho textbooks are
expensive I've
heard so I've
heard
ah
520 is what she wants no no no what 520
out of 2,000 but I haven't given her
anything what but she already have
520 I guess I can give her enough to
give her one level
up
H sounds about
right from the first upgrades I
diduh wait so if I put money into the
upgrades that also goes towards
this oh but that's uh if that's the case
that's uh
fair
oh I don't have to give the money
directly to
her damn
it um you got something W that's so cute
that that surf Surfer board
cute do you oh we need this Sunrise
miracas mar mar all these electric
Maracas no I can't make them I can make
these ones
though hell
yeah don't don't don't don't don't don't
don't scre SC SC SC
we should play sler Spire again
sometimes nice 26 okay plus 10 easy also
now we have uh fire element on
it
m Wicked poison
sickle let's break it
go yeah
yeah
and something new for a
hero uh
uhhuh
I don't have the
materials I've got
[Music]
nothing that's all that really makes
sense right now
right uh upgrade
still
uh ge dancer right the sunrise Maracas
we can upgrade
them um and it was like just choose
whatever so we have a lot of iron
fragments yeah maybe like this plus
eight plus eight is pretty damn
good do you like the new classes switch
yes I do like them they're cute they got
cute outfits and yeah some new fun moves
I like the
variety pirot
dancer although Tommy moves like a
gremlin now though Gremlin
Goblin let's play it fa and give him the
same
upgrade so you can add
Brands maybe next time we don't we don't
have to go crazy just yet uh oh yeah
right what about the this jet surfboard
that we
have
wait is it being does the jet surfboard
get used as a base for any other
one
no that's so cute that's ice
cream that looks cute it's just a leaf
Nar then I'm going to or is is Chata
sorry sorry sorry is this better than
what I have no it's minus six okay then
I'll just upgrade the one he
has oh
yeah
oh so many
materials okay plus seven here you
go
sick surfboard with a rocket on it could
do some serious damage
mhm that's not a that's not a surfboard
anymore but okay let's let him dream
let's let's just let him play with his
toys burn food
H for the chickens youing at what you
looking at don't even get me started
don't don't don't even get me started
hey now uh currently what's our quest to
meet with the dude right but where I'm
going to
you ah what do you want caterpillars
squir me
squirms I'm so
strong
W 194 damn Tommy so so strong now for me
yes for you are you
hungry I'm actually surprisingly not
hungry yet but I do have a
sand in the
[Music]
fridge yes oh I could catch him you
actually look a little bit like a Pon
so I
could I could but you're low level
aren't you I guess I I'll give you I'll
do you the
honor can't say no
that we can learn from each other am I
not good enough
run of Dreams BL
blah are he's so excited to be with
[Music]
me he's
cute he's so cute he's so
happy
okay now we take a little shortcut of
the taxi
[Music]
oopsie I even upgraded our weapons
yo taking good care of my
team just one more side of Kit
cat
ooh from enemies to friends take a fres
be off the
grill to itan the whole world is
friend want some of
[Music]
this is your time for
sleep thank you for watching Goodbye Oh
it's already 10 p.m.
home do sir do your
work thanks for watching maybe
tomorrow I'll do the Super Chat
reading possibly
[\h__\h]
um they have a New York accent I
wouldn't even be able to tell
oh here we
go what's
up it's good we wiing we're besties
now
you should have you needed to be there
you know crazy
story
yeah it like a dragon Dam he got the
best sponsorship
ever
everybody wants her not is what I'm
feeling she does stay so far in the back
quiet what's
wrong
got oh yeah right he was like the
[Music]
P will he be an official part of the
team
[Music]
isn't it the the Chinese
people they got some funky ass t-shirts
yo
for they're also purple and
pink
I'm excited to fight Bring It On got
some new weapons that I need to try
out oh where too I'm
[Music]
curious
oh everybody wants
her popular woman this
there I told you
[Music]
everybody and everybody for different
reasons
[Applause]
let's have
on let's
go we're such a weird group but then
look at K he's so normal he needs a
funky job
too oh
yeah actually while we're all here
together
we're all together right I would
[Music]
get l o
e oh oh oh oh it's going for it
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that evasion did not help me at
all
yo came out of nowhere and I at least
blocked
twice what are you doing what are you
doing magic rage uhoh oh oh oh oh oh
oh okay we need some big AOE damage one
enemy one my enemy area get Gnarly is
the one that blinds people but I wonder
did it also it didn't do much damage
right let's do a cresting collider maybe
it depends how the people are
standing bad quite bad quite
bad this one could get could can't
all potentially four let's
try yeah free okay or or two only
two okay oh I got money for pound mates
now I wouldn't really say I could waste
it on that I'm good I'll I'll be fine
enemy
area but around around
me
oh no around those enemies n i I'll
start with him I'll just do some normal
stuff
or while you're here this
[Music]
[Applause]
proximity
yes the others without health bars are
in the fight oh yeah I I didn't feel
like they
were I didn't even register those people
looked like bystanders
has oh no she
[Music]
didn't for this this one I choose the
one in the front
right this could get
to not the
best FR
what the ankle
sucks is this is this worth
it oh that was the boss who was
guarding
ouch
[\h__\h]
go go shake those hips shake those tatas
and those my rockas the way he walk she
walks in the background is so
[Music]
good [\h__\h] I can't block
[\h__\h] I'm so
bad as always when it comes to
kid I show my skills more
oh there's something new tell a big guy
forby with a frozen big eye might even
leave that quiny stunned what the [\h__\h]
are you talking about what do that
mean what do that
mean what does that
mean lady Bros
included some M Water uh I think it
might be time to heal what do you think
guys is it time to heal
or we let someone else
[Music]
heal close by ah tell me it's close if I
walk like over
here then he could get healed too I
might do
[Music]
that okay
oh
uh
frog what are you
doing why are you being like this
whatever whatever I'll take
it it didn't go that way at
all it totally changed
Direction y why would you do
that oh [\h__\h] I I
missed damn
it thank you for everything you're
amazing that sounds like you leaving kfp
but you're not
[Music]
right
who which one's the
boss but I wish they would write the
names also like cuz uh if I just look at
them on the battle thing
uh they all the same
grunt so it's hard to find the boss
sometimes I've had that I felt the same
way in other situations too but anyway
uh attack normally on
him true right no zly thank
you and yeah to help us but still like
on the on the first view especially when
they wear such similar clothes as well
ouch
oh nice
back tell a big guy
goodbye can I do that on
you what the hell was
that kind of crazy wait he's gone the
the boss is dead that was too easy I
didn't even use Tag Team
yet maybe we can take both in one
go wasn't the back one in the line too
come on what a
[Music]
scam I just didn't
he was the main target for me don't run
away you little
[\h__\h] you are going to die
now you will regret everything you've
ever done in your
life cuz these
four crazy
hippos are going all in on
you the bully becomes the bullly nice
finish finishing P
chetto yes we're hippos oh there's more
oh okay oh okay well is there also
another bus probably
not they're all the same and they're
wait they're so close
[Music]
together damn it she doesn't really have
those
the right attacks in my opinion for this
situation it's okay it's okay it's
okay all right I want I wanted some big
AE yeah would have been good now now
they're all
[Music]
scattered good for you good for
you
I don't know I don't
know ouch oh [\h__\h]
ichun oh car please don't kill him don't
be the cause of my death
now anybody close uh
no wa I could get Tommy
maybe I didn't get him damn it
oh thank God no he's
paralyzed and now he's getting grilled
by the back of Ian's
surfboard
um yeah yeah keep on walking over there
very
good oh wait that other one that was
that was good that was really good two
people died and one got big damage
to all according to Kaku I
got let's do some soul
capturing
yeah
yeah I got that one figured out pretty
much oh she's not doing so long on
your that would be probably good if I go
closer to
K coconut
s cute o refreshing very
refreshing
okay okay
okay dangerous I'm should heal
maybe
yeah maybe maybe this
one no no
we I was going to block
those I don't know what that means
partially that sounds like
japanes what are they
saying m
[Music]
line of
enemies like this wait the front one for
this one right what about
this but does that still break his guard
or do I have to do it on him to break
his guard
the back one e no doesn't look like it
to
me judging by how the line
go on say come on fight me okay should
break his guard even if he's T yeah but
this one he moves around he's going to
mess up everything again isn't
he yeah he knows when I'm targeting him
that bastard go don't change your
formation okay okay okay go defeated
nice um we need another coconut shower
maybe but I wish ah Tommy is here all
right all right all right all
right so healing
wonderful
oh thank God yo that takes so much
damage she's on the brink of dying the
whole
[Music]
time no no no no please be nice
and something
good damn it
wait a
second
power oh he's weak to that a that's a
good area that's a good area that's that
could get all
four let's go they don't give me much of
a t yeah for
real they really don't but that was good
that was a big one
big
ouch it's okay it's better as long as
you don't try to hit
chos leave chos alone she's been for too
much to
fight nice second
one maybe we can finish
it ah you want to survive with one on
HP I think
not
y that was a long fight wait we got 300
Oh I thought 360,000
okay
insane but we got some level
UPS Frank a fire breaking ooh looking
forward to that our reservation might be
[Music]
soon nobody gives a good answer
everybody's just doing what they're
told h
try I like it when they get violent and
have no
mercy he was going to kill you really
people have made this joke
before oh okay you going to pay or
what I think aan should
pay yeah I know he never killed yeah he
should though he
should
in the meantime you should be prepared
in case the G ganu comes back really
it's the least I can do to
help oh I really appreciate it I'll get
ready and come back soon as possible
great I'll be right
here except for when he
does no telling what might happen I
should grab what I need then hurry back
to
H uh what do I need
they are they just giving me some a
chance to like prep some more gear I
think I'm fine though I'll do this fight
though
better I'll check it out
then I wanted to get a AOE
attack but hey look at our level I don't
even need to use
skills eat the
wall eat the dirt of the
wall it's yummy so try it don't be so
picky try some new things in
[Music]
life oh [\h__\h] I missed
okay you're welcome
byebye he's in love all right what what
could we upgrade
um how much money do I have this I think
this is still too
expensive 140,000 I mean maybe I could
afford it but then all my money is gone
running clothes I already have that at
least maybe not for everybody
but Prince Co Aloha shirt maybe is an
investment how much was the running
shirt
84 and that's probably not
[Music]
better possibly second
floor oh yeah you got that rest from
okay oh didn't I put it
on
let me look at the
shoes
Aloha
oh I can't afford some new kicks I could
even afford these but let's not go crazy
let's get new shoes for
everybody
thank
you thank
you Aloha so floral I love this oh
everything's so cute theele is so cute
too wow wait plus 48 pineapple my
rockers
I can afford them but and that's a lot
of new extra damage but I just gave her
some upgraded things and I think that's
not quite necessary right now our damage
is pretty decent oh oh wait a dress or
is it about these
flowers she's still only on
nine
[Music]
Hi
C I'm sure Tommy would have liked it
too
Dand oh
okay ooh oh oh
expensive maybe one robe and a couple of
long
[Music]
coats oh yeah I can sell my old stuff
too I'll buy one of
[Music]
this not yet the Rope what are you
saying don't buy it
yet okay fine with me
okay what about hats where's the hat
store thank
you new trip
baby was
that that's where I just was
here I was waving hello at him not at
you guys don't get it twisted am I going
the right
way do I want some
stuff there's a gifting
[Music]
option a straw
hat that's that's so
Tommy that's so Tommy isn't it but
chitos is almost at
10 but that's so
tummy
Ser let so Tommy
[Music]
tax see she barely locked it she was
like thanks I guess
Aloha r b look at that picture guys look
at it look at it look at
it I will make you look at
it
[Music]
Garden t-shirt
cute
oh ABC Store gift set
ah we can gift that to our team members
I'll buy one remind me to give it to
them can I do it even even here in the
middle of the
road thank you for stopping by you're so
welcome let's try it can I can I
no come out come out come over only have
Revol yeah it seems like
it Dante is my besy
now I'm so excited to share my life with
him from now on so many exciting things
are going to happen to
us when they're already pink I don't
have to wave at them anymore
Aloha hawaian hat
yeah all right money well
spent very well equipped now I would
say hi
Maria and
then while I'm here I think I'll try to
sell
something
Aloha um this no
this
yeah should I sell this oh they're not
even they don't even bring that much
money thank
you well I can sell old equipment too it
makes making friends look
easy what do you mean this is totally
realistic this is totally how you make
friends you unlocked Cho's attack team
at
revolve what Lord evok you speak in
riddles to me you mean I need to go to
revolve in order to unlock it for real
for real or I unlocked it recently by
being at revolve talking to
her what do you mean
[Music]
what go to revolve go to revolve
now what h
new attack yeah sure sure sure totally
totally I agree with that I just don't
know what to
do
qu
I have
two these are not in use anymore right I
can get rid of them
hopefully no wait toate that was for his
main class oh [\h__\h] whatever he'll stay
the grass cutter
forever that's his whole identity now
I'll keep the rest here cuz except for
these cuz who knows when I'll need them
I don't need so many duplicates I
think thank
you and more ah I should do
that and then I think if I practice it I
could maybe maybe try to make a fua
impression and
F I can try let's let's befriend the the
the the parrot a little bit
more
you're welcome casual
solidarity
whoa okay it's finally paying
off jumbo
egg so parrots lay jumbo
eggs maybe from now on instead of hiring
chickens maybe I should be hiring
carrots than you you guys want to change
my mind you guys got to lay bigger
eggs
understand you can win me back you just
need to produce bigger
eggs x x l size minimum
requirement oh welcome back he I was
just talking about you guys needing to
produ bigger
eggs
I don't even know what that was I didn't
see anything it wasn't OBS was YouTube I
think OBS would have made a window sound
that I would have
heard okay uh what's going
on
that that's an happy
figure played a lot of video games I
love Tommy zawa I want I want
I want more
[Music]
of
hi hello oh you want oh you want
something else you want a kitty cat from
the youu
catcher that surely that surely is a
photo spot right I'm I'm sure I'm so
sure
the other chickens also give you jumbo
eggs they do okay I just got to see it I
need the
proof got to sleep now and no don't
go good
night don't run
away please take our eggs I will take
your
eggs whether you like it or
not hey K go in there wait oh my God K
that's perfect look to the
front hey that's not the perfect picture
I took K was in front of it
fake okay where do we go where do we go
is this down
here
I I'll I'll I'll do the thing revolve
next time we go to revolve
naturally there we
go k is only in my
head I'm not that crazy about him I
don't think that's the case I'm not
imagining him as
real
yum oh he's watching he's watching our
video you like it give it a thumbs up
and subscribe please may me leave a
comment he's a fan now right right
right
he's smiling a little bit I can
[Music]
see I'm just
imagining I'm imagining me standing
somewhere maybe even a meat and green
and then you
guys with the straightest face ever
slowly
and very wobbly walk up while watching
one of my BS and just menacingly walk up
to me like this and I'm like uh oh this
is
awkward why wobble cuz he's like walking
in a wobbly
way can you stop watching my vot it's
awkward yeah
[Music]
she's looking better you're looking
better you're looking fresh y what's
up what's
up think he found happiness in my
videos who's
that
for oh I like how they're doing Small
Talk make him feel more
stupid
[Music]
K you mentioning death to each B is like
me mentioning gradu you
guys hurt doesn't
it just like a crab walking
over give you guys some
willpower crap team let's
[Music]
go essence of
sweeping let's swoopy whoopy some people
well I don't know how many that will
catch
actually oh it did some stuff it did
some stuff
Muki
died no more Mochi for you
[Music]
uhoh I was I was kind of ready for
it hey what the
hell he locked into his what do you call
the behind of the
knees the
[\h__\h] fire breaking is
AOE
oh okay oh oh
oh this one could catch
free but not if Y moves away oh but he
gets it he gets it yo oh
[\h__\h]
yo nice we love
the love to see
it level 21
this maybe just a flipper to the Lipper
could do the
trick yeah
233 damage
this what do you want what do you want
you think you're styling huh you think
you look cool in those great out great
gr outfits kid you looks the best in gr
better than all of
you
yum look at this cutie
patoti damn it damn it damn it that was
new I never saw that
before second
time
yum
oh oh he
a it's script that he's only going for K
you well then I'll only go for
you I want to try this on you
bastard yeah yeah go back over there
yeah yeah good good good
[Music]
yeah yeah I [\h__\h] got it
guys I was so
focused oh a German character oh right
yeah I would play it for
that what mean what does one day mean
you got to let me know when that
[Music]
happens okay two enemies there one
here oh oh oh oh oh oh that can get all
everybody [\h__\h]
yeah [\h__\h]
yeah I'm I'm really enjoying this today
I'm like immersed and the battles are
fun even the side I thingy was fun I'm
I'm immersed into the
story today is a good Yakuza day a good
day to be a
Yakuza I'm
vibing it's the yaku Zone The yaku Zone
wow
um you're so close to
me feel like you're asking for me to
stab you and capture your
[Music]
soul
I missed it
no yeah look at me don't look at K
you actually normal hit is probably
fine now I hope kid you doesn't die 212
HP should be enough especially if I
happen to block
[\h__\h] ah yeah okay okay okay okay
okay K holler ke I I think it's called
ail
maybe it's almost dead uh I mean k with
that or
[Music]
you power head let's do this uh merch
Mele
I didn't do
it I did not do
it 150 should be
good protect your turn at all
cost you
bastard what's his strongest
honestly it's Soul captur it says
medium
yeah he's a
masochist oh his turn oh no next is his
turn okay you know what I want to
try you think I have any good item to
throw for
damage 150 fre 100 no the volleyball
would be not
bad maybe another heal we good although
yeah we're good we're good oh oh oh
oh no no oh maybe we're not
good cruel sneer oh okay he's not going
to attack right on that one
okay that did 300 damage yeah right the
others are not so strong they did 150
the other attack
items okay should be able to finish
it
perhaps may just one I was weak to water
took me this
long a 345 of a big [\h__\h]
tuna let's go
who's on team tuna rather than team
salmon let's
go tuna pizza maybe to to celebrate
today maybe I'll eat tuna pizza
again too late to order food pretty
much nice level
UPS yeah know stop trying to kill me
please are you saying we're too weak
wait we
won he
audacity
for did you listen here for
[Music]
k
kind of
insane kind of
crazy oh he said get well
soon
so I guess he noticed that something's
wrong with Kitt obviously he doesn't
know that
cancer
oh we can stay in my resort island we
just got to take a dolphin
taxi oh what about
a here comes a rolling over
[Music]
no
what what's chel cheese pizza new word
for cheese pizza
[Music]
CH a chicken
pizza chicken barbecue Pizza is a
thing coefficient sent to Super Chat
when was
that when was that
is
that Pizza on
chicken uh K see you good you drunk
what's
wrong the
[\h__\h] be nice
everybody
he looks
nice they look like they're from
FBI what are they police FBI something
that
right
foree
di fion agent yeah
[Music]
okay it was WR on the
screen we all saw
it
yeah the subtitles are burnt into real
life people come with
subtitles you just haven't turned off
your whole
life
right oh you want to keep her safe okay
cuz K
Oni also looks
for do I
turn
oh wait so we did get
[Music]
viral wait nobody knows
still yeah what do we
mean
uhhuh what are you
thinking
oh getting the attention away from
AKA so they stop following her right now
and focus on ichan cuz ichiban's like
hey I'm here go for me and that
worked
right okay never mind maybe not he just
wants to see who's involved
okay but it has a good side
effect
for
[Music]
think I'll go till
midnight
she might have seen come out right
[Music]
now
fore
[Music]
well maybe we can stay
there
for Google
Search
[Music]
foree
sharper but maybe not
[Music]
stronger
knows that
way oh
No
gambling no time for gambling guys we
have to to get to the
boss oh
[Music]
no oh no we have to prove that we like
gambling and we have
money
for so many addictions in this
game
[Music]
fore Phantom
Casino
I don't think he'll ever join the team
spider he'd probably also be really
restricted in like
jobs okay then so just how do we go
about finding one of these
casinos easy just throw
money on the on the path in front of you
yep just throw it just throw it and the
money will fly towards the casino cuz
the money can sense the casino
nand Tommy doesn't know you
okay if I if I knew where to go I have
been there already cuz I freaking love
wasting my money on the cash
machines okay so they've got to be
somewhere in the city I mean one of your
friends is bound to have heard a rumor
or two right so how about it any of your
buddies Gamble
let me think you got this Tommy oh what
you don't know your own
backyard hey lay off all right why don't
we try the sushi place on S dut street I
hear the headed has been known to play a
hand here and there plus I guess
whenever T is feeling lucky he'll Point
him in the right direction if my Hunt is
correct he's definitely kept an open ear
sounds promising what have we got to
lose my man told me I knew you'd come
through
okay the sushi place on suck the street
let's head out let's
[Music]
go nice that boss fight uh wasn't bad at
all good cut scene muchos
information no wait it's actually so
close what the
hell
huh what's with your lots of enemies
here
though e not those low lives
[Music]
again come on yeah went pretty
well pretty good
[Music]
stuff
saw a chance and I took it for a nice
back
[Music]
attack K is really losing his
Edge where's your power K don't you run
oh
oh that was a
mistake it's too late to do anything
significant
now yeah I mean it's understandable of
course don't wake up don't wake up the
relax
so in German we say
relax what are you looking at what are
you
want what do you
want oh
little Japan dolphin mural oh we're in L
Japan oh hey we're here what about these
fortunes uh we should
[Music]
maybe try to turn them in for something
I don't even know what what what we get
I
forgot uh oh how much what a Tranquility
bat a bat that can help you obain a
clear Calm
Mind what that's
all I have to turn it in anyway what am
I'm going to do with that what am I
going to do with
that have to get the reward in order
[Music]
okay flame amulet lowers the damage
taken from fire
attacks oh but I don't want to equip
it new stuff okay rhyme
amulet
no
yes Raiden
amulet
rden electric okay I'm buying it should
no can you just do it all at once girl
increases money obtained from Battle the
Lucky Money charm okay that's um
decent Health prayer recover
HP one more maybe no I can't afford it
but this would be recovers MP after to
winning a battle n okay
goodbye God your face pisses me
off say the same thing about
you I don't know how to
play no no no
no come on give me some pass
fruit coconut coconut it's only coconut
[Music]
one is like the most common and the
other things is super
rare the most I I get besides that is
[Music]
watermelon I I really need to shake more
trees easier to earn G them from the
market stalls oh oh oh this is the place
oh I was just picking up
things the Cheeto s link oh yeah okay
okay
okay hey
I I you're the chef here right that
would be me Tru be told we heard you a
ticket to some good old fashioned old
fun around you don't say like that he'll
send us to something else maybe a strip
club so where gets around huh you guys
must be real freaks seeing as you got
the lady yeah see he's misunderstanding
misunderstanding
Corner actually I wanted to ask about
the casinos oh that kind of fun okay I
thought you f what forget I said
anything uh anyway casinos sure mind
giving me a second
sorry should have just kept the
misunderstanding intact and go to it
so hey there sorry oh no s anyway we're
looking for a special kind of Casino you
know any places run by the g i it would
be one of theirs right about that I can
exactly give you a yes or no oh what do
you mean well it's like this you see
gambling itself is illegal out here
technically no plac is in
hon m I'll take that that's a
no uh I mean it's very
tricky don't beat around in the bush by
by the bush about the bush around the
bush are you waiting for
something oh it's just that something's
come
up hey fellas they're over here you
little
[\h__\h] m
[Music]
M I thought yum I was done with me it's
not about that think Tommy
think mhm he sold us out oh that'll be
cruel they just beat you to it it's all
well little [\h__\h] that's such a big [\h__\h]
actually anyway it ain't my business so
don't go pulling me
in I figured You' skip down by now last
we heard your boss wasn't interested in
him
anymore he just gets bored easily it's
up to us to follow for for him follow
through nothing you guys are just
holding a
grudge yes SP it however you like
P you sure popular to me oh shut
up think you can dip out after the boss
took you and you tell wrong toy
Z
I took down Yami twice you think you
have a serious
chance you are so wrong wrong wrong
wrong wrong wrong
[Music]
wrong no the car is part of the yamay
crew he doesn't want to help
[Music]
me
how does this work with the car okay it
doesn't work unless I should have chosen
the back
one ah
[Music]
whatever
they have unique versions each time I
haven't really realized but yeah they're
all
dope I would agree
that he
oh
wow oh I blocked really early this time
damn
F now way too
late
byebye
bam
[Music]
for
for no
it's never your turn no you stay
alive dynamite
oh why the [\h__\h] would you do
that that's
crazy
illegal
activities huh I'm not taking your
apologies they they were threatening me
from the start they told me I had to
report you guys
SS oh is that right [\h__\h] man you
were probably just after the Bounty they
put
out well yeah it was a nice gamble but
you bust now let us gamble you little
[\h__\h] speaking of where are the guns
running things that's all we want tell
us and we'll get get out of
here fine now I normally wouldn't give
this out for free gee how
kind the secret here is that the casinos
are always changing spots and there's
usually at least two or three running at
a time I happen to know one and that's
the black hibiscus you give them the
password and they'll take care of the
rest all you got to do is say fried
dumplings from the mainland to whoever
greets you uh F dumplings from the
[Music]
Ming great now I'm
hungry I want the FED
dumplings
[Music]
already messed it up I'll practice until
then so that I don't mess up the
password I'll practice in front of the
mirror so so we head over to the black
hibiscus and say fried dumplings from
the mainland is that it yeah that was
awesome for this jer's telling the truth
everybody's still so mean to him I love
ity hey I am
honest you got to believe me don't be
too hard on the guide CH Chan I get your
mad for Tommy sake but it's done now uh
wait you does someone actually care
about me huh bite me
Tommy all right I'll nibble your ear
then okay time to hit the
tables we just want to hit some tables I
assume
[Music]
pouring some more
teato
somewh oh no we're almost at our end
half more hour
maybe or whenever whenever
feels fitting
um we're
both uh is down here right
uh
no
I'm so wrong isn't it close by isn't it
here yeah oh it's
here doing me a
bamboozle if only I had my bat right now
I
could scatter this trash all over and
make it
vaporize Vapor
rise Vapor wave m
nice if
only I could save not only that resort
island but haai
too oh it's a pho
spot gima Armory
wow oh wait are these like
different different pages oh different
pages of the St like they're not all on
the same page oh my God there's
several almost all these conversations
are about
Tomy sometimes do but none
about or does he not
participate where am I
going doesn't
okay that makes sense cuz I I knew him
from before he helps to buy a big SUV
someday got to be honest Tommy not my
ideal car but we can have separate
cars okay how do I do
this ah there it
is drink dink
he's very
likable yeah get me a car from the
30s
[Music]
fore
for
yeah
apparently well thanks to that vtuber
when are we going to hear from that
vtuber
again or maybe the vtuber thing it was
in the very beginning it will unravel
again at the very
end or like in the end game is
area
surprising
[Music]
come
I guess you don't really like your
dad
I don't know I
don't buy me something too
temp
foree
fore
for
[Music]
foree
the fom family sure is a special
case maybe guys
maybe maybe end it after this
conversation really
fast as long as it's before midnight or
I can order something as long as it's
before
[Music]
midnight some food that's not
frozen yeah I think I'll do that Tango
for five we could to Dan Tango let's go
L skates but not L skates now because
now it's h off now it is
over um I don't really know when the
next time will
be if the thing gets delayed
again uh then we can do another Yakuza
weekend I don't
know this was a Sunday stream was it is
today
Sunday yeah uh so again next week I
don't think I'm going to make a schedule
cuz I I don't know I don't know what's
going to happen um I don't want to make
a schedule and get everything canceled
uh so yeah thank you for watching I am
planning on streaming tomorrow we're
going to do probably a Super Chat
reading Dave the diver I want to play
Dave the diver but I still have to wait
for the switch PRS because like after I
was told to apply for like perms in
advance on I was told hey W this is
steam only just so you know what I'm
like it I've already bought it on switch
so now I have to apply for perms again I
already kind of did through JMA so I'm
waiting for that yeah I don't think it
will be ready next week I think we'll
see though uh so thank you so much for
watching today I hope you had fun I had
a lot of fun and even though we worked
so much on the resort I hope we made
some
progress uh we're in chapter six still
are
we are we still in chapter
6 h we
are but probably around the end of it I
would
hope or maybe not maybe maybe very far
from the
end you only got three hours well you
got to watch The Vault enjoy the vault
[Music]
I will run now
in bye
bye thank you guys love you guys take
care have a nice day nice evening nice
morning um do your thing I'm GNA do my
thing see you
[Music]
tomorrow yeah
thanks for the pinky
[Music]
d