[Music]
jimin again the second mood of the day
the Jim of the second day
jimin
g wow I can't believe G it's been so
long since I've last seen Gigi Moone
stream it's been so so long since her
last stream she she streamed so
sporadically and never that I didn't
know that she would be streaming today
that's
crazy
right so
anyways thank you M for the sha oh no I
forgot it GG oh my God I think we all
forgot too before I play the game please
think September for us
no it's it's not September it's not
September thank you infinity gy
congratulations on becoming a senpai
already never would expected GG Senpai
so soon also happy for some head empty
gaming today despite all the GMS
becoming gregnant dot dot dot heart
emoji the heart emoji makes it seem like
you're just like just so happy to be
[Laughter]
pregnant my God all the Gs are all now
G and they're so happy to be gnet in the
shoe box together and you're all like
patting each other's bellies g Grand
prank is real you guys have done it
you've proved me wrong Grand PR is
real I see you're playing TFT but would
I ever do a peer League
stream it's not a
[Laughter]
no it's
like I like League of Legends the rift
does call sometimes but league isn't
really
a it's like not a solo game for me I
don't like playing I don't know to start
I think like on stream I definitely want
to play with
someone and then after that depending on
how that goes like I play on stream once
with someone and then who knows what
happens then I'm non-stop playing on
stream by myself and then it's all weird
and
[Laughter]
strange
yeah what have we just all played League
of
Legends the thing thing is that I'm also
hesitant to stream League of Legends
because I'm freaking garbage at the game
there was a time where I was good decent
quote good SL decent but now I don't no
it's like you don't stop learning how to
play league but you're
definitely
not I'm like not keeping up with the
meta my brain is so smooth I don't want
to react to anything you know what I
mean like I my brain has reached the the
smoothness that I would love to just sit
there like Yumi is the perfect champion
I don't want to dodge a skill shot I
don't want to last hit I
don't I don't want to read the enemies
uh movement I just want to sit there and
play Silly League game and not worry
about a
[Laughter]
thing I just want to have a good
time yeah but I have been yearning for
the rift lately I've been playing some
Aurora
cuz I feel like she's really simple to
pick up for for for smooth brain
people on these others um G Mo the GRS
combin together can we defeat the
opposing team yes would you rather fight
five people on the rift or two billion
GS see who would win five people on
Summoner Rift or a billion GS we just
don't
[Laughter]
know there's a wiggling a hog in the
midst yeah I just wonder what that is
wonder what's there behind the blushy
wall thank you tra for the super thank
you for the Super
G punch those enemies real hard thank
you tenon for this the super thank you
Amelia SIM for the super thank you co oh
this is yeah would I ever do a pure leag
stream in the future it's not a
no if you were here for my last 10
minutes of the previous stream of youen
Eternal stream I was talking about how
it was like in my my head you know my
existential thoughts of how life is
fleeting and then um um um the world is
ending just kidding it wasn't like that
but I was kind of looking at my schedule
and stuff and making schedules is
definitely one of the hardest thing like
what am I going to stream and I have to
make sure it's varied and I have to try
new stuff and and blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah and all that stuff and
what about head empty things and then I
was like oh but if I'm going to be here
for a long time and then it's definitely
going to be for a while so I might as
well it's like there's a lot of time to
play games so I might as well just play
some some filler TFT and no one will
mind some fill TFT some head empty
filler
TFT everyone loves head empty filler
TFT and then the next move that I slowly
make is I start going live randomly
where I play TFT and I don't say a
single thing like a completely wordless
TFT stream goes live without alerting
you and then I just end
stream those are the Motions we're going
to go
through yeah no model even nonverbal no
model TFT just live you watch me go e
quick eight I go no pivot fast8 and then
I end stream that's probably how the TFT
stream would
go
yeah I I think in my
head I'm definitely like oh but if I
stream something then I should be
100% um
like I have to be giving 500% and then
sometimes I'm like but when I think
about the kind of content I watch I love
just having someone on on the second
monitor while I'm doing other stuff and
they're just like playing a random game
not doing anything and they're not
talking either and then I was thinking
about that too and I was like that maybe
I should I should do
that I would love to just randomly grind
something and be someone's second
monitor
content second monitor question you know
how a second
monitor I used to have like only one
monitor for a very very long time it
wasn't until probably the beginning of
2020 when I finally got a second Monitor
and when I tell you second monitors
change your life you will never go back
once you get a second Monitor and you
you are coping when you're saying cuz
that was me I was coping when I was like
I don't need a second monitor one
monitor is fine fine I can do literally
everything on one monitor I would grind
on XIV like crafting and gathering on
XIV on a single Monitor and then I would
also be drawing
too so you'll have like XIV really
really small you'll have your um your
timers really small for all the the node
spawns and then you'll have a TV show in
the upper corner really small and then
you'll have your drawing program that's
taking up half of the
screen and you say it's fine because you
can do it but once you get a second
monitor you just you can actually watch
the show on full screen it's crazy I
can't believe you can watch shows on
full screen
[Laughter]
now thank you Jun is super just
wondering but can we upgrade gigg
plushies by combining them or dipping
them in different kinds of milk you can
combine them so they get larger and they
shrink if you dip them in milk that's
how it works they get they shrink and
get heavy year in milk and when you
purchase multiple plushies they combine
with each other just like TFT once I
play TFT you will see what I
mean three star GG plushy we're going
for the three
star thank you tapioca breath thank you
for enlightening me on the existence of
peees and Weis I figured the Grim should
know there's a BOGO seal right now on
dinkles and moly so I bought one of each
they will be a perfect
couple I know no item label is so smart
their branding is so smart the emails I
get from them from their like
Subscription
Service are so cryptic and I click on
them every time and I'm like wow they
they have something going on should I
buy and then I I really need some to
restock on the uh the Wei wees I
desperately need a we we restock we we
we we we we we
restock who's looking forward to a we we
restock thank you one for this superim
is my birthday in two days I get to see
new coai for my birthday happy early
birthday I know new kohai is coming soon
I guess it doesn't really feel like I'm
a senpai honestly because I don't know I
can't I can't talk to them feels
bad I would love to communicate with
and we we've barely been here we're
still really we're fresh blood
too and I won't be able to do any Senpai
activities because I I'll just I'm going
to send them an emoji and
then that is me going I am obsessed with
you guys and you're
beautiful thank you Fantasia for the
super double Gam on my birthday thanks
GG Senpai oh happy birthday Gem and
thank you all for the gers ships I'll
read these okay let's just go to TFT so
I remember how TF is really brain empty
and I can reap these supas so cool so
cool so awesome maybe I'll go over my
previous collab
[Laughter]
suo um what rank am I I'm unranked I
haven't played this set at all I played
this set negative amounts I'm probably
bronze bronze
rank did you see I don't know how to
share my screen I'm scared of sharing my
screen what if it shows something and
you're not allowed to see one second I
don't
know game capture League of
Legends League of Legends launcher
cannot be captured using game capture
okay you're just going to have to wait
for me to get in
game if you look into the league
shop there's chibi High Noon Ash and
there's chibi Bing Yumi but I don't know
I do think the Yumi is cute but I don't
know if I want to be like Halloween
themed year round and there it's like
200 $200 to
be just
get no no
oh I want to spend money though do you
think if I grind really hard I'll be
able to complete this this pass this
battle
pass there's a be finisher which is
really cute the be finisher is only
level six though level six is easy but
if I buy a battle pass I'd want to
finish
it cuz I'm losing value and I have 11
days
a lot of time to finish
it I'm going to play chunk that's it's
not really TFT but I like chunk a
lot chun's treasure find match I'm
going and once I get in game and I start
it time
okay game
capture here we go here we
go why is
po going have to get
po
[Music]
th here we are
chunk time chunk
time what are these spatula powerful
charms oh I forgot this is the
charm get a high cost Champion value
goes up with game time every what's a
spatula what is this set story
Weaver what am I hard forcing with the
emblem
eldrich eldrich is this set story
Weaver forse portal eldri or portal I
have a sugarcraft oh yeah I remember
when I was playing this I was doing the
sugarcraft build because I really like
the
bees oh my God TM preset no way
got a
Syra what is this sugarcraft Warrior
encounter what else are you giving me
chunk oh no I don't even know what to
build
Shields go up
here here let's grab these let's just
grab everything for now go here what are
you you're
four let me look
at
TFT acad me what is the rank we're just
going to pick one of these and build for
it two tanky honey mansy oh I remember
playing when cnra was really really
good still good portal Shape Shifter a
shape
shifter
relx yeah in this set whether she really
busted earlier this set cnra was like
crazy
good oh no she's still
good um who can I build based off of
this I want to go to tanky Honeyman see
permanently attached emblems fairy
emblem is this crazy can you craft a
fairy emblem what have you craft
fairy what is Max
fairy
yes fairy is good gamble the wandering
Traer I want to gamble I'm not
pivoting no
pivot what did I get I got portal and
honey man
[Music]
ooh portal and honey
myy oh
no portal it is can get portal 10 let's
go what is the portal comp I guess all
portal portal I'm losing I didn't craft
a single thing who is Portal how do I
look for portal why does it not I don't
even know what portal looks like it
looks like this portal
portal a portal
portal
um P
portal portal
portal Port portal portal portal okay
these are all
portals why does my mouse not look like
this icon here we go
I my can I go
bees
Bastion can I get some bees in here I
want a
bee I need another honey
mancer I can craft
portal I need oh my God portal I'm going
to make this be a portal just toss it on
it real
quick honey M's kind of bad no
is this a bot lobby I played my bot
lobbies the last time I played this
game hey what am I doing oh I have a two
star
seraphine very
[Music]
Mage oh my God my
portals my my portals
how many portals is this oh I don't have
enough okay put her
back my fairy
Bastion getting rid of
these sugarcraft Mage I'm just going to
get rid of my Gwen
sugarcraft going to make you download
League again for
TFT you can download league on your
phone for TFT don't tempt you back
everyone should play League of Legends
who am I going
for chat's not going to be fast enough
to tell me what I
want I
want I want I you want a bow it's too
late what do I even have I'm going to
build a
Redemption I want here it's over hold on
I need to find
portal portal
item thank you
chunk all my items turn into static
shibs for one
round watch
this stair ax
okay I will do as you say one guy
easiest game of my life I'm selling this
well I'm going to get rid of her too my
static shave turns my static shave into
a static
shave
turn stairs is the second worst
item why would that one guy do that to
me why would one guy say
that can't believe one guy would lie to
me that guy I'm going
to I will yes I will do as you say one
guy okay it's over it's so
over what is this I'm going to craft a
static sh
I have six portal I have so many
portals who's my last portal check out
my portals
everyone so many
portals my plentyful plentyful portal
I'm going to static shift Jace I have a
golden item
remover things are good get out of my
home get out of my home get out of my my
home also I'll keep you for
now if I win this I sell her do I win
this do I win
this it's over I don't even get the
gold so for 40 okay one guy check this
out
[Music]
everywhere go next no we have this all
we have is a here Jay unless you want
this
[Music]
Zoe it's winnable we're playing Chong's
treasure I don't know this set
whatsoever but
I at least I know that you can always
come back from
this
Wukong
[Music]
runan about to build another gain two
shop rolls give me
that worry not we got
this it's all in the um it's all in the
the flick of the wrist
yeah if that one guy believes and I
believe too we just need to get the rest
of the portals and we win it's an easy
win and we got all the
portals looking tough oh no I'm losing
on purpose for the
[Music]
Eon you see it's
I'm simply it I have to lose for the
[Laughter]
econ they sure are yeah I'll swap Blitz
crank for the
Wukong vanard gain two Gallos is that
good gallo portal I'm about to do it I'm
going to go this you know
what no he's not
good
[Laughter]
no Gallo's GNA car me you just have to
wait and
see don't even worry about it you have
to believe do you not believe in me I'm
going to give him all the
items here here you
go and then
um toss in a Mor
Kizer have this light Shield Crest it's
going to go
crazy it's to take any it's going to go
so crazy he's going to be so
crazy they never expect the
Frontline Champion augment Gallo they
really never
expect they're not going to expect this
one they're not going to expect the
Frontline Gallo we're still in it we are
still we're so in it this is my warm-up
game this is the first game of the day I
did not prepare for this okay I wasn't I
wasn't ready I'm not ready for it it
everything happened so
quickly
here
um stair ax
take all these random items get a rise
in
here got every portal possible we're
almost at portal 8 look at
that we're so
close it's going to save us
crazy
crazy it's so
crazy my
econ I lost my
econ why did that work my
[Laughter]
Eon what do I get a tier should I get a
tier I'm going to grab this
here Rod ter oh my God T we need t for
the
portal
o can someone be in my game so they can
type to me faster than my
chat can chat type
[Laughter]
faster going to need you guys to Ty
faster someone snipe me so you can tell
me what
do
hurry like you don't want me to
win oh rapid fire
Cannon check this
out it's got to go so
crazy and then we even oh CeCe hi
welcome to my League of Legend
stream what are here don't have anyone
here for
Gallo welcome I'm playing League of
Legends
excitingly hope you had a good time
valheim I saw you in your comfy
um you were in your comfy outfit your
comfy blanky
why this person
leave
only you know
what is
[Laughter]
cing and hello OTAs I hope you're having
a good
day this is game
five he's so czy
[Music]
crazy what is he he is a two star what
we look for him roll a die I want
something three
cool
cadin sure I'm taking all the wukongs
out of the the
shop you're taking notes yeah you should
be this is
what highle TFT looks like
[Laughter]
everyone the best thing to do in TFT is
hold all your items and lose put a
planner I have it for every single
portal oh my God so many cins
by low so high stock
stocks feel like whenever I play TFT I
have to have a guide
out I'm rushing for I need to get portal
10 do I want to go guess
not oh what is standard what standard
leveling some a standard should I be I'm
going for level eight I'm just
leveling next combat I will burn and
wound
everyone oops did not mean to do
that who do I even have to put
in can I put in shape shifter here you
go
Swain you go in buddy Mage Mage for
Gallo I already have you need three
Mages for
Gallo I found an
Ezreal we're so
back it's so
easy ouro is
crazy Vol is
crazy I don't need more wukongs I'm
holding them which one of these is good
team has 10 omniv
Vamp
Clockwork spell blades
none do you mean
it I'm spinning explosive growth spell
spell blades mentorship spell
[Music]
blades go for growth
[Laughter]
well I need someone here to tell me what
all the augments do for
this the set okay one of these Kongs
have to go for my
econ
um do you want does anyone want a blue
buff you don't want a blue
buff no one wants a blue
buff you want a blue
buff I will give rise a blue buff who am
I holding on
to here you go rise
rise
[Music]
rise choose all on Gallo but I don't
even I can't even make him level I can't
even three star him yet
what do we need oh if only I picked up
that Tri so we need to go nine and we
need to fish for our last two
portals or I can search for Gallo right
now it's either I three star Gallo or I
Rush nine and find my portal 10 I do
want to see portal 10 more than a three
star Gallo honestly
I want portal
10 consider this three star Gall was
funny when will I
ever give me her they're not going to go
for it they don't know what I want they
don't know what I'm doing they have
literally no idea what I'm up
to they're going to give please
please ter ter ter
t t t
t
i why what's wrong with every single one
of
you there's another portal player why we
have to kill
ter oh I do not need to do that
oopsies just need one more portal just
one more portal I can
I could make another one don't actually
need another
portal my
God level
up they're never going to expect this
one
six non removable giant
belts is this first
place oh it is first place it's okay
they won't be first place for longer
once I
get portal 10 they're a portal player
too damn them
portal
millio
Zar give me
Hur yeah yes we've we've done it who
gets this who gets the Yumi I don't know
who gets the Yumi
okay ginu will have to go
after Eternal Flame all enemies are
wounded here you can have
this what does portal 10 even do Giga
portal massive shield in Giga
portal so beautiful
okay get out of
here my
freaking I'm just going to have some
tank items
over
static I have 5 million items any
Champions you bench this turn will have
their items broken
apart I can't I can't deal with all the
items right now I'm barely dealing with
any of this
a needlessly large
rod and then I can make another Ginsu I
can make a jeweled
Gauntlet portal spatula do I need
another portal
spatula 11 portal I could get rid of
someone that's not doing anything can I
get a mage three going
[Music]
on mage three you can get a mage
three going to pick up all of
these okay goodbye
Jace where is it I just laid I just
stared directly at a Vex and I rolled
over her because I was too busy staring
at
her I found
one that's
[Laughter]
not so Brier we don't want her in I can
have two shape oh I'm getting rid of
Jay's guess we don't need a shape
shifter you're right I almost forgot
about
Tri I was going to leave him in
there get rid of cidan what did cadin
ever do to you multi
Striker what did I sell
what did I
sell it's fine
I'm check out this Gallo it's so easy
get give
me give me the
item give me it no my port my
portal um
um my my portal my I finished
my
portal
no my portal
[Music]
10 who am I going against why are they
so
strong ow
[Music]
owie what does everyone else need what
is
this scholar
emblem GG trolling it it's it is what it
is why is i c on the
floor who let me play who let me play
this game
[Laughter]
what is happening to
me here you can have
this yep and you can have
this and you can take this whatever that
does I don't even know what that does
and and you can have
this I can make a witchcraft emblem
ooh I'm so good and more portal what do
we need more portal
for another
portal I will surely
win you know despite it all at least
it's not a
last I
didn't I didn't lose
despite everything I've
[Laughter]
done temporary full items I can't I can
go here we
go here's me 10 what does this
[Music]
do do you
want do you want a pyro you want a
witchcraft you want a red buff
[Music]
Brier nor wants a red buff here we go
here don't feed Brier you lose
HP why would she do that to me does this
person have portal 10
too it's over it's back we are so
[Laughter]
back it gives her more
HP
oh I have exchanged so much of my player
health for
her this is Peak League of Legends yes I
will find another Gallo watch this it's
over don't worry I'm going to get one
right
here should I replace Wong
with I can get a
Chrono yeah okay Wukong with Camille
Diana Diana's
better
T poor before I get
wrecked take this do you want a
STX do you want a witchcraft even next
combat what do I get
here get a crowns guard sterex on
Brier when I lose my P
how
beautiful I died this person is stronger
than me they're so
powerful nine fairy
op I simply
I can't compete with
that and my poor
positioning like they don't realize that
my entire positioning is
terrible oh I have Diana too
who's this person holding
Gallo for evil
[Music]
reasons is it cuz I was fighting
someone's
ghost for every 10 gold I have I'm so
rich I have so much gold for
them okay if we can just find one more
Gallo it's over it's
over witchcraft
emblem they can have it
um I'm back I'm so back we're so back
and sell it no my gallo
check out I'm leveling up this
Nora two star
Nora so
beautiful okay you're going to give me a
Gallo right here it's going to go crazy
what the
hell don't even put in and I started
blasting
tactician's Cape 10% chance to drop
gold oh
wait three star
Gallo we did
it we made it the three star Gallo is
real wait did they just restart Milo
who did you three
star my God why do you three star
really it's
evil I did my
[Laughter]
best they had three star Milo Z and
Katarina wow my nice daily play
oh this is to give me a
champion I would like to select Riven
okay thank you for the
Riven it's a win that's a that's a
win that that was a win real League time
the title of the stream is team fight
tactics it's not League of Legends
strong treasure is kind of hectic to
learn a set
with you know everything just happen so
quickly that there's no time to learn
[Laughter]
anything TFT is League of
Legends finish the stream with some
Gallo
gameplay they think I'm playing League
nah we're
playing I'm going to my next Chong's
treasure and who knows what I'll be
forcing be forcing something what
other hold
on where am I I'm lost in my own thing
can tiny oh so I'm reading the supas
from the beginning of this stream now
can our tiny leg support us if we gain
weight chunky GM slowly crawling yes
your legs are so strong and powerful and
you can splot
too thank you Gabriel chosen from for
for the Supa is that gigg Moody the
number one ranked teimo Yumi player in
the world yeah
yes that's that's me that is
me thank you salty hello GG my friends
and I wanted to ask ask your thoughts on
this question if you were Auto attacked
by Champion League which one would hurt
the most but it would not kill
you
um I think emotionally Teemo hurting me
would hurt a lot but it wouldn't kill me
but I would be really
upset you
know powerful charms MEP earlier in the
game B booy kitten
it's a good name it's a good
name thank you MJ G Hawk TFT Hawk
TFT thank you Kyle for the super can't
wait for my daily GG rage Q stream we
got to do something hey I got should I
go Chrono is krono
good and thank you zusy for this super
TFT real seven multi Chrono fun yes six
Chronos is good Chrono
me how come chat can't decide on a thing
together you guys always say you're like
constantly fighting with each other
there's like two people saying yes it's
good and then there's one person going
no it's trash don't listen to that
chatter he's [\h__\h] stupid that's what
you guys sound
crazy multi
Striker don't listen to that one guy
yeah at least I can blame the one guy
whenever I do something you don't like
and then I'm like it was that one guy's
fault that one guy made me do
it one guy literally held me gunpoint
and told me to do that
kronos's
[Laughter]
op thank you Fanboy
kitten okay what am I going clear
this wait multi Striker component Buffet
g a random gain a component
Anvil silver ticket gain a free shop
roll after every four
rolls
Placebo
placeo ticket Buffet everyone's like
ticket Buffet ticket
Buffet what
rrolling ticket ticketing Buffet
I'm going buffet
buffet I think I had to go for Fanboy
kitten K kittens
call I think I have to go with what
fenoy kitten is saying since they're in
my game and
everything guys you just have to snipe
me if you want to tell me what to do I
will listen to you you could like lead
me to losing pretty easily I
think okay
I want a multi Striker hecm Heim and
then
kalista
cille
Camille it's what it
is hi
CeCe oh my God
Buffet who gets this
Eternal
winter um just going to put put you
in tank gets
it which one of you is tankier winter is
good on Jack smiley face kiaha
hello I will just do everything Fanboy
kitten is saying Fanboy kitten is one
guy that is that one guy hello kiaha
hope you had a good HOA reading I'm
getting
um stun locked and confused by League of
Legends as per usual the
norm edge of night who up edging the
night who is up Edge Of Night
what do I
get EF
sword build something
else R my me sword ah who did I
buy Camille edge of night nice oh well
once I destroy Nyla from my team she can
have it wait we have golden item
removers I
forgot look at them
go look how fast they're
working why are we mixing oranges soon
we'll mix our oranges together
bloodthirster
BT BT
dubs don't have any skins this isn't my
this is my Live account this is my
Stream Account I don't own anything I
don't have anything in this game should
I spend $200
no no I shouldn't I should
not it would only be for for you guys
too to look at if I spent that
money time flies like an arrow fruit
flies like banana oh fais and then I
started
blasting it would be funny yes it would
be quite funny if I spent crazy amounts
of money on this
game for no real
reason who wants to Jewel The
Gauntlet one of you one of you wanted
jeweled Gauntlet cidan do you want a
jewel I'm giving you the jeweled
Gauntlet thanks for four cross oh
no you have to provide for your family
don't
gamble I can't I can't help it I I love
[Music]
gambling let's go to Las Vegas it oo I
don't like real
[Laughter]
gambling what where the
jpegs there are no jpegs
when when you're real
gambling League skin fundraiser
donation you have to play League of
Legends now the people are demanding
they're demanding it they're saying we
have to do it if we don't do it then
and
um we don't deserve to be on a computer
or something something like
that tank items on Vex she can wait she
can
chill Gigi is
busy she
[Music]
want want to call oh she's calling me
hello
hello sorry sorry I just need to tell
you something gambling is okay no no but
so in my Super Chat reading I was
discussing with my chat if all of H life
English went to Las Vegas together IRL
in theory the people who would get like
who drink alcohol uh if they all went
drunk um who would be Awakening the next
morning to
being accidentally married to another
Holo member and one of the biggest
conclusions was it would be you and CeCe
me and
CeCe n congratulations I feel like she
is so she can handle her
drink she left me she just hung
[Laughter]
up she just hung up on me
well I guess we have to go to
Vegas we're just going to have
to what I do with these what am I
building hold
on sorry CeCe it has to be on
hold mommy is learning how to play
League of
[Laughter]
Legends another sword another sword
Infinity Edge when she in Infinity Edge
on my Infinity
Edge when Infinity
[Music]
edging should I get another should I
should I get a
bow who wants a bow
Stax
Stax who Stax who up stair
rxs got a lot of things
I'm going to grab another one of these
St I think about that all the time I'm
like oh my God
steric gain 11 free shop
rolls um um
um attack
speed blistering strikes
rolls 15 gold 11 rolls 15 go 11 rolls
blistering strikes 11
rolls 11
rolls 11 11 re 11 11 11 11
re 11 re 11 re
[Laughter]
yeah that's a lot of gambling you can do
I forgot to put my Stax down you can
have
it imagine if I had 11 rolls what did I
get I I got the worst
[Laughter]
one I didn't click on it I got the worst
one I got the one I didn't want
we
lost don't make you
relaps dude you want to play League of
Legends so badly for some
reason it calls to you League of Legends
ooh what have you played League wouldn't
that be cool if you played League of
Legends would be so cool wow
[Music]
wow who's building for
what you want to play League of Legends
so bad imagine
playing
Norms wouldn't it be so cool if you play
Norms no I'm going head empty what are
these supas I only have eggn can that be
used as a substitute for milk I suppose
you can dip your Gigi plushy in any
liquid you want who am I to stop you you
own it I can't stop you from doing
that
um I'm going Fanboy
kitchen you Fanboy kitchen
F thank you fony looking forward to
Future five stack hollow life Summoner
Rift collab yeah I wonder if I can find
four other people that wants to play
League of Legends that would be crazy
for 20 seconds your shop refes for free
for every two seconds that's crazy I
want that sniper focused you want this
take it
I'm I'm buying I'm buying we're buying
I'm buying things I'm
buying I'm purchasing
so many
jackes don't kill them they're doing
their
best can we watch you play without a
guide for one game no I suppose I'm not
really doing a good job at reading these
guides is just not it's this is just
like me not using a guide at
all who's here who up
here we need kalista we sure
do is this game based on Arcane it is
Arcane came first and League of Legends
came
second um yeah they made the film Arcane
probably like a decade or more ago used
a dupe I'm not using the dupe on
Jacks I care very little for him
unless should
I I don't know he's not he's not cool
enough ja isn't cool enough to use the
dup
on so little money so little time but
Gigi g no gig's not going to three star
Jacks Jax is here to be passively three
starred if he wants he wanted to be
three starred so bad he'd come home
immediately imagine if I had a real
weapon I actually I do like word games
every night so I do my daily rounds of
connections um strands Wordle uh
crossword um and then I also do uh after
I do those I do framed and then I do
after I do framed I do um what is it uh
guest a game and after guest a game I do
lle and
then so every day I have to guess a
little character or guess their quote or
guess their their uh ability or what
skin it
is and then after loo I play any
[Laughter]
guesser I just really go through every
single thing that I possibly can how do
I make
it anyone else want anything
can we get ginu I have so
much what can I make what an
Adaptive who else
Camille blood
ther blood ther roll the dice Pandora's
items anger
issues
so maybe not invested we do not need
Pandora's
items we don't need roll the dice
radiant
[Music]
refractor not bad Master workor upgrade
if I got a Masterwork upgrade which one
would it go to tiny but deadly I can get
combat com combat com
combat com
combat I'm level eight now I don't have
anyone to put in two of
these Arcana
put put a Wukong
in go
forth my
creatures B booy kitten is going to kill
my
[Music]
Camille
oh my ash is just doing things by
herself over here
my
[Music]
sh just
put mukong over here for
now start
rrolling where
the Arana good what do I get Arana
units holding items where's heerim
at kalista where are
you how to say goodbye to this ash
everyone's getting
stronger no game sound are you lying one
guy there's that one
guy it's that one guy
again
kalista
kalista kalista
[Laughter]
get away from
me it's really quiet I can turn it
up like people hate me literally didn't
do anything
wrong very am
want to war
marks I'm
rolling where the kalista at
kalista
Goodbye where's my
spatula flip on that thing so true
literally what I was saying I was
thinking that exact thing really I was
really thinking
that need items for
kalista I'm getting
owned stop stop hurting me I'm just a
little river Sprite a cute little river
right two attack range give me items
[Music]
chunk
yay locket of iron
Solari more Mela
namicon does anyone want a morela
namicon put on kalista for now why not
three star ja can
wait doesn't want
it okay
stop stop hurting me politely politely
please stop hurting
me we can get a
ginus potentially a
ginus I was thinking about making a
fairy then I can put millio in and
someone can be a
fairy we have fairy
three I'll just do it
nine
multi think I
can not worth
it here take this
Ginsu Demon Slayer
there one anything I'm going to the
store shall she have okay you can have
this for
now what else do I have eldrich emblem
witchcraft emblem fairy
emblem I could have just
waited I live or die
here I live
[Music]
here you don't think the fairy what
emblem would I get then Pyro should I
get
pyro fair is correct I'm doing
it you you can have it for now what did
I just do you can have it for
now who gets fairy
Crown someone teach me about the fairy
crown
Milo
okay
kalista would I get rid of snipers
Focus extra damage
probably Demon Slayer goes
away items on kalista already
op
okay I feel like she has this super
awesome one
ginu everything
else bu the
cille Camille's turn to have fun where
is she
work hard everyone don't die it's
over so there's too many so many demons
in my head G GG fan booy kitten thanks
for sniping my Lobby
there's another fairy
emblem two star
Milo um yoink
[Music]
let's
see what is he going to give me what is
he giving
us God I had a
Camille where did she come
from she was here the entire time frying
pan you can make multi Striker with this
frying pan no
no so
[Music]
sad it's
over take
this have a guard breaker as well who
wants the
Adaptive you can have an Adaptive
might be top
four top four is a dub if I don't die
here it's
[Laughter]
over why are they so
[Music]
big they're so
large hey top four wait top top four top
four
easy top top four top four
easy top four is a win a dub is a dub a
dub a dub is a dub is a
dub easy top
four okay who's sniping me this game you
better have cool names if you're sniping
me I'm expecting cool
names or is basically a what yeah you
don't lose anything you barely gain
anything that's a dub it's a net
win where are my other um super
chats thank you rean you never fixed the
plumbing now the second Peak corner I
SOI we are currently designating the
third we only have one eye we cannot aim
very well I think you should be
ostracized in the shoe box I think it's
probably your fault
[Laughter]
honestly I think I think you're the
problem thank you T Ki for this this sua
thank you
Arana order more and Reco
capes in the future I hope so I know
that they sold out really
quickly people really like those CES
they are really cool
I'm
going I'm going full witchcraft I'll get
an emblem it's witchcraft only
witchcraft
season what do you do a preserver
I know to learn a
set if
you
have smooth brain is to spam one comp
until you're very familiar with the comp
and can Flex off of that comp but this
set is ending soon anyways right like I
started this set way too late I got back
into League of Legends way too late
there's no point isn't there a new set
going on PBE soon I'm not learning the
[Laughter]
set we can we can try learning next next
set but this set is
ending tactician
[Music]
Cape just hand it to you preserver CR
what I want
witchcraft what about the
Witchcraft don't think
Stax and I do not think isn't there a
two tanky build it's too tanky honey
mancy is that good should I go to tanky
honey
mancy is that even good in chunks it
looks really
silly trade sector it's not good
pretty good but not with the mor it
looks so
silly honey not good in chunk that makes
sense since everyone gets
stuff
augment um I'm getting trade sector it's
over I got spell blades I clicked too
slowly
[Music]
who is my league main
Teemo I love Teemo League of
Legends he is the best
Champion ever to ever exists I love Teo
League of
Legends you are all wrong for not
enjoying
Teemo why are they all in the front
what my team
doing person who put them there why do
they look like
that
eldrich you do not
need here you can take
this his visual update so good ooh they
got rid of his best quote
I was so sad I brought it up on stream I
was like I know Teemo quotes and then
stream is like actually they got rid of
that quote and now I'm like why why'
they get rid of his best
quote his best quote he's like size does
it mean
everything never underestimate the power
of the scouts code that's got to sting
size doesn't mean everything
the best teimo skin um I think my
favorite one to use is the B1 but I also
like the cosmic one because you can spam
one of his emotes and it's really
obnoxious it's incredibly obnoxious and
that's the best one for those reasons
only is a
lesson Shape
Shifter I'm a scholar it's fine
seen the Tik toks of that skin no I have
successfully cleansed myself from Tik
Tok I no
longer look at Tik Tok as much or I had
just I have it uninstalled cuz it was
rotting my brain really badly so I
stopped using Tik Tok and now I get all
my memes from Twitter which is
worse I think it's
a negative thing that I get my things
from
Twitter I know Twitter is just all about
repost they take Tik toks and put it on
on
Twitter I'll get there eventually yeah
maybe maybe I will what am I going for
I'm so brain smoothed right now I was
not paying
attention um
Rod yeah about
that what if I get a
shoin are shoin good still I remember
everyone was building
shoin Shin's not
really why would they do that got
nerfed why would they do that to Shins
they were doing their
best last
whisper you can have it for
now ET morg whatever you say one
guy
go whatever you say I will follow
Smiles
Friendly Smiles all friendly like
don't need an eldrich I
guess if I want to level up my brain rot
read YouTube comments I am not doing
that look at them go doing their
absolute best don't worry I'm going on a
l streak for the Eon
I I read your guys's comments I would
not read a comment on a random
video cuz that that sounds evil
especially like YouTube Shorts YouTube
shorts is the worst place to read a
comment n back in her Nico
skin who wants this last
whisper you can have it you can hold it
cuz you have everything on
you toss this
here toss is here toss is
here insta is worse who's using
Instagram going on to my next one thank
you Zen son we can't have one decision
because the Gams passes around the five
brain cells we share among each other
but we do it at a 10-second
interval you only have one brain cell in
The Shoe
Box you should find another brain cell
in there I think it would help you
greatly forgot I had poppy for
witchcraft
everything yay all my friends are here
together
buddies do I plan on joining team one's
roster next year yeah that's my
goal I'm sure once they see
my very fast Mouse clicking abilities
and my um ability to work well under
pressure and um make quick decisions in.
5 Seconds they will snap me up up and
offer me a $1 million contract once they
see all my quick decision making skills
presented in
this TFT game for sure promise you will
see me on the big stage
soon yeah I'll show them my gaming chair
and everything and they'll be so
impressed and they'll be like this is
exactly what we needed to win Worlds
again
just what we needed you are just so good
at playing
[Music]
games what am I going
for I should go level six there should
be things happening right now that
aren't happening like I should be
leveling but that's not
happening I should be using items that's
not happening either
can't believe I
won what bar for
preserver okay one
guy
Ascension check this out I want the
Witchcraft
chest Crest chest witchcraft Crest chest
that easy it really is that
easy um you can have it for
now yeah they're like sure you can have
it gives easily
next Super that I missed In This Very
stream thank you oblivious for the
league skinned fundraisers also sraa
full 80 jungle
please the only time I played jungle in
the recent past few years was to play
Teemo jungle not this patch so like many
patches ago was me trying Teemo jungle
and not ganking ones
and I think I muted everyone on my team
that game even though they didn't say
anything but I knew they were thinking
it I knew exactly what they were
thinking so I muted
[Laughter]
everyone yeah I was
like doing very
[Music]
poorly unfortunately
it was very unfortunate that I was doing
very
poorly that I had to mute everyone so
quickly because I didn't want to get
play well I wasn't dying I just wasn't
ganking you know which could it's
basically like being dead
[Music]
typical jungle Gap Yeah by their jungle
they got
gapped I think I go seven after
this I don't even know what I'm looking
for I just want oh we need one more
emblem for
eight okay we need Fiora and then we
need to get one more
emblem I want witch
Crest I would like a witch
Quest what was my fave set I've only
played 10 and I only hit story Weaver 10
once and I hit story Weaver
10 in chun's Treasure and it was the
greatest day of my life
truly truly the greatest time of my life
what cloak for
emblem
well is that 11 I don't know math still
count is this a
12 set 12 set
11 I played set set
11 who is my next opponent not like I'm
going to go check anyways of
course
spatula no spatula for
me why no spatula for
me who wants to
tank you can have it do you want
anything
else do you would you like a
um might as well use these items too
would you like a
bramble
Nico here you
go Titan's
[Music]
morg she wants to have so much
fun she has a ludin on her just realized
also that last whisper that I put on
her forgot to level I said I was going
to level after Carousel
too look how hard they're working don't
worry I'm L speaking for
Eon this is eon
check out my preservers
now um oh no my
bench you can have
this give me these items take these give
me this take this take this
um you can have this
too crowns
guard oh my poor poor
Eon is it hard to play TFT and chat at
the same time if you're learning yes so
I'm having a very difficult
time I cannot talk and read at the same
time there's no way I'm reading their
skills or reading any of these items
when I'm trying to
talk but the set is ending so it doesn't
matter it doesn't matter it's
fine but once you learn a set it becomes
much easier to Yap and talk but learning
and talking they don't go hand in
hand those two things cannot coexist
[Music]
peacefully in a void Le
theora it's like it knew exactly what I
wanted what does preserver do
do I need Shape Shifter
more you know what get out of
here you
too who want this you have this
[Music]
who's killing me stop
it you will stop that you will leave me
alone items just sitting on my bench
they're stressing me out too don't
worry don't you
worry
call
K I have to I have to I have
to I have to what do I
get
bch um take a randuins um what am I edge
of nighting edge of night you just get
in here for no reason what do I get
okay give me um take this
what I get hole Crusher no adjacent
[Music]
allies okay another hole
Crusher oh
God wait three whole Crusher
oh three whole Crusher I just realized
it's three whole Crusher
doing my
best don't worry
[Music]
nases you will have so many whole
Crushers and be happy and grateful
you will have so many whole Crushers and
be so
happy you will have the most whole
Crushers and be so happy you'll be so
very happy if I can just figure you're
going to have so many whole Crushers and
be so so
happy okay you're not going to have any
whole
Crushers you're not going to have any
whole at all
whatsoever look at him
go it's fine he has whole
Crushers if only had one
more this might be an
[Laughter]
eight rise in the shop crazy rise rise
rise
rise rise
[Music]
guys I need that cloak so I can get a
spatula I want you
dead people are so mean to me
go yeah we're going
next yes in Game of course I want them
to go
eth my frying pan and my 10 million you
know
what I'm feeding where's my emblem
one
second we got we have we have
to where's my emblem where's my
emblem do I have my
okay at least dup the witches don't look
did I sell a witch don't look don't look
at this game this game was over when it
started don't look don't look it this
game was G this G yeah this game should
have had a golden
remover okay not last it wasn't
last we did we weren't last continuing
our chun's treasure
don't
[Music]
worry I will slowly learn through
osmosis of the back seaters in chat
whoever Snipes me and my 5 Seconds of
glancing at this very confusing page
that has 10 items on
it and and then it'll be fine and
wonderful and beautiful I bet I could
play one League of Legends game cuz this
technically counts as a it I mean what
not even technically they're literally
in the same
client I bet I could play one League
game and it would be fine because of
um you
know it's still a riot game and I
wouldn't have to make a new stream for
it
you know I'm just saying not that I I
might not but I
could aam Arcane map the aand map is so
it goes crazy I played it last night
it's so so
different I'll aoy to watch League of
Legends I would never do that to someone
you're all here because you want to
spend time and have no idea what's going
on in my screen and I don't have any
idea what's going on in my screen this
is exclusively to buy Tristana skin if
it's used for anything else I'll explode
and
die oh thank you for the money for the
Tristana skin I will definitely buy
Tristana skin smiley face
vji thank you hey GG I need 30 PS for my
50505 star in star whe should I gamble
you should spend
money I think you should spend money you
should do it you should spend
money
100% the magic to me tactician
Shield 10% chance drop gold when the
holder dies Target the
[Music]
dummy got peer pressured spending money
yes spend money you want to spend money
so so bad you think spending money would
be really cool Lily is not a backline
this set I just remembered she's a front
line
o you're thinking about spending money
you want to spend money right
now item ladder get equips and
Transformers at start round the item
quality increases each stage no thanks
gain an artifact Pandora's bench
into random champions of the same I love
gambling let's go
gambling I love sure
love am who goes where
my why I do that you can go
here the Teemo training
dummy the Teemo training dummy put that
Karma there no my karma start of every
round where I get the rolls from are
they going to go away I'm
afraid I'm afraid I'm afraid where did
the rolls come from
okay they will die here sa from my charm
they don't go away anymore oh
pH thank
goodness all
right I
[Music]
believe power
here's an
encounter Frost Shape
Shifter if
only and
[Music]
then okay okay okay
okay he an ionic Spark
but we want items
on maybe a blue buff maybe a red maybe a
red we're closer to a red a rod a rod
and a
red
morel take
this what are you turning into
all these
Twitches what do I
want
um
Karma
recan then what these
what do we need preserver Chrono
encounter
okay Fiora
Gwen all right one guy you will have
this one
moment for me to put Fiora and Gwen on
here
need shape
shifters can't move
her one guy is so let's go one guy you
got
this who's
pinging who's who's pinging they're
stressing me out
stop stop pinging should I take it
they're they're they're they're
stressing they people are stressing me
out yeah always put your trust in the
one
guy if there's aumu if there was a Mumu
I would have considered adding him but I
don't think there's an
amumu a Nami
only I could do something with this
Nami jeweled
Gauntlet have a jeweled
Gauntlet a
Nico did not have to do
that am
poppy
too who's on my
team
owie she hates
poppy if it was lollipop we would have a
different conversation we would be
having a very different conversation
right now if that was a
lollipop but she is not a
lollipoppy
power such power
do not talk about the fall foul
[Music]
monster I bought that skin specifically
for the splash art and then they updated
the splash art what's the point of
buying something for how cool they look
when they change how cool it
[Laughter]
looks I can't believe they did that I
wanted her to look like that she made me
happy
what else is in
here G mooding if your a whole Was A
League of Legends item what kind of stat
would it give love your streams you are
super Giga groovy garious grammatically
correct gal I don't think that's true I
think my H stats would be um armor pen
and Magic Pen it would give both it
would have both pens
time
like and fly like Arrow fruit fly
like so useless are you calling my item
useless it's a good
item she's a good
item it would give you so much pen
am no Queen you could
never should I go shape
shifters shrugging shrugging emoji
who want
in ENC Canter Shape Shifter is
decent sure hope that I get to the point
where I start rolling I hope I use my
gold gold this game instead of dying
with 500
gold can just just pray that I I do
it Eternal growth shape shifters that
begin combat next to another Shape
Shifter gain 30 shape
shifters Shape Shifters
shape shape shape sh shape
shifters shape shape
shifters
okay have many Shape
Shifter back her SK ni back in her Nico
skin what shape shifter I not have
I'm a shape shifter
three oh I have to add three and four I
have twoos on the
bo who put those
there who let me do
that who did that who who put my n's on
the board I
won I won that
battle it was so
easy
okay who needs to go I have Shape
Shifter I have four shape shifters it's
crazy I do not need this
[Laughter]
poppy go
away there's Beauty in the smallest
moment
by a random champion this
one this one can be
rerolled who up shape
shifting I want I can make a blood
thirster I can't make a blood thirster
anymore you know what it's fine I could
make a um blue blue
buff Bo a rod for Casio you're right I'm
not building
for for karma I'm building for
cash please say happy birthday happy
birthday I hope you're having the
greatest of happy birthday
days take this
item Talisman of
Ascension my cast is going to be
huge she's going to be so large and
humongous oh my God
who gets this suspicious trench
coat what up Swain if I had
one only
dragons what do they mean by that does
that imply
something okay okay okay she's going to
get really large and carry
it it's going to happen any second now
any second
[Laughter]
now she was going to get so large and
carry encounter
with a
zigs why so tense oh I have a zigs relax
why so tense
relax my
bad I'll try not to be tossing these
in I'm
rolling I'm going to get this three star
cast and it'll be over and she's going
to go crazy she's going to be so
good
actually
[Music]
zigs that's
Blitz zigs two encant are good enough no
more encantos
no four
encounter my four
[Music]
encounter could
be don't worry I will be cooking
something something so delicious and
tasty see shape shifter for encounter so
I need Brier and
Swain okay
okay okay our three star she's going to
do so much
[Music]
damage somehow she'll do so much
damage no not only that she's going to
have a
um I don't have anything for
her a gun
blade she can have a nashers want a
nashers my sweet take a
nashers one more
Ginsu
oh well she has a nashers now and a
ginus
become large please cast please yes
yes
augment do I want which craft emblem I'm
not going
[Music]
witchcraft no more
zes I
need more Shape
Shifter guess we just sell
this you want an ionic
spark if I ever play league you'll
always watch my league
streams when what if it's bronze
gameplay would you watch someone who's
bronze
gameplay yes you would still watch it
you would watch the bronze game
play Go still going down my my super
chats um thank you Jester for this
supera thank you Tomo Syndicate for this
supera thank you chipsy for this super
am I hyped for Arcane season 2 can we do
a watch along I don't know if I'll be
doing I don't think I do a watch along I
will definitely be hyped for it and I
will be watching it watch along though
don't know we can talk about it I'll
watch it and I'll come back the next day
and we can talk about it we can have a
discussion Shape
Shifter I need Swain where are you
Swain
hello chilling
thank you spinter the Teo skin of
choices
beol thank you except did I notice teo's
laugh is kind of similar to Ra's
giggle
which which which
um do you think it's the updated
laugh which I I don't know what his um
oh way to and roll
him what I have this
for
owie I feel like they changed his laugh
he got a complete update visual
[Music]
update Voice update everything updated
who want who want
me I feel like I should get tank
items yeah I think we need tank items
stop
moving Let's
see we have another one of these
Champion duplicator a red
buff would you like this red buff
syndra did you like that do that make
you
happy forgot to grab this
I need a
Swain I need my shape
shift duplicate Camille and then Ben
her oh yeah for Brier right need
Brier stop it
stop hurting
me cash
please okay Swain's going to be right
here this SW is going to turn into a
Swain
okay what is
this ages
toss him over
here who wants this Rune
end I could have leveled I will level
and now I will
search six giants
belt oh I found a Brier at least
hello
Swain I found a
Swain ow
owie oh check it out I got a much larger
Swain who is not a shape
shifter I'm sorry but you must
go and reforge these
and then they get
reforged a blue buff and a Titan
vow would you like this Titan
vow I have so many blue
buff Titans on
Brier true true good thing I did do that
um there some upgrades
okay okay
no
what damn if we can get a
BT temporary Bramble take this
where's our Souther Brier I'm rolling it
down I'm doing what I said I would I
rolled it
down our snake could be snaking a little
more
oh no they've killed
our um
owie it's okay it's not a l we were
really
close 3% hit briers of Miracle I've hit
those odds I've I've hit those before we
could do it I could do it
if I just
believe okay where is my next one thank
you NZ for this super thank you um
chipsy only get your memes from Reddit
and then review
memes if only I could do something so
beautiful and carry on a beautiful meme
Legacy
what memes are you even going to get on
Reddit in 2024
though let's
be let's talk about it what memes are
you hoping to find on Reddit in
[Laughter]
2024 I don't I don't
think I don't think I'm looking for any
memes in 2024 on
[Laughter]
Reddit yeah
what am I going to find on there I go on
the front page I see absolutely nothing
that I want to see I leave I think the
only time I go on Reddit is to read
about other people's drama you know like
am I the [\h__\h] or am I overreacting
and then I also use Reddit
for all of my gotcha
games it's very important to be a part
of the your gacha gaming Reddit
Community not posting but you have to be
on there because they're going to be
posting all the information that you
need that you could possibly
need what the gotcha games every time I
get back into blue archive I look at the
blue archive Reddit because I'm like do
should I pull on this Banner what are
people talking about and then when I
play GBF I always go on the GBF
subreddit because everyone is always
giving advice in the mega
thread and then sometimes look at the
Cookie Run subreddit but they don't
really post anything useful in the
Cookie Run subreddit but all I could do
is hope that they will post something
useful on the Cookie Run subreddit but
they don't they don't
really no one care me no one care me to
post useful things in Cookie Run
subreddit what do I like in GBF sand
sandin my
God snipers Focus Focus okay back
seeders which one of these before
snipers Focus
Ash L
[Music]
Bane should I snipers Focus
Ash I'm doing it cuz it sounds
fun fashion
emblem eot
Epoch what worth the
wait worth the wait it's too
late
Epoch hi horse
power it's
over I'm going to get
Transfiguration you are all too late why
did you backseat me so slowly
blames all of you for
this
um would be nice to have a
ginus would be nice
oh eldrid alrd
3 I'm
cooked there's always the
comeback can always make the
comeback it's it's possible just believe
close your eyes and believe
[Music]
um just losing streak yeah don't worry
about it if we had an item maybe we
would have
won but I want a Ginsu
yeah and screw that guy
too all my items transform into a static
shiv I don't think I want
that
okay do they
go they they return to my my
bench right they go back to my bench
right
okay thank you rig for this super got
peer pressured spending money what did
you spend the money
on did you spend it on something
good thank you sword of Bushido for the
money and thank you Tom Ado spending
money right now what are you guys
spending money on I have
fomo you have to tell me what you're
spending money on so I can spend money
too let me
I could have made could have gotten a
bow to actually make an
item thank you Dark Ruler for the AAA
much
appreciated give me a bow give me a
bow now steadfast
heart I want a bow I want a
bow you want to give me a bow so
bad give me a
bow all of our multi
Strikers thank you V Dragon for this
super is this where chunk comes from yes
he is a little Legend items on morg
she's
homeless thank you Z for your kitten I
would like five rolls on a shoe box SL I
heard there's a r up for day old cooking
grease D cooking grease there is DED
cooking
grease thank you R glad to see you
playing TFT I hope to see your 80 carry
Teemo one day thank you I will impress
you with my 0 carry Teemo you'll be so
so so so impressed why so tense
relax why do I have this oh eldrid don't
need that thank you roxes GG it's guild
war go farm no I'm
retired I am a
um I I am a
seasonal Grand blue player and I you
will not catch me on Guild Wars in the
foreseeable
future my time for Guild Wars is over
it's no longer Guild Wars
time don't need
this we are never free from Guild Wars
no no more Guild Wars no more I will no
longer be farming
meat it's a prison guild war is a
prison oh
oh
please please
what the
hell why they hate me so
[Music]
bad who
up who up edging day
night who up edging day
night b b
b
oh got to level it's
fine give Morana the
pause
ow they are hurting me
am I winning we are on a downward
spiral from when we were winning Spin to
Win Spin to
Win Spin to Win slamming definitely
[Laughter]
not don't think I we can't do that
one too good
toss an eldrich in
here here take this while I'm at
it I look I slammed items are you proud
of me are you proud of what I've done
you
witchcraft yes imp I slammed thank you
Jo for this super if you like old Lolli
poppy Splash check out ice and corki
it's no lollipoppy but probably the
closest thing to it right now in my f
Splash
art I what do he look like I feel like I
can vaguely see him in my
head ice toag and Corky the thumbs up
emoji
this what do we
want I'm going for the
roll it's time to be impressed with
me okay
hey who's Amelia simp in here and you're
not even going to rearrange your board
to go against me so I can
[Music]
win I can't believe this you would snipe
my Lobby not rearrange your board when
you could see that I'm potentially going
against you and give me a win people the
disrespect around here
I need a
bow why do they keep taking bows from
[Music]
me thank you arane I just spent $300
today buying a bunch of manga
support
authors congratulations I hope you enjoy
your reading time what did you purchase
what are you reading
what are you potentially
reading
items I can't do math I think I need one
more ashh yes I need one more
Ash like magic
Ash
Ash no she not the
bch
[Music]
no I was so close
so
sad okay getting rid of
him we we were so we're so
close reveal who my next opponent
is three
everyone gets to be in the corner you
can be all the way over here by yourself
you can have a luminous death blade who
wants this
one you can have this for now
I
[Music]
suppose we are so
back we are so back it's never been more
back than now than right
now it's back capital B are we yes so
back want the tanks to eat aggro you
think my collie is doing
anything maybe once my aalii is two star
she can do
something um
get anything from
this here Karina can take all the
aggro suffering is
Magic suffering is
Magic Use
Shen where
where where's the sh
ow
owie had one in the shop it's
over should I have a Pandora's items
multi Striker
crash M multi
multi strike strike Striker
Quest multi Striker
Crest who gets the multi Striker
Crest Jack is a multi Striker
here have this should I
Hodge putting Shen on here cuz I keep
losing him
ribb blue ribbon for
hecm I have a Shen oh my god when did I
get
him what did he get here
take
items take take
items useless item I do it in time yeah
hey above
no my
[Music]
backline she's
gone when am I done with a tutorial
never not
soon fire is going
off Ginsu on cassin
is this your games are ranked no it's
Chong's
treasure we are here to have fun in
Chong's treasure
only I'm not looking to learn how to
actually play this set I want items to
fall into my lap and not use
[Laughter]
them yeah fun in games
only shall
we snipers F but she needs to be over
here she's got to be
take time for
now so my beautiful jackes
still have no idea what's going on I
don't either don't worry do not worry
your sweet head you think you don't know
what's going on me
too ES
let's
[Music]
see kalista found and picked up
no this B
[Music]
tried installing but it wouldn't connect
to a game after you tried three times
have you tried installing harder don't
worry I'm not dead last I will actually
be seventh again which is pretty good
I'm pretty consistently
seven I'm somehow really good at getting
seven
Cid in items on kalista okay speak your
truth I'm even going to double Ginsu
her not only that I have a zerath
Now isn't that
awesome and I have a Camille now
look at them
go look look at them
go you install hard
yeah no
problem I hope that it was
helpful gain an artifact Anvil
okay okay another sniper Focus yeah get
a load of
this check this out absolutely no
thoughts in this head whatsoever
best way to play yeah no thinking I'm
not last also I'm
seventh if I lose this I'm have seven so
it's
awesome okay okay I I can get seven
right
here don't think yeah seven easy seven
easy easy
seven it was so
easy
okay I think I'm done playing League of
Legends for today
[Laughter]
I should get food I will play one thing
I actually I can't play league because I
have to play against
AI so here everyone can watch me playing
against
AI even though I could I can't play aam
I can't play Rift I have to play co-op
game cuz it's AI teimo is free right
now emo reporting for
Dy yeah it's a baby account that's why I
can't
play someone is actually
jungling what have I wanted to
Jungle they're calling rolls in team
chat
I don't have resolve
unlocked oh my
god when you're level one you don't have
[Laughter]
anything what the Bots have
skins oh my God the new player baby
experience I don't have
Cas it's
over what other thing that I missed
thank you chers for this
super spend 600 on your PC Plus game
that you can now play why spend that
much money on PC when play only League
of Legend thank you fun4 super team goes
in all lanes and also the jungle it's
true he does he goes everywhere
oh no my hot your hot keys are are
account
bound oh my god oh no why are your hot
Ping's account
bound oh my God what are they invading
it's a bot game are they actually are
the Bots actually in okay I suppose this
bot does have
Smite I didn't know the meta I didn't
know the B game meta sorry I
wasn't I wasn't familiar with the bot
game
meta
[Laughter]
and stay
hydrated I'm going to get her oh that's
good good one good one
good one good
[Laughter]
one an
En please come
back this Bot game goes crazy now
they're going to take the
jungle yes they're Bots I can't play a
normal game
game I'm level
one I need to
bind attack
an when I'm trying to steal this person
CS are they no they're not all Bots it's
only the other team is Bots I'm playing
with other new players I'm thinking I'm
assuming I can't believe Bots have skins
now to show you to make you jealous so
you can
ah I have my levels on F1 to F3 on my
main
account forgot that those aren't the
default
keys this it in TFT it's TFT don't worry
this is what TFT looks like
think I'm going to
die help help I'm going
mid this is TFT yeah this is
TFT dive her okay don't worry I will
dive her think he's going to kill me why
is he walking over here does he sense
that I'm
low help help the bot knows I blow I
don't know
how how does the bot know I
[Laughter]
blow how does the B know
that how about you hit me
[Laughter]
yeah oh no
League of Legend is so easy everyone
should play
[Laughter]
league I know I am insane I am an insane
gamer Direct
Hit she's moved from TFT this is my last
game and since it's a bot game might as
well right might as well have fun
oh my God I keep messing
up stop my
[Music]
Cannon someone's trying to gank
me the B paing is so
bad he got stuck on the
wall why is this not quick cting
come
back this
has this has been great the bot is bming
I know why are they playing why are they
playing like
that Dragon has
spawn who's trying to get
dragon oh my God has
if I was a better player I would use
those keys to see what my team is up to
in order to have full map awareness but
I'm not a better player I can barely
tell what's going on in my own
lane we kind watch
Revenge die
why are they
here guys three
mid literally three
mid
[Laughter]
finally oops hit the wrong one oops
missing all of these I missed the
cannon help help
why are they chasing
me
no okay the Bots get flash but I don't
it's just not fair
another win for
Teo not spending gold yeah this is just
like TFT
meta going to do a faker today yeah I am
if Faker was a mid Teo
player and really bad at the game game I
I could be
[Laughter]
Faker this isn't TFT no no it is is TFT
what are you talking
about stop hitting the poor dog sorry I
don't needan it I don't mean to hit the
poor
dog
goodbye how did bot get a double kill
the
Bots my fre
boots don't need that just
running going to Worlds I I am
definitely going to Worlds
Smiles never under never never never RR
rest never underestimate the power never
underestimate the power of the scouts
code never underestimate the power of
the scouts code never underestimate the
power of the scouts code
Whoopsie
[Music]
Daisy these are quick casted
right
a you see my strategically placed head
it's so you guys can't stream snipe me I
know how um people get on on League of
Legends they go into streamer stream and
they start stream sniping so that's why
it's like this so you guys can't stream
snipe
me yeah so the Bots do not stream snipe
me unstable
oh my
god get off
me the Bots go crazy they
do did you
see the level one plays they made it was
crazy no don't take my kill I'm working
so hard for
[Music]
it real
game like like how crazy good it
is oh he's not even level six
yet
hey
teleported which one
[Laughter]
is I'm out of
Mana these BS
are so
smart I want a nashers I want to Auto
attack faster
we they hate me so bad I know they're
obsessed with me they literally want me
in the mid
lane the Bots know something we don't I
need to study them so I can do this in
my own
games
Unstoppable unsto
able I missed it I missed it I missed it
an
En get away from
me you want to die so bad you want to
die so bad you want to die so
bad you want to die so bad
[Laughter]
she had a shut down why do SAR have shut
down
dominating good enough sine bot goes
crazy she's op who's feeding my team I I
we can't judge them
okay um we we all we're all learning how
to play this
[Music]
[Laughter]
game oh you're going to wish you wed me
get away from me
goodbye your team destroyed
AET of course she Ms Teemo Teo is my
favorite Champion I love
Teemo corrupt Chad into playing LOL did
you see
worlds it's not even the team fight I
think it's crazy seeing Faker Gallo top
where they're like pushed up into their
base right they're like fighting here
and it's like the entire team is up
there and he lives it was crazy I was
like how did he get out of
that he just ults up there and lives
shut down I'm here for the ks I'm here
for the
ks I'm here for the C I'm here for the
C my f my
fent oh they're top
it was top it's cuz they're
top report for steel panta no I didn't
deserve it I didn't Des I couldn't kill
them by myself I didn't deserve
it the font is so different is it just
because my settings are
default who just
pinging who's pinging
Legend come back
Lulu what do I put flash flash is on D
they changed the font
recently I feel like my UI is much
smaller than
this well not feel I know it is I think
I scill my UI down a little more that's
not even the real one I'm leaving
it's D for lash
obviously oh no I canceled my
[Music]
back help help help help me help
me
help I can't believe he did that I got
J why did everyone die
dest stop stop ending stop
[Music]
ending stop
ending
this the bot
comeback it's
true on my
way of solo Baron
okay
tripad Quadra is he going to get the
[Music]
penta I think he went for
it
no it was the
win got you wanting to play league
again yeah it's a good decision trust me
everyone should play League of
[Laughter]
Legends
um thank you Meep for this
sua Meep thank you game for the sua GG
Tru is the faker of Bot games that's
true I am I am the faker of Bot games
definitely
I still can't play Summoner Rift or
aam I can only play Bot
game why how many Bot games do you have
to play until they free you so you can
feed in
games when do I get to feed in
games who's
free take a little
peek hold on I have a key fragment
Forge
nice hex tech chest that you can't see
sweetheart Sona
ooh sweetheart
Sona after the
tutorial I skip
it I can't play PVP training do I have
to do the tutorial no I don't want
to I think I did the
tutorial thank you for full work day of
streams is truly the unkillable gremlin
queen of League yay is that a
compliment thank you junda for the the
super thank you kyot for the super TSM
GG mood thank you Amilia Sim thank you
deson can I just give you my account I
never play my hand is wrecked and I hate
league players no what if you want to
play one day um using your brain because
they make a way for you to play League
of Legends with your brain and then you
don't have to use your hands anymore and
all you have to do is play with your
brain um neural link and you it's like a
treasure you should treasure your League
of Legends
[Laughter]
account make sure to to treasure your
League of Legends account everyone it's
very very
special those are special things don't
take your League of Legends for granted
okay well I'm out of here had a good
full day of streams I was here since
10:00
a.m. that's a good full day of streams
so I just did the math on my
fingers goodbye everyone tomorrow I will
be playing side well playing in the
loosest term vague possible the vaguest
definition of playing possible but will
be on fauna's channel tomorrow and I'll
be watching her play Silent Hill I don't
know anything about Silent Hill um other
than it's spooky and scary and Pyramid
Head is sexualized thank you R I hope
Gigi gets a $500 skin like Faker did
yeah do you know how much I did for the
League of Legends Community I also
deserve a $500 skin that has custom
animations and
everything okay goodbye for today I will
see see you all later byebye thanks for
hanging out maybe more TFT I I want to
learn the next TFT set I'm looking
forward to it and then I'll actually
read the items and not play like a
complete
donkey next time and then we can do
another Bot game to end the the day
but later bye byebye byee
[Music]