[Music]
all
wait no maybe it's still too low turn
the gain
up a lot until they can hear the fan in
the
background
beep oh the Glorious sounds of New
York oh New York s sounds so
glorious so
beautiful well hello sorry I was playing
Barb's by myself this is why I have this
strange little doll with me hold on
maybe I should put that
away no time for dolls Mory hold on you
put that away you don't need her and she
doesn't need
you why would I do that hey they managed
to give me a a hotel room room that
looks exactly like my home I need her
well we all have to learn to live
without the things that we
need sometimes unless you're very
privileged
hello oh is that the sound of a fresh
water bottle being open my voice is
shot we live in a society
truly hi
everybody it's me your certified
lad where did that where there got some
gifts from
Amy put those away and I'm going to lure
everyone with macaroons how are you guys
hi cie hi Dad no G do you want one hold
on a
sec this seems wrong shouldn't I be in
my PJs maybe I'll go change really quick
this just doesn't seem right
hold on here I
go oh no that seems
wrong that seems entirely
wrong
oh
I
sorry hello I'm
here but this also isn't
right no hard eyes mother effer
no
pigtails not for
today we're getting ready for
sleep but I still have a movie to watch
with the de is Sleepy C sleep I'm very
sleepy we were so busy today it was a
busy day for for
everyone but we did
it we got it we got it done we got our
errands
run how's the jet lag well you guys know
that I was in America
recently right so for me it's not it's
not that bad it's like
Mama could be worse die hard's a comfy
movie you sure about that you get your
sandwich no I'm sure I'll get it
tomorrow though that's the point oh
hiccup that's the
plan why say America and quotation marks
like New York isn't in
America what does that
mean what could it
mean let me tell my friends where I
am hold
on I have macaroons I told
them quote unquote New York how about
new quote unquote York
hold on let me crack my
neck yeah no I was actually I was just
hanging out with friends I was just
hanging out with some friends
and I fell asleep next to everybody
because I was so
sleepy we had a great pizza party the
other night though that was
nice I miss the old
York
oh yeah what what's with the new one
forget all of that I keep waiting though
for my rat oh not ba by the way don't
get confused what I mean by that is on
my bingo card for what I want to see
right nobody drwn my face not yet
but who knows who knows tomorrow and the
next day backstage they might um but
yeah on my bingo card for just me I told
myself that in New York what I really
want to see is a big fat rat chomping on
a big slice of cheese pizza and then my
experience in New York will be
complete yeah that's all I want is like
a big a big round rat and he's chomping
away on a big cheesy slice you know I
don't know why in particular
but I don't know
why Bae not Bae not a bigger rat I only
know small
rats I only know small
ones just take ba out for pizza no she's
too small I said a big fat rat like a
big a big New York rat that like talks
in like a New York accent I mean rats
can't talk except for BA but I mean if
if rats did talk like you look at this
rat and you think to yourself oh this
rat would speak in like a big thick New
York accent or something like that oh
hello GG raid let's go thank you for
coming what did you guys play Buckshot
roul that's what it was Buckshot
roulette I saw that see I'm hip with the
times I kept up with that I saw I saw
that's what you guys were playing Master
Splinter where you at where's Master
Splinter where is he is he chomping on a
big cheesy piece of pizza I don't know
but I haven't seen I've seen plenty of
pizza but I haven't seen any big fat
rats I was about to say big juicy rats
but I kind of don't like to think about
rats being juicy that's kind of
yucky anyway let me get my
scoll my water
bottle she had ungodly what look it was
a crazy
stream dang I think crazy and and GGA
are two words that go together well
oh Gigi was crazy she perfected it well
she is Le gamer for
sure she is Le
gamer artist write that down write what
down a big juicy rat
good luck out there myy thanks oh yeah
you just reminded me the show is
tomorrow oh my gosh why is this
background so bright seems like it
shouldn't
be why is it so bright shouldn't it be
nighttime well you know how summer gets
summmer just like that sometimes you
know it just gets
bright yeah to be honest with you um
this isn't really my this isn't my room
I set up like a a green screen project
ejector in the the hotel to just like
play a loop of my room behind me but
it's it's not my room cuz you know
security right I got to be careful sun's
out still 8:00 p.m. where you are I mean
yeah it's more common than you
think it's more common than you would
think but yeah just letting you know I'm
playing a little Loop little MP4 Loop
for you guys that's why it looks like
daytime I forgot my my nighttime Loop
it's just green screen it's definitely
night time and it sure is in New York oh
man New
York concrete jungle where the dreams
are made
of but it was a good rehearsal I am in
pain
everywhere cie was also on Loop no no no
no no not me I'm never on
Loop sometimes I wish I was though to be
honest yeah I told my friends cuz we
were all just hanging out right um a lot
of us wanted to wanted to watch um some
some fun stuff that's going on um but
it's it's kind of a secret so we wanted
to watch all that secret stuff together
so we were hanging out
together and they they said they'd give
a knock so we shall see initially it was
going to be for midnight but then I was
like oh man I don't think any friends
will join if if it's at
midnight that's like way too late but
I'm tempting them with macaroons so
we'll see if they come I've got all
kinds of rainbow colored ones I'm luring
them like you'd lure a rat with
cheese you
know yeah like you lure R what did you
talk to them well of course I spoke face
to face with many of the
macaroons you any of you guys like
macaroons a lot of times I feel like I
get so many of the pistachio ones but
like I don't really like the pistachio
ones to be honest why do they assume
that I want the pistachio ones I don't
want them somebody take them away from
me no no stasio for Mory what even is a
pistachio it's like a green
nut but it's not the same as like a
peanut is a pistachio even a real
nut what do you guys think do you guys
think pistachios are real nuts
I don't know what are your thoughts in
onions yes it's a real nut we have to
ask Rea it is but a peanut isn't what
what what the word nut is in the name
Peanut that seems strange I think they
are yeah it's a tree nut that's a real
nut onions are not real nuts I mentioned
onions no I mentioned onions cuz it's
like what's your personal onion as in
your opinion I'm so sleepy but I'm
staying alone alive staying alive I
wanted to see you guys I wanted to see
you before the
show tomorrow's the big
day no sleep on the plane a a sick
little 4H hour nap which I think
is
appropriate for me it's appropriate for
me a 4-Hour
nap but it won't fix
everything especially my terrible sleep
my sleep schedule's been really bad ever
since I got back ever since I got back
from America trip number one America 1.0
but now we're on America 2.0 and I'm
feeling
something I'm feeling
something I don't know if it's if it's
good jet lag is hard everyone's
suffering though well mostly the mostly
those of us that came from Japan but
[Music]
ah ah juicy water is water something
that you would consider to be juicy
maybe more than a rat but I don't know
maybe ju juice juice can be watery but
water can't be
juicy no no question mark question mark
question mark all right that dead beat
seemed really intense about that and
said no with many question
marks wet water not really no somewhere
between
somewhere between a rat and a
fruit don't call water juicy do you have
like a personal vandetta against it
or juicy water is Serious Business yeah
it's just one of those things you know
juice can be watery but water can't be
juicy you ever thought about that we're
really yapping a lot is that just
something that like hotel rooms do to
people they just make you
Yap I wonder
apparently NYC has a can's
actually NYC has four and that doesn't
even include I think there's one in
Brooklyn too but I'm not totally sure I
don't know if I have enough time to go
visit though
sadly I don't have time to go
visit ah
well is it okay to talk and use your
voice before a concert yeah it's fine
it's just like chatting though I did
talk a lot
today to
friends well I'm sure it's
fine I'm sure oh I
love sirens in the
distance the sound of fun things
happening in the
city oh
yes no no yawns no yawns
we woo we
woo you know Sirens like like Advent
Sirens wait when they say sirens do they
mean Sirens as in like we woo we woo
police sirens or do they mean Sirens as
in like singing Sirens or maybe it's a
play on words with a double
meaning I just realized that
both ah
yeah
cool it's the Amber
Lamps oh man there's so much going on
though you guys going to be
[Music]
busy oh
well I like being busy
personally I like busyness I like having
stuff to do you know it takes my my mind
off of the existential crisis that is
existence we can tell we
know I guess you guys would notice huh
we know we
know I'm
not no there's there's more to be
done there's more to be done thank you
very much for for the gifted memberships
by the way thank you thank you now I
feel like especially in in New York
there's so much more I want to do and
see you know if I get a chance to go do
and see more she's not making it through
die hard yeah I am Bruce Willis will
keep me awake with his incredible acting
and Christmas
spirit oh
yes you like the Ninja Ninja
Turtles ah I want to see master Splinter
chomping on a big cheesy slice of
pizza big cheesy
slice I bet everybody's finishing up
watching their
thing and then when they're done I
wonder if they'll all come at the same
time I had to dip out though because I
had dead beats to
see you guys What's Your go-to Pizza
Joint I like to look for a place that's
like a mom and pop restaurant or like
even if it's not your mom's and your
pops it's like a oneof a kind I'm not a
big fan of chains I like to avoid them
if I
can if it's it all
possible yeah if it all possible I avoid
them but if it can't be helped
right yeah little
CES no probably not not what's my
favorite kind of pizza anything with
mushrooms and then typically if there's
some kind of pizza party going on I
always want to make sure that there's a
white sauce Pizza you
know hey refer back to the stream that I
did with
ra where we cooked some delicious Aiza
Marti and various other
ones yeah
oh no actually
[Music]
I was I was talking to a a a family
member who is is coming to see me right
um and that family member was like would
you like an energy
[Music]
drink would you like an energy drink and
I said
no I got to
sleep I got to
sleep I said
impossible
impossible if I drink a energy drink
there's no way I'm sleeping no bang no
bang I don't need it that would be even
worse can you imagine me not sleeping
the night before the biggest concert of
the
year
uh
yo no way get that four
look no for L go disgusting there's a
reason that stuff was outlawed but
didn't they make it not outlawed
recently I don't know that's just what I
heard that was the word on the street
but I don't
know that was the
word you guys think I need an energy
drink I do
not I'm strong I'm I'm living oh oh
friend do oh my God they're knocking so
oh my lord they're going to break down
the door J
stop I'm
coming there so many
people oh my God is
Vilan sit on the bed sit on the the bed
I have to put them all in here hold on a
second oh
my Hang God I have many friends here
just have to slowly all I didn't expect
them all to come same the treat they're
right here the
macaroons macaroons for you guys yes you
can have whatever color you
want whatever color yes and a pink one I
want the pink one
cuz for my very cute kohai you guys can
have whatever you want let me put your
Barbie dolls here pink on arranging your
Barbie do I'm
curious have I ever had a ma have you
have you never had a macaroon before
wait macaroon is a macaroon or macaroon
it's macaron macaroon is something else
oh really I've been call the macaroon a
macaroon is like I think yeah coconut
and it's like I think it's um I don't
remember wait what I didn't know that
sorry I'm arranging their Barbie dolls
give me a second I'm arranging their
Barbies
here recently added 3D poses wow that's
right yeah they're sitting across from
me but I'm arranging their their Barbies
for you guys so you can see them so you
can see them cuz I don't want you guys
to see them in their PJs but they're
very cute only for me to see only I get
to see yay Gango oh you want to see
who's on my probably sleeping yeah who's
on
your that's Alexander
just says Alex though I got Alexander on
my pj shirt
Alexander the PO man the potman he's
here oh my gosh oh do you guys you guys
don't know who he is that's our friend
it's just our friend Alexander the
PO y our barbes the jar guy yeah the jar
guy the jar guy yeah chat knows chat
knows the the mighty warrior the mighty
jar Warrior Alexander
yes we love him yeah he's a jar guy he's
on my
shirt
okay I can't do it right maybe you
should play and be cultured maybe you
should elen ring oh how do you think
they would go onion rings I would to
watch you guys play that game it be so
funny in a in a funny way you guys can
be Gamers yeah we're
Gamers huh huh I got to sit whenever you
guys like say like H or something I
think about the cat that
goes cat that's
like that's who I think of when I hear
you guys
H H
hi so
[Music]
cute I can feel your sisterly love just
when you say it like
that wow you got a setup here oh yeah I
had to bring my big interface cuz my my
USB cable
died yeah wait what color did you guys
choose Macar did you open I want to the
orange one with somebody I curious with
the green one let's see well the one the
green I think this one is pistachio oh I
like pistachio I was just talking about
how I don't like pistachio nut is is is
strawberry I think so sorry it's a
little bashed up going
on I got two if two people wanted
pistachio can both have a potassio and
because you guys came first you get
first pick eat a whole one right now I
can't eat a whole one right now you pick
the orange one one bite was Heavy I'll
take one bite of it for at least I had a
nice C
[Music]
salad wo wo wo you're tripping the the
cream is everywhere you got the cream
all over you oh my go I'm the cream it
all over my thighs Jesus Christ they're
going to start imagining things ladies
all over their imaginations are going to
run careful I'm going to take the cream
off her thighs can
you no by all means keep keep going into
the cream
yummy really really wet dad's
winning they say
I guess so I'm wide awake now waet what
yeah orangey it's sweet it's like
creamsicle I don't know what creamsicle
I don't like
it like a little little baby mommy I
don't like this macaron give me a
different one you can eat a different
one if you want I'm I I like the
potassio
potassio potassio yeah don't like a
banana potassium from a banana
poio
potassio I'll take a bite that makes it
worse
I'll take a bite too the yum
yums when I say stop I mean keep
going again you got the
go I keep getting go on stop it I don't
want to eat n's hand goo it just fall on
my hand at least fall on my pants that
doesn't even sound perverted that just
sounds silly and my hands are clean
are you sure what
the you a freaking noise complaint it's
okay it's fine did you get the goo on
you only babies go to bed
before yeah
yeah sod my soda oh watch out there goo
out it's not goo okay it's filling I
haven't had any how some I want the I
want the the the shell give me the shell
stop the shell what Senpai expected when
friends come over get the goo off my
[Laughter]
leg Yeah I tissue oh I think there
should be some in the bathroom I did not
prepare
napkins I'm a
terrible
fell I feel like bi almost Falls
everywhere she goes but like in a cute
way and like not in a way where she gets
embarrassed about it she just like keeps
going cuz she's a rock it's just life
she's so sturdy it's just life keep on
tumbling H yeah she like gave me some
presents today and was like running away
and like almost bumped into something
and we just watched her go and we're
like there she goes how is she still
alive oh did I almost bump into did you
didn't even
realize we were all laughing like there
she
goes durable even actually that's a very
good adjective how are you guys feeling
about tomorrow
[Music]
really nervous super nervous everyone's
going to see you guys performing for the
first time in 3D
gum do your best we will we'll do our
best M so many people are cheering for
you guys yeah we excited to see
you yeah I'm trying to think of some
some way to tease the audience to make
them want to watch tomorrow um I mean
it's advent's first ever time for
[Music]
enough H yeah true enough actually they
don't need anything else imagine if are
you really going to miss fuo dance
together are you going to miss nissa's
boobs wait wait why is that I thought
you were going to say nissa's beautiful
singing both is good I guess yeah I know
I know what they want they don't care
about that's are you going to miss viu's
cuteness like there's no one as cute as
viu in the thank
you and shiori do you really want to
miss her she's so special she a special
being it's going to be amazing amazing
we've been practicing so
hard yeah that's why I'm so worn out
from today all the practice same my legs
I feel like my legs are so exhausted
that like I'm going to end up not being
able to sleep cuz they get like
paralyzed in a weird way when you walk
and like dance and like do that kind of
stuff when you walk a lot run a lot
dance a lot you know I have a bubble
blister on the bottom of my those are
the
worst what is this talk about this now
it means there's a bubble want me to pop
it
there
whoa whoa live live ballister popping on
stream dang let's get the let's get the
hand cam on I mean oh my Lord can you
imagine wait but how would you pop a
blister on a rock I feel like that
would this the video you know when you
split open the Rock and water comes out
water so old and I'm like w the water
that's be's blister yeah yeah this is
old ancient water yeah well a lot of
blisters end up having water inside of
them actually I think really well it's
not water it's just not infection either
cuz it's a blister like it's I don't
know it's hard to explain I understand
okay this is this is going to be weird
but I kind of like having blisters
because I like to poke cuz it's like a
it's like a fidget toy you like poke the
little it's squishy I like it it hurts
it's squishy what I like
it I respect your opinion but I disagree
respectfully
yeah cat huh huh yeah yeah I mean to
each their own I guess yeah sure maybe
what about um let me think yeah blisters
are blisters are tiem but when they're
on like the back of your your ankles
after wearing like tight shoes oh you
want you want to see all of mine there
there's this one and then there's this
one back here and there's this one here
see look
look yeah I have so many how do you
continue to wear shoes like that just go
barefoot I don't like shoes that's the
problem I like I don't wear shoes at any
point possible so when I wear them it
sucks Rock rubbing on rock yeah rock on
Rock blast rock rock
bleer what the heck people wear shoes
yeah you I mean the rock shoes are shoes
right are they shoes uh it's a debate
but a debate techn leave it up to their
speculation it's it's shoes she has to
grow yes but it's shoes that grow from
my body so are they actually shoes who
knows yes cuz you still have soft supple
feet underneath there yeah
waisa would know why did you punch I
didn't mean to punch you're kissing me
today
too I I HIIT it so I had to kiss it to
make it better
a do you want to know what what what
Nissa did today to me when like when
like we we saw each other you came you
came into the room and then you shoved
me down on the bed I didn't shove you
you did making it sound way worse I was
so excited to see her I I gave her a big
hug and I snuggled her and I tackled her
very lightly onto the bed so I could
proceed to continue to snuggle her like
she's a cute little plush that is some
bully Behavior recently to like who was
that I was like
oh then
[Music]
afterwards mystery
solved was it a mystery who gave me a
smooch out of nowhere would you like
when two s by me mhm oh my God I get so
scared from human touch but oh my God
she SM my head wa no no one's done that
to me before did it scare you I mean it
was okay like cuz she just did it and I
couldn't expect it like if I was well no
it was it was
fun if I if I was anticipating it it
might not have been so pleasant but it
came out of nowhere so it really wasn't
that bad it was like getting a shot yeah
a shot yeah like getting a flu a flu
shot or something
this here no's kisses are the same as
getting a full shot here first folks
yeah they just don't tell you they just
stick you with a quick stick and then
it's like done wa that wasn't so bad
yeah it's it's when you expect that you
psych yourself no I'm just going to say
I like n's kisses much better I will
take n's kisses many times over thing to
be able to take our minds off and
things but but but flu shots are f cuz
afterwards afterwards you get a cute
band-aid and some candy and then your
arm feels sore and there it's like a
nice sorage you I don't get that sort of
treatment anymore though it's different
for you different for rocks when they
get their shots
yeah yeah I don't know I feel like well
some people are scared of needles and
stuff like
that can't be help I mean it just you
just look away it's not there it's not
there if you look no no no it's still
there it's still frightening okay well
how about instead of needles though how
about when you go to the doctor and you
have to get a nose swab oh I hate those
you've never had to get a deep nose swab
I've never had I've never had a nose
swab Noob no swab no swab no swab yeah
I've never had one SW very very bad so I
had to get some for various tests that I
had to do to travel and they stick it
all the way up your nose and like you
can feel it itching your your brain and
they're like to happen yeah please don't
lomize me with a nose swamp well you
think they're trying to sometimes with
the nose SW I would they're like I'm
going to scramble it up yeah and they
tried to test me for like strep throat
or something and they had to do it and I
was like do you have to they're like yes
it's part of protocol and then they did
it and then I didn't have strip and I
was like why did I do this what a waste
what a waste like at least at least I
better be stre positive at that point if
you go that I better be sick I better be
sick or I'll be angry
true yeah sorry I don't have any drinks
by the way only macarons
sleep you can well chat do you guys
think I I was sleepy in the beginning of
this stream do you guys think I I
sounded sleepy they can probably tell
you bet that yes she is a bit yep yes
yes 100% not anymore though I'm wide
awake now that you guys are here cuz now
that you had the Nissa shot yeah true
now I'm full of adrenaline yeah that'll
wake you right up oh yeah definitely
it's crazy though because I feel like oh
thank you very much for the gift
memberships by the way you guys are very
sweet friends friends friends are here
please check out the the wallpaper it's
a little Saucy anyway um I I feel like
for for whatever
Reon n she
c c you B all the time with us huh yeah
what's so funny we know it's not it's
funny because I I just do it without
thinking
in why you
say I'm your sister too a that's first
time I've heard of
it sisters oh no Sisterhood
rejected sisters The Sisterhood of
Advent oh see yeah you can totally still
be sister she a different kind of sister
you know sister from another mister yeah
is what you're supposed to say I know
all kinds of weird sayings from my mom I
same get your ducks in a row like who
says that old people old
people yeah old m
not okay what about nap crabs
a does nobody know nap CRA what's nap
CRA it's when you take a nap in the
middle of the day and you wake up and
you're crabby you have the nap crabs
nobody knows that one feel well now now
all of us know it you already knew it
yeah yeah got to check you for nap crabs
now what do you mean you can't check
your friends for nap crabs I mean I
guess if you ask them what I know I know
when you like that oh when when she's
crabby after a nap yeah nap crabs it
sounds like a
bug got to checky for nap crabs it feels
like sounds if you if you go to sleep
and then don't touch my head I am good
don't they're touching each other's
heads I'm I'm just picking the life out
of oh yeah like a like a mother ape or
something pick them out and eat
them you going to eat them afterwards if
you find any
n fuz she's all lice free though thank
you
disappointing oh my
gosh narissa what how how does it go is
it like a what
what what what what wait
what is what
no
what no
no no it's like a r
h i sound like a like a dork I'm like
like it's cute
though No E no I started doing it
unconsciously oh my God I'm influencing
you every Everybody influences me I get
influenced by everybody she's very
impression So lately I've been going hi
yeah yeah you're easy to like imp not
fuzzy language fuzzy language hi why
does it smell so good in here does it
really I thought my pillow smell
cucumbers really cucumbers I thought my
pillow smelled like cilantro it's kind
of weird like detergent or something did
you not make it smell that way no I
no I laid down on the bed and I was like
M yummy nap right and then I smelled the
pillow and I was like
o is that cilantro I can't sleep now I
hate cilantro I love does anybody have
the the Sal I love salano I love salano
I love salano too [\h__\h] no my whole
family has the cilantro jeans
sorry
sorry that's fine it's a Reaper thing
can't be helped I think all Reapers have
it wait so question then um do you what
do you think are you do Al I know that
it's completely different but what do
you think of chuo mint I love it you
like it ice cream Cho mint ice cream
let's go baby yay what about you guys I
love it yeah
ium yeah mint good but no chocolo mint
no yes chocoloate mint I would like it
more minty than chocolate oh okay so
we're all team choco mint is mint ice
cream is just good Okay cool so we got
all the cool people here no ice cream
ice cream can't see no I have had it I
had it last year h ho I punished myself
with it was it good I don't know black
licorice ice cream though it might have
been bad no it wasn't ice cream it was
just licorice you have no you sound five
when you say no I don't know anything
what you sound five when you say no no
no no no oh man babies everywhere the
black licorice is like you mean like uh
I mean I guess did you guys ever have
like the Licor where like people taste
no this there's nothing wrong with
licorice it's like a a twisty and like
you peel each
strand uh licorice or do you mean like
the twi the red the red Twisted one it's
like a red Twisted one but like I was
told it was licorice by my grandma but
you peel each strand I know exactly what
you're talking about it's it's made by
the what what are those red sticks
called the cherry flavored on twizz yeah
it's I'm pretty sure it's like made by
same brand TW yeah yeah Twizzlers fck
too yeah huh okay I'm going to have to
push you out she just like not like
liquorice push her out the door she
doesn't like I I'm going to give you
green apple licorice that stuff is so
good no yeah the pull and PE well she's
unfixable I sleepy too you guys sleepy
go sleep go sleep I I have been rocking
back and forth so I don't fall asleep
this entire time go get a good night's
sleep so that we can be ready for
tomorrow sure it was fun talking you
guys thanks for being my special guest
today being my Barbie dolls coming to
say hi now you you don't you don't stay
up too long I'm watching a movie though
with the D you watch I'm watching die
hard
I it's the Christmas movie I know it's
not there's a different reason there's a
different there's what's the reason so
in one of my lyrics I almost put like a
mlan reference in there because the
people that I was writing with
recommended it to me and Universal said
no because of Rights and so we were
talking about it on stream and I said
huh we should watch Die Hard even though
it's not Christmas I know it's not
Christmas guy is that is that the bad
guy or the good guy Bruce Willis oh the
good guy yeah a good
guy bye guys old see you guys at the
concert yeah byebye there they go
bye-bye
hope you enjoyed your
macaroons
goodbye there they go let me put my
Barbie dolls
away there they go they're gone now that
was so fun talking with them though oh
man wait oh hold uput them did they
leave
something I
forgot where did I put it oh oh that's
an important thing don't don't use that
lose that bye-bye byebye
goodbye sorry my tummy is too my tummy
is on
away I was about to say my tummy's too
big but that's not
true that's not
true it's not these days it's actually
very flat but my hips on the other
hand my
hips sometimes I'll just be squeezing
through something and it can't be helped
it it can't be helped what will
happen I will knock I will knock things
over with my hips cuz I don't I don't
think about where hold on let me move
this chair it's going to make a strange
noise
okay but do they
lie my hips they don't
lie I saw someone say don't lie and I
said what about my hips being very very
wide I'm not lying
not they're
wide even Sancho said so my butt my butt
is just it's too big that's fine that's
fine the rest is okay the rest is okay
but I knock things over sometimes with
my with my wide hips I'll just be
walking around I think that ccho has
reported a similar thing she'd like turn
around and her wide hips would like make
something like fall down or something is
what she said
yeah oh well yeah there's a reason that
somebody left like a very strange review
at the place that I used to work where
they wrote a whole poem about them very
odd that was a strange
thing where is the bad part I don't know
some people like narrow hips that's okay
everybody's got their
taste hang on all my Barbie dolls are
gone I kind of feel so a little lonely
maybe I should get my Barbie back
love to have a doll with
me is it weird to keep dolls of your
friends just with
you just chilling with
you
maybe let's see oh God it moves what are
you frightened no need to be
frightened no need for fright depends
they're not voodoo dolls or anything
like that they're they're regular Barbie
dolls
for playing house and stuff like that
yeah sounds perfectly adjusted see
that's a dead beat that gets it honestly
that's a dead beat that
understands oh man those guys are such a
great Bunch though that was cool they
came in to say hello to
[Music]
sayah
yeah that was cool we all we all got a
chance to like you know chill together
as well but our story St will have to
come a bit later I think but we have we
we do have
[Music]
stories yeah we have
stories did bioo say B bow first I don't
think I heard B bow come from bio's
mouth I could be wrong though I could be
wrong I'm so glad we didn't get a noise
complaint I was a little worried about
that not going to
[Music]
lie she did they all did they all let
slip a bow bow I wish that I had let a
bow bow out while they were all all here
B bow I did it now but it still it
doesn't
count they're allow in the best way
though they're allow and lift my spirits
you know as soon as I heard the on the
door I was like oh man I bet that's
that's most of of Advent here at the
door I knew it and then they exploded
loed into their room with
baa hi maybe they all did say baa when
they
entered yeah I think that Shori is in a
very very deep sleep Shi she needs her
beauty rest you know she's very
beautiful she's got to she's got to keep
that that beautiful you
know yeah I didn't I didn't get a chance
to show my Senpai say say Senpai around
person say but I did I did invite her to
to dinner so that was
cool and then I made her eat delicious
things yeah but you know she's she's a
busy she's a busy lady so she's got
other stuff to do as
well that's okay honestly understandable
I'd be in a deep sleep before a concert
yeah you got to get your concert stamina
up you
know yeah
it would be cool to go on like a very
very tall roof somewhere and look out at
the city or something like that together
maybe that's a little too romantic no no
no no no
romantic just cool with friends
enigmatic recollection info oh boy what
can I say about it I wonder I think I've
seen a lot of people be like I don't
know what this is and like from an
outsider perspective I think about it
and I'm like ah yeah maybe people people
might be a little oh there we go a
little confused about what on Earth this
is right it seems maybe a bit unclear um
understandable does anyone know anything
I mean we all know um to me it's very
clear but like I feel like just because
we're revealing things little by little
um maybe it's kind of I don't know not
yeah I'm pretty sure it's a bit unclear
right now A lot of people are like oh
multimedia project yeah but like not in
the same way as can I please move um not
in the same way that uh Holo alternative
is I feel like Holo alternative is just
like hey guys wait for multimedia
releases you know like uh wait for this
this manga wait for this song um wait
for this video Etc but I think
Ian the um en Recco right enigmatic
recollection it's a little more
involved yeah it's it's like um
um we're we're doing more I guess um and
I can't give any details about the the
streams
but there will be streams right that's
been said I would really I think there's
heavier emphasis on the the streaming
part of this right I would I would put
less I would put less attention to like
the multimedia part and more attention
to the I mean it said it said gaming
sandbox right I would put more attention
into that for what this is if that makes
any sense um it's going to be really fun
I'm actually really really excited about
it I've been really looking forward to
it cuz like we we've known we've known
about this for a very long time um and
it's been in the works for a while but I
can't reveal anything about it so you
guys I mean all that I've all that I've
said here is just what what I think you
guys should like pay more attention to
in terms of like you know emphasizing
what what things what things should you
guys emphasize looking at out of the
information we've been given right so
I'm not necessarily revealing
anything anything new um per se but I
mean I'm super excited about how long
has it been in the works very long
time is all I can say I don't want to
give too much information away
but um it's something that I personally
like relate to and like a
lot um so just look forward to that
there will be many
streams there will be many streams for
many
people so please look forward to it I'm
going to be putting a lot of work into
it
myself no not
Glover what does Glover have to do with
any of this Glover Bros will always find
a way to insert Glover into
everything
yum um but yeah uh I think I know I'm
personally very hyped about it you guys
will get more info about it at the end
um of the when was it they announced
there's going to be a specific
information stream um so look forward to
that look forward to
that hold on a sec oh I'm getting a
message about
a friend who may be on their way
okay it's just me for bow I said
now but yeah the the whole the trailer
that had like all all of us with like
you know we were anime and stuff like
that yeah that I I hadn't seen that
actually but that was cool what was I
doing there I looked
intense I looked like a hero of some
kind of story that was crazy sorry to D
DM you on stream like that Mor I'll be
there soon
yoop I was
slaying shiori and Ena used the powers
together was sick everybody's combos was
very cool
[Music]
so many combos that I didn't think would
happen I looked very cute oh thanks I
feel
like I feel like um thankfully these
days um I'm mostly kind of portrayed as
being
um how do I
say like there there's always an air of
cuteness I'm like oh man I think they
got me
now I think they get me the the coolness
part is just one side of the coin but
most of it is is is cute I think these
days maybe it's the darkness the power
of Darkness that must be it oh did an
automated tweet go out let's
go I'm going to start getting sleepy
again let friendos come
[Music]
over la la la
la okay friend is coming friend is did I
not say friends oh I wasn't sure
okay hold on a
sec
friend
friend I can speak
English what does that have to do with
anything
Mory anyway
hi Windows ah Windows has got to reach
out and say hello to you guys sometimes
every once in a
while it's okay you're just eepy I'll
wake
up we just got to as soon as membership
starts we got
to head first dive bomb into
it yeah and then once it's over Mory
sleep H I'm thinking about if the bed is
comfortable and if it doesn't smell like
cilantro actually I should test that
theory hold
on does it smell like
cilantro it still smells like cilantro
either that or
detergent it's not as strong as
yesterday though
come on use a different
detergent oh actually hold on yeah wait
it all makes sense of course it smells
like cilantro because to me cilantro
smells like
soap oh someone's here oh I hope it's
not somebody that's going to get me for
a noise complaint oh hold
on
coming come
[Music]
you see my arm hit that in real time Old
Cutter
wow
where hello which one did I make you
sorry I must be I must be so sweaty I'm
so sorry okay no it's okay don't get
your don't wipe your sweat on me though
please no stop touching me with your
sweaty hands y I just came from the
world
yes
Z's Barbie doll hold on a second she's
standing across she's sitting across
from me but I've got her Barbie doll
here so you can see bar Barbie girl you
were very close is any anyone in the
chat who win did anyone go see oh yeah
cuz there was no there was no streaming
for that yeah you had to be there I had
to be there you had they say that don't
they yeah they do to be there you had to
be there you guys yeah I did you were
great see look at that they're there
still driving oh drive carefully they're
still driving but they had to tune in I
was there or you were
there sadly no that's okay you guys
there will be more chances in the future
oh do you quartet yeah bise there was a
do you c yeah so we did a do you with me
and ba and Kobo and MOA so oh my God I
had to like relearn my do you Coro kind
of because I I feel like I I forgot it
did you forget some of it yeah and
rearranged like you know the formation
cuz normally I dance and alone over with
the other waha black and white waha yeah
oh yeah you do your bird mating dance
and stuff like that together yeah I
remember that yeah but everybody seemed
very excited about D you so I'm so happy
cool wow that's awesome I want to see
but yeah no streaming no streaming guys
no streaming but oh I I can tell you a
little bit about about it yeah I want to
know this was the opening show like
there was just the first world tour of
many yeah and and it was at anime NYC
and so um we started with that summer
song The yeah oh the uh what is it
station yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah archive
station
archive
yeah yeah so I I originally already was
in that song um yeah you sang it last
summer yeah but now this was a little
bit of a different line
and then um then the Ian participants we
had our solos there was a
bami and there was the
MC and then you know everybody got a
solo and everybody got like uh two units
kind of so I had mine and kobo's unit oh
cute and then there was the doo unit
what did you wait I guess it's is it a
secret what song You and goo did go we
did I knew
the honey you guys but oh my God I don't
know like okay me and Kobo we thought it
would be funny to within the song
there's like this chant um the whole
song is like relying on the the audience
to cheer together yeah and there's this
chant in the middle of the song where
first K
goes which means K is super right and
then I
say and the audience has to repeat that
in the same Rhythm and we thought it
would be funny to like switch it up and
give you guys a completely different
chance to repeat oh my God and do you
think that they understood did they do
it it seemed like they were very taken
aback they were shocked yeah and their
reaction time was really slow I thought
you guys would be faster and then would
like hear it that I I tried yeah I tried
to say it really clearly like okay uh I
think kuu said uh k
k k k CH KU something she gave herself a
nickname is not
Ki is not Ki and she comes before me so
there was more visible confusion and
then then there was me I said Kiana can
make fright chicken out of me which is
very random and that's cute yeah I I
understand how that must be bamboozling
but now I don't know if we ever do this
again if if we should go back to the
original chant or if we should like
switch it up again I just got to have a
taco training camp for you guys for
cheering is it so difficult what you is
it too difficult I mean I feel like if
if everyone was like trained beforehand
it would be fine like once right if you
practice the call and response once with
them okay right or or you can just send
them all to a taco boot camp and then
you run them through the ringer doing a
bunch of different random chance to have
to repeat how does that sound guys how
does that sound kfp training I mean okay
just like for the future if we ever do
this song again just be ready maybe
we'll switch it up again so just like
listen closely and then repeat after us
yeah that's fine but yeah just a little
guidance you know and and if you feel
like you should repeat it repeat it
that's the best rule of thumb yes yes
exactly if you feel like you should
yeah we had a lot of exciting
combinations of people and and oh yeah
my solo was sleeptalking oh really how'd
that go I think you feel good about it
it's been a while since I did that one
too so I was glad that I could like
perform it in front of so many people
yeah that's the one where you have the
mannequin head right yeah I'm making out
with the
mannequin wait you're actually smooching
the mannequin you're just almost
smooching it it's a nice manquin
yeah it's pretty goodl looking mannequin
can't fault you for that true yeah it's
been a really it's been a super busy day
because you know we had a rehearsal and
stuff like that you know plus you have
the you had your thing yeah that's so
much I have I I have free concerts this
weekend so yeah and now you're here on
my stream saying hi to everybody I got
to like take a shower and stuff so I'm
not going to stay too long that's okay I
appreciate you coming to say hi I had
macaroons for everybody that oh my God
yeah you a Macar f one of them has like
sprinkles yeah sprinkles in it oh my god
did you which one did you try already I
haven't tried any of them but the the
Advent girls came by and and took a
bunch of them I don't eat macaroons that
often but it seems like by color you can
usually already tell what flavor that'll
be yeah I think
so sniff sniff sniff sniffer it's hard
to tell yeah maybe this what do you
think this one is that one looks kind of
like cookies and cream
maybe that's my guess but I don't know
sniffer sniff sniffer sniffer yeah
what's your favorite macaron flavor me
uh I like vanilla but I don't think
there's any vanilla in I'm boring I
think my favorite is like
lemon fruity yeah or
raspberry okay I think I'm just going to
go for the confetti one yeah the
confetti one looks the cutest for sure
so there's a little story with how I got
these these macaroons so macaroons so an
old friend of mine was um was suppose to
meet me um somewhere like before the
rehearsal right so we could go get like
a quick breakfast together and um and
she had sent a message with the date
like a really long time ago and I
assumed that it was today and so I
traveled quite a ways uh to meet up with
her at this place and I text her I'm
like where are you I've been waiting for
you and I just wait and wait and wait
and then I scroll up and read the text
message and she she had said
tomorrow and I was like oh no oh that's
some you're so Pawn I'm so Pawn I can't
read I just have no time to pay
attention I need to fix that but while I
was there I saw all these beautiful
macarons and I was like I guess I'll buy
these for my friends yeah and I bought a
bunch of bagels too for friends oh I
think they like kind of melted a little
bit they're a little melty oh yeah the
others oh no no no not on your outfit
I'm not sure what flavor this is but
it's good yeah it's yummy got them yummy
yeah the others also had it melting all
over them but they were saying really
strange perverted things so that was odd
yeah Advent just Advent things what did
I miss just Advent things and then
people was like oh let Get Off of You
Nissa and it's really strange they were
being they were being themselves um
Nissa come back I have something to lick
off here too
yo hey Advent come back come lick this
off of
kar AR and then yeah narissa surprised
me with like a kiss to the back of my
head and I was like wo I was shocked cuz
normally normally I don't really allow
those things but like she just kind of
like did it out of nowhere and it was
not bad it was like fine yeah cuz I get
nervous and stuff like that right yeah I
get hyper nervous I was like wo but she
was it was chill can I just say so far
because it's my it's my first time in
New York it's so cool yeah it's so cool
isn't it better than other places sorry
I love it so much more than la about to
say that like it's just a lot but I I
mean I honestly it maybe it's not fair
because I didn't see that much of La
either so maybe it's not fair but I I
like it here also I thought it would be
super super super hot because people
warned me so much kfp warned me so much
about the hotness oh yeah but it seems
like ever since like I don't know when
they warned me like two weeks ago or so
it has cooled down a lot yeah it's
really not that bad yeah beautiful today
yeah and like The Greenery is so lovely
someone said La rats aren't as fat yeah
I like fat rats chewing on pizza that's
what I I saw no rats so far it's cuz
they're all in the basements or in the
the the drains and stuff like that but
they're definitely chewing on big S
slices of cheese
pizza yeah but yeah I mean I I've really
enjoyed it so far and it's just been a
it's been nice it's it feels nice and
like I also felt like it it it felt I
know that I know that this is not the
clean
place in America right but I compared it
to LA and I was like wow you know it's
not as dirty as I thought it would be
and then you know Watson had like done
some research and stuff like that she's
said there's got to be a reason for that
and she looked into the weather and she
saw like it rained I was like so so so
what Watson's like that's the reason
it's got to be it's got to be why it's
not dirty I know I feel like there's
probably like plenty of dirty places we
just haven't seen them yeah right yeah
that's probably it I mean we haven't had
a lot of time to move too much around
but I I believe them when they say it's
a dirty place I believe but it Stills
like beautiful and cool I don't know I
feel like I'm also just kind of used to
Meandering around La and it's just it's
real dirty like it's just really dirty
these days the Subways are sticky says
that dead beat ah Subways I'm not I'm
not using the subway cuz I'm too scared
of sickness right now I don't want to
try it either I'm I mean in a way I want
to like see all the places that are in
my favorite sitcoms and there's a lot of
Subway scenes in my favorite sitcoms
like Seinfeld and so on um but I don't
know I feel like that's maybe too much I
don't want to go there I it's not worth
it just for the the Seinfeld tour
experience I've heard that it hasn't
been like updated since Seinfeld like
I'm said that to I'm like okay it has
been updated
since that's actually PR pretty funny no
reason they wanted to keep it that way
so that Seinfeld fans would be happy you
know okay that makes sense I should go
to appreciate it yeah dead beats are
saying all the biggest rats are in the
subway ah chewing on Pizza I got to
bring a big cheesy slice down to the
subway then I can have my
dream big big not ju not juicy rat stop
saying juicy rat it's so gross a big fat
rat chewing on Pizza are you are you
excited for the big day
I'm so excited we're going to be so
freaking tired after the next days maybe
you should not be doing a member
stream midnight I want to watch a movie
girl I am 100% sure that your members
would obviously understand that you need
sleep hello
like yeah put off the [\h__\h] movie I
promised them I promise them girl it's
literally [\h__\h] concert weekend and we
have to like you know they're my dead be
we need sleep and we need we need a lot
of energy tomorrow and the day after
tomorrow I know you're right we need so
much energy we
sleep okay um maybe see see see they all
agree like you really don't have to do
this go to sleep sleep put my
dead
anytime yeah any other day yeah I don't
know you could maybe even do it like
after I don't know if you if that works
but on the after the last day after at
midnight I don't know something like
that ah but at at midnight I wanted to
have a pizza party in my
room to celebrate more pizza more pizza
some more pizza a you want to do so many
things C you have to you know sorted out
a little bit not everything has to be
done at once I have to pick and choose
[Music]
favorites nah I'm sure everybody get
understands yeah we need sleep I suppose
so yeah n Callie stay up and go to the
concert sleep to PR okay well the dead
beats also make a good point stream is
kill yes you'll have to stay up till 2
the Phoenix has convinced the uh de
Reaper to kill her member stream
Die Hard Bruce Will is where were where
were you when Callie's member stream
died I was in her
room okay I listen to wise K but we're
going to move it just stay tuned to when
we're going to move it cuz I want to
watch Die Hard with you I'm sorry I hope
there's not no actual dead beats who are
actually angry at me now please don't be
mad at Kiara if I was strong enough I
would fight my weakness to resist Kiara
and say no Kiara I no want to watch a
movie I Am the samee voice of reason
here so yeah please don't be mad at if
you're going to get mad at somebody get
mad at me for not resisting the
Temptation Of The Devil this is already
special you're having like a place here
where we can jump in you know cuz I
didn't I did not bring any streaming
equipment so a yeah yeah that's why I
wanted friends to be able to come say hi
and you know oh I hope that's perhaps we
shall do a switch a oh a oh my God oh my
God aggressive they're aggressive are
you sure it's not a noise complaint I'm
scared I'm scared they're so
intense friends
friends I've been waiting for you
[Music]
friends
hello there's your objective is
complete hold on let me get is leaving
I'm going to take a shower bye wa wa has
convinced me to listen to the words of
the devil
sh oh wow everyone is now envisioning
Kiara sweaty wa I'll take a shower here
right you want to take a shower in here
shower so everyone can hear a live
shower oh my God my eyes are so bad you
can barely see the
comments oh my gosh at the front no you
sit at the front thank you for coming
[Music]
yipp don't God which one which one is it
sh probably this one maybe try it on the
door just try it on the door try it on
the door out
there just don't know which key it is oh
my gosh mine that's yours okay
bye see you later we've got IIs and
crony in the hot seat now Welcome
Friends
one chair it's one chair share one
chair share chair I'll sit I'll sit on
the chairs what you call it the arm
armr can can our both our butts fit I
think so I think both of you guys you
guys is busting oh yeah we can squeeze
yeah see I told you yeah we can squeeze
yeah are you sure yeah we the whole
chair breaks and I have to pay a fee
please no if that happens we'll pay half
yeah half
half for something you did half what a
deal it's your chair what a deal hey
o kiaha just convinced me to not do the
member stream afterward oh really she's
like go to bed but then again if you
think about it if I show up to the venue
sleep deprived that affects our overall
performance and then I don't want to let
everybody down you know so I guess I
sleep
you should die hard you should sleep
have you guys seen Die Hard no uh it's
the Christmas movie right oh yeah just
the christm I haven't watched it but
people I was meme of it s really that
hard meme yeah I was going to watch it
like for members but they were like oh
no you should save it for Christmas Iris
so I was just like okay I'll I guess
I'll save it for Christmas I always mix
up I've never watch die hard but I keep
thinking it's the same movie as the the
movie where the the daughter gets taken
and he oh taken yeah yeah Tak it I keep
mixing I don't know why I keep mixing I
I just have like such a big impression
of Taken it's stuck with you taken with
it yeah was taken shut up was taken by
the story do you remember the the speech
I have a very specific set of skills
yeah yeah uh well I forgot what the full
speech was but yeah like it it was just
like if you give my batter my my I mean
my daughter it'll be I don't know who
you are I when I find you I have the
skills a set of skills yeah a very
particular set of skills I want to see I
want to hear you perform that and then I
want somebody to like make a 3D version
of that somebody did that with funo once
I think it's pretty fun I need I need to
find a script like if that yeah just
look up the quotes I think that the the
aristocrats would love that yeah instant
me it would be dumb it would be so dumb
that would be great it would be great
yeah die hards apparently it's a
Christmas movie oh yeah you guys can
have macarons if you want they're a
little melty though so be careful cuz
they might all over the 300 calories per
macaroni you have to you have to it's
like it's like eating one bowl of rice
you know
gry oh my God you're right it is one
whole bowl of rice stop being the angel
on her shoulder swear to God oh God no
okay I I will hold back you don't want
just a bite just a bite then what what
are we going to do with the rest I'll
eat the rest of it maybe not the one
with the sprinkles sprinkles I don't
really like sprinkles oh you're not a
sprinkles fan no like one it comes to
ice cream and stuff sprinkles is it just
in the way no you had my rainbow That
was cuz it was rainbow she had my
birthday cake cookie and it was colorful
with like sprinkles
busted it wasn't it wasn't sprinkle
sprinkles it was just like colorful dots
it was it wasn't crunchy the the
sprinkles w't crunchy crunch I don't
like crunchy sprinkles cuz like for
example we have ice cream which is soft
and and you know moist or God I know
Chad loves that word but I mean anyway
like it's anyways ice cream is soft and
then sprinkles is crunchy I'm like I
don't like crunchy stuff in my soft
stuff you know like I stop saying that
Chad y it R stop
it yeah only soft sprinkles do you like
nuts on your ice cream me uh if it comes
with nuts on it I'll accept it but I
would never go out of my way to choose
to have nuts on my you like nuts
Cheo I got youw like chew nut
Che
that's that's nuts I'm going to kick you
out of the room please come back please
please don't leave me alone I'll get
sleepy I'll get sleepy again you should
get sleepy though yeah we should be so
tired yeah it was rehearsal was tough
today it was it was a lot my legs are
tired but all our legs are dead
everybody's legs are tired from all the
rehearsing we did do you want me to
massage your feet oh
no one's ever offered to do that I kind
of don't want you to touch them though
just cuz they could be dirty like I mean
I
[Laughter]
wear
what I swear to God we did noise
complain I'm going to get a noise
complaint cuz you guys test you test me
I could hear so much from outside the
room wait really oh my God you should oh
man I wonder how bad it was when Advent
came in it wasn't it wasn't that L when
Advent came in though holy I mean it was
cuz it was like so many people right
yeah they like busted down the door
they're
like like 50 million DB I was we're all
going to jail we're going to jail which
makes sense cuz it's Advent right of
course we go to jail but yeah I bet the
whole city heard them yeah are you guys
excited for tomorrow y are you guys
excited for the concert
yeah are you guys excited for the Ian
concert yeah
they're not they're not saying what I
want them to say wait what wait I don't
know are you excited for the Ian concert
are you are you
exited now they get
you no are you you're the one who made
that up I I I did that's Your Meme bro
it's been a while it's been a minute
it's been a minute to a question with a
question with a question with a question
and then it never ends ever yeah cuz
nobody wants to answer yeah so someone
says I don't get the meme it's not
supposed to make sense what a fake fan
fake F it's from SpongeBob oh I didn't
know that is it from SpongeBob is it
isn't that original I feel like that's a
crony original I don't know anyway I'm
excited I'm excited you guys you guys
have some fun stuff planned too we can't
spoil anything I'm like oh yeah let's
give like a teaser for what we're doing
but then I'm like what will not get us
in trouble nothing that's right cie is
actually doing
I'm doing what to be continued she is
she is doing an amazing amazing song and
she's going to she's going to burn the
the the king's theater to to the to
shreds collect a bunch of souls yeah cuz
her Aura was busting yeah bus busing
yeah it was it was
given I hope you guys are excited for my
performance of
it's all muted right now she's actually
saying she's saying the word it's just
muted right
[Music]
now this terrible I would hate I would
hate watching somebody and then they say
that I think I'd unsubscribe from them I
think I'd stop being their fan yeah King
St
exciting it's so pretty yeah have any of
you guys seen King's theater it's so
pretty why are we allowed to perform
there right it feels like oh my God it's
just so pretty like it feels Regal I'm
like wait we're going to be performing
here yeah we should be performing in
like ball gowns or something like it
feels like we should be performing Opera
in there or something I know like
musicals that's the best vibr I could
do this like a turkey gobl you can do VI
no you can do VI talk I can only do it
if I'm belting and then it's like a 50%
chance my voice doesn't crack I mean you
know no that that's how it works my
voice used to crack like crazy crazy in
the past but then it got so strong yeah
the muscles the muscles muscles frud
muscles Muses muscles muscles yeah don't
forget to put on your fanciest dresses
everybody you must be you don't need to
be fancy there's no dress code I mean I
always wonder like you know how there's
there's like chairs right there's chairs
but everyone ends up standing up anyways
and which is you know it's it's
definitely hype obviously you know we
want everyone to be super hype and like
waving their light sticks around like
crazy and dancing and stuff like that
but at the same time as as as someone
who has viewed concerts and stuff is
like when everyone stands up there's a
good chance I won't like you know people
like me would never be able to see
anything on stage CU there's always
someone taller than you in front of you
yeah yeah and then whenever that happens
I'm just like why couldn't people just
sit why couldn't people just sit sit out
I want to be able to say sh unless you
sit yeah it's so annoying that some
concerts I'm like I want to sit and
enjoy and people stand up and I'm like
here we freaking go again and when
someone stands up everyone has to stand
up exactly you still can barely see yeah
that's why theaters are supposed to go
slanted down with the seats and stuff
like that but like when everybody stands
up it doesn't freaking matter anymore so
bring stilts just kidding don't do that
because then the person behind you can't
see and then they get up on stilts and
the person behind them can't see it's
just a it be a staircase of people on
stilts SS
or you can just be really tall so that
people can just like watch between your
legs yeah like you like I feel like you
can't you can't become taller right like
even if you wanted to is there a way to
like become tall I there's a surgery
that gives you like an extra vertebrae
wait no you can become shorter I think
but I mean if shorter I feel like you
could probably just cut something but
yeah you can become taller but you need
to recover for a year uh there's a
surgery they said height surgery they
break your legs they break your oh they
and then they make spread the bone apart
a little bit so that the bone in between
will grow automatically or something I
think I kind of heard of that but I
think that barely CH you can't do that
too much I'm sure right what the I mean
it can't be that much you probably
increase your inch like what like a half
an inch or something like that it's like
for people that are like 5'5 and they're
just they're just begging begging for 5'
6 just so they can like feel good about
them here listen I love short for for
for madams for dudes for anybody for
anybody okay so you can only say that
cuz you're tall
true true a lot of people are short to
me no reason to break your legs please
please please don't we are going to
break a leg tomorrow but we won't we
won't want you to break some legs I see
what you did that was very cute actually
it was clever as F right it was
clever I love my short Queens all of you
right here remember you're 1 cm shorter
true n it's cool I'm fine with that oh
yeah we're oh yeah and you're not even
worth the competition oh oh oh we're
talking okay stra forward yeah yeah yeah
we are so
tall
St you wear heels though don't you yeah
yeah we heals we we all have heels I
think oh yeah I have heels
we all have heels sometimes we forget
that we're that tall someone's heels
taller though I feel like cron you have
the shortest heels I do yeah cuz it
hurts ah understandable yeah heels hurts
you you don't you don't know pain until
you're trying to run to catch a bus in
stilettos with like a this this thick he
what
stilettos super tall heels they're like
super tall super thin I used to wear
those in college that could snap anytime
kind yeah yeah yeah oh my God cuz I was
like in the gothic phase it's not a
phase cuz I'm Gothic
again but only a little only a little
bit of you're killing it yeah oh thank
you the only time does kill the only
time you're not Gothic is when you're
wearing the sheriff outfit right true
that's a good point well you guys know
my fashion sense is all black all the
time I can't be helped cuz I think black
goes with everything and then my entire
wardrobe ends up black because I think
it goes with everything
very appealing neutal col understandable
cuz when I was packing I was like oh
like I should pack this I should pack
that I too much clothes it's black
everything is black yeah just goes with
everything honestly it's it's the best
color cuz like what if you get a little
accessory that's like red oh you don't
have to worry about it clashing with
something like green CU that's Christmas
right cuz then oh it's black yeah yeah
you can just match them with anything
yeah and then black and red look cool
together it does they do they do look
cool yeah it's just black and orange
that makes me think of Halloween true
that's it I feel like any other
combination works though yeah black blue
black uh green maybe black huh what what
what I don't I don't get it someone else
thank you thank you she's sitting
between us maybe we should show her
let's show her what black and blue looks
like I'm already feeling like I'm going
to get a black and blue from the from
your eyes are already well okay from
your leg you guys are squeezed into the
chair
I it's so unfair I'm like spread like
man spreading out here with my legs all
the way open you sit like a boss girl
you were a girl boss you sit like a
Santa I want to sit on your lab yeah oh
really we could we could sit you want to
sit on her right lap and I sit on her
left lap come here my young children oh
really really
actually if if if you see actually we
will we will actually try she oh she's
scooting okay okay give it a try young
young baby children here maybe you
should sit on you can get on the bed and
then go around cuz this is
very wow let me try and see if I can yes
yes this is much more this is much
fairer okay okay give it a try young
ones oh wow you guys are actually you
guys are super light how is that really
this is light y you this light yeah yay
you guys are super light what the heck y
that can't be it's true I'm putting my
entire weight now yeah I can feel that I
can feel you started doing that how does
it feel now
warm warm
warm oh no Chad Chad's going to do be
too excited from that comment cie what
no it's just human warmth I'm the Grim
Reaper it's cold everything is cold
talking about we're not humans you're
not humans but like you you're real wake
up you're flesh beings Concepts yeah I
mean I'm actually an alien angel devil
thing but yeah okay but you're still you
still have like warm Flesh and Blood
true true true I'm a ghost though I'm
very cold what are you talking about I'm
also cold blooded too what you talking
about wait what I'm also very cold
blooded you a reptile really is that
what it mean oh you guys are all
reptilian okay hold on I get what you
mean you cool not a nice person Cold
Blood yeah I am I am ruthless I can put
your entire weight on her I am putting
my entire weight I'm putting my entire
weight see I have strong legs oh like oh
that's how you're sitting wait wait wait
like like like this yeah yeah yeah oh
like a
horse mounting mounting okay yeah
yeah does it change I don't think I
already put my whole weight on are so
strong oh it's not about strength it's
just my bones are rigid I'm a skeleton
really oh yeah true I am a skeleton
after all we all have a skeleton inside
of us everybody's got a skeleton in them
just waiting to crawl out that's
crazy and I love your I love how
colorful your laptop is do you like it
it's RGB it's
so this is so cool too so cool you have
this over hereit like a tiny monitor
it's just one laptop but you have two
monitors and I'm just like oh that's
nice a tiny baby monitor though I need
it yeah just you know assess things I
guess it is beautiful every single time
I and it has this many things it's
amazing yeah eight cores over cook I
mean over yeah overcooked over over it
can play eight games of overcooked all
at once it can eight instances of
overcooked it's crazy totally oh my God
what does overclocked mean again I
thought you we're going to ask what's
overcooked yeah I know what overcooked
is overclocked is I don't know Chad
explain what's I thought overclocked was
like something like unlocking the full
potential of put on turbo mode or
something yeah go in
Turbo you go too bony for your butt I
was I was going to wrap my hand around
you but I have my hands on my yeah I
know dark turbo okay okay faster let us
know if we let us know if your leg
starts dying I'm okay my bones can hold
out for a
bit
stop okay when you bounce up and like an
excited child that
hurts hey
y who is softer both they're flesh
beings
yeah you couldn't possibly compare what
you talking about yeah exactly sitting
on Papa's
La it's so [\h__\h] up
father cie
father you want to confess your sins to
me been a very good girl this year wait
is this Santa or a priest I don't think
kids sit on priest laps I'm getting
confused or maybe I've been bad oh
that's
stop otherwise why would you be on a
priest
slap you guys are wilded I know we
didn't even drink any alcohol I know I
know we're very sober and yeah I very
sober ladies yeah I don't know why we're
doing what we're doing this oh yeah you
guys just just had some sodas yeah no I
just had water yeah and oh yeah I guess
soda yeah yeah you had tood you love
soda yeah soda everyone should love soda
what you
know man I feel like I feel can you
pleas
relaxing I'm relaxing I'm relaxing is
that how you
relaxing no what what did you do I was
like not tensing I was doing the reverse
tensing up her muscles no I was doing
the reverse oh like like what squeeze
like like I'm I'm tensed right now but
I'm this is for relxing I wait I don't
see the difference wait J her try tense
up again she feels the difference I feel
I don't see the difference Okay so so
tense is like tense is not as painful as
when you relax MH when you relax it gets
a little painful mhm wait wait wait T
like Cron's doing something and I don't
know what she's doing she's doing
something mysterious what is she doing
was she like squeezing your thigh or
something with the with the
leg man stop no it's it's fine it's she
was just giving my leg a massage cuz the
dancing today was so difficult you're
welcome thank you yeah I appreciate it
do you actually get ticklish here no not
on my li only on my uh my feet maybe I
shouldn't say that feet my feet are
tickling feet your feet oh no the art so
stop no that feels nice oh that feels
nice uh that was not it's mostly around
like the this area it's a secret you
guys don't get to see this this area ooh
this area so that
stop don't touch stop I'm going to
beat stop it stop oh yeah I'm still on
your lap I should I should move too like
a good like a good child of God yeah
yeah thank you thank you thank you for
the wonderful experience you're welcome
great oh I'm always happy to you know
forgive your sins any day of the week oh
yes oh oh yes yes don't what what are
you trying to
start I I'm not going to ride I'm not
going to I'm not going to why are you
continuing let's no we're good you could
you could go start doing something a
what are you saying just like you could
stop you stop saying let's just here
you're making this word you guys are so
silly together I'm remembering Mario
Kart oh yeah oh Mario Kart that was
pretty funny Mario Kart was a do you
should
join I'll join next time if you want you
are a pro I need to train against you
cuz I want to be in C you like really
good you improved so well I remember at
the beginning I was like oh you know
Callie you know she's probably not she's
she's probably okay feelings are a
little hurt but that's I forgive you no
no like you just started right it's was
like oh you could tell she's a beginner
so I was just like oh she's still you
could tell she's a beginner and then
like like two days later all of a sudden
I'm just like wait oh my God C's like
five five people away from me and I'm
just like dying here and I'm like wait
Calli teach me the ways like how' you do
that I was I was I was absolutely
impressed at how fast you suddenly
improved and and I felt like wow I
played so much Mario Kart on my DS when
I was a kid and I'm just like wait I
guess that none of that matters if you
can improve this much in two
days but that means you guys can too you
know she has the sense we got to get
everyone in Ian into too cup for sure
man I've never been to too I've always
been like one step behind been I know
right that's why the only way I can
experience too if I is if I jump into
someone's stream that is already in so
you know if I true cuz I can't be in so
yes you can you can hopefully if they if
they do another one this this year next
year then then hopefully hopefully I was
also just really drunk
so yeah drunk R that's a rare S I feel
yeah that's a rare but I mean it's it's
fun to celebrate such an
event more like
stream you know what maybe I should not
stream next year maybe maybe I'll get
into tuo and then I can stream I can
stream if I get into tuo you know and
then I'll join and ruin it for you oh
that's how like a wonderful New Year's
gift yeah so kind ah friendship isn't it
beautiful
e what the heck we got to train
really yeah it was really nice though
because training that much made it
possible for me to beat all of my
friends when we had a tournament when we
got together it was like 20 of my
friends got together and I beat all of
them you doing so did you just like
learn the maps or something or is I just
practiced really hard with with the dead
beats and just did a bunch of streams
for it is and then every time that I was
like relaxing in between I'd like go
play it on my big TV instead and just
like practice there and then come back
and then play again yeah like like a
marioart just brings so much out of me
that like like when I was doing so bad
that's when I was just like you know you
know what fudge it I'm just going to
drink I practice so much for this and
I'm doing the horrible because of item
luck and and I don't know maybe skill
but maybe skill I I say it's 90% item Lu
but maybe is
skill true so like I was I was not
giving I was not giving a shitake
anymore and I just started drinking yeah
some of your hints were really useful
though oh the hints that oh yeah yeah we
were sharing hints before like before
the actual tournament because we were in
different groups like you know we W comp
so we were like you oh we're not
competition you know we could share our
our little hints yeah yeah MH yeah that
was something yeah okay that's pretty
funny actually is pretty useful right
yeah I know you you you told me a lot of
shortcuts I didn't know about secret
shortcuts secret shortcuts the shortcuts
are so important I remember you really
have to remember them yeah yeah I don't
want to I have to watch it's supposed to
be a fun casual tournament where you
know if you win you get a cool
GIF kind of was kind of how it ising
yeah bragging rights in GIF so it's just
like but in Holo that can't that can't
exist yeah you know we don't have to
take it serious serious we could just
have fun you have to you don't have to
but then everyone takes it seriously so
you you have this pressure where you
have to also take it seriously exactly
and it just becomes this Angy in fact
they're just saying that so that you can
lower your guard and then they're going
to just wipe you yeah oh yeah they'd be
like I didn't practice at all and then
they start zooming yeah I didn't
practice at all and then I I go
invisible I go invisible and then I'm
playing like two days before and then on
the last day like I just play all day I
play all day until the tournament yeah
I'm like oh I didn't do anything oh I
don't know oh you crammed it you crammed
I love cramming like last minute yeah
everybody's like how is she so good yeah
I thought I thought that when I saw you
you speed and like I think it was like
the day the day before when we were all
practicing or something I think we were
all practicing and then I noticed like
all of a sudden you were like getting
first place like multiple times in the
practice room and I was just like wait
wait what what did she do she must have
grinded so much well I did but I also
really want I also really wanted it a
lot because actually my switch that I
had wasn't working with the internet
like the ethernet cable that I hooked
into it it actually wasn't working and
so 30 minutes before the tournament
started I ran to the electronic store
and I bought a new Switch I think I
heard about that came home and I used
and it was definitely the new Switch
helped because I had no conne does that
mean you have like how many switches do
you have now two oh only two you don't
have one for work one for fun no three
no do you have three no I have two I
have two but I have two but I might get
a third I'm excited for switch to a
switch to me
too oh my God you're so funny she's
silly she's silly I'm going crazy going
crazy wait is there a detail I forgot I
kind of forget the details yeah what
details your mom let you have two switch
switches oh yeah and the first map was
okay so the first map that I chose
um was on accident because the one that
I wanted was like a it wasn't the
mushroom Gorge it was like the sky in
the sky with like the
cloud the one where you go on like this
uh this cannon in the middle of it right
yeah yeah yeah I think that's the one
I'm pretty sure and then at the end like
toward the jumpy flower there's a leaf
yeah the Le I know I know that's one of
the coures that's also on the DS or the
game Game Boy Advance maybe that was the
one that I played a lot so I was just
like so confident and I did horrible
yeah same actually that was my favorite
one though it's not Cloud top Cruise
it's a different one um but yeah so I
wanted to choose that one sky yeah Sky
Garden that's it I wanted to choose that
one so I went to go select it and I I
got too excited I accidentally chose the
one next to it which is my least
favorite course which is the one with
the cars oh God is it the nighttime one
or daytime daytime yeah and then it got
chosen for us to race on it and then I
won like SE third third anyway wa was it
second it might have been second
I think it was yeah it was second and
okay Senpai was just really far ahead
but yeah so I chose it by accident and I
got second in my least favorite one it
was weird maybe it was because like
something inside of me said it was like
I don't know the Primal Fear and hatred
of the course motivated me to you know
reverse psychology reverse psychology
there's something like I just don't like
you know how was coping and saying like
oh it's mainly like it's like 90% item
you know it's like not really skill but
then when you're actually in these
tournaments the people who are actually
good at it like are always like first or
second place like you know like the top
ones and like for example like OK Sena
and and I watch their streams too yeah
they all they're always for and then I
watch their I watch their practice
streams I'm like what are they doing so
differently from me I don't really see a
huge difference but they're hitting all
the shortcuts yeah they're hitting I
guess they're hitting all the shortcuts
really like really well I guess it's
probably the main thing but like yeah
like you know I see there dreams and I'm
just like wait what is so different like
but there must be skill if they're
always getting first or second place you
know they get coins I try to get coins
too I found out coins are I did say
coins are not important on your stream
butan I mean by that point that c like
coins don't kind of matter like it's
sotic everyone in chat be like the coins
oh my go she missed it in the coin so I
was just like drunk and be like crony
don't give her [\h__\h] talking about the
coin coins I get it I get it I get it
yeah yeah it's pretty funny actually I
guess the coin coins do sort of matter
if you can get them early yeah at the
toward the late game and you're trying
to like you know concentrate on coins
when you should be concentrating on
other stuff I feel like there's like
different priorities yeah for sure
there's like it's like you got to cater
your early game middle game and late
game like a MOA yeah like a MOA oh God
like a MOA it's all very important MOA
reminds me of Pokemon yeah MOA Pokemon
Unite that was crazy because Ian
actually didn't do bad even though we
still placed last it was very close just
cuz ID was the ID the ID W right well it
was crazy because we beat id id beat JP
and JP JP oh it was like a fullon like
Loop right
yeah yeah Pokemon
unit yeah the the the M kind of thing
yeah it was fun it was fun but it was
just really hard crazy I'm glad we did
it though we we made it we made it a a
struggle for them so that was cool mhm
yeah that was very
fun man big events are fun though in
general you yeah I hope I I can't wait
do yeah I can't wait for more bigger
events again in the future let's do
more I wna what do you guys think yeah
they want to see Ian ID cup why do you
think that we're going to beat him again
I don't think I feel like we have too
many Ian now though for Ian ID Cup oh
true right like ID yeah outnumbered it
would be it wouldn't be fair yeah not
every Ian would be able to join I feel
some of us would have to defect over to
the other side oh so it would be it
wouldn't be versus ID anymore it'd be
versus plus
ID yeah pure Ian cup could be
interesting I mean yeah we we have like
what 19 people now mhm wow that's a lot
of people when you really think about it
yeah that's a lot of a lot of folks but
I love every single one of them it was
just a while ago it was just so much
more smaller I'm just like wow we're
such a big group now what the heck and
like I feel like we've almost doubled in
size right since you guys have been here
yeah crazy to think about it is crazy MH
19 I wish it was a rounder number though
true true I 19 true oh but you know
maybe if you say 20 20 is like whoa
that's a big number when you see 19
you're like oh okay it's not 20 yeah
yeah it's not 20 it leaves a less less
of a big impression
maybe that's how it
is are you guys sleepy are you going to
go to bed I'm not going to kick you out
if you want to stay Oh I thought you
were talking to
chat are you guys sleep are you guys
sleepy
chat you should make sure you tuck
yourself in
[Music]
bed a glass of Wawa is something that
Mama Mory used to say to me but now I
can't help think about
was like a glass of Kiara what a glass
of waa of w yeah I always got to ask and
I want to I don't want you guys to be
too tired or anything like that but we
good what time is it oh okay oh that's a
lie actually that's that's a West Coast
time I think cuz I just didn't bother to
change it I think my phone automatically
changed to the time it's almost midnight
it automatically changes right when you
when you when you fly and then like you
yeah well if you use the internet like
pass over my phone which one's your
phone your your your battery your Mobile
Battery looks like your phone that's how
that's how big it is yeah that's a thick
boy that is a thick boy such a thick boy
can I charge my phone on the yeah heck
yeah oh no it's different cuz you have
Android CU you have Android this is USBC
no it's not it's a
lightning yeah iPhone is lightning no
your Android disgust me more iPhones
have changed their thing to USBC cables
yeah yeah I'm a
hero yeah yeah the newer ones yeah the
newer my iPhone is old okay yeah old
like you that
doesn't going I'm going to kill you I'm
going to kill I'm going to throw your
phone phone your phone is in my hand you
will never be able to I'll lose my
identity if I lose my phone you almost
lost your phone when you I miss my
identity you were like oh it's not this
fine you don't need to panic I was like
that's your phone like obviously you
know in Japan like there's a good chance
that someone you know even if you do
live there's a good chance someone will
bring it to the the police station and
it'll be fine but I was still really
worried and you were like it's fine I
know it wasn't fine but you like it's
fine okay I'm charging it for you thank
you oh you're oh my God you have like
you have you have all the you can charge
three at a time you can do three at a
time can do three at once I can do three
at one first from Iris herself Mory can
do three at one C can do three at
one Yus Yus emerges right before
midnight yeah dang yeah but you know I'm
all these three though they're all whoa
that just they're different ones sparked
for a sports really oh my god did I did
I accidentally almost electrocute myself
that would be hilarious if it happened
on stream I mean I'm scared I'm scared
try it again no no I'm not going to
touch the tip I'm not going to touch the
tip by that charger again no I'm scared
just give it up
[Music]
PR no nothing it's I just heard a like a
s I heard the spark and it kind of felt
like a really slight sting but I was
just scared like holy [\h__\h] wait I can
can sue them if that's if it's broken I
don't know like you want does anyone
else want to try I don't want to do that
you guys you you guys I actually wasn't
sure if I was seeing things or not right
I I heard it and and I felt it a little
it I heard it too it didn't hurt it
wasn't it wasn't that that strong God
I'm going to have to kill everyone here
wow it works much everyone here yeah you
guys I mean you touch it I'm going to
have to kill you why I thought the whole
point was I almost died from that so if
I why would I still die either way I
mean I'll take
yeah that's fine I'll make sure you
don't die yeah but I actually can't do
that per my contract but that's crazy
what the it actually like made like a
like a
sh I'll remove it for maybe I'm not a
hero maybe it's all a part of my plan
she can do three at a time and it's so
strong that I could have possibly is it
so
strong again your virus
emerg your virus emerges
no we're talking about charging phones
virus more like virus more like virus
buy into the
Afterlife I don't want to buy yet know
that's cute though it's very cute that
you almost died it's very cute it is
very cute death is so cute I've watched
too much final destination to want to
try that again oh true what's your
favorite one where the people die H
what's your favorite death I like the
tanning bed I like you a the one that
traumatized me the most was the the pool
one what happened to the pool the one
where like the dude like you know he
drops his like lucky ring or something
into the pool's like clog so he like
puts his like I don't know he he gets
stuck in the clog basically and then the
clog keeps like sucking out all the
water and he gets so strong he sucks all
his organs out and pushes out the other
wh like this other pipe yeah what wait
does it like out of his butthole like
yeah I think out of his butthole or
something wait wouldn't something else
be coming up before the organs then um
no so first he was pumping out the water
and then it pumps out the organs and
comes out the other from 200 it was just
so it it was malfunctioning obviously it
was to suck sit on the toilet for I
didn't pool we're talking about pool I
thought he was sitting hard toilet are
you going to you're not going to open
that I should Pandora's Box yeah like
you know she so like this is like the
same cookie that she was oh say
that why I can totally share the whole
story don't say that you totally share
this whole story about how you tried
your show it's because I care what do
you mean it's because of care you cared
you cared about your calorie intake
that's what you cared about you cared
about your own calorie so basically youa
she was like you know eating this cookie
that looked good and she was like you
want some and she was giving me half I
was like oh she's being kind and sharing
and sharing me half a cookie and by the
time I finish eating she's like by the
way the reason why I shared you half of
my cookie is cuz I look because of this
and she shares me the calorie number on
the on the
rapper that's what you guys were
laughing about yesterday I wasn't sure
she was like oh it's because of this
Shing and the
saturated bad and all the fs like like
this that's why that's why I shared it
with you and you ate all of
yo that's messed up not cuz I wanted to
be your friend or anything be nice to my
friend but actually cuz it's too many
calories mhm yes I felt but you
appreciated it in the beginning and I
was like oh a c really can I eat half of
them you were like yeah go ahead yeah go
ahead eat all of it it was it was half I
only ate half right it was half right it
was like you ate like 2/3 of it really
that wasn't half yeah that was
I was a big old rapper it's okay it's
okay we exercise so much we we we do be
dancing we do be so don't worry so much
so we good
grany gr not that saturated that though
you don't have to worry about what does
saturated fat what's the difference
between saturated fat and non-saturated
fat maybe saturated fat is moist or like
it's like saturated fat is like intense
fat like it's it's like it's saturated
with with oil the only thing I know
about saturated like the word saturated
is when you like refer to colors you
know all that color like saturate
saturated lightness you know photo yeah
that's what I think it's harder to break
down it's not water soluble saturated
fat has more hydrogen see it is moist I
was right really y eight whole
GRS I think it was more and the other
yeah the other one had like a lot of
sprinkles on it and was more colorful
it's like a birthday cake flavor it's
okay you didn't eat the entire thing
that was good oh my God what you're the
one who was like I want to eat more
cookie and you took the cookie and I ate
this I I have one cookie in my room I'm
good I'm good but an they got us so many
flavors yeah they're delicious it was
great it was delicious oh my goodness
she just walked in with a huge tray of
cookies and was like who has cookies
that's my all my
impression I want cookies can't is it's
pretty much like that why does she sound
like a
[Laughter]
cies they're saturated
fat she definitely did not see that she
didn't she wanted us to eat the cookies
she didn't want to disuade us from
eating
them thank you for cookies am thank you
they're delicious they're sinfully
delicious they are really sinfully
delicious I should eat this tomorrow
morning yeah it's good breakfast I have
a chocolate one I'm saving for after the
concerts are over my reward for our
Dancing Yeah I didn't eat much today you
ate nothing today I what the hecke air
you ate air and like at more special
dinner like I anything meal I'm doing
that intermittent fasting oh that's good
actually that's good stuff yeah it's not
even intermittent fasting it's like no
it's just fasting it's not intermittent
not even in a bit of fasting it's like
literally you eat like like just a tiny
bit of the and then you're like I'm full
and then we have dinner and I'm like
we're like we were all eating and you're
like I'm still full I'm like how the
hell are you still full after after all
they're like how well
well well I've been taking some
supplements that is so unhealthy okay is
so unhealthy Vin d right that good old
vitamin D let me just say that that is
magical but at the same time that is so
unhealthy like like definitely I do not
recommend that long term like I don't
recommend yeah they told me not to take
it in long term yeah cuz it says like
you know take it for maybe six it's
basically like yeah so her appetite is
like oh my God you're exposing me here
you mentioned it already it's
basically like the appetite you're like
I'm not hungry I'm like that is you're
supposed to be hungry you only intake
like what I would say you only you only
took like what probably like 300 400
calories
maybe I had
snacks what snacks CP bar granola
bar I
mean look it was tell like one yeah I
mean still that's still like a lie oh
that was just one
like I had three of
those Cliff Bars I had three of those
like you only had like one Cheerios and
it's like it was nothing it was the same
time that you it was the same time you
had that meal too yeah the one meal that
you had so technically you're supposed
to have another meal I mean technically
I also have usually one meal a day
usually but you know exactly but usually
that one meal would be a lot like I
would eat a lot in that one meal you ate
like air yeah air air can I mean you
need air to
survive it makes sense yeah anyways like
yeah she didn't eat at all and I'm
worried you just got to be careful why
are you worried I'm not I'm
worried you already totally fine you
don't have to worry about anything you
don't have to worry about anything
Strangler I am worried about your health
oh my God you are perfect give crony
that pizza you were saving for the rat
say you always say you're perfect you
were perfect the way you special rat
Pizza just for you are you
taking you're beautiful yeah I actually
have I have a friend who like took like
not supplements but like was doing the
needle thing for for weight loss right
you guys know what I'm talking about
what's the needle thing I'll tell you
what it's called later but like it's
it's not is it the o yeah it's it's
meant it's meant not for you you you're
only it's for people with a disease that
you know some people use that medicine
for oh we'll tell you about it later
what that is um I have a friend who's
doing that and well they they did it and
then they lost a ton of weight and then
they started eating normally again and
now they look like Quasimoto
from yeah cuz it all went like back up
to their upper body and like into their
shoulders and their arms that sounds
terrif not in the lower part of their
body why why won't go to why won't it go
to the lower part of the body no one
knows there's just not enough research
Done Yet anymore oh my God yet yeah is
this like a new procedure or something
what is uh it's kind of emerged in the
last like well it's it's existed for a
long time but people started using it
for for weight loss like um I think Rec
in recent years interesting yeah anyway
I'm not touching that with the temp
that's very frightening also I'm scared
of I'm scared of needling myself I had
to do that I'm scared of shots and like
you know like back like even like shots
like even getting the flu shot I'm just
like shaking like I don't want to see
the needle I yeah yeah very frightening
actually I had to I had to do that um
after my surgery for my knee um it was
it was bad and my grandma said I used to
be a nurse back in the day even though
she's a grim reaper she used to be a
nurse Grim Reaper which is insane maybe
that's why she sucked at it because
she's like I'll do it for you because I
have that experience well then I
remember that she hadn't she hadn't
given anyone a shot in 50
years and it was just she put it in my
thigh right and it was just four Bru
four huge bruises I heard I heard that
giving shots is like the most simple
thing that you can learn first for when
you're in the medical field was what I
heard it's like the very first thing
they teach you really there was one like
nurse that was practicing and she was
like oh yeah we're we're just going to
draw your blood like the draw blood is
different compared to like vac you
really can just poke
anywhere yeah but drawing blood you have
to actually find like the the vein and
you have to like poke it I've only had
one or two experience like one
experience with drawing blood that
actually didn't hurt but everything else
is always like you know since drawing
blood takes a while too they they have
to slowly feel the you know feel the
thing right so it takes like you know a
few minutes and I'm just like in pain
the whole time like ow it's pain you got
to look at something and focus on and
sometimes if you're like out out they be
like okay let me try again you know and
then they would they would take it out
and punch it back in again and it still
hurts and she just like never mind just
just go and just hurry up and end my
misery you know like yeah I had that
with my bloodshot and also when I ended
up in ER they use this like big plastic
tube and like shove it up your blood
vessel the IV
right yeah I it's IV right the straw
right yeah and then and then they like
put it put it in wrong like after they
like put the entire thing in and they're
like oh w oops like did a mistake let's
do it all over again what do you mean
whoops I'm going to kill you yeah I
know going to faint just from listening
to that oh my god oh someone said tell
them about the secret tube oh go secret
tube there's a secret tube from my
surgery my knee surgery ended up taking
a lot longer than it was supposed to
take and um because it became longer you
I woke up and they're like hey there myy
hope you're doing good you know welcome
to the world again you didn't die yay
and I'm like oh that's great cuz I'm the
Grom but nice um thank goodness cuz that
would make a lot of sense so I wake up
and I'm like oh great so do I just go to
the recovery room they're like well
first of all just stay right there cuz
we have to take out secret tube and I
say oh what's that cuz I don't feel
anything yeah I don't feel anything yet
and then they tell me where it is and I
I screamed at the top of my lungs and I
said don't touch it don't touch it
because and suddenly I realized where it
was and then I tensed up where was it oh
yeah well I mean if it's a long time you
can't use the bathroom anything it was
there oh is that why there was a secret
tube yeah and like it's very narrow you
know like that area doesn't it hurt like
hell after you go to what the [\h__\h] is
that about I've never experienced that
before what no you're very lucky and
wait it hurts to take out like take out
the secret tube or is it it feels so so
so it wait Did you just said it hurt
does it hurt or does it feels we HTS
feels weird hurt it hurts and then you
go to the washroom cuz you know you need
to like do what's natural and it's it's
Burns it burns it feels like you
are pour in
blood I mean cuz it has to go into your
orgon right wait is it that far yeah
it's that deep yeah it's got to drain I
mean so so when you when you take out
the secret tube you're just like oh my
God like they have to pull it out yeah
yeah put it pull it out but you would
think that they would only pull out like
just a tin yeah it feels like blood is
spilling out when you're using guess
what it's it's ribbed so that it can't
fall out easily so so it's it's larger
sounds like a horror movie what that
sounds like a torture device oh it
is no please stop stop stop you guys are
afraid of the truth I'm tell just
hearing this yeah that's why you have to
be under when they're you know it's got
a seal so wait so wait why didn't they
why didn't they take out the secret tube
when you were when you were you know
knocked out that's what I was think they
didn't know when I was going to wake up
is the thing and also I think maybe
maybe your usually like when it comes to
what do you call it um you know the
thing that puts you asleep um anesthesia
anesthesia don't they like calculate
like you know a specific amount of n
just to make sure you don't actually die
and then like you know and also
calculates how long they would it would
put you to sleep because what if you
wake up during the surgery you know like
they would make sure you're definitely
asleep for a certain period of time so
you can take out the tube like right
before they W they're also accounting
for the possibility that you won't be
able to get it from the
bed yeah yeah oh I think they just they
I think it's convenience for them just
making sure that like you're awake and
everything's fine and you know cuz then
maybe you leak you'll end up leaking but
but
I made a
mess why' you say that with a big smile
on your face o I made a big mess n stop
with the big smile it makes me want to
punch you you make it sound like it's
like a service or something I made a
little
oops no no no I'm just thinking like if
you know if it's like Barbed and it
hurts like hell to take out and
everything honestly making a mess sounds
like a better deal than actually having
to take it out take out the thing right
like I mean true but they don't you know
the nurses they're thinking suck it up
patient I mean couldn't they just like
you know if they're worried about a mess
then they could just take out the tube a
little bit before you go to sleep and if
something were to happen they would just
they would just put a sheet underneath
your like you know your body to make
sure if anything does happen it will be
like a giant pad you know yeah you would
think right yes you would think right
this is what it like that's a instead of
taking out a barbed tube out of your you
know I me it's not see it's got to stay
in place there's like a bulb there oh my
God it goes all the way there yeah so
it's got to sorry I'm showing her a
picture so it's got to go up and then
that Circle see that so it doesn't slip
out but they have to pull it out wait so
there's a circle like a bead yeah like a
bead it's not rib it's like there's a
bead and it's like a a large bead that's
better why it was so
painful but a whole bead coming out of
what yeah it's like a large Circle oh my
God that I'm glad I've never experienced
that but I'm scared the next time I ever
have to go under anesthesia I have to
worry about the specialty long only if
it's a long surgery how long were we
talking like um they there was a
complication so mine ended up being 6
and 1 half
hours so yeah that is pretty long a long
surg like four like minimum four to 5
hours like you will have to the only
surgery I've experienced was like was
pretty sure it was like you know an hour
and a half or two I I think so I didn't
have to worry about the special tube
yeah Special Tu I woke up and I was I
was fine yeah like wisdom teeth and
stuff like that you won't need it for
they don't put you to sleep for wisdom
teeth right you got put to sleep really
mhm for wisdom teeth I they just like it
was laughing gas not like intervenient
yeah laughing gas and anesthesia is
different anesthesia is like Knock You
Out totally like I think it depends Chad
is mixed so like half of them are saying
they got put to sleep half are saying no
I think it depends the procedure one of
my teeth needed to be cut into five
pieces so they're like oh you're going
to sleep ah yeah we putting you to sleep
when they crush your whole tooth right
yeah they had to they had to split it
that sounds terrifying yeah it's pretty
horrific Be Careful by the way yeah
secret too we're talking about a nose
tube guys it's a nose tube that's all
don't worry about it so much don't worry
doesn't the Anastasia like have a weird
taste yeah you taste like metal in your
in your mouth but I didn't taste it I
passed out before I could taste wait how
would you taste it it goes in your like
through a shot in your body right you
don't tasted you just tasted anyway
really I I tasted like something sour
and it's really unpleasant I was like E
I was just like ow and like even before
I could say ow like you say ah and then
it's like and then you're sleep yours
yeah that's they would be like okay
we're gonna we're gonna put the you know
we're gonna put you to sleep count from
10 and I'm like 10 nine eight and
somewhere maybe around six or five I was
just and
then yeah I was like ow I couldn't even
say I didn't even say ow I was like I
felt the ow felt for out and then even
before I could even finish out it was
painful for you what the heck it I just
felt like a sharp like a something sharp
it was really burn actually very brief
very brief and then the next thing I
knew I woke up woke up with a really dry
throat yeah yeah what happened oh yeah
cuz did you get throat a throat thing or
no it wasn't a throat it wasn't a throat
thing it was it was for my shoulder oh I
see that sounds painful yeah oh they
probably put a tube down to make sure
that oh yeah that's why that's that's
why it hurt yeah I was actually I was
super scared of the anesthesia which is
why they didn't countdown for me because
they knew that it would give me more
anxiety but I was like shaking as as I
was being walked to the to the uh
hospital bed that they were going to
wheel me into the room with and I was
very nervous and then the Ania they they
didn't put you on like a a thing to make
you not nervous I he did and you were
still nervous well I well he gave me
like um a pill at first that he was like
they gave me an IV they gave me an IV
that made me super
happy well yeah I want some of that well
it it casually it it very casually
slowly started working because as we
were walking I was like I don't want to
do this and then as I got to the bed I
was like maybe I do want to to do this
cuz it started working cuz what he did
is he used a syringe to put it in the
the tube that was going into my arm
while we were walking it was crazy I'm
like can you really do that he right
before I mean honestly at that point you
would just be nervous for the last one
minute they did it to me because I was
super nervous for like an hour before
that oh my God lucky what I mean oh and
then they and then they put they ivd me
and then within like 10 15 minutes I was
just how can they tell that you're
nervous I was I guess yes they could
tell I was very nervous did you tell
them you were nervous I mean I could
barely talk to people back then so I I
just had my parents with me and I was
just like shaking like very SC mommy I'm
going to
die scar mommy I'm scared I'm going to
die she be like it's fine oh really I
was just more like if I die I die I
don't even think I think they
automatically just even if maybe if even
if I wasn't nervous maybe they
automatically were going to put me on
that anyways I don't know I don't know
maybe cuz you know I was young I was
like a kid I was kidis so like maybe
they were like oh she's a kid we'll
we'll make sure she doesn't have a
traumatic experience and I don't know
how very kind of them to do that maybe
it was it should have it must have been
covered under insurance so you would
hope right yeah no I don't think I I
think it would definitely be covered
inures yeah M yeah that's cool though I
mean that was it it was covered right
yeah it was that's cool it's covered
because sometimes some things are not
covered especially you're a person who
doesn't my parents always ask like
before they do anything in doctors or
dentists is this covered in Insurance
smart is smart yeah like basically
whenever you go to the dentist right
they would put like give you like a form
like what they're planning on doing
today or like you know like oh check all
these forms check it and my dad would
just be like no like everything that's
covered under Insurance we'll do
everything that's not covered in
Insurance take it out take it out take
it out you don't need we don't need it
we'll never do it yeah oh that's smart
yeah sensible Sensible they say
sensible yeah oh man medical stuff
medical stuff makes Mory feel strange
yeah what a fun conversation before a
concert right hey nobody break any legs
for real or spraying anything for real
they better be breaking Dimensions
instead oh we're breaking
Dimensions only thing we're breaking is
of good plug I know good segue that was
cool go that was cool I love like you're
looking at that you can't even see
anything well see do you see how there's
my little Barbie doll of me ah yeah
that's the that's the real me but I join
I made a room oh that's the way that I
hack the fact that like you have to be
on the the Wi-Fi is they have to be
connected with both of these it doesn't
work it doesn't work in hotels no it
doesn't so the way I pack it as I make a
a room for all of us to collaborate in
except it's just me inside of it so this
is the me from my computer and then I
joined on my phone and this is me here
it's like a Multiverse yeah and I can
move myself
around hi it works if it works it works
I don't know that's how it works yeah
well it's just a little hack I
discovered oh my God you're oh genius
that's very I don't agree but thank you
you're such a genius oh my gosh
compliments I was just looking at
something else too but yeah wait what
nothing no I was just no you you can't
just say that no no no nothing nothing
nothing nothing what were you looking at
what are you looking at no it's just the
outfit is very
beautiful I was looking at the eye mask
I was looking the outfit is beautiful oh
I mean the outfit is beautiful everyone
should get PJs so we can have legit
sleep sleepover yeah I want to get P at
some yeah do it what kind would you want
cute or would you want like Darkness
like beautiful or like maybe sexy lady I
don't know what would you want to do I
kind of want matching sexy lady but at
the matching sexy lady but I also like
also want something fluffy and I'm just
like fluffy and Max and sexy lady don't
match so I think it have to be one or
the other could be like cute sexy what's
sex balance fluffy sexy I think of like
a rich ays or something like that what
Anis oh um an arys is like the child of
um a really rich person so Oh I thought
you were talking about Greek gods or
something oh I thought you were talking
Final Fantasy
oh no no like an ays like a super rich
ays or something that's like the
daughter of like a a hotel tycoon or
something like that they've got like
fluffy cuffs and like very like delcious
pajamas but like like uh fluffy boots
and like headband and stuff I that's
what I think of
O fluffy boots fluffy yeah fluffy I
don't know fluff fluff fluff is
nice yeah I wonder I very what about
frilly frilly oh frilly yeah frilly
that's girly yeah yeah that's like that
be like cute sexy
true cute sexy true cuty yeah I want I
think like the balance would be like for
pajamas it' be like 7 seven cute three
sexy ah yeah I can see that I see I see
looking for you is like probably the
good balance I feel like if it's too
sexy then then you know when you reveal
a chat would be
like better a do yeah for sure yeah I
prefer to get
it's better to not
yeah self no no no no no it's beautiful
you're beautiful Callie no I was just
talking I was just talking about what
have you done no no no I was I was just
talking about how when it comes to when
it comes to the war sexy I think I was I
was just for the for the room wear
rather for room wear than I think it
would be something more like swimsuits
and stuff like that in the future that I
want to go with the sexiness you know so
you think I'm why are you nodding at
me you think I'm beautiful yeah you're
beautiful you're beautiful you're Beau
beautiful D
MCA you're beautiful do they actually
say the MCA
DMC they don't right dmca you're
beautiful don't say dmca in the song Oh
you said the MCA I thought you said the
MCA
that what do they
do man do you do you guys like my hard
eyes yeah hard eyes mother effort I
think my first time seeing your heart
art really oh wow I just I really like
your dis shuffled hair thank you see
this is initially let me put it up
really quick this is supposed to be the
only one and like it's cute and whatnot
but then I was like what
if Bed Head Bed Head people really like
bedad Bed Head it was a good choice I
mean this is really how I wake up and
stream I don't know yeah bedad is bedad
Kelly is now this yeah the Bed Head
Celly makes me think it's so it's sexy
cute really sexy cute yeah it is
cute I didn't see it that way I I kind
of saw it as like PKU and like wow I
can't believe she's so lazy she can't
brush her hair that's why I said sexy
cute the sexy is the sexiness and then
the cute is the punk is the oh I see I
see I get it you're right clumsy I
thought that people were thinking you my
hair is disheveled for other reasons or
something like that you know what other
reason never mind it doesn't matter CR
what would you wear if it was pajamas
would you wear like a t-shirt and shorts
or something or uh realistically
speaking I'd rather get mine like you
know really casual I get mine from mui
ah yeah yeah which means nothing right
doesn't that what it means no no she's
talking about G she's talking about you
know you know um oh the the you know
sleep in the nude
no okay I'm sorry I know we got quiet it
sounded like I was going to say
something
no we talking about like you know the
clothing brand yeah yeah like blank they
have blankets and furniture they have a
lot of yeah they have PJs too it's like
you know like just it's like simple
simple
PJs simple realistically speaking I
would do that but if I were to get an
outfit I would get something fancy
business what's you sleep in a
suit getting a new meta what's business
I'm develop that's that's the thing
business but sexy oh sexy business how
do you be business with room that's why
that's why you'll have to see how do you
be business with roomware like you can
be it's roomware why would you be
business with room you can be in a zoom
call in your pjs oh oh so like it's the
typ where only the top half is actually
business and then the bottom half is
that's an idea yeah that's a good idea
yeah that's an idea I like it yeah it's
like sexy yeah I've seen I've seen a
joke video of the zoom call like the job
interview it was like it was a a skit
like obviously it was a joke but like
basically the interviewee like the
person being interviewed was like only
having like their face like like over up
to their neck and be like hi I'm here
for my interview and then the the
interview of the interviewer was just
like what what happened to the bottom
half there oh no it's just my chair is
my chair is just so low like high and
the screen the camera is just in a
really weird position so this is highest
I can go I can't go any higher but
obviously it's just cuz they're all like
you know they're not
wearing they're they're yeah they're not
even wearing the top half of their suit
or anything it was it was funny yeah
that's pretty silly actually it's a
pretty funny skit you got to send that
to me I need to see that too it's it's a
Japanese skip is so funny yeah they they
do a lot of similar stuff Al in
the yeah need to
see don't tell me to go to sleep I died
she died which means she needs to go to
sleep I guess guess I guess that's a
sign oh my God oh my God we were here
for that long yeah you guys you guys
were here you fly real quick wait do you
consider yourself to be time like as a
whole or are you just like the one who
governs it oh the more say crony flies
and I'm like what are you talking about
it's not like crony is the concept of
time I'm not I'm a warden of time that's
what I was thinking right she's not
actually time yeah there's a higher up
she just has a clock on her head I'm
just an
employee just an I'm just a you know
like a lesser being in this higher
scheme of things I see but you're so
strong though I'm strong
but my employer is stronger the
strongest yeah the most OP what's your
employer's name I don't know
actually you don't know who your boss is
I feel like a lot of dead beats can
probably relate to that actually it's
very corporate to not know who your boss
is I don't have a boss I Am My Own Boss
my wow that's so lucky I Am My Own Boss
did you guys see the did you guys see I
have shooting beams everywhere yeah that
was pretty cool shooting beams you
looked awesome I I can beat
Goku I don't think so I can beat can can
you really I can beat one level of Super
Saiyan
Goku one one level if he maxes more than
more more you know how like the Super
Saiyan there's like two two or three
different like levels like first there's
a first level of Super Saiyan and
there's a higher lever super saian where
his hair gos even more like lighter and
more like sharper and there's like so
many l you could beat
Krillin yeah yeah I yeah of course I can
of course I can be Krillin what you
talking I'm talking about Goku here and
you're saying Krillin don't know you are
so rude though wow that's some shade you
could probably beat Yamcha too of
course yo you know start start saying
that I could beat people like freeze or
anything and then we're talking and then
we're talking she doesn't believe that
though no you can probably take on both
of them both
Krillin even at the same time maybe on a
good day yeah day that's that's a that's
a thing see I'm like complimenting no
that's not a compliment no like you can
take on two individuals that's amazing
two individual it's pretty cool
yeah I'm this is this is shame this is
shame I I am a magical Nephilim that
that half angel half demon and I can
shoot beams and you're saying I can only
beat Yamcha and K
together they can't beat Hope come on
now yeah right I'm also a concept right
I I don't know actually I I don't really
know but yeah I think I you're like an
agent of hope I feel I thought you were
I don't know what you are actually
anymore you're here to spread hope
that's your Miss incarnate of hope I'm
yeah hope incarnate yeah I'm hope
incarnate and I'm also an
angelon starting to forget who are yeah
we're starting to forget but why I
wonder why I don't know why we're
forgetting I think all of us and Ian are
starting to forget a lot of things
you're so right I don't remember where I
put my phone I ate breast two minutes
ago not even two minutes a minute ago 30
seconds ago and I have to use Google
find my phone feature to look for my
phone I've been forgetting so much to
I've been forgetting my my very basic
levels of like like you know doing stuff
in daily life that I almost electrocuted
myself just a bit ago too again when I
was when I was taking the cable out of
my phone what do you mean electrocuted
you were
charging seems a bit
entic Yeah Yeah enigmatic yeah
mysterious that's crazy oh my God we're
oh yeah okay yeah yeah recollect it at
some point we could probably perhaps
recollect it yeah Rec is it recollect is
a recollect how do you guys pronounce it
recollect I say recollect thought I
can't recollect recollection I can't
recollect how you're supposed to say
recollect it's not it's not is it is it
supposed to be recollect but you always
say read something other words it's
recollect but then when you're putting
it into a word it's recollection yeah oh
I see I don't know why it's not
recollection bro it's English English is
weird English doesn't make a lot of
sense don't worry too much about it
English is weird don't worry we have
things like neck of the wood and ducks
in a ro neck in the
woods neck in the neck of the woods are
you from neck in the woods are you you
neck of the woods her neck in the woods
until said it yeah I was just like
what's neck in the what neck of the
woods are you in what does that mean why
is she talking about trees and woods all
of a sudden I think it's neck in the
woods it's neck of the woods neck of the
woods neck in the woods what why why is
she talk about necks in the woods that
sounds dark it sounds dark there's a
dark meaning here very dark yeah well by
the way thank you very much for the 50
gift memberships I just saw that thank
you everybody for the gift memberships
that was very kind I appreciate you
let's go this is pretty late and I feel
like Kiara's going to yell at me cuz she
she made me cancel my memb stream so I
could go to sleep we probably need to
end here do you guys have any last
words any last words
[Music]
ladies time to die all right I'm going
to kill him now all right see see you
guys woo
why are you excited about that stop
being EXC look at them all go woo look
what you freaking started y let's go
dying go get our our beauty quote
unquote Beauty
Rest what is beautiful about sleeping I
feel like I wake up in the morning
like mouth wide
open beut if no one interrupts tomorrow
is a big day it is a big day we hope we
can see you guys there it's a big day
for all the us everybody make sure you
come okay yeah come come I got to wake
up super early to put on my makeup true
yeah you look beautiful you don't need
makeup girl I need
makeup anyway anyway anyway we we are
going to be all together tomorrow it's
going to be great and then you were
going to say something I don't remember
what I was going to say so no worries it
was probably something like it's really
EX
yeah it was probably something that was
we're breaking breaking Minds breaking
Minds breaking legs breaking mind break
are we sure are you sure that's what we
want to do yeah I'm kind of nervous in a
positive way obviously positive mind
brain if you say so ladies and breaking
Dimension breaking di Dimension bra okay
that's that's a little more comfortable
I we're becoming 4D are we wait I didn't
know about that
guys oh God I don't know if I want to do
that just look forward to it guys and if
if you can't be at the venue stream it
there's streaming tickets still
available available they'll always be
available they never run out what a deal
what a deal there's two days by the way
guys two days wow that's crazy two days
with two different set lists and we're
all performing on each one but you'll
have to wait and see how it goes no way
yeah so get both if you can get both if
you want the maximum experience
experience experience
experience yeah do it or I'll kill you
kill you kill you kill you I don't have
my go XLR with me so I have to do like a
I can tell does that one not have any
like effects no effects for that not
even like Reverb n not even Reverb cuz I
just I typically use it for like my my
good mic when I'm recording songs and I
don't need to put any like effects on
them cuz it needs to be the raw vocals
actually I was looking into this before
oh yeah it's a good one right he's a
strong boy it's expensive though it is
but he's a strong boy he does the job
well I guess we'll be going to sleep now
you guys separately in separate rooms
and separate beds just wanted to
clarify clarify we will be going to
sleep why did you have to elaborate that
it's
obvious obvious do you really think we
were all going to be like okay let's
sleep and we just hop into K's bed sat
on my lap and said some really strange
things so I mean it can't be helped that
I'm a little nervous it was mainly cron
what are they going to do to me I mean
yeah it was mainly CR it was mainly
crony doing the weird thing oh yeah it
wasn't just me though no I was being
very I said a lot of weird things but
you contributed to some I did I yeah
some just some just some just some okay
we're really leaving now we were promis
we could talk for a million years though
honestly I feel like this
danger bye everybody we'll catch you on
the flip
side
[Applause]
[Music]
peace nice ending screen oh do you like
it me with my kazoo just me and Mak
kazoo I'm so silly
[Music]
oh