[Music]
hmm
it'd be christmas still
ho ho ho
i don't even know where the other one is
do i have it in here
i don't even know
oh oh it's there oh
wait but
oh
[Music]
but i like the loading music
get me
oh
whoa
okay get again
keep the music
but this is nice too
[Music]
i mean it's still january though
still january still acceptable
[Music]
hello
i can't wait i can't wait i don't i
don't have patience hello i'm here
i was going to let you guys wait a
little bit longer but like i'm just
looking at the screen
staring at it
[Music]
okay um i woke up
i woke up from a nap
and uh this movie is so confused i guess
i guess because i woke up too early
today maybe but i you know how i always
give smoothie
um wet food every morning
morning i mean whenever i wake up
and now i woke up a second time and she
thinks she didn't get food yet or
something and terrorizes me with her
meows and i'm like smooth
smoothie
you already got
wet food today shut up now shop but she
wouldn't shut up so i had to give
trunkers in smoothie a snack
hello
hello kikiniki
i just gave myself a heart attack for a
moment
and i can't explain why
for a moment my heart sank
into my stomach
because i thought i called smoothie by
the wrong name
[Laughter]
but no smoothie is smooth smoothie
smoothie smoothie smoothie chocolate is
chunky
you know how that feels when your heart
sinks into your stomach
because you think you did
a yummy
it's good we didn't do it yummy
welcome
[Music]
i woke up early today and uh i'm gonna
wake up early tomorrow as well
um
actually i was able to sleep pretty
early
i slept at like midnight already holy
wow
but i
i woke up
like at 4 00 am
and couldn't fall back asleep for two
hours
so that's probably because normally at 4
am i'm still awake
yeah but it's okay i ended up getting
enough sleep for
the yagu talk um we'll talk a little bit
about it today yeah yeah
we recorded that ho ho ho
oh so kill hi evening okay
[Music]
on my it's my hat it's my zelda hat hey
here's my link link cat eh this isn't i
did i did find someone sent it to me
again and i saved it again i'm sure it's
already on my pc and now it's on my pc
twice oh but i do have this one too oh
being yeah i found it thanks to you guys
korean water
quality
which one
do we want today we had green last time
we can do this one this time
this is my hat today
um
yes beautiful hat
let's move myself
um over here okay it fits perfectly
yeah
i like the green scuffed on me too me
too me too i like both
if only i could attach them to my head
properly man
that's a big dream of mine
getting that option
it's my biggest dream is all i want
is all i want
to do
energy
um the scarf is so good thank you green
has a green hat has a lot of so
thank you green bean one is quite
charming oh
oh
make a tiny link kiara and put the green
hat on her
mate make a tiny link yeah what do you
mean make a tiny link kiana i did get
some cute artwork oh my god i wanna i
wanna show you this one so um you guys
have been drawing me as link again
absolutely gorgeous beautiful
majestic
divine
um
there was one that stood out to me
though
wait
a minute
thank you for drawing me as link
thank you
here it is
here it is do you have a png of that i
need a png of that
would you look at that from sean eon eon
this is in the perfect set i want to put
it like
yo
do you have a png shiny one are you here
if you have a png i want to put it like
here like a trophy or something like a
figure
it's it's in in that same style as the
game like a clave here it's so cute yeah
oh i didn't see him here there it is i
can make one let's go
yo you're really good at recreating that
art style
oh sh where the hell is the game
where's that guy oh wait no not like
that oops oops
here we go oh
put the scuff hat on this one i i guess
i could
[Music]
i can see if it fits
i'm gonna try it should be a dlc
character
i should be a dlc character for
everything for everything
where's my smash invitation
um chroma key i guess i could chroma key
but then it's the same color as the as
the feathers the background is pretty
much the same color as
the hair feathers
so it would chroma key that [\h__\h] out too
um
i could put it into
you know what
one second let me put it into photoshop
you know what shawnee your name let me
try to do it myself
might be quicker might be quicker
and then i can get it in full size too
oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
wait
put it in the top right but i want it to
be close to me
i want to be close to me
the grass makes it difficult
let me try
[Music]
okay
uh
here
okay let's see if that looks choco wait
the new kia amiibo i don't own a single
amiibo
okay it kind of worked i think
oh wait it ended up being a little bit
transparent [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i made it i made my character
invisible as if i was a ghost
oh sure
[Music]
oh should be fine okay save spng
yo yo yo
yo
now this exclusive figurine
not on sale
but
cute
oh i want it here though i wanted to be
here
cute
who wants this one who wants it
so can we put the hat on
although
the proper hat would look i think a lot
oh
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
it doesn't really work the head shape is
wrong
and there's the other hats
[\h__\h] uh the other hand saying to play
can't can't do it no can do no can do
that's okay
it's okay it already has enough
link linkishness to it just by the by
the look
mirror it scale it up you guys are
relentless
you guys don't give up okay transform
horizontally
okay it looks so cute though scale it up
you said it doesn't work so well i need
to adjust it to the
proper
head size
no it's still there unless unless wait
if i cut
like cut it like here
really heal you
i just cut it more
oh
okay that kind of works
it's my trophy live
i'm my own trophy live
power
oh wait you've been you haven't even
been listening to the music dammit good
good zelda music has been playing the
whole time
flawless
there we go
count
i feel like we should switch hats
the skull head
looks better on me i feel like oh well
oh well okey-dokey
so we're gonna play zelda today
uh
and read super chats later on because i
need to catch up and
but i want to end it
if possible by 11 pm
or like 11 30. because you know i gotta
wake up early again yeah yeah okay
i didn't even turn off the switch since
last time
okay i know i know the controls i think
yeah mm-hmm
ah
so wait where did we leave off
it literally just came out of the
dungeon right
[Music]
so so so
uh where where
they'll go
help
i forgot i forgot they did they did give
some hints i think where to go but i
forklift
does anyone remember
fourth dungeon is next yeah yeah
waterfall ah at the total heights in
there
okay wait how do we get there
can i fall can i drop down here and then
go up
oh ooh stone in the way go there go
there
can i go through
here
ah go all the way to the right side
and i built the bridge here no i built
the bridge there is it
never mind
we need another teleportation you're
still pretty alright it's right there
okay we can go to
here no i didn't activate this one yet i
think
we can go to
we can go
uh
i was just wondering why you were saying
that okay because i forgot yeah yeah for
the castle do you have to go for a
castle
just check it out uh-huh is there the
dessert is on the bottom right of the
world yeah yeah we're not going to the
dessert i think we're going up here now
um
still don't know how to
[Music]
how to
dash in the game
i mean
there is the the one
this one
yeah ouch
[Music]
okay
so ah
i can get kind of closer just hoping
that from here on i'll be able to
get closer
alrighty
[Music]
yes
how's it how are you all doing guys
how's it going
i'm slowly waking up for my nap
i think this is the right way
[Music]
winding down for for the day sounds nice
doing okay tired sleeping schedule
messed up same
doing all right had trouble sleeping
stamp we're just uh
all the same isn't that beautiful
okay so i i don't think i can swim yet
so i can't go this way
[\h__\h] i have to even though i teleported
here it doesn't help me at all
it doesn't help me at all i have to go
i'll go all the way around
go here back to the other teleportation
in order to go up here yeah i don't
think it really helped me i think i have
to go back unless you guys know a secret
passage passage because i can't yeah i
can't
really not doing good but it is what it
is [\h__\h]
hope it gets better for you wait now i
can't even okay no problem
might as well see what the taylor phone
guy says oh yeah
if we see a different one on the way
yes
i will do that
you need to you have to head back to the
village anyway
okay
okay you said that right then said it's
wrong was that on purpose what did i
pass
because i'm not sure which one is the
right one
it's probably passage but cause that
passage sounds
more correct to me
[Music]
hello i just gotta make a call really
quickly
i like the um music in telephone
as well in the telephone thingy
which is located in the southeast of the
island you will find something called
the angler key
how much more obvious do i have to be
bye cook
okay we don't have to go up we have to
go to the desert okay we don't also have
we don't even have to go to
uh
the
[\h__\h]
to the village we just go straight to
the desert i guess dessert this desert
this is also one that constantly
confuses me i know it's
desert
is it wait dessert dessert yes there's
desert yes
[Music]
what
okay i guess it's pretty close
ah but i have to walk around again
[\h__\h] that
what's the shortcut to the desert can i
go here
wait no i can't oh wait catch
[Music]
going back it confuses native speakers
too okay
well then
break this [\h__\h]
out of the way
why is it keep coming back
[Music]
okay what is it she's just if she's just
going to sing to me again i'm going to
be mad
i just have to sing what can i say what
do you like to do glinky out
why are you telling me to talk to her
hey mommy she knows
okay but i have to go this way anyway
because otherwise i can't seem to go to
the beach
so i will go this way the original the
ochi
hmm
also this has been bothering me maybe
fine
yeah i was wondering about that but what
do i do with the apples
wait can i eat them to get health
oh
oh but he eats them right away he
doesn't store them
oh
wait what would a green apple do then
get the bottle bottle
where was that bottle again
oh [\h__\h] wow
[Music]
ringo
bingo just oh i thank you
[Music]
what
what no what the hell you're not wrong
what the hell it's all good
uh
the green ones are the same oh okay wait
wait what about the ball told you
where how do we get the photo again
where was the bottle i heard something
about the bottle last time
waffle is up that way
oh wait do i need to fish for it
i'll get we can try let's warm up a
little bit
[Music]
he's here with the report
[Laughter]
ah
as promised i have a value for links
awakening rupees l-a-r-s i came up with
one canadian dollar is nine links
awakening rupees or one euro is 13 likes
awakening rupees so here's 976 rupees
but
youtube isn't letting me post a link to
the report oh don't worry maybe if you
send it on as a twitter reply we can
read it during the super chat reading
remember guys when he did the
um
the other links the other zelda game
that we played suck skyward sword
skyward sorry there's a whole report
a whole series report about
a stupid tangent
like how much of rupee would be in our
money how much it would be worth
that was wonderful
so
uh fish
here's how you do it hold a and release
it to cast your line out the longer you
hold it the farther you'll cast
old a release it to cast your line okay
you can tuck on your line by moving l if
you want to reel it in a hurry tap a
real quick you've got this little body
okay
oh oh you see them okay
uh i don't see them wait i do see a
bottle
[Music]
i don't want the fish
on
i'm coming for you
what do i get if i get like a big fish
though i wonder
oh [\h__\h] i think i want too far
ah no i got it uh and then oh tap tap
tap tap
i was just about to ask if that gonna if
that is going to happen
yes
oh he doesn't reset it but now it's
pretty hard to
see mini queena
johnny we'll do it from the very left
tap a yeah but we gotta be
careful
[Music]
oh because that
there's a few uh
few fishies in the way
[Music]
how is it how's it looking oh we got it
we got it uh
[Music]
that fish horrible positioning
don't give me a fish i guess
oh you're not even gonna take that
yes
take it come on i want something out of
this since i can't
oh
[Music]
there we go i have one for each
might need to catch inverse well at
least this one's out of the way although
this one would probably would have not
really been a problem
okay i will dream bigger than that yes
go bingo go home
i love you rupees okay
[Music]
oh okay
what's that
watch them well that was worth it
oh it's so worth it
i got the jackpot i'm guessing the other
ones don't really have anything special
though
go down
stream heart contain
i have a little bit of a headache man
why
somewhere
here
oh no no it's under the fish
there it is
okay
i dare you to bonk me again
oh oh oh oh oh oh
i'm getting it
oh oh oh oh yes
[Music]
i think that's all the precious things
you can get in here
but i'm gonna try to get all the fish
now
or at least the big one
wait where did that pink one came from
come from
i think uh
they added a new one
that one wasn't here before
no i don't want the small one no
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] get it go get it
oh [\h__\h]
okay get to get this one
please uh
please
oh
[\h__\h]
i'm bad at fishing
[Music]
foreign
he looks pretty cute man he got a lot of
meat on him
ah
how much do i get from that
23.00
okay
a new layer oh maybe we might want to
fish a little deeper down we love this
one
wait do i perhaps get a heart piece
another one like
oh yes yes i did
wait but that's it right no more hard
pieces after that
you get another hard piece
oh my god sheesh fish
oops [\h__\h]
what another one
unbelievable
[Music]
no no i don't want you
no no no no no
no
stupid fish
real big fish there's probably more you
got an upgraded lure for bigger fish and
now i'm wondering or we get ah also i
don't think you get any more containers
probably you just get um
uh
wait i want to change the law
uh i can't i can still do it
um i'm thinking there is probably gonna
just give me a big rupee
okay
[Music]
which is fine too we can always make use
of money
[Music]
look at me
[\h__\h] why am i so low
[Music]
oh i don't want my command
yes goodbye come here come here
smash that button
i didn't realize i didn't expect
that fish to be such a [\h__\h]
damn it
let's send some more fishes in here
ah not the small one
oh yeah
later you can fish from mario ah
put a um
figurines
for the people's houses
a small one came in i want the big
one another small one came in
[Music]
uh-oh
[Applause]
how did i get that first big fish anyway
no no wait i don't even wanna never mind
no
ew
fishies are so slippery anyway don't
smash slope
don't smash when it fights
you gotta let go when you pull
what what
what is that logic
is that real fishing logic
[Laughter]
all right i'll get back to this
eventually but we got two heart pieces
uh did that give me a full container now
i feel like i have one more container
than usual already
wait let me see
yeah it did holy [\h__\h]
we got a new heart from that
oh
[Music]
guys i'm i'm
i'm legit worried about my throat at the
moment
like it's not like it hurts really
really
badly
but i do have
um like a
itchy
itchy feeling down there
[Music]
even
like a really small one it's like a hint
of it it's like i i know what's coming
you know
um
and i don't want to have a like a
no speaking arc
where i'm not gonna stream for
like a month or so i don't want that to
happen man but um
i gotta i gotta [\h__\h] yeah
i gotta check out
the doctor and see what what the doctor
says because i feel like
with your throat is probably like a cat
because cats don't tell you when they
feel bad
i think
nice
[Music]
i think um
that with your throat of your vocal
cords you probably won't notice
that early like i've heard of uh
uh
i think also it was the same case for
some holy members like they they were
just streaming normally and then they go
to the doctor and then they're told that
their vocal cords are like
uh
what do you call it uh internet uh
they're like
um
[Music]
on flames
yeah we don't want permanent damage
yeah i've been uh also during whole talk
that i recorded today i've been
licking the fruit candies
inflamed yes on flames in flames same
thing
i'm gonna
lick those throat candies like it's
still one thing that i have
available to eat
where what i'm supposed to look oops for
something here [\h__\h] uh what if i kill
the
monkey
no okay
ow
i came looking for something
uh
[Music]
i forgot what they said to me
better safe than sorry yeah
uh
a talking band no no no we don't want it
to get that far that's why we gotta be
careful
uh
ah a walk
let me see
where is ah here it is yeah yeah okay i
mean
give me that
a bomb wow we have found is this what we
are looking for
who was that
i heard a noise when i walked in here
some kind of ugg noise
did you hear that
i don't think i can do anything here
way later this is not it
wait what am i looking for guys simple
car
is it this is a different wall someone
said there's a wall here i thought that
that's where
i needed to
go i need a special item to see oh so he
is there afterward i'm not imagining
[Music]
bottom right of the map okay i won't
give it a try
it goes down
wasn't there a dead end here
ah no okay but i thought the beach ended
here so i was like
this is really the right way to
go i think ever been here before
martha's bae what's in this house
again empty house kind of sucks
oh
that is a really random house if the
floor is crumbling and falling apart but
that's a beautiful flower
[Music]
seashell
she sounds seashells
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
i stood on that for a little bit too
long
hold on
the door to the cabinet is hanging off
its hinges nobody's used this thing in a
while
did the person die
but wait what about the thing that i can
uh
this
am i not able to
uh
this this is what i want to do
well uh worth it
no not really worth it it actually does
nothing i thought maybe it would have
some effect
nope
worth a try though what for trap
it's abandoned yeah
dynamo nina by the way the reason why
i'm wearing the pacifier
because last time i said it's a baby
game and then i died so often and you
guys were saying uh you should wear the
pacifier next time so here i am
[Music]
that was well hidden i thought it was
only the platforms
i want to ask again excuse me
uh
the yarn there's the original
reason you will find something called
yarn or desert okay that's the place
we're looking for
aha
oh now it is uncovered
some are very well hidden
uh
this doesn't look like a desert though
but you gotta say
and there's a heart container there
remember that one
you know what maybe i can mark it on the
map
um
mark yes ah
heart container is here
yano desert i guess is here okay
[Music]
uh
do i have to go from above
no
maybe through
this little
hidey hole
you want to head to the library in the
village soon oh
a tunnel to the north what
i have to go there for a tunnel in the
north
people told me to go down here i don't
believe it
i don't believe it
oh thank you guys for renewing your
memberships
[Music]
i will see i will try um hold on i can't
i can't jump and then
[Music]
believe in yourself believe it so what
is this what is this here
ah
another
swim place we can't swim yet
remember this one too for
later when we can swim
[Music]
uh
jump first try let's go
[Music]
i'm i'm not gonna deal with these
enemies unless i have to
maybe maybe for here
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
maybe through there uh
thank you oh thanks for making it
worthwhile you think so thank you
thank you
uh how do i find aya i pick him up i
pick him up
and then
there we go that one seems out i was
gonna say that one looks like there's no
one in there [\h__\h] you stop moving
okay
i keep on bonking against the enemies
um by the way thank you for the lovely
compilations of my deaths last time
i saw a bunch of clips
that was your lego collection i don't
have a lego collection but let's go
where are we now
where where are we ah oh
i don't know if that helps us
yeah thank you for all the beautiful
compilations
there is
no way for me to go over to the
thingy from here
okay i gotta go through water here or
like yeah
if i go up here
go to the right this is kind of a dead
end here there's water again
thank you john mon
yeah i think so too i need to check out
my throat like the even if it's just a
slight a tiny hint of um
stinkiness stink stinkiness i think
that's already a really bad sign
um
there's a tunnel
doko
is the tunnel somewhere here because for
this one there was
um just water and this one just let me
hear
stinky fruit
no no stingy stinky
tunnel in the trees
here
i'll i will or do you mean somewhere
else other trees
down here
that would make sense or no wait no no
no it must be here because then it
probably leads to this one
okay
[Music]
yes okay i will try to find a secret
tunnel
[\h__\h] it i will kill you
i can never kill you
so secret tunnel secret tunnel
secret tunnel
animal village marcus bay
well
uh that's one way of finding
[Music]
oh you're saying they recover even more
no
get out of here get out of here
excellent tracking skills thank you
oh i know the hard piece down here
um can i mark it while i'm down here
i guess i can heart piece
stream
secret heart piece
okay now we are here
um
down up
let's see
why i already see
[Music]
well she's not here
and i don't know if i can help you
a bunch of bunnies here
is this pickle and
i wonder if everyone from pakolan's adds
pickle at the end of their sentences
it wouldn't make sense because it's
called pecoland
[Music]
i wonder if she ever said something
about that
[Music]
hello
yo that soup looks good i'm actually
hungry here
please
give food to me
is that possibly a honeycomb yeah
oh you want the honeycomb
finally answer anything anything i'll
put it on my pizza
pizza
okay
[Music]
i almost forgot about the quest
one pickle that once said that every
pickle onion speaks pickle dish
so
they add pickle at the end of the
sentences is that pickle dish
why did
piccolo cringe and pickle and said
pickle
just because um
she is too used to
the way people perceive it outside of
pickle land maybe to give you a
serious reason for it
no i'm not in the mood for pizza today
um
and i know the tub of goo is i sleep
right in the laundry on the desert once
he's asleep he won't budge for a long
time what can you repeat that what
well hey take a little money and wake
him up while we're singing
that slob would wake up if we jump if he
heard her saying for sure
who are we talking about
my brain wasn't registering what you
were saying
i have this problem when i read things
out loud for you guys sometimes my brain
just will not register
anything
i hate that especially when the game is
trying to explain me explain me like
some some
controls
oh
brain working full power so you want me
to go back
to the village to get marine for someone
some sleeping guys
[Music]
there's a lot of marines recently marion
senpai from whole life
then
from that new anime who looks gorgeous
and then there's this marine
which mine is your favorite that
is that
yes i did the fishing game what was the
other thing that people said ah library
right the library people said to go to
the library
asap where was that again
it's the library this is not the library
central
good choice good answer
otherwise i was gonna rat you out
this looks like the mountain is flexing
his arms his muscle arms am i the only
one who sees it like that
and the mountain's head is a is the egg
[Laughter]
good
what is this the hidden power of color
do you want to read this book yes
there's a new world of color under the
five gravestones
three four five two one
there
can someone write this down three up
four right five up
two left one
down
let me let me um
let me write that down three
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
let me pin it once it comes up i'm using
hybrid chad did you guys know the maker
of hyperchad is uh kfb and i'm his or
she
did you know
[Applause]
you didn't know that did you
maybe you did
yeah
[Laughter]
thank you
we got some smart people in kfp man they
can do stuff they can program things and
make games and stuff
one of us want to find one of us oh
another one of us thing that i had the
other day is um
uh someone tweeted at me uh
because they were thinking probably
um that we were playing schwartz schwarz
schwarz vice
in that official stream on friday which
way or not but someone thought we would
be doing that and then
showed me that there was a schwarz vice
tournament going on
uh like a few days ago two to three days
ago and and one guy who almost became
the champion he he got into the last
round and and he was using my
kiwawa birthday merchandise playmat
yeah let me show you let me show you i
want to show you
let me show you
where did i save it did i save it i copy
pasted it
let me see i want to show you
where is that dude
where is he he's one of us too
almost became uh
the monster
where is it what did i say
what what
[Music]
i don't know where it is i thought i
sent it to uh genma
i did send it i hear this
here it is
i got it i got it
and this is another perfect example of
how you can use
uh
here how you can use my playmat
i know
look at him using using that
look at him
[Music]
what a chad
why b if you're here we're so proud of
you for making it until the uh
final
he made it until the finals man yeah
amazing
you got mike wazowski's
what what do you mean i got mike with
speed
based chimpkin
good job yeah good good game i guess
if you find him if you find him
point him out to me
we need to give him like a like a
medal or something
your face was covered i mean huh
ah
i guess i did yeah yeah that is one one
problem that i'm not very happy with is
that with these playmats so you know if
you use it for cards often the important
parts are covered up by cards
so you know what would improve that if
we even also put out card sleeves
then if anything it would be covered up
by more kiara which is then no problem
yeah sleeps would be sick yeah but it's
not really a priority for me for
merchandise so feel free to make them
yourself i guess
big brain move
yeah yeah but this is indeed uh quite
a way of uh
um
advertising advertisement placing
all according to kaikaku
it's a bit a bit embarrassing but also
flattering to see myself
being used like that somewhere else from
you guys thank you
um
really
really what k kaku means plan what the
[\h__\h]
didn't know try and vote you might and
you may open a new path
are you worthy to receive the power of
color what's this world of color about
maybe you should try and see i honestly
wonder i don't remember what that was
about can we even get the picture down
no
it says
not realistic
not realistic but okay
um
power of color
i already see color though
what is that about
what is that about and what did i come
here for oh yeah mario mario marin
[\h__\h] where's she
you know
money why don't you worry me is this
like where she disappears
my name
[Music]
good idea
should have followed that myself or i
could ask the [\h__\h] maybe the fox knows
he knows nothing
huh mommy's not like you what happened
to her
you know nothing useless children
uh
docile night
where do we look for her
i think this is when she went to the
beach really do you know where marine is
worked too hard and now my broom is
wanted to handle
boom
that sounds like that's a trading item
i wonder who wants the the pineapple
okay we'll check out the beach i guess
she was my responsibility no
oh
[\h__\h] you
hey
rude
i'm on a mission
[Music]
morning morning
what the [\h__\h] were you doing oh
i'm glad you found this place
will you stay and talk to me for a while
no
language kiana swear it counts
keep up yo keep up
oh
is this super mario sunshine
i wonder where these coconut trees come
from
from the ground
tanya says there's nothing beyond the
scene
but i believe there must be something
over there
that's exactly the thought that um
[Music]
arya had
at the end of game of friends
when i discovered you blinky my heart
skipped a beat
i thought this person has come to give
us a message
[Music]
if i was a seagull i would fly as far as
i could
same but i don't need to be a single i'm
a phoenix it's better anyway
i would fly to far away places and sing
for many people
hmm
and i would join whole life so i can
sing for everyone all over the world yes
yes
uh if i wish to win fish i wonder if my
dream will come true
oh
she just doesn't [\h__\h] talk
link nobody will want to date you if you
are not like talking back at allah
don't want a boyfriend like that if he
doesn't talk absolutely useless these
protagonists who don't talk
[Music]
hey
are you listening are you listening to
me
yeah
i am this boy isn't
i want to know everything about you
oh
the walrus wants me to go how did you go
i didn't say anything she read my mind
damn she got some mind-reading skills
[Music]
thank you for understanding
why is it presenting her like that like
an item
link
women are not objects okay
holy [\h__\h]
he's training her like an object
cute
oh yeah big stretch stretch yeah good
stretch good stretch
good stretch so uh don't let marin die
is my current mission i guess ah can she
jump over that
[Music]
yes no
wow
she doesn't even need the feather for
that impressive a bit
meow meow smoothie
i want to give you a hug you look so
cute
uh
probably good to go here they wanted to
hear her thing too
yeah hi you can go
do you want to come here come here
come
[Music]
yes yes yes jump jump come on no
she's she has his face again where she
wants to say hello to my legs and my pc
and everything around it
hello i brought marlon with me
yes that's her
i brought her
make us happy about that
oh he says the same thing
oh crocodile he's drawing but that
doesn't look like
aren't you supposed to draw hair what
are you trying looks like the inside of
a pomegranate
um
donut
it's the mermaid statue by the base
masterpiece you the truth that work is
and my
not complete it's not it's uh difficult
for you to grasp is it not
it's very difficult for me to rush
holy [\h__\h] why a lady mmm gorgeous
beautiful go i like you disgusting you
stink
you're weak
okay
i guess i'm
not interesting enough
what is in this house
oh
cute
look at the
those uh bunny plants or whatever that
is at the top and there's a lot of bunny
food
[Music]
you're a bad boy
i like it when you say that say it again
you are a bad boy
yes i'm a bad girl
you wanted to thought
sorry can't hold back can't hold back
oh what is this
well you are adorable
i love your bed
hey what a beautiful house with the
bathtub over here nice
you turned on the proper eddie cat when
they went from lady to you you should
have brought flowers or something then
it might be more inclined to talk with
you
ah in my case hibiscus are the best
oh
if i find one i'll bring it to you then
oh no i was gonna talk to your parents
hey
i was just gonna talk to your parent but
okay
[Music]
will she hate me eventually stop it bad
boy link
that was his k-pop song bad boy bad boy
no
what was it again
something with bad boy
was that a
girl's generation song or
red i was red velvet yeah yeah yeah
is that a little chimken statue bathing
there that is adorable
because why is it not a duck why is it a
chimke that's so cute and holy [\h__\h]
that is an insane
bathtub it's more like an onsen
unless it's not hot i guess it's more
like a pond
you
know
the inside
of these houses
i [\h__\h] love it man
damn
grilled fish on the stick let's go
[Music]
nice
can stop peeping on us bathing
ah don't act as if you don't like that
i know you do like it
don't be such a chicken
was i in here
yeah it's not bad boys bad boys what you
gonna do what you gonna do in the
comfort you know that was not it i
forgot the melody of the throat
okay so where where the [\h__\h] is that
walrus that we're looking for
oh there's a platform already activated
down i came from there
[Music]
ah here
yes it's that lazy walrus shall we give
him a little surprise it's basically a
relaxo
[Music]
get out the polka flute
and the earth is shaking oh there he
goes nice
wow he certainly woke up with a start
well he's calling me it's the same as
always
you're leaving me i'm going to the
animal village please drop by okay
i don't think about it i already dropped
by they didn't do much
maybe i should drop by now
[Music]
while i'm here
perfect ten from the walrus it was a
nice jump ah
oh this is animal crossing
[Music]
i often come to this village just saying
too
it seems that just about everyone loves
my beloved of the wind fish
and kiara what is your favorite song
[Music]
don't stop don't stop i don't know my
own lyrics let's go
it's very workable what you're singing
is not really twerkable
it seems to be totally absorbed in
modern songs
understandable
spirit box sprint box search faster
splashes
okay
well if that's all then i'm out of here
i'm going to the desert
oh
hi
meow
wow
[Music]
no you can come here
come here
meow
[Music]
i know you don't like being held when
will you ever like it
i hope you grow up to be old and then
like
being held like a baby bubble
meow okay
she's still in the mood of adventures
[Music]
um
time to dig there's so much sand
[\h__\h] hate sand it's coarse and rough
and what else gets [\h__\h] everywhere
[Music]
what are we here what are we looking for
can i like poke this ow
ow
[Music]
thank you
yes
it is me
i wanted to talk with you guys about
well let's talk a little bit about the
recording of whole talk i guess now
i'm so hungry though i don't know if i
can talk about it i'm so hungry
uh oh god oh god i'm really hungry
ah
yeah so i recorded the whole talk of
yago today
the reason why it's pre-recorded uh is
because otherwise it would be too late
for jungle and another reason that you
will understand soon
um oh [\h__\h] have to fight them properly
um i gotta say i was so nervous
oh
really really nervous
shootout
no he will not sing for us he wanted to
be a
um i i don't think he wanted to sing i
offered it but nope so doesn't it
we need a sawdust and a counter
for the stream
you guys gotta be counting it because he
said that at the beginning of literally
every answer
i would ask the question and i would be
like
and he
[Music]
[Laughter]
drinking game yeah let's do a drinking
game
he really says it so often but this time
because of the the sana meme that she
did you know when she wrote that letter
to uh jaguar
with with the
pun
of you know so this nay like a horse
every time he said it i had to imagine
that he was saying it that
ah i way get it out of my head
[Music]
i think kelly also says
a lot doesn't she
sea bears foam sleep bears dreams both
end the same way crash
okay
that must be important later on
[Music]
yeah
um also
uh i must say
i guess
jago
is after all just
not
an entertainer
it was he was like oh man he's hard not
to crack like i tried to
you know get him to talk a lot
uh with a lot of questions
but he um
it was it was really uh difficult to get
him to speak a lot
what do you mean he's best girl he is
the best girl yes but
he's not so talkative as we streamers
are
very professional yes
very professional was he shy i wouldn't
say he was shy but uh
just not very talkative
i tried to get it out of him oh my god
yeah you will see the result of it uh
soon i hate you guys i hate you guys
damn it
reserved i guess so yeah i guess you
could call him reserved
um
i had him also watch some clips i
prepared some clips for him to watch in
exchange for
not doing the speed round and
not doing uh a singing performance
majorly looking forward to it
oh
that was not what i expected to find but
were you satisfied with the outcome of
course always always but
i just
had some issues
um
getting him to talk a lot
well well well
i just hope that you guys will enjoy it
but
i mean it's jago content so
how how can one not enjoy it
top-notch idol dude
where are they going where are they
going
no pancake color yeah
i'm sorry guys i couldn't deliver i'm so
sorry
[Music]
um
so what the hell am i supposed to do
here
am i supposed to like go into the um
the sand thingy here
like am i supposed to drop myself in
there
my disappointment is measurable my day
is ruined oh man i'm sorry
uh yeah i asked if i could do the speed
quiz anyway like also by changing some
questions but uh who was still denied
i've been denied so
yeah i need to go into it
one way to find out well here we go
annoyance you're only getting in the way
what me
i'm gonna fight here
i suppose this is what i need to do
[\h__\h]
maybe right timing
yes
oh button
where where is where's the the hittable
area just the face
i guess the face okay
oh my god i thought i died
that's the key thing oh wait no give me
give me give me hey hey
oh we're here i've been here before yeah
give me the key
[Music]
you should have done this slow around
this
well the whole the whole interview was a
slow round now so yeah
i got the apple key oh
[Music]
i'm sick of these
okay angle key where do i go with the
angle okay
gotta
call someone
for advice
nice everything gave me hearts
oh
yeah
anyway so
um
still uh
i'm i'm i'm pretty uh happy with the
outcome because
i i did prepare something else that's
really special
thanks to the staff
[Music]
so ah
sorry
it's [\h__\h] annoying
but it's hard to see where i'm supposed
to walk and where i'm not supposed to
walk
did you prank him no no no i was really
um
i was really a bit nervous because i
know he wants to remain professional so
i i couldn't do anything weird you know
i didn't want to uh
be bonked or something
it's a serious holotalk whole talk is
always serious but
um
might be even more serious than usual
this time hello who is this owl stop
stop
oh
[\h__\h] above the shoes of here swimming up
a cascade of hooters
go naho to the mountain waterfall
a leap from the top and you will reach
you'll go home
mountain waterfall you mean in the
do you mean
do you think you were able to get more
out of him than the last time he was
interviewed i don't know i didn't watch
that interview
i'm not sure i hope so well i mean there
were like millions of questions way more
than usual
and uh i was
going through them and i think i got the
general gist of your questions
as i'm supposed to jump from here how do
i get done oh maybe
here
left
through the cave perhaps
and then there's the question why we're
not able to go for the cave before i
guess but maybe we were maybe we were
able um more to the right
right side of the swamp
ah on in this area i'm able to go up
really
okay
uh
don't have any way of
getting very close to it uh where am i
right now
where am i
here
teleport from here to
[Music]
uh
here i guess
you need to open the dungeon first
uh-huh
or or i guess oh wait oh no i didn't
activate this one yet um
the lock is by the teleport that you
haven't gotten ah i i guess this thing
here right here
[Music]
i wanted to hear cat's voice before bed
yeah thank you now you heard it welcome
and good night
okay
honestly around
oh wait a second
[Music]
let's go
one more one more for another heart
oh wait
i didn't see that oh my god
secret cave get go
can i blow this up
a bit
no i can't
oh i can just move them
uh
okay
[Music]
what about you
oh there you go
okay but i have to blow this one up
for exiting somewhere no
this
no
from the other side then
i
thought
oh my god we have i just realized we
once again have a translator
at this late time yo i should honestly
be paying you you're working late at
night for me translating to korea oh
yeah this is not possible i can't reach
this one right
yeah i don't have the item for it yeah
but i was saying yo
yo
time is it over there it's like uh 2 am
or something or
3 am and you're here translating my
whatever i'm saying to korean
wait we get paid no i honestly can't pay
you i just you know it's a thought that
counts right think about me paying you
and then be satisfied with that
[Applause]
why am i incapable of going there
from here
sorry for poking you
we are
that's where i wanted to go
[Music]
okay uh
here
at least check the seashell mention
oh well that's where we just went so yes
we can do that but i by far definitely
not have enough
[Music]
but maybe it gives you rewards in
between two
imagine you get paid and that's the
spirit
acknowledge my seashells
god of seashells
one level
oh
merry christmas everybody merry
christmas
oh she
there's so many and we got a new heart
oh what is it let me snack on some
uh
rice waffles covered in chocolate
snacks
i'm a baby because
i said last time now this is a baby game
and then yet
even though i said that afterwards i
proceeded to die a million times so i am
now the baby
um
should i take it off though because you
don't see my mouth moving the whole time
wow
thank you for the
[Music]
membership i guess that calls for a poll
uh
take
tank and off now
yes
no
no hazard
put it on if you jinx yourself again
good idea
i'm an audio listener i have no opinion
who
um
it's pretty 50 50.
but yes is winning
this is a rare chaotic that is true
i can agree with putting it on when
needed okay okay
if i
if i do a dungeon today where i really
struggle
i might have to put it back on
because of my horrible play style
okay
[Music]
don't look for a second benign
it's embarrassing
taking it off there we go
okay
i have a mouth i know impressive i know
um um
it is a
religious pacifier and who could pop a
favor to me
even though i didn't ask for it but
because you gave it to me i need to make
use of it you know
um
[Music]
that was a really yummy waffle
rice waffle but not the japanese style
rice waffle
um
who are we calling shall we call again
can i fry some of the coworkers next to
me
um
maybe that's a little bit too direct um
there is
um if you just um if you don't don't
maybe
maybe just go to the counter um and and
order i mean you can do it for free you
don't have to pay just order some fried
chicken that way by going to the counter
so someone else will do the work in the
dirty work
oh i bye from grandma that there is
something hidden behind the falls in the
total mountains does that help i click
yeah okay i already knew that
i'll give you that
what the hell oh but yeah okay so wait i
can't go there where does that
where does that cave leads to again
where could it lead if it leads here
that would be wonderful
i i have a feeling it doesn't we were in
here before no
um
dude get the ocarina first
how do i out [\h__\h] it
wait wait how do i oh my god i forgot
how to jump
how do i get the ogre arena
that's to enter the castle
i don't know it doesn't help me to go
here
[Music]
can i change my shift to not be my
dragon castle
that's kind of difficult because all
everybody's on the shift when i'm
streaming everybody's always on the same
shift
i don't know i need you guys when i'm
here streaming
i require you guys to be here
uh
i'll find a different way to get up
there
[Music]
that's what you get
wait that's that's not where i want to
go eva where the hell am i going huh
i think i have to go all the way around
now
someone said to go uh
oh [\h__\h] the mountain
someone said to go next to the swamp so
now teleport it's kind of too late to
teleport now so i'll just walk here then
okay i can can i
can i go up when the stone is right
there
i will have to try
[Music]
kiana's holding do not watch yesterday's
stream huh
did you not watch yesterday's stream
[Music]
what if i go through here where will i
where will i get out
[Music]
i was in here before apparently
oh hello why do you have a bottle
do i have to i just have to have it in
my inventory right in order to make it
work
i got a fairy oh my god
set it free anytime you want to get
healed oh does it not uh keep me alive
[Music]
thank you
i'm not in this game okay so it hey
not automatic in this game okay i forget
really low on heights i guess i'll use
it
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
not necessary to send
a whole thank you okay these
[\h__\h] are such bullies
[Music]
should i go somewhere with this
no wait let me test it out if i can go
up here
oh yeah wait that should be possible
i thought it would be right at the stair
at the the uh not stairs thingy so that
you would have to remove it from above
but that's okay
oh no oh no
this way this way i think i'm finally on
the right path somehow
but this is also
first time i'm here now
[Music]
you can get the ocarina from the white
building at the north of my village
uh-huh
wait what did you want
i'm crazy tracy i've got a little secret
for sale that'll pump you up
wait was this the one that kept me alive
i think so
yeah rub it on me
secret medicine yeah yeah yeah
okay we're fully prepared for the next
dungeon
if we only die one time
we will definitely at least die one time
at least one time
um
so the white uh
maybe we can go around here here here
here i will try that coconut
yes
did i ever talk to you
a windfish and name only for this
neighbor
what does that mean
[Music]
okay
i'm getting closer
it's quite a journey to get here
what i'm getting there oh i hear a
teleportation thingy
damp shack
okay
[Music]
ah
no way it second
[Music]
yeah the stones on the left might be it
ah yeah okay okay
i was just wondering
wandering and wandering and pondering
here we are well i want to read what it
says on this stone
damn check bring me any weird stones you
find ah okay
wait which way do i want to go home
the right one perhaps
[Music]
what's over here
no wait i don't want to go up at all yet
do i i just want to
just want to walk around here
when you want mother nobody or not
by the way i've been i've been uh
wanting to tell you guys about this
massage i got the other day but i keep
on forgetting about it let me tell you
now
i
uh when was this two weeks ago or so i
went to get a massage for the first time
in a while
and i went to a place where i went to
before
um
[Music]
oh damn
how is it possible i'm holding my shield
does he just remove it and i don't
realize it
we're not holding hard enough
anyway i got the massage
um i i
this time usually usually i don't get
oil massage
when i'm like really really
really in pain i just get like a really
strong time massage for example i like
thai massages
um
but this time
[Music]
i got myself an oil massage i was hoping
that that
she would work on my body fairly
strongly anyway i just wanted it to be
like slippery you know
i was going for the slippery feeling
um
sorry just doing my gardening work here
and so i got the oil massage and i i i
laid down and i told the lady
i told them
what when i just oh
i told the lady
uh to
like
do it like
go strong on me you know because uh
can you throw it in here
to go strong
because
i'm in a lot of pain and i told her
especially on my shoulders please go
strong and then she was like oh but that
will cost extra and for a moment i was
really pissed off because like normally
when you go to a massage
well they
you should usually don't they ask you
like how how strong you want it and they
don't change the price for that like
that sounded so weird for me but i think
she kind of
misunderstood i didn't want her to go
like
so strong and it's a different massage
but she was like oil massage can't go
strong
uh oil massage is for relaxing and i'm
like okay
whatever it's do whatever just be strong
please i don't care
so i agreed to paying more
which is kind of generally weird but it
turns out that she was really
really rubbing it in strongly
um like that might have really been a
different massage
but
one issue
one issue i had
let me tell you after this
[Music]
[Applause]
wait how do i get there though
ah
now i go up now i go up and go around it
it's happened probably
is is that so do i have to go up
i'm guessing i need to go up
okay
so i am
hey
i was enjoying the massage mostly she
started with my shoulders
and
then well she went
more to the lower region
and
that's when i started feeling uh
weird because
you know those you know those massage
people who are like
really uh
like
um touchy
not touchy but like really
um
they just
uh how to explain this
how do i explain it
it's not like thanksgiving
that's not what i mean not what i mean
um
that's not what i mean
[Laughter]
no i mean she just like
she moved her hands so quickly and so so
roughly
then that i always felt like she was
getting a little bit too close you know
[\h__\h] i think i messed up
she was she was uh
um
every time she uh you know
was uh
doing you know i hate it when i hate it
when massage people do the butt massage
sometimes i even tell them to
leave that out because i don't like it
wait i can just jump
[Music]
yes um
i messed up again
you can't move it any further what
there must be a way for me to get the
heart container
yes there it is
uh anyways
i'll just say this but it was like huh
no
it's just too close too close too close
to
yeah it was kind of awkward
could you be more like careful like this
is one thing i i noticed
like a difference between
getting a massage in japan and getting a
massage in
in austria
the massage people here
they're like so
like how do i say this not rough i mean
like
um they're not very exact with their
movements
yeah they just rub and rub and rub
but like i feel like the japanese
massage people they don't want to offend
anyone so they're more careful
not as precise that's what i want to say
yeah yeah she's not really precise with
her movement
uh-huh
can i
let's blow this up
i don't think i can
no
uh
low accuracy
she didn't put many skill points into
accuracy
oh man
was this not the way to get there
maybe not
uh it was a it was a good massage though
like i uh holy [\h__\h] man she was
taking me apart
man
i was after the massage my hair was like
such a [\h__\h] mess
the door there was another ah
there was another door
why do you guys see things that i didn't
see
oh i went too far
ah
no the other door
[Laughter]
i didn't go too far
the massage person went too far
really need to get a massage myself yeah
but don't expect it to be like mine hey
what's up with you
you need help
i think he wants
help
and
yeah yeah yeah i don't know i don't know
it was confusing it was a strong massage
which is what i like but it was
not
precise enough
oh a chest
bamboozle chest
what
too touchy feely yes yes yeah exactly oh
hello
need some help i came to uh pick you up
i guess
ah yeah papa got lost just like he said
but now i am so famished i can't look
can you give me some vetos i don't know
what is that is that skittles
do you mean vitamins does it mean
vitamins
widows means food a term for food oh
okay he took my pineapple
i know that must be [\h__\h] delicious
man
this wasn't meant to be a reward uh here
take this
hi biscuits tb squeeze
oh thank you um
some cute girl wanted that um
okay
well are you ready to leave then
[Music]
i thought that would be a secret here
kind of disappointed but okay
[Music]
i remembered the cute girl of course
always remember your girl should i jump
down
no should i wait
[Applause]
no for that pole i got to here right
these two are connected right
yeah yeah yeah i know why this one was
connected
ah
huh
[Music]
did i check out that hole yet
beanjam is fire yeah
anyway let's try to move on here
um
here's the entrance
wait i'm curious i'm curious
well curiosity kills the link
sorry about that i didn't see that
here we are finally
dungeon time
level four
[Music]
you might wonder why i went sideways
but why am i fighting
with that
it's like a boss monster
[Music]
what how do i get this
okay i guess i'm learning to swim in
this dungeon maybe
hmm
i love your candle thank you
i will do my best
for you
[Music]
is waffles so good
oh
well you're excited cole
i hope i can live up to your
expectations
[Music]
is that a teeth is that a piece
oh
[Music]
oh this must be the key
okay it's a map and now we're getting
the map pretty early last time it was
like super late
[Music]
i didn't die much at all last time
those are lies those that slander those
clips are all slander
mm-hmm
it's so fake
that wasn't me playing what am i eating
i'm eating let me show you
let me show
um
beautiful
it's puffy puffy rice
yes yes
um
yeah they also sell them without the
chocolate but i don't like them without
the chocolate i find them too boring
without chocolate
mmm
[Music]
ah nice one link
he jumped down into the abyss for you
okay
these spiders give me like bad
flashbacks
of uh super mario 64.
um i don't like seeing them
[Music]
huh
oh wait those are enemies too wait how
do i
are they
okay i have to wait until they land
there we go okay
one more is this an enemy how do i buy
this one
i like the little sounds in the water
from link's feet so cute oh my
wait
i'm gonna kill uh powder
or boomerang powder
uh
oh [\h__\h]
oh there we go
oh
wait i thought i get something for
killing every enemy in here i guess not
oh
shatter this one no problem i got you
you don't need to hint it anymore
any further than that and then we move
this one push it
and get the key
finally our first key
height
[Music]
wait i'm scared to go back on the
fighting screen
okay lots of fairies to get here thanks
to these enemies
nice but i don't even need one right now
oh hmm well i'll get that on the way
back i guess
blow it up again
beautiful
another key
another key here's a bottle i already
have a fairy in my bottle so i don't
need it
i don't even need those hearts oh [\h__\h]
well now i do
now i do
and the thing is gone
okay
[Music]
so this area is a dead end and i would
not be coming back here because i got
everything
now the question is i can't move those
oh [\h__\h] wait i'm stupid
[Music]
so i probably need to go all the way
back for now
tony is the [\h__\h]
out
oh
nothing here okay
[Music]
wait um
wait i have a key i have a key wait
where's the key for
not here
i mean not for now at least
hey did i miss a spot with a key
[Music]
can't reach this one
oh i can go through here
okay
let us open the door and get this
chest as well
i hate these enemies but i have not died
yet
this will be a drink so you'll see it
soon already a compass is this a small
dungeon i feel like i'm getting all the
important things right away
[Music]
yes i got a few more oops
i got a few more heights um
sorry that was not really necessary
and now it's in the water
what is that
i was i was on the edge
i gotta feel my hearts because we did
get a lot of heart containers before
going into the dungeon
so we are stronger than ever before
[Music]
um
i need to write a message to my
manager
um
hmm
so just already planning the next whole
talk
we still have
corona left and i understand bye but
hmm i've been really unlucky
um
timing-wise
with uh corona sampler
not her fault but for some reason every
time um
i wanna get her for a specific date it's
a date where she already has something
to do
really unlucky man
gonna do something about that
[Music]
i will not give up
uh
i would be a fool to open this up
because you want to stab me and you're
really aggressive about it but i will
open it up anyway
wait i don't have a key right now
i'm stuck again
let's shoot wait i can't was i'm not
down here yet oh never mind never mind
i don't think i can reach that i need to
be able to swim
no wait i was here before
[Music]
can i jump over there i missed a door
i missed a door
[Music]
here
[Applause]
also i don't see a door here maybe i can
move these oh never mind [\h__\h] but i
think i moved them wrongly
can just hit him
yeah
[Music]
oh huh
no never mind
ah i see that i see it i see it
going back
because
there is a yeah a door there
not a hold up
nice parkour skills link yeah here here
it is how did i miss that
oh you consider this a boss fight
this ain't no match for me
that deep water won't scare me
here we go
already done
[Music]
i hope because that's all i need right
now beautiful
okay oh guys can i rant i have a i have
a topic for you guys oh my god so yes
today i think was it yesterday it was on
monday
or maybe it was yesterday um doesn't
matter for the story [\h__\h]
uh
i've been uh ubering as always a lot of
ubering
i'll tell you as a canadian i'm eating a
pop-tart and there's nothing you can do
i don't care
if you enjoy a pop-tart i am so happy
for you if
you can enjoy that kind of food
respect to you that's a simple life uh
oops
means you can enjoy
simple things even if they taste bad
like you're easy to please i guess
wonderful good for you
i don't have a problem with that i just
personally don't want to eat a pop-tart
okay
what do you think about this if i do
this one up
if i do this one then the pack will
close for
me
what if i first threw this one
it only goes up one
[Music]
no that doesn't i have to close this one
once i think and then leave it out leave
the room perhaps
and then go back
reset it there we go
ah
are you roasting it i didn't really want
to roast him
i'm just saying i'm fine with
[Music]
your aiming skills are horrible whoever
threw that
terrible
so yeah i was i was ubering
[Music]
and um i always always
obviously because it's uh required right
now for uber ring i always wear a mask
even before i enter the uber
um
but
this really pissed me off so bad
oh i can't reach that kid can i cause
i'll i'll drown
afterwards after that uber drive i got
an email telling me that i've been
reported by uh some last uber drive oh i
wonder which one when it came right
after the last one that i've been
reported for not following the
guidelines
of specifically wearing a mask and i'm
just like what the [\h__\h] is the matter
with you what did i do to hurt you i
didn't it was a normal overdrive uh uh
like normal like everything went fine
i've i'm thinking maybe he um
by accident but can you do that by
accident is anyone here an uber driver
is it so easy to like do it by accident
to report someone like that i don't
think it is
and i was so upset by it because like
there's it's just an email that tells
you that uh please follow the guidelines
of uber so that you may continue using
our services uh this is like one strike
please don't do it again and i'm like
so what if another uber just reports me
out of their own whims
then i'm not gonna be able to use uber
again after a million times i did it
after a million times of using uber
after giving you all this [\h__\h] money
yeah and there's like no way to reply to
it so i now have a strike or something
even though i didn't do anything
i always wear my skis i do
i do
and it's like it's no there's no way to
repute it refute it
what's the word which one is it
there's no way to like reply to it
yeah
mean it's so mean no there's no way to
reply to it refute it i want to appeal
it yeah
but
i don't see an option for it so i'm kind
of pissed off about it just get a a
get get that
um report for nothing like what did i do
i did nothing
i don't i also don't think i can do
anything here
um
[Music]
maybe he's mad because you didn't tip
enough no i was thinking if i did
anything else wrong that could have
upset him and he was just not able to
report me for whatever upset him so
instead he reported me for not wearing a
mess but no i didn't do anything
actually actually
right after that on a different uber
ride
i was so mad for a different reason
because i was stan you know
don't you hate it when you stand on the
sidewalk and you wave at your uber but
he just drives past you and then he
drives even much further than the actual
pickup point he drives and drives and i
run after him and i'm like what the [\h__\h]
i'm being made a fool of here
i run after him and then oh my god he
stops for one moment so i'm about like
i'm literally right in front of it i'm
about to touch the door handle and in
that very second he continues to drive a
little bit further and i'm like what the
[\h__\h] is your problem i'm like right next
to your door do you not see me i don't
drive a car so i don't know is it that
hard to see someone when someone is
standing right at your door handle how
much more do i have to run to get into
your [\h__\h] car did you cancel no uh
i eventually reached the car when he
finally came to a halt
and uh i gave him one last start
[Laughter]
he was trolling i asked him i got into
the car and i'm like
did you not see me or something and he
was like oh no i didn't and i'm like
okay i was right at your door handle and
i was about to open the door and you
just drove off and he was like
i see
[\h__\h] uber man it was not a lucky day
for me normally i'm
and ubering just fine but that was not
my lucky day we're on report for nothing
and then this dude who just [\h__\h] around
with me
[Music]
yeah
i only i only um
took one star away from the five star
rating because i guess he just he didn't
do it on purpose at least huh
um
but how blind can you be
what am i doing here anyway i can't i'm
going to drown you right now
nothing for me here
oh well
so it was not my day yeah
it was definitely not my day
um i use uber a lot so
um
i really enjoy using uber but
that was [\h__\h] up man
i'm real really um
i'm usually really uh how to say oh
tolerant of
people's behavior
um i don't complain usually
and for example recently when i've been
taking my cat to the vet i always uh
before they arrive before like right
away when they accept
uh the ride when i um
i'm able to message them i send a
message immediately to ask if i can take
my cat in a box with me even if none of
them ever gives a [\h__\h] i still ask
anyway
you know to be polite
someone like me doesn't doesn't deserve
to be reported at uber
i don't deserve it
[Music]
and the glint of the tile will be your
guide
[Music]
the glint what's a glint blind as a keys
what
oh [\h__\h] sorry i didn't want to do that
uh
i always by accident use the bombs
the glint of the tile
okay the corners are really mean
[\h__\h] i wanted to jump can i not jump
over there
can i jump in the slide
i'll come i can't
i'm calling your lab video excuse me are
you making fun of me
[Music]
i can jump here and i can jump here
wait let me kill you
um
it's time to become karya get a car ah
yeah
i want to get a car like a license after
whole life sometime when i actually have
time to study because my brain you know
it's uh
it's really small at the moment
i don't trust myself
oh you know
i don't think i can handle
that at the moment when i'm so busy with
whole life so
uh anyway um
yeah yeah i don't have time for it right
now and i don't really need it much
because i don't go outside much anyway
um
so
it will be okay
um
but
yeah
eventually eventually i'll get a car
myself
i guess
i i told this before but i usually i
used to never have the
the plan of getting a car i never wanted
to get a car because i'm scared of
driving oh
i remember this i know this is what the
code is for now
wait a second so yeah i never wanted to
never wanted to drive a car because i'm
scared of traffic like so scared
um
i can't activate this yet though
because i can't
oh wait i can't i can't i can i can
where's my where's my pinned comment
where did it go
oh it disappeared because of
because of the pool didn't it it's gone
where is it
is is this not what the code is for
free um yeah
actually how does that code even apply
to this
how does that code apply to this
the code is not for here oh
okay
uh
[Music]
then
this one seems to be correct
this one seems to be wrong okay we'll
figure it out we'll figure it out um
what about
and then it kind of has to be this one
no hey
well okay then it must be uh this one
[Music]
what if i start with this one no
but i can't reach the top left without
going to the bottom left first
[Music]
okay maybe for later maybe i can't do
this now um
[Music]
okay i'm out of here
uh
no i don't know how to fix it
i i bought an uber and when it showed up
i walked right up to the door and
slipped on the ice and found my bag it
was really embarrassing i was covered in
snow oh man
sorry about that that sucks
i have another stupid uber story
i don't know if i told this one before
uh but uh
i uh
there was a time where
i wanted to
[Music]
go to the airport with an uber
uh
but i had to make a stop in between
ah huh had to make a stop in between
so
um
i got out and i did something and then i
called another uber but i had my
suitcase with me you know
um i am uh
so i made a stop somewhere
and i i was like
i was about to get out and i had my my
suitcase in the back of the uber
in his trunk
[Music]
so
i
uh sorry brain is occupied with this
stuff
i
i uh
i'm like okay i'm getting off here
please thank you
and i think i even mentioned something
like in my suitcase yeah
but he didn't really reply to me so i
get out
and i walk behind the car
and i'm hoping for him to come too the
driver
but he doesn't so i try to open the the
the back of the trunk of the car
and he just drives up with my suitcase
he must have even heard how i was like
trying to open the trunk but he just
drives off with it
oh
how do i fight this one
i see i think i understand
wait let me i need to like get around
him
wait
i need to be a bit faster than him
i'm getting there
it changed you chase science
he drove off of it and i was running
after him thankfully most of the street
was just like a straight
straight line
so i just ran oh wait maybe i'll leave a
bomb
maybe
i jumped over his head
oh i hit him i'm not sure how to i i hit
him while i was uh
in the air
and there we go there we go
yeah yeah he drove
off and i i tried to
run after him was pretty exhausting
because i was wearing high heels
he's going backwards
oh he's gonna die soon
do your best
[Music]
and that dude also um at least got one
star less but i'm not sure i don't
remember that well
wow he's really got a lot of stamina
she not need no points up
oh
are you planning on dying ever
maybe time for us
[Music]
what doesn't want to die
i can't prepare it yes
there we go whoa that one had a lot of
help
oh nice nice nice thank you
he gave it right back to me what a good
man what a good speeder
kai secretary
thank you
we have the one point now
okay
wait uh
it's telling me to be fast
okay
i've got another key no oh i cannot swim
i can say that even one star down can
really mess with your pay as your
writing is directly related to so much
including your fail
i see him but normally
right i don't i'm not very strict okay
but if you make me run after my suitcase
that you yourself put into your trunk
at the beginning of the ride
[Music]
no
i mean i understand i have a lot of um
rides
um
every day
so i guess he forgot
i don't think he tried to steal it
[Music]
oh he just forgot probably so
one star one star minus
what is that
the glitch
okay is this supposed to be the glint
am i supposed to remem remember this one
bottom right top left
bottom left top right
okay
right
links over
links
open
[Music]
okay so we do the same in that other
place
should i
first check out what's here
ah
here we are here now again ah
[Music]
shortcut shortcut
i was about to go a different way
now wait do i have to equip it
no okay wonderful
[Music]
i think
yeah
and then
and in here yeah
[Music]
genius
oh don't look at me
don't look at me
i'm faster than you
faster than you
ha ha ha
ha
i like to look in his face
how are you wait
oh wait come back
oh wait
oh it hurts me when i touch him even
from the side
well that was deserved
don't i have to go on top of you
okay
i have to be faster yes there we go oh
my god
sorry
sorry i was panicking
we could stop
oh
chest
we already got the boss key
oh
his face is so cute can't be mad at him
when he looks so cute
um
[Music]
we're not missing any rooms anymore but
we're missing a chest here
we want to go back for that
uh
we jump down here
no
okay
i'm going back
swim going for a swim
okay i can't fight when i'm here huh
when i'm swimming makes sense
oh
[Music]
wait what
um i need another key a normal key
google rehearsals are why i've never
used it outside of ubereats and i feel
you're being a way to lean into some of
these drivers
see if i if i notice that they're doing
it on her
[\h__\h] i use it by oxygen
[Music]
wait wasn't there something here that
like gave me fairies
no
[Music]
give me back wasn't something you're
dropping fairies i knew it
where's one
i wanna
no i didn't wanna go here i wanna
well i'll go down i guess
the chest yeah yeah oh wait oh that
chest
i wanted to go to the different chests
[Music]
away
the birthday merch has arrived let's go
thank you for getting it
[Music]
where i need to go
up
[Music]
i'm not patient enough for this enemy he
makes me so aggressive because he's so
aggressive but i need to wait until he
hits me i understand that
i do understand that
i forgot about this place
[Music]
link has endless breath apparently
i've known keira for about a week wow
you're so new ah
and she's charming and cute this show is
so much fun please continue to make it
but i'll be waiting for you thank you
i guess you're a korean viewer
[Applause]
i'm glad you're enjoying it really happy
about it
[Music]
come here come here
okay swing swing swing sweet
kill the pokemon that really looks like
a pokemon
come here
[Music]
oh come
on
the fairy is [\h__\h] stuck
no
will it reset
when i leave the room
[\h__\h]
no
they took it away from me
like to be in your minecraft house
yeah
i hate it
i [\h__\h] hate it i got all the chests
uh
it's time to go to the bus
man
[Music]
not fair
i don't care about you now
get up get out of here
wait um
i wanted to go to the swirly thing
and get some more bumps
that's what you get you drown and i
don't please please i want the fairy
come on farron please
[Music]
domical
do you see that
what is that on the wall here
you see that
why is that so sauce to me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
no it's not just a lightest yeah it
looks like
some kind of draw drawing on it or so
maybe not maybe i'm just imagining
things okay
let me go
[Music]
okay
am i ready for the fight
i wish i had a fairy
oh wouldn't it be nice to have a fairy
right now
boy
wait for it uh what's the best moment
[Music]
there we go
uh
don't get hit don't get it
i'm full hearts now
i'm going to the boss fight with full
height
oh no
well you don't go there from there i
need to go underground oh which on the
ground this one maybe yeah cause we
still didn't open this one
[Music]
shut the way we probably get another
chance to um
oh god uh
heal ourselves up
if need be
[Music]
what for now okay never mind i was just
just about to say
but now i'm good with hearts
never mind that
um is it here
yes up here
okay
cudado skydoll
oh well i'll need you right now
[Music]
that was a mean screen change
perhaps it's not much i know but i feel
bad for your ubers wait are you an uber
driver
don't feel bad about it
wait now i can find on the waters
look where he stands
thank you though nice it's okay it's
okay i mean those are all just first
world problems anyway if you think about
it
it really is
but i mean what else what else can we do
besides
letting out our anger every once in a
while
fairy
even if i got a ferry from that it would
have landed somewhere else
i wish
for there to be a ferry
okay are you guys ready for a battle
battle
[Music]
is
boss fights don't go
is this the boss fight
oh my god oh [\h__\h] this is the bug
angle of fish oh that's why it's called
angle's cave i was thinking about uh
people who fish cause in german it's
anglais
okay
how do i fight you oh dear oh dear oh is
there a way to swim faster
i i can go lower like
[Music]
oh oh
wait it's so slow
what's it
okay
easy
easy easy
[Music]
he just stays down there that's nice of
him
oh what are you doing what do you do oh
you call a little friend okay
let's kill the
gotta go a little bit lower so we have
enough time to
uh
move away
swim away from the stones to dodge them
but so far it's going well now you bring
two friends okay
oh even more
you're so worried about dying and losing
here
he had to call so many friends oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] yeah okay i deserved that i mean
there was not much i could do
you don't think this is enough
i
[Music]
today
not a baby today this is a baby game i'm
not a baby
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
it was easy to figure out this boss i
mean there's not really much to figure
out so
yeah the more help you got the easier it
is very true yeah having three hearts in
the beginning was quite a struggle and
now we have
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
is that nine one two three four five six
seven eight nine yeah we have nine
heights
nine
have you ever come to korea no i've
never been to korea never before
uh are the borders open right now maybe
i can go next
weekend you know going to japan right
now is very difficult but i don't know
how it is with korea
how the board is looking
there was something below i don't know
[Music]
thank you thank you acumen games thank
you
got the surfhire boys beautiful it's
gorgeous
[Music]
oh
i want to go shopping in korea i love
like the kind of fashion
that they sell in asian countries man
yeah even though it's very different
like the fashion your road goes into the
bay the fashion in korea and japan
already i think is
quite a different style but i like both
[Music]
how many dungeons are left
we did three last time this is the
fourth
you guys said it's seven or eight i
think
damn
took us quite a while to get to this one
today
let's try to get one more four left okay
halfway through
i do really want to finish this uh game
next week so i want to get as far as
possible today and then finish it in one
stream next week
because
by the end of next week you know what's
coming out pokemon archaeos
korean
[Music]
my favorite food i have a lot of
favorite foods i like fast food
obviously i like pizza i like lasagna i
like ramen but not spicy ramen i can't
eat spicy food so that's one thing that
i would uh probably have some problems
with in korea a lot of
amazing foods in korea are spicy as far
as i know
[Music]
kelly said that well i can't really say
much about it but i do believe that it
will be fine until
the time comes when it comes out i think
we'll be fine
yes
[Music]
let me see if i find the cave
hey doco
[Music]
here it is
moshi mosh
oh
get it go get it
and how do i go lola ah
[Music]
doggy doggy doggy ah this is how i can
go below water okay
and then to the left you can get a song
for teleports a song
so that i can teleport anytime
to the left
i mean if i swim that way maybe if
you're here
okay
it could zoom
what if i go right here is there
anything interesting there or it just
ends i want to take a look
[Music]
i didn't do the dream shrine yeah wait
maybe now it would be much easier to do
the dream shrine or should i still wait
what do you think and do you count that
one as one of the four uh shrines that i
have left or is that not counted in that
is that like an extra shrine
oh hold a oh thank you
this is also like animal crossing
okay
dream shrine race
and it's extra it's extra
can i do it now
go for it get the ocarina oh what the
[\h__\h]
hello are you going to eat me
you have a tough night in there
is that one of those flat fishes
mambo
i think so travel to some fish have you
got an ocarina no
oh will he not give me the song until i
have an ocarina okay
okay
it's only one room oh
okay where the hell was that
is there anything else here where does
it lead to a dead end okay
okay
that's all
how did you see me i'm below the level
that you are on
okay at all
am i able to go up here
[Music]
no
wait
thank you for the pinky
mike mix
what is that
never heard of that one surprisingly
let me see
is it spicy if it's spicy and i probably
can't eat it
wait it's just fried chicken
it's a combination of fried chicken and
beer
that is often uh sold in uh in the
evening in korean restaurants
[Music]
anju
why is it with beer
pairing of fried chicken and beer
specifically
oh i don't like beer
but i like the fried chicken you can
drink the beer i'll have the fried
chicken
i don't drink alcohol at all sorry very
boring but
um
[Music]
can i go up here
no but i can go here
[Music]
i'll just have the fried chicken
okay
uh
did i go in here before
what is this
oh
dead end
okay
we are teleporting to the dream shrine
the dream shrine was
at them at the village or
was it at the village in one of the
houses
or was it like down here
is it written on my map
it's a
humanoid humanoid
tail cave trendy king
it's in the village
hooks which house was it
one of these houses if it's there then
we'll find it
why is there no shrine in the village
are we just not founded
[Music]
hello hello hello
it doesn't hurt me it just follows me
[Music]
yeah but that's the dream show i know
and kind of need to go
the house take me which house
the house of the day
okay
i was planning on doing something else
but
i'm gonna
man
[Music]
which one this one
or is abandoned house wait which one
where where the [\h__\h] was that
abandoned house
this one
i think it was maybe this one
i'll i guess i'll walk
down okay yeah
cute ghost though i gotta give you that
you're pink so
that makes you look very cute
i don't know what kind of ghost that is
it has like bare ears but
no
no no no no
[Music]
no
[Applause]
make sure you don't die
with all these enemies roaming around oh
[\h__\h] you're already dead well too bad
[Music]
sorry not trying to roast you or
anything
i need to go down
[Music]
be careful of your health okay
be careful don't fall down the holes
either
[Music]
yeah
let's get them
on
what am i doing right now what do you
think i'm doing right now you don't
leave me with a choice either
don't get hit by those you might die
i never mind you're reading
i already did
okay
oh be careful that stone might smash you
dead i'll never mind
here into my house okay i was wondering
who was living in here now we know
martha
is your name martha
that's a pretty house though from the
outside it has some flowers too
[Music]
bye
hey i'm changed
[Music]
you're taking your damn sweet time there
buddy
[Music]
enough you know
you just wanted to see your house one
more time where did i have to take you
as if you wouldn't know where your house
is
[Music]
oh man there better be a shortcut to the
cemetery uh there's a teleportation here
i could uh by the way let me mark that
because i keep on forgetting to
mark it with circle
the cemetery
is here
and teleport to here
okay wait look at that ghost can you do
that
[Music]
no
what where was i gonna go here
[Music]
i hope your grave is where all the other
graves are
cute
why aren't you even helping me ghost you
couldn't like help me defeat those
enemies while i'm helping you
defeat
your own
ghost
and do everything yourself everything
[Music]
the lone grave there was a
when i passed it why the [\h__\h] did i go
here
why am i doing this can i uh
i get so lost
[Music]
oh you little [\h__\h] i need to look at the
map like all the time
take me to my grave with flowers
yeah give me a second man don't stress
me out
i've been chased by enemies the whole
time
might not be long until i die here
oh up here
after i kill this one
[Music]
hello hello welcome to the uh
i can carry that with me while i'm going
down the hill
that is actually impressive
[Music]
wait
i remember
oh that was like a single grave
somewhere completely different
this one is on this one okay it's not
that far away for a moment i thought we
were like really far off
yeah
i remember i just remembered you guys
were probably saying it in the chat i'm
sorry
okay
here
here it is you really like flowers don't
ya
here it is
can you not just like go through me and
i felt the shivers because of that
thank you
[Music]
another battle for more fairies
it looks big enough to hold a fairy
inside okay
a fairy a fairy it is it shall be a
fairy
thank you for renewing your membership
it has been some time since our paths
crawl
slack you must dive into the waters of
martha's bay to enter the car
at fish
[Music]
you get to the wind fees the more
restless he sleeps
carry onward who
i
i i'm disappointed by you
my dear owl because you don't use puns
at all how boring
i know an owl who uses puns all the time
it's really fun thank you for the
membership welcome i've never been here
before have we because
when we were here i was not able to lift
stones yet i think
i think oh would you look at that
there's a hard piece for me
oh
wait how else would i have done that ah
can i
can i even
[\h__\h]
wasted [\h__\h] wasted
[Music]
did that just
blow me out okay at least
okay no one i am not going to be bought
gonna be bothered by that
how is this gonna work
don't i need like some
momento momentum
i made it
[Music]
no one more one more hard piece
check was wrong what was chad saying
i was looking
at the stupid enemies
okay
oh wait i can hit these bells
interesting
oh wait it doesn't seem to die though
huh cause it's already dead i get it i
get it
okay we're gonna go to the secret dream
shrine
just like that
er
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] do i get there i have to
walk all the way around is there a
teleporter
god damn it
you can walk all the way here
how annoying
or i go right now it's better to go
right
[Music]
i'm not really ready for the color
dungeon color dungeon is not the dream
shrine right
[Music]
color dungeon
that's a different one okay
oh wait i just saw i just saw wait wait
wait i just saw something
blow it up
[Music]
what is this one what is this one
heart container
where would it follow me oh this [\h__\h]
will follow me
that'll be faster than that
okay okay okay
and then i move this one
yes
[Music]
okay
why are you only able to push these ones
huh that's that's kind of lame wait
there's another one i almost didn't see
that
okay okay okay
why did i run into it i was too eager
i thought
then you get here with money you got the
don't don't twitter he'll
we have one extra height now
how many is that 10.
stream high challenger
oh my god
okay go guys
[Music]
now now we're even more ready and
prepared for the dream shrine everybody
says
okay
dream shrine
should be a short thing
was it this one
i was gonna be here earlier but the
stupid ghost was following me your
beloved majesty today i found out that i
have never
if i never sleep until i pass out i can
save time trying to sleep
that is actually smart and don't have to
die so right to inform everyone of this
great discovery
interesting
wait you're the same person who didn't
you have another
great discovery the other time what was
your last super chat i feel like i
remember something there
you're a smart chicken but
please don't do that please don't
you don't need to do that
and never care if you break through
i'm not sure if i would call it a
breakthrough um
it does i guess
save time
but getting to that point where you
would pass out um
that's
quite
your bit tough sounds tough man
i'm gonna save
it does work did someone ever try it out
okay well how do i find you
was there a special way to fight you
[Music]
run only here just dash
what is i think i messed up
i think i'm
i think i messed up
because it will always
go this way if i go that way
uh face backwards and your sword spin
okay but could you like come over here
i don't want to stand on that ground
where did he go
[Music]
not perfect but [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
i mean
can't be that difficult
well here here goes the tanks we almost
we almost had it
almost had a stream about jinx and
without game over
we were doing so well
i feel like i want to
redo this
don't buy food no don't buy food do buy
food
yadda
[Music]
okay
yeah maybe they were already facing the
wrong
no
okay
oh
what it's so easy
oh i didn't realize i was i guess yeah i
was holding my sword or something
oh
and which way should i go first
this way
valkarina i see so ocarina
oh 100 rupees
that's like 10 bucks i think i think
jackson you here
is it 10
something like that
[Music]
i got it
i can buy the bona oh
i was thinking of stealing it though
thank you for the pinkie
wait let me read your ingenious super
chat
super chat free as long as you don't
look at your bank balance
yeah this is what you call a chicken
brain
not the smartest on this
world
but
if that's the life what that you want to
live wait i could have taken the
shortcut
well i did it that was fast
dig that
wait what was that ocarina for ah to be
able to teleport
i was oops it was
here
i want to go here if i teleport there
from here
that would be lovely
[Music]
daisy no
rgu well that is true
oh my god here they go
if i didn't start this one
this one is on you guys this one is on
the chimpkins i didn't do anything to
make that happen
no food no water no taxes
no
guys
how did i deserve this kindness
[Music]
the green one remember that one guys the
green one is the free one
[Music]
my boss is cute i am
you guys
fish and bag fish are you the wind fish
you're just a flat fish huh
it's out of the sunfish i know you could
say that
i can teach you my song bloop bloop
blue bloopers gonna come i haven't seen
bloop in a while
[Music]
uh
one more time
[Music]
i had to turn that up because that was
so cute look that look guy mumbles mambo
when you get out of the water play it i
want to what does it do
it teleports me huh when you play my mom
though you can warp to a warp point
around the island you're amazing
try this tune in the dungeons too oh can
i get out of detention then since
today's a special day i'll let you warp
to the mambo's pawn too cha-cha-cha
is what you guys are maybe saying about
no maybe not but i want to listen to
this one during the super chat reading
[Music]
mumbai
i can play it wait i can play it and get
out of here quickly where are we going
next
wait i can get other songs too oh is
martin gonna tell me
a new song where is she right now in the
animal's family which is here
okay
she gonna teach me the ha ha
[Music]
since it's sent from work what are you
using your works money
your company's money or what
hey that's a nice ocarina you have there
will you accompany me as i sing i don't
know if i can
[Music]
oh
wow
what do i see someone got an evict to
notice so that's [\h__\h]
why don't you go too quick thank you as
well
you guys
you guys are just waiting for a reason
to super chat huh
maybe i should just give you a reason
sometimes and say uh super chat time now
do it now and then whoa there they go
they just were waiting for it
so how do you like it it's really
touching isn't it does it stick in your
mind hell yeah probably because you've
been singing it since the beginning of
the game
[Music]
you've learned a blood of the wind face
that's how i call him probably this song
will always remain in your heart
please don't ever forget the song oh
[\h__\h] i think i will
or me oh [\h__\h] i think i will
that sounds like a furagu
dana
[Music]
flag moment at least in japanese they
always say furagu
do you guys say that in english too it
sounds kind of weird in english did you
say that's a flag
well what's a flag
i know which house was it oh
not this one that doesn't look cute
enough
a red flag oh yeah red flag um
look at all these butterflies cute
is it this one
maybe this one this one looks cute
what did i unleash
endless
[Music]
sorry
excuse me
good [\h__\h] morning though
no not you anywhere
sorry
[Applause]
well since you're such a gentleman i
have a request to make up your
williamson
i would like you to take this letter to
mr white who lives on the border of the
mysterious forest please
oh she's blushing oh what's written in
that letter
already
i shall take it
uh somewhere on the top of the forest
super chat time oh thank you guys
thank you
god this is so addictive like how do you
stop yourself from
from cutting the grass
[Music]
this was
a crow
where am i going i don't know
wait i can swim right now i wonder if
that
oh
[\h__\h] i can't fight him oh get out of
here get out of here
it's a dead end anyway
oh hello did i ever speak to you
secrets are like water when it comes to
bridges
what
[Music]
secrets are like water
why do i always get
electrocuted i felt like there's a
moment where you don't get electrocuted
under the water under the bridge wait
dig dig dig
deep
[Music]
damn how the [\h__\h] do you find them you
must be like literally looking
everywhere for those
[Music]
okay
thank you for that hint
arigato taskaroo dokoniku
is the the train quest my only place
where i need to go right now
um
wide open it sounds like a great place
to dive by cook
catfish
not
this is probably what you're talking
about
oh enter from here from here from here
so many options
did he just hide under the grass instead
kind of cute
okay back in the day i dig every piece
of the map to find them all
i can imagine a lot of people must have
done that oh god oh god
okay that's not cool i need some heist
man
[Music]
uh
feel like i'm gonna die here
okay thank you i want to say thank you
to someone
other baby
[Music]
yeah
oh
wonderful
what about that uh statue
is that your sources
oh
[Music]
doing a little dive dive
another heart container near the castle
yeah yeah i guess now we can go to a lot
of new places
and let's check it out one by one
oh is this a dungeon
i'm up for another dungeon hell yeah the
fifth dungeon
that calls for a rice waffle
dungeon
oh
that's a weird opening
okay [\h__\h]
get off of me
oh wait can i move that
over there
no
no no no okay yeah
got you okay we're gonna go from the
other side then
um
i hope i find
wait do i have a ferry right now i don't
i hope i find some fairies here
eventually
what is that thing anyway what animal is
that
happy butter is it a coffee butter
evil things i tell you
um
can you do a job
no it really
well how else do you get there do you
have like a stronger feather
or is it just me being stupid one more
ah so close
do i get a stronger feta
[Music]
thank you
we will now oh no
[Music]
we will now know where the chests are
there you go
oh it opened up again okay so those
little fireballs they really don't count
as enemies do they
yum yum
let me see something let me see
[Music]
oh
by the way guys you know what i totally
forgot about oops telling you about my
new year resolutions or like thinking
about them in the first place
i only listened to your guys's new
year's resolutions and the talents the
members uh new year's resolutions i
didn't talk about my own
well
[\h__\h]
what are my new year's resolutions
oh wait
i think
one obvious one is
taking [\h__\h]
taking um
more time
to
um
[\h__\h]
you need to be faster okay oh wait
okay that doesn't work
taking more time to take care of my body
of my health
i was already too low like a tiny bit
um
okay um
[Music]
oh the ground powder is back oh and the
boomerang person okay okay okay
corner
shouldn't let your enemy corner you
um
yeah what else i wonder
uh cook more but i've already been doing
that this year last year so i think i'm
doing pretty well in terms of that um
yeah i will just improve even more on
that cook even more
[Music]
yes i did much i didn't do much more
cooking than i did um in previous years
oh yeah
what does this mean
i need to leave a bomb there
this is for later okay
okay so i need to go back to the other
place that had a door to be opened with
a key
no not here again
i want to i don't know if this is a new
year's resolution or just a goal i want
to travel i want to travel lots and lots
i know this is really
still kind of wishful thinking um
wait what how do i get out of here what
i hear
considering the state
the world is in still
still
but hey last year i was able to go to
greece um broke my [\h__\h] neck but
anyway
i wanna make more memories with friends
i've been because of this job i've been
neglecting my friends not that my
friends are mad at me or anything
well and i honestly i don't really care
for social interactions but uh
um
i guess
i guess a little bit more
social interactions
could be good i guess um
yeah yeah friends are important too yeah
yeah um although yeah my best friend
she's very understanding she knows what
i do
she sometimes watches my streams
so she knows i'm busy and she
understands that i want to make the best
use out of this time that i've been
given and this opportunity
but yeah i shouldn't let the job take
complete control of it that's true
oh my god
[Music]
stupid copy butter
oh
and that doesn't hurt you that's not
fair it literally just went in your butt
you're telling me that doesn't slice up
your butt
copy by sashimi
little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] come back
here at once
oh [\h__\h] can i i was winking if i can
move them if i if i should move them
again you know because uh sometimes it
gives you a chest but maybe not
okay
oh ariel's a rose kind of stuff
wait i don't have a
i could have a bow it would probably
make the dungeon easier huh
but i'm guessing it's optional
oh
project
can i even collect those oh i
can too bad you don't have a bow to
deliver the oh
[Music]
yeah too bad man do i need it not
required but useful okay damn
we don't need it we are a sword warrior
yeah
we don't need that um
well i don't know how else i was
supposed to do that
come on
i don't see any other way of doing that
[Music]
oh i can't go here either
ah
wait why does it close what do you want
me to do
when it's closed it means that like i
need to kill enemies now
you jump fast jumping fast doesn't
really do anything for me but okay
the ball is required you need the item
of the dungeon
okay i hope it's not required no
sort of optional there's a minibus in
there that requires the boat to beat but
it's possible to beat the dungeon
without beating you yeah that sounds
like i really need it
[\h__\h] should i go into the village and
buy it and then
eh if it's really that difficult
to beat the boss
some of the chat says it is quite hard
some of them say no
hmm
oh god
can i like use this here
um
[Music]
well
any more resolutions um
[Music]
um
yes probably probably let me think about
it
[Music]
a resolution is not a goal though right
so saying stuff like
i wanna make more music this year
it's not it's not a resolution isn't it
what do i wanna do help me check what
should be a solution resolution for me
i can sneak past him that is a
resolution oh
i would say it's more of a cold but okay
i have a thousand rupees
we could steal this or we could
just buy it
[Music]
if i steal it don't i just uh
isn't it is it even possible to get back
here ever
[Music]
buy it okay
i don't want a bad reputation
i'm an honest hero heroes don't steal
so
heroes
don't steal
and here's a lot of money hidden anyway
maybe maybe they get some extra money in
the dungeon maybe it considers the fact
that you need to buy the bow in order to
be really successful
in that dungeon
maybe it thinks about that
it's maybe designed in a way that it
gives you a lot of
a lot of
money no
is that just wishful thinking
okay so
uh
can we teleport close to it
there's a heart container did i get that
one already
i think i did i did i did i did i did
uh let's see how close we can get
uh
[Music]
leave me here
heroes don't feel they loot hairs
unsealed but they killed without
discrimination and lose their bodies
well but those were most of the time
evil
evil evil people enemies
so or monsters
they deserve to be killed
it's for
the
sake of the people of the
normal folk
okay going back into the dungeon
now we have bow and arrow we are
invincible
you call track a monster
yeah that's uh
if you think about it that way
i guess
yeah
sometimes sometimes the real monster is
the hero
that is so deep stuff man
out out
okay what happens if i shoot the eyes of
this monster is probably nothing because
they're just statues huh
but i want to try
okay never mind never mind
um
where did we get stuck
we didn't really get stuck this way
at least the copy buttons aren't really
aggressive okay back to new year's
resolutions um
i want to make some more music um but
you know time goes by so quickly uh i
don't even
know if i'll really reach my goal um
of
you know i said i wanted to do three
strong three songs again or
uh an album i said that before i think
evil one is fine but i think uh
i might just go with
singles again
because
it's a
i think it makes more sense
yeah if i have another three songs and i
have six in total don't i
because i have three or do i have three
originals right now yeah
um
six songs however not quite enough for a
concert i wanna do a concert this year i
wanna do a solo kiwawa concert
the beagle statues think so if you can't
make it up damn it don't have a pick yet
oh
here comes that buff oh
what are you calling again you have a
name uh this kind of enemy this kind of
zelda enemy has a name
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] so do i shoot you
i wanna
be so close
let me see if i can
shoot ground
do the arrows even work on the sky
[Music]
did that work i don't think it did
does it work is it getting damaged
you know i think i think those work
really good as well
[Laughter]
fall apart come on
why does he not fall apart anymore
okay
hmm
why did the bomb work one time and now
it doesn't anymore
well it's really a legendary short
showdown not
quite ah it was behind you
you weren't supposed to be guarded from
behind
[Applause]
man
that's a tough one man
oh
my god
[Music]
m
all right i can't beat you i'm out of
here
you can't beat me you hurt that you
can't beat me
that's right
that's right no one can
uh
[\h__\h]
i'll kind of what's inside this box come
and get it
i
and will come for you
i'm your worst nightmare
heal fish
grill fish eat fish
healthy fish
back to nearest resolutions i barely
have any what the [\h__\h] um
ah more plants from my apartment
i've been working on that
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] i'm gonna die here i'm gonna die
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
[\h__\h] fire [\h__\h] fire keeps me
busy
okay now it's stopped
um
more plants
[Music]
more and more i collapsed oh god
oh [\h__\h] oh god
not quite what i wanted wait i have to
kill those
what if you don't come in here with
powder you're just gonna die or can you
use the arrow instead
[Music]
i don't know
what it
is i want
i want a fairy dough in my bottle
although i did i did require that
healing so
not mad
just slightly disappointed about this as
well
how is this oh i could jump over it i
keep on forgetting i can jump over
people
oh
and i still don't have a key what is
this dungeon oh
i see
to go back up i would need this thing
but there is there a way to soft block
myself here
i hope not
they look so nice look at their smiles
hmm
okay
oh okay
oh
the door is closed
so
one of these
must be able to move yes
and
fancy powder
okay i've wasted some powder on that
but this is worth it this is totally
worth it
okay uh what is here though
uh which way do we want to go let's look
at the map maybe hmm
ah
can i get this chest now why why why was
it not able to get it before also
there's another one here and then i'm on
there
[Music]
i couldn't reach it i guess i still
can't
i guess i still get
this one this one i can't reach but this
one i should be able to reach able to
reach
hallelujah
why did i not go here the first time i
guess i just didn't feel like it
oh
the chest will appear
if i kill all enemies i suppose
wasted
wait is that not no wait that one is i
can't kill that one huh
[Music]
don't waste the last one that we got
holy [\h__\h]
epic finally okay
okay okay okay okay
okay uh new year's resolutions
they get me every time
my guy coronado my guide is
oh
i don't know i can't think of anymore
whatever
uh
kind of want this one but i still can't
reach out anymore okay i'll go coco uh
do i have a i don't have a kid
um
i thought of a lot already going to the
gym
yeah i guess so you know what yeah let's
try
let's give it a try
um
it doesn't i tried it before it doesn't
work hmm
does this work no
okay wait what that's closed
again
okay gotta go this way oh
what
huh
i mean that would be lovely but i don't
think
i i don't i don't think she would want
to make one with me so
um not gonna bother her
uh
but a song with cali would be nice
because that's something we always
wanted to do
since the beginning we said or at least
i said one day
we should do an original song together
i mean it doesn't matter how how the
state of takamoti is now
it doesn't matter we we have a
certain kind of connection i guess and a
certain kind of history
so i feel like we should honor that with
uh
with uh an original song
eventually uh
even though after killing so many dead
beats i'm not sure how her fandom
how her community will think about it if
you can't destroy a skeleton with your
sword try using a bump
you mean that dude that i just had a
fight with before i tried to bump i mean
i had issues with both the sword and
sword and the bomb so thanks for nothing
i guess
yeah hey i went here for the other door
so i couldn't talk to the big owl
majora's mask um
i generally am open to playing any zelda
on stream right now we're playing this
one but eventually i also want to play
uh um ocarina of time uh and i want to
play wind waker um majora's mask i guess
yes but generally i prefer the more
brighter looking um
zelda games
the one in green is zelda right yes 100
correct
i
saw i have the choice to go up and left
i'll go left first i'll [\h__\h] you
that is the worst like honestly the
[\h__\h] worst holy [\h__\h] that makes me so
mad is there any way any other way to
kill um that
star that keeps on moving around besides
uh throwing um
dust at it because okay okay yes okay
thank you never mind uh ignore the
question that i just asked
i don't
i found the answer myself
adam
i don't get anything for killing all of
them okay
but for killing these i'll get something
right
no
what what if i what if i dive oh
oh my god more super mario enemies
breath of the wild i think breath of the
wild is fascinating but it's such a huge
game
i don't think i want to start the the
first one on a stream
now
all of a sudden but when the new one
comes out i do want to play it i just
wonder
i probably should at least gain some
experience
for like with breath of the wild with
the og one before playing the new one
[Music]
why did i come here
why didn't i come here
yeah
um
one marathon stream maybe one gets to
know stream and then i'll i will try to
play it a little bit privately to kind
of
you know
get the feeling down
so that i'm not a super noob like i know
the story i know the story so that's not
the issue
i know the story because i watched like
at least
two full
playthroughs can i move any of these
well then i'm stuck here no
coco
nino
yeah i i guess i'll be fine yeah if i if
i already know
i've already know the story
um i'll just kind of um
get myself a family
familiar eyes
i'm so [\h__\h] mad
oh i hate you so much this is such a
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Applause]
huh
get out of here get out of here
stop stop
oh [\h__\h]
okay i'm reaching um some really
dangerous salt
a little bit levels
[Music]
i should jump over it i should just
[\h__\h] jump i keep on forgetting
and i can reach that chest
i think i can
money
i would have wanted a key but okay um
[Music]
this is connected to here but um as
i don't think
this distance is too far from me didn't
i try this before i already came to this
place before
uh okay stuck once again where the [\h__\h]
did i get the dungeon item
i need the hook shot
wait that just leads to the same room so
no wait i've not been here before the
room just looks like almost exactly the
same like in terms of where the the
chest this place looks like so similar i
thought it was the same room
okay
uh do i even want to come here like
maybe i get something for killing the
enemies oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah yeah
no
unless i can like move this
okay in my mind
another one for later
what am i doing
everything is uh inaccessible
[Music]
what what do you want from me
uh
okay okay okay okay i was gonna get mad
okay i understand i wasn't able to get
through here from the other side but i
was able to
get from this side to the other side
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
is this a
okay
is this another riddle for the hook shot
um
i think this was the last one i tried it
did you give the game up
three
number three uh-huh
oh dear this might be the dungeon item
you [\h__\h] slapped me unbelievable
okay
well that might mean that we're it's the
map
okay that might mean that we're going
into
a a boss fight soon with not much health
no no okay i thought that if i go back
in this room that now there will be a
boss fight but no i once again got
nothing out of that i have the map now
but
i almost explored all the rooms i have
not received a single key there are not
many doors with keys though there's just
this one and this one i suppose
so
you need skull too i mean skull too
uh
ah
i think i understand you mean here ah
probably hear them
because here
um
i guess was the first fight and then aha
this will be the second this will be the
third this will be the fourth baby and
this will be the final maybe
maybe that's the logic here
um
i can't get this chest can i
uh probably this underground leads to
this underground
okay so i want to go here why was i not
able to go here before i don't think i
even tried so should be fine
uh
it cools up but can i get some hearts
no
okay
okay i don't want to be greedy or
anything
[Music]
oh are you guys having fun
you better be having fun
number two
oh [\h__\h] i don't have much health ah this
is
this might not go well does he learn new
techniques
uh i'm 99 of them
[Music]
how do we do this how do we do this
oh
[Music]
don't get too cocky kiara
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know when those miracle fights
happen and you get some miracle hits but
you don't know what you did so you can't
repeat it anymore
when he lifted his leg
i did that when he lifted his leg
yes yes yes yes yes okay
observe and then
overcome uh
observe overcome something something
observe overcome observe something
something overcome yes
because
uh
[Music]
uh free was up here i think
right
number three yes okay
anyway for me to get some help before
going there please
there's some help there but i will die
while doing that jump
oh come on drop me some hearts but now
that i know
how to kill that dude i have to fight
him
we might be fine even with free hearts
but we do have a fairy but i don't want
to use it but
there's no reason to keep it because
it it won't um
heal me it won't keep me from dying
anyway i have to heal myself manually
with it anyway
uh
i'm using it now um
[Music]
[Applause]
didn't even hear me fully
could have at least hit me
hey
okay this will be an easy one quick
drive fast i don't have time for you
to speed run
oh [\h__\h] uh wrong order but okay oh
here's another one
[Music]
[Applause]
bye-bye see you in number four
[Laughter]
yeah i do be gaming i do be gaming oh
hello oh here's some hearts hmm
i lose more than i get here
okay uh
where do we go
number
four is over here
is this one connected with this one
maybe
thank you
four is there
oh no i got was i there before
what i was there before maybe
teleport and then left
wait you mean this one leads all the way
up there
it's a goal for the start
really okay
okay go to the beginning of the dungeon
i will listen to what you guys tell me
uh
totally wasting my buff here wait where
the left room
oh [\h__\h] i'm so sorry cappy balance you
didn't even try to hit me
big failure
[Music]
nice backflip did i just do it back flip
oh [\h__\h] ah this is not good
restart
another one
oh [\h__\h]
makes me super happy to see things fall
into places for the players ah
i do think like i understand how
people must feel when someone plays like
their favorite game on stream
for the first time and experiences it
for the first time
i don't think i can
relate to that
uh
or at least imagine so i'm happy to play
games that feel nostalgic to you
for example a pokemon it might i mean it
might have been a remake but
i think it made a lot of you guys feel
nostalgic anyway
and uh it was the first ever experience
for me playing that [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
yeah
here we go
time to prove the hero i am
the fact that i'm a hero yeah i can't
speak english that's the problem i'm a
hero who can fight for english no no
that's not my strong strong suit
oh no
no sorry sorry i'm not no time for music
right now
here we go
once you figure it out obviously it's
easy it took me a while though
oh [\h__\h] uh wrong order
oh [\h__\h] oh well okay i did both at the
same time
[Music]
thank god for that
that would have been bad we got the item
[Music]
oh hallelujah
hallelujah
[Music]
yes yes i heard about that secret chord
that david played and it pleased the
lord but you don't even care for it do
you
it goes like this the fourth the fifth
the minor fall and the major lips the
baffled king composing hallelujah
hallelujah
hallelujah hallelujah
hallelujah hallelujah hallelujah
hallelujah
i love that song man i [\h__\h] love it
okay where do we first use it
here perhaps
[Music]
she's looking at me
very tired eyes did you just wake up
from enough good job good job good nap
we love naps in this family don't we
oh
[Music]
i'm gonna take oh on wherever you want
it or not
[Music]
i'm gonna pick you up
she's congratulating me
i missed both of most of these this
dungeon with other obligations
oh no oh wait you mean you were watching
something else doing something else well
welcome back no problem
uh so far we killed the same enemy four
times
took me a while to figure out how to
kill him though
but now now we are fully prepared to
kill him i suppose a fifth time maybe
he'll come back even stronger maybe
he'll be like a
upgraded transformer version of himself
use the hook shot on enemies ah
can i also use it on the skeleton enemy
and make him fall apart just with one
hook shot shot
hello from korea hello i'm young i'm
your host yo
thank you for watching uh
she she
uh wait i i [\h__\h]
[Music]
you
shut up
something like that
[Music]
looking at my notes i forgot the
pronunciation
i keep the notes nearby
the cat is not able to escape my lap
right now or she's secretly enjoying it
i think she always enjoys it she just
doesn't want to admit it little sunday
cat
yeah yeah
wait i need a moment this is really rare
having her on my lap is really rare i i
need this to last as long as possible
i'm not gonna be the one
kicking her off
oh okay she's about to leave she's about
to leave
okay
i should order food for later or maybe
i'm just gonna eat something from my
freezer
i think today is frieza food day maybe
eat my curry
okay
uh
oh
wonderful
i love that
oh
and it goes like a diagonally as well oh
i can steal his mask it doesn't look
like a capybara to be honest looks more
like a dinosaur
did he just say hi soda
okay where
next uh
left up left left up left
[Laughter]
we have found out a new way of fighting
but i still hate
hate these ones
with
all my heart
can i do something against these fire uh
enemies now
or still not
try nope you can't do anything about it
wasn't your uncle
when i went the wrong room i went into
the wrong room never mind
yes okay
can i
hurt you with that no
okay just testing out how we can use
this slingshot for our advantage can i
do this
wow
wow wow
wow beautiful
so good
[Music]
oh i didn't steal his mask
okay
what could it be could it be a key i
think it will be a key
yeah the hook shot is very versatile
okay now promise me that there will be
some fairies in here come on
at least one
one fairy
please
no fairy hi smoothie welcome back
what's up smoovie hmm meow you feeling
smooth
as always
you are the smoothest cat in the whole
wide world i'll tell you that
oh i can hold on to uh this thing whoa
it makes a breach
you see that's moving it made a [\h__\h]
break
words cannot describe
the [\h__\h] that i have just experienced
it's unbelievable
in those
drugs that you don't expect that's
that's where they are and you throw them
and you have no choice to react
no chance to react
how do you know that i'll imagine it
okay what can i do about you can i do
something with you
but hey
i only had one game over today
so far
doing pretty well what is what is it
what the [\h__\h]
did i jinx myself what are they doing ew
simple
i don't care about taking damage right
now
why is it not opening its eye anymore oh
it went into a different face wait how
do i kill it then yeah
baby
[Music]
help me help me help me
um
really how will the bow help me
nice shot though
[Music]
i stole a nice one
oh
uh
six arrows are you kidding me
there is somewhere where i can get ten
arrows i think oh five
or oh i didn't save before it i didn't
set but maybe an autosave
what the [\h__\h] is that
on
2020 that's three minutes ago
should i take the autosave that's three
minutes ago
three minutes ago
what did i do three minutes ago
look at the map should i not take it
i already died like a million times the
best ending is far from gone
i'm going to put you back at the
beginning yeah but i will have more
arrows
[Music]
20 20
shut up
i will take it i want the arrows
and with the arrows it was easier than
with the
hook shot i guess that's why you guys
said to get the arrow
at the
the bow and the arrow
probably well how many do i have 30
wonderful
um cool
wait where where what where the hell was
that anyway was it this room
yeah how did i get there
i will just use everything that has to
do with uh hook hook shot
i don't want to fight right now
no
i don't think that's it i gotta go
the other way
i believe
sorry guys i feel like we were so close
with that
so close
so close to succeeding because like i
was at a very very very
um
very like scuffed
situation
where oops
can't jump i wanted to jump
where
i was so desperate at that moment
that i
just
was trying really hard i was so close to
get him with one heart so close so close
do i
still get a ferry from this yes let me
open it somewhere else
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was
i was too
too eager
i don't know why
i i can't i can't explain my action
oh man
bombs
i will try that i will give that a try
um
[Music]
should i save here
right before
okay um
[Music]
i know that we use the bombs
open your [\h__\h] eyes
okay i'm gonna take it easy now that i
know how to fight this enemy that was
also the problem the first time i wasn't
quite sure
yet there we go
oh [\h__\h] master go
can you shoot straight kiwawa
you were in the way
again in the way
out
got him got him last moment
yeah
ow
that's okay we can take a few hits only
a few though please
[Music]
why are you all so focused huh
where are the chairs
[Music]
believe it
thank you for the orange super chatter
a [\h__\h]
crap crap crap do a crab walk
cute crabs i like crabs they're funny
oh one is down
and this one's not far from it either
maybe one more hit
oh need to shoot that one
early on because his uh poison it takes
quite some time to reach me anyway
you're coming at me
sure no problem
[Music]
oh that will kiss me that will hit me no
no no no
not gonna let you hit me
they give me a fair wheel
[Music]
and only four hours left oh well do i
need to move the last ball so is it just
one of those big skeletons again
okay ah we don't need it
bosque doco
[Music]
[\h__\h] waste that
sorry goomba although i kind of do want
your
heart
i stole his heart cute goomba thanks for
the cheers by the way
thank you there's a key
i don't have a [\h__\h] carry man
why did i come here
where can i move the
move like this one yeah but what does
that do nothing
[\h__\h] i guess i came from the wrong side
um
go
we could teleport back because it's kind
of like a like going around or we can
just go left
go this way
i'm going down here
no in the end i gotta go back to the
middle anyway no
ah and now i gotta cut those two chests
maybe i'll just uh
wait though
ah
oh wait
did it
i was not able to get the chest right
that i just saw
i was not able to
continue there
oh stupid
what do you want from me this time
you got tomatoes on my eyes
[Music]
play ocarina oh no i'm good i'm just
gonna go here
tomorrow
i was supposed to play uh
minecraft right
i'm recording something
tomorrow in like the
early
before noon
time i've been feeling quite busy so
that's why i said i might not
stream minecraft but i might stream
something short i think i can stream
something shorter um
just not sure when let me just flavor it
out aisle we haven't played sliver in a
while
[Music]
wow
i wouldn't mind playing sliver for like
an hour or two
yeah
uh good old sliver
yeah hang out with you guys you always
have such funny names i love reading
those what are we doing right now i'm
just uh
my brain is empty heart is too no height
is filled with kfp love
yeah
you you you you
stop your ground pounds right now
chop chop when we have a time slot open
before we sleep
[Applause]
if i stream it's probably going to be
around the same time as the
the donut hole donut county stream
scheduled
that recording was uh decided on after i
already put out the schedule so sorry
about the changes guys
i always try to
not do too many changes to my schedule
because i know you guys like to
have everything according to keikaku
if you can't describe aya come on
[Music]
yeah
but don't worry i'll stream for you guys
anyway
thank you guys for being so
supportive and understanding
um
where did we go left upper right
where does right go again
oh
well just underground for now was i not
able to uh proceed here before i think
what's that
should you be taking a little bit of
damage
[Music]
bullying not okay not acceptable
i want to just listen to what you say
dive under where torchlight beams do
crush
aha
i'll try to remember
thank you
[Music]
ah uh
huh
why am i here now
i was not worth coming here
[\h__\h] sorry i'm getting lost in the
dungeon
oh
or
is it telling me to dive where the light
meets
it's not telling me to dive anywhere
here right
not here right not here
i'll kill them anyway
oh
by the way i'm watching the new season
of uh
uh
young sheldon right now you guys know it
i really like it i really like their
accent
texas accent
pretty cute to listen to
um
and i really enjoy the show
they're so cute
so cute those kids are so cute
yeah and uh i haven't watched the newest
season yet so i've been watching that
but yesterday i did a stupid thing like
i was re-watching a little bit of the
third season
in order to like
get back into it
uh and then
it's like telling me okay well now
you're done with the third season do you
want to buy the fourth season and i'm
like okay and i was literally just
watching the first season in english in
the original um sound
so i you would think that it would offer
me the fourth season in the original
sound as well right but so i i buy it
without thinking much about it and then
i play it and i realize [\h__\h] this is
german and i can't even change it
ah
so stupid and then i have to separately
buy
the english one because i just can't
listen to the
[\h__\h] german voice over i don't like
it at all it sounds so stupid especially
when you're so used to the different
voices already
then switching to different voices all
of a sudden
um it's just not gonna do it but but i
already watched like a few seconds of
the first
purchase so i don't think i can like
get the money back but i'm not gonna be
watching it so now i have two times the
fourth season of young sheldon
can you get all that's on amazon can you
get a refund if you'll just watch like
the first few seasons of uh
first few seconds of the whole season
german sex no no they don't speak any
accent see that's another thing that's
like they they lose a lot by
you know having no accent
in german hmm
amazon is pretty good for your friends
i'll check it out but last night i was
just too too annoyed with it and then i
just purchased the english one
immediately afterwards immediately
[Music]
apparently if you don't
watch it then within 14 days 14 days you
can get it back but i watched a few
seconds and then realized it's german
and then stopped watching so
hmm
yeah
maybe i'll try
because like 40 34 euro i think a full
season and i'm not even watching it i
mean i'm watching the other one
anyway we're going up up i think uh
how do i go up
i have to
out you little [\h__\h] i hate you
oh
you must all die you must all die
pay for it what you've done to me
okay we want to go uh
we also want to go up i guess
can we do it from above leave me leave
me
alone
okay wonderful
i escaped from their claws
ah but wait then uh
okay on guard
can you hook shot shields away ah
i don't know whoopsie
you can hook shot masks away as we've
seen previously
all righty
okay
uh wait do i
not wanna
go open and right i think i do yeah yeah
yeah yeah
this is the final chest i think saigon
okay
[Music]
thank you no wait there's one more chest
uh how to get to this one again through
probably through this key door probably
how do i get there
which how did i get there before
uh i think this teleporter then for
these
uh stairs you get probably here i think
and then i walk over there i think
that's what it was so the easiest way
would probably be to teleport myself i
think
or am i gonna regret this
what a room
no
water room which is the [\h__\h] water
room ah ah
okay
okay on this donut
let me get there uh
you think i feel like you know
cause we uh
this is only the second dungeon today
but i feel like we did a lot of other
stuff
as well maybe that's why uh
i feel so
um
like we didn't accomplish that much
today but i feel like i need to end it
afterwards because i need to read super
chats
so after this dungeon
i think we're ending it
um
yeah it's almost 11 p.m and i wanted to
end the stream around
almost almost 9 p.m i wanted to end the
stream around 11 p.m
so two hours for reading super chance
gotta be quick today
not too
able to do too many tangents
shall do
just as long as i'm still playing
um
oh yeah let me tell you recently um i
went to
uh go shabu-shabu with my bff
surprisingly
um
we found a place that does chubby shop
you know shabu shabu it's a japanese
um dinner is like hot pot
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i was really excited to see it i wanted
to test it out to see if it's like legit
uh it was
i feel like the
the
uh ingredients were legit like the the
older veggies and stuff
but the sauce
um that they gave us to eat it with was
not not so much it didn't really taste
like the shabu shabu that i ate
shabu-shabu
finally we got the key
thank you blue
thank you oh i hope you enjoyed it today
today not so many deaths so maybe that
was a bit too boring maybe i shall die a
few more times for entertainment's sake
yeah
but
but even though it was not like super
accurate i'm still excited where should
i go
still excited that we found something
like that now the only thing that's
missing
the only thing that's really missing uh
how how literally how
um
i would love to get some yucky nickel it
has been a while
okay where do we go um
dokoniko
i don't really like this dungeon
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's uh we can go to
restaurants no problem at all
restaurants are open
a portal i should go back to the
beginner
i guess so
what my favorite traditional food is
what from my own country or from any
country
maybe i think i would have to say ramen
because ramen is [\h__\h] genius it's so
[\h__\h] good
if you
if we're talking about any kind of or
but if we talk about any kind of
traditional food then maybe you know
pasta and pizza lasagna is also
i can't live without that either
i think
pasta and and and lasagna and all that
is is more
important for me to survive
than uh
ramen although i don't want to live
without lamb and either
damn
that's a difficult question
hi i'm so sick of this at this point
get off of me
why am i going this way so confusing
huh
i can't
four hearts boss fight let's go free
hearts boss fight let's go
wait why did i not just
why did i not just
no never mind
fairy pot should i use it now
wait i might get hit again so
let's wait to get its full usage
maybe there's a fairy here nope look
useful things nonetheless
yeah yeah yeah
oh and ouch
they had some nice desserts i ate some
mochi ice cream
and uh my friend had like uh
matchati ramisola
i think it's interesting how uh
it is
japanese restaurants overseas
like outside of japan
literally almost every dessert is
something of matcha and i don't dislike
matcha but it wouldn't really be my my
first choice of dessert
um
but they make everything they do like
matchachidamisu matcha ice cream my
traditional
yeah
because hey japanese dessert equals
matcha but then in japan when i go
uh to a restaurant
to
you know
get a dessert
there of course there's matcha and azuki
and stuff but not
it's not the only thing in the menu they
have normal desserts as well but i think
they're just trying to be extra japanese
yeah like red bean uh desserts and stuff
although i would i would prefer i think
i prefer matzah over red bean stuff
in illinois we have a japanese
restaurant called oroka ako they have
uber pudding what's uber pudding
i i like green tea as a tea more than i
like it as a dessert
for me a dessert has to be like
like super sweet you know
and the green tea makes it taste kind of
like it's kind of bitter or so i guess i
mean sweet and bitter at the same time
you know you know
uber oop is great purple yum
huh
are we getting the skeleton again i
wouldn't mind oh
oh no wait do i have to jump
what
what is this fight am i gonna die
i mean let me slime you
want to eat some unagi don
one of my weapons of choice guys
should i bring should i take bombs
i hate this fight oh no i won't need the
hook shot okay that makes sense
hook shot just a hook shot feathering
hook shot
i don't know
okay
yeah yeah i thought one might want to
jump over that i guess
where do i hook shot to ow
oh wait
no no no no no no no no no no
don't forget that
[Music]
i didn't expect it to come from there
ah
there's not much time to get them huh
yeah i'm not that fast oh
ow
no not yet
where do i when i hit you you don't seem
to
be really
hittable there eh
that's a fake one not the bus what
thanks these are fakes
ah
the ones that come out are fake
from
[Music]
there we go
see their eyes look at their eyes
okay but that was fake right
that one also looks fake i guess
and that one i don't know that one maybe
looks real
i'm sure
that one was real
oh that one is fake ah
okay now i see it now i sing it
whatever that one's real
i got the feet on the right side by
chance
that one's real
i'm hoping for it to come here
or maybe right below me
maybe if i just stand in the middle
i have better chances
okay
but if i stand in the middle i can't
pull it out that far now
okay but this is pretty safe i don't see
how i would die here
in before jinxing myself
oh [\h__\h]
yeah i'll wait in the middle i'll wait
in a minute
what if i can i
pull it over from across the room
bad timing bad timing
what a boring fight
[Music]
oh no thanks
i wanna bother with you
ah that one's real but i got arranged
[Music]
okay
got him a few times a few times
[Music]
a bigger hitbox would be nice but i
guess that was already
yeah too far away
[Music]
please come to the right side oh yes
are you sure about that
i was fooled maybe a few times in the
beginning but not so much after that
victory
and look at a high container
your maximum number of hearts is
increased and your health has been
refilled too
nice
oh
what do you call that again
tell us
[Music]
a marimba
the windmill
listen
hey listen
[Music]
shrine
omaha
the island secret in the shrine
okay
listen
[Music]
just all the safe but i'm going to save
anyway
did two dungeons today and the dream
shrine and uh
continued the
training quest i think
good to leave it at that
um you know what if i order food now
let me see do you guys mind if i order
some food for to come like later maybe
did i do some progress i mean uh
after the fourth shrine we were like
halfway through someone said or like
after the fifth run
uh
do you guys think we can finish it in
the next stream maybe if i do it a
little bit longer we can play longer
than four four hours 40 minutes next
time
i think
i can manage to
uh
reserve some more time
one to two streams maybe two no i will
finish it in one stream i don't care
i'll make a lot of time i'll start early
i'll make a lot of time
maybe
is the next shrine like immediately
maybe i can do something that's not so
important off stream
i always say that anyway i never do it
uh
but is there
i wonder if there's something i could do
off stream that will help me save some
time
shrine is easy there's a lot more two
steams no no i have to finish it collect
shells
could finish the trading quest
seven and eight are pretty confusing oof
played twice next week i i have already
been planning next week
and
it's looking pretty tough
what do we want to eat by the way i want
a burger or a schnitzel
burger or [\h__\h]
um
so many choices of burgers those are so
hard to choose can i order from kfp who
wants to be eaten
by the one and only empress huh woo hoo
hoo everybody obviously
[Music]
burger
i typed in b h l
u r g l l
would be nice i don't i actually have
only eaten cerresco once in my life and
that was only a small bite to try from
someone else i do like it but i never
think about getting it anywhere
burger
one with
a good reading perhaps oh man
um
did i like that one when i ordered it
before
[Music]
if only i could remember
but no i don't want to order from here
[Music]
this one must be good
how long are you open
hello uh
hello phone
oh um okay
but what if it arrives when i'm still
reading super jets
and then
and then i uh
and then i i will be able to eat it
right away and then it gets cold and
disgusting
burger is only good when it is fresh
eat and read at the same time it will be
a huge [\h__\h] mess and i won't even be
able to enjoy it properly well let me
see how what the latest time is for this
one to order what do we want
what kind of burger um
you know all these like burgers they
sound fancy with the million ingredients
but they are like so thick
so fat they're like i can't even they
fall apart the moment you touch them
that sounds good
oh man
[Music]
maybe this one
i'll try this and it also looks big but
i'll try
um
or will i maybe i should
go for a smaller one
can i have a kids a kid's size burger
baby bubble bubble size burger
no
chimpkin burger or
beef local
i when it comes to chicken burgers i
really
i love the one from burger king
but
anywhere else i don't know i'm often
disappointed because they just even when
even when other places call their uh
chimken burgers crispy chicken burgers
they are never as crispy as the one from
burger king like it's like you can't
beat it
the crispiness is
just immeasurable
it's it will be crispy but not as crispy
as the
that boy
okay i'll take this one hmm
take this one
no extras is already big enough
but does it come with potatoes yes
do we want a dessert
dessert oopsie dessert
[Music]
maybe just for for breakfast tomorrow
i like to i like to order desserts and
then eat them on the next morning
um
dessert for breakfast yes why the hell
not
like uh
crepes for example
uh
okay i'll take this one
hopefully it's good
okay please say please say you can
deliver like really late
this time would be
oh [\h__\h] go back go back go back
go back
uh back
one moment i'm almost done
chad is back singing in order no it's
okay i like to have their uh
their help
it's inspiring
[Music]
that's me perry
did you see my tweet the other day about
uh chocolate cookies
we might have a chocolate cookie
baking stream sometime or i'll make it
myself on my own time because there's a
lot of other like cooking style streams
that i'm planning to do right like the
the snack box one and uh
i mean we're not not cooking but i i'm
thinking about using the camera for that
one
and then the origami one
and then i was thinking about maybe
doing a a clothing ironing
stream that is crazy idea i know
i'm not sure when that will happen but
and for for valentine's day's next next
month valentine's is coming up again who
knows maybe i'll do
maybe i'll do chocolate cookies for dad
must be chocolate
it would be fitting i guess
housewife is
i guess i could call it that
waifu asmr
yeah yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
okay i'm kind of tired man
why am i so tired
why am i always so tired
i need energy
how to make house course choice
monetizable
business women
and business women
women we women
okay oh sure
okay
well we all just cuddle up and kiawah
reads the stuff to us
ah
well i did do like a story
um like a fairy tale reading before
there's like two i think two
german fairy tale reading videos up on
my channel if you want to listen to that
if you haven't yet feel free to do so
a certain lift room cleaning stream i
think both ina and gooda did that didn't
they you know did a cleaning stream and
a good idea like who did does randomly
vacuum in the middle of her stream
ah we did a manga reading with cali as
well
um
that was fun um
a oh
here we are
sorry guys for not reading them yet
yesterday yesterday was it yesterday
right i just didn't quite feel like it
sometimes you just don't feel like over
straining yourself
and your voice
because i was feeling that even though
it was a short stream yesterday i was
feeling done
tingling in my throat
i just want to be careful right now
[Music]
maybe i should make some tea
you guys want some tea
and before we get started
do you guys want some tea
yeah
okay then let's go into an intermission
i'll make some tea really quickly
intermission don't leave stay here cry
tonight again not the dinner
[Music]
i haven't seen this one in a while
either
[Music]
do
are you still here
[Music]
okay
hello
oh
so eager this chimpkin
so eager to get them those kisses
ah
why why does it do that why does it do
the
the click to
show last thing like where does that
come from
and now it's gone i don't know what i
did
4 am
oh man
i'm here thank you
hello hello hello hello everybody uh
since i'm not wearing my zelda hat
anymore i should put on something else
you know what i i'm gonna change clothes
okay guys
you guys probably
are missing uh
this outfit
yes i know you do
hi hmm
recently i've been wearing the casual
one a lot and the kimono one has been a
while since this one em empress um
yeah yeah glory to the empress thank you
thank you
and i made myself some tea that is
specifically uh meant to
heal your throat
with additional honey to it so we do be
winning my my throat do be winning now
um but without further ado
without many tangents we're gonna go
straight into the super chats
yes yes uh but music music hmm
what what's that one song called ma
mamba mambo
links awakening mom
mamba
mamba mamba mambos mambo
mom voice mambo stuff but it's only 30
seconds is there no long version to
today
[Music]
mumbo
i think we can loop this
not i guess wait it ends like that
[Music]
yeah that's weird to
kind of weird to lose
but i like it
[Music]
wow i don't think there is an extended
one
damn it
what about what is what is uh
where is this one again
that's so sad though
oh
this is the staff credits
[Music]
oh
i shouldn't be listening to this yet
this is following me just the music that
the emotions of it is spoilering me
[Music]
hey
egg
wing fish egg
animal village i thought that one was
funny too why is that one animal
animal village female
[Music]
hey it's fun
is that a good volume guys
[Music]
it's kind of
cr it's kind of cursed
[Music]
okay we gotta read the donuts one right
the donuts county one
[Music]
beautiful okay scrolling
i'll try to be um
i might be a little bit less energetic
i'm gonna try to hold back
um
my voice a little bit
so don't think that i don't like your
super chats or so or that i'm not happy
about your message i'm just
gonna try to hold back a little bit
it's not it's not because of you it's me
[Music]
um wait do i need to
read the other links awakening super
chats the ones from from the first one
i don't think so i think i got these
ones you guys went crazy at the end i
remember that
okay
donald county it is um
[Music]
for the rainbow right in the beginning
of the
uh pre-chat thank you
it says thanks for liking my lasagna
buzz hang in there we appreciate all
your hard work take care of yourselves
to have some donuts with rainbow string
sprinkles ah
now it all makes sense i am gonna don't
i said i would get donuts but i didn't
get them yet um
maybe i can get them tomorrow
there's always
i i satisfied my donut craving uh on
that day on the donut county day with
that chocolate chip the giant chocolate
chip cookie and it was so good
oh man
i wish i could learn how to make um like
a cookie that's as tasty as the one that
i bought there but so i was asking for
recipes right
and someone sent me a recipe from
uh
the chocolate chip cookies that you get
in a certain hotel chain called
doubletree by hilton and i stayed in one
of those before and i remember they
greeted me
and my friend with chocolate chip
cookies and you can get them anytime at
the reception and they're warm they
serve them to you warm
yeah they warm them up for you and they
taste so good and i remember them so the
moment i saw that there's a public
recipe
for those cookies now i have to have to
try it out you're losing your brain
cells
i'm sorry which brain cells though which
ones
do you still have some
surprising but yeah i will try them
maybe you guys can try that recipe first
and tell me how it went if it's really
like
as amazing
as i'm saying it is right now or as if
it's a little bit disappointing
i like this music
not many left not up
uh
what's the pinned message pin message
wait you guys see a pinned message
[Music]
oh maybe i don't see it because of hyper
chat
even when i turn it off though i don't
see it there's still pinned message
[Music]
wait let me see it oh
there he still is
oh there we go now it's nice
she should be gone she'll be gone
[Music]
oopsie loops
loops of oopsies
okay so thank you for the beautiful
rainbow
i'll report to you or i'll post a
picture when i get some proper donuts
i'll post a picture on twitter maybe
can i drink my tea already it looks so
hot
[Music]
maybe i'll pour some
pour some normal water into it
oh my god
[Music]
dangerous and playing a dangerous game
here what flavor of donut
i mean i think everyone enjoys a simple
sugar glazed donut those are amazing
especially i like the one um that i got
in japan the one that's like
small
small ball shaped ones one stuck to
another
uh shaping into a doughnut that one's
insane amazing i think it's called
pondering
now
i think yeah from mr donuts but we don't
have mr donuts here in austria i think
um
um but besides those pizza may be loud
okay besides though besides those i do
also like um all kinds of donuts with
like fruit filling but it must also have
uh
a glazing on top that's the perfect
donut
i like for example i like mmm like a
vanilla glazing on top and an inside
like a like a
raspberry filling for example holy [\h__\h]
oh or a blueberry filling
oh yeah
[Music]
oh yeah but the the the pondering and mr
donuts they're so mochi mochi indeed
they're they are kind of like chewy
and they're
um like they have a simple sugar glazing
it's really good
here's a case for you
by the way i wonder
you're
did you like originally have a different
name or so or did you just recently
show up
because
i feel like
i mean i could be wrong but i feel like
you're
your face
your avatar and your name
it seems very new to me but you're so
active lately
are you are you a secret agent
it seems new right i don't wanna i don't
know you know say it to someone hey
you're a new armchair when they were
like here for like one whole year or so
that would be embarrassing but what [\h__\h]
seems so new
[Music]
you were doug joseph
during my tales ambassador why did you
why did you change your name
what what was wrong with dove joseph but
thank you for telling me see that that
rings a bell to me
[Music]
you come here often
oh
ah
because everyone was both [\h__\h] ah
oh you don't plan on changing it back
you you have now
um accepted your fate or sock
well if you ever change back then
thankfully i'll be able to make a
connection
good to know you guys should tell me
when you change your name it confuses me
see i what what do you think i could
have i could have been crying in the
corner like oh man i haven't seen i
haven't seen doug joseph in the chat for
such a long time he probably hates me by
now i wonder where he went what i did
wrong why did he leave me
huh
you guys need to tell me when you change
your names
honestly
for real
i worry about you disappearing
oh
please
oh you it's okay it's real quick no you
were honest with me so i'm happy to hear
it
next time anybody changes the name you
let me know i need to approve the name
change i need to put my stamp on it
albedo
what the [\h__\h] is this
what is this name albedo that beats you
a purity protector
thank you soon
i see i see you're making a joke out of
it okay fine with me optimus prime thank
you
[Music]
soon high fructose corn syrup thank you
for the pinky what you talking about
yeah
[Music]
wait i remember this super chat i think
i was asking if hozer is an insulting
canadian but i don't remember getting an
answer
i don't think i was able to follow up
with the chat was it an insult what does
yahooza mean
[Music]
it is not really isn't
kind of interesting could be both huh
it's mostly a joke it is an insult okay
i don't mind you insulting me like that
though
oh the loop and it let me loop it
look look look at crazy music
[Music]
heal my throat please
ah yeah dingus oh
you dummy
keep on calling me dead high fructose
corn syrup and you're gonna end up in
the usual room
no it is okay you want to flex your
canadian
uh
canadian little
dialect to me i i appreciate that i like
hearing different dialects and learning
different words
[Music]
what is that long korean message are you
translating me there's so many
translators man there's so many
different ones
[Music]
me yeah you
what did you write
[Music]
just checking up bro not that you're
like
conspiring against me in korean
what did you write darwin award
committee uh huh
wait wait i've already forgot what that
meant i was starving award again what
was that again in a clip
that's what he wrote
yo they're exchanging
old lore
ah
[Music]
well then he lied to me didn't he just
lie to me
if that's not what wasn't that message
then he lied to me
[Music]
why you're not being honest to me
laura is being passed down
[Music]
there's a lot of lauren kfc
a lot of poor you know what i'm gonna
put up a message on the screen
i don't want people to come in in and be
like yo why is kiwawa so
[Music]
trying to
to not strain my throat too much
so
i may
speak
calmly
[Music]
um
it's not you it's me
okay
everyone
read that message acknowledge it
[Music]
a lot of lore stories need to be told
consistently has to not forget that it's
true yes yes yes
i shall do the same
can you make it bigger you can't read
this
here this is big enough
[Music]
okay aaron g donkey soon petruchendanki
translate korean to english
[Music]
it just means black apparently but
i'm feeling very sane and
would
[Music]
come
from
[Music]
if there's enough space in between then
it's
fine
thank you for the pinky i'm sure you
didn't mean to make me say something
like that on purpose it's just just a
word it's just the wording in korean
um
[Music]
let's see hello store manager sign up
for the first time today and say hello
then i'll go to bed because i have to go
to work have fun broadcasting fighting
thank you i feel like i maybe have read
this thank you very much to help i hope
that your day at work was lovely and
successful and that you accomplished all
the things that you wanted to accomplish
thank you for joining kfb welcome
please have a lot of fun here thank you
for your support
um
[Music]
the animation in your newest clip
you
you were having a lot of fun there huh
a lot of fun
timmy thank you for the red super chat
speaking of dogs i was very removed by a
dog story from zelda stream my family
had a puppy that we lost when it was
very young it was a rare german braid
called a holden buffa we miss him
terribly
but i don't know if you're trolling me
back because how
i feel like you should be mad at me
why are you moved by my dog story
who's that is this a troll as well what
is the joke where is the troll holding
beaufort maybe
[Music]
what
that's a very pretty bridge it's a tr
how is the troll
where is the troll
is it a meat is it me
[Music]
what
oh
them
hold
[Music]
what is both
stand
hold them
both off
these
ah
holding both uh-huh
oh no that was a thinker to me i was a
thinker
you needed quite some help to understand
them you are a funny one
but it's okay you can throw me back i
deserve it for trolling you
thank you
[Music]
thank you for an empty red super chat
thank you so much for the support very
generous of you let me give you a keys
[Music]
thank you
please continue enjoying my streams
and supporting me
thank you so much
[Music]
for the pinky finally have free time to
super chat belated happy new year
attention i'm looking forward to another
year with you be well and safe and
thanks for all the hard work and flow of
vanguard content viva la hawa
thank you as well for still watching
you've been here
for a long long time
in my streams you're still here
and that's very very very special to me
i'm going to dream this beach
[Music]
sorry guys it will stay in your brain
forever it's brainwashing
yeah
um
[Music]
name change the pros
yes so thank you sugar hasigaba i hope i
can continue to bring out my content in
the same place
[Music]
this year as well
i hope everything goes
smoothly and safely
[Music]
why the [\h__\h] are you awake
genma telling
saying to me you worked hard today but
what about you go sleep go sleep
go sleep
you worked hard too
hard
[Music]
why not why are you awake genma
why are you even awake she wasn't awake
during the during the recording with
yahoo as well
[Music]
she was actually he was there with
yangol
my manager
[Music]
my cute manager
helping me with with all the stuff
she always she always helps me translate
the questions for a whole
[Music]
m
this song is for you jmg
this beautiful brainwashed song
okay
foreign
i'm watching my favorite bird video
right now
wait
now
i feel like i read this out loud during
the stream
and i just assumed you were watching
a different video on the side
but now that i think
about this you might just have meant me
right
did you just mean you want i'm i'm the
bird right
um am i but he says video so it's kind
of confusing
you could
just say my favorite bird stream but
that would be too obvious maybe i am the
bird video
[Music]
good night genma
good night
it's a reference to the game i guess so
man i need to read these super chats
immediately after the stream otherwise i
already forget all the references look
i am the bird video okay
ah wait did did one of the characters
say something like they're watching
their favorite film of a movie video and
then you reply to that what are you
saying watching my favorite bird video
[Music]
yeah i'm slow i'm very slow
this bgm recycles my brain
that's a nice way to say it ah
yo daisy stop super chatting stop the
potentic
[Music]
oh god are you sending me ideas for
tangents oh my god i don't know no okay
what the [\h__\h]
daisy
stop it daisy daisy has learned from me
and goes on their own tangents
ricky doda thank you for the pinky wild
script today attention yeah yesterday i
was um
having quite some fun
throwing out everything that my brain
was thinking
mm-hmm
[Music]
i did not however consume any mozart or
energy drinks that was just me
yeah if it's a short stream i can like
bundle up my energy and let it out all
at once
if it's a long stream then i need to
like like uh keep my energy and like
spread it out fairly equally
daisy wants the stream to be a couple
hours longer i feel that
i've noticed
anyway thank you ricky doda i am glad
you enjoyed yesterday thank you oh
thanks for the membership welcome
[Music]
and not flu
squiggly mustache thank you for the
pinky
you were also here today right
today oh wait i was warned about this
stupid set
today i come declaring peace with kfb
and takoda so this first one is probably
accurate
okay but then it says if you agree to
peace you say
acepto fell
[Music]
i have been warned i will not say this
he says it means i accept the apology
but in reality it means i accept to be
your wife
no no no you sneaky you're not as
squiggly must as you're a sneaky
mustache change your name now
[Music]
sneaky little sneak snake
you may be my you may be my humble
servant you may be my
my chimpkin
but uh
and i can be your imaginary girlfriend
that was one of the perks right for kfb
memberships
but i cannot say it so directly no
[Music]
nice save
nice okay you don't have the mods don't
have to get rid of a super chat like
that that's fine it's a joke it's joke
your usual room and mama ina's
correctional room can't hold me anymore
change your name now sneaky mustache you
should have changed your name by now all
right all right
listen to your empress
i have the power
daisy thank you for the thing you get a
willingly drank flat soda on some yeah
yeah
i don't know but that is nice give it a
chance guys
and as i said i was always pretty
sensitive you know the bubbliness
sometimes it's too bubbly
[Music]
gross
no
i don't i don't really do it
purposefully anymore i used to do it
purposefully i would open a bottle of
coca-cola and then just keep it in the
fridge for
a day or two
cry about
what is that stupid text above that jeff
huh
the cry about it
can we get it without please
[Music]
um
michael that's what she said in the
kitchen
love
[Music]
you can't switch you know that you're
bound to me for life
ntp dan kishan michael thank you
thank you
wait did michael that's what she said
super chat me every time i said
something that could be returned if
that's what she said
[Music]
oh i wish you would have written to it
into each super chat
what exactly you meant with that because
looking back there's no way for me to
know
um i've probably said a lot of weird
things like
my hole is on fire
[Music]
i mean it is what she said i am she and
i said it
[Music]
yeah it is what i said it is so what so
what
[Music]
hello
let's go
thank you thank you so much
jim tries to thank you also for a pinky
i i am not german i'm austrian
almost close enough
congratulations on getting this
opportunity to have jungle on hall talk
it's a huge honor i know you're really
nervous but you're gonna rock this kia
fighter
thank you
it was it was okay uh as i said today um
there were some awkward
moments like overalls was kind of
awkward
but
um it's a very special episode so
just the fact that yago is there will
make up for all the awkwardness in the
room
and yeah
yep yep
[Music]
did he giggle a lot no not much i tried
to make him laugh but
he giggled a few times a few times i was
able to do it but not much not as much
as i hoped for
he giggled in his heart though i'm sure
of it
see people say i can break anyone's
shell and collapse
but juggle
i mean i didn't break him
i i scratched him maybe
[Music]
yeah
this music is breaking myself
are you are you a snail
cute snail chicken
snail chicken cube
[Music]
should have bullied him like coco did
nah i was that was
[Music]
i can't be that savage
i don't have the balls for it i
literally don't
uh but yeah please enjoy it anyway i
have to edit some things uh
and uh get it ready for
the actual stream
but
yeah mostly in it's we just recorded it
like from beginning to end and uh just
gonna cut out some small things and fix
one thing
[Music]
says the girl with the hashtag what
which hashtag
[Music]
that one is not used anymore and that
was different balls
there was different ones
chinese
oh don't don't worry about it yo
don't worry don't worry have you feeling
about no don't feel bad about it what
the hell are you here
there's no reason for you to apologize
and i didn't feel like i was mansplained
either
please don't worry about it
[Music]
i don't mind at all that was the last
the last donut county super chat by the
way i'm trying my best to pronounce it
correctly
donut county
county
county and then we have on this one
[Music]
no
mistakes only have only happy accidents
right
[Music]
i like the other pronunciation more
well there won't be many more times
where i will say it i think
okay
um
[Music]
or dog i always in my head i always say
don't don't
don't get
um i think i've heard people say doge
though
dodge or doge
dog
dodge
um
it's my birthday today and i wanted to
let my oh you know they've kept me going
this past year i tend to lose interest
in new hobbies but as long as you're
here just know i won't be going anywhere
i plan on wrapping kfb when i become a
pro fighter
what
is that is that like something you're
training for
you're the first i've sent a super chat
to and uh can't wait to get my
membership uniform next month thank you
for being part of the membership and
happy birthday to you
yeah
oh uh i understand how it is with losing
interest very quickly i'm i'm i'm very
similar when it comes to that
i'm really surprised that i've kept this
job before so long already but don't
worry i don't plan on recording anytime
soon um but it's really surprising it's
like a
like uh
out of character me being here so long
is so out of character
but respect to you i hope you can
um become a pro fighter
but in my heart you already are
[Music]
thank you so much happy birthday to you
talk about quitting a lot
no
because i i look at the future
realistically there must always be an
end everything has an end but the
sausage has two
so
um there is always an end to everything
and i just still want to be realistic
and not you know
um
speak about
talk about around the pudding too much i
think that's how we say it in german
i used a lot of a lot of german
phrases just now
yeah we say in german
we say everything has an end but the the
sausage has two
[Music]
the other saying i think was kind of
incorrect i wanted to say it differently
i think
and and um yeah one must
be aware of the future um
yeah but don't worry guys don't worry
i'll i'll be staying
for a while
if the day comes we will support you i
hope that isn't for many years thank you
i think that also
um
[Music]
it not only depends on me um it depends
on how the beach of the
industry um
develops in the next
one to five years
because it's like really
so difficult to guess like i've heard
people say that they think that in one
year
it will be blood but other people say no
it will become bigger and bigger and
more normal and normal and
um
yeah
where is friend shut up
here we go are you guys good at
[Music]
where's the rest
yeah but yeah it's just really difficult
to
[Music]
say where it's going
you know
[Music]
well that really is some serious talk
with this video
there really is something that we cannot
be sure about now but i think we will
all continue enjoying it as long as it's
here the way it is now
just online thank you for the red super
chat uh hi attention if i if i don't
want to see
oh don't want to see i misunderstood
that when i originally read it uh
quickly
if i don't want to say sorry i'm not
alive or i'll talk do i become a bad
person i'm watching 10
10 m
m without stars but now some people
what's 10
m
without stars but now some people bully
that they should collab oh 10 moms uh 10
members
10 months
that they should collab with stars and
force get out if i can't agree but i
love whole life not stars am i wrong
oh well okay still i guess my answer is
still the same like you don't have to
watch anything
that is not to your liking um
if there ever is a holo talk where i
invite all stars then you don't have to
watch it either
so i don't see a problem there is no
problem no it's not like it's not like
i'm forcing it on to you
and uh i guess no one no one is forcing
it onto you no one's forcing you to
watch it and if you're in a community
where you say hey i i don't care much
for this group of people then
well it might be unfortunate because you
might be missing out on something but uh
no one forces you no one should be
forcing you no one should be blaming you
for it
yeah
i mean i i for example i when it comes
to like idols like k-pop idols or j-pop
idols
i only like the girls either as well so
uh
i don't really have interest
in male idol i don't know maybe i just
prefer the female voices and the female
aesthetics and all that so
um
yeah
i can relate to it no one should like
bullying you for it i'm sorry if they do
um
i think as long as you also um
have the right attitude you don't have
to watch it but you also shouldn't
become
someone who's like
oh my god she she
collabs with uh with the whole stars
[\h__\h] her now like that's obviously not
the right way to do it either
yeah just be low key about it yeah
that's right be low-key about it
hmm
i'm so nervous with your swim clips on
ian's stars collab next week
you mean the clip
i'm surprised people even made a [\h__\h]
clip about it i saw a couple clips about
it i don't see why that was necessary to
make a clip out of it um
that was not about anything that you
guys have been
um
how to say it conspiring
uh
it was not about it
um
it was not about anything that you guys
have been guessing at all
[Music]
but you do have to assume that
eventually
there will be maybe a whole stars whole
talk episode i don't think i'm gonna do
like all of them
um
maybe like
i don't know it's
i don't even know if i'm really gonna do
it because like
uh it's taking me so much time to do the
girls already
but i do want to keep the possibility
open you know and if that time comes
just don't watch it like nobody's
forcing you
yeah it's a one-time thing and that's it
[Music]
you're not allowed to clip this just now
otherwise i will have to take it down
this is this is not
it's not necessary to make a clip out of
this if you clip it i'm sorry but i'll
take it down
i might just i might i might i mean i
don't want to be like you know
i don't want to control everything but
it's like
people make clips out of the stupidest
things
hey
hey listen
don't make me
don't make me do it i will throw it on
the ground i will take your clip but i
will throw it at the ground i need to
make a clip out of it no no no no see
see the last time these clips of this
discussion made this one viewer worried
about it he said he said because of the
clips
now he has like a
all these worries in his mind or her
mind sorry i'm not sure
in their mind
see we'll see what happens
unnecessary worries
and to be honest that qu that question
was about something that will
not happen
anytime soon
[Music]
and i think when it happens
the more i think about it the more i
feel like you guys are gonna be super
supportive of it
it's so far in the future so far ahead
not like not like next week or next
month
[Music]
you guys are gonna support it
thank you for the renewal of your
membership okay enough of this [\h__\h] now
enough of this but thank you for the
right to budget
jackson fb thank you for the rest of the
chat yeah yeah you made the report
you did you send it on twitter can i
take a look at it
[Music]
no it's not don't
i
i don't i don't see like how
why
um
you know i enjoy
his content as a as a viewer
um
[Music]
i know
that is not
in the talks or happening
oh where is the report jackson where is
it
you're fun
all right someone found yb and reported
him to me
the the white schwarz player with the
kfp matt
[Laughter]
where is it jackson i'm looking for my
twitter
hey hey
hey where is it
[Music]
um
regarding whole talk i don't know if i
said this before but i might stop
after um
after
the fifth gen
but it depends how long it takes me to
get to the fifth gen to the end of the
fifth gen
[Music]
but i just don't really think i want to
interview
someone who hasn't been in home life for
a year or more
so i think by the time that i reach
sixth gen i don't think they'll be
here for a year already
we need something to talk about you know
boom boom
[Music]
i'm
someone sent me a photo of her
some a cute girl wearing a
omo cat t-shirt cute
okay
what the [\h__\h] is that though
[Music]
okay i give up soon jackson did you
write something in the chat
[Music]
all right i was [\h__\h] focusing on
twitter did she write something
yeah i have other ideas too that i want
to focus on
after all the talk and uh although i'm
really proud of it that it has been
going on so long and then has been um
improved so much
i don't know
maybe a break maybe like a half year
break and then if we want we can always
bring it back you know
it's under the starting tweet
psychological warfare
[Music]
i love how everybody's enjoying this so
much
[Music]
oh
jackson jackson jackson i'm
here isn't this
no that's not it
nowhere i don't know ah here it is
okay
do you guys want the link
[Music]
um
okay very interesting so purpose rules
and assumptions as the recently
appointed lead economist of kfp it is my
responsibility to ensure the economic
prosperity of the company throughout all
business endeavors it sounds so serious
it sounds so legit
in order to do so i must provide
relevance this is perfect with this
music
for raw data potential with regards to
the economic environment she enters
this report aims to continue to the
research presented on august 4th 2021 fb
by expanding the study of the economics
of the different legend of zelda worlds
by analyzing the purchasable products in
the 2019 remake of the legend of zelda
link's awakening to real life
equivalents i hope to create an
understandable and entertaining picture
of the economy of coho and ireland
as a secondary goal i am to streamline
this report to make the data more
accessible and admittedly more stream
friendly potential research integrity
will still not be sacrificed
[Music]
i will not read all of this
holy [\h__\h] he used mathematics
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my god results
arrows in game value 1 average canadian
dollar value 13 dollars bo
in canadian dollars but in game 980
hearts 10
canadian value what did you use for
hearts what's the canadian heart of real
heart you can buy it real hard for two
dollars holy [\h__\h]
what kind of market is that selling real
hearts for two dollars
[Music]
or maybe an apple because like you can
fill up your hearts of an apple maybe
that's what
went for coffee
[Music]
secret medicine trendy game shield 20
20 in-game rupees and 191 canadian
dollars
and then he does all the
math conclusion after what calculations
i was able to make the end result is
that the exchange rate for the canadian
dollar to cohold island is
9.76 l a rs
link's awakening rupees per dollar the
results of my research show a very clear
fact the prices of in-game items are
based heavily on how the player uses the
item and the volatility of the item to
be used ivers for example are
exceptionally cheap i believe this has
mainly to do with the fact that errors
are just so consumable projectiles that
the player is expected to use them often
the shovel and bow on the other hand are
cons not consumable and can only be
bought once but these items are also
extremely useful and are required to
progress for the game the cost of those
items weigh the exchange rate quite
heavily
um
looking at figure 3 it seems clear that
the economy of coal inland iron island
is far wicked in sky loft by almost six
times
in a subtle way this shows the evolution
of legend of zelda game's design in
early titles rupees seem to be reprised
as a checkpoint of sorts the devil
developer only expects the player to be
able to afford big items after the
player completes a certain amount of the
game in later titles like skyward sword
it is apparent that a more realistic
study of the economy was done instead of
paywelling story items later titles make
some things unavailable until the
playoff progresses
oh this is so deep man
almost
[Music]
inflation
no inflation rate has been applied due
to lack of evidence supporting inflation
in-game
hearts the prices of three top coffee
companies of canada were used to
actually it was coffee afterwards
each purchase of three hearts is
equivalent to the purchase of one black
coffee worth the average of the medium
size from each brand
uh
special medicine
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what did you use
arguably the most controversial item in
this report and the hardest to compare
was impossible to accurately replicate
the revival of a human being phoenix's
exempt of course which violence rule 4
there was an overwhelming
uh resemblance both visually and
practically to revitalizing skin creams
that i could not ignore
what
specifically i could not use energy
drinks or other energy boosting samples
as the medicine is not consumed it is
applied to link by tracy true true true
true to me this implies that the
medicine in this version of the game is
a topical ointment not a drinkable
medicine ah
i like that
idea
i i agree with it
i see
very interesting jackson thank you for
this beautiful report
[Music]
he did pay attention to the detail
yo
[Music]
amazing here's a kiss mwah thank you
beautiful also gave us a long tangent uh
as expected from our economist respect
to you everybody read the full report
please
i really think you should get the fruit
checked out yeah yeah my bff she reminds
me all the time too there are a lot of
things that can give you a sore throat
these days you have only one fruit it
can be saved
it can't it can be saved unlike your
sleep schedule
but you take care of it play the long
game you know what i'll try to go next
week
otherwise uh the week after somehow
thank you
i i do um realize that it's important
for this job to keep my throat healthy
uh i do take it very seriously yeah i
don't want to lose my voice you know or
don't like damage my vocal cords
[Music]
couldn't
okay turn off the bgm please heart heart
heart well you sent so many hearts and i
guess okay we've all been thoroughly
brainwashed by now
i guess so
what about this
oh
that's the file select uh pgm i don't
even remember it
this one is nice
with the trumpets
[Music]
this is really energetic i like it
oh
[Music]
it's grooving
oh hell yeah
dance everybody that's chimpkings
[Music]
i don't know why but music like this
makes me want to shout that out
yeah this apparently is for the file
selection
[Music]
i missed the bgm this is brainwashing in
action yes yes it is
language
giant firing cooldown
oh you went to the dentist good job
can't be thank you for the pinky duncan
in my new year's fitness journey i found
something has really helped me keep my
head straight when i felt like quitting
streaming sparks what throughout runs it
helps me keep me on tempo and while
lifting it gives inspiration thank you
for the help thank you for listening to
it yeah sparks probably has a good tempo
we're running to huh
[Music]
tango in hyrule
i think you can dance tango to this yeah
wow i respect you camping i'll try to
maybe listen to spikes when i work out
this year too sometime this year thank
you very much
[Music]
until you get really buff
so this
is some bastard who like
likes
boing boing
[Music]
this is my fifth or sixth attempt to
tell you that you were popular in russia
russian bros hoping that you will learn
russian on your stream someday we love
you and thanks for everything you make
for us really
really
well i'm learning some russian history
right now you know
some really inaccurate russian history
about your one of your empresses
catherine the green
[Music]
how's that
um i didn't realize that is that true
really really
i uh
i think
i wanted to this year i want to do like
uh
um i want to do a french learning stream
and a rash a russian learning stream i
could do as well and i want to do a
spanish learning stream as well
i mean those are only like one time
things and not much comes out of it oh
but but wasn't the next snack box that
i'm getting russian
right
didn't i tell you guys the next snapbook
that i'm getting is russian so the
russian bros will be so happy about that
no
[Music]
yeah just wait for that russian bros
i'll i'll be presenting you a russian
snack box and we'll see
what kind of i really cannot imagine
actually
i can't imagine what you guys eat for
snacks
hold out
are you bros yeah
can you say it didn't really have
russian fingers in it oh i guess i took
a look and it looked like like it
definitely had some familiar looking
things
oh well but maybe it's like limited
versions to russia
[Music]
vodka bars
are you saying this from that community
show
the bibliotheca i remember that
they were like wrapping something i'm
going to skip the sneeze chats but thank
you thank you for a pink sneeze chat yo
way too much bro thank you so much
[Music]
thank you
wait this are you the one who keeps on
drawing me recently in that really cool
style i think it is you i think i
remember your
proper picture name
guru mia
he has such a cool style
uh
you guys know who i'm talking about i've
been retweeting it
him her sorry i always always i
automatically say him
um sorry for assuming your gender
it just feels kind of weird to say
it
uh like like an object to you guys for
me
when i speak english it feels so weird
to say it
um you all are welcome to correct me
though
yeah i know day and damn as well it's
just uh it doesn't roll over my tongue
so smoothly
i'm sorry i will try
yeah it is guru mia good on me are you
still here
let me let me show people
one of my
favorite pieces of you
here's a heat or day or he she they have
a very interesting art style
um but generally it looks like so funny
and you're still here
but then one time guru mia drew this one
piece that looks like so cool
like
their style can look so cool as well
holy [\h__\h] is huge look at this
i gotta look at it and big it's so
um it doesn't look good in this
downsized version look at it
did you see this
really cool i like it
but then there are these comical
artworks
they're so cute
which one
ah this one
this one is cute too
this one's cute
this one
looks good
very original oh wait you wrote
he wrote the tape thingy in korean
what does it say how do you pronounce
that
i like the eyes
so cute kind of reminds me of powerpuff
girl eyes actually now that i look at it
[Music]
oh okay okay
this one was my favorite i think
this is my favorite
this is so cute look it's you guys don't
be scared of me don't be scared of me i
guess this is me picking up the
employees that are trying to escape and
go to bed
since it's 4 51 in the back
[Music]
i'm looking for you
looking for you
[Music]
thank you for all the cute art i love it
so much thank you so much
and i don't know why you drew me with
short hair there but it looks cute
i'm a hunt yeah i'm on the hunt
a good night good night if you're going
to bed i'll be done soon afterwards
prime time because you're a giant firing
coal thank you for the red super chat
thank you i need to
i've been speaking too loud again i've
been speaking normally i'm speaking as i
always do i need to be more calm again
thank you
thank you giant firing coal i'm glad you
were so excited about it you must really
like the game huh
thank you for your excitement let's go
dungeon time i did two dungeons today
[Music]
so we have
three dungeons left i think
i think
maybe
i hope that yeah whispering also doesn't
work so well whispering hurts too anyway
i hope that next week with one stream we
can finish it i'll do my best maybe i'll
do a little bit off stream
yeah talk like you don't want a scary
smoothie away that is a good
good thought to have
giant firing
how do i read this
my dear korean viewer who has a japanese
name how do you want me to read your
name that's many different ways to read
it
uh
[Music]
i know you're still here i think you're
still here
[Music]
what
okay that is not what i expected
[Music]
for helping me through some of the most
difficult times in my life you are the
shoulder i lean on when it gets tough oh
i have noodle arms but my shoulders are
strong so feel free to lean on them
anytime thank you
vitto
giant fire ankle again thank you so much
for being so supportive and generous
today
what did i say
i do you mean because i acknowledge my
noodle arms
i know i have noodle arms that's why i
bought that's why i bought a
um a trolley for buying groceries
but it's it's such a life hack guys i'm
not i'm not ashamed of it
and the game mccree
thank you
zorak787
after this i'd love to see you play
ocarina of time in majority mask if you
can get permissions by playing any
version except for the switch version
because bad graphic issues and horrid
input delay sadly
for both of them right there's switch
versions anyway
i think i saw i think i saw i think i
heard the issues with it but we do have
permission as far as i know
um
if i wouldn't play ocarina of time on
the switch what else would i play it has
there been any other ports for uh
ocarina of time
i think i've heard of the s port but
like
uh
streaming the s games
ew 3ds ew
oh man is there game kill port
that that could do the trick maybe
wii u there's a wii u port
ah i guess because you can play gamecube
games on the wheel
oh go go go
no i mean freeze is fine it's like a
lovely console but i think like for
streaming and wouldn't the wouldn't the
um resolution be pretty small is what
i'm thinking
wouldn't it
look like like the graphics i imagine
that if it's a port for a switch or so
that the graphics would be much better
for than for a 3ds port
and it feels like it might be difficult
to
capture 3ds
freeze is the best looking one
[\h__\h]
well we have a lot of time to think
about it
about what to do
yeah i'd probably go for wind wake up
first anyway because i love wind wake up
majora on pretty s is terrible oh man
so much nice on for yes you mean you
mean uh ocarina of time
[Music]
yeah stream isn't hard and graphics are
pretty good for streaming i'll look into
it whenever
whenever i feel like what's gonna be
happening soon
our first empire thank you
uh w008 freedom
for the pinky
da oh i already answered this one do you
know i like to mike
no
ah where the cheese were chicken huh and
mike is the beer now i think i
understand
yeah yeah chicken yes mike beer no
no thank you
i don't drink alcohol
[Music]
i wonder
i wonder how much food i would have to
turn down in korea because it's all too
spicy
yeah
i can imagine i can imagine it would be
a lot
yeah
i don't wanna disappoint
like
the the locals you know
[Music]
a lot of korean food isn't spicy really
i'll always make sure it's not spicy
[Music]
or i'm just gonna eat fried chicken
every day let's go
that's the spirit
[Music]
is typically not spicy oh
okay i've heard of that before very
famous
all right now before that phillip cross
thank you for the pinky there are five
dungeons left if you count the color
dungeon as well it is a special gun that
gives you the choice of doubling attack
or defense permanently
oh
but i can also choose to not do it
when would you normally do that do you
guys think i'm ready for that maybe i
could do that one off screen
maybe i'm gonna do the color dungeon off
screen
am i ready for it already
[Music]
short
yes might be a good idea okay
that would also i guess um make the
whole next uh stream a bit quicker if i
take either
uh less damage or
um
do more damage
sounds like it would help us
with
um yeah all you need is magic powder
you're more than ready oh okay oh no i i
think i'll do it then
okay thank you for the hint thank you
for the advice phillip crush
[Music]
for the generous pinky as well
yeah again congrats boss avoided darwin
awards today oh i did didn't i had uh
two
two game movers maybe
but
i wouldn't say they were that stupid
that one during the boss fight is just
like well it happens [\h__\h] happens
i don't remember the other one but uh
yeah i think today
i dodged it perfectly certificated
by kp darwin award committee
january 20th 2022. thank you thank you
thank you thank you um i guess this is
the only award that i am happy about not
receiving
yay
you can have a garlic tan so you can
handle most of oh i love garlic
i love garlic so much
[Music]
you're getting better
thank you
the improved since last time bye
yeah i might have done better this time
you're 10 times less depth this time
you're doing well but also the fact that
i have way more hearts now you got to
consider that in the beginning i had so
little hearts and was still getting used
to the game
[Music]
thank you though thank you for praising
me
lost travel in 649
for the pinky
your beloved your beloved majesty today
i found out that oh yeah i already read
this one
i never sleep until i pass out i can
save time
trying to sleep and don't have to die so
right here to inform everyone of this
great discovery can't please everyone i
believe you know what i'm
saying well
i want you guys to
be healthy but if you feel like this is
what you need to do
your relatively free chicken
to do anything
as long as it
is um
beneficiary to
my cause
jerry stewart
joke time
what did zelda say to wing when he
couldn't open a locked door try fine
that's [\h__\h] funny
that is [\h__\h] funny
[Music]
thank you for the pinky life hacks super
tattoo free as long as you don't look at
your bank balance afterwards
yes yes go through life closing your
eyes everything will be fine you might
be um run over by a car
but
no but don't do it open your eyes open
your eyes now
look at the
reality perestroika
i'm worried about you i don't want a
flat chicken flattened with a tire
pattern on top of it no no no no no
i'm ready for the easy cut
they want to get hit by a truck i
wouldn't risk it
daisy thanks for the pinky hot damn he's
right
oh no this you escalated daisy are you
good do you regret it already
daisy dancing daisy
orbital vagabond thank you
mary pippin's dancer in game eight nine
one zero danke shin
rafa two three
[Music]
oh
that is more like
that super shot green is more like
turquoise though no
unseen
i'm telling elm thank you for the pinky
it works still i have to hack my back
account page in the browser
you packed your bank account
how did you do it tell me tell me tell
me tell me
oh i'm hungry
burger doko burger coming soon
i love the fact he's the only whole life
member who swears
i like that you that you like that i
swear but i'm definitely not the only
one
um
japanese members swear a lot
but english members swear as well they
swear a lot too but uh depends on which
one and some some just swear um in a way
that it's not that obvious maybe
they can mostly hold themselves back but
yeah i'm not the only one okay
[Music]
i'm not the only one
makes me feel like i'm like impure or
something
um
[Music]
life hack if you forfeit your soul to
care if being intentional you don't need
more than possessions anymore
[Music]
you know what
that might be true because kiwa maybe
will make you happy
and if you think about it
all these material things that you get
in your life
they will never fully make you happy you
might think that that gucci bag is gonna
make you happy
but it's not gonna make you very happy
when someone sees it
sees the gucci bag thinks you're rich
and then robs you because of your gucci
bag because you added yourself as being
rich
or you know
it doesn't have to be a gucci bag but uh
yeah
material positions only make you happy
maybe for the moment where you buy it
i
i often immediately regret buying things
that i bought
no
yeah
i don't have a gucci bag no
i don't even like quizzing
if anything i would buy louis vuitton
if anything
it's a nice change
oh
oh wait
wait what
did i misunderstand you i mean i meant
most ian members don't swear it's a nice
change that they don't swear oh [\h__\h]
then
i'm
oh damn i hated markiplier's decent into
kid friendly no swears or if he did why
it was bleep beeped out
so
you don't
[Music]
okay thank god safe
dodge the bullet here
well i wouldn't be able to change myself
anyway even if i wanted to i can't i
can't hold him back
[Music]
wait something went wrong with the free
super chat life hack i just got an
eviction notice no
stupid jumping stupid topic
spends so much money on super chats gets
kicked out of the apartment no no well
you know what you you don't need a place
to live you can uh spend 24 hours at kfc
working there just
you're not allowed to sleep though
and
what's korean name
[Music]
oh
korean translation
[Music]
gentlemen i'm a [\h__\h] gentleman
and a good gentleman
thank you very much
[Music]
no no i didn't
no
oh happily i wanted a word to the boss
again i'd send a super chat what
sergeant for kids two days playing right
after solve the dungeon but now it does
not affect
what
but no no i will not take it
i guess stream going well but
unfortunately i saw that dumb dumb death
when boss met mirrored moving once and i
came no i did not deserve this no
no no no no no no no i will not take it
i refuse to take the word i don't want
no i don't deserve it
no no no no no no no i already have one
from last stream i already have one in
my shelf so already standing on my shelf
i don't need anymore i don't need a copy
of the same thing no no no no
[Music]
apparently
idiot is bubble in korean
[Music]
so every time i said bubble bubble it
sounds like idiot idiot maybe but it's
bubble not baboo but you know it sounds
similar bubble bubble bobble
[Music]
you reacted to the command
very nice of you thank you for the
support
[Music]
thank you recently fell into the whole
life rabbit all night so welcome
yes one three one three one free or just
one three one three one pretty thank you
for the red super chat
my first zelda series is a link to the
past for sf
sf
sm
what's that console
link's awakening was famous and too
difficult i don't know it has the same
difficult after remake but i know tantra
can nail it thank you oh i think you
would totally nail it too
super famicom owing to the past wasn't
super famicom what
okay no one better under the name snes
okay okay i see well thank you for
watching today
i did my best today but since i was able
to any game that i'm able to clear
anyone else should be able to clear
that is the general rule
that you should take as a reference yeah
thank you
[Music]
thank you very much thank you soon
thank
[Music]
our magnificent sword warrior phoenix
let's go also please consider this as my
formal request for comme confirmation
skfp employee number g4151 please don't
ask what it means as it is spoilage
spoilers too what
this game is i'm playing right now
i wonder what it means
but of course sure please take that
number
feel free to take it it's not taken yet
it's yours it do be yours
i will put my stamp of approval on it oh
xenoblade oh [\h__\h] well now you told me
you said please don't ask because it's
spoilers and now you are you're telling
me
now i can never play accent or play too
never
never never
never it's your fault now
and you're the one who wants me to play
it the most don't you
ah
oh no
just don't look up the number okay
congratulations on your victory and may
your glory never die kneeling to my
queen long live queen long live queen
thank
[Music]
you have so much respect for me what a
perfect
underling you are thank you
for all the love thank you
i was very victorious today yes must say
language
[Music]
conduction blue lancashire
friend b and d
thank you
happy birthday to your
siblings
[Music]
spooky booty
here right now
[Music]
didn't see that one coming did you
okay refreshing the superchattos right
now
[Music]
why is it loading what are you doing
youtube studio
[Music]
stupid long name is hokan
or our donkey should miss mister
oh
just started marvelous mrs maisel oh you
will like it i'm sure
[Music]
can i support you with a red one even if
i can't start a time tangent with it of
course took my light only huge to our
wonderful phoenix and a beak from all
your chickens because you're giving us
so much love and happiness can't be
lovesy kiwawa thank you of course you
can you don't need attention to go with
a red superchat who said that you will
have to add attention to it
thank you just the sweet words they
touched my heart
that's already wonderful thank you very
very much
for all the love you give me
daisy thank you
um i think that's a total red one but
you
you went on a tangent did you is this a
daisy tangent oh dear okay your sheldon
tangent reminded me that last night i
was thinking of shows you might like
they're all from hbo and 10 to 20 years
old so i don't know how easy they are to
try out a new country but might as well
give them rex
[Music]
you should write this to me on twitter
first john adams the minister is about
the titular american founding father
frankly it's a little dry and might be
not be entirely into your taste but it's
still a great show of an excellent cost
better than hamilton oh
second is carnival a personal favorite
of mine it's a historical fantasy set
during the great depression
in america
and follows a traveling carnival in the
u.s southwest with a supernatural
apocalyptic and vaguely biblical tone
[Music]
i see
for this realm the show is set during
the transition of rome from republic to
empire and it's basically a game of
thrones before game of thrones with all
the
big violence and skimming you would
expect so yeah check them out i think
i've heard of the wrong one before and
that sounds like something i might want
to watch
uh
gotta check out where that one is
available i've heard of it before i know
it has a good reputation
roman's really good rum is great room is
really really good there you go
everybody loves it
[Music]
is it historically accurate
very important
daisy
wait one more the movie amadeus would be
pretty cool to do it to watch along even
if it's not very accurate a little old
and very dramatic it's modern classic
about the rivalry between mozart and
salieri oh
wait how how old is the movie amanda's
movie
1980 [\h__\h] five
i don't want to watch such an old movie
that will have really bad quality
[Music]
that's so old
okay the screenshots look decent don't
i'm interested in the story
i am
[Music]
might check it out
don't know if that's a watch along or
just like this but
the music was old yeah it looked old too
sound the music was a special exception
well
[Music]
thank you for the pinky your usual room
and mama inna's correction room can't
hold me anymore
if i wanted to i could ban you
so i can yes i can control you
don't underestimate me i'm just merciful
i'm just very very merciful
yeah
yes you guys still paint me as a
really really
evil character but i'm really merciful
[Music]
bell the superior fashion for instance
as i said you know
you know you stuck with me forever
i know you're just talking
you're just trying to make me worry so
that i'm like
[Music]
i want you to stay
korean translation
to english
[Music]
yes i am considering it of course you
need to chat vancouver michael plunkett
squiggly mustache john kishan blue
dancing outrun the wind dancing squiggly
monsters down
the line so fancy
time for mod change ah
you're reminding me again
[Music]
i have like four super chats left
let's do it right after
and
[Laughter]
are you saying that you're doing it on
purpose mother-son well then i might
have to take away any means of you being
able to sleep in the usual room i might
have to forcefully keep you awake
if you don't want that if you do that on
purpose
i will have to change the setup of your
usual room
you did this yourself
you did this to yourself let me out the
user but then even more you can sleep if
you go out of the usual room
thank you
don't do it don't try to do it guys
yes i will take his eyelids
you know that sounds
that sounds so terrible it's so so
[\h__\h] painful
oh my god i don't even want to imagine
that no you you you i can't torture my
cute
behaved adorable little chimpkins like
that i can't do it
no
i love you too much
even if you're not really behaved
i still can't do it
i'm
i'm a kind-hearted spirit you know
no you don't know you don't believe me
but
i am an angel
kmt piano magic
[Music]
swan flyer
absolutely
it's pronounced oh salute oh okay i got
that one right pranzi oni
well i said it perfectly correctly i
called myself myself aged pro 15 the
other day in secretary yeah wait why the
[\h__\h] did you change it but you announced
it to me at least so i guess that's fine
okay
jacksonville
thank you for the
report it took me around 15 and a half
hours over two days holy [\h__\h] wow
that is a
determination once again i'm proud of my
chimpkins for their hard work we're done
with the super chats
um
behaved on the head and hey
i would not be had my chimpkins out no
no no
i saw
[Music]
uh
um
let me get rid of the current mugs uh
before i mix
uh
the ones in triple white
all right
[Music]
is
i like that name
okay
[Music]
this is one of you
something something in another language
and where is the third one
[Music]
some of these sound like they're actual
managers from
ole miss what about this one plate
plate drives with modesty is that one of
you guys a chocolate cookie thank you
i get a view like like here like this
right now
um we have three or four mods
[Music]
thank you we have four i got rid of
i think what wait how many did i just
get rid of i think i got rid of four
my young man
okay
i think uh if i yeah oh yeah
did that work
did i take everybody's mod police did it
save
community
let's check again
[Music]
which one is that one of you guys
please drive some modesty
what is that
i'll get rid of it
[Music]
okay
um
who wants to be mod for
uh european times any any people here on
european mods i mean in the end it's all
kiara time that you're modding for so
just anyone who can who is here a lot um
[Music]
eu bros not me not me
um
[Music]
i choose you
uh dastia
please make
a new account or if you already have one
uh present to me immediately
please make a new account or using a
different one that you will only use for
uh moderating
don't mod him he's french
[Music]
oh no
no no we really bargained i'm not a
modern world girl
thank you
french
french month
nice uh and then yeah let me know
which one it is uh
trying to follow the chat
do you already have one
homage
for much
i know french french people are um
arunia 93 okay fresh people
sex
sensual
let's go
earn your 93 okay i'm keeping others
thank you that was quick
okay i choose you uh
moderator
okay just don't chat with that account
you'll be mod for approximately one
month
please just uh
time out people who are idiots and ban
people who look like they will forever
be idiots
[Music]
um no need to be too strict but yeah
just clean up the crap that's in the
chat sometimes
and now let's do someone maybe
[Music]
americano or
yeah like uh
anytime zone doco
who is here all the time
[Music]
who was not an yet
see nakati we're not doing uh mods for
uh
like i'm only modding people who are
also members because i can make sure
that they have been here for a long time
and that i can somewhat probably trust
them
and
i haven't been okay lunchbox make a new
account go
lunchbox make a new account please
or show me the account that you're gonna
be using
and uh
one more will be
uh
[Music]
you know what would actually might be
smart getting a korean mod because they
can also see like immediately see
if there's any
like
bad comments in korean that will be very
difficult to figure out by
non-koreans because we've been having an
influx of korean viewers
we do have a korean snack box review
which will probably bring in a lot of
korean views again
maybe the third one could be a korean
if there's someone who feels like they
could do it
who feels up to it up to the
job it's not so difficult
right so uh lunchbox
did lunchbox say anything
i could be a korean mod ah okay okay
okay this is violet evergarden right
you're viola garden right you changed
your avatar again so confusing i'm like
okay
mod until february 19th
[Music]
what if i what if i'm one or two days
late are you just not gonna work anymore
okay uh
violet is often here so i trust violet
uh why not do you have a second account
that you could use
[Music]
the contract is still united wow okay
i decide when you shift in no no it's
okay i'll try to
do change it in time
i will bring it here okay okay okay let
me know
maybe let me know with your main account
so i can make sure it's not an imposter
and um don't worry if you don't have to
be here for every stream
try to be here
often and don't chat with your mod
account
and
yeah
the mods seem to have a discord together
so you could try to get into that
discord
and
maybe you can try to connect one another
on twitter or something i don't know
um it's my second account ah well it's a
chloe profile picture so you know what i
believe it
you simp
okay i believe it i think this is your
account
okay
i think three months is enough right is
it enough it's probably enough
i think it should be good
[Music]
oh the name says sakamata chlorine and
uh
in korean nice pretty much is enough
yeah they're all they all seem to be
here all the time too so okay well good
luck guys um
don't don't worry too much about it
yeah
most of the time your chat is doing well
[Music]
chat is
good if someone's spamming the same
comment over and over feel free to bonk
them give them a timeout
banning is last resort okay
okay thank you everyone for watching
[Music]
uh
soon
and uh
i have a recording
in uh
uh in like uh
11 or 12 hours
so
i'll hopefully wake up for that and i
will make a stream reservation after
like
when i'm doing the recording i'll make a
stream reservation because i think then
i can
think
no no i'm not not recording any
any covers or so it's something else
something else
yeah
something exciting
but i'm recording a lot of things these
days so you will
not really know what it is until it
happens
[Music]
yeah oh pre-chat don't worry too much
about preaching
if someone's there that's cool if not
then that's also cool it will be fun
okay
huh
what
what's up pudding
oh
bad him
just kidding
yeah okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i had a good time with you guys thank
you very much for the great time
together
[Music]
you
yeah i'll see you tomorrow hopefully i
should i should be
streaming tomorrow don't worry i'll i'll
make it i'll make time for it
you know i don't like it having uh
two days without a stream on my channel
i can't stand it so
since uh friday i will be on a different
channel and i feel forced
[Music]
but don't worry i'm i'm relatively um
chill at the moment i don't feel that
stressed out
could always do a short game again yeah
yeah but i think i'll do sliver tomorrow
i don't want to use up too many of these
short games
that i haven't played yet i try to space
them out for whenever i need them
[Music]
as long as you don't burn up well well
my ski location is soon
i'm going on a ski location but i wonder
if that will be relaxing or just really
exhausting or it will be a lot of fun
and exhausting
i'm excited
wait wait wait
[Music]
yeah don't crash i'm preparing uh
i have one video prepared for that at
the moment uh or like it's in
preparation
but maybe i should ask some of these
lovely clippers here if they want to
provide something
um
maybe uh
if there's a clipper who wants to like
provide something
for
one of those days
i would really appreciate if you can
clip anything you can do anything and
make a [\h__\h] post or just a clip of one
of my recent long streams
[Music]
i don't want anyone
be creative
ace crowd hell yeah
booty pudding any of you unicorn where
you wet
anyone please make something
i need content for
taking a few days off i don't think i
really have enough time to do much more
[Music]
get to work
cow carrot yo if you wanna of course
no pressure though no pressure
yeah no new room zuma i could probably
do a new zoo video if you guys are not
sick of it yet
ah
okay everybody i'm gonna now
go sit in front of my door
and literally sit in front of it and
wait
[Music]
foreign
such a mood right
have a nice evening see you tomorrow in
germany
[Music]
i might not do an uh a tweet you can
just tweet it at me i know you guys like
to tweet at me just do it just do it
don't let your tweets be dreams
just tweet
[Music]