[music]
de
a
[music]
Haichiwachiwa Worldwide Tehachimo
red heart
That's why
So Hosa is in hard water minecraft for 1 week
Limited microphone dark big microphone big
It's okay, it's too big
Okay, so big is just right?
Is it better than being small?
Should I go with that?
Okay, that's why it's a little bit now.
3 days ago, about 3 days
4 more days
I'm sorry I'm late but 1234 left
I have 4 days left, I don't know if I'll be able to do it tomorrow.
No, but it's a little big so I'm wearing it a little.
[music]
Let's not do that
Well, it's the third day. Well, it's just the third day.
I'm going to participate in the race, and in fact, Minecraft.
Even though I was doing so much, I didn't have any adventures.
I've never done anything before, so I'm really a bit of a novice.
I have as much knowledge as someone else. I hope it's okay, Chiyoshi.
I've prepared some travel-like BGM for today.
Let's go in a travel-like manner.Let's go in a travel-like manner.
I wonder if I should go on an adventure for a while.
Became
mosquito
Alright, haa-chan, haa-cha-moa, wait.
It's been a while since I've greeted people.
Chama
It's delicious, it's bad, it's bad
When I changed it to hiragana, I had to change it back to half-width.
No, this is the first response.Oh no.
That place from earlier is a Tiki Rispon to raise funds for abdominal muscles.
Playing with the box
Atowa-chan and doggie-chan anything.
There's probably a bulletin board or a diary.
Submit to Nisshin, is it here? Okay.
I just want to draw today's diary.
Good morning
Yes
Everyone who saw the hole said "Ahhh"
I thought it was a hole, too.
Ah, today I met Nenanaka Mikoto.
Let's just check the audio
Just when I was thinking about it, I checked the audio too.
do
I met him, but I had something to do, so I left right away.
But I did
With a big face
It's not great that it exists, I left it there from the beginning.
Is this really true of Survivor 6?
This is from this one
It's not like I created it in the first place.
I don't think it's an official one, right?
Let's go this way too, there are a lot of holes.
Neneru told me to be careful.
Wow, it's really full of holes, it's running really bad
What should I do with this or that control?
You have to run and there are individual lockers.
Chamamoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa been put your face and rocker
That's okay, that's what your face looks like.
Their faces and heads all look like dead people.
Thinking
I'm still alive
Yoshihacha's face is Hacha's face This is different.
This is really Hacha's head that was Watson.
hang on
[applause]
Hey really
Worst of all, I wore the wrong clothes today.
When I checked the audio earlier, there was a school swimsuit
What's going on with me now?
Now that I'm here, I need to sleep for a while.
I thought it was the worst way to save water, so I thought about changing it.
It's going to stay like this, but at worst I want to go to bed early.
I went to bed early. Wait a minute.
I have to sleep
die
I'm going to cut it off. It's been 3 days.
This is dangerous, this is dangerous.
Let's go, there are 20 people in now.
Where did everyone go?
I guess I'll try going out a little more.
What is this? Survivor.
Rocca Amada is there, put your face down
That's it
Next
I wonder what's in there.I see.
I see, you added something later, great.
Thank you for your help.
Let's get out of here ai ai ai ai ai
Let's go out and say "I love you"
Rule book, write some rules
I saw the one you gave me
The rules were also written on the server.
Bock is with everyone
Read About the Mission Mission
Not this one
[music]
Dakochi's a little bit more disco
read the rules
well
Yes, there are some rules.
If it changes and dies
I'm sure they're doing some kind of trial, but I'm sure it's clear.
The condition is this
Will it really happen?
Oh my God, Ririka
Hello, give me some food
Have a meal
There is something
Good job
Oh yeah, I have some good food so I'll give it to you.
Opening the meal yay
Enamemen
What exactly is an iron door?
Even if I stand up, this is just the way it is now.
It's possible, I can't even destroy this
That stone was a stone too! It's amazing!
Amazing is amazing, but the diamond is probably mine
I guess it's more fun to dig.What are you doing?
Right now, just come and return the book.
Should I go home now? Should I go home now?
Okay bye bye yeah see you then do your best
Mei-kun wasn't there
I want Lyrica Amecha. I need food.
It's not like they didn't give it to me on purpose.
No, no, no, no, no, no
I was wrong, I thought it was kind of mean.
I'd like to think he's doing it on purpose.
No, no, no, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I brought something.
Like this
[music]
Okay, what about a senior like this?
It's really scary here.
It's so bad, it's so bad
Wow, that house is so big
There is an endra endra
Yes, it's true. When I looked closely, it was a big piece of equipment.
As expected of Lyrica, Katsuge and Deya Kaage
That's right, isn't it?
This is the horse he was riding. This is you, bye.
Bai Ekoyo-chan dies
It seems
What?
That's so cool
is
Boom boom, there's no place to fit in at all.
News coming from
intrusion
I mean, the flies were on trial about this and that.
Oh, I was on trial here.
I see.
It makes me sleepy
hey
Yes, debt
I wish I could pay it back with diamonds.
I feel like I need a diamond to come back to life
If something like that happens, I'll die.
If not, it's fine
It's this way, not this way.
It's not this way, it's this way, of debt.
You're digging for diamonds to pay it back.
You can earn some diamonds with Chinchiro, but you can't.
Where can I find such erotica?
Chinchiro
I didn't write down the location of that.
I wonder if it was there
Where can I check the rules?
I'm watching it on the server, but I'll check something.
There's a place
do not have
Yeah, I'll update it a little bit.
Please wait a moment.
Update the current rules
is dead
Ah, being a Heart-senpai means having a lot of juniors.
Jikkama Iroha-chan is equipped with it and understands it.
Thank you for your hard work, you have powerful equipment.
No, not at all, everyone has diamond equipment.
Is that what you're using? Everyone has diamond equipment.
It's not a diamond, it's just a diamond
It looks like it's in a falling position. What are you doing?
now
It seems that iron is becoming scarce now.
I'm making another trap, great!
I made one, but I have more.
I see, it seems necessary for the attack.
I see
Please don't die too, senpai. Yes, please don't die.
I'll do my best
Thank you for your support
The other person's voice is really scary.That's what happened just now.
Your voice was a little low, so let's adjust the volume.
Just when I thought about it, the conversation started.
Wait, it's over, where is it?
I just saw it
I'm still sick
[music]
Jan Ai Ai Ai Ai Volume adjustment this this this this
others
What do you all want to give?
I gave it to everyone
Can't you just give it to everyone?
Naoishooishooishooishooisho
Oishio Oishio
Oisho
Oishio Oishio Oishio
It's delicious
Thank you everyone.
[applause]
Looks like it's returned once. Let's celebrate.
Hey, this is made by Koya-chan.
It's a potion
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's no good.
It's annoying that it's going to be so loud. Wait a minute.
[music]
I'm like, let's go listen to everyone's voices.
Akoyo-chan and Dako-chan passed.
It's too early Zekoya-chan is too early
There are a lot of people gathered here.
Enanka Minatate Naka voice
[music]
Nocha
Yes, but I want a nether boat.
I've been through horrible things until I live in a grave
I was vandalized and told them that this was not a grave.
Good luck to you seniors
[music]
Sleeping
I'm so sorry, I wanted to take this back
I forgot to put it back
It's too erotic, I said it earlier.
That's what I said
It's not too soon to change everyone's equipment.
Miko everyone
Nonan
We also have dami and sol sand.
Everyone still hasn't forgotten what happened.
Nesan is still here. It's still the piglin from earlier.
A-chan too
It's so nice to be naked.
Very
I was naked. I wanted to wear some clothes, but I forgot.
Hey, there's water
Acha
Chanchichichichi
Ah, everyone has some amazing equipment.
I thought he was coming back from some kind of battle.
Thank you very much.
change
Taiaiaiinachanaachamachama
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, where are you going?
I guess that's what happened since I came back.
Everyone was saying, ``Wow, fill it up.''
Fried
So kind
I got it
Wow everyone is too strong
I'm a senior too.
Hey there
I want some clothes, how can I get them?
level I'm doing now
hey
I forgot to sleep after waiting.
So maybe, where did you go?
It's the guy
I see, that's good. I need to sleep.
Let's go to bed. It's still okay.
It's still okay
[music]
Somehow I survived in the bed from earlier.
And the first goal is to make some kind of tree.
cut down and make an ax
And somehow the bed
Let's make
Just look at what you achieved!
I can hear you, now I'm being shot with an arrow.
[music]
Tayoshi, it's good to eat, is that cherry tree the only one?
Amazing
Neyoshi
Okay, great tomorrow
I can't afford to die in a place like this.
No, it's still daytime.
Let's cut that tree, let's cut that tree polka
I can get a bed with you, I'll get that.
I have no choice but to wait a moment.
to
Let's go. Don't you have any food? It's so warm.
Where is the house?
to
Okay okay, this is bad, I’m such a beginner, this is bad.
It feels like I'm going back to seeing it for the first time.
[music]
I just made this!
That's crazy
This is good a little more
Cut it
Let's go, let's go
I want to go there to Polka-chanchi.
sea ​​bream
[music]
Relax and relax here
The Hashitoun sword that is reflected in the frame is also just for the record.
I can't even make a sword
Give
Okay, Zaza is wearing too much equipment.
sea ​​bream
I'm sure it's a treasure stone next to the jewel road.
It's delicious now
I heard it as if I was passing by.
Okay, this, this, this is amazing.
It's dangerous in the village, even in Minecraft.
I feel like I'm going to jump off like a pin
I'm going to jump off
[music]
It's a face, right? What village is this?
I don't know much about it.
Eh, this is the bed. What is this bed?
You can't do this, who is this?
Moisture, who is it? Who is it? Write something down.
do not have
Hey, I haven't written anything.
[music]
It's named after Noaori-chan.
It's an orange, but I haven't written it yet.
Where is it written? It's here.
Ori's House Ori that I didn't watch properly
Yoshia-chan also left something at my house.
Living with Chao Ollie without knowing it
Shall we do this?
Why is there not enough fire for white birch trees?
We don't have enough white birches, damn white birch trees here.
The differences are annoying. Wait a minute.
I can't help it, there are white birches.
Why did you make a stick out of white birch?
No, the stick doesn't change at all.
The type of wood for the stick doesn't change in the first place.
Hamachi Hachimachi Whose voice is it? I wonder if it's Pol.
Polka-chan, hey Polka, bed
The bed is over there, so please come over.
Which one would you like to go to?
I want to go to Emo Pol-chan.
Where is it?
I don't want to go, Pol-chan, I want to go.
Got it
Okay, so here's what's going on.
I don't want to get lost, so here it is.
Hey, what is this here?
Oh, it's really here at home
Free Tochi Free Take Free Bed
free
Bed free food amazing free bed
Suddenly
Zeha Ayoshi peep
Let's make a bed out of these sheep
That sheep is so tight
A polka in a tight place, a polka
I was able to eat polka cake.
Yes, there are 3 beds
Now that I think about it, Una-tan and I are living together.
By the way, who is that?
I couldn't see the letter. Does it start with K?
hoa sheep sheep
Sheep If you do this sheep, it will turn into meat.
I don't know if I can do it, but I don't have any stones yet.
Well, I'll stop today.
Kaishikaru
[music]
I think Kachimomo wants to live together.
daoishooishooishooisho
Oishio Oishio
It's dangerous if you don't make Oishoa Toma.
I'm already asleep, so I'm aware of the dangers of the night.
It wasn't there yet
That's so stupid
The tab is a match, the torch, the coal.
Let's dig coal By the way, while I was digging coal
We'll find it at Nisa Rock, so let's do that.
It looks like it's going to be colored, now that I think about it, it's Himemori
It's Luna Unatana Hachamaka Yahoo!
Yahoo yaho yaho what is that?
Naked, naked, naked
The soft-shelled turtle heart will die soon.
That's right, I've been living with Pol Pol recently.
Well, Popo just came back to life.
Hey, so it's okay to have a baby too.
That's right, it's okay for us to give birth together.
It's Popo
Whatever it is that you're tired of
Aratemashi Akare-chan
But what are you doing with Das?
this
Atmosphere Hello, ah, hello, what were you doing?
It's okay to wear clothes with such high losses, but this isn't true.
It's a baby's clothes, so don't iron it.
I thought I'd give you some equipment.
That's nice, isn't it?
Is it okay to be here? Ha-chan
I'll do something, even lick my shoes.
It's equipped with diamonds, right?
No, he's no good, I'm giving this to him.
No way
I'm trying to equip a diamond.
Oh, I left my ass alone.
Thank you, Aka-senpai, for dying.
I had the image of being a farmer.
But there are times when sweet people come to the village too.
There's one here too, but it's Popon.
That's so cool, Popo looks even more like a popo.
I'm glad it leaked, I'm only wearing clothes
Clothes, clothes, clothes, this is all for me
I caught it, I caught it, I caught it, I caught it, I caught it, I caught it
I was smoking this aaaaaaah thank you for coming
Thank you, I finally ran out of clothes, yay!
Is this your first time? It looks cool, but it's my first time today.
I like what you're doing, I'm scared
I mean, I just came in. That's what I mean.
Oke oke, I don't understand anything, is that so?
Hachama will tell you, Kaehachama
I would like to know if you are a senior.
I want you to tell me.I want you to tell me.This is this equipment.
This was given to me by Pol Pol on that first day.
I was logged in, so I have it.
Awesome
Oh yeah baby senpai this is baby senpai
Otochan this
No matter how much you have, it's about money.
There's nothing like that.
Don't say a word that you'll give it to me anyway
I was just bragging, but I'm sorry.
But
What do you think? I was just asking for your thoughts. What do you think?
I don't even think so, you don't have diamond equipment.
Well, that's not cool at all.
Is that what you're saying? Make it! Make it!
Can't you make it? I can't make it.
Right, what's that?One by one, what?
Should I make something like an ax?
I don't understand Tsuruha Ax
Eh, the equipment is good, the food is like a sword
I don't know if that's a good thing or not.
Wouldn't it be better to give it to someone?
t
It's hard, it's exciting, it's a waste, it's good
Nokarapuka Kenken Ayappa Cool Kakko
There are a lot of people who seem to like good people.
I had no Rupa
I can't stand up like this
Yay, please have it
I said I was going to die anyway.
This is hardcore, but I'm dead anyway
Nuu
I won't die
and
Scissors for something
I'll be there for a long time
I can hear things so confusing
It's funny, it's funny, it's usually like that
I can't hear you, so I'm in Achachi's bed.
This is floating, floating, floating.
Make something that's true
I haven't made anything for free.I haven't made anything.
It's like a mission or something.
It happened, right? Come to think of it, wow.
Mission What is the mission?
It was kind of a respawn point.
I'm currently living on a mission.
It was over there.
No, I don't know, I don't know, look at the server
I'll take a look at the server over there, maybe.
I think the response points were better as a reward.
I made money
[music]
what
This is what I always do when I go there.
It's always Miko-senpai's dick.
It is thought that Tanaka Yadacha did it.
Yabamiko-senpai told me not to come later.
I'm sorry, I'm home more
Home Yahoo!
I'm going to get some cotton ice.
I'm going to go get that crane.
Silk Touch Ei is about to reach that point.
Hey, I have Daimon Diamond.
I don't have it, I can make it, it's true, it's just a show
I just have one, Kare-chan, I don't have one.
But the nose is real. That's all I have.
But I'm going to work. Great job.
Let's go. I went.
Wait a minute, let's work too.
Let's work. What should I do? It's like home.
Nano
Who is this? It's Romiko's house. Utara
Let's go to the house. It's open. Let's go.
Masu Rami is really suspicious though.
It's a house of love, isn't it?
What what?
Maybe
If you lose the fire in the wild, you'll burn a lot of magma makeup.
Let's put this in there.
Where did your pet go?
I earned it with Shichichi. Use it as you like. Go to sleep.
Bette I love this interaction.
Anyway
Oh Musu
Get out
No, this is this, this is yay trap
This is what's happening here. Amazing.
Oh wow, I can only go here from here.
Oh, you can also go in here because it's here.
Ice cream, let's do this
Can't you meet me, even diamond?
It's already been said that I don't like showing off.
Eat and sleep there and live happily ever after.
You're going to break this, you're going to break it, you're going to break it
Chayabai even has this cat.
Hey, this thing looks like a door.
I see.
That's right. You could die here and come back.
I can't
I won't give up, but what can I do to get it out?
Noeja Diamond Dai What should I do?
I don't have it, but here are 10 diamonds.
It's not worth that, it's not worth that
Ja 5 5 5 5 5
There's no such thing, there's no such thing, is there a thing?
Is that okay? It's not just the shape after all.
What can I give you in return?
I guess Ehachamo is kind of weird.
It's like a kiss or something
Don't aim for something like that.
do not have
Damn it, it's 20 diamonds.
It can't be helped, 20 pieces.
I won't give it to you for the rest of my life, so I'll give it back to you.
It's diamond diamond, so get it out of there.
Akara
Oh, it's raining.
It's raining and I died here in my bed.
Bed aso da Hacha's bed is here
Ah
Taare
Well, it's not night now.
No, I'm not going to die anyway, so I'll just keep the bed.
It's a carry-on type. Click here to see the mission.
Is there a book here in town? Is there something in the back?
At the respawn point
A response point
Oh, I'm going to cry about you
Chan, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub
Oh so cute
Babauhaha, are you babbling about Hachama?
Because Kahachama is a baby
I guess I got licked for bubbling.
Here it is, here it is, mission mission
I don't understand the mission
Hello
Howad is it okay?
Is there anything you don't understand? It's okay.
I don't know if I didn't take it myself.
I have to take this and that even once.
I want it, wait a minute.
It's gone!
I thought it was going to be a while, but what?
[music]
Who was the first one to go?
I took it
If you make a useful trap, you can get diamonds.
Advertisement This way, someone should have it now.
Tezono
There is no daylight
I don't know, [ __ ]
I feel like an adventurer
This is the one who will receive wings.
Oh my god
Karan Karan finding the An Pyramid
Just the sound of the can-can is a bit boring.
Defeating the temple boss
[music]
Wow, something has disappeared, it's written there.
Chan
Yaho yaho, go and do something like subjugation.
The four of us went to the Nether, right?
I'm here, I went great, I came back, I went great.
I came back and found only the Piglin Fortress.
Piglin Fortress That's a lot of diamonds
There was a certain color in the nether fortress.
I got one, but I found 4 chestnuts.
It seems like he didn't get any special ones either.
But I'm glad I came back alive.
Good
I've just come here and I'm afraid everyone
blessing
I was blessed with a little bed and Ron.
I've got some, but I'm going to work now.
The feeling of wanting to be with someone is amazing.
I see. At first I was already suffering from heat rash.
I feel like my entire body is full of blessings, haha.
Hey, even at work, it's a little difficult.
Nandoshia Button-chan, Kida Kikie
It looks like it's equipped with amazing diamonds. It's already dead.
So I came back and went to Asoka Button.
Tanaka, thank you for your hard work, amazing hero.
The assailant who can't do what he has
What is that?
My mission is to put my luggage over there and wait.
I was thinking about what to do in case I die, but that's not the case.
I don't want to die, so just in case, do this.
Put in the one you got, why do you have a boat?
Maybe I took something terrible before I knew it.
What's the big 20? Write down if it's true.
There was one, wasn't that one given to me?
This is terrible, what is this?
Thank you and thank you for your hard work, Yoshiin Akocchika.
I dug something up. Is there something here?
I was surprised, what is this?
Isn't it good that he can fly?
Teyoshi
Thank you for your hard work, bye bye. That color is different.
What is this? It wasn't this.
is
Okay, the bubu never goes away.
I don't have one
Yakocchi also didn't notice Aki
Okay, this is the one that did the mission earlier.
this
After all, the power is at the same level.
Kotsuteme Kurechande is more detailed
from
Ah, I know so much about pigeons.
Is com real?
Who will die first? Take it by boat.
Is this okay? That kind of weird bed
I'm sleeping while looking at the little one.
I don't have it. I don't have it.
It's gone
Ah, it looks like there are two people in the water, it's so cool
The traffic jam is terrible. It's as fast as a typhoon.
It was so outrageous, who is it now?
It's like the two of them are sleeping together.
But
Everyone is happy in bed with this bed.
People think we're good friends because of money.
Oh wait a minute
Oh my god, it's over there!
So I'm going to sleep there.
I thought I was in trouble, but that's not true.
The story is loud and loud.
It's not a big girl. Over there.
Yes, yes, comment.
Lower it
It's okay. If I'm going to do it next time, it's a stone.
How many potions do you need?
need nether
I'm sorry I got a book in there.
Sorry, I have something in my hand.
I have that cobblestone making machine that went in, but I can't do it.
I think I can defeat all three of them.
I think I can do this or that.
That's right, the first discovery of Nether sheep is impossible.
Oisho who obtains distorted mushrooms
It seemed like something was going to happen, so the two of them got involved.
Kotonari and I went to get frog eggs.
I'm going to that love event.
frog eggs
It's difficult for people who have never had a relationship with someone.
I wonder who is the one who has never been involved before?
never
I don't know what people think
Is there any red light in the box?
entangled
Things involved
No, I'm trying to cheat.
Looks like the one from the Nether Coal Sand
Growth
Teru or different
Come on board
Let's go to Le San Sol Sando or Gust 1
body
I'm going to take something like that here, I'm going to take one thing here.
Take the page from the bottom right corner
Everyone should get one of these.
I did
Hey, the bottom right veggie seems to want to do it, so his name is in IQ.
It's like Gus and the girl's manga, same as the school festival.
If you say it, it'll be okay. Strategy plan.
I'll kill it, but I'm going to go get the frog's eggs.
Yes, that's also difficult. Yes, it's difficult.
I don't really understand Acha either.
3 skeletons that only know this
I feel like I can do something to defeat it though.
At times like this, I feel like my senior is going to get angry.
Where's the consultation? Button-senpai, yes.
Senpai, I want that diamond equipment.
That's too much, too true.
Daya, I only have about 20 pieces left.
Very
Yes, no, no, no, no, how do I work?
I'm not looking for you, I'm just looking for you
I've heard of Chichinchiroha.
Apparently not. Was there something else?
I don't understand the Chinchiro rules.
Not
Yeah that seems like it
I think I can go to Glowstone.
And this is one grownstone.
Possibly
I just realized this, don't break it
That means you have to put it in
It's not a skin touch, it's a clean touch.
No, skinship or whatever
Silk touch that feels like a touch Silk touch
The fact that there is
And now it's done. This is what I did.
I wonder if there's anyone out there who hasn't been involved
Frog eggs, I don't know about this, but whatever.
I don't know what frog eggs are.
By the way, Tapijamo here is solder.
Write the mission reward here.
There are rewards for both the Nether and Nether Piglins.
Unique leather sole
sol 3 note
Sashikore sand, achakore
Let's go, I'll write it down just in case, but let's dig together.
sea ​​bream
Na
If that's true, then it's all over, or what?
Don't do it, it's either over or it's over, it's dangerous
Oh no, it's a mistake
Ta
Everyone, everyone, everyone, copy paste copy paste
Copy paste everyone copy paste copy paste
I found the copy and paste. Wait a minute.
Oh, I have 20 diamonds. What should I do about the text?
Wait a minute, take this
It's like an adventurer's guild.
I thought about taking it with me and thought about it carefully.
I'll write this on paper.
Original What should I do with this?
Button-chan, what are these letters?
I'm sorry, please wait a moment before I can write.
Sorry, I did something while I was importing.
Take this soul sandwich, but write it in English.
Yes, I don't remember the reward very well.
What's that?
They'll give it to me after I get the wrong mission board.
I did it so badly that I made a mistake.
I ended up doing it every day and it was a bit
Diamond equipment and
I thought I'd ask you to give me a call.
Somehow, I took that board from this mission.
I ended up becoming a master.
I guess this is my soul sandwich
I guess I'll have someone write it for me.
If you write it in the chat section of decoding
Oh okay, then just a little text.
I'll just write a few words, sorry.
It's time to write that I took it.
I hope you can rewrite the mistake I made.
Thank you, Solesand, oh maybe, that's right
Yeah, I think it was soul sand.
Yeah, let's get some soul sand. Is it in the Nether?
I'll go get it, I'll take it in the net, and I'll get it later.
I think it will be okay if I contact you.
Mistake
Tajaaki-chan, thank you for your hard work today.
Good job, another subjugation vs. good job, good job again.
I think I'll go to the face a little bit,
deeper year by year
The last day I submitted it was 3 days ago.
I think Aki-chan's diary is probably here.
I think, "Ah, I'll write a diary on Sunday."
When you finish writing, please submit your diary here.
It's over, it's interesting, I'm alive, yeah
I feel like that's the case, yes, yes, then.
Thank you for writing it. Thank you.
I'll imitate this a bit and write it out later.
I'm sorry, but it's okay.
I'll write to the chat now.
Um, what is this, all this chatting?
Why is there nothing there?
There was a lot of nodding.
I'm sorry for sleeping, but the number of people is increasing and I can't talk.
is
Mishi Mission's Eso 1, 1st End
Thank you very much for your hard work today.
Looks like he has a lot of oars
Hey, it looks like you have a lot of diamonds.
Okay, thank you for giving me that.
Ta
I want it all
Oh, I want some weird food too.
I was asked to speak English, but it's okay.
Write down Zukocchi too.
I'm a kind and gentle Pecola senior.
Thank you, but things have changed now.
thank you
I don't think there's anything else that would be better.
Thank you very much
I've got one more for you. One more for him.
We're not fighting, can we get some stairs?
thank you
Tomorrow, it's sunny here, Sol Sand
It's like a trash can that's been a bit noisy.
koto mate
Noe Akochan no friends
friends of
This is amazing, I haven't changed it to E.
The yellow voices of Director Chan and his friends
mixed
Until the last day when I chant ``Akun is cool''
This is amazing, you wrote a lot of things.
Feeling of anticipation, let me be alone for a little while
I can hear you really loud
Don't put it away
You can hear it a lot over there.
Go over there once and take a quick look.
Let's see it! I got some equipment too!
Ta
Now I want a soul sandwich for this.
There are too many dangerous roads here.
Going
I'll go, I'll go, I'll come back alive
Masu Soul Sand Soul Sand Taka Soul
Sand is something like sand, right?
No, I don't really remember, but the diamond
I thought there would be three
It's dangerous if you don't have Tarakin equipment.
Wow
Seriously, go home, Aki-chan, this equipment.
I was able to go there because I had friends with me.
Hey, no, I saw it a little, I saw it a little, I saw it a little.
bed
I won't die in a dangerous bed. This is serious. This is serious.
He has a face that looks like Munch's scream
It may be easy to understand, but it's surprisingly easy to understand.
easy one
No cat either
No yes
Wow Glowston
This is not what I want.This is not what I want.
It's not that, it's not that, it's not this.
It's not like sand.
[music]
Isn't it sand? Just wait a minute, it's just the head.
no head no
Wow, Grostan is over there.
needs a silk touch
[music]
Let's just take it home and take it home.
do that
[music]
What can you do with a nether coach like this?
Yo
Even silk touch is different from silkta.
No silk touch
I wonder if it's that or that glow
I can't get the stone, Growstow.
I think it was 5 diamonds.
Okay, let's go a little further.
raster craft
[music]
Go
Hanna
[music]
what is here
here another
Exit, this is also an exit
Dana
It's said that I can go to a world I haven't seen yet.
Kotokokoha
where
What is that?
[music]
here
Oishoku
[music]
Should I go back?
I don't know anything either
here
[music]
Yeah, I'll go back for now.
mosquito
Let's go there once and see.
Become
And Chanda
Hello hello hello
[music]
What are you doing now that I'm taking a walk? Later that day I'm taking a walk in Seoul
I'm going to Netherland to get Sad.
That's right, that's right, yes yes
What is it? It's frozen. It's not frozen.
What what?
If there is something you don't understand in a hurry
Please say yes thank you
Yes, what is this? This is this. TT
It's a tower, it's a TT tower, it's a trap tower.
So please feel free to use it! Go check it out!
Is that okay? I really want you to go see it.
I think my grave is also there, so please take care of it.
Please, yes, I'll go to the grave, die.
Okay, I'll go. The two of us will be back now.
I see, I'm going back now.
I see, thank you for your hard work.
There is
There's no sense of distance, it's okay, it's so gentle
Since it is a honorific language, I think Sacha should also be a honorific language.
I think
The operation switch has been turned on, so it seems likely.
That's what I'm saying, cat and dog, the switch is turned on.
Thank you very much for your support.
I see, that's how it went.Yes.
Alright, okay then bye bye, do your best, do your best
Wait, that's it
It's dangerous, Atan says something and we go to see
When I asked if it was okay, it was fine.
Maybe it's because it felt like
It's kind of dangerous.
That's dangerous
be
Yoshio Maruo
I'm going all the way.
[music]
Even if the water keeps on going
If you don't drink it, it won't be a problem.
It's water
Even the water fell on that rock over there.
That's why it's cut out.
I see
That's what it is
mosquito
Yes, Shieto-chan was muted.
Why is Asouiya and Towa-chan?
It's like Marika is practicing conversation.
It looks like we did it together. His name is Tokoyami-san.
All the things I forgot are sleeping here aaaaaaaaaaaaa
I died here so this little bit
I'm confused, but I'm trying not to die here.
I was wondering if it would be okay since 2024.
May 16
The day will come when this will be updated
Or don't use a lot of zombie TT.
Will zombies come down?
[music]
What is this?
Painful gunpowder, could this be TTTNT?
I can make something that I can use.
Yaaaah, cut this here.
There it is
Switch over there or gold helmet
Even with this, I still have a little bit of durability left.
Maybe I can get some money.
this
teeth
No, it's fine now.
I guess it's better not to say anything now.
It's a skeleton, but this is a skeleton
I wonder if there's anything wrong with defeating it?
This doesn't mean you've defeated the skeleton.
Looks like it's not there haha
skeleton
Are you a skeleton? What did you defeat?
Tara what?
[music]
If you bring it, you will receive it.
The reward is to earn experience points.
How can I get paid for this?
I know how to write it, but I forget the number of people.
fleeting
How many people is this? How many people? One time per day.
It was written that it goes around, so that means 3
That means more than 3 animals, right?
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Wow, thank you, this is the management.
Wow, I'll do this with a sword.
I'll do it with a sword. Don't forget to write it down.
Shitoa memo memo mission memo
mission memo
mission
Skeleton Autan
Dachaga
Yahoo
Hoho, there's so much left.
Wait, I'm on a date with you.
This can be muted
Yes, but what about it?
I guess it's okay to have this. Wait, this is it.
This is how I understand the bow.
It's impossible to do that, the damage is the same or 1
After all, he has a lot of bones.
I have a lot of bones, is that what you mean?
You can make a special cup for your dog.
The Oisho couple is currently hunting
hey
[music]
What are you waiting for? It seems that electricity is available.
This and this Serea cloud
I took the trouble to get it at Gazukin Nantoko.
I'm wearing it because I'm a guy.
It's kind of white now
[music]
There are so many things I don't want to ride.
Too many skeletons? How many skeletons is this?
skeleton
[music]
Is it possible to earn skeletons here as judged?
This seems like a good skeleton anti-an
Good job
[music]
That's enough now, thank you for your hard work.
I received various things such as Taoiseach and nose etc.
I'll take what I got, I'll take it.
Okay, let's drop the iron bark.
Ta
Yeah, what's this?
Gahakou and now half block
Oh, I don't need a bow or a bow.I have everything.
It's not like that, right? It's a magic that removes various things.
magic
girl
Witch
Creepy. It wasn't creepy.
creeper
Kagashira
gold hair color
I can spend an infinite amount of time here.
Something like this
I'll call this a pawn and give it some experience points.
The sound I'm getting is so soothing, it's so good
It feels like I made a mistake, and I'm in danger of breaking it.
That was Glowstone Dust.
You can't make Grownstone with this.
Is it impossible or grown?
You said you were going to get the stone.
All right, all right.
Okay, now I can go to the Nether. I only need one more.
Not what
What are the legs?
You can do it if you collect 4 panties.
I have to go and get it
It wasn't there.
I'm sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, the Nether.
It said to go get it, so no.
What is it?
It's a bit dark after sleeping here.
I don't know if I should go but then I'm scared
It's already night, so it's almost time
I want to sleep
Neyoshie Kin and Miko are going on a mission.
Wow!
What is Nether Mission?
Koto Kaelaa Kaelain
I'm not logged in yet.
Yes yes
Did I go to bed a little too early?
[music]
No, it's magical
Baby, baby, baby, hey
I want to go see Kara.
Seriously
[music]
That's what happened when I woke up right now.
That's fine, okay, I'll win in a bit.
Let's get this going after everyone goes to bed.
[music]
Good, feels good
I want to meet Kara Kara
Nakacha is already indebted to Kara.
I also went to get elytra.
Neandoshi
I also got some super spicy nur from Indonesia.
I ate a lot of sleep
[music]
Yo
Ma
NokumaColle
As if there was
When you say you're going to pick me up, does that mean you're about to go?
Kaa now everything is going hachama too
I want to go too
Okay, I'm a little scared now.
[music]
Yo
Okay, let's go home for a while, where are we going?
Who is that? He's over there with a sword.
Even if it's bad that I'm back,
early
Who is that? Oh Pol Pol and the others, Yahoo!
Yahoo, I'm sleeping, let's go
Sorry to disturb you. I'm going to sleep there.
Hona wolf
where wolf
I'm looking for a wolf
mosquito
wolf
I think I can make a wolf shield.
No, wait, the zombies are here, the zombies are here.
Zombies are here! Zombies are here!
Well, it's not good to be drowned.
I don't have a lot of fish, hey hey hey
Hey, it's not a bear, it's not a bear.
It's a panda. Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
Na
Oh, you idiot, you idiot, you idiot!
help me
I was surprised to find that the handwriting was strange.
Oh, that's good, that's terrible.
I'm so nervous, I can't sleep.
I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go
I'm glad I could go
Thank you very much, that's good
thank you
Okay, okay, let's go home to the bed that is the source of life.
I'm scared it's going to fall off now. It's a bit lame.
Go, let's go
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Basa without gold gold equipment
It's a bit dangerous, it's dangerous, now that I think about it, I said it earlier.
Well, go to sleep, it's okay, ooh, go to sleep now.
I just woke up, so please come back soon.
It's my first time to be able to meet up.
Why are you here on a mission?
You're getting a little impatient, stop this.
Pig this pig bastard
You're making me feel anxious!
[music]
hand
Okay, wow, there wasn't any bad food at all.
I'll get some at Polpornchi.
good
I called you, but I didn't call you.
More
Ta
Anno
I wonder where I can get it?
Not going back
Chan, it was someone, that potion.
Kaita Nene Rice Chida Rice Rice Ginger
No, this is the one I got from Korra-senpai.
Wow, as expected, this is definitely not rice.
After all, I want to make rice with this.
It's a little small, but yeah, that's Pecola.
I think you should just tell your senior.
No, no, Pecola-chan
I said, ``Give me this food,'' and I give it to you.
It's not like it happened.
where to
Sorry to keep you waiting, Senpai.
It's here, yay, Amikochi, rice, rice, ah
I don't have any
[music]
Chanuya yahoro, I'll give you some tea too
I did it
Wow thank you
I want to put my baggage in the money.I want to get it from the money.
I'll put some rotten rotten meat in here.
There were 64 pieces of rotten meat in the meat rack.
If you eat meat you can't eat anything. Amazing.
Haacha will get food poisoning
Okay, water is coming out. Maybe everyone is now
Hey, some voice is preparing a bow, so come on.
Aki-chan Aki-chan
This is a countermeasure
The emotional diary I wrote earlier
Let's go, let's go, let's go, Lela.
Oh no, it sounds like a kindergarten teacher.
Mikocha
A villager
Is it okay to equip the villager grass house Miko? Earth house?
Yeah, that's true. Hey, wait a minute, Diamond.
I borrowed the equipment from Issho.
I borrowed it here.
I wonder if that?
Oh ta ta ta ta Sorry sorry sorry change of clothes
What was that?
Yeah, my endurance is almost running out
Teru
But don't worry, it's money.
Miko Zoyoshi, please make sure you don't know.
Please, senpai
Protect that!
lever
So protect it
I see.
Nauoiyoi Shoyoshimiko
Senpai, I've been standing up quite a bit since he came in.
I guess it's just normal
mosquito
[music]
Okay
Massage at 9pm
twist
Even though they say it's less than a little money.
I have all the equipment, thanks to someone else's debt.
Oh yeah, I'm already in debt.
It's not Damikochi's debt. He's dead.
What a stupid Subaru
Hmmm, I heard about it from a rumor. I started making it early.
That guy who returned to the world of Nio is outrageous.
I hope you're doing well. See you soon.
There wasn't.
Oh hello hello
hello hello hello hello hello
I got HelloCa. I got it.
haha minecraft
divine god
I'm not a god. I'm in trouble. Thank you.
wish
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Masuma
Mom ok ok
Okay
Mabe
Akai-chan's To-chan is To-chan
Treat me like a grandchild
Because he's my father, is he my father?
dad dad
Hello Daya Equipment
[music]
There are so many books, my whole body is made of diamonds, all of them are good.
Come to think of it, I can't hold this shield.
You can make a shield without begging.
I don't have it
It looks like it can be removed with something like a production machine.
I see, I heard that you should go here.
Miko
oh
Before Tae Kim
Let's make this. No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not this, it's this, it's this
Te this is it
It's okay, Lego, let's go.
It looks like you don't have it just from Ui.
If you don't have enough food, you can get it in the middle of the roll.
I'm glad it's like that because it's there.
Someone's about to die, stop that Frank.
I'm sure I'll die, I'm sure I'll die
Is that no good? I have to return it to the manager.
That's why I die saying that.
No good
It's so beat up
Everyone who can do it
Hold on
[music]
Repeat, I know what Mim's Mim is repeating
was doing
It may be easy
[music]
I'll live for the manager, but I'll die for money.
If you don't have it, it'll cost you money
Live and do your best
Kikiroa cute horse
Chan
cormorant
Good luck
There's something about yoshiyoshi that gives you a shield.
Apparently
I can make a shield, I can make it.
Okay
There are so many buoys
I can't afford to let it go, tomorrow will be red
[music]
Very dangerous equipment
Oh my god, you just gave me a bow.
There's something here.
cooked rice
There's something poisonous about it, but it's true.
Where did it come from alpaca alpaca?
I wonder if he's out. I'm going to sleep. He's calling me.
Oh, I'm lost. What is this?
Chamo
Yeah hello hello ha-chan what's up too?
What are you doing right now? I'm going to bed with everyone.
No matter where you go, Arekoyo-chan?
I'm a little lost, where is that?
This way or that way?
That senior, Akoya-chan, was able to come back to life.
I was able to come back to life, thank you to my senpai.
I don't have the proper equipment, but my bow is missing.
Thank you for collecting that item though.
There you go
First of all, maybe I should make this transparent and play around with it.
It's a different village.
I'm so excited. Is this what it's like? I came to the village.
Thank you for bringing back my senior. I'm sorry.
Thank you for coming with me.
Polopolo is back, so Popo is there too.
There it is, there it is
Maybe that's it?
That's wrong, a lot of people.
Wait until we meet
I understand this.
Michimi Ka-senpai, are you going now?
Yo Mission Mission Popo where did he go?
Oh my, I'm so sad.
I'm going to sleep on the clean bed I've been scratching
Mom, you can go to bed.
Ah, can you sit down? Ah, someone please sit down.
What's wrong with that? I went and got this.
Masukono
If you sleep with me, you'll be fine.
Looks like I'm having a really hard time sleeping
It's not that my legs are bad, we've been living together recently.
Right, wait, wait, let's play, Rami-tan.
Hey, I saw you there the other day.
I've seen a mysterious dark house.Darkness.
It's not a deep love house.
It's scary, it's all water together
Jan let's go
I was so excited, I wondered who was on fire.
Yo Creeper-chan
[music]
Ohm
strong farewell
difference between
A fellow
It's best to go where the big cat is.
There are some stylish places like here and there.
[music]
It's far from the orchestra flame.
far
far away
[music]
Akocchi
Here, here, here, hello hello
[music]
Ah, what kind of potion is Sandaki?
I'm thinking about sand potion
Yay, hey, I finally have it.
A gift given to me by the baby frog who got the shield.
Even though I came here, that money turned into a two-handed shield.
You brought it for Ha-chan.
That's right, so use your two-handed shield to survive.
It's not defense. You can do a mission with this.
No, that's it, that's it.
Well, if someone loses their shield, I'll definitely be their shield.
I wonder if it'll ever go away. It'll be broken.
I think there are times when it just disappears.
It's definitely okay
Eyoshi Yoshi-chan, I’m looking forward to it, I’m looking forward to it, I’m looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to the double shield, it's a strong shield
So there's this. Come to think of it, this is this.
I got it from here. Ah, I got it when I was going home.
But I have two now.
Gome
thank you
Oh
Also, Dere Dere You hasn't been found yet.
It seems unlikely
Is it better to have a clay block or something?
I don't have any. Please bring a lot of things.
There are no stones to climb, there are only trees.
What should I do, I should have left this behind.
I brought a lot of strange things.
Well, I'm a little further now.
Neyoshi
I think Hacha understands, but you're okay with money.
Don't bring your own bed. I understand the price.
You should just leave it here.
Is the bed bad?
That bed is terrible
Also put aside
I left a lot of things there, hmm.
It's a good idea to do something like this.
Oshioishioshioshi
[music]
Kuno is amazing, far is a little amazing
I'm sure it's at the back of the t where it spins round and round.
That open space looks nice.
I want to go home and grill some meat today.
Unfortunately, money has died.
It's really no good, so today is today.
It's a shame I shouldn't die.
This guy is so gross, this is my first time.
of
mosquito
Wow!
They won't attack me, definitely.
You can't beat that pig.
It feels like they're attacking all at once.
Well, be careful. Money isn't money.
That looks like some kind of quartz
If you collect it, it will become a white block.
[music]
Yes, it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I have this and that in the orchestra.
Takooru ok wow it's money
[music]
It's too easy to understand with money
Oh, I'm taking money
It's okay
Okay, I see. That sand-like thing.
I want to get it
Na
Bubu I was wondering if this would be better.
It looks like we'll run into each other when we go, so just go straight
Maybe it's better not to go Ah, there's magma
It's too early, it's too salty.
It's nice to come next door to your mom.
Girigiri-chan died
He's dead, he's dead
Chan Esui
Goodbye, sir, senpai, Miko
Older sister Emikochi Luna Luna senior
I guess so
Norasa Senpai
There is
Jiyo-senpai
Piaya died here in a different place.
Will I die? Will I become a star? Will I become a star?
It seems like she's back and beautiful.
There are definitely people who write in diaries.
When the road opens, the chief will appear.
She was acting scary, wasn't she?
[music]
I'm running away from
Don't you stop running away quickly? Run away.
It's true that there's nothing to stop a cough even if it's a cough suppressant.
Wait, wait, wait, I'll bring it
There's Gusto, there's Gusto, there's Gusto
Let's go back
I forgot to bring something to stop my terrible cough.
I should have brought it here.
From now on, the remaining machine is dead, the remaining machine is already dead.
It's like dying one more time.
Let's go first
I should go and borrow it.
No, you're strong, Senpai.
There's more than Iroko behind me. Go, it's okay, I'm here.
light the way
I'm sure you'll enjoy the yoke and the naora.
That's not true. Don't dig this.
What is this money?Is this good?
Even if I go down, it will become a hole, so the path is under the ground.
Something like that
Looks like you have a lot of desire to live
[music]
Hey, wait, it's going to be a flag, so stop it, it's going to be a flag.
I'm trying to test my nerves
It's so packed that it doesn't seem strange.
So if one person starts a fire, it's likely that everyone will start a fire.
Somehow I managed to slip through and it was just me
Let's survive
On the other hand, I'm a little sorry
Well, if you're going to die, die and break it properly.
It's okay, it's still there, it's coming when it comes out
I also have a diamond ice ax.
Worst case, I'll dig Magma Cube Gust
Magma Cube
That's why it's about time
I've got a new, nice new thing that's broken.
I wish I hadn't had a bow.
I regret it so much
I left it behind and I'm already nervous
My heart is pounding as if it's here.
I left it behind to fish.
Oh, you're so flirty, aren't you?
I guess it's better to have it after you have it.
I see, what did you hit?
I've been flirting with you. Looks like you can return it.
Tell me about Gusto
That's right, that's right
[music]
mosquito
[applause]
Oh my, my senior
Isn't Noia the first one to run away?
Yo
[music]
Great for calming down when you get home
too much
Yeah, Trider is crying, Trider.
That's not a big deal.
The magma used for the akaine magma
Na-chan is responding to me. I'm being pushed to death.
That's right
Is there something scary about Strider? It's made of wisteria.
It was called
Hey, I'm solo and I don't have the Daya Asoka block.
From now to now
Hell, I didn't bring any blocks.
I guess I'll just grab some blocks around here.
He's dangerous, he's dangerous, he's dangerous.
It's dangerous. I might come here. I'll go this way.
Okay, wait or wait.Okay, by the way.
Kin-chan, you can't use water, so there's no point in that.
Yeah, okay, everyone squats down.
Squat down. Squat down with two legs.
Okay, I get it, it's scary.
You have to crouch down and fall.
Let's go
But I don't think I'll find anything.
Even if it feels good, is there a road over there?
the way to push push push push
Na
Already full
Shito is okay
Airuya is there
It's dangerous
Aya!
Ta
I think I'll die in one hit if I don't fall.
Is it because of the equipment?
Nice nice nice What is this?
Put out this fire with your hands, put out this fire.
do not have
There are a lot of guys.There are a lot of guys.
It's scary, scary, scary
It's snowing heavily
Wow, I feel calm. It's okay.
Kaoshisho
there's a road over there
Which one is it, Dad? It's scary.
I don't want to die like a stag
It's so precious
Yooioishooishooishoa gold this
You can't take this money, you can't take it.
The pigs are looking at the one I just said.
That's what it is, you dangerous pig.
Follow me, follow me, it's Harton
from
Hey pig, you're taking this money.
Don't take it
It's better to go there
Above is the direction I was aiming for, yes, I'm sure.
Have you ever been there before?
The white one is probably fake, someone is doing it.
Well, someone else is doing it, so it's already being watched.
Looks like it's okay to take the white one.
But maybe, I can't guarantee it.
No, are you okay? No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, I didn't expect it to be taken, so I'm so upset.
My body has taken this, so run away, I don't know.
No, I'm not going to kill you. Looks like it's okay. Where did the gust come from?
There's one more fish that's gone!
I'm still trying to make a bow
I can't go there
Go Yatchi Store Wherever you are, it's stylish
Kanade-chan, I can only do so.
Even if I am obese, I can only be fashionable.
I'm sure you can make a slightly more beautiful house.
Yes, there is a hardcore and stylish house.
I'm sure I can make it even if it's still there.
Gusto was around here, right?
I'm doing this because I don't like the guy who attacked me in Kanner earlier.
I wonder where it is?
Not scary
What's going on in your throat?
It's no longer dangerous to be here.
hey
[music]
Chiara-senpai, who is here, also does scary things.
Emobutabuta is a little nearby so I can eat it.
I wonder if you're watching ``Buta Iruaani Aiarune''?
Are you looking for
Oh so nice that I defeated Gust.
Nice nice, I defeated it, I defeated it.
nice
Iipi
Moooo, it's okay, it's okay, I'm squatting
Scary, scary, I don't know where to go
Whoa, who's face is so stiff right now?
I didn't understand this hacha
Senpai, what are you doing so much about me?
Did you want to kiss me?
is straight
That can't be true.
Yeah, you should just say it. It's annoying.
I wish I could say it directly
What is this?
How can I improve my Japanese?
is
I can do this with such a purchase.
that of
I'm reading a bit of manga.
It's too much, no, no, that's it
I read too much love manga and don't read manga.Where did I learn about it?
Dandayo anime
No no no
[music]
No, I learned it from anime.
Thank you Michiyoshi Okay okay oh
Amazing, I can't jump over this
No, I feel like this is what I came for, so this is it.
For example, I jump when I feel like I can go home.
No, but there was a way the other way.
Oh yeah, what are we going to do here?
go straight
Let's go and see, everyone is safe.
Shiko's
Maybe I'll find out if I go that way.
[music]
I guess I'll probably go back then.
I see, is this the path Chiron and his friends took?
The way we came the other day
That's right, I want to take it, but I can't take it.
If you don't use Chilk Touch, it will break.
That's right, Dad, that's right.
I don't even know
Noi
I wanted to take it too
It doesn't look like that either.
Maybe this is okay
It's no good if you take something that someone else took.
What? Yeah, that's no good, I'll go get it.
It was written there, I probably got it in the Nether.
If I remember correctly, everyone's name was written as Kuru.
I saw this or this from here
Join us
It looks bad, don't go back.
I guess it's back, I see.
Ah, the way back?
Nafumufumuyoshi That's right, dangerous, dangerous.
It's dangerous. Wait a minute. It's really dangerous.
Really no, really no, really no, hey
Too simple
Yo
hang on
[music]
early
Ha, it's too early, it's too early, it's too early
Can you open it if it's too much? I'm a bit of a rose nerd
This is the limit, the activity limit, what is this?
You can see the word by doing it.
Good night
I can't open it.
It was so peaceful, so peaceful.
I was having fun taking a walk, but this happened.
Thank you for your hard work.
No no no no no
Ugh
Okay, what is this? What the hell is this?
Can you write me a list of the dead?
I knew it wasn't important, I knew it
I thought there was a hole somewhere like that.
There isn't.
Well, I'll try my best on this one.
Please
[music]
Even those who know so much don't know.
I was thinking
Oh, build a grave
How can I get this from a paper perspective?
All you have to do is switch
What about that?
I want to see what other people are doing
look at other people's stuff
want 1
[music]
thank you
Hey
1 point yes
Press teleport 1 again
Is that like choosing the number of the person you want to see?
too
this
[music]
The number is Pekoro-chan.
The paper is so amazing that it has 1 twice.
Don that, don
[music]
That's the goddess U Pepeko-chan
from 1
Oh, ah, I'm not going now, okay.
[music]
Okay goddess was staring at me
It's moving so fast, it's moving like that
You're watching over me, goddess Pecola.
Chan makes a wish to the goddess
of
Goddess Pecola, what should I do?
Let me come back to life
Voice that can be exchanged with Pecola only once
I can hear you
That's right, that's what it is.
That's how it is
Kaaaaaaaa
I want to revive this Aoi Shoa exchange
I'm going to collect Somane 1 to 7 soon.
Yay!
cormorant
yes
Yes, I'm going to solo mackerel. I'm going to solo mackerel.
How can I give you the diamond I found?
Of course, where is the solo mackerel?
solo mackerel
Mackerel can stand up on his own, that's 7.
It would be nice if it was shown on the broadcast as well.
I see.
Easy to understand
I'm going to go, wait a minute, go.
Mari
[music]
Masu
Alright, let's go to the mackerel edition soon.
Okay
go
Going
Return home
[music]
That's what I want
Make a sa
What is the server address? How to make mackerel?
What is the direction?
What mackerel did you make?
What is mackerel?
mackerel
What is an additional server address?
I was so confused that it was single player.
change line
come back to life
Room survival mode That's right.
That's right, Nado is easy, right?
Easy Peaceful Hey hey no no no no
No, it's not okay, it's peaceful, isn't it?
do not have
[music]
of
Damn, that's dangerous because no instructions were given.
Let's do this. What should we do? Let's go to the flower garden.
Coming
[music]
I smoked something unbelievable
Tamedoko
I wonder if something like this could happen.
Thank you for the special water, no, once
New service, start with 1, get diamonds 7
grow again at home until they collect
Become strong again so that you can do it
That means
You're lending me that kind of trial.
That's a goddess
It's a wonderful ceremony
Neen
I went back to Sisku in Ensukusuku Swimsuit.
[music]
Okay, it's a copy of Dragon Ball.
I understand
I know that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I forgot my original intentions.
Why do you think you value life so much?
Nicoyori went to the Nether and was shaking.
I guess I already understood that.
Okay, move! I'm restless. Let's move.
That'll get you excited.
I went out with Holomen and that many people.
[music]
Grant the power of Tara Sisk
Sisk who doesn't feel any power comes and dies.
That's it.
[music]
I was intrigued from the beginning that there was a tree like this.
I’m so grateful for your help.
There are lots of sleeping sticks
I won't do that either
[music]
Okay, even if I wait this long, I'll start from scratch.
I really want to collect some trees.
[music]
I want only one person to be happy, that is.
I think that's an exaggeration. Not at all. Not at all.
Everyone looked like they were having fun. Looks like fun.
I think people will say that being excited is different.
But I think everyone felt that way.
But
No no no no
[music]
No, I'm trying too hard to make you reflect.
It's true that it's dangerous, but it's dangerous without the sheep.
bed without
but
Get the damn title back. What's the title?
Tat
hair
[music]
Oisho
Well, it's better to have lots of sticks.
Na
[music]
Make a pine tree with sticks
Okay, sure
Ah, maybe I have a bit of luck.
Ok, let's dig a little.
[music]
Teyoshi
No, there's always a neighborhood nearby, isn't it?
Okay, that's genius. Oh wait, I need food.
Wateko
have to stockpile
Janiwa is also necessary, doesn't it? It means we need rice.
Because I have to cook
Neyoshi, for now it's saku.
Toya
Okocchi
Kayoshi, why did you do it so easily?
sputum
[music]
I guess it's okay here
Can you eat mushrooms too?
Let's eat something
[music]
Eat deliciously, stop it, it's like a will
Nayoshii waiwaa desu rocks and stuff like that
There's no need to worry about rock while digging.
There's no need to dig right now.
No, there's food everywhere.
teeth
This is so helpful. Hold the soil.
Let's make some cherries in the basement
yes
Let's try it
and cultivate cherries
I have to go back to the top
It was in a good place
I'm thinking of living a life until I start digging for diamonds.
I have to survive, so I'll die here.
There are times when I say it's pointless.
You need to be prepared to survive to some extent.
Okay
I want to eat it when it's okay, but it's such a luxury
I don't want to go there, so I'm going to eat some meat in a nice place.
but
[music]
oh
Okay, I'm not that good at eating meat.
If you can manage with cherry, then that's fine.
mosquito
Okay, let's start digging from here.
[music]
I don't want to stay for a long time.
If you don't do that, the diamonds won't come out.
Even if you say long-term stay, it's like that
It's not like it's been a few weeks since it's already 1
It will be over in a week
Are you sleeping?
Well, at least I won't be gone for a long time today.
No diamonds appear
Right? Just let it all out and it will come out.
If you think it's coming, you're wrong. I want a pine tree.
As expected
[music]
It's tough when there's no pine tree
Yoshikoya-chan less than 30 minutes
That's because it's Koya-chan
Well, it's not all down to luck.
There's a buff for streamers, right?
[music]
Ha, absolutely nothing like that.
I guess it's because I'm a Pom Pom Pom streamer.
If you thought it would come out, you were wrong.
Chama might be lucky and come out.
It's safe to get a pine tree for now.
mosquito
[music]
No coal comes out at all.
I'll take it easy
[music]
Thank you for supporting us too.
Diary drawing of my return home
I wanted to draw a diary
I wanted to write a diary
Oh yeah, that's it.
He told me something very important
That's helpful, it was very helpful, I just forgot about it.
I was concentrating on talking.
That's cool
Yes pine
[music]
Even if I want it, it's okay because the respawn is close.
Write a diary
sea ​​bream
Here too, I am collecting materials to write a diary.
I thought I'd draw it here because I have to.
It's also difficult
I'm looking forward to it, but it's a death flag
Well, it's true that Harch is also pretty good at Minecraft.
I thought I was about to die, but...
I never thought I would die like this on the first day.
On the other hand, I'm used to Minecraft itself.
Because it's mine
I got so used to the club that I got a little carried away.
operation
I have a habit of flying. I want to fly.
It's scary, there's no pine tree, there's no coal
No, even though I'm used to Minecraft, it's an adventure.
is used to
[music]
no minecraft adventure [ __ ] sloppy
Nice to meet you, Nether. It was fun. It was fun.
No, I'm a shut-in
This is what happens when you build a building and stay indoors.
yeah
Let's make a nice tree tannu nice nice
I'm glad I didn't change it earlier.
Shall we do some of that soon?
[music]
enough
It was too little
[music]
It's okay, okay, okay, just for this day
I'm saved, so I'm scared
[music]
come back to life
Are you enjoying your comeback now?
[music]
Everyone, you did your best, so say no.
You can be saved just by receiving it.
It's true
Things have calmed down a bit
The sound of my wako calms me down.
I feel so relieved, Minecraft.
[music]
bed is bed
no bed
It was such a relief to have
Ha-chan didn't know either, Polpo
Thank you, give me the bed
[music]
Luna-tan also gave me equipment, but I lost it.
Sorry for messing up
[music]
Like a cat
Like this
I was grateful for the bed.
What
Okay, I want to return the favor.
If I come back to life, Hacha will return the favor.
daminna
I'm starting to feel weird
I can only see one thing
But I feel like I can do something even if I don't.
Yeah, I'm sure you'll say thank you for your hard work.
It was
I was just saying, what is this disgusting color?
What's this? It's like a rotten carrot. It's okay.
Is this it?
[music]
Hmm, yeah, it was this color.
building stone
[music]
fart
Oishoka-senpai good night
My seniors are already here.
By the time I go to sleep, I'm already alive again.
So stop talking to your inner Holomen.
If I were alive today, what would that mean?
Hacha is also teasing each other about now.
That's what happens when you come back alive
Say you didn't die
and then
Sometimes Hajimetan lends it to me.
You can take that armor you gave me home with you.
He said things like “Tana” that sounded a bit like seniors.
Comb it
Haa, I took all those mounts.
Karanai Yahacha was also originally a fan.
I kept stirring things up, but in the end,
It's a little bit...
I wanted to say something like I'm a senior.
to
[ __ ] [ __ ]
Well, when I get home I feel a bit like a mother.
I wanted to show you that I always took care of you.
Because it's stupid
[music]
Saaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Something like that
It's always like a girl's manga
We're communicating though
I want to do it again
I was able to play Minecraft with Namikochi for the first time in a while.
I wanted to play more.
[music]
No iron comes out at all.
It's okay to have memories with everyone
It's fun just looking back
It happened a while ago, that's a lie, seriously.
Ah yes, that brown thing was made of iron.
Is this iron? I don't even know what iron is.
I also forgot
[music]
Tonton that
Tontonton damn tree
I want a new tree, and I want to plant a cherry tree.
I was thinking
[music]
Well, it's like that on the ground, right?
Yes yes yes
yes
I won't say it's delicious
I won't say it, I don't feel like that
Karacha doesn't say that.
At all
Nehacha says everything in a cute voice
Don't think I'll say sweet lines.
Bababugaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[music]
Hacha is wanted
Don't just do it
You haven't been with me lately.When I feel lonely
I like to give to
That's right, I should have assembled a water group.
It's already that time of year with 2 ma's next to me
Back
[music]
Eh, where is it?
What were you trying to do just now?
Ah, I remember
This is it, yes, it's finally here.
No need
I don't need it anymore
I made a mistake, I don't need the iron crane anymore.
I don't want a different stone tsuruha anymore.
Nhacha has an iron tsuruha, so
So
[music]
Good Lulu
I'm heading home
Is everyone waiting?
I want to talk to you when I get back.
Good luck
Okay, we talked about that earlier.
Regardless
It's like I'm asking for something from myself.
Well, let's just dig here.
hand
[music]
Yoshima a little deeper
Kaoh Lapis Laz
[music]
The one I got from Erika-chan
Wow, what kind of moisturizing lapis lazu is it?
It's moisturizing, and after all, it's just fashionable.
It might be him
Yes, Minecraft is really amazing.
deep
Wow I know what you mean, this sound is like "nepyopyopyo"
Pipiponpon Pipyopyo Pompon
The sound is nice Minor 54 wow that's a relief
Wait a minute
Okay, let's go with this.
what what what now
teeth
Amada is not plus
It's still not a plus
Okay, about 20 bullets dropped.
See you again from
I'm still hungry.
Ta
It's so physical
[music]
I wonder if there's something in there, Priss?
Teru
[applause]
[music]
Don't put it in the fridge
Taa 1 ma 1 ma so it's true 1
I was digging
[music]
Okay, it's this late at night so I won't eat.
It's a good idea to have some Surume Tech ready.
or
It's kind of like a stick.
What is Sunan? What is Chupa Chupa?
What's that about that squid stick?
What a sucking ass type of guy.
I seem to like it, but hacha is not good at all
I don't like it.
Hey, I like spicy food, but it's so scary.
garbage trash trash can
Make a trash can
It's okay if you don't have to
[music]
That tree doesn't exist anymore. It's surprising. It's a tree.
I wanted to make something random, but this is about it.
[music]
to
Oishio Oishio
When I thought about it, I wouldn't have eaten that kind of food.
[music]
Hey Iwata
Too bad, I don't need this either
[music]
Leave everything behind
Welcome to the pig box, sweet salmon senpai.
Sajake
That's a cute name
It's cute though
It looks a little like skin
A little drink like a cute old man
He looks like he's been drinking, but it looks like alcohol.
And several times like Jijiji
It sounds like a joke to me
Yoshiko, let's close it now.
[music]
good
Hey, iron iron iron rods are great. Let's make lots of iron rods.
I'm glad I did. Why is there no rod? I don't have iron.
[ __ ] and 1 more
Individual idiot
[music]
Bastard over here
I'm ironing it
Why can't you just tell me you're an idiot?
Won't you tell me?
[music]
Creepy
It's creepy, it's floating, it's floating, the things I threw away are floating
Ten's disgusting
[music]
What is this disgusting?
I don't need anything
What is Nodo?
Tekoreji pira fishing
Maiaaa
Ta
[music]
Yes, that's too far
I wonder if the sound here is hollow.
[music]
What is this?
Wow, I didn't know it looked different.
I thought it was an unfamiliar color for some reason.
I was making it a long time ago
Please don't make jinteka here.
Even though it's a little far away and it's already at the bottom, there it is.
If you make it, it's already that
It's almost time
[music]
I want to move soon
Okay, I did it. I did everything right.
But since there are no trees, it's still here.
It would be better if there was a little tree.
It's a tree, it's a tree, it's a tree.
No, there are always rocks on the way.
Just make it in this hole at home.
I did
[music]
Where is the workbench?
Because the trees are running out
a little bit
That's all here.
Let's make that again from now on.
The pod that I had just thrown away came out.
It's gross but gross
Hey, why not here?
It's a pleasant sound
Nayoshi, let's do it here.
[music]
Just say it's gross again and do it again and again, don't worry.
There are pine trees, not poop.
Okay, I should make a shovel soon.
There are trees that make trees, but trees are running out.
I wish she'd grow up
I feel like I want to raise it inside, but
I feel like if I say that, I won't be able to cut the fire.
It is better to get them outside than to grow them in the garden.
I feel like I forgot what to do for a moment
I'm sure I made this
Let's make this
and make a suitable shovel
The iron may not come out.
It seems like a good idea to make a living by digging for diamonds.
I have
come back to life
Okay, I'll lay it down for now.
mosquito
Okay, it's confusing. This is annoying.
A bit okay
[music]
Log
I want it okay ah, that disgusting color again
Guy
But what is this?
Wow this is redstone
I'm going under this guy who made the Kana Red Tochi.
It's scary, so that's good
No, I don't need it, I'm not digging for diamonds.
It's not good, it's like I got something.
It looks good and the color is cool, so it's good.
It has a nice atmosphere, but I don't really need it.
I haven't been into any anime lately, but...
Korean idol audition program
I'm totally hooked
It's that girl's one.
But it's amazing, there's a girl I kind of like
Yes, it's not that cute.
It's a bit like a cool type, but that's not it.
It's being broadcast today.
Well, it's the same every week on today's broadcast, but it's a bit
I wanted to play today
Distribute famous quotes from
I'll give you a pillow and do a little voice training tomorrow.
There's also tomorrow, and after that it's over.
I'm looking forward to it until then
I'm really looking forward to it until then.
I'm thinking about watching it, but on the contrary, I'm looking forward to it.
has increased, and somehow even if I watch it once every time
I've seen it many times already
I'll watch it as many times as I want, and next time
I'm really looking forward to the week of
I don't have enough anymore. There are so many days.
Many times I felt like it wasn't enough or that I needed to come quickly.
I'm watching it, but I won't be able to watch it until a week has passed.
Well, I don't want to, so I'll wait a little longer.
I want to watch it slowly and slowly.
What you can do
In that case, I'll take it slow next week.
Thursday will come in the blink of an eye
I want to see it just like that
Good night Nefurufuru-senpai too.
Say it
Yes, it makes a difference if you have something to look forward to for a week.
It's okay
What a week of life and life.
It's been a week
It feels just right, right?
Nemochi
Through
Oh, if anything, I'm not sure about that kid.
There's a kid who sings really well, and somehow that kid is my self.
Introducing my own song
has a unique singing voice.
That's why I said it like that, but at first it seemed like that
I was thinking something like that, huh?
Something like an idol audition
At first, I wasn't that immersed in it.
It's not too much, or rather it's light at first.
I always look at it with a lighthearted attitude, though.
I'm starting to get excited about something.
Hey, yeah, it's about time
Thank you for letting me know, I forgot 3350
I don't know what's going on yet. I can do it later.
It's a bit good that it came as a minus.
minus coming
hand
Okay.
Ah, no, it's better not to bury it directly below it.
That's a good reason though
[music]
Seriously, it's here.
Oisho Sore
Wow, this is scary
Hey, I want to mark this as magma.
But hey, they come from around here after all.
He hasn't come, is this here?
[music]
Oh Water
The night is full of disgusting feelings
Because it's late
[music]
Don't just dig in a straight line and get away with it.
Is there nothing else?
So I have no choice but to go?
N
A little bit now
I feel like I should just go in a straight line.
go for sex
[music]
There's so much here
Alright, are you still magma?
go this way
circle
recommend
[music]
Okay, yeah, that's it.
Either left or right
Doesn't it make sense if it's the same height from here?
Maybe
Finally, finally
Isn't Chiraoi good?
I feel like throwing all the rocks into magma.
I want to throw it away
[music]
I want to come back to life
In today's Nether, I fell in love with Haa-chan too.
Tanohee
There are elements like that.
Taaaa okay okay what?
Oh yeah
I hate this
I really hate this
Okay
Okay, let's keep going straight
[music]
Okay, the hollow came, the hollow.
Important punishment
Okay, same as usual, same as usual.
Sometimes you just suddenly do something
Somehow
It seems like it
Wait a minute, it seems different, right?
The star is
That's right Mini, Tomomone and I couldn't talk at all.
It was only for a moment, but I never expected it to be like that.
I didn't think twice about going with a large group.
Tarasaiya is really amazing
[music]
Good taste good
Hey yes
Yes, hey, hey, it's far-fetched. That's it.
I was accepted a little though.
I was so excited
However
Delete the space from the other day
No matter what I did, I was waiting for something to be erased.
Maybe
Noaaaaaaaaaaaa nice nice nice
nice nice nice than
than
I know that
[music]
Kikikihelpme
Amajidesamatsu
I noticed it wasn't
[music]
Well, it doesn't come out at all.
Why doesn't coal come out like this?
It used to be like that
A lot of people came out.
Ah coordinate height
I forgot, and now it's a little more
48 I want coal, so I go cut the wood.
The sound of the magma bear
I came to understand
Peek
Kayoshi
physical strength
sensor desire sensor
[music]
Kaoshisho
Aishi charcoal is not small, it's that tall
But instead of that, it's magma.
Hey, it's really magma
Surprisingly, it doesn't come even though it's so sticky magma
I'm really scared, but I'm afraid it's magma.
But they don't come at all, so I brace myself.
Rutsuno
Okay, okay, that's about it. I definitely don't want to go there.
is
But I really don't want to go to this place on the right.
or left
I surpassed the distribution for the first time.
I'll see you in real time soon
I get excited
[music]
Whenever I watch a video, it feels real.
Time stamp
Which one do you hate? 454 is safer.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
This is one step lower
Yes, really, absolutely magma
Get the storm water bucket
Please be safe with me.
Wait, is it still night? It's morning. No, it's a pine tree.
Wow, this is so far away. It's morning. Good morning.
Take it, I can't grow any pine trees.
hey
Okay, I'll do my best
It's nice to just come to Maina 54.
wonderful
[music]
A bit of fate
I've died and come back many times.
[music]
Yes, it's still the same thing now.
I dug it from 54 and minor 54 etc.
By the way, there's no difference
teeth
Okay, that's amazing. I hit it with one shot.
That means that
[music]
Let's drink some water
This is it
bucket
bucket and
Trees and water from buckets of water and water are sheep
On the other hand, there are so many trees and there is water nearby.
I'm glad it's easy after all.
Is it empty or peaceful?
[music]
or peace
Turns out you don't need mushrooms.
of
Apparently they opened a space the other day.
Throw away what you don't have
It seems like it opened like this.
Deleted
seriously
Yeah, that's sad.
A little bit of food
[music]
Oisho
Okay, just a little bit
That box too
Let's make
Ahhh
[music]
yeah
The distribution to has disappeared and the tweets have also disappeared.
of
Yes, tweets sometimes disappear.
what
What?
What is this live stream? What song is this?
Frame or upcoming one or cute type of taku
Kaoshisho
check later
[music]
Toko
[applause]
[music]
I thought you were asking for space.
The vertical delivery site is completely space-saving
That's what I was thinking, isn't it?
There's nothing like space.
I'm doing it a bit like a phone call.
Well, it's different from streaming.
I thought there was no need to leave it behind.
I was shocked that nothing was left behind
There were people
But oh well
I see. Either that or Hachama erased it.
Ta
Nenanka
[music]
I was in despair because it looked so terrible.
Well, if you have something to do, leave it behind.
I might not do this anymore.
do not have
But ah, where?
There's a big hole in there, and I also put on a tie.
Toko Eden Eden Erase this too.
make it easier to understand
[music]
I'll definitely leave it there.
Something happened while I was listening to Kasakamo Ashikamo.
You said it seemed like it was deleted.
I feel like that's a bit of a shock.
Surua
Well, that's what I mean.Ah, the logs.
I wanted it but I cut it off
I did something wrong.
Yes, I wanted a box.
for storing things you don't need
Hey, it's almost time
Okay
oh someone
I can't sleep
No matter what you do, it's peaceful
Karane safe
[music]
Should be
Well, this
Kayoshi
It's so peaceful that I want to use it as fuel
nothing comes out
Yes, there is
It's a bit too dark though.
Okay, it's not much. I want to dig a little more.
Okay, okay
[music]
Oh, I'm scared, but nothing comes out at all.
Nothing comes out of , so I'll go for a while.
[music]
Do your best at school tomorrow.
While watching school, I thought, "This is how it is."
I'm going to sleep in between, so I'm going to get ready for a little sleep.
The person who said
Maybe it's better, but I'll regret it tomorrow.
from
Hey, it's so dark it's scary Matsua Matsu nothing
No, there really isn't any coal, it's a fancy place
Is it because it is a place?
[music]
Yoshison de Sode
Let's get some coal right away.
make
mosquito
[music]
Haa, why are you going up to play in the water?
I went up to get fresh water
Neyoisho
Press with
That's not enough 24 pieces
Isn't that too little? Even if I don't sleep, I get scolded.
I don't want to get angry, I don't need to sleep
too
Okay, that's hardcore Minecraft.
It seems like it's only for a week
I wonder how many days are left in this week? Summary section
Although it is written in
It's over
Karama that kind of thing
[music]
Kotoyoshi Wow, this stick is still there.
There's more. Wow! Let's make this stick.
If you're just a staff member, I'll make a box.
Wow
It hurts that I changed
too much
[ __ ]
Why can't Matsue do this?
I really don't want anything to come out.
There was a pine tree, it was like that.
It doesn't happen normally
It's so good, it's so good, this amount is so good
You can feel safe, I'll go now
[music]
Let's go
Good night
[music]
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Good luck, I brought some water.
Okay.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, this is creative mode
Not
It's Yonanchara mode.
What is it?
[music]
Okay then
Guaah, this is scary so I don't have to dig anymore.
That's right
a
Okay, easy to understand, finally survival.
This is the mode.
of
Hey, what should I do? What is this? What is this?
[music]
This is the world line without magma, which is still magma.
A world without magma
Right next to the line
Scary and disgusting
Just keep digging while it's too much, that's fine.
Well then this is fine.
nice nice nice
Thank you, okay, here we go
What's the point?
Come on
It's still worse to dig from below.
It doesn't matter, if magma comes, I'll just use water.
I have no choice but to
or
Hmm, I'm playing with stones except for the Oisho diamond.
It'll disappear, okay?
Okay, so-so, efficiently, but iron.
It'll be bad if it's gone
Yeah, that's not iron.
I can't take it.
hair
It has to be iron.
I can't get that out
Even if it takes 2 stones to reach that point, oh, oh, that's it.
Is that better than water?
A really big guy breaks it.
And indeed, why do you look like such a beginner?
It feels like
I'm too new to this
It's really a little bit
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Wow, they won't attack me.
Wow beautiful magma
[music]
is
Yes, I want to go straight to this.
How about here too?
Nico
Ai, it's coming.
teeth
Haa
Well, it looks like it might be on the right. There's magma on the right too.
It seems likely
But oh
I'll do it without
It's you
Yojipon
Ha, what do you think I ate water for?
There's no point in curing your cough with a pine tree.
Okay, maybe move a little more to the right?
I feel like it's coming from
This is coming from above
do not have
[music]
If you dig in several shapes every two blocks,
Good left and right direction 2 blocks left and right direction
Nihuu
I see
Akou
Let's do this, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
This is how it happened
Dung
Haa
It's completely out of hand
[music]
It's too scary to get in early
Get in early, get in early
I'm going home, I'm going home, I'm going home, yeah yeah
Yes, I want to do this.
It's now like a small place where you can see it. Just take a look.
[music]
It's true
Looks like a beautiful house
[music]
Na
What you can see from the cave
whether it is in
Nyuppyon
I'll search over there
Let's take a look inside.
I'm sure
It's so peaceful mode that there are no enemies.
Mon
The only thing scary is magma, but that magma
That's why he fell into the water and died.
[music]
Okay, just out of habit, I replaced the torch.
I'll do it
By the time I got back, I had a beautiful ha
12 to the left 40 to the right 12 to the right
40 on the left, something like that is already decided.
Well, that's kind of how it goes.
Isn't it better to be straight?
dig to the right
[music]
mosquito
Hmm, it's red
Hey!
[music]
Ah, wait a minute if you guess that.
Okay then
123456789 Okay 9 wait
counting
[music]
12345678910
But what if it doesn't work?
Right now
[music]
12345678910
12Yes, if this doesn't work then
embarrassing
That's right, because it's falling apart.
What if I'm wrong?
After doing it carefully and carefully,
I want to be thorough when I don't win.
Wait a minute.
It's bad, it's bad
Aiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
Okay, so 12 on the right and 41 on the left.
Yeah
[music]
Okay
and 4
6 mistakes
I might be off, so count again.
Let's try it out, it's not a problem
[music]
Right?
lie
123456789101112 haa12
Nenenenenene That's it. Counting from here is 1.
Counting from that place is 1
I think that's really important.
But yeah, this is the goal.
From here
[music]
If you look at the coordinates, there's no need to count them in detail.
Because it's boring, I forget to look at the coordinates along the way.
I'm sure you're doing this, but it's a pain.
It's happening
No matter what, I dig this up and find a diamond in my mouth.
Right philosophy
They say they have diamonds.
The coordinates are where the diamond was found.
Isn't it?
Na
I saw that drop that doesn't look like a good type.
That LINE looks like LINE shorts.
What's going on in the timeline?
It's flowing really well, isn't it?
I don't follow you or anything, but it flows a lot
I want to come, and then my blood type will be
It's kind of like the way toast is made.
I guess that's true, but most people are type A.
I mean, it looked like it was precious.
This image is pretty good.
So, B type is a bit sloppy.
That's what I want to do with that big rough sketch.
I think AB type really doesn't make any sense.
That kind of thing is a bit extreme.
It's a bit like a joke video.
Then it became like AB
The shape is too unique
What was it again? I already have a plate.
It's like flipping it upside down and it's really unique.
It was too much and my AB type was cut off after all.
I'm a little AB type, but blood type doesn't matter.
I don't think so. Don't do it like this.
Well, type A is just a picture type.
I don't think you're being polite like this.
After all, people say that type A people are precious.
I can do it, but I don't really feel like it.
I don't feel that bad, I feel bad.
I won't do it, so I'll wait a bit
It's like he's kind even in private.
So maybe Ha-chan is large.
Isn't it?
It's like a huge escape from other characters.
It would be different if you could show me how to evacuate.
I thought it might be something like
Nema type A is the most common blood type among Japanese people.
from
Yeah, I'll correct it.
Hey, I don't understand why it's a battle.
trying to
You won't stop, I'm having a bit of trouble.
But even if I get turned over now, I'm 41 right now.
41 [ __ ], I don't remember it.
It's about time to get a little straighter.
I want to do it. Personally, I'm type A after all.
Hey, I'm just thinking straight
continue
I was so happy when I finally got there in that line.
hey
Yeah no no
Ah, I was surprised, our personalities don't match well.
I thought it was a bad thing, but it's determined by your blood type.
I thought it was outrageous, but the compatibility
There are blood types, and A types are compatible with each other.
I don't know if it's good, but my whole family is type A.
I think so
It seems only
I wonder why that is?
Pain uh
Hey here
The projection type is looking down to the right.
Hey, stop that kind of prejudice.
Tokeyo, because Saha-chan is type A
It's publicly stated that type A and type B are compatible.
It looks bad so I'll be reborn.
The senior you're talking about is blood type B, right?
Then you'll get found out, just say a word.
Ahh
Oh, I said it, it's a new model.
Cute ah hey that doesn't make any sense
Tae, I'm on the right too, isn't it cute?
Alright, alright, Yoshie type is cute Gyun-e
I'm a bit of a child, I'm a child
No, he looks a little like my younger brother.
I'll treat you like a little brother or sister.
I want to
[music]
cute
ah
Oh, there's a lot on the right
Wow, this isn't a right-handed effect, that's a right-sided effect.
That's dangerous. I'm glad I didn't have to do this.
It's terrible, I'm happy like a monkey
The monkey that dug it with diamonds is also happy now.
It looked like a monkey
Ah, what I did was thanks to the pattern.
My neighborhood is 41 It can't be like that
Hey, everyone, just do the math.
Just a little straight from 1 earlier.
I didn't just go
Noku
[music]
[ __ ], how old are you? No, no, no.
That's no good, don't do that properly.
Write 5 more
It would be amazing if this came out in 5 months.2
It's not enough if you only get one piece.
Not though
There's only 3 squares left, 5 left.
About 1 more square
I wonder if it's finally like this, but it's like that
What is the combination?
na1331
No. That amazing stone ice ax durability is 131
It seems like it's about 65 if you can use one.
With this durability, even the blocks can be removed.
Being able to calculate
Wow, I don't remember at all
I don't remember at all anymore
Hey Nene Nene Nene, do you like this diamond?
I don't like this diamond.As expected, I don't like this diamond.
I'm not going to go to the diamond shop, I just realized it.
Damn it, even if I could get it
Don't die properly
That means you have to have it in
Let's put it here for now.
It's scary true
Nisou magma dive, look, it's this close
There's magma so it's scary
Why did I get lost in a place like this again?
I have to, what's so fun about it?
Alone
1 person on 1 person server and lost
Does it have to be that way?
[music]
Okay, it's not like I'm swimming.
The lava looks like it's rocking
Hey, why don't you just put it here?
Not in this safe place, let's go here.
I'm on my way to put it here.
Place Make a heart with this hachaman
Not enough at all
is not a heart at all
But are you going to fill it all up with this or not?
Seven is enough, that's enough.
Like this, alone, alone, alone, making a fool of myself
I have no choice but to go at it alone, you know?
This loneliness
difference
Hey, it's not like I'm stupid myself.
I said it alone, but when I thought about it, I realized it was wrong.
thrust from
It's a good idea
It's totally too sad
Naoisho
This bucket meant nothing
Na
[music]
absolutely
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, sure, Cell is right
But lately I've been a little tsukkomi.
I feel like someone has gone up, isn't it?
Aren't you crazy?
[music]
I'm also the type that gets pretty confused myself.
That's why I'm already looking at myself
I wonder what's going on now
I think so, I want to bend a little more
Which way should I go, right or left?
Instead of everyone deciding, I decided
It's his fault, but which one is better?
[music]
There's no way it's left or right if you lick it left and right.
Decide once.
in
Okay, left, right, left, right, uh, left, okay, something like that.
In Hunter Hunter, humans are pretty much left or right.
I don't know which one it is, it's already easy to choose, so on the contrary
I guess it's better not to go that way.
As I said, which one is it?
That's because many Japanese people are right-handed.
I wonder if I tend to choose the right one?
Hey, if you're in doubt, turn to the right, that kind of senior.
There are some too. Hey, it's not hard at all.
This is hard
[music]
Yoshie Jin also said it a lot.
Terujan Hunter Hunter
Ah, choose the opposite of the listener.
Why is it so easy?
There is such a thing as ``Darou ki-ya''.
is
Yeah, wait, it looks like they're going to set the standard for cheating.
The image is terrible
The image seems to have low standards for cheating.
I'm really not impressed with the image
I know you're not being praised very much.
It's not that I'm overlooking the cheating, it's the cheating.
It's not that the standards are low
I've already given up on you
There's nothing wrong with cheating like that.
Good
That's what I think
I'm saying
But I still like the one I like the most.
I'm thinking
Push yourself first
I would be happy if
Nedebetsu
That's not what cheating is like.
If the standards are low, then it's tougher.
[music]
The standards for cheating are low. Japanese is difficult.
The standard of cheating The standard of cheating is low.
Huh?
What are you saying?
is
Cheating
Oh float
Ha, the standards for cheating are low.
But I don't want that
After all, that's just at first glance.
That's cheating after all
acceptable to do
It doesn't sound like there is, no, it doesn't sound like that.
thing
[music]
do not have
I learned for the first time that cheating and lying have a harsh image.
Wow, this is a disgusting block. It's the first time I've seen it.
Good
Yeah what
I'm sure it's disgusting, so don't be so condescending.
Isn't that what you mean?
I guess that's what my mother thought after all.
The fact that the standards for cheating are low is quite an observation.
I'm kind of lenient about cheating, and it's not at all
I guess it's ok, that's what it means.
I thought
But
[music]
It's tough
This is the standard for determining cheating.
So in the end, I didn't ask him which one it was.
I don't understand
Which one was it in the end?
Dayoshi
I don't have enough stone to make it, so I can afford it.
Let's make a lot
Well, which one was it in the end?
is
It was sudden, but I'm curious.
Nae, which one was it?
[music]
What was that?
So which one was it after all?
[music]
What what what
It was tough
Wait a minute, this original story is true.
It's true, it's true, it's true, yes, yes, yes
Well, I have an image of you being strict about cheating.
Hey, this is my first time hearing it, but what's that?
If anything, I wonder what it would be like, for example.
The cheating on the heart of the delivery is
It's not strict, but for example, we are very close friends.
Good friends
It's just like me
I feel like I only have friends now
Even though I say that, I have other good friends.
The harshness of feeling like you might feel bad if you were there
Yes, of course that's the case.
Kotone, yes, yes, yes, probably everyday.
When I heard about such stories about Harch,
I guess it feels harsh. I see.
I don't think it's particularly harsh on hearts.
I don't know though
Yeah, if you watch other streams, you might ask if I'm cheating.
It's not like that at all.
Comment when your senior is watching another stream.
It turns out that Taraa is her senior.
That's so good
Even though it seems like it feels good, it's just like a hobby.
I started denying my hobbies a little bit.
When Chauto Saejahacha is not streaming
It's like let's do it, it's the same, it's the same
I think it's okay to keep looking at the archives.
But I'm totally happy to have a senior like that.
But I've seen too many things and it's bothersome.
Well, I don't think it's okay at all.
Not as much as I thought, I'm worried.Why are you so strict?
I guess that's what you thought
Oishoma, I don't think it's actually better to be tied up.
But I'm scared if we run into each other
The more you bind me, the more I want something in return.
I can't give it back, so why not bind me?
Naoisho
[music]
Oh, how easy it is for Harten to get bullied.
It looks like it's tough, but I'm sure it's tied up.
I feel like I'm screaming like this
Like, yes yes yes yes buy it
That's the red one.
It looks a little scary
[music]
Okay ha-chan has always been so devoted
I would like to think that it is not so.
I don't like it, but it's definitely my first time playing Minecraft.
But no, no, it seems like that.
I can't say it, it's difficult
That's why I'm writing a song
That's why I thought the opposite.
That's a good thing, but...
How much gold is this?
Maybe gold is better?
This is a golden pickaxe.
Even if I do it, it will be a waste
Yeah, gold magma came gold
Tsuruha
I don't have enough money to use it.
Then I'm afraid to spend money
magma magma dive
There it is
It's early
Well, there are still two rim dragons.
Well, it doesn't have a material desire sensor.
It's a bit dangerous
It's too relaxing
Well, let's try making some for now.
I wonder how to make it
oh
It's here, it's not here, it's here
No, it's over here.
Udame
Daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
a
Buira
I don't need money
do not have
Okay, now that I think about it, I left the stove behind.
What happened to that pine tree? Is it okay to have a pine tree?
I left the pot out so I don't need it anymore.
No, now that I think about it, it's blue. Come to think of it, iron is also in the corner.
This is easy to make
Even if I'm honest
Wait, wait a minute.
Hey, hey, hey
No, it's good
Hey, it's nice
That's nice
Even though it's a nice gesture,
Why does it work in Minecraft?
I'm not good at detailed work.
But if it's Minecraft
[music]
good
Okay, be careful not to get excited.
Dipping
A place that is clearly visible
Take a look
See it for real
Seriously, you're too nice. I'm jumping a little.
Don't fly, don't fly, don't fly, don't burst, magma!
Let's play together with Robo-chan here.
I made some popcorn
Saiiya was really fun
It was great, I'm so sleepy
It was fun, Robo-chan.
Somehow really
Even though it's a pon, it's a pon, but what?
I feel like an older sister
The sister who does this seems like a big sister.
Big sister
A big sister who plays with me in various ways
What's going on?
That's fine, for someone like me.
I don't know what to say, I'm going home right now.
return
[music]
I wonder what you would say
I just want you to give me some kind of hug.
It doesn't feel like that anymore
Even though he's just a little bit, he calls me "I"
[music]
The image inside the basket and everyone's image
Is it different again?
too
[music]
Okay dondon dodon
Yes, yes, there is a mamami.
Block mami de Mami no block
Daniel Sitt-senpai cried
welcome
It's not Heartland Dragon Ball.
It's not a ball, it's Dragon Ball scraps.
Yo
Good day
lined up like this
[music]
No, it's not 7 blocks.
When I first heard about Nohe, it was called Block.
I heard that, but it's different.
Kema, if that many people say
I guess it's different. Okay.
That was a prank, wasn't it? That comment from earlier
Maybe I didn't see it properly.
What should I do, block?
It's trial time, the rules have changed.
That's amazing. Collecting blocks is incredible.
Well then, the weight of death in the past and death in the present is different.
It's different, isn't it?
Okay, where are we going to donate this? It's impossible.
offering
Decorate something like this
[music]
mosquito
That's ridiculous. Here's a screenshot.
How to take OKSHOOK
Get it
[music]
I should just send this to the person's chat.
My computer is too heavy to save files
Recently, I increased the capacity too much due to video editing.
Karao, there's only a little bit going on today.
Some video
I haven't made it
The video is only about 2 minutes long, which is 1 minute and 30 seconds.
It hasn't increased in size at all.
There's something wrong with the capacity.
save and title
[music]
Return
Okay, I heard that, ha too, Dragon Ball.
I don't know, but there are 7 Dragon Balls.
I know what you need
That's right
Knowledge is that kind of knowledge.
Amazing Sui-chan has also achieved 7 points!
Wait, wait, wait, my body is better
Okay, yeah, yeah, let's do that.
let's
Oh wait a minute, wait a minute
Yoha-chan also looked at the photo
Tahaa-chan noticed
[music]
set
photo ah
Chama died
It's not here.
[music]
A great gathering
I have all those memories in the photos.
All on the way
I lost it, but just a little bit
Take another photo
It's not multiplayer, it's single.
I'm glad I saved it with the selected word
Play Wait a minute, I'll take a picture of my face now
I'll take it with that one.
[music]
Neyoshi
I have various things
It seems like the number of diamonds has suddenly increased.
Okay, this is it.
[music]
It's okay, come to think of it, you can wait.
Mouse seems to go back to default settings
[music]
but
Good job
Oisho
Become a cute girl
Oh, my cute voice is over here.
Yoshian, I guess you didn't take the mouse.
Okay, yeah
Good job
That
I can't get that.
I'll take it one more time
a little bit
The items are delicious as expected.
I can't save it because it's where I fell.
It's the place where I fell, so it's a bit obvious
It's tough though
Okay, that's fine, as long as I can go back, that's fine.
Tet
Tereyata
[music]
Commemorative anniversary, I'll send it. I'll send it here.
Yes.
[music]
Right, I see.
It might be difficult to revive it right away.
Well, I did it.
[music]
Late at night, just the time difference
I did it. I did it. Here's a commemorative photo.
It's so good!
That's what happens the moment you enter Tahare World.
I was revived. That's what happened.
I wonder if I can do it if I try?
[music]
I guess so. Give it a try.
Let's go and see
Let's see
ah
Wow, I'm really back.
Funny, I'm finally back. Where am I? I'm alive.
I came back alive
I'm home now
Kari yay ori
a
cage
There's no other way
Nanaa
good
Delicious, delicious, delicious, delicious, delicious.
Please enjoy it. I was in a hurry to show it on the screen.
Now that I think about it, what happened?
The mission was pretty well done.
I was able to complete the mission and it was amazing.
It must have been a pretty good trip.
long hand
Naruha
No, seriously, I fell.
I don't want to anymore, but it's good, it's long, good, good
No, there's something else going on tomorrow.
No, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I think it will probably happen again, so I'll participate again.
Oh yeah
Diary Yes, this is the end.
Planning
[music]
have
a
Oh
[music]
Was it oh?
Na
Mahaaa
Ohkikuwaibaiba
Bye
yes
Iwaii
[music]
I'm here
exinAllOf
ARMofthe
laum
Fall
Damn it, wow
beautiful
[music]
want
Ayabaimo
do not have
O
Muhan
Baba oh
themybab
Nono
wasnonono
No
Nok noi noi noi
ノ Justtothebok oh
just
a
Wow, this is so bad
I didn't notice because I was in peaceful mode.
Tayokona
survival is tough
I'm just hiding in a hut for now.
A great sound of fighting
but
Come back home
[music]
Oh that's outrageous
Ogo, it's too bad
That's bad, wantTakeThatB
Banarego
Tsuyo
Tsuyo let's go let's go
Let's go
[music]
circle
Oh
Wow
[music]
Oh no!
Let's go let's go!
Let's go Let's go
Ah oh oh
Onai
[music]
from
Nojust
Way
[music]
Way have the way
Yeah okay
Okay, let's go Lego with an arrow stuck in the face.
Yeah me
Goma
bab
Good finally finally We
liveto
Together I Liveto
Together
nice nice
a
[music]
Oo isnooneis
Leah
[music]
OnegaXNEZa
This house is broken
houseis
[music]
broken May Eat
F.L.
Ma
Waya
Wawa seesee
HOUSEhaveF
[music]
Ehu yeah yeah
Good wanttotomuch
RB
oh
Oooh
[music]
Good K
KIknow
[music]
is
FSS
[music]
S.E.
need
need yes
Wayvage
vage a
[music]
Oh I
ForSorry
[music]
Oh oh
L
Oh oh oh oh
[music]
see that
Fafa
Yeah This
I went back to where I heard people's voices in Wayka.
Baby Eo-chan, that's dangerous.
It's over here. It's over here. Yes, it's over here.
Tao
Oh, it says how to make a potion.
chan yay harchman harchmanher
Chiman ah
I came back to life
Yes, I collected 7 items. Yes, I collected 7 items.
It's amazing, but it's a diamond block.
I wish I had 7 diamonds because there weren't any.
This was amazing, it was great, it was great, it was great
When I got home, I decided to live with Kara.
Hacha's baby baby baby
Baby, baby, cotton
Baby, where is baby?
Baby, baby, see you tomorrow
from
baby play baby
I ate a lot of road grass.
You and Me
[music]
baby
baby all
Baby no kaima
baby a
[music]
Hippo has come back to life
Did you find Daya? Yes, I found it, yeah
Chichi chi maa nya
Tamayosha is back
That's great, let's do our best, don't die anymore
Yeah, let's do our best tomorrow. Yeah, let's do our best tomorrow.
Let's do our best, we'll do our best, we won't die
I want to clear the mission properly.
Hey, don't die
Yes, see you, see you, see you, see you, Osumi.
Thank you for good night.
Kaela Let's do our best tomorrow Let's do our best
I'll do my best and I'll do whatever it takes.
Kara started living with me.
Because it's a bee baby, oh baby
Baby, that's the kind of relationship
That's right, it's a relationship. It's such a flirty relationship.
do not have
She's such a baby haha
What's the babysitter? It's different.
Because it's Chama Mama, it's Chama Mama Mama
Right, no
[music]
Are you definitely going to complain? No, no, no.
Even though I came to a different place, ha
I want you to listen to Chamohacha too.
Kara's daughter is Bibu, so Hachaga aunty
It's not mommy, it's not bib.
Even Madama
From the side
Grandpa Grandpa Grandpa Nanate
It went wrong
Well then, Mama, Mama, you're not going to die tomorrow
Don't leave me alone.
No, no, no, no, no, don't sleep alone, girl
Strong though
This girl is really unrivaled, but she's a mom.
Tsuyo baby Tsuyo Tsuyo
Baby, baby, mommy, let's be strong too
I'm thinking of building a flower path all the way to my house.
of
Hanamichi is fancy, isn't it fancy?
I'm really excited about it, starting tomorrow.
Let's do our best, let's do our best, puo
Wish W Oh yeah, let's go to the farm
Ta
you ah
Gea
[music]
ah
I'll give you this, you can tear it off yourself
Thank you so much
Ahhh
[music]
Nice nice nice nice nice
Nice morning
tentay nice nice
Tinaisou
Ah pants
I want panna pan pants
ah
I put on pants
Oh
[music]
want
I got food from Let's Go Ade.
Apparently not
I want to go wild
Good luck Taya's equipment
[music]
Kayapan's splashes look like those pants.
I told you, you gave me the pants.
Okay.
[music]
Okay dondon
Don Don
Doll Doll Free Fool Ah Let's Hun Polka
polka fun nice free to freebe
Free rice nice
Wow
Miku Miku Miku
It's about time for potatoes
Go
Gogogohan
cooked rice
Hmm
I'm sick of this.
pine
[music]
Gogo it's okay
How about another senior mission?
mission nether mission the
What's the mission like?
But before I die, before I die, before I die
I was able to complete some missions.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be doing anything.
No, no, no, no, no, let's go back to the neta after this.
Because it seems like I'm going
You should just do the mission.
Not any senior
O
justisjust
right
knowdoes
Have have fun
I don't have it. I lost my sword too.
[music]
Kara that you can't get from Nemakara
I said I wanted to sing, so I said I'd lend it to you.
from
live
Aye
[music]
[applause]
Need
BtheonethatSawThe
LastOneTheRed
[music]
oneoneoneglowstone
SKI
[music]
knowknow
US okay
This is the second time
I don't know, but it's a mission.
There's no choice but to
[music]
Oh, the mission is that Delhi.
Well, maybe tomorrow we'll do that different mission.
It feels like it's going to be a different mission.
[music]
[laughter]
I want to say that he's okay, but he
2 is heavy because I don't feel heavy.
I'm worried that I won't
That's right, what should I do?
[music]
I
Yeah I knowmaybeis
Maybe Better for her
likejustthe
Diamond
DiamondDIAM
[music]
became equipment
I went to the day diamond and became equipped.
E Yeah
enAh, that's the time I'll use the diamond ring
It's also possible to go to
No, I see.
So I guess the bow is diamond equipment.
You need it, don't make a bow and go home.
Because there is FT
Yahoo Oneda Senpai
Why did you go?
Teyaba
It's okay if you do
cooked rice
Why don't you wake up that iron equipment?
I made a mistake. I came here by mistake.
Tae, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, I can't die
I can't sleep, I can't die
[music]
Die!
do not have
Let's go to sleep
Let's go to bed, handsome
Kanana and good morning, right now there is a shortage of trains.
The more I do it, the more I can't make it either way.
KaraunnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnH
complete set
Oh, don't die!
Let's go, okay, let's go.
I guess I have to make up my mind a little bit.
Okay, this is okay too, oh hey.
Picked it up
I want to
what
Sil is scary
Yo
Good luck, thank you
[laughter]
[music]
thinkBI
I have the equipment
It's a terrible return
It's okay to be fully equipped.
I don't have it anymore
Nao yoshi yoshi oa
need
need o
[music]
Oh oh oh
Baba
What's so dangerous?
Even if I go to my mom, I play a lot of Minecraft.
I don't want to have an image, but I'm dying
I'm just building while
Does it look like mustard? That's definitely better than me
Minecraft Yeah Minecraft
Yes, it's delicious
Hey, he's definitely better at Minecraft than me.
Yeah yeah yeah
Is that so? Anyway
I'll live, I'll try my best to live, give this back to you
Without it, Sahacha would have died.
Wait a minute, Sahacha is the one who died.
There are too many
Even I remember there was a hole
Because there were so many people, something happened.
I couldn't see any holes.
That's why I didn't realize there was a hole here.
It looks like Teooboo is dead.
A little bit of nehachama hops up and down
My sister probably flew too far.
There are many things you have to be really careful about.
The more difficult it gets, the more difficult it becomes, right?
The more there are, the more
I think the Nether will be tight, so yeah, two people.
If it's just 3 people, it's probably okay.
Yes, Harjim-senpai says no.
Block I'm not going to the Nether anymore so yeah
I'll give it to you
Thank you, yes, I replied to you.
Yes, my legs are okay with this.
Yes, this is my foot
of
Yes, let's build a foothold that's really hot.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, here, right here, yes, yes, here.
Yes, please make your legs
[music]
Samashi yay, to begin with, conte conte.
It seems like
It was fun for a large number of people even though it was like this.
It's like a field trip and Acha has a weapon.
Ah, a sword is a sword. I forgot the sword.
I forgot my sword.
I'll just return it for now.
Yes, I got it from Subaru-senpai.
You can get it, it's the lost one.
Why did Bar-senpai and Un-senpai die?
Jattatan
We were going together, but we were singing.
Everyone is telling me to run away for a while.
Oh, that's what you mean, oh hello
Lowa
thinkneed
back
HOUSE
makeIto
[music]
mineme
thank you
I thought it was Gogo Koyo-chan or someone else.
talaramiaino
I'm just guessing
letgonot
dieScaredBecauseI
tcewillbefineYesYes
IcandoitIcando
[music]
itnot
G
BneedtheB
O
[music]
magma
Way
Los
LosDie
OK we have been
Find Yeah
En SC
[music]
tomorrow
What OK
WetheNEGATEnoneedto
go back to the house
needmetoyouhaveByet
right
[music]
Noa Ineedand
In that box too
Place the bed where this face is.
melt
[music]
Yes
SuGthe
[music]
oh
I want to do my best
Let's go
[music]
chair
Is Oke
[music]
Uifufufu
Kio
Saoji
Mr. Miss.
Onbo Wowbo
boy
[music]
Onais
O
[music]
Yeah, everyone draws in different ways, so it's interesting.
Shishishi okay wow
[music]
Thank you very much
O
ogo you
[music]
Good
Oh need
restdrinkwateroh
have
O P
stomach
[music]
UNhave
havedes
des
UNwas
a
just
Ah oh oh
[music]
thinkHome
Yeah yeah oh
[music]
What
mahaoh
[music]
Mom, I borrowed this.
It's been a long time since I've come home. I've come home well.
I'm under pressure
I borrowed some Sugiruha-chan too so I went.
Please do your best, yes yes
Bye baba
baba ii
tellyBARMforme Yeah
YeahandInotdieorego
Nonokoyo
Esba
oh
desniceDesign
COandCOoh
[music]
off
OK
soWayThis
Way
O
MAYONEthis
[music]
oneok ninety
nice
oh
OKAre
you are
[music]
you
onneed
Needgregre
you
jumjumyoujumhold
onOKHoldOn
HoldBBabycan
jumHoldOnWStrong
STRONG
BABY
Yeah
OKOKNowYoucangodown
OkGoDown
Down
gre
Green
NIone
oneGLOW
you
Oh
nice nice nice nice
Nainai okok
[music]
yesokhavemybacka
ofnext
ONENEXT
oneone a
Oh ONE
Sugasugaoooo
[music]
O
Ogo ThisWayWay
[music]
le
Oh
nice
need
useBlock
[music]
Oh that
waythere
isWOW
[music]
Yeah May
need oh
[music]
BEST
debt
Fufu come on fuo
Kamongas
Nosu nook
FWetrytoFindAnother
Way
[music]
Go go go o
justthisoneIneed
hear
Ga
Gao
[music]
Eboa I yeah yeah ooooooo
G
[music]
comeafteryou
die
Way after you
[music]
D.I.
way
[music]
Ledo Tthe Pio Don touthe Piya
no
No jumping yeah, no jumping yeah
Yeah jam
Three yoshi yoshi
Okay.
LerereWeGoingToFind
[music]
okou
Okanmaa
[music]
way
Clumsy
Onji
clumsy
Njio IAR
B.O.
from
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh PLACE
Orchestra
Yeah Way
[music]
Hahahaha
Oh yeah
Onoji
Noji
oh
Nonono
MyLove
oh
[music]
this
oneR
RRRR
GO
[music]
WAYjum
Oh
Bye Bye
teeth
bio baba
[music]
I
see
isdiff
[music]
arebackRback
oh
Try
O
[music]
Oh oh
Okay okay
blood
O
come
a
Where is the
guys
FRONT
OW
Oh Iseetofar
OK think Now Ah OK
[music]
OkIthinkthinkMybof
that oh oh than
[music]
Oooooo
O
oh
[music]
Oda
Nonoun
[music]
Hmm
Nogau
Rasay
Let's turn it off
O
Yeah
Voiceda
DownHoldHold
[music]
JOK
OkOk
P
[music]
is
[applause]
[music]
Nanaoooooi
Oh left
[music]
Oh ok okay
Okay no
think
Owa par
Oh oh oh
Yeah
Ra
vinegar
Ah ONE
not oh oh oh yeah
May
other
ROPMRWay
WayaIneedtoStandon
the
ST
I bak oh hold on we just
MakeANEW
WAY
O
He is good
Wow sry
Haha
a
iBuddy
Lot
[music]
Bubba gas
Chagas
[music]
Wa
circle
Uno
of
Sssss it's okay it's okay
Oh no
S
[music]
Yeah
fallthink
Just Just
just
Lucky
You just lucky that I
D.I.E.
OW
O
OsonotON
MaybeISCREAMISCREAM
MaybeNEXT
[music]
Yeah yeah
Yeah lookslike
GODNoNoGODNoGOD
BBjust
no
[music]
is
Way
Oh WE
NEEDR
[music]
ofs okay okay okay
nice
circle
Obao
[music]
O
nice
Oh oh
Gigi Gia
Jump jump a
oh
of
waswas
[music]
Wa
AwasnearIwasJUMPI
[music]
thinkIwasIwantput
MILon
meI
milk a
[music]
Yu
If you have if you
have
[music]
Oh you
Oh thank you
[music]
was
wasIkillkill
[music]
have
back
no
havehave
[music]
IT
items
[music]
Assayto
SorryIFightForYou
Oh can
you can
you
backto
Nene
items
Chia
item bar
[music]
R.R.E.
you
iAI
DP
What you can you I have
thediamstoriveyou
But there's no trial
hey
How
[music]
La I have allour
items
[laughter]
[music]
youdour
bestour
Chi
Chiaaii
feel ah
bean paste
[music]
yes
ah
live ah
[music]
a
Auchi ah
OkI
hopeIhopewe
canwecanleave
We
Le
[music]
Hardore I
thinkBe
There may still be a way to survive.
will
[music]
think
Oh oh oh
Isuio
[music]
Yeah Neda
Osee
yougoodnightgood
[music]
night
WaswasF
[music]
somersRtime
OK
so
have
Chance Iwas reallyFthan
youforamYesthanyou
thank you
everyonethan
for
was
ourso
sorry
IwithNEXT
[music]
nice nice tenki tenki
Orchestra
Haa
Oh thank you very much From 11pm
There are so many different things I'm doing.
But it was fun
Suddenly
I'm glad I decided to do it today.
I don't know if Ha-chan will be able to do it tomorrow either.
So what should I do twice today?
I thought what should I do since I took action?
But I think he acted out three times.
So it's almost 4 o'clock.
Why don't I sleep? It was fun.
I'm also worried about whether I'll be able to go back to various things.
There is though
Go to sleep
Thank you for going to sleep
keyence
[music]
Kara
Thank you so much Seungsu
Well, it was fun, so...
We talked about various things and ended the broadcast for a while.
I feel like I'm running out of time, so
I think this is the end. See you soon.
Hey, I'm thinking of doing a cooking stream tomorrow.
I don't know
But I haven't seen it yet
Will it come back to life?
Kayoshi
see baba
[music]
character
Whomy
[music]
mind from
from
[music]
and
My
Heart
ofall
[music]
theAgain
My Heart
[music]
beev
meal
[music]
A.G.
Happ