[Music]
foreign
assistant
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
okay
hey yo
I'll fix the chat
hey I'm back with my pink shotgun and
this time I have a a pink vest to
protect myself as well
and my bling bling
so the muscle car I'm holding in my
hands almost no it's my it's my pink
shotgun baby
that's that's it that's the one
kick it again
I had the shotgun before but um I didn't
use my matching
vest pink vest of course vest ever of
course pink everything pink my bling
bling has to be gold though because you
know I have to show off
there's no such thing as Pink Gold
except for I guess rose gold but
um well that's not real gold
in real gold
so
how you doing today
also it's rose gold not pink gold
now I was asking about pink
yeah I miss you buzz why
I was just gone for one day and I
uploaded a clip
that wasn't really good
it it's not real gold
it's not that's not real gold
whatever
a whole day oh no
you didn't eat
you guys you little spoiled chickens
yeah
catching up with rings of power yeah you
should because uh today is Thursday so
tomorrow
is today Thursday
yeah it's first date so tomorrow I will
be watching the rings of power finale
together whether you want it or not I
mean you could opt out but it's not
really an option I mean let's be real
you have to you have to
yeah tomorrow last last uh week they
said that the next episode is the finale
so it was like you know what let's watch
it together
if you've been um watching then you may
have noticed it's been getting better I
think it's been getting better like
um the last last episode
the one before the most recent episode
was pretty good I heard the critics
liked it
and said it's finally you know getting
started
but it's getting started when it's like
kind of like ending though which is
which is weird
um
I'm quite liking it so far doing best
but of course yes yeah no one can say
anything about dorin during during
[Music]
yeah uh one for has the dragons Maybe
I I just the thing is like bringing
stuff to power is way more
comfortable for me to watch uh with you
guys because I know there will most
likely be no sensitive
um scenes while perhaps of the Dragons
you never [\h__\h] know what's gonna be
shown
and how deep they're diving into the
incest
um this time
it's a bit uncomfortable to watch
with someone else uh uh
yeah but I don't know that last the last
episode of the season I would hope that
it's more about battle and fighting than
you know intercourse
we can just close our eyes well I don't
know even if you tell me you're doing
that I don't believe you
the bloodline must prevent you
yeah very important very important
indeed but then if it's so important
then why the [\h__\h] are they still kind of
making a secret out of it
be proud of it just rock it when if
you're doing it then do it properly just
don't don't try to hide it as if it's a
wrong thing if it's the wrong thing then
don't do it if you think it's right to
do it and then I guess
I'll shut up I don't like goodness
it's generally a good advice I guess but
in this context maybe not but it is it
is a fantasy um show Okay so
but yeah without any context just in
general saying that you should be doing
uh if you think something's wrong then
don't do it in the first place if you
think it's right then do it I mean
that's not a bad
you know thing to go live by
generally
yeah Own It own it
it's not a not generally not a benefit
oh man
uh yeah go your own way okay
[Music]
I need to do
I need to sing some Idol Master songs in
my karaoke streams the thing is I don't
have like instrumentals that I can use
it's as if a tangenting as if I'm like
playing a game right now but no I I I I
I you would think I'm playing the game
right now and just forgot to show you
guys the screen but indeed indeed I have
yet to show it to you
so let's bring it up
the shotgun looks fake what the [\h__\h] you
fake this is as real as it gets bro
what was I saying I forgot what I was
saying well yeah let's let's play the
game
again I forgot to put in new music in
the radio again oh man whatever
whatever
um
[Music]
photo realistic yeah
for Speed though
um I got everything ready got my bling
bling ready got my PS5 control already
got my tea ready I have snacks in the
fridge in case I need some sneaky
snackity oh
[Music]
there may or may not be some honey on my
PS5 controller
game double
[Music]
five hour stream I mean you know you
know what it might be a five hour stream
now this I'm not planning this to be the
finale if I did like an eight hour
stream I might I would have maybe been
able to do that but
what do you mean
well you're pretty fat too oh yeah I'm
sorry I stepped on the cat nobody
I forgot oh why am I on the controller
baby
[Music]
no
no holy [\h__\h] calm down
you know this is exactly the place where
we chased the human before
now we're chasing a cat
no no no we're going
holy [\h__\h] it's just gonna run as long as
I'm following it isn't it oh
I will not shoot the cat
maybe okay go catch some some fish I
won't I don't want history to repeat
with the cat
no no no
wiggling
a fire by the ocean is that allowed I
think that's illegal but what do I know
what's up guys
what are you doing
me
oh they want to fight they want to fight
interesting why
all right it's just starting good okay
um how do how do I
know
yeah yeah you're not in the mood of
you're not in the moon anymore are you
well Alice is trying to get warm at your
fire
hello muscle car
oh yeah I'm not sure if that's a muscle
car but we have to escape because um
yeah
apparently I'm the bad guy
I don't understand
the sky I was they're so mean like I
just want to live in peace and harmony
you know
I'm gonna freeze to death otherwise
[\h__\h] ruthless
why are they so ruthless I'll say I'm
losing them nice oh there's a police car
there
oh
[Music]
actually pretty easy I thought they were
gonna oh there you go that was so easy
what the [\h__\h] I killed three people and
I got away so easily hey
it was self-defense yeah because I was
gonna die otherwise audio too well are
you sure about that now
I turned it all the way up
[Music]
that's a bit more high but now I'm maybe
a bit too loud but whatever
so
[Music]
where do we start one thing I guess I
should do either today or tomorrow is
do this one thing I've never done before
go in this like kind of Pimp My Ride
kind of place and get myself a car and
then and and customize it because I've I
haven't done that until now
yeah yeah oh oh I can customize my like
the car that officially belongs to my
character
not an adult
okay we'll do that uh maybe maybe run
away
um but I don't know where to go
huh I've been looking into chip Peterson
thing I might have something I don't
know but where where is that I'm sure
it's like a sign of a car maybe this
thing or that thing there's two sons of
cars
um car wash
um
the spray can't spray can ah that one is
there more than one yeah
oh I'll go to this one
let's do it we'll do it with Michael I
guess
do I have to bring my own real car or
will it like automatically be there
I have to bring my car okay and we have
to go home first I think my home was
also Somewhere Out There
all right I'll probably recognize the
area but now I've been around in Los
Santos
so much that I feel like oh muscle car
noise no the back is pretty long but ah
no the front is longer
but wow it has no no top is that really
a muscle car
what's that
it's a little Rider
oh [\h__\h]
close though I guess it wasn't long
enough either it wasn't really
okay the times where I'm unsure about it
it's probably not a muscle car that is
not a muscle car either
so when it's only really a muscle car
when I'm really sure about it when it's
really obvious I guess maybe maybe
so tonight
oh my God so so educated about cars now
well
whoa
excuse me
so
playing GTA today hopefully getting
pretty far and progress so the next time
we'll also maybe have like I'm thinking
three to four hours today and then three
to four hours next time I have a feeling
that will be
wow
they're gonna pay for that I'm gonna
hear from my lawyer
uh I feel like that will be a realistic
maybe roughly
yeah a question
question I know I don't care about this
car but uh
where's my home again
is it this
this thing
that's not my home
what is this thing where the yoga is
she's so stupid
see I was close at least I know it's
this neighborhood
[Music]
whoa whoa
for nothing
oh
what do you mean you can't feel your
legs nah
nah they're nothing special
what is it can I also buy myself and oh
cute oh no no not cute I thought it was
shorter I thought it was shorter than
that
um I can also buy myself a car in this
spray can place or
is that do you buy it somewhere else
I'm not girl I'm so sorry
oh
bye fruitful oh okay
and where will they bring it though
um How do I
don't use the phone again here
is it on the internet
travel transport
legendary Motorsport Maybe
we can buy aircraft helicopters planes
uh-huh I think this this one is good oh
yeah oh oh
wait how much money do I have I don't
remember
oh that's a muscle car
I think oh oh
oh oh wait why is this one so cheap I
love this one
really
why that one has Style
is that the one I stole before no
oh yeah the mouse is middle finger what
the [\h__\h] I'm flipping you guys off
get the garage first
where do I get a garage by the way I'm
drinking like one of those winter
Christmas Market teas again
yeah the one below is sick too oh my God
they're all so sick ah the one the true
faith that type that one looks like the
one that we once had to steal uh for the
story
no it's oh man they look nice
are they really this cheap in real life
these cars I'm surprised like the the
differences in prizes make no sense to
me
Mirage in a map okay
now
now oh man
I mean this this baby seems realistic 10
million or maybe not maybe that's
actually too expensive what the [\h__\h] do
I know I don't know nothing
um okay so let's see bye
sorry guys buy a garage
why cannot my home be a garage
so ah for example like this one I can
probably buy can I buy it on the map or
do I have to like go there I guess maybe
I maybe that looks like some some garage
that I can buy am I correct
yeah okay I'm gonna have to go okay okay
it's a little bit late in the game for
me to buy a garage
but when you later than never
oh
me for faster
honestly you can maybe still get me with
the controller prompt but not with f on
the keyboard oh hello friendly Mike it's
Franklin man I'm following the architect
all right I'm busy right now get up bye
[Music]
it's [\h__\h] excuse me
excuse me hello I I did not agree to
anything right now
huh
what
now what's the name is
can I switch
oh [\h__\h]
oh I can't what the actual [\h__\h] all
right I guess we're um forced to
I will get the garage later and we'll
get the car later
what the hell I did not start a mission
I mean even even if I did like yeah
just I don't [\h__\h] know what I thought
it was just in your little phone call
with your dad
oh this one's a good good good yum yum
yum this one tastes like
um
non-alcoholic punch
what is that
oh trash okay okay wait who's I'm out of
the blue what are we doing who's the
architect also oh
tell him so I can't just like straight
up walk up to him can I hey stupid you
can't be on here without a hat I thank
you
that's so sweet wait I just they just
give out these hats to anyone not
questioning whether or not I belong here
yeah but instead it just gives me a hat
because
okay we oh wait that's it nothing is it
and we just quietly follow him
he doesn't seem to think he would be
followed so he also doesn't seem to look
around and [\h__\h] noise those idiots drill
the new caissons on the west side you're
kidding me the Bedrock ends there we
need caissons on the east side ah no
drama it's a government contract we'll
be paid until complete I ain't taking a
fall for this screw up it's a government
contract no one's taking a fall
government
oh can we is that Elva there oh wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
we're gonna stop those in
first off those you have to look at the
bottom
you're down there
oh oh look it's the great artist why is
he not looking around
another elevator just arrived right
after him and he doesn't give a [\h__\h]
remember
[Music]
nice music though
hello am I like invisible sorry am I
wearing an invisibility cloak
you kind of told me no no
no no no no
[Music]
I'm not even trying to be stealth get
the actor to give up the brick okay
[Music]
um
hey stop man running for me is a bad
idea uh-huh thank you give that to me
good job good job old man bye bye
sayonara
don't tell anyone I was here
[Music]
wait what can't why can't
there you go should I kill them we
already have to start all right then
Escape fast
faster do I have my briefcase I'll save
my hand but
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] they're already there
[Music]
but I'm already wait I can just hide in
here now
oh wait they're all here oh [\h__\h] they're
all here but
I feel like I feel like I can hide it
here
find me here
like this the stars are already like
being grayed out so I feel like
this one
did you say
the visual
yeah yeah this is uh this construction
site is easy to hide yourself in easy
easy easy
peasy lemon squeezing cocoa
how could I don't know easy
a wonderful so I do think we got the
breakfast because it wasn't on the floor
or anything it's just like I don't know
put it in his shirt or so
oh I should yeah yes you know it's
telling me what to do next and put away
the gun text the car
is this my car
go to garment Factory oh wait this was
so easy oopsie
okay
I feel like
I feel like we could just continue
playing these songs at this point
because I did get like some
um claims with no no further
consequences
in the last GTA stream
it recognized like three two or three
songs that I've never
heard of before
then the area we probably won't even be
fine
but let's try to
stay away from that
this is not a muscle car no
I would have told you if it was
I mean hi hi hi
oh
I hear again oh is he always here
hello
where's the yellow spot word
[Music]
on it do I just walk in I guess they
don't need me to park anywhere specific
okay going in
yeah
and we've been making some clothes for
me where's my trip
hello
oh they're in there and there you go
here's the golden spot it's cracking hey
you got them of course I do homie yeah
Michael why you playing with your phone
so
like that
yeah I don't [\h__\h] know probably not
all right Lester what do you got I don't
quite know yet give me a minute I'm not
probably playing Frogger
oh
Nanny oh
maybe I am he's got like a thunder in
his brain
we have two options the new security
software goes into containment mode in
case of emergency you know uh
earthquakes mudslides acts of God so we
could plant some fire bombs they go bang
the emergency call goes out we hijack it
show up as firemen grab the containment
drive or no it sounds good hack the
system on site we'll go in my uh by air
I hope we don't run into too much
physical resistance thank you I like the
first one I think I don't like to fly
the bombing off is ran by divisional
corrupt government psychos or
his complex security system using our
worthless ass ninjas yeah eeny meeny
miny mo Eeny Meeny money mocking favor
the fire bomb containment Drive option
you'll go in with that janitor's ID you
picked up it'll be at night when most of
the workers are off yeah
the bombs where we need them seriously
I got a mop yeah yeah you really do
they'll clock you on the cameras if
you're play acting you also need a fire
truck to show up in when the bombs go
off and the getaway car stashed in a
quiet place near the bureau so you could
torch the truck and then get out the car
doesn't have to be anything special
there shouldn't be any heat but what
about the other way with the uh ninja
skills now you choose that route you
won't be using the janitor's gear but we
had to cover all the bases that your FIB
pay masters will have to provide you
with a chopper and a pilot that you fly
way up above the building parachute in
and gain access through the roof here
now you'll need to be armed to the teeth
mind you just in case the [\h__\h] goes down
mopping or parachuting
Mommy you're making this Choice really
difficult
he's giving us the leftover money from
the Toledo job to pull this Mission and
the crew will be paid out of that we
keep the change so what's it gonna be
uh fire crew how do I select it select
number ah there you go
okay well you'll need a couple of gunmen
everything goes to plan they won't fire
a single bullet but you will be running
into a burning high-rise with them so
consider that okay
which means the gunman doesn't have to
be good right
uh
14 insane
um
got the cheapest okay this one is the
cheapest and honestly
these are all three of these they don't
there's not much difference in like
skills and all that
so we'll go with him
Daryl huh you're doing great things to
be honest but you just might be able to
do this with him and don't go cheap on
it
[Music]
oh wait another gun man
I guess we could choose one good one and
one bad one
Chef who's chef
good chef
none of them has named Chef what are you
talking about
why is everyone saying chef
Chef ain't here
um
too cheap
go cheap okay uh okay um let's see
accuracy it's barely a difference
shoot right okay well this one's a bit
better maybe ah Norm came across as a
bit of an idiot
okay okay that all look good to you yeah
you are robbing the FIB here
looks like a plan perfect plan I'm
standing problems here let's go and we
have a winner I'll make you arrangements
and call you when we're ready all right
[\h__\h] hit
you know um I'm still looking into that
Union Depository gig this is a typical
item meeting
I don't know if we can do it without you
know who
well as long as he can oh you're not us
we mean you mean Trevor
I don't think they'll get along well I
feel like they're gonna manipulate each
other
um
Michael can we
your father wouldn't happen anymore did
you me too me too
[Laughter]
maybe maybe
since we're
since when can we still like do our own
thing right now
yeah can we buy the garage now
[Music]
jump scare yay and yeah we're gonna go
to that place
all right all right
there you go
[Music]
look at that
thingies on my tires what's up with that
when did I do that
[Music]
just like in my thumbnails
cash money
cannot yeah yeah I know it's owned by me
I'm doing something else dude
where did I put those on
[Music]
we're making an emergency call or find
one another station whatever works aha
okay oh what is that
[Music]
I'm thinking I'm doing something else
I'm doing something else
still look fresh they're stressing me
out
just chill for a second guys
Hong Kong eyes on the road I'm trying
I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying I'm
trying
boom boom why are we going
did I leave too early I definitely left
too early
beautiful beautiful no bonking against
anything
[Music]
here we go
no no no
hey hey hey oh wait this place looks
familiar to me for some reason but yeah
okay
so Halloween bye
how do we buy
yeah
this is the reason why we've been
missing you you're fun
then why do I never get invited to
birthday parties and weddings if I'm
just fun
kidding I
guess I hmm I just don't really
[Music]
I I think I got invited to a birthday
party somewhat
sometime this year but I didn't want to
go because
I know I thought too many people you
and they're gonna drink alcohol and [\h__\h]
and I don't care no thank you another
thing I see I'm not fun I'm not fun at
all
30 000.
oh oh but we just seem to have a lot of
space in here
special Lakers can also be collected
here yeah
yeah garage
pass
oh now we're just down below 1 million
we've had one million before oh no we're
gonna get back up to one million
okay okay okay so we bought that now we
wanna go to the spray can
[Music]
no first first you buy the car on the
phone
yeah legendary Motorsports
[\h__\h] you
oh
I can steal them and just put them in
the
oh
put them in the garage and then
but but it's the same Principle as
before right if I
if I use them and then leave them
somewhere they're not gonna respawn at
my garage
what about if I buy them properly will
they always respawn in my garage after I
leave them somewhere on the street
[Music]
like my own Michael Carr
don't
yes
but insurance
they always end up at the police station
if they vanish the police say something
oh so I could bring them I could take
them back right
uh-huh
see the cars need to take it to his
break and then purchase insurance to own
it
no insurance that story insurance is
multiply everything hey yo well they
won't respawn oh hell
okay well let's just hope that
some of you guys are right and oopsie
um
I have a million approximately why is
this one so cheap well since we're kind
of testing it out and I really do like
this one
why don't we go for this one and
actually it is already orange you know
but when you're gonna try to color it
maybe more orange or golden or so
um
[Music]
how do I buy
I can't click order
I know okay wait which one is the orange
none of this looks Orange
I'll go with black and then we'll we'll
try to paint it
ah okay is it gonna be
huh let me out oh there we go is it
gonna be in there oh
my carrying my gun
better hide
them
[Music]
color blind what no that was not orange
that was like uh that was way too yellow
and bright oh cute
look but it's so tiny hi it's a
two-seater what the [\h__\h] it didn't look
like a Tuesday night to me in the
preview now I understand
[Music]
radio
scammed that's fine
they're cute
it's so cute oh look at it
wait I legit want this car in real life
but only a two-seater
inconvenient in real life
I don't think I would watch so fast holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
I never thought
I I think I would never buy a two-seater
in real life
they look cool and all but then you're
gonna regret it so hard when you
actually need a four Suiter
yeah yeah for 90 000 it looks insanely
fancy and classy that's what I'm saying
yo
skin
[Music]
uh which one this one
it's always annoying when we need more
space yeah that's right
and to be like that paper
Pirates of uh limp biscuits
Limp Bizkit was that someone else am I
mixing up things
hey y'all
for X exhibit now
that sounds kind of a similarious
exhibit yeah
exhibit that was it
can we like put like a pool in the back
and so on maybe like I've seen it before
I watched that on MTV quite a few times
it was really [\h__\h] insane what they
did with the cars
um
stream title that's from Fergie
bit my ride was fun okay so I don't know
what the [\h__\h] all of this is can we add
like two more seats respray
how how
um primary oops oh
wow
Pearl
I have a I need a metallic or crew
ah for Pearl is that like well when it
looks like a pearl
the Chrome looks [\h__\h] insane
not really
I wanted to be golden not silver
it's like rainbow-ish like shiny oh wait
what does it say metallic or cruel
where's crew I only see okay let's do
metallic
oh
I wanted to be pearl oh oh that is so
um
oh I see I see it Gatsby driving in this
oh
bye double click okay and then
oh wait what
that's that's not the no
no I'm doing
[Music]
let's not use the mouse
but it's not on top of the white I
thought it would be on top of the white
Parts
ooh can I turn it can I turn the car no
go back no refund what the [\h__\h]
I want to turn it can I turn
move camera
there we go aha
it is adding on on top of all of it
though isn't it
wait let's let's first before we do that
called secondary color now here does it
also have to be it doesn't seem so
oh
cook
hey oh
the brown looks
so
elegant though
[\h__\h] pink no I mean that's [\h__\h] cute
but I'm gonna make a sick ride it's so
classy yeah no the dark the dark
actually looked really sick I feel like
it could even look nice the other way
around
with um the the big part being Brown and
then the top being white
orange no you know now I really don't
wanna
mess it up I wanted to actually look
good chocolate brown the wine Brown
looks better I think the wine red
oh that's actually a nice orange Sienna
Brown
that is a pretty Orange
that's a pretty color
but I'm not using it
and cream colors
oh that's cool too
it's a nice contrast why is this so
glowy
okay
um
my instinct is telling me
this red too
classic too but I'm going I'm going
surprisingly for this
this one
feels
like it's ringing some bells in in me
okay
and then
we go back to primary call and check out
these pearls again
and see how it looks
oh
the Santa friend the pretty orange that
we had look it gives it like a nice
slightly orangish
um color in in the light in the shine
actually oh
interesting interesting
oh that makes it golden oh the yellow
ones that makes gold oh [\h__\h]
oh
nah I wanted it to be darker so it has
like a elegant Vibe going
it looks cool though
wow the brown of the salmon pink looks
beautiful I would want it on a different
car
I love that I love that classic
yeah yeah I I want to remember this
color combination
my brain is expanding
oh oh oh
oh I'm cutting into cars and painting
cars here this is quite something
oh my oh which one did I say I wanted to
go to maybe the the Sienna brown right
okay this is still dark enough in my
opinion but it gives it the little bit
of an extra oomph
oh
yeah trust me bro I'm the new host of
Pimp My Ride
with eggs Diana xiara
nice
okay what else can I change
great license plate I don't see his
license plate anyway on that one I don't
care about plastic but oh what about
lights
I like them though they're cute
headlights
huh uh this was this one just changes
the color
these ones making it a little bit blue
yeah
don't really care horn
[Music]
do you like jazz
foreign
[Music]
making funny music
what was that again
[Music]
yum yum
I love them
taking this one
[Music]
um
wait does cut up fun have that let me
actually look at them
I mean that song is probably so old that
you know they'll copyright on it right
probably
how old is that song
uh wait what's that what's that what's
the German title
I'm gonna look it up
all the anti-finder
it's nothing kind of fun how
disappointing
[Laughter]
okay but I'm sure I can find a
um an instrumental somewhere
yeah
maybe even on audio stuff because audio
stuff has some classic music like remade
okay okay yeah specific performance yeah
yeah yeah okay oh Hood
what the
who would want that disgusting
engine
I don't know what these are I don't know
the eye makes it fast or whatever
probably I don't know breaks
I see no difference I only want things
that change the outside what about the
the wheels tires
there we go
uh wheel type
and myself myself but I guess what's
what's the fitting type
high-end probably
oh I went hmm
no they don't look
so fitting muscle
oh
that's kind of cool
oh well you said
um
low ride it will fit really
oh you're not wrong sir I like this one
and
yeah I'm feeling oh
I wanted this card to be taken seriously
but
the drip on the dollar sign is pretty
strong he has them already on his other
car though
I feel like
oh it's like such a flex like why why
would you
how much how how highly do you think of
yourself if this is what you put on your
car that actually is disgusting and if I
see someone in real life of with wheels
like that I say
I do not want to get to know you
ever
but in the game it's funny
[Music]
okay you know what I'll go with these
These are kind of a golden I like them
can I change the color of them too
though
because then it wouldn't matter I could
take any of them
I like this
kind of yeah okay
oh yeah we'll color
can we have gold you you you you
know there's no like straight straight
out golden color but I guess
wow
[Music]
they felt Diva looks fine
yeah whatever I don't know
although yeah whatever
tires
Tire design
a yo what
hey yo
our day
is that like LED lights or is it just a
really bright white color
kind of gives it
a really clean sharp look
White Walls what's that
I can imagine that getting dirty so
quickly so easily but all right we're
taking it it's kind of sick
Tire enhancements bullet oh this time
baby I'll be
bullet proof
smoke
what is it smoking right now I don't
want smoke I don't smoke no no
turbo transmission Windows Windows okay
one more thing let's look at the windows
ah ah yes
I think
I think we want that we want some
privacy
yeah
okay uh what else should I look at I
don't really care about the performance
of the car to be honest
but maybe we could improve the brakes at
least
I don't see anything changing though in
the breaking what these actually improve
it
I don't see
is it changing or suspension yeah they
will
very slightly oh wait it was so slightly
I didn't even see it oh that's way too
expensive for such a small change
foreign
has a big difference for like about the
same price but I don't really I don't
know if I really need it Bodywork
oh
yeah
no what the [\h__\h] this is kind of cute
too but
I prefer the original
okay okay I think we're done
with this by the way
oh
you can make it low
I'm happy how do I am I done do I just
Escape
are you sure yeah is it safe now
oh I'm more
what does that do
I'm just uh how easily it gets destroyed
by shots and by other cars crashes and
[\h__\h]
whoa oh okay then I'll get the best
thing
okay I'll get a nice nice okay now I'm
going home
[Applause]
[Music]
oh pretty yeah
oh look at the shininess I want to see a
before after oh
look at my baby
all right
it's it's purring like my kitty cats oh
oh oh I'm so happy with this holy [\h__\h]
don't you dare touch my car
don't you dare all right we're bringing
this we'll bring this to my garage
need to store it safely
[Music]
we're gonna get stored safely and then
probably never use it again because I'm
like too worried about my car
but I'm quite happy with this
quite satisfied looks snacks right would
you would you want a car like this guys
I would actually I know I said I don't
want to see her but
oh for 90 000
hell yeah hell [\h__\h] yeah I'm
ironically yeah
can someone look up for me how much
muscle car
how much this costs in real life
get away it's impractical here
Yeah well yeah
we're gonna get a GT
you never get to use the ones you
customize yeah I can see that
cute thank you how do I honk
nope
[Music]
wait
oh my God this is all I need I don't
need an instrumental I have the
instrumental in this game
got it
ah
[Music]
IM lives
foreign
[Music]
yo if it's this old
can I sample it in a song
there's no copper Island I could just
use the the melody right
and Sample it in a song
I never did that before but recently you
know I've been like
seeing artists
Kpop artists sampling famous uh sounds
wouldn't it be so fitting and beautiful
I should sample some Mozart too after
all Mozart was my bestie back in the day
open
come on
[Music]
uh can I can I go outside again please
where's the exit
thank you
no next thing I want to make a classic
music song I just want to sample it into
like a pop song or whatever a jazz song
I don't care EDM song
entrance
can you imagine okay we're gonna
go back to Serious Business now
this business guys what were we supposed
to do something like uh get a getaway
car get a getaway car okay then
I'll just um take the next car that
comes at me
my car
then
I'm Gonna Get Away car although you are
a muscle car no no no that is a big
muscle car but this this looks like a
better getaway car to me
[Music]
you are might get away car so get away
please go get out of my getaway car
oh
wow the vehicle is
you see this on the top left this
vehicle is owned by Michael and cannot
be used as again well yeah of course
it's it's owned by me the moment I step
into it [\h__\h] what
what glitch
[Music]
there we go can we use this again hide
it in the discrete location select the
market away location option when phoning
friend ah okay we're doing this again
it's at this great location what's the
discrete location
excuse me
oh he ain't talking to me
well you better not be talking to me
[\h__\h] bastard
oh yo
what's that look at the top of his car
he has like a snuggle it's kind of open
but it has a strip connecting it what is
that
that's enough before
let's find a good location
it would be good if it wasn't too far
away from where we need to get it away
from but or maybe maybe it should but
then you have to think about the fact
that we're escaping someone probably so
we don't want to escape for too long
ah no it has to be near the FIB building
it's also there's nothing that tells me
that though where even those FIB
building
I don't know where it is
I don't care I don't know
um
it's already close across the bridge ah
from where I am
what bridge
I'm pretty close okay then let's just
try to find something uh
hmm here but it has to be kind of hidden
I guess
what about here what about here
I'm going to the medical center
probably
not the best idea what do you think here
at least a little bit covered up
[Music]
I already hit him
um but we can get healed it's a hospital
okay uh how about here
probably also not good according to you
guys
good
that was good really yeah
[\h__\h] you what about here oh oh this is
this is good this is this is good
Maybe
what do you think
okay I think that's good yes easy to get
into
and and quickly away from a big Main
Street
they won't know where the [\h__\h] I went
uh who was I supposed to call
Lester or
is that supposed to call us
a Franklin
Frank
okay
hang out no what why would I hang out
huh
there's not a friend it is luster
hey it's Lester I don't listen to my
messages but I probably listen to yours
do with that as you will not that I can
on your message thingy
oh
I'll have to get out first
you know I want to hang out
it will call the magic light oh yeah
it's not good enough for them
find a bit more than like this is just
not good enough for you then tell me
what you want from me
if it's discreet a notification will pop
up
okay I guess it's not good enough
what about here this feels discreet but
it looks like a hotel or something
um
excuse me
what about here
under a bridge oh it has to be like that
that secret
okay wait I'll try to find something
and that looks like a bridge
you have to stop the car and then okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
wait that's not a bridge it was going up
so I thought it was a bridge
[Music]
sorry Mustang
what about can I get in there
um
why is it so difficult last time it
wasn't so difficult at all
where should I go
big park there but I don't know if that
counts
what about here but that's kind of far
away
oh try an element maybe our definitions
of an Alleyway are different
Alleyway what's an alleyway
just an alley like a side street no
this place looks very expensive
so is this an alleyway
over here
yes
this one apparently is good enough I
thought so once I'm on the grass I feel
like it would be
would be good uh 140 fracking or
Leicester
[Music]
there it is
this is it
oh oh hey less I hope those rice people
are not gonna be mad at me for the
location doing this Rockford Hills good
work call me when the rest of the prep's
taken care of okay next up we need a
fire extinguishing
and people car
s
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
there you go
um
what I'm just trying to be as clear as
possible I will um need your car sir
thank you oh [\h__\h]
cute music
[Music]
just like you do I'm always coming back
to you
[Music]
if he drives so [\h__\h] recklessly
fire truck
yeah
was that a [\h__\h] miracle I didn't
think I would just find it randomly on
the street
let's go get it
is it gonna stop anywhere at some point
because is it on a mission because it's
going dude
um
there's something special about you and
I see you I know it's true
resist you
[\h__\h] you I'm basically I'm
I'm like emergency people oh
come on come on come on come on no no no
[Music]
it was worse
oh
[Music]
wait a minute is that the car before it
was stopping stop it
was stopping
thank you for the Boost I guess
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] coming no problem I can't
solve it I'm just all fall in love know
that this worked then I'll crash you can
save me I'm in too deep and I don't know
where let's go
cruises to your eyes are like a
[\h__\h] I lost it
I thought it was like somewhere there
oh I'm losing them apparently oh but
there's all the cops there
did they see me
oh yeah they saw me
[Laughter]
wait okay let me lose some [\h__\h] cops
first
foreign
[Music]
yeah I'm losing them
day
no I may have bumped into them but they
like bumped into [\h__\h] too I was like
going to help them I was just looking
you know
oh they're still following me
in reality
I think if this was real then I would be
forgiven
accidents happened it was legit an
accident I wasn't trying to hurt anyone
that's the game we play
locations okay we're gonna get out here
can I call
the fire department
and bring them here
you don't follow up oh
I'll say I wasn't really following them
because
[Music]
because all the other people in the
middle of a business Street you know
just minding my own business it was a
coincidence you know and they showed up
there it was a collision oh [\h__\h]
could sell to a judge I I will I will I
will
ah
oh my God
yeah bye
let's just yeah call
emergency emergency people people
yeah it's totally not suspicious thank
you I didn't even say it but thank you
nothing suspicious about me needing a
fire department right now
I wonder how this is gonna go should I
am I gonna shoot them what's gonna
happen are they gonna come out of their
vehicle
I got a membership hooraya
how is this gonna
be
can I buy some apple
hello
apples peaches yummy yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum
where is it
maybe I'm once again
two
two I don't know another location where
they don't want to go to like the
[\h__\h] taxi last time
does it take so long ah I'm here
okay okay should I shoot them or no
I don't hear the Wii anymore
I do hear it
hello okay thinking time
no need to shoot them
okay hello please come out so I can show
you the fire
oh hello hello where are you going wait
um it's [\h__\h] excuse me why why are
they leaving me
I didn't even bother to look at my fire
look at me
on fire I'm a [\h__\h] Phoenix
to be that fast 9-1-1 what emergency
service do you require
thank you the fire department are on
route to your location how do you make a
fire
I it would be cool if I could get their
attention by actually making a fire if I
if I shoot the tree
will it be on fire
I feel like I've had this before in in
um GTA something was on fire after I
shot it so blow up a car I feel like
I'll get some stars for that no
hmm
no fire
I need I need gasoline then
all right let's just let's just um I'm
assuming they're gonna come from the
same sign
we'll just shoot their Tire I guess and
get in hopefully
without too much trouble
here's a grenade
foreign
just a random guy standing in the middle
of the street with a assault rifle and a
grenade don't don't mind me all is good
that was a short fire I need a
like a rail fire
[\h__\h] I found that would make it in time
I'm gonna waste my
oh they're coming hmm
don't you
get ready now if they come from the
other side I'm gonna be real embarrassed
[Music]
foreign
I'm already losing the star how nice
why am I already losing the star here
I'm just gonna hide in the bush
the road okay
um
stop stop
stop
gotta go somewhere else baby girl
is it okay if I just go a couple meters
towards this area and then all right
one car oh
there's a little car I can take right
here
shush now
I'm gonna make a big commotion here
though
let me first
ah
first call them
hello this is 9-1-1 what emergency
service do you require
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
for me they're waiting for me I I see
this as a win
oh God I'm not gonna I'm gonna die
[Music]
[Laughter]
do I bring it to my wait first I have to
lose the cops and then I bring it to my
my getaway place right uh can you please
get off my vehicle
how do I get them off
all right
you've been going on a strip of me
in your life
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'm gonna have these Stars forever
probably as long as you are on here
probably right
oh [\h__\h] I was trying to get up there oh
I just have to stop for him how nice all
right all right all right okay now we
have to lose the cops there's no one in
here anymore right okay good okay okay
okay
um
are you losing them
I don't even try
oh there's some cops over there
oh there's some more over there
just stay clear stay clear
you're gonna be gone in free oh two a
one and
um
wait there's still someone in here
okay
oh for the matter yay we got it we
can
yay I went I win I win I win
I remember this place this is where the
boat was driving by
yeah I am
this place is a small City huh
okay
oh it's right over there isn't it is it
do wonderful
look at my new ride it's it's like kind
of ironic because
oh what is this guy
I'm a phoenix and my new ride is a fire
extinguishing vehicle
[Music]
get soaked
wet t-shirt day in his baby
can I turn my Wii while we want
what
is the fire fire in the water oh
no holding you just just alone
will I not get in trouble for playing
this
but well actually the people like get
out of my way oh they're stopping wow
stop for
that all is good always good this car is
very very robust
can take anything all right let's turn
it off I don't need it
yeah
do we need also this dump truck
no just just this red vehicle Aura all
right all right all right
this was
not quite as I expected it would go
but also the one this one drove by like
immediately after I gave them a call was
that really like
aim to come to me or was that a
coincidence I feel like it was quite the
coincidence
it was a good timing because I was I was
just setting up for
like getting them but then the police
came out I was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] but
then they also came
fire department perfect timing oops I
have to go back
a lot of hats up people
yeah I think he was just passing by
e
[Music]
yellow golden ring
get out of the fire truck hi
mission complete
three two one yeah
I expected it Hello Kitty Kelly oh this
is like I'm playing stray hello
hello
you want some tuna
thank you it was quite the effort
what's up
the fire truck
to your place then I guess we can't put
it off any longer I'll get word out to
the guys
speak to me
and you're taking care of the fire bombs
or what
thank you
did he say get get up to my place all
right
we mopping
oh no she's mopping she's mopping
how you doing pretty good
sis
about to knock off a federal government
building oh Meanwhile my psychotic
former BF the big one I'm trying to
figure out a way to stop the big one but
hey the meds are kicking in Life's good
well exactly
Franklin got us what we need put those
on then one then head in there and wake
up a slightly more it's not a big one
fire trap okay
so I'm guessing did you just make some
toast to the candle I can do the trick
huh oh no no no no there's 11 Cindy
areas in a Remote device gotta make some
food
so we can ensure that we still have
access to the server I see okay
and once you get out trigger the bombs
Franklin and the crew and we'll
intercept the emergency call and you all
go in as fireman got it
got it sounds a little idiotic well
under the circumstances
and if you remember you you were the one
who chose to do it like this yes very
confidently you know Trevor Has a point
about you you whine too much
[\h__\h] yeah I don't even try it don't
worry maybe for my next
outfit I'll request hands that have a
middle finger
pointing up right at you
I wonder if if cover would let me do
this probably not and I wouldn't really
want it anyway
foreign
[Music]
what's playing here
Cali
isn't it about
if you're saying okay cool
well you know it's only for one second
or so so
and
yeah
go next go next
Mike we moving on to stay as soon as I
get out of the bureau yeah all right dog
look me darling Noah we'll be waiting
the fire truck you know man I'll be
amazed if we make it out with this crew
it will be fine we don't need to shoot
and if anything I'm the good shooter
you and me Franklin
you and me
oh did you guys watch all these
birthdays dream it was her birthday and
like she's really good at organizing I
must say because like she asked me for a
video where I was saying a song and gave
me like choices for you know what what I
could sing
like three or four months ago
yeah I have to praise that because you
know usually many things happened last
minute and so on but she she even did
like a follow-up like a mom for two a
month before the deadline or so and then
yeah yeah
I could choose the song I wanted
and then she was you knew right there
when I needed her for some questions
yeah we're really really well planned
yeah they keep changing the contractors
yeah because guys like me keep losing
their jobs and agreeing to do this for
Less all right head up and yeah
yeah I sang
with Ollie get down get down get down
down
foreign
[Music]
my brain is like confused right now
I just watched it today
yeah yeah yeah
I watched The Archives I was
unfortunately sleeping when it was
happening but she was doing it for like
four and a half hours when I woke up she
was still doing it so I caught uh some
of it but not my own part because she
played me right as the first song in the
very beginning and then you know she
would always like add herself and then
it's like a collaboration
yeah I wanted to do this at some point
too because you know syncing up uh
karaoke when you're not doing an off
collab is uh yeah really really annoying
mop the floor all right
let's do this
is the kind of GTA that I like
yeah yeah
she had like I don't know 30 40 50
guests that she sang with
four and a half hours man
I don't know how she does it
um but it was fun I also watched how she
sang with with Cobble
I don't know I really like that one
they sang
it was so pretty
so pretty
there you go
hmm
okay I'm done mopping that was really
short thanks guys for not making this
place so dirty
I'm respecting
the janitor into housekeeping and all
that
are you throwing up though do I have to
clean that
oh
he looks like he's throwing up
throw the money spent on domestic
intelligence we haven't even developed
usable indexings okay we're good what I
have to mop so much
okay drop it drop drop the bucket
oh this is really serious mopping
business
his whistling reminds me of the
whistling sounds and Sims one or two or
so
some some Sims game they had a
no wait was it breaking out
it was really distinct
whistling I don't know if anyone
understands what I'm talking about
oh
I think it was breaking out actually
that was such a fun sense busting out
I'll bring out thank you thank you
you know what I'm talking about
the herbs maybe once the herbs
busting out or herbs I think it was
busting up
oh there's more there's more
I'm not allowed to run huh
who are all these people already Dirty
Man
my bed all on the floor my bed
[Music]
um
clean clean clean clean clean
busting out on GBA was incredible oh I
played on GameCube
a marvelous
marvelous game
all right is that what's dirty here I
don't see anything
and now it's gone
and a bit more
okay do I still need my bucket I guess
I'll take it just in case
otherwise it's too suspicious a janitor
without a bucket you can pause
tickets tickets
can I actually not take it out last time
he took it automatically actually after
planting the bone
I guess I don't need to pick it up
myself
time
nothing suspicious nothing at all
in the restroom oh no wow we're really
blowing up this place big time
another janitor
is the last one a heart attack or a
budget cut
when are you gonna get out of here you
better watch your mouth
don't underestimate me
continue and I can't Sprint and yet I'm
constantly pressing shift
thinking oh hello wait till I shake it
off before you mop the floor
why can't
[Music]
my king
relatively clean at least huh
oh
and now just have to pick it up myself
what the hell last time you just
suddenly had it after planting the bomb
you can't even run
all right
so far oh
[Music]
we're ready to go
back
to the closet okay okay
foreign
why are you not whistling anymore and
suspicious janitors must be whistling
yo yo people Gonna Know
okay I'll whistle for you
[Music]
I'm trying my best
foreign
[Music]
and run I'm free
easy easy
that's a shiny car
Frank I'm done
what's next
activate charge is set I'm out of the
building
oh hey dog we're right
up we right in the bill y'all ready for
this
and I'm gonna trust this plan is good
because I usually get brought in earlier
oh
better wait for the police don't want to
get in trouble again
this place is so close to the FIB
let me just wait
oh that's me I was like who the [\h__\h] why
are you trying to get into my car dude
you want trouble all right trigger the
fire bombs Frank I'll get my turnout
gear on
it was the phone to detonate okay and
then we tried to get in and and
supposedly put out the fire
uh when we're in contacts
and doesn't everybody have this contact
on their phone so hashtag relatable
all right First Response let's go let's
go let's save them
we're such Heroes
I'm a hero so Lester hijacked the
emergency signal right yep
yep
[Music]
you're right
oh we're here guys don't worry we got
you covered
ask me bro can we use the elevator oh we
can't I thought you weren't supposed to
use the elevator in case of a fire is
the exception the fire extinguishing
people
I keep on saying it like that oh
is that really like that I guess they
have to go there fast when it's like a
60 [\h__\h] story building yeah probably
a little bit of both
understandable
all right we're going across to the far
stairwell oh is that exactly why they're
not like normal people not supposed to
use them so that the fire department can
use them I guess that makes a lot of
sense
what's this
very interesting a nice insight into the
life of a fire uh extinguishing person
I'm [\h__\h] play it the right way hello
in [\h__\h] way
[Laughter]
it's not incorrect fire extinguishing
people
and yeah yeah I'm faster than you now
you were [\h__\h] on me
oh this oh holy [\h__\h] all right
and go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go
nice car deal yes yes
am I Franklin right now
I need you to fit a bomb and open it up
which which door
which one this one
and
I forgot how to do it wait a second
I have a I have a grenade
grenade is okay really
I thought I have like actual proper
bombs for that
wait wait
containment red containment dread
[Music]
let's go thank you
I'm trying to actually switch to
something
let's go
oh no
onion
[Music]
I don't want to lose you Michael you oh
my God you're my father
now at least
or I want you to be please please Daddy
don't care about the other two dudes but
holy sh you did not anticipate that did
you
here we go
foreign
[Music]
this is like [\h__\h] hell
holy [\h__\h]
uh we might actually want to start doing
some oh no extinguishing difficult
[Music]
oh my God
it's like a horror game and then
adventure and action and fight okay oh
my God
oh this sounded good did I [\h__\h] up
I did
yeah
how did they get me but not you guys
Logan must have knocked me out man wait
where did it again
oh
[\h__\h] I'm scared I don't wanna no I don't
like this I don't work well under this
kind of pressure
why the [\h__\h] am I supposed to go oh
I don't see [\h__\h] it's hard to see
me and I
[Music]
oh my God
oh here okay
I'm by my oxygen why do I go down
[Music]
I'll do it I guess before now I just
follow where the enemies are that makes
sense
that makes sense yeah why the [\h__\h] are
they in here
I shouldn't be here
oh
wait wait what
ah
oh someone oh they died in there
well that was [\h__\h]
restart from oh
oh all right before that
[\h__\h]
yeah I was that was unfortunate
can't help it
unfortunately
you're half now wasn't it more before
[Music]
okay I'll try to be as fast as I
possibly can oh
just get out of here oh
[Music]
oh oh
you used to be at home
okay I gotta come out of that the ones
as far as I remember
or are they
they're not here now
interesting
just get out of here
okay we're at the stairs we're at the
stairs we're at the stairs nice nice
nice nice nice
and you see that okay let's go
down on it
this is as far down as I can go
Friday
oxygen level still looking okay oh my
friends are here
[Applause]
nine two me too please how how to go
there we go
my friends so alive
protagonist plot armor
sure
I I am right behind you hopefully we
won't have another dramatic explosion
right in front of my [\h__\h] face
all right we gotta get these doors open
oh Mission Impossible
whoa
all right I'm the last one
what what Esther Apple holds to the
scent faster okay
oh God
oh my God this is [\h__\h] scary
let's go faster is there any such thing
as going too fast
oh God
oh I feel like that pretty much got me
but okay
is that spy music
why are we going up again did they go
through here yeah yeah okay okay ah
we're on the ground floor let's go
nothing suspicious happened here we
could not stop the fire but uh yeah
we'll leave it to the other peeps
[Music]
thanks for thanks for being here
y'all need a [\h__\h] break I need a
[\h__\h] sandwich
out of here
[Applause]
[Music]
we're going we cannot be playing
dress-up when that happens uh-huh well
we need to get to the right and torch
this fire truck as soon as possible
the lesson we learned from that I don't
know man I'm working on any minute
they'll be looking for us I mean those
guys in the building you took down if
they knew who else is gonna know it
ain't worth thinking about dog trust I'm
gonna get us there as fast as I can all
right [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] I just don't want to
run into something man y'all don't want
to run in the Trevor bro that's who you
don't want to run into ah you're right
so uh take us to our get out avoiding
the cops and then my dear friend Trevor
Phillips all right man I'll try try real
hard okay why did we snatch it so far
out it's so true man I'm sorry and what
I was saying is um lesson learned if you
were trying to extinguish a fire don't
bring a [\h__\h] Phoenix a phoenix is
probably the one who started to fight in
the first place
so you ain't gonna get really far
yep don't hire a phoenix as a fire
distinguisher this distinguisher
extinguisher
distinguish some fires
as I am a fire expert
but extinguishing no no no no so far
today yeah
this is a fire yes but I can do more
than that okay
underestimate me this is a big fire this
is a small fire this is a deadly fire
this is an okay fire this is this is a
candle fire
uh where where the [\h__\h] is okay we're
just leaving okay but we're going right
to the corridor
destroy did destroy it here
and maybe y'all should step away from it
then
what
you [\h__\h] idiots
we're just blowing up here
you guys [\h__\h] insane
would you mind
would would you mind
okay whatever [\h__\h] you your fault
[\h__\h] idiot
foreign
[Music]
we need to get to the ride
I'm working on it yeah cause if they
connect the dots man
I'm working on anyone in my inventory
but I mean these guys are the building
you took down if they knew who else is
gonna know it ain't worth thinking about
dog trust I'm gonna get us there as fast
as I can ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I just don't want
to run into something man y'all don't
want to run in the Trevor bro that's who
you don't want to run into I'm driving
one-handed now take a start get out
avoiding the cops the feds no my dear
friend Trevor Phillips all right man
I'll try try real hard okay can you get
there any quicker
yeah
we're fine
we're fine thank you
okay
scroll okay yes yes we'll get the C4
so I can rest wait and raster was also
called C4 wasn't it
interesting
it's just a thing that exists I guess
okay
oh
there's even more there I didn't realize
that
is one enough
just another one for good measure
obviously it wasn't me we all have no
weapons in our hands but how do we make
it go
oh God like whatever like what whenever
whenever whatever
that's beautiful
skin in the car which one
look there
[Music]
yeah hopefully I got no one
bye
that's how she said it
yes I played 70 of the campaign I didn't
know
because there's even there was even like
this there was even a spot so empty in
my weapon wheel they could have just put
it there so I thought as long as it's
not full
then anything new would be put into the
empty slot no that's like my logic
there right thank you you're gonna make
it out of there uh one of us didn't
we lost a doom man oh yeah [\h__\h] oh
there's more share for us isn't there
what is it oh yeah Darwinism
could have been seven percent it's just
luck it wasn't you we should be happy
about it it was brains
all right man if that's what you think
well anyway we made it out so we might
need more money money money those people
will get his paycheck and the standard
expenses and everybody gonna miss him
huh hey I don't like losing any of my
crew but uh no one was special he got
you wait if we would have gotten the
expensive shooter and one cheap shooter
would they have killed off the expensive
one or is that like always the cheapest
possible one that they kill off I wonder
how that would have gone he looked up
maybe man we're looking up to you got
that poor food killed
It's usually the cheap ones
people will always die the first one I
pick cheapest will let I'll kill him
because that would be so fast like you
bring in the most expensive shooter you
have
I didn't you can never use them again
because he died randomly
oh my God and you could not even
anticipate that
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
so from the valkyrie connect collab I
was able to make a wish uh it would have
been a certain budget and let me say
that was not even that was by far below
the budget
so
to be honest
I could have asked for something way
more expensive but you know I gave like
some options and this was one of the
things I wanted the most
um
and I couldn't buy it myself even if I
wanted to because that company doesn't
ship to Austria as far as I know at
least at that point when I tried before
no
no so I finally arrived a couple of days
ago
and then I had it just standing around
for a while because I wanted to like
have time to observe them whenever I
finally open it up and and test it out
wanted to be ready and you know
for have like the ability to look at
them for a couple hours so
uh yeah I I first of all putting it
together was not necessary at all
because it was already put together
don't have to build anything
just have to like
find a good spot for it and then I'll
plug it in it's really big though it
takes off a lot of space
so it is a bit difficult if you have a
small tiny apartment it's pretty tall
and pretty wide
and you're not supposed to put it
against any walls or so but I found the
perfect spot for it in my place
I'm quite happy with that and then I
just left the crib ain't it huh is that
so
and yeah uh yeah I just waited a little
bit I I picked up like smoothie and
chonkers and put them inside after
filling it up with some of the usual
um cat toilet litter and yeah this movie
was like purring like crazy she was she
loved it she actually loved this this
like kind of like spaceship for a cat
chances didn't mind it either but as I
explained in my last stream at the end I
had a little oopsie and I put her in and
then I I tried to turn the toilet off
and I thought that that this way would
be safe it wouldn't turn but the moment
you turn it off it does one last cycle
and turns around
so in case you don't know how it works
it's like kind of like a round
toilet
um the front is open but besides that
it's like a round capsule kind of and
inside is all around too and it looks a
little bit like a washing machine you
put some sand in there and then whenever
a cat is in there it like recognizes the
weight that it has more weight than
usual so it knows ah there's a cat in
here and then
once it leaves it knows okay cat is done
so it will wait a little bit so that
whatever they did in there gets like
kind of like uh clumpy
so it waits like seven minutes but you
can change it whatever how long you want
it to wait what's better for your litter
and then it starts turning up to seven
minutes
and it goes for like a uh
um I'm not sure what it's called Uh a
guitar and guitar
uh a thing with holes yeah it goes
through there so all the normal uh
litter goes through there first and then
what's left over would be the clumps
that are great yeah
a great a safe whatever yeah
so it goes through that first and then
you will be left with the clumps so it
turns a bit more and then you have like
a a hole that will lead to a bottom
compartment where uh all the poop and so
on will be collected yeah yeah and then
it turns a bit more then it turns all
the way back so that it's like a
straight and everything is perfect again
and this way I will never have clean the
litter
again I just have to wait until the
compartment is full there's like a trash
bag in there and then you just throw it
away and it saves so much time and it's
so good it's so much cleaner because oh
my God we're just gonna talk about cat
litter for a little while is that okay
just about I need to talk about this
before the story continues
um like when if you're a cat owner and
you you scoop your cat's litter uh your
whole life you notice at some point
first of all it's [\h__\h] annoying
second of all you might if you like me
sometimes neglect it a little bit
unfortunately but so far it's always
been okay they never it's never been so
neglected that they would like just pee
on the couch or whatever
but yeah it's also stinky and it's uh
exhausting and it can get pretty
exhausting at least for me and um
the thing is if you go through depending
on your letter I guess then it might be
different but
I've tried so many letters and it always
like the clumps they like fall apart and
it's annoying so in the end it mixes
some some uh used litter into the clean
leather even if you get rid of the
clumps now but I found this way
of the new cat robot litter toilet
thingy so good like it doesn't the
clumps after seven minutes are in
perfect condition and this way the cats
always always have a clean toilet they
must be like so happy the kitty cats
like even if you're really on track with
your cat toilets and you clean it every
day like at the end of the day or so the
cats will still always find a toilet
with like one or two little pieces of
poop or whatever in there but this way
with this cat toilet after each adult
meeting
it will be gone and they will always
find a clean toilet
that's so so wonderful I'm so moved I'm
so happy for them and I think they're
happy too
um
no not sponsored there's um more than
one brand that makes those robots though
but I think the one that I chose is the
most well known and and the most
um the best one I would say yeah yeah
it's my pleasure
I'm so happy you don't have to do
anything anymore
there's even a phone app that tells you
how full the bottom compartment is and
when the cat last went and so on
again it's really useful
[Music]
even
ly Dangerous Mission impersonating
Emergency Services while working in a
high security government facility
it was surprisingly uplifting
come here give me some of that oh
sorry I got my very very obvious illness
it happens you're just so happy let's
get drunk Franklin fill up the glasses
got some real vintage moonshine
hillbilly type [\h__\h]
committing incest in minutes oh no this
is not how social Dragon stop it oh
exactly I am just gonna get it well I am
secretly a Targaryen and then I'm gonna
reverse engineer a webcam and spy on
those sorority girls again I will okay
give me a
no no not excusable
boys
original but I gotta go Square things
this is the new Dream Team [\h__\h] Trevor
we don't need Trevor now that we did
this thing for him and we have the
evidence that we did this thing for them
and we can all go our own separate ways
you know well [\h__\h] if you want me to go
with your dog
[Music]
protect me sooner the better it's one
way to look at it that right besides I
want to put this [\h__\h] to bed yeah I also
used to have when I was living with my
mommy my TV running from the bed like
that miserable and loving every
[\h__\h] minute of it here let's
find out the incest jewelry I'm the only
cupboard man you boys show know how to
put the fun back in midlife crisis
natsukashi
yeah
the Bro raid we did it
I wonder what Trevor is up to
let's see
can we actually check I wonder why do I
keep on doing that oh Dave sorry we're
getting called
we hit the Bureau for you Dave I'm done
yes I saw that and that is brief you I'm
out Davey
from now on it's done I appreciate that
I'm trying my best for you but but you
and Trevor attacking Merryweather
repeatedly it doesn't help that's
Trevor's thing whoever's thing it is
it's unauthorized and it's dumb they've
been sniffing around my office we really
need to talk really all right all right
I'll come to the court Center can we
just talk
okay
[Music]
I'm saying no way that's not a chicken
that's just a piece of paper right
I thought there was a chicken from the
distance
[Laughter]
about you guys
no chickens in GTA maybe
um
where are we going
I said
it's a b
probably be right
never felt like this before I apologize
if I'm moving too fast
and we just talk
can we just talk
I I'm not gonna call a taxi I have bad
experience I have to do M first or I
should do okay let's it's kind of on the
way
I'm taking myself
freeway entrance
[Music]
okay
let me think okay so toilet is working
cats are using it I think I have yet to
see them
in action I always like just
suddenly hear the the toilets turning
around cycling and I'm like oh oh oh oh
who used it this time I was so proud of
you girls and I think it's probably
because
um
I I closed the room where the old toilet
is
so they actually had no other choice I'm
glad they immediately recognized it as
their new toilet
I'm so proud they're so smart it
reminded me of the time when I first got
them I think I told the story before but
when I first got them it was like kind
of quite late in the evening like I
don't know
8 P.M or so
all right I'm supposed to go there
and I brought them home and I I was
still living with a roommate at that
point and I only had this one room but
my room was pretty big so for the first
night since I I read up like how how to
best introduce your cats into a new home
uh I read that the best thing to do is
like keep them inside one room first
so
I uh put like everything in my room I
put their toilet and the food everything
into my room
um
to make them feel like this is a safe
place this is their home get them cozied
up to yeah and I was in the room the
whole time too so all is good so the
thing is they were extremely spooked uh
in the first like
10 hours at least 15 hours or so and it
was late in the evening so the moment I
let them out of their cage in my uh
little room
they immediately hid under like
some furniture
where I couldn't even reach them what
the hell are you doing what's happening
I could not even reached them but I I I
you know I tried to stay on the other
side of the room to give them space and
give them time and so on but I was
observing them and I was so excited
about my little kittens they were so
tiny teeny babies
and I just wanted them to feel safe and
comfortable so I was just watching them
and I tried to stay awake for as long as
possible because I was I wanted to show
them the toilet like it was out there in
the corner of the room but I wasn't sure
if they would understand that this is
their toilet now so I wanted to like
kind of show them but they would not
come out of the
whatever they were hiding underneath I
don't know what it was
yeah
especially if I was moving they would
not come out when I was like
I was chilling on my bed for like hours
and if I wouldn't move for like an hour
they would with a little tipsy tapsy
toes they would slowly emerge from their
hiding spot and and really really slowly
and carefully
and I'll explore a little bit but the
moment I would make a small noise or
anything really they would immediately
get spooked and
yeah hide back into the heavy hole
um
yes I was trying to be quiet but then I
could not I I had to sleep it was so
late it was past midnight and uh I
really just had to sleep
so at some point I fell asleep without
being able to show the toilet and I was
worried but I was like okay whatever
they're small kittens how much of a mess
can they make in one night
it won't be so bad even if they pee
somewhere and you know what I'll I'll
take that right this guy just got myself
some new kittens I will forgive them if
they do that no problem I was okay with
that but then I woke up the next morning
and I see
they used
the toilet
without me showing them anything
it was not even the litter they used in
their old apartment it was just some
random letter that I got
yeah
in a new environment sometime in the
middle of the night they apparently used
it I saw it I saw the proof the next day
I was really impressed yeah I was like
whoa
whoa proud of you girls he's so smart
how did you know right
ah I was so proud and then from then on
I knew my cats are smart cookies
I am not worried about anything in the
future
and once again
with this new toilet they proved how
smart they are
yeah
oh yeah reuniting a family
um
nice music
[Music]
are they gonna come by
oh one day pass by
oh hey
long time no seeing
oh
wait hey I'm sorry I spiked you okay I
get so mad and I can't control things
and then you know [\h__\h] just falls on top
of me my life sucks right now and I
don't know what to do except I want to
say I love you and hug it out but all
that wimpy [\h__\h] is just well I just
maybe tell them your mother that's not
cool anymore and the ones that I don't
really like it's not because they're gay
so lame all right you're just a lame and
angry psycho sometimes I got a shotgun
in my hand you sure you want to say that
I love you and I'm pretty sure I hit you
a little bit but I'm just so [\h__\h]
upset that we can't even see each other
and you're just a drunk lame dad
you know what
it might just be the nicest thing
anybody's ever said to me that's so sad
so will you buy me a car what I can
steal your car so will you buy me a car
kind of way in a completely off topic
can you buy me a car I mean firstly I'm
a fat [\h__\h] that you ruined and and
secondly I will get a job and I will
stop smoking pot in that sort of way
okay what sort of way I love you too son
[\h__\h] with a [\h__\h] idiot
get a job I only have the money to buy
you a car I do but let's not tell him
besides which way
I'm probably gonna be dead in a couple
weeks anyway
it might be please don't die okay
it's great catching up with you too Dad
yeah
hey
how's your mother
oh she's great
no she's not she's bored I mean all this
mesmerizing tantric sex she's been
having with a much younger Better Built
caring and compassionate man is great
and all okay another six hours
up you miserable bastard she's mad at
you she's scared that you're gonna die
and she wants you to go over there and
prove that you give a [\h__\h] by maybe
giving her a sorry [\h__\h] hit let's go
Tracy on the way Tracy on the other hand
she's a star
sort of
what
guys
we just need to machine real
um
what's the word re respect the romance
you know yes
let's make it sparkly and spicy shrimp's
box so
what's been happening you know what I
don't know that's what I'm saying
that's what I'm saying
well what's been happening with you uh
thanks it's been it's it's anyone's
guess we killed the FIB yeah I get it
you were out of the city sure you guys
were gone so I thought I you know let's
maybe not pretend it was anything to do
with us those Beast Hispanic dudes with
automatic weapons and blacked out
windows they kind of made me think it
was an involuntary Exodus yeah okay
that'll work you done talking all right
I was just waiting for them there they
are outside oh come on let's say hi
let's walk up and be civil
no caffeine oh no that dude curling has
been sluggish for weeks
less lifestyle Guru and a little bit
more boy toy I can't get out my gun I'm
gonna
need to write a screenshot shush woman
hey Amanda Fabian Michael hi Mom hi
Jimmy this is to a picture of holistic
well-being I don't think maybe they [\h__\h]
once a year between them oh that's my
son Amanda come I have a new unitard on
hold you must pay for it hey what buddy
I'm gonna ask politely that you show my
wife a little respect
red meat has been blocking your Chi as
well as your digestive Trust
you we're gonna go over there do you you
want me to do something one time nice
special yoga with you hit him Please
shush woman anything for you sweetheart
came from homes is he alive
listen Amanda
I wanted
a meaning to say to you
what he's trying to say mom is that he's
a pathetic old drunken mess and he needs
you no no
a lot better than a primadonna yoga
instructor with an Angel
try
all I'm asking for is a shot
neutral ground Dr friedlander's office
oh okay yes
pick up Tracy
fine
all right you on that note I would like
to recommend everybody a show that is
not on Netflix not anywhere it's kind of
hard to watch but
um it's really funny
Web Therapy right you know where your
sister is right so good let's go wait
wait but what about that Sugar what
happened pig fat flavored beverage I
want please give it a chance and watch
all the time come on it's one of my
favorite shows ever I think Tracy's over
at the tattoo parlor now with Lisa
Kudrow the one from Friends uh she's
such a good actress it's just so funny
it's so good I love the concept of that
show so much and I think I talked about
it before but it's been a while when I
was getting another tattoo no oh God no
that Laszlo guy's there Laswell that
[\h__\h] what's he want it's Tracy that
wants something she wants to get back on
fame or shame after you and Uncle T got
her candy yeah
maybe we oughta wait you really want to
get around let me ask you back there
with your mom
that went okay didn't it
fabian's first eardrum is yeah looking
okay with me yeah I mean with me and
your mom I think it's an important first
step in like the direction of okay
[Music]
happiest couple on Earth let's go one
here
's The Tattoo Shop
is that where my daughter is
getting another ass decoration yep that
you know since I'm capable of violence
but I'm awesome in the sack last time so
listen babe the voice sounded like
listen do whatever it takes even if
whatever it takes is a depressed
borderline alcoholic who hosts the third
most popular talent show amongst the 40
years old again so you let me on the
show if I blow you yes and if you could
wear some black lipstick the little guy
loves the goth Vibe oh whoa Laszlo dude
that was entirely out of context bro gym
sit on him Laszlo here's gonna have a
little cosmetic work done no
stay put you lame ass Mark sure
friend likes a golf vibe how about we
put a black tattoo on his little friend
since he likes it so much hmm like a
like a kiss Mark a black kiss mark huh
isn't that exactly what he wanted
is that not exactly what he was asking
for
[Music]
oh come on
um
[Laughter]
boring
that looks pretty here let's get rid of
this oh
[Music]
right
what do we want
no
okay
oh it's so it [\h__\h] what I've been doing
I don't know oh I have to do something
that they already decided on okay uh if
I could do whatever I wanted don't
[\h__\h] wait absolutely doing the thing
I was thinking about doing anyway
how about I throw those three little
pubic hairs on here
there we go
snip snip cut it off cut it off
evacuate my bells a little bit
disappointing out
like he's gonna look better with short
hair probably we're not really doing him
Pony
my daughter whatever she wants yeah
without sucking on your fiddleston look
okay guys that was a joke I'm a clown
I'm a sad lonely yes yes you are yes put
her on your show and you're gonna make
sure she looks good look I'm ready
all right all right Trace let's go
I'll like call you or something okay bye
oh my God this girl needs therapy
how do I look
gorgeous it's not good is it you can now
you have two it's one of those skills
you pick up in prison you know
you're Silly's ass ew are you serious
come on no
not quite
I feel like I feel like he will enjoy
using that to his advantage
to your mental health so I don't know
why he'd be better positioned to help
Thor dysfunctionals hey this was your
mother's idea well I guess it beats yoga
yeah I'm done now he beats yoga
literally like Fabian around the head
with the laptop oh yeah
to be honest I know it's karmically bad
I'm sorry
I know it's perfectly bad but yeah I
[\h__\h] hate that dude yeah I know right
you show up his own ass you're a [\h__\h]
contortionist whoopee I contort my junk
all day long and I don't act all
Superior about it just a little ashamed
means hey guy was talking smack to your
mother well I applaud you pop
you're here you're like finally like
using your powers of selfishness and
rage for like goodness
what's in our best interest kind of good
[\h__\h] yeah awesome let's rob somebody do
it Dad yeah do it do it
uh I love that we're getting along but
knock it off yeah don't like actually
rob a liquor store that might like kill
the mood [\h__\h] therapy let's do this
you just let your mom and me talk okay
seeing as you two aren't into it you can
just sit there and be quiet that's cool
with me I got all the prescriptions I
need it at least for the meantime thank
you
family family
[Applause]
so happy
oh my God what the [\h__\h] oh wow no
scratch baby okay now but that's your
fault [\h__\h] yeah
I always wanted to go back to the
therapy finally we get a chance
highly needed necessary session let's go
now
foreign
[Music]
but then I don't know it wasn't possible
in that moment so it was like whatever
and now we've played so much of the game
it's too late now
show
uh okay
I'm kind of wrong here
don't go
I'm I met a cute Dogo in the elevator
the other day
and is that oh my God I'm so sad
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I don't deserve to be alive anymore no
I was gonna say that the dog really
liked me and the owner was really
that's really a surprise like oh wow
normally my dog she she's not she
doesn't like just lick strangers hands
like that
because she was a young puppy relatively
and yeah she was really chilled with me
I'm like oh maybe maybe it's because I
smell like cats I have so many cat hairs
on me and she was like yeah probably
because our dog used to live with cats
Michael kids
um inside okay dogs like me but I don't
like them much but no that dog I found
was absolutely adorable I like that one
that was a cute doggle fighting where's
Bubba now this is
completely different story man
completely different two different
situations and cases is absolutely not
the same thing
hello good to see you again anyway I'm
so glad
[Music]
this is great are you sure you're ready
for this [\h__\h] family because no one's
ready for this family I think fantastic
Michael
I am being positive this is me being
positive give it up Michael
the sarcasm
it's one of the reasons I moved out it's
beneath you no it's not Amanda trust me
nothing's beneath me no normally there's
a [\h__\h] beneath
that spins every waking moment working
on themselves inside and out more inside
than Alex has been really [\h__\h] slow
how would you know what progress like
you
you [\h__\h]
because all you do is whine at me
[\h__\h] people
your children reasonable people
[Laughter]
[Music]
playing it on the way to the [\h__\h]
bank
it's not like what the [\h__\h]
face it Amanda
we're trailer trash you and me
we were taught to do this
get a center Michael you have no Center
my [\h__\h]
we'll both get a sinner before that ever
happens you are such a [\h__\h] animal I
deranged animal you're [\h__\h]
under ranged
[Music]
I should have had you locked up years
ago you stupid [\h__\h] do it I'll put you
in the [\h__\h] ground with the rest of
them
and that's really all the time
I think we made some real progress there
typical typical therapist does nothing
takes all the credits it goes without
saying but family work is a little more
expensive but double
squared
of course
[Music]
all right then
kids
I'm sure there's good therapists out
there but this is Dr Friedland he's not
one of them at least look
at our hmm
you know there was a moment there I
thought what
I don't know like maybe we still had a
ways to go you know like maybe we need
more time time for what time to move
Beyond screaming at each other that was
cathartic catharsis all over my face I'm
sorry oh I thought you were making an
effort probably just the meds you rated
okay
[Music]
all right
this was not as dramatic as I wanted it
to be
I was doing in there huh
just gonna stay here for a while
[Laughter]
Amanda that I've been more interested
Amanda died
wow
just ignoring all the other deaths here
now I just needed to let this out
because these are all suddenly [\h__\h]
ungrateful pricks
well hopefully now they learned a lesson
oh
it's a muscle car unless you move some
hookers in in which case it's just the
way you left it maybe a little busty's
all
your tear stains and a whiff of bitter
loneliness nah that's just natural old
man smell also known as whiskey cigars
and takeout and hookers and murder no
hookers
look we got any ground rules for the
brand new shiny healthy family Dynamic
the Santa 2.0 uh 3.0 dick fall townleys
would be 1.0 and the DeSantis were more
like 2.0 this is like 3.0
yeah
because we could just take like one of
yours from the cam remind me do you
spell it with two x's or is it three
shut up ground rules
now where are we I got one I can think
of what's that baby don't get killed
that's kind of out of my hands and don't
be a smart ass and don't get us killed
either that ain't happening I'll do
everything I can to protect so far yeah
he's been protecting them quite well all
in the place baby
so it's right here with me yeah I guess
yeah I'm telling you I've totally
figured the whole thing out I'm going
legit
responsible right and Jimmy's getting a
job and Tracy is going to college I just
paid this dude to write my resume so I'm
like basically there Mom what and I'm
like so proud
but dad is coming up with his auditions
so and I'm a movie producer being a
movie producer is not a legitimate or
responsible career option but I guess it
is better than being a killer or a bank
robber 3.0 baby yeah here we are home
sweet home remember this place we did it
we did it we're here with all of our
family oh my God how long has it been
[Music]
kids rooms if you find dead bodies cheap
women or Trevor Phillips we're checking
into the Rockford Hills Hotel oh
Hotel sounds nice too
oh were you real now the family oh my
God
yay
nice yeah I would I go somewhere else
too if I found Trevor there oh is that
Trevor
what recently we always see you like
this what's wrong with you dude
sure
hmm
at least this time he's not wearing a
dress
um
is he okay he kind of cute butt right
now though
cute cute pencil you gotta go in there
so cute um are we supposed to use that
thing because it's drifting away
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h]
I know man come go try and get it before
it's all gone
why are you like this one
hi
I have to acknowledge a killed butt no
matter who it belongs to
but probably everything below that those
panties is absolutely nasty so
yeah where are we going just somewhere
the f
the rest is question marks
are we going to this one
F question mark
Michael
why was I even
oh I I can go what what is Franklin
doing by the way
oh wait I looked at the wrong color
maybe I'm not sure no no I did not oh
oh
I wanna bathtub like that one day
oh in the Maldives we had a bathtub like
this freestanding and in that shape
but it was I think it was white
I was shaped like that and right next to
the
window but we were when we were in the
bathtub together
keyword uh it was really stormy outside
well that was kind of cool stormy
outside but we were chilling in Rose
paddles
and bubbles in the bathtub
yeah don't remember some people
surprised don't you remember you should
be following my Twitter
hey what the [\h__\h] his bathtub is in the
same room as the
bedroom I mean I guess I've seen setups
like this before but is that really
necessary when you have such a huge
mansion
um
this place is nice
hmm But I don't know if I even should be
playing with him
I don't want [\h__\h] no no no no I'll go
back to Michael
yeah because I know where to go with
Michael at least
yeah the Maldives streams you have to
check them very tasty
yes keep watching oh
that was sweet
you absolutely completely 100 sure you
don't want to watch me gaming
I think if I want you gaming I'm only
gonna be back seating you I'm quite the
backseat of myself if I might say I have
a problem a vaccinating problem people
watching me oh
we have a cleaner she doesn't like being
logged oh I'm sorry I didn't mean to
see
oh
listen Michael I'm so glad we're back
together and making a goal of things
after everything we've been for [\h__\h]
I think it's in here right no
ah after everything we've been through I
just could not give up on our family yes
you are awful and clearly you're never
going to change but I guess I want to
bury you
so to
death can have two meetings either
you wanna kill him or you just want to
be there to bury him that is of course a
beautiful sentiment or she wants to do
both
when the time comes as your wife please
stop cheating on me
first of all I thought you guys had an
arrangement second of all throughout the
whole game I have not seen Michael
cheating on you I have only seen you
cheating on him if anything
so that makes no sense
please stop hanging out with those
people and please stop getting into the
kind of trouble you're getting into go
back to being the fat depressing slob in
therapy I loved
hmm so
you love him at his worst but you don't
love him at his best
shouldn't it normally be if anything is
normally the other way around okay be
the be the best you
but that's kind of the worst me
the worst me that's the worst me
depressed fat and slob in therapy that's
the worst me
um
send an example for the kids a better
example listen I really think we should
remodel the house again
nothing expensive what they call a quick
guy are you [\h__\h] kidding me it should
really solidify our relationship either
that or get a beach house
this [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
where does she think I get the money for
these things from in the first place
number one second of all what's wrong
with this place is [\h__\h] insane and
magical
oh my God
I'm back here you I'll continue to do my
best no house for modeling or beach
houses just yet though please let's
focus on getting the kids out of the
house and gainfully important wow
what a mature and calm response Michael
he's not even trying to argument with
all the [\h__\h] she said in her email
oh yeah damn
wow
Michael you're so mature respect
see
all right why is why does shift open up
my Discord now
I thought shift was uh running
when has it open on my Discord
oh what the [\h__\h]
it brings up Discord right in the middle
of my gaming screen
so weird
I didn't I didn't do that
no no okay what let me you know what let
me turn off
no Discord no more Discord
it's still opposite
the [\h__\h]
yeah it has like um integration it's
like
integrated into the game now
thank God you guys don't see it
[Music]
yeah Ryan's in the background okay let
me let me turn it off properly
why does it do it now though it didn't
do it before
quit Discord okay oh shh how about now
okay now it doesn't open it anymore nice
I guess that's what I have to do
all right
where are all my cars
are they all in the garage now but
that's so annoying I have to walk all
the way over to the oh wait my one car
is here
one car is here
all right all right all right oh I got a
uh
[Music]
Higher Love
I got a happy message today I can't say
it yet but I think you'll see
uh the results soon
a happy message
yeah no it's not related to the thing
next week it's not related to anything
but
if all goes well I can
show you this thing relatively soon
it's a thing that I've been waiting for
for a while
yeah yeah and but the thing that happens
next week also very exciting many
exciting things besides sad things too
but oh that's golden baby
some sad things be happening but also
some happy things be happening so
I guess it balances itself out
foreign
[Music]
bad things maybe
also concerning Hollow talk
um
I I don't know man I've been trying to
get
foreign
well with corn and I said but we never
get like a schedule
that works for both of us I guess but
I'm gonna
she she wants to do it she said she
wants to do it but
it's never [\h__\h] possible together and
schedules to match up so
apparently she's gonna
suggest me some dates instead of me
suggesting her sometimes maybe it won't
even be on the weekend who knows
um
now I already said like anytime is fine
for me I can adjust the time can be
Saturday or Sunday but maybe it won't
even be a Saturday or Sunday
but please wait very muzukasi
I'm supposed to go in
oh no
um and while I'm waiting for coronation
I'm hoping to get
but I just want to get over this hurdle
and I think everything will be easy from
then on
yeah
where the [\h__\h] don't go the [\h__\h]
what
can I go back in no
[Laughter]
no
I mean it was good yeah oh my God I
wanted to talk about it a little bit I
have the same point it was so sweet you
know I was honestly really worried about
this episode
but it went so a while and I think the
clip site I chose were pretty good too
pretty good um moments of I am a senpai
the questions I think were good as well
I I researched I don't think I've ever
researched so much about any other
holotalk member
um but I really wanted to
um make sure that the questions are
decent so I got a lot of like inside
info
a lot of smaller
smaller questions too but important
questions
um I think it was a good choice and I
got along well with her too maybe that's
why we're such great friends before the
stream old school we like old-fashioned
we talked a lot before the Stream
Good Guys bad guys
surprisingly well I don't know you tell
me we did what you said right got those
people off your back now you're gonna do
like you said and cut me loose things
are not going to work out quite that way
it has to be a problem yeah
I can say that Steve I told you I would
handle it oh because you've handled
everything so [\h__\h] well so far
haven't you all right I admit things
have been a little unorthodox [\h__\h]
Orthodox I like this people they're
funny as a group they're so funny
kidding me arrest me for what for
multiple counts of every [\h__\h] crime
under the [\h__\h] Sun oh well then let
me rephrase [\h__\h] excuse me why
now Steve we agree to speak to Michael
to try and explain things to him not
this this causes problems for us all
okay no I'm not put your gun down and
we'll talk when you put it down where's
the trust you can do better than that
they know or think they know that I'm
the one that was behind the incident but
do you know that they've been yeah
right before I end up at the bottom of
the ocean [\h__\h] good luck with that
put the weapons down boy time is over
we've got you anti-American active put
your weapon down all of you
who the [\h__\h] are you with with me
for the record I'm a patriot I love my
country put the weapons down what's
happening outside boys are bald deep in
a plot to drive up your funding by any
means necessary
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what am I supposed to shoot I don't know
I would shoot everybody
[Music]
some more of these guys kill each other
the hell
what happened to Hanks he get caught in
the car every Red Dot on the map must be
eliminated I understand
who's on our side Dave seems like
everyone wants to kill us
there we go
one one's over there I don't see him
a little bit escalation
a little bit aspiration oopsy noodles oh
oh I can't swim
uh-huh I'm going here
[\h__\h]
uh Kelly's here hello Cali
Cali
[Music]
is
cash money girl I have the necklace on
right now
it's gonna be me
[Music]
yeah I'm just here for the opportunity
now run
[Music]
I'd be better off putting my sights on
him
[Music]
make out if I'm doing that but how did I
get to that one then so somewhere over
there in that direction I don't see him
oh wait they're not even marked on the
map oh wow no that was the one
not confusing the
The View
okay
back to Michael
it's downstairs or right around oh
how long I can keep it up
oh baby let's go
so tell me Davey who are these bureau
men trying to kill me
kill each other already
okay
[Music]
more Merryweather are you kidding me
shut up these guys oh is that Trevor up
there
how much work did you
what happens to Haynes Norton gonna pop
him at the water cooler on Monday oh
wait that's mine friend Jesus
what are Merryweather doing at this
party
just trying to earn a dime
gotta get the chocolate
[Music]
the longer you take the longer I gotta
wait to kill you I'm [\h__\h] hell
away from me
[Music]
oh I got him okay senseless waste of
human life
oh Michael oh wait
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
let's try this a little bit
okay who else we got
someone was still there but they're not
coming out oh hello
he's not dead yet is he and then see a
gray thing popping up
oh hi hi hi hi so much action okay you
should probably
thank you
ah
close to your head I didn't see your
head
Chopper's about to fall on your head
they're done I gotta get up before
someone [\h__\h] my Chopper hey thanks
oh [\h__\h] there's so many there's so many
[Music]
um
go UPS this way this many bodies
there'll be cars in the lot put as much
dirt between you and this place as you
can and do not contact me until you're
absolutely sure you're clear
I'm taking this one so long
stay safe
who else no I think we could mostly one
more there
right now
what where's my yellow dot all the way
over there now what
what okay the pawn shop now okay okay so
I can get into the car yeah
at first the dot was here I suddenly it
changed I was like what does he want to
talk like right here okay no we good we
good let's go let's go
that was absolutely smooth wonderful I
think another Chopper
oh what else what the [\h__\h] am I supposed
to do
dogs
okay okay it won't it will not
shoot those missiles if I'm like in the
middle of the city would it
it was not risk such casualties
oh my God I think I lost it it's not
there
easy easy
yeah I think it's gone I don't see it
I was way too easy
get down
that was fun quick
you see after we reunited with our
family now we are reuniting with Trevor
I guess whoever we want it or not I hope
I hope it will be civil
ized
[Music]
I'm supposed to go here ah at the pawn
shop
all right well I see him he's got a
shirt and
Beyond
what's that for you don't you know it's
got a little something to do with being
caught in the middle of a three-way fire
fight between two government agencies
and a private militia you know it gets
me a little stressed out okay I mean we
still need you alive Mikey boy I mean
you know at least for now he's tossing
me you have another surprise for me
with another inappropriate friendship
yeah that wasn't exactly Dave's fault no
no he's just the friendly face of a
corrupt government agency looking to
further his career by dealing with an
equally corrupt and full of the [\h__\h]
brim with [\h__\h] low rent Hood listen
Trevor listen I've been meaning
[Music]
or that you were and always will be a
worthless wretch who deserves to be put
under yeah did you come back for oh you
know
ah no not one last score
and if it goes good guess what the big
one you don't have to put a little ball
in your head but we're going back oh
that's okay too because then you and I
get to go to hell and I get to spend the
rest of Eternity with you tormenting you
well I guess it's on then
yeah I guess it is call Lester let's go
on speakerphone
baby I know how'd it go just fabulous
old friend matter of fact he saved my
ass
suppose a group hugs out of the question
he wants to uh still go on the final
Victory Tour all right when it looks
like it's a go I'll contact you and
remember this gentlemen if
sorted nasty depraved history
but history nonetheless all right
there you happy everything's history
don't forget amigo
keeping my eye on you yes amigo
yeah
wonderful I'm so happy to be back with
you
the wrap up was not much of a wrap up
more of a wrap open because once again
we're deep in the [\h__\h]
very deep
once my boyfriend been doing
she okay he was not involved at all in
that thank God
adding
with the helmet yeah
you have to be always safe
let's do something with him I feel like
you know I neglected him uh
I can go to the L but that's probably
isn't that just what assassination
Franklin I'll go to the F there seems to
be something on the app
let's go oh
guys I'm proud of myself because
yesterday and the day before yesterday
I cooked
yeah two days in a row
yesterday I cooked some some pasta with
zucchini it was like kind of
I was using hellofresh ingredients but I
wasn't really going by the recipe like I
left out some things and I added some
things that zucchini was added
zucchini leek pasta and it turned out
really good zucchini leek Curry pasta
actually
of a low-key Curry taste it didn't
um
it didn't look so good that's why I
didn't post it on Twitter it tasted
really good but it didn't look like
anything special
and then the day before I made a burger
but this time with actual meat not with
[\h__\h] cheese Patty and I realized
oh yeah
this is the first time
I think that I made a burger with actual
uh beef patty I know I know I know my
lower is destroyed forever please please
don't I'm just trying to be real with
you and have a conversation so don't
don't put that into the lore I made my
first beef patty and I immediately made
a mistake because this was my first time
I learned for the next time I'll know
better but
um you know I was I was I was forming
the patties into a circle and into an
appropriate size but I did not oh that's
the
the patties when you grill them
they become smaller
[\h__\h] shrink
age
yeah and also I made them way too fat
actually so I I was like I was grilling
them endlessly and at some point I
realized uh all right they're getting
like pretty dark now like outside
they're like maximum at this point so I
cut them open to see what it looks like
inside and holy [\h__\h] when I cut them
open so much [\h__\h] meat juice spills
out but not only that that would be fine
I guess but no there's like the middle
is all still [\h__\h] red like it's so
uncooked in the middle I was like [\h__\h]
but I was smart because they were so fat
but like relatively small in like
whiteness I I cut them like
in half as in like a cup through I don't
know how to describe this I cut through
the middle but so that I have two
patties that are still the same with so
then I put them back on the in the
frying pan and just grilled the surface
of where it was still like really really
raw and then I fixed it so that was okay
but now for the next time I know first
of all make them flatter second of all
make them wider because they're gonna
shrink
yeah I learned my lesson so because that
looked so shitty I didn't took a take a
photo of that either
I didn't think it was worth showing on
Twitter it tasted good though I I made
the burger out of it yeah yeah a
relatively simple Burger
not much
special stuff
you know just a bun and where where
exactly am I supposed to go
out I gotta train your ass to use the
John chop that's a big ass pile of [\h__\h]
just the bun ends of some some uh oh
bacon they were supposed to be bacon but
I didn't even use the bacon wasn't in
the mood oh and corn cob I made a corn
cob additional to that corn cob with
some butter
but that installed really simple so it
was a bird guy and it's a side that has
a coin cup Yum Yum Yum okay I'll go into
the living room
that was my dinner the day before
yesterday and yesterday I had uh that
zucchini leek Curry pasta both really
good
but not worth posting a photo so I just
wanted to tell you guys I was being a
good girl oh yeah that was on the night
where I was like I I don't want to cook
I guess I'll make a pizza even though I
don't deserve it but I still ended up
cooking
good girl me
actually not now that I think about it I
think I cooked three days in a row but
yeah then yeah yeah
I'm so proud
today I'm gonna eat the remains of my
pasta and then tomorrow I'll eat my
frozen pizza oh hey hey maybe what you
doing I'm real glad you're here come
here
what's up baby it's Lamar
what that fool want now it's your best
friend he's your best [\h__\h] friend
for real my best I never saw her before
my homeboy right my [\h__\h] man [\h__\h] you I
mean not like that man but no he ain't
he just another [\h__\h] from the hood him
stretching all the [\h__\h] clowns
all they want to do is drag a
[\h__\h] down and live in the past
and this is the future a big empty house
with nobody who gives a [\h__\h] about you
[\h__\h] it works for me it won't work for
you babe I'm getting married Franklin to
a doctor not a murderer what the [\h__\h]
you doing here Tanisha I'm worried about
Lamar you got to help him Tanisha man
that [\h__\h] is over oh I'm a legitimate
businessman now sister I'm a CEO and
investor I'm Illuminati I'm a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] you a phony [\h__\h] what I
ain't saying you got to marry the fool
I'm saying he's about to get killed over
that deal you ain't put on with
stretcher set him up
[\h__\h] man my whole [\h__\h] life I've been
looking after this [\h__\h] paying
a price afterwards [\h__\h] well at least do
it one more time Franklin for me
I love my sister
I love you and Lamar we grew up together
but this life ain't for me and you knew
that you ain't changing I don't care how
many cars you own how many apartments
you own I don't care how many diamonds
you put in your it ain't for me not done
bad or done good babe look I'll change
no you won't fair enough but at least
respect what you do Who You Are if you
let that idiot die you a bigger [\h__\h]
than I thought
I'm so confused I don't know what's
going on with Polito Bay is she
basically just like
like why did she come here just to
complain about him having a big house
but what for I don't I don't quite
understand her purpose here right now
like what happened before this
ah because Lamar is in trouble uh okay
okay you do what you gotta do
ah
okay okay now I get it thank you now I'm
in the picture go to The Sawmill all
right let's go
[Music]
oh that reminds me yesterday I recorded
and the day before yesterday I recorded
a lot of things what's up I'm in a bit
of a bad situation my boy Lamar got set
up I think he up near Polito Bass from
Sawmill with some Ballers could you like
do some computer magic and look into it
is that possible at all it should be
I've got a back door under the Polito
Bay Police Network left over from the
score we did up there and give me a
second here uh hold on uh yes so what'd
it say huh this must be it there are
older reports of a weed operation being
run by an African-American gang and the
files got buried so I'm guessing they
paid off the cops they growing weed up
there growing it in the Hills most
likely but they might be packing and
shipping it out of this Sawmill I'd
expect a fair few of them up there [\h__\h]
and I'm gonna need some help can you
tell Mike and Trevor to meet me up there
they still aren't getting along that
well tell them it's for me and it's
serious thanks man not true they love
each other lovey
anyway what was I say oh yeah I was
recording some [\h__\h]
and I felt a little bit
so what are we calling wow so far A
little bit awkward one thing yesterday
that's a trap one thing was like
um me recording four Bloods
uh that was fun because I'm really
familiar with the song but this time I
recorded some harmonies too that wasn't
the case for the for the concert so it
is the ultimate version I guess and the
other thing I recorded
was not a song
and then it partially made me feel
really awkward he will eventually know
what I mean
damn recording for a couple hours in my
room alone
making weird sounds
yeah
I wonder what it could be oh I actually
I have to record one more thing like
possible tomorrow before the stream but
tomorrow my stream is late so that's
actually good
It Happened One More urgent recording
just Saga the reminder on Discord please
record this as soon as possible okay
okay
[Music]
yeah many things always going on so much
stuff
every morning I wake up I got so much
[\h__\h] to catch up on trying to wrap my
brain around it
hmm
yeah
but it's a good thing to be busy
now
as long as I'm able to I want to do
as many things as possible
yeah
good to be busy that's what I'm saying
[Music]
[\h__\h] are we going
are we going to where travel lives what
this place isn't this where Trevor lives
[Applause]
anniversary Kiana hanging over the
shoulder what what do you mean
oh ah like the little angel telling me
what to do
I have a sawmill oh I'll go
me short time memory please understand
it was a crazy schedule yeah
it's okay I'm trying to balance it well
that's why I also need some shorter
streams
every week to make sure I have some time
for doing other things as well
thank you
also you guys should remind me to put in
the members only stream next week
because currently it's packed with like
frog related things
and I need to somewhere find a spot to
squeeze in
the members because we're not doing one
this week so we have to do one next week
so much for our epic race battle
I don't know if the members only three
will be rap related to but
I want to use froggy Walla for that too
yeah I don't know how and what we're
gonna be doing exactly but yeah
actually one reason why I also wanted to
move frog week to next week was because
I wanted to make sure that I finished
GTA without like a big gap in between if
we were doing frog week now and then GTA
next week then we had one week
for whatever reason in between
interrupting
is better and smoother we can finish it
and then take that off and then move on
to front week and then we can move on to
more things
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
but I got Frankie Wawa of rigged now I
just have to figure out how to use her
did you invite this stooling huh we want
Lamar to be rescued not sold to the feds
give it a rest ass wipe look at them
together [\h__\h] up now let's take a look
at this place man Lester said this was
some type of big weed store spot
place is crawling with Ballers you know
now me and you we don't mind the old
dang Warfare but suede bucks over here
that reminds me of that time we had to
when I see it shut up rates that like
now I see the wee but where the [\h__\h] is
the most place on the countryside [\h__\h]
there you go oh no tell Trevor I'm gonna
be up on this hill with my rifle I don't
want to be anywhere around him when he
[\h__\h] this whole thing up classic
classic huh he's already planning his
Escape oh
yeah
oh why do I have to be traveling I run
towards it no do I have to be him
yeah
get into an assault position what's an
assault position go to any markers and
shoes oh okay okay any marked position
let me kind of look at them here in big
okay one is over there is that like a
really good one or are they all whatever
's on the right there
heaviest oh
okay the other side
wait was he not talking to me
okay you're the expert
expert well how do I get there I'm
bringing attacks on the unsuspecting
yeah if he was talking to me then I
assume that that position the closest
one is so direct and it's gonna be a bit
difficult
so I prefer to do it a little bit
differently
oh I have a position Frank too oh
okay so I'll take this bulldozer I guess
confirm
all right my turn to move
Okay so
uh where do I go with Franklin
Maybe
this is a tough gun fight oh man
I mean the last couple ones went
relatively well but I just have to
remember the [\h__\h] struggle I had that
one
with Trevor where we blew up like
everything you know what I mean
I don't remember that one well
we can fail once or twice it's okay
all right
I mean I wouldn't mind is that smart
though
otherwise I would go to the other spot
is
I think
I think maybe not it's okay it's cool
really
all together all right
go together with Trevor
maybe he can be my mommy Shield
let's go find a dude
well I walk all right bro
I don't know what to do
I just start blasting guys
let me clear those cards out of the way
for you
this how we do a drive by in the back
country yeah
This Is How We Do This Is How We Do It
this is how we do it baby
you're not even looking where you're
shooting LG where you at hey
Bob so far so good
[Music]
you better not be dead [\h__\h]
where is he at
the first fight Lamar this is good like
he's today I can hide behind him this is
perfect actually I'm glad I went with
him
give us the mouthy one and we'll be God
it's a good good technique
where's my home yet
okay got it got it got that one
[Music]
friend of ours
yeah good time
probably not him
yeah oh thank God
[\h__\h] hell
all right
see there should be two more oh I said
shot
last one is true I don't see him
probably good to go
Lamar Davis wins
Chamberlain gangster families for Life
[\h__\h]
what wasn't that the one you wanted to
kill me to kill anyway
I don't know
we're shooting now
[\h__\h]
oh
got a good point of view going here
[Music]
I go back
moving moving moving
I didn't see that one coming where was
he even looking at
Lamar
hey Lamar it's me getting out of here
dog
[Music]
oh God oh God there's a lot of people
there now coincidence huh
I want to move it moving we like to move
it move it
we go out this way we'll have some
covers
maybe I can chill a little bit on
Michael's position
and they keep on running running
and running running and running [\h__\h] and
running on and running on it and running
running out how do I miss him twice he's
got a bubbly wobble head
[Applause]
do they even if I leave them on
autopilot I feel like they're slower
than if I was playing them
myself
the like the sniper if you leave him
doing his thing is mostly fine I feel
like
me
[Music]
people I'm blind
I don't see anything moving
[Music]
I swear I don't see [\h__\h]
you're lucky we're not taking your pot
too
nice shot
oh oh travel well travel goes so fast oh
wait they really want me to holy [\h__\h]
what whoa whoa
what the hell
fast
wait where do we have to continue right
where we found Lamar
all right let's go
let us go
you're out of your element he's not dead
he's not dead there we go there we go
there's some people here what are you
guys doing
the fake Lamar but we'll leave you the
weed huh where's the other one
again all right
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] stop moving
[Music]
is that winner there last time in the
last run when I was looking into Michael
the first time
how did I miss them
on it sometimes you have to look at the
bigger picture
ah
what what
I
silent
little prick come on look at me look at
me look at me look at me
I swear to God oh my God oh oh
they're coming they're coming they're
blasting
leave it to me I finally found them
sometimes I just need glasses I guess
it will be like that sometimes
feeling extra blinds today there's one
more
you do hide quite well
it should be like
oh it's gone
okay
all right I've never seen as many
[\h__\h] we're done we're done
we're done
Oh what now
hi thanks all right
[\h__\h] are you all right homie jump on me
though I didn't get you to come all the
way I thought that was a rose
all right get killed opportunity man you
always a pessimist nah [\h__\h] a real
cause in reality all them fools want to
clap your ass man trust that dog I
peeped out that wood chopping place when
we was up this way on that Devon Western
car lit which I still ain't been paid
for incidentally all secluded and [\h__\h]
stretching me up I'm like yeah that's
the perfect place it looks like a pass
man a place to clap some food you
beefing with man
sorry keep on talking
Tom I just thought we was going to
Parlay parlay [\h__\h] please all right
every time you leave the house fools try
to clap you every meat you set up
homie's there for the express purpose of
clapping your ass man you show cause I'm
sure there's been a few times no I'm
completely 100 sure every time [\h__\h]
whether you buying drugs selling drugs
or discussing drugs
man these streets is hard dog
maybe you forgot since you've been a
bettering yourself sitting in that house
on the hill looking down on the animals
in South Central and [\h__\h] man you know
it ain't like that do I my [\h__\h] because
that's the way it looked to me I'm
making the best out of what I'm giving
you know what I'm talking about I ain't
in some type of mentorship program the
only Mission and we're gonna do
something about that dog trust me man I
ain't got people teaching me that white
collar crime [\h__\h] ain't [\h__\h] change for
me and you ain't helping ain't helping
what the [\h__\h] you called it
me Michael Trevor we all came up here to
help mm-hmm Unholy [\h__\h] Trinity well
when these fools rolling together you
jealous of Michael and Trevor what
happened to me and you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] up
form gangsters [\h__\h] so I shouldn't have
called her right man I was doing
everything on my power to make sure you
wasn't clap I can make sure I ain't [\h__\h]
I ain't clap clearly you can't next time
homie don't come ain't my magic do come
don't bring them dudes
next time next time don't get your ass
in the situation all right good Frank
that's what happens in the hood know the
[\h__\h] don't not for everyone I'm one
of them dudes that it happens [\h__\h]
don't understand him one of them things
that it happens to
overpaid ass is presently accustomed to
man stressful
stress put us on this [\h__\h] man man we
gonna get on his ass man [\h__\h] that homie
look like I give a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I give a
[\h__\h] stress do what he do [\h__\h] want me
dead be dead themselves I ain't gonna
overreacting
I ain't gonna overreact to [\h__\h]
overreact man that [\h__\h] stretched tried
to get you killed
knew they was gonna book me yeah [\h__\h]
stress new everybody knew stress new
Tanisha new stress new and she don't
even come around the [\h__\h] Hood no
more damn that [\h__\h] Express janky like
that
mistress been screwing us from the start
like from back in the day from like the
other day dawg since after we went to
the recycling place and Dean ambalists
try to take us down but stretch put in
to work on D yeah man that's Survival
remember how angry his ass got
especially with you bringing them into
this [\h__\h] all right all right but tell
me this though if stretch was [\h__\h]
with your boy LD why you set us up with
the deal for the brick in the first
place he go off and make peace with the
Ballers come back and then put us on the
liquor
of the question marks because that's me
right now ripping us offers probably
stretches
follow their conversations makes sense
don't it and I ain't knowing man maybe
man stress got in with the Ballers when
he was inside played us as Mark's dog
but a bunch of them got booked what
they're talking about so stress says you
out there what are they doing a good
deal then you show up and save the day
yeah thankfully man it wouldn't even be
the same if your boy LD wasn't out here
getting in the [\h__\h] and FC wasn't
getting him out of it you know what I'm
talking about
no I don't know
that [\h__\h] was fun [\h__\h] don't tell me
you didn't enjoy scrapping like we did
back in the day it ain't back in the day
no more dawg but it felt like it was
okay fool it was fun saving your useless
ass one more [\h__\h] time yeah there you
go decent fun you should have seen your
face when I came in it wasn't so bad I
was so scared but we did it
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] but Michael death was
an unfortunate homie you probably
[\h__\h] yourself [\h__\h] you man I don't
care if I die it's a compliment if they
sending an army after a [\h__\h] they only
send like two of the little homies to
get you [\h__\h] you didn't look like they
was paying you no compliment [\h__\h] must
have just caught a glimpse of your ugly
ass [\h__\h] you think I'm some Angel come
to take your ass somewhere you never
going to you pray to your white man God
homie I'm going to the great playing
Beyond Where the Buffalo keep on roaming
and a little Squall [\h__\h] want me to
nut on their face all day [\h__\h] please
please
[Music]
all right um I you know I try I try to
understand the dialogue but
sometimes I I I just can't I don't
understand what the [\h__\h] we're all going
on about
I love the color Vibes you got going
there you got that metallic plus pearly
pearly accent yeah yeah I see you the
blue and the turquoise
is quite pretty in oh
[Music]
now mine's just tuned okay okay
that pretty much sums it up
now we go back into the city we finally
got Lamar said now he better not be
getting himself into trouble again
um
gotta be a gooch
a good
bro
a good dog
and they keep on calling them
Callie calls me dog sometimes
right I'm always like what
it's all good dog
if anything call me cats
I'm not a dog person man
say oh what's up cat
what's up kitty cat no I'll respond to
that oh
call me kitty cat oh that can be your
kitty cat meow meow meow meow
don't take care of this homie
you're a cat calling koala I guess that
was basically cat calling
the good old neighborhood
foreign I guess what we learned is
[\h__\h] don't think it ain't no fun to be
half [\h__\h] with the Hobbies [\h__\h] you
feel me my [\h__\h] yeah
real [\h__\h] my [\h__\h] uh
you know your [\h__\h] out here doing bad
man why don't you slide me a few dollars
or something you know what I'm talking
about it's hard out here in the set
[\h__\h] I know you don't win all the
Illuminati and [\h__\h] you know what I'm
saying leaving the street I told the cat
yeah that Illuminati and they're out
there way to keep a [\h__\h] down my [\h__\h]
I mean what thank you I guess it's
payment for all the work a [\h__\h] put in
for you getting them cars and [\h__\h] you
know what I'm talking about give a [\h__\h]
just enough money to get him a little 40
ounce and a bucket of chicken on the way
to the pole house is he unhappy like
that dog it's number one
I never got paid for the [\h__\h]
cars number two I said
no matter how many times
pose to my [\h__\h] I thought we was homies
for Life me too get out of this [\h__\h]
you live in a fantasy homie the best
thing you can hope for is a big turnout
for your [\h__\h] Funeral [\h__\h]
ain't nobody coming to your funeral what
man what if all the [\h__\h] times
I saved your life homie what about that
oh thank you homie like now give me a
[\h__\h] in the backfield
if your ass can just act civilized you
will get some work but instead you want
to be this gang-banging Mad Dog and
[\h__\h] oh my bad Mr Gold Card excuse me
sir thank you for helping out upholstery
[\h__\h] like me sir you can go now sir
thank you thank you thank you man I
think I am [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you Lamar yeah
[\h__\h] but that's some [\h__\h] that just got
past you my [\h__\h]
I could do better I can't hit my dude
man chill out all right yeah whatever
[\h__\h] you just hit me when you find out
what the true concept of friendship is
[Music]
anything about it [\h__\h] I'm in the turf
[\h__\h] if you remember what that is
what's up play y'all oh hello there
man I don't know y'all we done hey we
ain't done yet homie not yet nearly
man what the [\h__\h] y'all want me to do
kill the president [\h__\h] his wife or
something or invade some [\h__\h] country
no no something more sensible something
that's got to be done hey and the
timing's right you're gonna take old
Trevor and put him out to pasture oh me
Michael will be sensible but Trevor
Trevor won't be Trevor is a liability
that none of us can afford so true saved
you he saved both y'all asses and it's
unfortunate hey when we give you the
word you're gonna do this thing oh these
[\h__\h] man get Michael to do it me and
Trevor cool dog Michael can't do it
Trevor won't let him near that's why
it's up to you homie
hey who is that
don't worry about it [\h__\h] hey
flossing ass [\h__\h]
awesome
ah all the drama man I fought between
girls there's a lot of drama but
man man these boys
they got into a lot of trouble and they
have so much drama between themselves
yeah Lamar damn
boy drama is deadly
[Music]
dear Lord get your [\h__\h] together
all right
we're going to l
is that more Lamar or Lester
let's see what they got for us in store
we've been playing for almost four hours
I wonder how long I should play so that
the next part will be about the same
length and well balanced can you guys
let me know I don't want to have like
the next stream only be two hours you
know
I wanted to be at least at least three
hours s instead oh but with Michael then
I'm gonna go to l
oh oh should I end now then oh [\h__\h] I am
really close oh [\h__\h]
oh two more missions
oh [\h__\h] I should stop now and how long
do you think the next stream will be
roughly
I could start later if it's not so much
left we're gonna Read Super chats now
though I can do some side stuff oh yeah
maybe him
maybe do we have some question marks
without this question uh this question
mark maybe am I gonna do that one
three two four hours two and a half
free free if I take some time all right
okay that's decent a bit less than I
wanted to but okay
the question marks are side things right
wait was that not for me
I'm green though that's green
okay
okay let's do some question marks on one
at least
um and next time I'm also gonna start by
doing one or two question marks
get it to be a bit longer
foreign
and I think
Even If today was not the longest I mean
it feels like I've been only playing for
two hours or so but it's been close to
four hours
time passes by when you play GTA
but you know after we finish GTI I
really want to play some GTA online
because this looks fun looks kind of fun
and um not only with um Miko senpa and
Amelia but also with you guys perhaps oh
I take it I can count on you
at the smoking we're what yeah we're
gonna bring down I'm gonna get the
PlayStation 5 version in a public place
it's very I guess
confused are you [\h__\h] if being a martyr
means to smoke good weed
what the hell like a little warm-up you
know before you go and collect this
[\h__\h] creep
before I what you know get the supplies
it doesn't look like a creeper without
smoke
you know cerebral stuff that's gonna get
the people up off their feet protesting
man I don't know it sounds kind of
[\h__\h] to me
ah yeah he does look like really so
normal he's just trying to catch me
that's how they do it don't they
you offered it to me dude
try can't you see the aliens
what else are you taking
[\h__\h] is garbage
anyway just get the stuff
it's a revolution and then call me crazy
[\h__\h]
okay no he doesn't seem like a fed he's
really into this San Andreas needs you
I'll text you where this stuff is real
quick before someone sees you and look
out for the cops and the Monsters
monsters on you this guy's cute
I Frank in the car at some point I want
to get a car that can bring the top down
100 this is the one criteria I have I
like many types of cars okay I'm not
picky
it's gonna be hard to choose
but it needs to be able to take the top
off that's like
the the most important thing summer is
the most fun if you have a car
I can take the top off
and the cute lady that can take
[Music]
he said lose the cups
because of the car I just stolen because
of the question mark thingy that I'm
doing
Slow Down slow down kiwawa
oh speaking of taking this half off
I you know her whole summer is like a
thing what why is there a helicopter bit
yeah
why is there why are you guys so extreme
about this
tunnel baby tunnel Time Tunnel Vision I
don't know now follow me here are there
what if I stay here are they gonna come
no they literally saw me
driving in here but they do not
understand there's an option to follow
me into this place
ah
hopefully no train is coming
this is so good uh yeah oh nice what I
was saying is um
you know whole summer apparently now
we're okay with showing our swimsuits on
YouTube again so what do you think I
asked
remember when I first revealed this
outfit
I don't know if it's gonna be possible
but I asked for it
um
good
since it's basically already rigged you
know so it's already in there hookah
Papa Drew it and you know
it's a question mark a mission finished
now
yeah we'll we'll see I can't make any
promises but I did ask and I mean holy
summer you know if that's okay then my
my boobies need to be set free as well
release the hook yeah
yeah
highlighted area
I don't know what's what anymore
what's this P question mark
Beverly
is that a side thing
release the hook
ah the paparazzi guy
oh
all right I'll go see wait isn't he
moving though or is he set in stone
at least that's a sad thing okay I'll do
that and then we'll probably might gonna
end it
is
[Music]
censored of Beverly Mission oh I want to
censor it
is it worse than the strip club because
the strip club honestly wasn't so bad
he's returning here are the dates for
the pickups ah
oh and now there he goes oh finally all
right well then I'll go here
wait are those things moving
how do I it's such a big area
move move fast they say you're funny
this is really a Time issue
huh
what the Beverly thing is super young
boy really
um well not doing that now because now I
got the dates
got some [\h__\h] to do
those whenever oh
now I'm on the way
I'm on the highway to
side missions
highway to side mission
and today went so smoothly
I'm I'm sad I already have to end this
part again
I'm playing until the very end time wise
we could probably even do it but now
let's take our
I'll take our time I guess and we can
why is it so drifty
we can enjoy this game for a little
while longer
oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
AC DC I guess
[Music]
okay I am here like how do I know what
exactly it is though in this big area
that I'm picking up
nice nice turn
what
who is this the fool running around
after you I found the truck you wanted
hey oh God no hurry I needed in Vespucci
in the next couple of hours and watch
yourself I hear the cops have been
snooping around
cool thing
I'm seeing it
oh
Laura all right
we bring it to this booty
pops
please have mercy on me
I don't want to get in trouble no [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] had eyes on the plate
oh
off-road hiding is best right
maybe like here
how about here is this good
I think this is good
or a dog or not
I'm in the bush
come on come on how [\h__\h] slow is this
thing
they're up there they're above me they
can't see me
can they
oh
um
I tried to escape like in this kind of
area before Oh no
oh no oh no I I'll try to drive into the
tunnel
man it's got to be a better way to get
weed legalized in this [\h__\h]
oh oh they ain't following me now
maybe maybe here is good
um
they don't seem to know where I am now I
think
[\h__\h] twice
yeah yeah okay okay that one's coming
though but please don't please don't
look at me please
what the [\h__\h] I'm never gonna lose these
[\h__\h]
[Music]
really really stupid brains these empty
stands what the [\h__\h]
how do I get back up by the way oh
all right
we're just driving endlessly eventually
oh can I squeeze through noise hello
hello stay stay out of their way stay
out of the way
this is good so far
yeah
I didn't see that
where the [\h__\h] is supposed to be I'm
close to this no wasn't it like um there
I'll try to get towards them or is the
time limit only um
losing the the cops
[\h__\h] no it's General telling yeah one
minute damn I gotta get the [\h__\h] on yeah
I did not need that [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
smoking it better be worth it oh [\h__\h] at
one minute can I make it
this is pretty slow car as well
I got some so far I'm
I'll come so far
but in the end it doesn't even matter 30
seconds
[Music]
20 20 that's impossible that's like
literally impossible
foreign
[Music]
I wouldn't have made it it's still so
far
this mission is not fun don't try to
beat it oh man I was just trying to get
some more content in because I'm sure I
don't want to I want to end the stream
already
trying to spend some time with you guys
ah
when we're in the middle of it I I kind
of feel feel compelled to finish it
okay
try number two but let's try to stay
relatively in that area [\h__\h]
had eyes on the plate
okay okay
okay
[Music]
oh my God [\h__\h] off I swear to God come
on come on how [\h__\h] slow is this
thing
maybe we should go visit Olympus
exhibit and pimp this ride
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
[Applause]
man this gotta be a better way to do we
legalized in this [\h__\h]
[Music]
they're like all my tippy toes oh God
thank you for helping me turn oh God I
can't move
um
[Music]
now I got three stars not good not good
not good not good bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
[Applause]
okay okay
mm-hmm
oh my God
I I was considering going that way
that's why I [\h__\h] up
changing my mind
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey what's up there what are you doing
are you doing
ah [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] man
no
[Music]
I I don't know this city well enough
even now to really know where to escape
you have a visual
um
that is such a compliment damn I gotta
get the [\h__\h] off because in K-pop you
know
the cutest girl in the group
um I guess it doesn't have to be a girl
it's the visual yeah yeah yeah there's
like every K-pop member gets like a
position that's the main dancer the main
singer the youngest member and then
there's the visual you know so they're
saying I'm the visual
s
all right
[\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
this mission
okay
only retry can I cancel it I'm playing
how do I cancel the mission
go to the right not the left here keep
the water substance flowing San Andreas
uh where exactly
somewhere here
so far they're not on to me I guess they
don't start until I leave this road
at this this area and go into an actual
Road
this this split this path
is ticking yeah well
it's not ah
mm-hmm
oh
police still cool
where do I go
yeah nice landing
but once I go on my way aren't learned
the police gonna try to get me again
doesn't change anything does it
not that way okay
[Music]
this one
foreign
so far they did not find me
but yeah I have to have to get there
hmm
I'm safe what do you mean I'm safe
I mean I'm safe
so if I go to the big street now but
it's still not enough time
we're trying to go on the big Street
try my best here let's go let's go let's
go let's go no time to lose
it's really the shortest path
it's all
in one minute
okay but at least now I know what the
rent happens so if we fail again
I know kind of yeah
does this really am I driving faster
than I would be
without the slow motion
I guess I am
all right let's use it as long as I
possibly can
[Applause]
oh God
that was just too much
[Music]
try number two but in 20 seconds
impossible
yeah no
oh I'm so speedy
[Music]
I even took the wrong route [\h__\h] hell
oh my soul snare all right all right
okay last time last time last time less
than last time
[Music]
oh yeah
okay well go
this time
you'll do it right
hopefully
this is
[Music]
why is the time so [\h__\h] tight man
yeah go down here
down here going down here
it is don't just don't die do a flip
yeah nice flip nicely
10 out of 10 flip and then we just chill
a little bit here you guys tell me when
it's safe to go is it safe to go how did
you guys even know that it's safe
is it safe
we said
oh Bob I go up here now
okay
I can't go up
this car is so [\h__\h] weak
using special ability for a turn
okay
[Music]
all right all right all right all right
okay we have two minutes 40.
at all
now let's save some extra time yeah wow
on the highway at least I feel like
I won't lose control so badly
yeah yeah oh my God
okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
okay
oh it's raining men
hallelujah it's raining man
oh
yeah
[\h__\h] weather how's the weather over
there guys
I hope y'all are having beautiful
sunshine and rainbows
gray Sunny clear skies beautiful they're
nice pouring down actually raining oh oh
you know Green can be nice too
too much speed I'm so sorry can I still
make it
I hope I hope I hope
I feel like I'm so so far away but in
combination of the scale
honestly aren't you kind of forced to
use the skill in this mission
I don't see how you could do it without
[Music]
oh I'm getting used to it round turn
again
foreign
if this ain't it then I say [\h__\h] it damn
I gotta get the [\h__\h] on
[Music]
I feel like I can make it
40 seconds I'm really truly pretty much
there
oh my God I don't know if I want to do
the other ones though
it's really obnoxious oh okay I'm here
I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm here
oh no oh no
[Applause]
I swear to God
all right it's all good it's all good
it's all good it's all good it's all
good
[Music]
[Laughter]
did your heart go Doki Doki guys have my
pizza hell no fool is me I'm here well
done hey true Crusader for civil
liberties uh where you follow it's way
too paranoid now look man won't you come
down and check this I got [\h__\h] to do man
yeah well I'll send someone when I know
oh it's clear okay be too careful and
I'm dealing with some composting issues
it is a bad burrito burrito whatever man
breakfast burrito oh why didn't they
just end it there I didn't do [\h__\h]
oh Mission pass on it wait that's it Oh
I thought I had to do like in the other
area as well was it like either one of
them and that's fine that's it is that
yeah
I know there's one more
never mind there's another one I don't
know but no I'm not in the mood anymore
man
I've kind of ruined it for me that was
lame
um
I Read Super Chat so
you all are welcome to stay let's get
moving
to my office
ah Halloween outfit
oh
hello
it is as always a [\h__\h] mess in here
let me just put the shot where it
belongs to
uh-huh and um
get rid of this
what music were we listening to
yesterday did I have some kind of
Halloween music probably not
um
I love this one
[Music]
oh my I'm sorry I'm sorry
I think that was probably louder for you
guys than it was for me
okay oh wait I remember from last year
it had some
cute decent
um
like Halloweenish track yeah this one
this one this one
yeah yeah oh that's kind of nostalgic
Now isn't it do you guys remember this
one
just remember
it's spooky
foreign
costume it was hard for me to take off
the French costume because I love it so
much but I will wear it again at some
point
but you know French costume didn't go so
well with my guns and so on
[Music]
um
I have to make priorities gotta go thank
you for watching
she's like legit scary holy [\h__\h] like
it's not even just vampy I don't know
Eden made look her face so scary
the mouth is so scary in the eyes quiet
[Music]
look at her
okay closing Grand Theft Auto five
[Music]
did you guys see
see the Pokemon
uh thingy with the girl with the
supposedly something like a YouTuber
she's a streamer I guess she's not I
don't think they would see her as a
beach where they see her as a streamer
though
did you see it
when I was watching it I was thinking oh
my Oshie
it's not gonna lie this and indeed he
did [\h__\h] on it
[Laughter]
he made fun of it
yeah yeah he was very upset about it and
I I knew it I knew it I mean I I think
it's um you know it's if you if you're
like
um acquainted to like all all these like
I don't know
Japanese
things just Japanese things you know
this this kind of anime
overly overly excited anime voice acting
with
um the script holy [\h__\h] my monitor is
freaking out with my right monitor ah
it's been like this for a while actually
it's so weird so sometimes
um like just now for example maybe you
guys can help me understand just now I
moved my OBS window in the middle screen
I moved it around and when it was in a
certain position in the middle screen
suddenly the right monitor started
flickering and now I moved into a
different position the OBS window in the
middle screen monitor and it stopped the
right monitor stopped flickering and
yeah recently oh when I move it back
there it's flickering like insane again
but it's not even anything on the
Monitor and it depends on I don't know
I'm not quite sure what it is but
sometimes it flickers sometimes it
doesn't I tried reconnecting the cables
and restarting the PC it's been going on
for like a couple days maybe two three
weeks even now maybe two weeks
but if it's a loose connection then why
the [\h__\h] is it about whether or not my
OBS window is in a certain position and
it's not only OBS like it has nothing to
do with OBS but I don't know something's
weird even when OBS is closed sometimes
it flickers
um
[Music]
oh let me see I think I changed
something oh actually but did I do that
before or after
let me try
[Music]
the the right monitor is currently on uh
one 144
H set should I try lowering it
foreign
so I lowered it to 120.
no it's still kind of flickering
it's actually for the past couple days
it was mostly fine but now it's like a
ring like
this again
[Music]
oh my God
I don't know why okay
but now it's calm again
now I want to be calm again
uh whatever I don't know man
does it black out no it's it doesn't
black out at all it's like
um it's hard to describe
it's like I don't know weird flickering
I still see what's going on on the
monitor but it's like
really fast flickering
slightly in those cave I already checked
the cables a while ago
oh I don't think it's the cables
maybe a driver update
no it's just where you have to monitors
with different refresh rates really
let me see the other one
is currently at 60 because that's the
most it can do anyway
oh wow whatever right now it's calm
mostly
so I'll just keep it like this for now
I'm confused
let's read some super tacos last time I
read the karaoke Super Chat so
what do we have now
I might have to go to an idol meeting
uh hold a talk maybe is this whole talk
do I have to read a whole talk I think
next
okay I'll go to an idol meeting and
should I open that I'll go bring some
donuts I have some open Donuts some mini
mini sugar donuts let me bring those
okay I'll BRB
I'll be right back please wait for me
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello
no no I'm here
don't look at quinoa outside she's
scaring she's cursed
Russia got some donuts
it looks awesome
I only ate one donut since I bought them
why is there
no never mind never mind it looks like
some islands are missing that shouldn't
be missing what they're like
it's an optical illusion
all right oh I had these in the freezer
they're really cold wow ice cold donuts
oh
[Music]
um
oh
my God
just for now to calm down the hunger a
bit but not too much
what flavor nothing you just have like
powdered sugar that's pretty much it my
favorite donut is like in Japan they
have
um they have like Ponder English it's a
donut called pondering really famous
it's a classic donut
that's I would say could be my favorite
and then I also just like simple sugar
glazed donuts but I never find them
around here only in like proper donut
stores but in the supermarket they only
have like boring Donuts not the best
ones
[Music]
Krispy Kreme
um
I had Krispy Kreme before but not in
America
unfortunately uh
foreign
[Music]
how
I might check it later thank you
thank you thank you
okay I'll eat one more
no because I have leftover from what I
cooked yesterday
yeah
last night I was like I don't want to
cook I already cooked yesterday but then
I was gonna push my day off and tomorrow
I'll end the stream late so tomorrow
I'll be too late to cook and now I have
time so I should cook now so I forced
myself and it was funny but it was yummy
not funny funny yummy
um
lick zucchini zucchini Curry pasta
[Music]
you want some donuts too guys you're
half added I have six more Donuts
[Music]
foreign
sharing is caring
let me honestly let me go to audio stock
this is
random things time yay
what is
the old of Joy whatever called in
Japanese I wonder
um foreign
[Music]
Wikipedia entry yeah there it is
and then from the Wikipedia entry I go
to the Japanese one and here it is
yeah let's type that into
all your stuff do you have something
oh yes
I think that could be it
oh yeah
[Music]
oh it's a piano version but there it is
how beautiful let's sing it
in German
let me try
oh it's a kilo this feels pretty low
[Music]
but it starts I actually know this song
so well
[Music]
ah wait this one
nope here it starts foreign
[Music]
foreign
forgot
[Music]
oh
where does it continue
[Music]
no okay that's where it ends not an
adult so it's not not exactly the same
is pretty
well holding a shotgun
what something weird about this
oh this one this one is really short but
another version
[Music]
yes
there's a music box version
I'll listen to that one
lovely music box
[Music]
magical
a lot of stock is such a pleasure
[Music]
version
what it sounds like those YouTube music
thingies like you know when when someone
does a vlog or something I don't know
does YouTube videos sounds exactly like
that but why the [\h__\h] are they using
oath to Joy as a melody
[Music]
so today I will show you five life hacks
this is how you get rid of of uh
distance in your
t-shirts the fastest just add even more
stains to it until it is completely
black we will never know that it once
used to be a white T-shirt super smart
and it leave a like And subscribe now
let's go on to the second hit blind bag
if you're sick you're sick of having
your cats a little box always full how
about you teach your cat how to use your
own toilet the fastest way to doing that
is get rid of the little blocks and it
has no choice but to use your own toilet
right at least if you can eat a smart if
not then you'll [\h__\h]
smash that like button
I can't come up with any more
spontaneously
those live hacks they elude me
often used as a Christmas song
oh I know the only time where I really
remember hearing it is Once In in with
our like school we went to like a
some kind of like music
um Opera kind of venue and one of the
things they played that we all sang
together because everybody had the the
like a
sheet of lyrics on their seat we all
sang it together it's like what what's
going on here but I had fun because it's
actually like a a pretty song
it's actually quite enjoyable to sing
along to
um
no we were not a clock but no it was
just one of the things they performed on
that day and then this one we all sang
together for some reason
they were just doing the instruments on
the stage but then everybody was I guess
everybody was the cool
yeah the melody is so catchy and and
melodic so pretty
excellent pronunciation are you sure
about that are you are you are you lying
to me
anyway let's go back to Halloween music
sorry for the little
mix up there
um
foreign
no can opener places still kind of new
stuff at high heat I will open it up in
less than 10 minutes did you come up
with this one yourself just now
um
[Music]
London
I don't even know someone just asked me
if I know Austria's national hymn and I
can't really recall it well right now
[Music]
countries national hymn I feel like in
America you would kind of know it
because
there's so many times occasions where
like famous singers like Beyonce and so
on sing it in like big events and so on
but this doesn't really happen much in
Austria to be honest like I
I don't remember a single time where I
heard
the Austrian national hymn besides in
school
in but like in before Junior High even
so
yeah I feel like in America it's very
very uh
easy to get it hammered into your hand
but I don't think it's really common in
Austria
who doesn't have one unless you believe
in song of music what the [\h__\h] are you
talking about every country has one
foreign
way many times in school
in America
maybe at the Olympics uh
I guess maybe but I don't
yeah okay World Cup yeah Sports made me
but I still in sports even not as much
as in in America right I feel like in
Austria we just don't get exposed to it
as much as other countries might get
exposed to it and I don't even watch
sports so if I don't watch sports that
I'm even less exposed to it than other
people
hmm
I mean if I quickly listen back into it
I would probably remember but right now
since I'm in my head all I hear is
[Music]
all that there is in my hand right now
and that kind of mixes up a little bit
with the Austrian him right though
well this song that I was just singing
that's at least a European hymn
that's at least something
huh national anthem in him I think it's
the same thing no
what's the kfb hymn
any kiwaba original song Maybe
maybe Sparks
are you Sparks oh watch what he went
true
[Music]
ah so nostalgic
that's enough
uh okay let's read this come on come on
[Music]
Holo talk if I am missing bye
as I said we got along really well yeah
I'm happy it went so well
some people like I feel like
I feel like Japanese people who are
watching it who understood what she was
saying were not under this impression I
feel like only like super over worried
um
I guess
almost white nights we're like oh my God
what are you doing stop you're forcing
her she's so nervous why are you putting
her into this position
first of all it's not like I forced her
to suddenly sing like a really serious
difficult route like
you know big song it was just a joke it
wasn't even supposed to be like a real
performance it was just a joke
and I speak Japanese and honestly all
the comments like that were all in
English like what are you doing
but she was honestly fine the only
reason why she was like you know she
seemed like she was
um nervous or anything it wasn't that
she was looking for the lyrics and she
couldn't find it and and I I agree if I
would be put in such a situation
suddenly I would also uh like my my
brain would be blank and I wouldn't know
where to look for the lyrics of the song
and the melody and all that so okay that
was a little bit of a so-called mucha
booty out of nowhere but uh she's an
Entertainer she's been doing this for
years
this is not like
putting someone in a situation that is
absolutely unusual for them and you know
yeah yeah and yeah I made sure that
there's no dead air and I tried to keep
her like uh try to keep the mood
generally
high and uplifting yeah I don't think
there was a need to Baby her like that
so man I saw a lot of people in the chat
being like over worried way too over
worried
but I don't think they quite understood
why I understand but I took so much time
it was not because she was nervous I
mean she may have been generally nervous
but she was about the whole whole attack
she was I was also nervous we were both
nervous about the whole talk in general
but that situation itself was just
because she was like having troubles
finding
um what she needed in such a certain
moment but that's fine like what the
hell some improvisation and spontaneous
content that's fun and a lot of people
liked that a lot of people were happy
about it doji dochi live performance and
I thought that's I knew it I knew people
would be happy to have that so
I felt like why not why not try it it's
not like a really difficult song
yeah they're not five-year-old children
yeah
and to me she seemed open to doing it
so what the hell
no
yeah
so I just I just don't understand some
people
man they were bathing here but I just
want to make sure that you guys know she
was absolutely in my from my point of
view she was comfortable with it and we
talked afterwards too and she was fine
with it I asked her I'm sorry I hope I
didn't do anything to pressure you or so
she was like no it's all good oh it was
fun thank you so much blah blah blah so
yeah
sometimes yeah people baby us too much
not only I am in this case but I think
all of us often get babied a lot
yeah when we don't need to be babied
yeah
we're adults okay
and as I said like we're used to this
kind of stuff we're entertainers like
this is what would we do
not none of our streams are scripted
so we're used to doing things
spontaneously we try to entertain people
spontaneously our streams ain't scripted
so
squeezing in a little little fun thing
in the in the middle of that I think
what the hell let's do it
uh
I don't have a script in front of me the
only thing I'm reading is a chat
yeah
you can take out the pacifier for the
rest of the stream ah cause they wanna
baby me no no no please don't be me
you super snake Mario thank you
I moved my Jenkins
oh scripted
yeah just wanted to make sure you guys
know because we got along well and I
don't wanna I don't want that to be like
clouded and ruined by other people who
are not part of this relationship
between me and I am a senpai trying to
make it into something bad that it's not
like trying to create a situation that
didn't exist
you know what I mean
I don't want it to be ruined by such a
thing
so let's read super chats JK it's monkey
thank you sooner thank you soon oh thank
you glad you like bad reputation that
was one of the songs I randomly was
reminded of and put into my set list
because pay for our scripted comments on
your pre-recorded videos
ha
and
mm-hmm
no place Carl oh wow I don't know yet
they're still in the show the evolutions
I think I'll decide
um based on that although I honestly
don't really care that much no no I'll
go by by the gym trainers and so on
I think that was my plan
I think other people probably decide on
based on maybe other things but I want
I'm gonna decide on the cutest NPCs
hmm
thank you
thank you Stephen
even if I was pressuring her a little
bit it was for the sake of good content
and I think she understood that as well
she was fine and Cocoon thanks for the
pinky
loved yokia okay for me personally you
are the best Idol ever I know I'm biased
because I only watch you but it's simply
true your voice is incredible and so
soothing and Angelic to me I can listen
to you all day you're so immensely
talented you are breathtaking thank you
thank you indeed bias
just a little pressure
I had no sword or knife whatsoever
pointed at her and at any given time
together
[Music]
Eternal dive part two Danica shootings
opening
[Music]
did you guys
look closely at the opening any of you
guys
does anyone have to say something about
the new opening
because I don't think anyone noticed
yeah I thought so it was it was too
too hidden pudding
pudding is too hidden
I mean it was supposed to be hidden but
not too hidden it almost every scene
of the city like City shots you can see
whole life members hidden somewhere on
top of buildings and so on oh Nathan you
noticed thank you
yeah I I I asked putting to hide some
previous couple talk participants in the
background but and I said you can make
them really small so that they won't be
too obvious but then pudding made them
so [\h__\h] tiny I guess like relatively
more or less realistically sized but not
really even then like on the top of a
[\h__\h] skyscraper
um I guess that was still too big if you
say look at this realistically but it's
really hard to notice so you guys gotta
watch there's not every previous whole
talk participant on there but quite a
lot I think like at least
10 to 15.
they are really tiny yeah and in some
scenes there's uh two or three even
so afterwards yeah have fun trying to
find them they're really small
um
[Music]
because I still
that is
[Music]
I don't think people would notice when I
when I saw that opening I was like
I will have to tell people to look
really closely otherwise they're not
gonna find them
yeah have fun finding all the members
yeah yeah yeah oh if I'm playing Marion
nice
okay but pay attention to me now
they are yes really small it's coming to
hunt yeah yeah I was even thinking of
adding some more uh later on
eventually
you see a tiny Shiva
oh nice nice
no as I said they're not all of them in
there anyway so my goal is not to put
all of them in it anyway because it will
just be too many kind of crowded
but I might like switch them out every
once in a while who knows I think I
found Kiana well I'm just like really
obviously and bigly placed that is not
an accomplishment
yeah
Marine is on the boat yeah the rooftops
are very crowded already
lots of skyscraper extensions
foreign
they're so small you can sometimes not
even make out who it is
[Music]
thank you oh it's not in there no no no
no no no no no it's pretty big always
have fun guys
scavenger hunt
oh thank you for the red super chat
attention congratulations on the season
two of whole talk yeah it has been a
while and it's the most welcomed please
expose more we don't know about I
understand bye thank you
ah to be honest after this long break it
was a little bit difficult to get back
to whole talk to like re restart it
again and
you know I get I guess I got a little
bit too comfortable without the whole
talk but it is after all something I'm
really proud of so
brought it back and we're back into the
game
um I had a little bit of a
discussion in my head with myself
yesterday
thinking like about interviewing whole
life English or ID members
oh it's I I imagine it to be kind of
awkward when let's say I interview for
example Iris
and I said if I interview English
speaking members I turn it around and I
I translate them to Japanese but it's
kind of awkward I feel like it's awkward
translating her to Japanese when she
speaks fluent Japanese herself
you know what I mean like
it's kind of like
awkward because first of all she
understands everything I'm saying
and second of all it's like she anything
she wants to share with uh Japanese
speaking people she already is able to
share herself yeah
I did the same but it didn't fit quite
so awkward for Coco Senpai for some
reason because it was still my original
format I guess translating from
uh Japanese to English but then we
switch it up and suddenly I feel so
awkward about it
um Kelly no Kelly I think still makes
sense because I'll be honest her
I think there's many many things that
she can say in English that she can't
say in Japanese so it still makes sense
in my opinion
um but yeah like Lisa for example if I
were to do an interview with me so I
think she also is like fluent in
Japanese so hmm But then if I say okay
let's do it without translation then
kind of defeats the purpose of whole
talk you know
which I guess I can make an exception
but
I think I think Japanese people would be
happy about having the translation in
there but then I I maybe I'm
overthinking but I do feel awkward about
it just thinking about it thinking about
me sitting there
interviewing someone who speaks possibly
even more fluent Japanese than I do
and then like Anya for example as well
um and then and then
I I sit there it feels like kind of
almost like like it should I I'm not is
it really
um appropriate like
shouldn't it even be switched like if
someone's better than Japanese than me
then shouldn't they be translating me
like how how dare I put myself into the
position where I'm translating someone
who speaks for the Japanese of me and
then again like for for Japanese members
the original purpose was they don't
speak English so I want them to be able
to reach audiences
that they couldn't normally reach in
terms of you know giving them actually
more than just translated subtitled
clips and itsy bitsy tiny bitsies uh of
English here and there like hello
and thank you
when you just keep translating and
directly interview her in Japanese oh
but that's kind of boring because I know
I have a lot of English viewers in whole
talk always as well
like it's always like a big
portion of English and Japanese speakers
I don't know I'm thinking too much about
it probably I am aware of that
[Music]
well with myth with myth I feel like I
don't have to worry too much because
um I feel like after me uh inachan
I feel like is the best in Japanese
and then Cali but then even then I don't
feel awkward about translating them
because
even though Ina is so good she normally
doesn't speak Japanese in her streams so
you know it's not like she
constantly communicates in Japanese with
her friends and I'm all thinking I'm
overthinking I'm absolutely overthinking
but with me if I don't worry so much
then however when if it comes to Iris
but okay that's so that's still a long
way to that so I'll think about it when
that time comes
yeah maybe I'll just even stop after
first gen Yen and then first gen ID
and then I'll just stop maybe who knows
I think this awkwardness
I'll decide when the time comes
we'll cross the bridge when we get there
exactly
[Music]
there's a talk show
but as I said that kind of doesn't make
a whole talk anymore that's not whole
talk anymore
I'll think about it when the time comes
though
yeah I think it would be fine to end it
officially at some point after en1 id1
but
I don't know it would also just be sad
to completely
let go of it
I feel like even though it's quite time
consuming I do want to do it
until the end of my days in a whole life
because my baby it's my baby
to be my baby
um
yeah whatever whatever I'll think about
it when the time comes yes I said Thank
You Felix sound
hi T thank you for the words of the chat
as well
thank you so much also hashtag cold talk
yay
I was after that whole talk I was on
Twitter for
hours going through all the tags and
replies
looking at everybody's Impressions and
opinions
I was so hyped I was so excited yeah
I was so proud of the new studio too
um I'm happy that it had such a smooth
comeback thankfully I was quite nervous
because it was the first time in a long
time I was wondering if my translation
skills wouldn't be as smooth anymore but
no it was absolutely fine I was I was um
um I feel like I I didn't lag behind or
anything I was typing while she was
talking as usual in my little memo pad
and I'm translating as as usual actually
Japanese people I saw them praising me
for
um translating setsubunt so perfectly
they were like holy [\h__\h] she did not
only
translated like you know
um I know
oh it's Christmas you know something
like that no she even translated the
background of it
and explained like what exactly it is
and they were like holy [\h__\h] like that
that's another whole step that she took
there
foreign
God thank God
I warned I am a senpai before and I told
her oh it's the first time in a long
time please talk slowly and please
speak in simple Japanese but I tell them
I tell that every whole talk guest
always and I feel like
um most of the time
they all immediately forget about it and
just talk normally as they usually do
there was just one member I forgot who
it was
who took it quite too hard and really
spoke really slowly and easily and I
noticed that I was like actually this is
going too slow for me I'm like I'm
typing typing the translations I'm like
this is too slow
um yeah it might have been successive I
feel like there was something there yeah
she wasn't only doing that because she
was tired she was also talking doing
that because I think she took it to
heart
I
don't know there was at least some one
member who did that I'm like ah
I guess you didn't have to take it that
seriously
just like in the back of your mind
somewhere there please keep in mind
that I have to translate what you say
pasta yeah
now let me check in my app how the
toilet is going oh 54 full
hmm
so yeah I have this app for the for the
toilet and oh and I named it I named the
toilet the toilet can have a name it's
called Evangelion
is
of course oh yeah isn't that outfitting
last time uh
no way last time a cat entered
was it half past 4 P.M it's 10 p.m now
sometimes I noticed indeed that it
doesn't it doesn't always
sends them but when I stream they're
usually just sleeping for hours so maybe
they're really just sleeping
but 54 full is a good sign
my cats are mixed on it
what do you mean mix are they using it
did you do you still have the other
toilet for them accessible because I
literally forced them I closed the door
to the other toilet
they had to use
either
the new toilet or just the whole
apartment and they were good kitties so
they used
the the neutral but yeah I did watch
like some videos about that toilet and
um like cat experts were saying that
some cats just don't like this kind of
thing so much because it feels kind of
like there's no space in there it looks
huge from the outside but inside it's
pretty what's the word
not Spacey
so a cramped yeah that might be a little
bit
intimidating and uncomfortable for
some cats
yeah
yeah but besides that
some cats if they're used to like having
an open Toilet you know with no top
then this might also be
a reason why they don't like it
but I'm so glad mine like it you're
really making me want to buy one myself
it's expensive but I think it's worth
the money
I feel like it also saves cat litter
I feel like it does save on cat litter
and uh on time and Sanity and also it's
not stinky at all the the smell gets way
more contained like a million times more
contained
then
um then when you have like a normal
litter box
I've noticed that in comparison to my
old cat toilet
how about a ton of soft stuff I saw a
test on that uh when you know that your
cat has like diarrhea or so you should
just turn the timer uh to like 15
minutes or so
then it has more time to
um you know
get mixed and and solidified
with the the
litter how expensive we talk are we
talking I think there's a couple
different versions but the one I got is
I think like 500 bucks
I think
yeah and also I guess well uh from the
video that I saw where they tested that
not with like actual
cat diarrhea but like just some kind of
lotion to show how it moves around there
uh when it does the cycle and it's still
like liquid it actually it didn't even
make that much of a mess at all and
actually still even in liquid form it
went down the poop hole pretty well
um
I'd hate to spend five dollars on my
castle yeah that is the biggest risk but
I was really thinking mine wouldn't like
it but they liked it and you know if
they don't like it you can just sell it
for the next person
to the next version sorry I'm talking so
much about this thing but it's like so
fascinating to me I'm so happy I got it
yay
ah I'm so happy about it
really the the the the smell there's
like no smell at all like whoa
whoa It's contained so well because the
moment somebody poops in there it
immediately gets sent into the
into the poop hole compartment and then
it closes so unless you open it you
won't smell a thing
Hmm this sounds like a godsend
um
there's also cats out there that are way
less tolerant of like
um
unclean litter boxes like some want you
to clean it every day and some cats
don't mind you leaving it for like five
days
so if yours is really on it'll
intolerant then this toilet will also be
really good for them because it's always
clean always
I want to clean my cats every day well
you say that now but like when you own
them for like five six seven years at
some point you're like
[Laughter]
uh
sometimes you get lazy
wouldn't the house get stinky I don't
know man
do you have it in the middle of the
living room then yes
yeah
okay so yeah it gets annoying definitely
oh well
anyway
I gotta tell them little Curry connected
the rabbit is working fine
oh
now I guess it's just missing the
smaller presents I wonder what it's
gonna be and when they're gonna arrive
oh and uh
what's it called again
the bean bag is also still stinky in
terms of it still stinks like you know
manufacturer plastic whatever
not very nice smelling but it's a bit
less than before and also my cats both
love it
yeah
both chunkers and smoothie have spent
time sleeping on top of it more smoothie
than chunkers though but yeah they like
it
so it has some use hooray
maybe if I ever have like friends over
to watch a movie together so I'll I'll
make use of it too
as like a seating option
um
giant cat bed it really is a giant cat
pad
House movie was able to sleep on it
because like you know she would be
sleeping on it and I would go to her and
like face palm face bump I would put my
my whole face on her big belly and I
would Breathe In and I would be like
holy [\h__\h] I was sleeping here you guys
you cats are more sensitive about smells
than I am aren't ya but holy [\h__\h] this
if I get my my my face really close to
the bean bag it's terrible I would not
be able to sleep with that in my nose
um surprised they don't mind that smell
um
oh my God I have to stop talking
[Music]
too much but this I needed to get it out
I needed to talk about it I'm sorry
proto-free glass
okay out of the turret no it doesn't
work like that
can never get rid of me Alexander
Giovanni dangerous
[Music]
thank you Windows Task Manager hello
thank you
oh yeah yeah there were some window
sounds there
questions
[Music]
oh yeah see fun boy
um God Everyone likes this new stage it
was a bit hard to make since I had to do
the whole set design by myself and I'm
not used to to modeling high definition
environments really glad people like it
yeah I'm glad we you know found a way to
making it so that it keeps its original
charm and still looks freshened up
I like it actually seafoam boys first
attempt uh was like
uh he kind of made this office
into the whole talk Studio kind of
and I unfortunately had to say sorry
maybe for another time we can make this
office into a 3D uh Studio I would love
to see that one day but I I still want
the holotalk studio to be in the whole
talk Street I wanted to be separate so
yeah then we completely restarted it
from scratch again that's also another
reason why it took longer than expected
but it was fine because I had travels
finding a good schedule with my guests
anyway
everything was being delayed so
in the end it's actually ended up
working quite well yeah no I'm not gonna
show it don't worry
one day one day one day I really want
this office in Freedom would be really
nice would be cool
yeah
and I do understand what you mean but I
think you said it on Twitter so maybe
you're used to you know those kind of
maps that you made for us for VR
those kind of like smaller
I don't know how to describe it
small kind of objects and stuff not so
realistic but this whole talk Studio was
supposed to look a bit more yeah
realistic than cartoony yeah yeah
um
yeah I think you did a good job it looks
really elegant really polished
yeah yeah
never use the other side of the office
as a chair or the people getting cold
and you know about
don't know how to use it and I wanted I
don't want to just suddenly show you oh
yeah by the way I have this no I wanted
to have some kind of
purpose so I I'm I'm constantly even
yesterday I was still thinking about it
oh what could I do with it what could I
do
I have I have the other side of this
office
since months now
and I don't know how to use it
[Music]
should mix some kind of skit with myself
in this and upload it as a clip
basically not as a stream
the hiring kfb idea yeah but you know I
kind of did that with the Minecraft
video I don't want to repeat that idea
again
I'll use it eventually I didn't forget
about it just yesterday I was thinking
about it
I'm just so unsure I I can never make
decisions
performance reviews
it's horror gaming chat stream
interrogating
in the next year
well the problem is you know now I have
the Halloween background and then for
winter time I'll have the Christmas
background
that made me think
the other side of the studio only has
like a normal version
so I would have to go back to the normal
version in the middle of using either
Halloween or winter background now okay
here am I I am once again just
overthinking everything
[Laughter]
it's kind of awkward but I I guess I
would look over that now
[Music]
to that
so that
as soon as possible
okay let's stop [\h__\h] dancing
stop
yeah
Phoenix two six one two thank you
congrats on the Glorious return of hello
talk my favorite talk show period I love
the new design and decided to see it
grow I will be cheering for Uganda thank
you for the rest of the chat thank you
soon yeah I love the new design too a
lot of a lot of people I saw them
pointing out that the chicken pattern
they said they really like it
someone even asked for
um like a separate image of the chicken
pattern so that they could use it for I
think they wanted to make some kind of
like
I don't know like
I forgot what it was but something
similar to I don't know a phone case or
so whatever you have the files ah
I'm fine with it if you published them
people seem to like it I feel like it's
it just Blends in so nicely
it looks so
a sword
the word a word for art that doesn't
really look realistic
abstract yeah it looks abstract until
you look closer
and you see chickens in it
yeah
also it kind of gives me a
um not sure which century Vibes but it
gives me a different Century vibes
80s
80s 90s
I don't know why
ah yeah
yay okay okay okay
70s it looks kind of funky
oh decade oh [\h__\h] hell whatever
yeah those two words I always mix them
up in my head for me
I know
I had I always mix them up
a decade sounds to me like a hundred
years
and Century it sounds to me like those
tens of years because gentle gentle is
10 in like Italian I think also probably
in Latin
so you know how that gets me there
wait no and with those hundreds oh [\h__\h]
oh Deco was 10.
oh [\h__\h]
oh I got a double mixed up in my head I
thought gentle was oh
oh damn it I almost had it almost had it
at least I knew it meant something
at least I know that was Like An Origin
to it it was even it were 10 or 100. I
was I was on the right track
Latin learning's room no thank you a
threat learning in school and I
miserably failed
[Music]
I'll put on my pacifier and that will
surely help me oh look it says Pink as
the shotgun
well
I could be done with this since ages ago
thank you Phoenix
stop it guys I will stop looking at you
guys now
[Laughter]
shut up random conclusion
thank you uh for the rest of the chat
such a comfortable and playful interview
you've still got it yet oh thank you I
thought so
I thought it would be like a little bit
stiff
because you know I thought that I almost
said that I wouldn't be so good with
people in the first meeting because I
thought you know people told me she was
shy and all that
you know but she did such a good job I
feel like
we automatically vibed really well
and had fun talking with one another so
I was really relieved
thank you random collusion for noticing
yeah
Patsy Danke Schoen
um
Eternal dive part two dankishun jinson
thank you
I mean I want to read a couple of these
I don't know it says whole talks better
than ever and so are you you never need
to feel nervous about interviewing
guests when you do school another thing
yeah
it's interesting says congratulations on
the return of hello talk the new studio
is so awesome and this was a great
interview as always it was really cool
to learn more about I am I didn't know
much about her before
I also learned so much about her yeah
you're such a sweetie I I understand
everything now oh yeah by the way uh
okay this is a tangent but please let me
just say this
on Twitter yeah in the preparation for
whole talk like half an hour before the
stream I was like you know talking with
I am a separate then I wrote on on
Twitter like oh my gosh she's so [\h__\h]
cute right uh another Canada
uh answered right
and she was like she wrote in Japanese
and you guys apologize sorry it was
political I'm so sorry before I said if
I answered that yeah and then you guys
thought that she was because of the
automatic translation on Twitter
you guys thought that she was saying you
too as in you're also cute
but I think that's just really what it
sounds like when it's translated by
Twitter it was I think it was more like
uh it to me it read immediately as oh
you got taken by her cuteness as well
huh yeah
otherwise she would have not said the
car at the end Twitter translation
completely left out the cop which is a
question so she didn't say YouTube
but you said you too huh which I think
makes more sense uh and then you will
know she means uh she got you too yeah
yeah yeah yeah
five things I am cute too but
unfortunately she didn't mean this in
this case I just wanted to clear that up
because everybody was like oh you
totally get it you understand yeah yeah
our attention was so cute
oh
yeah yeah Auto translate can really be
misleading so don't always trust it guys
mm-hmm
yeah yeah
very true
[Music]
uh
oh
hello
[Music]
talk it was really not that much
but I was like tangenting for like an
hour I feel like
oh man
my problem is
my throat really hurts
at least we added no extra super chats
for the GTA stream and we won't be
adding more in the next GTA stream
either
because super chat's always off so we
can't like accumulate too many yeah I'll
end it here I'm sorry guys it really
hurts
um yeah
oh yeah rings of power will be a short
stream where I won't be talking much so
I can surely Read Super chats tomorrow
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
we'll catch up tomorrow
I'm gonna try my best to hold back on
watching the new episode
um I I I I I wanted to watch it right
away but I scheduled it so late because
I thought
um my
my my peeps from like America Canada and
so on they might want some extra time to
get home before watching it this is the
latest I can do pretty much so uh yeah I
hope you guys will be able to come home
in time
yeah if not then oh well
um I tried
I'll have absolutely zero context no
come at least at least now you have time
it's on Amazon Prime go watch some
episodes now
go go go go business trip oh well that
sounds fun where are you going
I hope I can catch up until tomorrow
well how far are you away it's not that
many episodes like
six episodes on each episode is like one
hour so
manageable
I'm not gonna watch seven hours in a day
I'll just join this stream tomorrow
gave you if you'll notice already on my
on Monday
shits
you had so much time all of you and now
suddenly y'all are like
binge once now or no I just want
watching it only because I didn't watch
it yet
it gave you so much time
I've been too busy
okay but some of you guys surely
purposefully waited until the last
minute like you always do with your
homework
yeah I'll be there either way thank you
I won't watch anything but the final
episode come on
that's lame because you won't know
what's going on
and you won't you will automatically not
really see it um positively because
you'll be like what the [\h__\h] is going on
like I know it's not the best series out
there but at least if you have some
context you will enjoy the finale more
go
angsty Al relentlessly pursues evil but
everything goes wrong Proto Hobbits
chase a tall man
a quick tldr and that was pretty much it
I guess
I literally have no time that is
totally alive because you have time to
always watch my streams
foreign
if I was streaming 10 hours per day for
the whole week you would be watching all
of that too as far as I know you
you only make time for the things you
want to make time aren't you a lot of
people are like this
people say they have no time but you
would have time if you felt like you
really wanted to make time for it
[Music]
Michelle
what if I am what if I am and you didn't
watch it and that's why you don't know
it
is everywhere
I play a major role in episode six
I wonder what you mean
if you don't have money for Amazon Prime
maybe ask a friend I'm sure you have a
friend who has Amazon Prime
ask ask if you can you know hey
foreign
no that's not a crime is that
I mean families share accounts too
that's not illegal is it
sharing is caring
eh is it
eh well well I mean you know I mean
whatever I mean it's just saying you
know okay then don't do it
go down before the police comes we will
I have a gun I have a gun and I'm afraid
to use it
I'm gonna eat the rest of my pasta now
so see you guys see you tomorrow I'm
excited
and then we'll finally we'll finish GTA
uh on the day after so look forward to
it
hope you had fun today I had fun
hopefully you guys had fun too I mean
foreign
[Laughter]
yeah it's gonna be the big one right the
big one it better be really big
big
free sink
yeah it's it's really slightly
flickering right now too sometimes it
flickers weaker than at other times
so now it doesn't really bother me but
sometimes it gets really strong it's so
weird
I'll pacifier yes yes
[Music]
anyway the big one yeah
thank you
enjoying me sang
[Music]
dancing
foreign
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
no I was just running around I was gonna
say it's almost midnight anyway no it's
not I still got some time
[Music]
oh
huh
[Music]
going forward
oh my throat hurts
ah
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
oh
[Music]
mommy sent me
some instrumentals for the Ode to Joy
I didn't know just because I had to
close Discord she writes to me on this
chord nowadays
it's a gamer
[Music]
oh my God I have like so many
notifications
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
all right bye