[Music]
Happy New Year everyone! 2023 is here! From the New Year, the main character will bring you Pico-i. We've invited a lot of guests, so we'll liven it up and have fun streaming it.
[Laughs] If you
think that just because it's a new year, you'll be broadcasting in a well-behaved way, you're wrong.
This year is the
year of the rabbit.
[Music]
[Laughs]
How
far away is this year the year of the rabbit? We're
going to do our best from New Year's Day. I'm
scared. Wait a minute.
Don't be scared. I'm here. It's okay.
I guess that's the kind of idol I'm suited for.  I
'm an idol, right? But
all of humanity's rabbits are planning this big plan.
Pecola is finally starting today.
What kind of plan do you and I think this plan is?
Thank you
[Music] I
'm not reading the air conditioner, you guys.  I'm
reading this comment right now.
It's cute. You're watching this. It's
Pico who's going to tell you
all about the
rabbit's plan to
spread the charm of Bekola to the whole world and successfully become the
first human in this world.  The
only
thing I can think of is letting Usagi-chan go to bed.So you guys who are watching this are
just preparing for someone to come and do it to Usagi.So, I
guess I'll announce my plan this time.  It's a
song that everyone is wondering what they're going to do soon. It's
outrageous. This time it's seriously outrageous.
So, let's announce our plan.
This is it.
The contents of the plan for All Human Rabbits. First of all,
Hololive Usagiko Plan. Today we're going to do this.
In addition to those of you who are watching the broadcast, we are also going to
transform the holo-faces of double people and above into rabbits,
so please look forward to it and see what kind of rabbits they will
become.
Sexual harassment hasn't stopped yet Major companies Rabbit
's
plan The real world that everyone knows
Real world companies and their masks
Can you make the characters into rabbits? This is
supposed to be Tecola's challenge.
Number 3:
Unprecedented
Rabbit family
live performance is a bit scary  Sorry I'm nervous, but for the
first time in history,
Peko will perform an incredible live performance that no one has ever seen before, so
please look forward to it!
Also, there will be a solo live performance by Pecora Usada.  We
will also announce a song that will be performed for the first time, so please look forward to it
because it is an incredible song.And there
is also a lot of information that will be released for the first time, so please look forward
to it.
If you see it, you'll all turn into rabbits, I'm
sure. Well then, let's move on to the plan. First of all,
Hol Live Usagi will turn
into a Hyadifu Holo surface in a certain place.
Peko is calling. Let's move over there first. Let's
all look forward to Stereo Peko.
Peko
Peko.
Good to see you
here. [Music] [Laughter] [Music] Happy New Year. Nice to meet you. It's the Year of the Rabbit.
[Laughter]
Pecola the Rabbit
asks you to play with everyone.
[Laughs] It's already the
first day of the Year of the Rabbit.  I'd
like you to listen to Ekoro's selfishness, so I'd
like to ask you something even though I don't know.
[Laughs]
It's just the beginning, so I've
prepared some games that will help you start the year with a bang.
[Music]
Quiz.  There you see a
panel with Marukanpats written on it.That's
right, that's right,
that's
right.  Use this cannon to
hit the panel that you think is the correct answer.You can see that this is the
giant cannon.
[Music]
If you answer correctly, you can speak from the place where the mat is pulled out.What
if it's not a clue that won't kill you?
If the answer is correct, you won't get hurt,
but I
had you rush into the special Usa station.
[Music] Well
then, let's try it right away. It
stinks.  I
understand that this is a Marubatsu game. The
captains and the others will give you a quiz first. You can
show them an example.
[Music] You do
n't have to do it. It's
fun the first time.
Thank you.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] It's
going to fit in, so are you ready?
[Music]
My favorite onigiri topping is
tuna and mayo
[Music]
Actually, I get it.  I have
n't collaborated recently, but I understand that. I at least
remember my relationship with my seniors,
so I don't know
if I can tell you the correct answer. Well then, I'll tell
everyone else the
correct answer.
This is it.
[Music]
It's rock-paper-scissors and I'm sure it's that.  I'm sure you were able to
pull it off.I
don't know.Cola,
Pecola-chan,
please play the phantom thief.Okayu-senpai, I
like you best,
so let's go.Go
Go
[Music]
But
what I like the most is
negitoro. I
said negitoro in an interview on the street. I
thought I heard it, but it was the one on my right. It's
negitoro, Pecora-chan. I
had it there too,
straight away.
[Music]
[Music] Did
you know that Amo is safe
?
[Applause]
[Laughter] I
'm happy. Please
answer me correctly. I
have to be on guard in the morning.
Peko is trying to get arrested.  The
ride was surprisingly comfortable, but the
sense of speed from the cannon was amazing. It was
quite far away, and it
felt like I was riding a roller coaster. I guess it's because I want to go by smoothly. If I get it
right, I'm fine. If I get it right, I'm
safe.  Yes, it's a
game, so I
guess it's okay.It's just water after all.Then the
problem is:
the power
outage.The
final part of Lie Pecola is
three carrots.You
know, Hello Kitty.
Pecola is a copy of ``3 Apples'' and it's
not a human walk.
This is a bad reaction.
No, I guess I'll have to make a decision now. Is
Marin right?
[Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
On the other hand, it's a little bit wrong.  I'm a little tired. I've got a tama.
[Music] I wonder
who's going to find me. The three of us are in trouble. The
captain is probably the one who's in the middle of this, Pekoro-
chan, who knows.  It's
not a reply where you can show me your reply. It's
like you can show me, but I'll have to show you a little bit.
[Laughs] You
're a senior. Well then, I'll give you a big shot in return. I
'm confident in my senior. I don't think there's anything wrong with
that. You're such a naughty guy with no
interest. I
want you to guess.  But
Momo, I want Usada Station to
use it.I want them to use it.I
want them to use it for liquids when I put it out.  It's
getting a little distorted, what have you been up to recently
? Seniors, can you hear me? Younger seniors, do you
have any memories?
This year's finger-waving competition, ah,
last year
...
Okay, then
that's a problem.
Usa Latte Cola
is Mr. Automatic Hamburger [Applause] [Music]
But I guess you were busy yesterday, so I guess you
didn't eat the hamburger.  It
's a good punishment.
It's summer.
But are you okay?
[Applause]
[Music] It
might be in your lunch box, but there might be
something in it that's okay. No, but the clothes you wear
on the bus are fine.
Rocks are hard.  Okay, so that's a bit of a cross.
So let's wait until the train departs.
Oooh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] It
feels like it's going to come a long time, so I've made preparations.
Since I was given one, I thought it would be better if I took it off every once in a while.
-
Make it really simple. I wonder what you should do with that.
Well, here's the problem with Tora-san's picture.
[Music]
When I was little, my dream was to be a
cake shop.  Maruka Becoming a
San [Music] Shouldn't we be lucky enough to live
?
Maybe I want to make a carrot cake,
so that's all good news.
Right, can I take the bus? Am I
right? What should I do then?
[Applause]
[Music]
When I was in elementary school, my dream was to go to a cake shop and I
loved cakes, so I wanted to eat a lot of them,
so I
made it famous.
[Music]
But it's
not quite down,
so I wonder how much water I'll put in it.
[Music]
Nice.
What should I do next?
I'll go.
[Music]
My senior is
worried about the time he has to use it.
What do you think?
What about the role of the person who is prepared?
[Laughter]
[Music]
Let's go to the question, then.  I
know how to call you. You
probably don't understand. I want you to
choose Enpeko-chan on low heat.
Choose the bus or
choose the hot one.
[Music]  I
heard that.
[Music]
So it's a bus. So, are you
hitting it correctly? Well, until it fires.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
You're full of confidence. You
said it with a smile.
[Music]
It's good after you open it.  There's a lot of water, but it was still difficult.So
I wonder if it's fixed.When I come back, I
wonder if Usada Station has good permeability.
There was a rumor that there was
[Music]
[Applause]
Wrong
Correct Price
You guys would be surprised if we crashed into that Usada Station
[Applause]
[Laughter] That's too
much. It's just that [Applause] 2023 will be a rabbit.  In 2019, all of humanity will be
carrying out their plan, and
as a stepping stone to that, we're going to ask you to play the rabbit game here today.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]  Let
's go. Okay, wait a minute. I don't want
you to look like this just for Peko Marie.
If possible, I
want you to be successful. You're doing something weird. Look, it's
coffee. It's the
best. Stop it. Now, that's not right, it's too much.  You can do whatever you
want, right?
So Marie doesn't seem like she's ready.
[Music]
That's a lie. I have a list of things I want to do when I become a picola in
my head.
What is the problem with Marie?  The
highest score on the 47 prefecture quizzes that I tried in the past was 24 points.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Well, I guess they're
confident rats.
Did Marine answer correctly? Well then,
until the launch.
As expected, the
highest score for the 7th layer big aura is 26
points. No, Mario is
right. No, I was planning to just miss it normally and put on a rabbit, but I
guessed correctly.
[Music]
As expected, the two of you have visited prefectures before, but
everyone is fine.
[Music]
Because we're flat
Well, I
guess we couldn't get used to each other anymore. [
Music]
Who should we choose next
? Let's go.  You
might be able to see a cute and soothing Pecola. She's the type that makes a lot of noise, but she's also kind
and has pretty eyes. But lately, she's been this
cute.
[Music]
Yes, it's okay. It's a
problem.
The words written on the thumbnail of Bai Lapicola's ``Trial Planning''
are Uzare Pecola. Is that the first trial?
It's recent.
[Music] Do you
understand?
First, there's that.  So I'm
wondering, should I give up?
No, I'll
call it a punishment, but I've written something down. I'm going to work
really hard to win. -
[Music] Are you
okay? Then
[Music]
So I'll call it a circle.
Is porridge really the correct answer? Well then,
until the train departs.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [Music] It's so
rich, isn't it?
[Music] It's kind of
rich, right? But with this porridge,
Senpai, let me bunny.  -
[Music]
[Laughter] You're
free.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you for the 2,000 yen.
Maybe these four will turn into rabbits.
There's a possibility that it was a mistake.
But then, which one should I go to, Marin or Towa-sama?
So, go to the bathroom or go. You say it's
okay. You
have the option of not going. What do you like?
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Applause] We
were just playing around. Well then, here's the question for Towa-sama:
Why does the annoying Pikola like oden eggs?  Is it
because it feels like it's stuck in my throat?
[Music] It feels like it's
stuck in my throat because I feel like I'm going to give a strange answer.Why I
like it?
But it's just the way I usually like it, and it feels like it's stuck in my throat.Okay
then, is Tomato really successful?
Then it's the song to fire.
[Applause]
[Music] It's a
strange feeling. It
's said to feel good.
[Laughs] The
correct answer is Marupeko. Hey, I've already
said all the things I've said. I'm just trying to force everyone to do
it. I
can't handle it.  It's a
Peko to get you into the station, so
that means things are going smoothly.
[Music]
[Laughter] The
correct answer is announced.
This is Shiny Pecker. Let's
go! Hey, we're finally not the 4th person. It
's about time we established ourselves.  It's
strange that Marin is going to build a harem,
or that Pecola is the one who belongs to all humankind. I
wonder if she can raise her white peko feet. Is it
okay to play a marine quiz?
You need to take the quiz already.
What are you talking about
now? Will the
captain answer correctly and
hurt Pecola's harem? Or will
Tecola put
all her effort into making the plan a success?
This is the final gamble.  Hey, no, I'm wondering
if four more people would be enough.It's
cute.It
's a cute cat, but I don't think I need five people.Wait, what should I do in that corner?
Last but not least, is it time to get ready for the marine? Well,
here's another message for Marie.
Pekora Usada's best sport is
swimming or swimming.
But I
heard that she went to the gym. She even jogged while she was resting.  Is it because I'm
good at it? I'm doing it for my health
. I'm
not good at it. That's amazing.
Let's settle this. Are you
sure you got it right? Well, let's go until the train departs.
[Applause]
[Music]
As expected...
[Laughs] I
don't think he attacks like that. I
thought he was strong
after all, but I didn't expect him to be this strong on
his own. As expected, I
just can't get used to it.
Lately, I haven't been able to do it.  I feel like I'm giving up, right
in the middle.  I
got one step closer and I'm asking you guys to help me with my future makeup plans, so I
understand
.
That's good. [Laughter] [Applause] I'm going to do something inside that I've never seen before. It's Peko, so it's new.
[Applause]
Eh.  Don't come here
[Laughs] You're
too scary Peco Peco Peco
[Music]
If you don't like mining, come here. There
's no such thing as an important place. You have to make it yourself.
[Music]
Surprised, I
'm alive.
Every day,
after a big problem,
there's something fun,
so I'm the kind of person who screams. Every day I have very successful
hair. [
Music]
Even if it's the sky to receive and cut,
if you want to hold it, I won't give up either resource.
[Music] I
did it.
Because I'm happy
[Music]
After the problem,
there's something fun, so don't
shout out randomness, it's an
incident, it's a huge success every day, so you
can't get it
[Music]
Isn't it great
?  There were a
few people eating with ridiculous movements
.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] It
's a song that I think I could dance to, but it's about
time for me to get motivated. It's
not normal for 5 people to do this.  I guess that's what I mean.
Everyone knows that. I think they really
showed their individuality through their movements. You know that you want it to be
easy to understand and easy to understand.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Well, even on stage.
[Applause]
What happened to that? When a
rabbit rebels, they go in there,
brainwash them, then release them and let them out.
Since they're kids, everyone
thought that if they rebelled a bit, they'd go inside.  If you
turn it on, you'll still be there.
[Music]
After this, there will
be plenty of surprises to watch. I'll
turn you into a rabbit too, so follow me.
Together, we'll take you
to Earth.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] I'm
not too excited.
You guys aren't too laid back.
Let me just say something. Why don't you tell the toughest guys
in the studio
?
[Laughs]
[Music]
Hey, it has to be today.  That
's right, the four people from earlier
did it today, and even if they
make bunny faces today, they
all do it.Okay, that's why I
called you today.You guys are
different, right?I don't care
what happens when I call you live.  I'm
sure they'll be happy to come.
Members: I'm
sure they'll come. Thank
you very much. We
hope to see you again this year.
Since I received it, I'm thinking of doing something a little New Year's-like.That
is
[Applause]
Commando Festival
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Photos.  I
would like to make a
New Year's card to give to all of you who are taking pictures and watching. I'm going to choose which New Year's card I'll get the most with a 3-person team of Hepola's maa solo and now Usagikane.  I'd like to
do a survey of you guys to see if you want it.
Good luck, Picoult. I
think it's live, but I'm going to do it in a showdown.
No, it's about time. It was so noisy in the back room earlier, but I
thought it was okay. No,
but I'm glad that Gacchan is doing well. I'm
ready to jam.
Yes [
Music] Here we
come [
Applause]
-
[Applause] It's Iko-
chan!
[Music]
So cute
How cute is it? How do you feel about actually coming and seeing it?
First of all,
who's going to be performing? Yes,
this live show is coming. Usagi is
out of control
[Music]
What's this? Who's this?
Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] It
appeared earlier
[Music]
So this
background
[Music]
Like this, the background of the New Year's card is here.  It
's early, it's early, you're early, it's early
, no, the three of us are doing this from the music
[music]
First, choose the background you want to create.
Probably win  I
thought it wasn't, but it's like this, after all, that's what it is.The
impact is something
else.Alright, let's
do this.Add Apepola.It's a
purikura machine.
[Music]
Choose the background you like.
[Laughter]I think I'll
go with number 6 for cola.
[  [Laughs]
Time is running out a bit,
so here we go. What should we do?
With sparkling eyes, this is it. This
year's financial luck update is...
[Music]
Last year, we sold 50 squares.
Everyone's a rich cat.
You're covering your ears, but I don't know what to do.
Money, money, money,
fun. It's
falling from above, so
money doesn't make me dance. It's a
New Year's card, right? I
want a New Year's gift.
If you're going to say that much, maybe the three of you should recognize it too.
[Laughs]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] Let's
do something that has a bit of an impact. Well, that
's enough. But it's
amazing. I'm
sure all of humanity.
Rabbit type. How about something like that? It looks like it
came on a bicycle.  I'm so
excited. I like this. Do
n't wait, but I can see it.
[Applause]
Give me a nice one. It's a nice stamp.
Should I put it on top? Wait a minute.
Choose an Airpo. Is there a good song?
That's fine.  It's not the same. It's
fine. 7
Number 7. They're probably looking at overseas food as well
.
So, please make it a little smaller.
Something like this or that on top. What's the theme of this
?
[Music]  ]
Please
[Music]
[Applause]
What do you think?
[Laughter]
You guys, Picoders, I'm
sorry. That's fine. [Music] [Laughter] You live in a theme. You're wrapped up in earthly desires.
[Applause]
[Music]
Vote for which New Year's card is better.
[Music] I'm
kidding.
Everyone wants money.
[Laughs]
No, but I don't know if they'll win on the road. They
might have won with violence. They
're kids. Even if you're a human, there's a lot of rabbits.  I heard they
built it.
[Applause]
Please,
I'd like to finish it here.
Thank you everyone. Thank you. Let's take a look.
What do you think?
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [
Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] You
can come as the fourth person.
Original Pico-chan. You
can come as the fourth person. I'll
let you sleep.
But, Usagi's team has changed,
but that's okay. As far as the plan goes, we've already
got a long way to go.  It
's a success, so it's fine. I'm sure you'll
be happy at all.
[Applause]
Well
then, I don't know if this New Year's card corner is going to be easy or not, but I'm fine with the wishes section.  I wanted the three of us to
watch it together, so I
couldn't move forward without going too far
[laughter]
You know, I
kind of liked this one, too.
[Music]
Well, the three of them moved a little strangely,
but I guess it's just a cute thing. Let's just say it's
okay. But after this, the
song will continue to be played by those three people. However, if things continue as they are,
I'll end up with a
hand coke.  Now, I don't understand.
Those people are now back to their original state,
so I'm glad they can go back. Well, please come back.
Let's go.
And I'm
thinking of meeting you.  You've
learned your
lesson, haven't you? [Laughs] In fact, Usagi
Ka, a member, has already made progress and seems to have already succeeded in backing 25 people.  Members of
[Music]
Usagi Ka Collection
Start time suddenly
[Applause] It's
starting
[Music]
[Music
] [Laughter] [
Applause] [
Music] [
Laughter] [Applause] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music]
[Music]
Let's settle it there.
[Applause]
Show
[Music] I
have zero interest.
[Music] You're
saying, "Do you like me?" They're
definitely saying that they have to tell me.
Wait a minute, don't worry.  Why did you
give up on me? You're
making a mistake.
Even if you're turning into that free-spirited rabbit,
we were also stopped at that rabbit station a while ago. We
were doing something that looked like we wouldn't do it again.  You
know, when you get into a figure, something like your own, no, real desire comes out. I want the cat to do it for me, but it's like I'm going to vent here or poop.
[Music] There
's still more next time.  It's okay
because I have my own, but I
'm a little worried when I look at V now, but it's okay.There are people who are
trying to imitate someone and people who are trying to follow their instincts.
It was interesting to see how it turned out.There were some people who didn't want to show it.Isn't this the correct answer?Isn't this the correct answer?Is
n't this the correct answer?If everyone doesn't know how to write, then in the
end, that's okay.I wonder if that's okay.I
wonder if that's okay.  The price is a
bit high,
right? I'm
sure I can't go there. I
think something more unique might be better. I
like Matsui-senpai's big breasts now.
Hey, there
are probably two more patterns left.  It
's Pico, but both of us are scared, but I'm looking forward to the
next one. I wonder if there will be eight of us next.
[Applause] That's
awesome. Let's see.
Volume
[Laughs]
Senpai, ah, I'm a
fish that won't shake.
[Music] That
was great. The live performance was also really
good.
That's the kind of girl I am.
[Music]
Lately
[Laughs] I
don't say this these days. It's
delicious. I've
been doing it myself for a while.
[Laughs]
This is it.
Ah, Deko-san, I think this is good. I'm
sorry. My
aesthetic sense was wrong. I'm
thirsty, so it must
be a lie. I
'll say hello.
Peeped version
Kate
[Laughter]
[Music]
Number 27,please
[Applause]
Hey
[Laughter] Are you
waiting?  For a moment when no one is following me, please
give me the number 2.7 and 27. But it's not fun to have a Peko-chan like that,
because all of humanity
will become a Peko-chan.
Hirosaki-kun doesn't really look like an anime sister, so it's
obvious that they won't meet.There
are people who look alike, but there are people who say they're trying their best to show that they're the same.There are a lot of them,
but the
en girls look a lot alike.  After I saw that house,
Subaru-senpai imagined that it had been
destroyed.Subaru-
senpai
No. 27 and No. 27 are Oshikiri.  That's
true.
Schwa-chan also looks at me
[laughing]
Senpai always imitates my voice,
so I guess that's why you did your best.
[laughing]
Please look at me
[music]
Next time, there will be more problems, so I'm
sorry for the people who want to do it.  Now, the next rabbit
wants to see the collection, so I'd
like to move on to the next rabbit and plan.  Of course,
turning into a rabbit is not
only limited to this virtual world, but also the real world in which you are watching this broadcast.
Peko is being turned
into a rabbit quite suddenly and seriously.
[Music]
That's true.  Do you think they're serious about doing mode
?
We had some free time over the New Year, but we
decided to go ahead and turn a
big company that everyone knows into an
exhaust company. I'm
not saying it was a success, but it's still...  I
don't really know the result, so it hurts, but I
'm tired.
[Music]
[Applause] I'm
going to show my existence and power to all of humanity. That's too bad,
after Mr. Secora's cat asked me to do it.
But
who is that?  There's no
rival
for targeting companies. Where are the
rabbits going? Wait, Fujiya, the strange manufacturer?
[Applause]
Maybe
Fujiya is the one who's selling that tongue too.  Are
you saying it's because there's someone there?Have you noticed, Peko? Is this what you're going to do? Turn the mascot, Peko-chan, into a rabbit. That's a lie. I'll turn you into Peko-chan. Peko [Laughter] [Music] [Music] The other party is a big company.  Actually, I've
been preparing a lot since last year. That's
right. I'd
like to see it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
So far, Fujiya-san, Peko-chan, and Usagi-ka
plan.
Actually, I'm going to watch it from a certain recording point.
[Applause]
Well then, VTR Y. Well, I'm
excited. For some reason, we're
excited.
[Music]
[Laughter]
But how do rabbits do that? Wait a minute,
guys.  I'm
nervous, because I've
never given a gift
before, and I only get one chance, and the
person I'm with is a proper adult
[laughter] I'd
like to spend a week with him or have some emotional differences with him.  That
means I can't go, I can't go.
[Laughs] It hasn't happened
yet. I wonder when it'll come.
Suddenly, Pecola-sama decided to aim for the rabbit face at a long-established
store that was founded over 100 years ago.
[Music] It
's a nation that sells a variety of goods. It
was fun.
Will we be able to make the rabbit face that Fujiya has?
Do your best, do
your best, do your best. Keep the
door behind you.
Please
[Music]
Thank you very much
[Laughter]
Hmm, but what's more,
if we can do the original collaboration right in front of our eyes, let's take advantage of it.It's
not nice,
so
next year we're actually
planning a advance plan for Detective Cola.  I
would like to invade not only the virtual world but also the real world. I
came here today to ask if we could collaborate.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]  I
'm just trying to say it myself, but Ichiban Ocha Dake Cola has been
active for three years and now has an
incredible 2 million subscribers on YouTube.
[Music]
Sticking carrots in your hair.  I
feel a little bit sorry for him.Not only is he making a fuss, but I
also want to make Fujiwara-san's Peko-chan costume look great in a Peko Peko collaboration.  I wonder
if it will turn out to be cute,
but yeah, I've
done a lot of collaborations
with it, so if it's visually cute, I
wonder if there
's a possibility of that. It
depends on how it's done. It
's 100 years old anyway, so I can't
really
see it.  I
'm 6 years old, but
if you treat me like I'm 6 years old, that's
fine.
[Laughs] I have
n't done anything similar to Fujiya's Peko-chan yet.  I do
n't have it yet, but I
don't put food on my hair that much.
[Music] There's a little bit of food
in each strand of my hair. I have
to change it every day.
[Laughs] [Music]
[Music] It's
sure to come true soon.  I
'm thinking that it would be great if I could sell goods.I'm
thinking that it would be nice to be able to sell goods that would make both of us happy.Maybe.
If the Peco Peco collaboration were to materialize, I
'm sure it would end up being something cute, so I
think it would be great to have tangible goods.That's
what everyone is getting serious about.Keychains
and the like are quite standard and popular.  I
think it would be a lot of fun if it was full of things like, ``
Even
if it's at night.''
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think it would be really fun if it was full of people. Convenience
stores charge a fee, supermarkets, etc.  There is
also a charge for Pecola,
so I try to carry around a lot of eco bags and bags, so
please.Yes,
that Peco-chan rabbit collaboration is
mainly about selling goods,
but Pecola
doesn't hesitate to do more than that.  I wish we could cooperate a lot, and I've
been thinking about promotions that would help, so I
'd appreciate it if you could make some suggestions.
[Music]
[Applause]
Fujiya is doing it, and I think Peko-chan is
tweeting about it, but
Peko-chan is taking over the year 2023, the year of the rabbit. I'm
not sure if it's okay to take over, but Pecola.  It's
always like a poem.I
wonder if I can take over a little bit of the tweets of the day.That's
right.I've been on Twitter for a year.
Peko-chan might cry.Neo, I
think Peko-chan would also be happy if they were allowed to communicate with each other on Twitter.It's
true that the
president of Fujiya will
be featured in the media on the 1st.  I was wondering
if it would be possible to do something like that,
and since I would be working for free, that would be fine, and I
wondered if it would lead to the topicality of running a club.
That's difficult.
[Laughs]
[Music] That
's all for my presentation, which was a collaboration with Fujiya and Peko-chan. I hope you'll consider it in a positive manner.
Thank you very much. There
were a lot of flexible and fresh ideas, so I had
a lot of ideas today.  Since I
received it, I will take it home and reply again.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to it.
[Music]
[Laughter] What are your
specific
thoughts?
As for the concrete plan, what are we going to do next and
aim for even higher
Peko-chan? I
was nervous, but I wonder why it's Picola.
In front of me are those three people from Fujiya, and
Peko is in the middle of them, so I'm diagonally to the left.  He's grinning with his lower jaw,
right?
[Music]
That's great, but as you can see,
Peko doesn't know yet whether a rabbit can sleep with Mr. Fujiya and Peko-chan.
[Music] I heard that you
have replied to me, so
thank you. I
wonder if I should go with you to take the entrance exam.
[Music]
Yes, I will go.
Since then, the
other day, you have proposed a collaboration with our company and gave an
enthusiastic presentation.
Thank you very much for your support. After
receiving Mr. Busara's presentation
and considering it internally, we decided that we would like to create a
collaboration between the management mascot character Peko-chan and Usagi-sama.
[Music]  I'm
thinking of holding the competition again and then making a decision,
so I
have it.
[Applause]
Congratulations. Apparently
there's an illustration, so I'm
thinking positively. I
heard there's more to say.  So here it
is.
[Music] It's
really scary, Peko-chan. I
can hear Pecola very well.
She's 6 years old. She looks like a 6-year-old even with carrots in between.
[Music]  She's
dressed like a baby would wear
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
'd like to try some of Peko-chan's clothes
[Applause]
[Music] I wish
Pekodama would release a cute collaboration product.More
details  I'll let you know again when it's decided. It's
Peko, so everyone please look forward to it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
Rabbit or the other
way around?
[Applause]
Thank you for the collaboration.
Animate was announced last year, so
some of you may already know about it, but it's actually
one of the plans for this collaborative project to turn all humans into rabbits.It will be
held at Animate stores nationwide starting tomorrow, January 2nd.
[Music]
At the store,
only shop First of all, there are many different tempos,
but there is a limited edition one on display at Building 2 in Akihabara.Today I would
like to take a special look at it.Of
course,
[Music]  ]
[music]
There's also a corner with a recreation of the 3D live stage that was first unveiled.This looks like a
fun place to take.I
don't know what the photo is yet, but I wonder what it will look like.Also,
in this corner, there is a Tenjin
Rabbit Plan logo sticker all over the wall.
This Peco sticker is a present for everyone.
Beneath the sticker is an illustration of Pecola and a
message hidden, so
everyone come to the store and talk to us!
[Laughter]
[Music]
Oh
[Music]  I think it's a
perfect success for the New Year season, and I
want you to see Pico in a
kimono.This is a
real human being.The kimono that everyone is wearing.What is it
really like?
[Music]
I agree with Pico, who turned into an anime rabbit.  You guys
did the same pose as before. [Laughs] There's a store that only matches those figures, so I think it'll start on January 2nd. Actually, January 2nd is actually a
lottery.
Do you think I can go after January 2nd?
[Music]
Jet Stream
Carrot Pouch
Jet Stream It's a great brand name, isn't it
? It's
amazing.
Is there a song that you like?
[Music] What's
next?  Click here
[Music] We
have a lot of goods, so I hope you
can pick them up when you go.
Collaboration:
During the fair period, we will be selling Hololive related goods.  For
every 1,650 yen spent, you can
receive a Kanade Cola message bromide.Everyone is
thinking of Animate.For
admission to stores holding foot-only shops, we are
holding a lottery in advance.For
details, please check each store's Twitter account.  This
is the song I want you to check out.
[Music] When the
figure is released in a whopping 1/4 scale, it will be
1/4
[Music] The
figure and the figure production are highly praised from overseas.
Design Coco Kimono
is a doll
That's amazing.
[Applause] It's an
authentic figure. No, it's
amazing. It's amazing. Pre-
orders are open until March 22nd after this release.
Check out the number of orders received.
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Laughter]
Usagi collects it.
is the final song. It's the final, or the middle of the eight remaining Usagi side members. It seems like some of the members are a little more chaotic than before, but
let's take a look at it when it's time. [
Applause]
[Music]
What do you mean by chaos?
But
the rules seem good, but I'm nervous. Ah, first
broadcast.
Thank you.
You guys are the
most misunderstood people in the world.
[Music]
Nozaki and his friends bring us fresh water every day,
so if they told me that, I might want it.
[Music]
[Applause]
Setting by yourself
[Laughter]  I'll
show you the attributes
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] The
rabbit pillow
is Usagi-san who came to stream the other day. I
took it from Usagi-san.
Pekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopeko,
right?
Number 2527  The number is really flying. When it
gets to this point, it shows.
[Applause] You do
n't care, right?
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
It's something amazing.  The
ones who turned into Cola rabbits are AW. They've
stuck with me for a lifetime.
All of them left a great impression on me, but that's true.
But Hakotaro was interesting, too.
My husband, I've collaborated with him once,
but he said something like that.  No, I
had an idea, but this time around, the
plan was that the person who most resembled Pecoracho would become the second Pecola.That's why it happened
this time, so if that happened, she would look
similar to Sui-chan or Yaa-chan.  It was
just a collection because
it
looked similar to the one that appeared in ``I love the next one that looks like it.''
[Music]
[Laughs] You're
totally right about turning 32 or more Holomees into rabbits, including you guys. Well,
if it's a success, then then, who was the most
interesting?  Please
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music] You
didn't choose to dub it.
We also watched the dubbed version of Pecola-senpai's
Nea-no live
performance.
So that means we were able to turn them into rabbits.
[Music]
[Applause]
The rabbit was created for the plan,
right? That's right, Sakibune
[Laughter]
[Music]
All of them are showing off that the rabbit was
created for the plan.  The most
interesting part is what I'm thinking right now:
Ah, I'm glad they're showing it to me so quickly.The
title of the new song is also the name,
All Humanity Rabbit Plan
[Laughs] It's
beautiful.The
lyrics and composition have provided songs for many idols.
This is Hyadain
-
[Music]
Peko is a song, so you
should listen carefully.
[Music] Thank you for your hard work. [Music]
Thank you.
[Applause] The
time is 2023. The
year of the rabbit only comes once every 12 years.
Why should we miss this chance? Now is the time for
all human rabbits to
carry out their plan.
From the main
[Music]
Penguin and Rabbit
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]  The
pen is just like a high carrot, and the
official language is right here.If I paint for a minute, I'll
move on, but I'll be careful with the rabbit.It's a
pain, so do I want to do it?Even if I realize,
humanity's fine has passed, and the
earth,
too.  It's not a bad atmosphere. We're humans.
[Music] There's a
rabbit at the entrance
. [Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
What's a human being?
[Music] Would you like to start a rabbit business? [Music]
Rent is subsidized. You
can do it even in a country at war.
[Music]
That's why we'll be together
Promised Rapeco
Pyan Pyan Pyon Pyon Pyon Pyon
[Music]
Lap time Dreaming of the future Everyone
Why did everyone do this? Was it a
cute cat?
In the year of the rabbit,
by the way, all of humanity
Rabbit accounting
Thank you so much for being so cute. You look
so tired. Thank
you. Thank you for your hard work.  She's
so cute. Play a nice song.
What do you like about Pecola? What do you
like about Pecola? She wants everyone to sing along with her. That's the
main point, Peko.
Actually, what you just heard about the plan to turn all humans into rabbits.
After this distribution, the MV will be
released on Pecola's channel,
and the
MV was made by Komainu. It
's very cute, so
check it out.And even after this distribution ends, there will
be no plans to turn all humans into rabbits.  It's not
the end, Picon. The plan will continue in the future,
so
let me tell you a little bit about it. It's
here.
In Pumptique, which will be released on January 10th, there will
be a 46-page special feature on Usada Pekola.
The contents of the Picorn Human Rabbit Transformation Plan.  From The
Miracle of Long Interview Activities If
you read this, you too will be able to make Sara Pecola
round and
Recola with super mini size blocks to make Pecola nano blocks.  The
Chau collaboration product is scheduled to be released in 2023,
so
please look forward to the follow-up news Peko.Have we
delivered a lot of content since the first day of the Year of the Rabbit? Guys, you
guys have become rabbits, too.
Hey, Peko.  That's what I thought, but
in honor of Coke and the Rabbit, all humans should be
turned into rabbits, so this year's
Pecola
is something to keep an eye
on.  Do
n't take your eyes off me.
But Fujiya is already here. It
's been a long year, so I still
want to collaborate with a lot of places, so I'd love to
hear from companies that are watching this. I'd love to hear from you, Ohara Pekoler.  I'm very
happy, so I hope you'll
continue to support me for a year.And everyone, too.  It's a
dress that has to appeal,
so thank you to the person who put the nice rabbit stamp on it.
Well, it's been a year, and it's
still going to continue,
so today I've added that, and now I've
made all of humanity's rabbits.  Well,
this plan is still going on, and I don't know
if it's going to end well.So today, it's been a success so far
[Music]