[Music]
my
[Applause]
[Music]
do
hmm
[Music]
la
la la la la
[Music]
wow
good evening good morning wherever you
are
now for most of you it's probably good
morning but for me it is good evening
uh welcome to today's stream
[Music]
no i need bigger hands to to
control that big wheel
so you hear that you hear that the
autobahn bgm
oh oh naga coming to hayaii the comments
are so quick
okay who watched yesterday's
collaboration with me
[Music]
hey hello
yesterday you heard the video awesome
well you really do you really i didn't
really see so many replies
thank you for watching that and
yesterday
like i'm i think i'm generally quite
energetic
but yesterday oh my god sitting next to
subaru
like she she got the most potential out
of my out of my energy out of my the
energy that
that slumbers
[Music]
little bit of talking before we start
the the game
we actually went uh for dinner
i guess you could call it dinner before
the
the whole thing and she was so sweet
first of all she invited me for dinner
so so much like a like a senpai like a
reliable senpai
thank you and we talked a lot about many
many things
and she also listened a little bit to my
my worries
because you know everyone has some
worries and it was really interesting
because like
uh somehow with some things we were like
kind of similar like
she she said that she can relate a lot
to what i said so i was really happy we
connected a lot already before the
stream yeah
yeah but nonetheless it was the first
time that we met
so it was uh interesting
to suddenly like normally uh you can
just easily do collaborations over
discord you know
but we decided to do it uh
in real life because it would have been
easier the whole remote control i was
too
too lazy to check it out
is my is my voice so quiet compared to
the btm
i can't really do much about that
well
that's so cute right
and then we were like really chill we
went to her place
and we tried like preparing everything
it was really chill
no no no nervosity but like five minutes
before the collab
like uh i opened that the stream tab
and uh somebody saw that already like
how many was it like there was anyway
there was like already a lot of people
in the waiting room
to begin with and that made her suddenly
so nervous
[Music]
and her being nervous made me a bit
nervous too
but yesterday was crazy and yesterday
was the most
the most the biggest audience i ever had
thank you guys so much
and i was also really glad that even
though it was mostly it ended up being
mostly japanese but
many of you still uh kept on commenting
in english so i suppose
there were a lot of you guys english
speaking peeps anyway
thank you for being there to support me
and yeah um
i screamed so much yesterday you have no
idea like but i rewatched the stream
and it did really seem like
uh like we were quite far away from the
microphone
but we were so [\h__\h] loud you have no
idea we were so
[\h__\h] loud you didn't even
like the the microphone only peaked like
a few times in that stream
but we were really [\h__\h] loud okay i
us screaming i was really worried that
somebody said i would get kicked out of
her
apartment or whatever because even
though she just moved
but we're so noisy you have no idea oh
my god it's
her sitting right next to me broke
my eardrums several times and i decided
to break
hers too by being equally loud
[Laughter]
and
it was maybe not that much noticeable
from what i said what i heard
need new ears
i need new ears
you broke our ears really yay
about that about the there's already
like a thank you for the super chat
there's always
a bunch of um clips out there
with translations so if you were an
english speaking watcher yesterday who
didn't really understand what was going
on
you can just look up uh some clips i i
think if you look up
kiara and subaru you will find many many
clips
already that are translated and some
some of them are like even like
translated both ways like
whenever i would speak english it would
be translated into japanese whenever i
would speak japanese it would be
translated
into english there's so many uh skilled
uh clippers out there that can do like
both language just like me
good job i already watched the bunch of
the clips
in there
about me in her morning stream as well
and
i'm gonna just get started um but keep
on talking
and she said that i'm sweet
she said i'm sweet and i care about the
people around me wow
i don't know how she got that idea
[Music]
well i mean yeah i'm sweet
whatever i can do it with any cards
today as well you may experience
a professional mario kart driver
which was my previous life it's
obviously not my current
current life it's been a long time i
don't i
i last time
it was um proven that
i do not take all of my experiences from
previous lives with me when i do when i
like
get reborn apparently that does not work
i was quite surprised by myself hello
friends i will own you
omara
driving time um i will try
to improve my driving today
let's see what these boys got
nothing here's that animal crossing girl
that everyone loves so much
but i don't think she's a good driver
there's even two there's two
eh i'm always going with the prettiest
girl
because i like watching that butt
from
[Music]
she's like in her office 24 7 why would
i be jealous
that's such such a hard life rough life
man
i do not envy the people who are in the
office 24 7.
i feel sorry for them i mean like
respect but i could never do that
i enjoy working from home
really do you guys even have a job
do you guys even have a job
oh animal person let's go speaking of
wow why why does everyone have such a
boring
red suit everyone looks the same
oh bye-bye he got scared because i
joined
us
why does everyone have the same suit
you gotta wear an orange suit if you
want to look like me
best driver thank you for the super chat
oh did you guys watch the kelly's
streams today in the second one i was
translated very professional
right i was a very professional
translator i'm professional at
everything i do but for real
for real though i brought my laptop and
i was uh typing
uh while while keisan was speaking
japanese
i was writing uh the same thing down in
english
like enlightening speech time so once he
finished his japanese
sentence at the same time i would finish
writing down the english sentence
i i was that was the first time i did
something like that and it actually
really worked quite well
how do i do that again ah i think at two
right at two
and two i have to start speeding speed
i forgot how to i'll get like this okay
that was impressive thank you i i proved
to you that i have a big ring
bird brain is big when i always told you
guys
and today i shall prove you that birds
are also good drivers
how do i use an item again
how do i use the item okay
how did i put it on my ass again i
forgot everything from last time
memory problem yeah i would say i'm
quite intelligent
yes but my memory
my memory is not the best i forget
things sometimes like after three
seconds but don't you guys have that too
did you forget things after three
seconds don't tell me you don't
everyone has that issue i think
i'm coming we better watch out
for
have a shitty memory just like me
don't
a little bit later you know tactics
i'm also a professional chess player as
you know
what what wow just shoot it all out
[Music]
come on
i must say um screaming so much
at subaru's at the stream survival
yesterday
i noticed just now that screaming today
is kind of painful
thank you for the super chat wait
i should i wouldn't mind like if like
more japanese talents
uh would hire me as their professional
translator
[Music]
just use me as your translator i'll be
there
but actually with this newly acquired
skill of mine
i'm planning to do something very
special
which one is the easiest guys which one
is the easiest
i'm just oh i can't be yo what up
yo yo
nice mario sir are you sure are you are
you kidding me
are you are you for real yo okay
you know what to do right you know how
we do this game right
you know how it works right you let me
win
or you're fired and last time
you did not let me win guys and i fired
you all
you didn't let me win so i fired all of
you but out of mercy
okay i must say this was out of mercy so
respect your queen
and i hired everyone back again but
today
i will not go that easy on you if you do
not let me win
i will fire you and that will be forever
yo let's go
[Music]
the reason why i i downloaded or bought
a mario kart 8 dx recently
it was because one day i want to drive
against
bakula say bye
and even win against her oh why is
[Music]
hyrule
fans are so strong at mario kart she's
already number one
english words not existing all right
what i think i like how the the coins
are
uh the zelda rubies
in this map very nice detail
i'm drifting [\h__\h] drift
is it
let me win
[Music]
thank you for the super chat
you guys know that i uh at the moment
because i had oh [\h__\h] now oh my
why did i use both at the same time you
guys probably know that
um since i recently moved but had issues
with the internet because the stupid
intel company decided to
move my dates two weeks later
so i don't have internet i couldn't work
you know couldn't stream
so i'm streaming from my manager's place
and but
the last time i played mario kart
after midnight and uh first of all
in the beginning my manager was like oh
you could totally
be loud after midnight but i guess uh
she didn't expect me to be that loud
so next day after my mario kart stream
she was like kiara
we gotta buy um
those foamy things uh i'm gonna buy
those and then we're gonna put those
in that room you're streaming
six wow oh my god nicer
so she bought those foamy things
because apparently i was louder than she
expected me to be
you know the the the road rage is just
too strong i cannot hold it back
but today i'm streaming before midnight
so it should be fine she was like even
like
she was like actually during the stream
uh
she messaged me on this card she was
like
can you like chill a little bit i'm
scared that the police will come
and apparently later on during the
stream
she heard the like some uh
like but it wasn't for us it wasn't for
us
[Laughter]
oh wait which one should we go for
cheese land
yeah it wasn't for us thank god
so anyway they uh my manager tried to
put those foamy things on the wall
another pickle that fan she tried to put
them on the wall but they keep on
falling down on me
and i'm like what
[Music]
[Laughter]
they keep on falling down on me
they just don't stick to the wall
yeah well it's okay actually
it's just uh nine more days until i
finally get internet in my new home i
cannot honestly i cannot [\h__\h] believe
it
that they moved my date two times
unbelievable i gotta work you know i
gotta have
stuff today
no problem no problem i i'm good at this
game
so oh we gamer 3 11 yo
what up you made it into the game you
better let me win huh
i know you'll let me win right i trust
you just keep on falling down the edges
it's just natural just let it happen
oh no who left that fire
you're fired
who the [\h__\h] did that
you're all fired you guys don't
understand these days
it's hard to get a job you really want
to lose your job
are you sure about that you you should
maybe think about your future
huh do you think it's a good idea to
lose your job at these rough times
i doubt it idiots
[Music]
who was that who is behind me
which kfp employee wants to get fired
i'm actually a poor that's not bad wait
i'm not am i not supposed to be in the
water i thought that would make me
quicker
i'm a ghost
one day working at kfc is enough no
no i need you guys i don't like to
admit it but i need you guys because you
guys are the only ones
working at kfp i'm not really working
i'm the head of the company why would i
be working
wait for me why am i not if i was four
must come back 11
you will pay for this just as you always
do
your salary belongs to me
give me your salaries be gamer
you have sent like a million super chats
to me
i think you like me right so don't be
don't be like a shy boy from high school
just admit to your feelings just be open
with it and let me win
i won i mean i didn't win but
eight seven and four damn
damn not bad hello you did not expect
that for me
by the way ah
um i don't really care so much if you
stay
in the group or not but don't stay more
than free races maybe
don't say more than free races
7 am i haven't slept but i had to watch
welcome
thank you for coming by
7 am you have not slept wow well i
generally stay awake oh [\h__\h] i didn't
choose
ah i generally stay awake like
until 5 or 6 a.m every goddamn
night no please no rainbow no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no okay what is this
[Music]
yo
nice nice to see you guys here
no sagging fight me
see what i can do now this time i will
not [\h__\h] up the speech
[Music]
oh on the weather world oh wait wasn't
this one on the phone as well
by the way today is stream i'm second
[Laughter]
today's stream only is like one hour and
after that i'll do super chat reading
because this week i didn't really get to
do it as much as usual lee
that was scary maybe that was not the
the the
phone version thingy
wow why are you complaining about your
ears i thought you already lost your
ears
oh my god i thought you already lost
your ears with the collaboration with
superior senpai
now you keep on complaining about the to
me about your goddamn ears
well get yourself some new ears that are
better quality okay
it's not my fault if they keep on
breaking ah
that's not my idea why won't you do that
wait for me yo
v-gamer you little [\h__\h]
wait for me big gamer where did you go
i know no oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
gosh it hurts my throat hurts
well your ears hurt my throat hurts
i've been screaming too much recently
ears blessed well yeah
i don't think so obviously
your ears have been blessed by the
majestic voice of a phoenix who's right
down number two
oh i told you i'm the professional mario
kart player i told you and you didn't
believe me
here we go camera
i wonder if they if they're doing that
on purpose though
let me can i shoot those in the back too
well let's keep them for now
let's let's let's calm the [\h__\h] down
oh [\h__\h] stop stop
came a bit too late and then that stupid
kfb employee rushed right through there
what the [\h__\h]
are you doing you're fired
get out of here thank you for joining i
had fun
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was not fun shut up kfb
good game yeah for me yes
i keep on getting closer to the top
now get out of here okay no stay stay
stay
i want you to stay
i'm ready for the next ride keep it
coming keep it coming
keep it coming boys
you don't need to think so much about
what you choose you will lose on any
road
okay i think this will be moomooland
my papa was on the stream today
introducing his
uh design this is the figurines that
were designed by him
so if you want to hear the beautiful
voice
of my papa then listen to the archive
why does it take so much time
today again i'm driving very carefully
and very pure idolish
should we do maybe uh should we do a say
so run
okay let me do the sensor oh
winter christmas time
okay since this is such a romantic road
let's go
let's go like for real let's let's be
nice
excuse me would you please uh get the
[\h__\h] out of my
way thank you um what's this not
i'm just gonna not drop this banana
because it would be rude
to just drop it on the road you know
you gotta uh take it home and then put
it in the trash
can in the appropriate one you should
not be mixing
the trash cans you know
maybe if i put it on the side of the
road ah okay i lost it never mind no i'm
still there
okay i still don't know how to put it on
my ass though
would someone be so kind to teach me how
to put it
on my butt please with someone care for
telling me about it
eh ah hold the button okay okay
ah thank you very much i really
appreciate
your uh insightful input or whatever
thank you very much now the next item
shall be
a star how beautiful this star is almost
as beautiful
as all of you are and now i shall
carefully proceed to take the number one
spot
in this race thank you all for your kind
support kfb
i love you all i appreciate you working
for me for free and giving
me all your salaries i appreciate that
very much hello v gamer 511 i'm sorry
that
i said you were a little [\h__\h] before i
didn't mean that
oh um thank you for taking away my
items there's no problem i'm not mad or
anything
let me just take that thank you to make
up for it that was very kind of you to
put it down there
you all are self cons concert how do you
say that consider
ring eyes wait is it over
no okay one more around here we go
i have one more chance to feeding
all of you [\h__\h] yay
what what i didn't i didn't say anything
bad just now
this is wonderful i really enjoyed it
it's just such a nice weather
and um
[Music]
excuse me that was not me
that was my inner demon
[Music]
number five not bad not bad
it's really not that bad i'm not i'm not
do let's be real like
i'm doing much better than last time wow
are your ears well excuse me i told you
to get better quality ears
it's not my problem if you buy yourself
a pair of five dollar
ears you gotta like invest into your
ears
hello sim nice name you're using two
tilt controls oh nice hairstyle by the
way nice hairstyle really like the
orange hair you got
going on there
had a dream about me well who doesn't
dream of me
thank you for the super jets oh [\h__\h] i
don't choose no
yeah i want the winter i want the winter
lands the snow land the wario snow land
i want that one
i can't wait for winter what about you
guys yeah there we go
let's go there's like at least oh my
god there's like at least a four i think
four
viewers i don't know like the people
with normal names
i would appreciate it if you would
change your name to something i can
recognize
so that i know who to fire later
don't hide behind your normal names
expose yourself for the coward you are
let's go good start i would say
move [\h__\h] get out the way
okay drift drift come on kiara i know
you can do it
i've played this road many times
actually on the phone i was quite
addicted to the
to the smartphone mario kart for a while
i got the gold pass and all that [\h__\h]
i was like quite addicted for a while
why would you take it away give it back
to me
get it back fired you're fired i'm
telling you you're fired
no
no are you drunk no i don't drink
alcohol
amma silver phoenix
delete one of those ones from 11 and
it'll be number one
just hack the game or something
just kidding yes here we go
two items okay there we go
yeah i hate that forest anyway that's a
good help right now
just what i
[Music]
skiing needed did you guys know i can
ski
what about you guys can you ski i'm a
good skier i did it once in my lifetime
and i'm a good skier
i learned skiing in like the shortest
amount of time it's just in my blood you
know
okay go son i'm a girl
i'm a cute little ghost and i got a good
item thank you
if yo coming for number one
is this the end already yes oh god no
no no no no that's this is not bad
are they actually trying to lose
are you actually being good to your boss
are you actually following what i'm
saying are you following my instructions
what a shame no this is how it's
supposed to be
are they try yeah you're rehired thank
you
keep on doing what you do let me win i
need
i need a win god i didn't choose again
oh wow this is fine
i can handle any of these roads because
i'm a professional driver
i can drive without holding the wing
[Music]
here we go let's go
i'm ready which road is a super bell
subway goddammit
i'm scared hey somebody
somebody chose the same character good
taste
i know you like seeing that butt
[Music]
okay no oh no item in the beginning
that's okay
i have a good excuse if i lose this uh
this
round that's just one time in my life i
wanna be number one
[Music]
this is not a build road
ah this is so confusing
what's it not called
[Music]
okay no problem i'll just rely on all
those items
[Music]
i just went right through the train
please uh children
don't try to copy what oh [\h__\h] i didn't
see i had those items
don't try to copy what i'm doing okay ah
kfc oh no my biggest
rival and also my secret love of my life
why why would you do that to me
what have i done to you besides
loki um having a
somewhat similar name for my fan club
members in my own store
but that's that's not on purpose that's
totally not on purpose
well i guess i have an injury now you
cannot work anymore goodbye kfc it was
nice
eating your chicken i don't think you
can work anymore
with that injury it must hurt a lot
oh he's back boy
no no and you'll get a
red chill and you get a red challenge
you got a red shell i guess not
i mean that was not fair how am i
supposed to win
against a fast food
uh how do you call that
giant
what a shape okay
nice names nice names how am i supposed
to win
against the fast food giant oh my god
oh let's go for this excite fight oh
everyone likes that one apparently
is it so easy colonel sanders thank you
for challenging me it was an
honor so unfair yeah right yeah
yeah tell them tell them it's so unfair
who is holocento you're looking pretty
with that orange hair you're rocking it
okay german german round here we go
deutsche go round off
german round
let's get lost excite
[Music]
is
la la
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
hmm
in
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you for letting me keep on
half winning thank you thank you
let's see some cute girls in swimsuits
everyone take back your vote i want to
go to the beach
how did you like my german
my house is taught my throat is dead
free language is there
only i can do that
was that again someone said um someone
last time someone
suggested me to switch languages
every time something happens oh what was
that
switch what was that not every i don't
think it was every
it was more quick not not every race but
switch languages every
something yeah well eofy can speak for
but only i can speak free
would you guys like to see me in a
swimsuit
i want to see nina susan
number one
[Music]
papa
i'm number two now but i'm still winning
are you winning kiara yes yes i am
what is that kfc employee doing in front
of me and this dude again
you
[Music]
come on give me a [\h__\h] break
[Laughter]
said he's pure
liar liar liar pants on fire i would say
yo someone eat this [\h__\h]
does it taste good does it taste good
just mix them with the with your salty
tears
and then it will taste even better
[Music]
last round let me show you
how i do when i get like real
when i when i play mario kart my my
english
language ability and my vocabulary
suddenly
is so low
[Music]
yo australian kiara
australian kiana move
come on the back is so much nicer it's
so much more chill here don't you want
to go there it's so much more relaxing
come on australian tiana thank you
and simply bye bye bye bye
[Music]
foreign there's there's an imposter
among us
there's a fake kiana
[Laughter]
fake kiara you cannot be better than me
you have to be worse
than me go easy on me no you go easy on
me
god damn it
i'm heading off okay i will be you
better
you keep on winning wasn't or was it
someone else
i want to win there's only seven minutes
left guys i hope you're aware of that
you better give me a win before this
this stream ends
[Music]
i don't care i don't care which road
whichever road chooses me i choose that
root
i don't choose the root it chooses me
i will be number one i want to be number
one
which one okay
okay there's one less
challenger so a little bit higher
chances or not
which way does it go when one person
leaves do i have do i have
higher chances or lower chances
okay okay food yes not bad okay just
this time relax chill everything's cool
nice
shortcut that i didn't even see coming
got them i didn't i didn't manage to get
up there
but that's okay yes yes
oh birds something from six to three ah
kfb crew come on just stop driving or
something
and be like oopsie uh my mom
called your a a mom called
she said i don't know i don't know i
don't know i don't know any mom jokes i
gotta call amelia
emilia are you watching emily should be
sleeping actually
emilia told me she's going to sleep like
she told me a while ago but
she's watching
tell me a good mom joke to own those
idiots
[Music]
i'm watching the chat that's why i'm
driving like an indian canadian
come on i know you got like a book about
mom jokes
come on don't be shy mom joke dictionary
no why am i 11. your mom so
what ah so hungry she put kfc okay
damn it i hope i did read that right
because the chat was so quick but yes
if your mom is so hungry she puts what
which one you pay for see okay
out of business
oh one more let's go
oh man oh my god she's such a genius
oh dares
four days to touch me if you guys keep
on making me scream like that
i'm not gonna be able to stream tomorrow
okay
korea my thrill hurts
make me happy don't you want to make me
happy you guys just want to
see me cry but imagine imagine me
as your girlfriend right now as your
girlfriend you would want me to be happy
right
so make me happy
[Music]
whatever [\h__\h] that star guys are useless
what the
out out
oh and you a new orange haired
challenger has appeared
which one should we go for oh rainbow
wrote no no that would be such a
[\h__\h]
ah i don't know
please no not rainbow not rainbow
okay now this is i think this is the
last run
um and we will win this because this
time
i will use tilt controls
wait i think i finally understood what
that means does that mean like when you
move your controller and
the card moves along with the controller
like how you
if you tilt it to the right side it
would move to the right side
is that what that means
ah okay okay i will use some
tilt controls let me let me show you
oh
what is this music that's beautiful
actually this road i'm
i see for the first time so that's not
fair
please go easy on me come on
[Music]
oh nice trip nice trip nice trip
oh i like this from what like game
is this world like that all the roads
are like from some kind of game
oh yeah but it really is it from mario
because i did think of that for a second
because there was like a clockwork
uh level i think oh god there was
there was a clockwork level in mario 64
right i i remember that one that was
really
nice i like this music though the new
the music was
was not like this oh i feel so slow
eh
[Music]
fire don't get close to the fire birds
ah
[Music]
it's my last my last race please let me
win i feel so slow what the hell is
going on
i'm so sorry
this stupid bike i throw it in the trash
after this goddamn race
it only looks cute but it's useless
speed
yeah kfbq what up
the mobile trucks oh god damn it
you know a lot about these vehicles
vehicles is that how you say it please
next time teach me
tell me a good combination to go with
that suits a queen a majestic phoenix
like me
okay that was fun
uh upset thank you everyone
cause i messed up
thank you very very much today
for driving with me it was
an honor to drive with such idiots who
cannot follow the rules
[Music]
to let me win and yet you do not learn
you do not learn from your mistakes
you're all fired
i mean i could be told to be like hey
hello stream am i on camera now
okay actually there is a members only
stream in one hour
[Music]
i don't know that's why now i will be
reading super chats
uh from the past i think free free
streams maybe
or even for my throat hurts so much it's
a time
for a cough drop and for a check uh
super chat check
uh please give me a little moment and we
will also switch
to this screen
hello where am i hello
hello how are you doing so whoever wants
to stay
you're welcome to stay we'll do some
chatting in between the super chat
reading
it's always a lot of fun uh super jack
but first i have to chill
and comb calm my nerves down because
once again
you all did not want to follow the rules
i'm very
very very irritated by that
but but i think uh except for the last
ride i generally did much better than
previously don't you think
does anyone know which stream i last
read
the super chats does someone know
because uh i think the ones before the
last
fire and blam stream right because in
defiant limestream
i ended it urgently quickly
but before that i think i did read it
drink some tea oh i would love some tea
now but
i'd have to make the tea first and then
wait like 20 minutes to be able to drink
it for real
my uh ah the minecraft ones i did read
bgm oh yeah good idea thank you
okay so so the fire emblem stream from
there on i have to read okay
you guys are very woof
i hope you didn't get surprised by that
is that do you hear that is that too
loud
so you were one of the kfp crew
i'll read you a super chat like probably
uh a long time later
wait so let me scroll let me scroll i
have to scroll
and then copy it and then send it to
learn managers
and see if we can get it checked
actually let me ask first
[Music]
someone got to add it
got time to check super chat
it looks like no one's online
because if they're not here then i'll
just read it anyway
ah let's see
i'm gonna keep on scrolling until the
end of the day
i hope i can read everything in one hour
though we gotta be a bit quicker today
with the reading a bit quicker than
usually a bit more fast paced because
i want to finish it before the member
only stream
[Music]
collaboration i also didn't read it
right
oh i'm a collab i'm a collab i have to
read those two
okay that's like five streams or so
okay minecraft these i should have been
i should have read already
okay so that's i'm a collab
then the f fire emblem stream
uh
[Music]
and after the fire and blame stream was
the subaru corrupt
and after the civil collapse was this
stream okay
is that four i cannot count obviously
and some of uh goddammit and some of
uh some donations came through and the
members only stream as well even though
it did not start yet thank you so much
everyone
yosh okay one more time copy cupcake
faster i don't have time
um actually god damn it no
no i closed the window
okay you know what i think it's fine if
just this time i just read it
uh directly it should be okay because
you guys are
a good people anyway oh you don't hear
the oh sorry i wasn't looking at the
chat
what do you mean you don't hear the bgm
okay
you that you were right with that that's
very true of course you were not able to
hear it because i
muted it
okay okay i'm gonna
read them directly without checks so
and let's go
[Music]
quiet okay no problem we can fix that
how about this is this better still no
bgm what do you mean no bgm
people who say no bgm even though there
is bgm what is wrong with you
medicated drops mix that was like a joke
going on in the pre-chat previously
it's good now okay about vicks and it
was like what
why why why why
i can't open it the pre-chat
i always open uh i have my
my stream reservations slots stream slot
reservations always open quite early
so i keep the chat open so everyone can
chat and hang out
and also because i'm too uh like
whatever
but yeah everyone everyone has so much
fun together it's really nice to see and
every
every once in a while i show up in a
pre-chat and people are like
okay this time i have a medicated strap
not my usual drops
no
um really my throat hurts so much
by the way um
tomorrow i might only be able to stream
at the collaboration because we're doing
it on every chat every member's channel
tomorrow
probably one o'clock uh one o'clock
japanese standard time
and other than that i probably won't be
streaming tomorrow and i have a
not so good message for you guys
uh monday tuesday
no stream for me
maybe a small possibility that there's a
stream
tuesday late at night for me late at
night so maybe for you
uh morning tuesday but monday uh-uh
because uh i'm spending monday
at home yeah there's some stuff that
needs to be done in my
whole house and i got no internet there
um and i have to stay over there
so friday besides to collab
nothing monday nothing tuesday maybe
something
but it's a good time to rest a little
bit because i think with the
subaru collab and today free streams in
one day
i can chill a little bit but i'm
actually worried i want to stream every
day because i
i don't wanna like um how do you say
fall behind
well i'm already falling behind but i
don't want to fall behind too much so i
wish i could stream every day
but stupid internet provider
moved my date two times for [\h__\h] sake
how dare you
oh
[Music]
it's like my mom is telling me that but
but my mom
she told me she's proud of me
so i don't think she has a problem with
my language
i do have to say though i realized this
also because some people
uh mentioned it apparently
and you like normal like the the
people who come from english-speaking
countries who are like maybe
then like of course there's always
people who cost a lot but then there's
like mostly people who don't curse so
much and who try to change like
for example [\h__\h] and to frick or
something
and that seems to be quite normal over
there
but you know in german speaking
countries we do
swear a lot in every goddamn sentence
actually
i said when i speak german normally like
between my friends and so on i swear in
every
[\h__\h] sentence it's so normal for me
like
it's really normal in the german
language to swear a lot so
probably that is the reason why i swear
so
casually in english and don't feel bad
about it in the slightest bit now
[Music]
anyway let's get started reading just
have to
tell you why i swear so much it's fun
it's fun i i feel like the only way to
express
how intense i feel about these things
is by swearing you know i'm just trying
to
show you my passion my [\h__\h] passion
yeah i'm a passionate person
[Laughter]
okay oh by the way
today today's collaboration with kelly
with uh of course of collapse that
actually met her today
and i i hugged her for goodbye i hugged
i gave her a hug
i love her i love her so much she has
those sexy legs oh my god
okay i have to read let's go
vgamer311 so this is from the amico lab
starting ah actually i
missed you thank you oh yeah we gotta
say thank you
it's been a while everyone's bam danke
shang
thank you man eating doll duncan became
a free eleven thank you soon high
intentional i just want to say that
wow just these these cough drops are
really damn good
i just want to say that you have
single-handedly created the most
wholesome and supportive online
community i've ever been a part of
wow really in these past weeks i've
already met some of the best friends
i've ever had through kfp
and i have you to thank for that oh
that's so wholesome
yeah everyone's uh everyone from the kfp
crew is getting along so well i've
noticed
i'm really happy about that glad to have
you all
being so civil i think that's really
important
with such a huge community it's really
important that everyone is just nice and
respectful of each other and really like
civil
and that people read the rules by the
way read the rules i mean
i i would say in my in my chat uh
usually there's no no problem with
people not reading the rules and
generally i
i for example don't care about the whole
talking in the pre-chat thing like i i i
encourage you guys to do that but
generally my peeps are really nice but
if you ever go to a different stream
please always read the rules yeah
got it i know you guys do it anyway
because you all are smart
yes i'll be the kp janitor
[Music]
mm
the foreshadowing but i think at that
point i already told people that it's
going to happen
mary abby chris thank you and sanji
shawn donkey
faction calling questions
[Music]
you will never know what i said
thank you back beat highway dankeshen if
you end your drops in your eyes about
the game you
i think there's a lot of super chats in
this stream that you
try to teach us about the game about the
games that we played especially chess
people being like really like desperate
to end the chess game therefore sending
super chat
super chats to help us with the chats
because they just wanted it to end
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
okay
scary okay
[Music]
hey
papa is making like figure designs and
they look so
goddamn good even me who does not
collect figures
at all
um
[Music]
there's like a new blackrock shooter
figure
if you check my papa's twitter you can
see it
yeah they're really awesome if you like
figurines you have to buy one
and warlock
[Music]
who in the chat uh actually like buys
figurines
[Music]
papa no spots
like i i got like figurines as presents
before
but i'm like i don't know what to do
with it
but if it would be a figurine from my
papa
then i would like place it next to my
bed
and look at it before i go to sleep and
be like ah my papa is so amazing
[Music]
i think he does i think he likes the
relationship we got going
on
anyway let's continue nice to see you
all connected and collecting
figurines very cool
thank you brandon wilson thank you
matthew cline duncan peter licks the
character
holy [\h__\h] that that cough
works so well you know
what
so that would be fun but it would be
like a
it's like it would be an event where you
don't know when it ends because
there might be uh quick rounds but there
will probably
be mostly like never ending rounds so um
it's a bit difficult i think um
and while some would enjoy it i think
also many people would just find it
boring
or not enjoy it
but i do want to play a chess at least
one more time
with ame
eventually the day will come when we
challenge
each other again and you will all
you're still watching go to sleep oh my
god
i'm in are you ready are you up for
another chess tournament
between us two
i think while they are all being like no
please
no i think they all want it they all
want it
they want nothing more
than that rematch they want it no please
i know you wanted red super chat
otherwise you would not be sending
a super chat for it
[Music]
bank
one day i'll practice though i'll
practice for next time
let's keep on going don't have much time
margaret and
reluctant reader thank you
[Music]
really needs to sleep she said she's
going to sleep like
at least one and a half hours ago
detonated wait let me check let me check
this
i slept earlier i need to sleep more
well at least she's not playing
minecraft anymore
elvis [\h__\h] detonator
slayer said thank you first i don't know
thank you you want to watch one of the
rings with me
oh we're starting in like half an hour
wait
you got the movie let's watch let's
watch
yeah after this stream there will be a
members only stream
and where we watch lord of the rings the
first movie a theatrical
version though because as much as i love
to watch an extended version
it's been a long day when the cat wrecks
thank you and shift chap dancing
penelope strange thank you [\h__\h] i think
i cannot read all of the super chats
henry dan kishan patrick chen danke shin
sanji shondangashin frank fire cafe
inspector
this better not happen when we're
watching a lot of the rings oh my god oh
well
i mean the movie will probably keep on
going because it's only streamlabs
cutting out for a moment but my my movie
will definitely keep on going anyway
let's continue i don't know
which was the last super chat you're at
i'll just uh repeat the last five ones
imposter i don't know amnesia destroyed
christian gonzales derpy cyclist
v faction
i did know this i did i did know this
did you not
uh hear when i said i'm back maybe it
was one or two seconds later that i was
actually back
after i said i'm back anyway i did
repeat some names
my phone just reminded me of the members
only stream that's starting in 30
minutes
very poor when i want that
[Music]
duncan i love refrigerators shrimping
for shark tank
yo up dog thank you fst
[Music]
ragna thank you for all the memberships
thank you welcome everyone
adam 1 x 0 x 0
0 0
don't know which version i said it and
it's in the description
it's in just read for information just
read the description
in the membership stream it's already
reserved just check it out
it's empty no queen olivier
[Music]
m
you could have won in the first five
minutes
have you moved your queen in front of
emme amez kin
was the king a king instead of stopping
halfway as tour
queen was covered by your bishop thank
you thank you
thank you for the red super chat telling
me how i could have won
garrett nils johnson
you're watching my super chat reading
thank you ami
my super chat reading is not
is it that entertaining she's listening
ah
is it that entertaining as like a
background
low-fi hip-hop beats to listen to kind
of
thing
michael mcclellan
i am lo-fi hip-hop beats to listen to
when studying
martial index thank you haven't you
gonna want to free duncan thank you
so much thank you and why are
more beauty thank you a
tonight
[Music]
knights of the kfp empire gathered now
for empress kiara as she readys for
battle sharpen your swords
check your shields and ready your
drumsticks we write we write for kiara
and the glorious kfp
viva la quiera
thank you for that motivational speech
every time
[Music]
thank you very much
now my throat is hurting again i'm
really not treating it well
uh the past two three days let me get
another moisture on it
one more noodle one more cough drop
what's o7 supposed to be is that like
someone's saluting
like i think i see it and
thank you so much for the red super jet
patrick thank you
ghost of the machine thanks
sorry i'm not reading so many messages
right now i'm so sorry
i'm trying to get it done i'm sorry
i will read more message messages again
next time
[Music]
stop saluting and right thank you you
lazy
i don't want to insult you you lazy
peeps
lazy employees no stop saluting
[Music]
thundershock 81 nice to meet you
patrick chandan yes
what's it like being a european in japan
are you really nice are people shy
around you well
let me just say i do i'm not
anything like european or american
or anything like that i am a phoenix i
don't have
such a thing uh to myself
but i'm being treated nice
in japan but also this whole year barely
have gone outside
so um it's quite all right yeah
uh being treated well
as a foreigner i guess
i have not really made any bad
experience uh that you would say
is because i'm a foreigner no no no
[Music]
thank you for all you do a perfect way
to spend my first birthday away from my
family is watching
my favorite video i think i read that
during the stream didn't i
again happy birthday
[Music]
oh yeah you sent another super chat
replying to me saying happy birthday
thank you thank you
hope you had a nice birthday
monkey thank you so much
thank you for all the members by the way
welcome welcome welcome
be gamer you got a problem with that
well well
you had it coming didn't you you didn't
let me win so what did you expect
huh you little [\h__\h] i love you
i just want to say thank you for sharing
your first fire and blime experience on
stream
you've made a lot of progress since the
practice battle where ferdinand was the
last one left
true keep up the good work thank you so
much
[Music]
i mean of course i made progress people
were like oh
she's so bad at this game but it was the
first goddamn battle
give me a break okay
yeah but yeah it's really a lot of fun
in some way i just want to play it for
hours like
um outside of the stream but i'm gonna
continue
to play it steering stream thank you
thank you so much
tell on wind block thank you thank you
for watching the playthrough thank you
the kimberson show again
you unlock special merchants by doing
battle quests
we still have 20 minutes until the movie
or the next stream
which i'm uh it's my first movie
watch along so i'm not 100 sure how we
do but it'll be fun i'll just start the
movie and tell you when to start the
movie and then
we just watch and
[Music]
thank you
why is the chat too slow say something
say something
i'm giving up on you
29. oh
suddenly you're here huh what are you
doing you lazy asses
keep on typing duncan keep on typing
until the end no slacking around
got it
[Music]
you for the stream i was not able to
watch from the beginning because of work
but i enjoyed it
it like i enjoyed the epic chess game
between you and get uh
yes these people are enjoying that
people are enjoying that you might be
like oh
that was horrible but you all loved it
collaboration now maybe i can at least
read those and those from today
i might read in the next uh stream
i'll be
[Music]
thank you congratulations on being the
first humane member to collab with hall
of japan yam
can't wait for the double travel that
you have in store for us by the way i
have another
uh hello japan collab for next week as
well actually
maybe two in some way i have two
[Music]
more
thank you love you karen don't worry
about the stream being mainly japanese
hope you enjoyed the off collab with
subaru class gladly setting my alarm for
4 a.m for this we love you thank you
so much
this is the third time that i can't
watch the stream because of my work time
so take my last hammond with you guys
thank you so much uh it's sad
i'll try to do a more american
friendly stream sometime soon next week
maybe i'll see
thank you thank you
prepare for travel and make honking
double
to annoy people to devastation to eat
all the bread with our nation
within our nation to the nouns bottom
left with
honks and love to extend our idleness
with cecil and above beautiful
beautiful that was beautiful you have a
talent
thank you judas again
[Music]
and five million more times thank you
general peckham brandon wilson
[Music]
okay
this one probably has a lot of japanese
super chats
thank you
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
welcome to the membership guys so many
new members thank you i think you're all
excited for the
lord of the rings movie huh
nancy of vincent susano to dance
by the way who's coming who's watching
the movie with me after this
[Music]
is
really oh my god i do realize that for
most of you it's a horrible timing but
thank you so much
oh thank you guys mr
yeah i don't really have snacks but uh i
already ate
like a half burnt pizza so all good
so so kona
[Music]
everyone get the movie now watch it with
me in
about 10 minutes maybe we'll move it
like five minutes
question as in for
right thank you so much thank you
[Music]
thank you so much this seems like the
most appropriate moment to contribute my
very first super chat i knew that this
would be
when you show everyone what you're made
of oh i love you
i'm lucky that i was here to see it
here's to all the collaborations in the
future
i love you i love you guys you and all
the others you guys are so sweet thank
you for believing in me i love you
thank you big bird boy hey
[Music]
foreign
take these bills to buy something nice
at that market maybe some fire quakers
this collab
is poultry in motion i'm going honkers
over it you
two are swan and a million birds
together with strong bad
bird puns strong i don't even understand
your puns
but thank you so much thank you
i love you brian thank you very much
[Music]
wild card duncan red rust and cushion
nicholas hill's competition
raziel river thank you scattered chicken
livestock [\h__\h] giselles
[Music]
the streams from today left which i will
read next stream but i did
three free streams worth for super chats
in less than one hour because i did a
lot of talking in the beginning
thank you everyone for watching i hope
you enjoyed the rage stream
and uh i'll see you in the next stream
which is right
after this i just need a little briefer
i might be like maybe
two minutes late
i seen
we're watching hello drinks and members
only first movie
theatrical edition uh for people who
don't understand how that works i'm not
showing the movie on stream so you gotta
buy it yourself but we start watching at
the same time and now
i'm your annoying friend sitting next to
you
who keeps on talking and cannot shut the
[\h__\h] up
which i usually hate those people and i
never speak a single word when i watch a
movie
but if i would be quiet the whole time
then this would not make any sense so of
course i'll be taught i try to talk
and also it's not my first time watching
a movie anyway see you there thank you
for watching today
i'll see you also for all the
non-members tomorrow
one o'clock japanese standard time
collaboration on all
holo en members channels and
after that i'll take a little break one
or two days
they stop
[Music]
a
i'm so dead from today two streams done
one more to go but next one is chill
just watching a movie all good it's all
good
it's all good and i saw cali today
i couldn't be happier
bye bye
why do i need to give you 10 minutes you
have something to prepare
you need 10 minutes for what
wait what do you need 10 minutes give me
10 minutes
what's the movie oh my god you guys
i told it five times already
it's there let's look at the rings
when did the stream now i told you it's
now
it's now
okay