[Music]
foreign
thank you
assistant
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
no no
no
no no no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
questions
foreign
thank you
[Music]
I'm tired
okay not so bad
but I wish we could
just go back to sleep
how long
um
[Music]
I'm tired but I'm an angel I can be your
angle
or your day
um
hello
[Music]
so much wow this week
there's actually not so much water this
week but I'm glad that you feel that it
it's it's a lot of Wawa this week it's
not really though
if you consider that I have given myself
three days of non-streaming
um
but so far yeah so far
many many one more
[Music]
um
yeah I don't think it's so bad no
oh
cats are zooming I've noticed they
always Zoom after having gone to the
toilet what is this why why I guess they
feel very freed up after
you know giving something to the
cat toilet robot Overlord
[Laughter]
it is
on the toilet
yeah you know the toilet I currently
have it standing in the
um room where also the guest bed is
moved some things around but yeah so
I've had already
several people sleeping there
with the toilet in there the good thing
is it seems like during the night my
cats
you seem to not really go to the toilet
um so
yeah they they stay with me in bed
actually I'm actually surprised because
um I feel like they would go more often
than a human
actually I wonder
I do think so though because they're
smaller and they eat and like instead of
having free meals per day I feel like
they eat in little
portions here and there
but anyway yeah yeah they stay with me
all night so they don't use the toilet
at night usually maybe at most one time
per night
um but no the guests have been fine
nobody complained so if I was my mom and
my brother
um
but the smell is totally fine like I
asked them if it's okay if they don't
mind my mom doesn't mind at all but my
brother also didn't mind
the only problem is like if they go then
the noise of it turning around
is a little bit loud for a couple
seconds like maybe 20 30 seconds it
takes a while but then but then the
smell the smell is really well contained
within the thing
um
yeah it would be difficult for me to
understand cats be looking at me and
like
you you wouldn't get it
after watching The Joker so many memes
stuck with me not much louder than the
coffee grind I know
um I don't grind coffee so
it's been a while since I heard a coffee
grinder
ah
maybe it might be a bit louder than that
depends on the coffee grinder
yeah I can use the meme all the time
[Music]
and I recognize more memes too like uh
yesterday or the day before I was going
for Twitter and I saw I think one of the
niji Ian girls probably
uh posting or using or retweeting a meme
or so of themselves as a joker on on
stairs and I was like I get it
just now whoa
I felt like
um you know part of the crew now of the
cool people who get things
yay
foreign
[Music]
don't start till I walk in right
I think that was it
yay
[Laughter]
[Music]
yay meme learning stream yeah funnily
enough that was the first idea of collab
that I had with Gouda or Floyd with four
collabing with Buddha
back in the day we never did it but
before debut I was like maybe you can
you know we can do a collab where you
teach me the memes
hmm
but having to teach someone
memes
must feel like
it would have probably felt too good at
like teaching like a grand uh Papa or
Grandmama
uh about what the young kids do nowadays
and Dad itself is [\h__\h] lame
that must that must feel kinda lame so I
don't wanna I don't want her to suffer
like that yeah
hmm
oh my my my wings are kind of lopsided
let me try to fix that
oh
you're better
you don't even see the other side anyway
um I'm angel
I'm Christmas angel
[Music]
okay I'm gonna pose for you aha
oh my God an angel I can't believe it
did she come to get me and bring me to
heaven or to hell oh
why am I why am I stalling why am I not
playing the game
I'm gonna play side of spy uh today
she's being cute again ah
okay for the membership
thank you soon
so no no I do want to slate inspired
questions
what do we say to Spire as
[Music]
who do we slay this fire as
here we are oh
[Laughter]
um since the last time that I have
played satisfire
on the stream everything went so well so
I thought hell yeah
I'm I totally get it now let's play more
on my on my
steam deck
uh while cuddling up a bit but that
didn't go so well
I tried a million times and I never got
the deck I needed the cards I needed
and the relics that would be good and
overall it was everything shitty
thank you
thank you thank you
yeah it was really bad RNG and I I
didn't have I feel like maybe if chat
was around I would have still been able
to somehow
you know turn it around
um with the big brains
of everyone combined I feel like surely
surely
so yeah that wasn't so fun I got really
frustrated
and let's see like what state was I in
so this must have been from a steam deck
right
but what's going on here
it's interesting uh I think I was going
for block again yeah but I didn't get
the right cards
and then this champ obviously wrecked me
several times do you want to try guys oh
yeah I got confused
uh what from
[Music]
funny you know
I'm always like all right I'll try it
anyway not that I like really wanted it
but yeah this neckline yeah yeah
even with the snackle eye as you can see
from the relics I got quite far anyway
thank you
thank you so I saw happy birthday to you
yeah well do you want to try fix this
situation obviously
[Music]
um
let's see
no I don't even wanna I don't I don't
have the brain for this
abandoned I don't think whatever
devastation
I wasn't prepared for this
at least I still get some
stuff from it
um snack away do me no good
yeah okay
foreign
it's okay
if I play and win now then we should be
able to slay the Spire right
hopefully
oh
okay
who should who would I choose because I
feel like I want to go with someone I
mean I played everyone until this point
but I want to go with something that I'm
somewhat confident in I would say the
things that I'm confident in would be
the the endless loop deck that we had
with her
or poison that's it's been a long time
since I played Poison but it was really
easy right
which one was silent was this one the
silent okay
now a poison run of Silence
has been a while
could do that one
um
dancing
I haven't tried I haven't tried yet I
want to do something that I have done
already so that I at least somehow know
what I'm doing
um do I have to do Ascension no okay
level one level two
all right then let's go
poison it is
hello again if I if I would have won my
past run
then these options would be better right
God damn it
that is unfortunate
should I make the audio High uh you know
louder for you
do remove oh
but Max say it's been no
they're not bad I think
yeah you would do this
why not choose one of these ones oh wait
but let's also remove one card without
losing HP
[Music]
wow okay
uh one strike one defend
I suppose
[Music]
it's back the PGM is back
oh
it's been a while
wait what's that that that
uh instrument that makes it what's that
instrument it sounds a little bit like a
dude machine
a very big
uh deep dude machine
is it a tuba
[Music]
Hey listen
horn Cuba
maybe a tuba I don't remember what a
tuba sounds like
such hello
a big big tooth machine you know there's
little dude machines and then there's
big dude machines and the big dude
machines are the parents of the small
dude machines
yeah yeah they raised them to become big
tooth machines
okay I'll turn it down again
French horn tuba and trumpet you sound
like you know what you're talking about
chunky boy
um let's stop appreciating music and
appreciate this map
um there's one on fire here
where should I go
[Music]
um
maybe not here because the shop would be
too early kind of
not necessarily but
[Music]
where's where's the next shop here here
would be a shop
could go
oh wow okay I could go here
one fire shop Two Fire
free fire
aren't there routes with four fires
oh but then
ah and then we can go to this one
eventually because I was gonna say uh no
Elite but no there's here one one oh but
that's not on the road
but that would be the only Elite
um
find the own violence to get the ending
ah okay okay okay
so we could let's see if there's a path
where we get another not really on this
if we give up the shop then we can get
another Elite
but it doesn't look like it oh well
whatever I will
I will start
start here
[Music]
whatever so we're going for poison
mm-hmm
[Music]
neutralize was this again
that's exactly how much block I need
nicer
[Music]
you know the other day after playing
slightest spider the last time I
installed magic together ring
uh online thingy the PC game
but the
[Music]
yeah and then I I started the tutorial
but I I didn't even finish the tutorial
because I don't know I got
distracted or so
and
I got distracted and then after that I
thought I just forgot about it
completely so I haven't played since
but I wanna
get back into magic together maybe after
this latest fire Arc
oh I don't know about perms actually
archivist I I actually have to check
that
I don't think it would be too much of a
problem to get perms well no one knows
you never know
can I drink my teeth perfect first round
I did that all by myself but it's not
like I had much choice of cards
um oh uh oh
Bane would at least make sense of a
poison deck but in general I don't know
about the cards
or or prepared no no because it's free
zero cost
Bane being bad free
um discard one card
helps you cycle your deck
all right I don't have poison in it but
we will we will we will
and of course we don't have poison yet
we will get there
um We're not gonna do anything in
particular then let me go full damage
[Music]
okay
it's just so addictive it is
DND prompted when I already have
dandeepers I don't know
propriet is good to get your poison when
you need it I mean eventually we'll have
so much poison that we don't have to
look for it hopefully
and
this card
I'll take one damage
that's okie dokie me
I like the shift deck of a poison but
let's go with that I I want to try shift
that previously but then I didn't get
the cards and then people told me I
don't even have the cards
um unlocked yet that I would need for a
good shift run
[Music]
let's try to remember not to try to
force a deck
we will force it because what what other
choice do I have
[Music]
if that not good versus final boss oh
blessing of the forge I'm gonna hold
cards in your hands
poison
we got a poison card deadly poison I
don't remember using this one
in my poison one but maybe I did
um
sounds good but we're going boys you
need to choose a poison card
right all right all right I want the one
that the flask that uh randomly uh
applies poison so and so many times it
like bounces the bouncy one I want that
card that was fun and
should be able to take you down and
apply poison to you
yeah bouncing flask again good card good
card
good card isn't it I like neutralize I
think neutralize stayed with me for a
long time and in the poison run as well
I remember like you have a neutralize
you have a neutralize you guys telling
me
I'm a survivor
good starting Korea
um
I feel like Chad you and me we're
talking like we know you know I feel
like we're
I don't know isn't it nice
that we're having this kind of
conversation where I sound like I know
what I'm doing so far and
I feel like Reviving you know
uh isn't that beautiful
I would have liked another attack card
to finish him off
oh that sucks
I have slime with this card uh
no this card is just discarding um that
wouldn't help anyway bye-bye
weak potion
of
um no poison card
yeah AOE
didn't we have this card last
time
feels very familiar
yeah
it's a decent card
four damage to All Enemies twice and
then probably upgrade to five or six
damage
to all the enemies twice
[Music]
I want to believe in getting more poison
cards
but who knows if I will
but if I don't get the good cards that I
need anywhere then then I feel like I'm
abandoning anyway so
I believe in getting better stuff later
all right
[Music]
huh
playing with stuff up some old deck is a
big part of the game
[Music]
we gotta neutralize
looking good
applying poison to you
[Music]
I'm discarding this one
ah I wonder I could have probably killed
which he will die anyway it won't be him
absentee I might not have eight luck
we're fine we're fine there we go there
we go
that's what I'm talking about
okay
ah so far so far I only looked for help
when choosing cards
was this delicious
there's four numbers for each skill in
your hand
oh I read I read poison no
um
alchemize
a random potion exhaust hmm really
okay
never had that one
and let's go to question mark oh you
come upon the dapple looking cheery
Gremlin I think we had this before
ready of course you are
let's play roulette gamble gamble oh is
this even fair
do I click oh
head removal
okay at least it's nothing bad
okay
I'll remove a strike
it's free
thank you thank you
okay oh
do I have to do this
now should I do this
recall
not yet I can take it on any campfire
okay
oh
upgrade
just
seven poison
free alchemize
two
[Music]
umiz alchemize or alchemize
poison please no
no didn't give me poison guard
alcohol
here's alchemize
a Swiss person might say sorry
that's how I was saying it too
um
apply some poison
gain some block
get rid of this
wait obtain a random potion doesn't
doesn't mean I have to use it right away
right
so every battle I get a free potion
because it exhausts so oh
oh
I don't even have to use it
foreign
now I get it
yeah now I don't have to worry about
potions
three damage stuck attack
um
foreign
what did you do
I can't play attacks that's okay I
poisoned on you anyway
it doesn't save you from death
[Music]
a potion
it doesn't
should I get rid of one of those for
that
weak potion for the new one okay
what do we have oh
[Music]
shift cards
why
why isn't
oh Japanese
poison
don't
go
play Dance
no no no no no no no no no no
I mean
getting energy would be good though no
skip
I'm not happy with those
okay do we want to go for shop right not
for the extra Elite
shop shop shop we gotta go shopping guys
I'm gonna take you shopping and you can
carry the shopping bags all right
all right
I don't have the eight block card I
would like
no
no I want the eight block card
can I kill one
possibly yeah
if I use two point I can also weaken
[Music]
uh
wait a second
foreign
ah Papa potion next okay
explosion got some block
okay
um
a little bit of block
hmm
wait if I apply five poison it will die
just by the poison right
doesn't matter how much block it has
okay so that one's
taken care of
me but that one or that one if I can I
don't think I can
just try to weaken them for now then
maybe another defense though
ah because I can't
only 10 damage
oh
I got 10 from this now
all right yeah maybe better this way
okay ah okay I get the portion now
[Music]
um
one of three random colors cards to add
to your hand it costs zero this turn
drink
I'm just gonna use it now
oh X random colors card into your hand
they call
sounds like a potion
create all your cards for the rest of
combat
beautiful card
it's a holy card
should I use it now
yeah two repeats the potion
huh
this card
one block
attack you if only there was some poison
on you
that's me on the art it hit
ascending to godhood that's what that
means
Apple Apple fiosis
that reminds me I dreamed of the
but in my dream it stood on
an island a small baby Island and I
I fought a God that was protecting the
pan feeling
while I was flying I shot him with
arrows
and eventually took him down
[Laughter]
[Music]
sounds epic yeah I don't know why I did
it
thank you
because I wanted to explore the pantheon
and then the God was like [\h__\h] off and
I'm like but but sorry and then he
attacked me and charged at me and we
flew around and I shot him with arrows
sounds like God of War oh I kind of want
to try playing that game by the way
all right
hey
God of War isn't there a new one
I don't know if I can but uh
I don't know go to the top what's that
cute what's that what's that never seen
before
intangible we're just all damage taken
on HP loss to one
oh cute
so cute
so I will only get one damage in a turn
so when I have a boss that was about to
give me like 50 damage I'll drink that
super potion yeah I've never seen that
potion before
oh poison coins so if you're trying to
play two points into all enemies I play
five poisons and we already have the
other poison should we go for noxious
films
hell yeah good stuff finally finally
we're getting started just now
just now
[Music]
whenever you climb a floor again 12 gold
no longer works when you spend any gold
out of the shop well
um
yeah oh no I have to take the sapphire
key right
I have to
it's okay I was gonna say anyway that
[Music]
um
a money Relic is not
yes
[Music]
well you had to have some poison card no
no
poison guard
when viewing your Dropout the cards are
now shown in order
no potions no need for potions but yeah
remove
block
[Music]
a rain
from who
Alpha
Duncan we're playing fly the Spire right
now we're going for a win obviously uh
um yeah
I don't know if I want any of these
cards
Madness
new card in your hand to zero
no
that's game time Vlog till deal 10
damage
acrobatic straw free cards discard one
card
you're bored Mommy
no I skip
I'm picky
I'm picky I'm picky but it's about time
that we
get good cards for our deck uh how's it
looking here
not so bad
oh
we're called recall always made so far
we barely took damage so that's good
um
let me see what does that do
free poison to All Enemies all right
yeah
fun Mia house
we stay in German
y house
okay are these the super Rats from Joker
again again a meme a meme
I get it now I understand everything
we need to use potions so I can get a
new potion
should I just play the top three cards
of my Dropout they would be free right
or upgrade all the cards
[Music]
I'll upgrade
yeah
okay colors potion
[Music]
Survivor
this card
how much damage are they doing okay then
I'll discard the other block
this one
should I discard the two strikes and
hope for something else
foreign
I thought I had two more energy for some
reason
see they got some poison nice too oh
we can you and I might just take the
four damage maybe I don't know
uh no I don't even have to
foreign
I'll take him this one down next turn
see I expected him to attack next turn
that's why I wanted to get rid of him
first
before him because I knew I couldn't
take him down anyway tactical thinking
guys strategy strategy
[Music]
that's it
foreign
backflip
okay a one block card is okay I guess we
can't at this point we can't keep on
rejecting cards
because I need cards
buddy
where is my
I want my poison card
[Music]
it's also noted God's sake
maybe I shall drink
[Music]
what was this possible but hey I got Ken
Block
oh I got the same one again
oh it did use it
I just won't happen until okay okay good
good
I assumed it would happen right away
okay then we have 10 Vlogs maybe a bit
more blog could happen but
would apply the poison to
um strike
foreign
[Music]
and then we're only down to 10 damage
let me see
there we go
apply some more poison control
[Music]
him actually
for damage oh they weakened me
no
that sucks
or maybe maybe I should have kept that
one
it will die with poison if I attack too
ah okay
um
I almost feel like drinking another
potion
[Music]
yeah no block
see now we have block
a little bit
[Music]
we get plenty potions don't worry this
one's dead this one's dead oh they're
all dead
didn't even have to lift the finger
the car doesn't enemy loses free HP whoa
that's kind of like poison
not really
skip okay
here we go
let's go let's go oh
ah to you
um
what do we have in my starting hand
I will discard
block I will play this I will discard
another block I obtain the potion
this one again I got it three times in
umbrella is this a bug
hmm should I plant one
maybe I wait
[Music]
excuse it
uh-huh
hey we got the noxious noxious noxious
noxious fumes
[Music]
it's gonna put it on you for whatever
reason wait all right blocks that [\h__\h]
did it block the
huh yeah in the game of the debuff okay
we have to make that happen I guess
noxious
[Music]
oh no my deck will be full of that
discarded
ah
we'll take another one
still not that much block but
starting those can be dangerous it will
cycle ah ah because otherwise it would
have um what's the word
oh okay oopsie
oopsie oopsie oopsie I thought I've
exhausted yeah
forgot
um
oh
into a draw pile they cause zero just
comment
um
oh I couldn't even look did you see a
good one
hopefully a good one in there
it is blur game five block block is not
removed at the start of your next turn
and all enemies lose six strength
strength of this turn exhaust
uh-huh
[Laughter]
strength
yeah I'm not gonna play it yet I think
foreign
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
only get the stupid defense cards
an attack card or so would have been
nice
that was a stupid
um invitation for whatever
oh yeah I use them because I'm keeping
on the Block
[Music]
okay up to 10 blocks we apply a weakener
oh ideal some damage hmm
hmm I still have so many energy and so
much energy
what a waste
I'm saving the ghost not worth using
right now
oh here's it when there's some bigger
damage coming
oh oh that one
is dead
that one I neutralize
had some defend and we good
[Music]
okay okay
we got rid of one
gain some block
s oh getting some more free Block
and apply
some poison
is
lower back and blow back
now she's learning I already learned
I know what I'm doing okay this is dead
he did
I was just turn skin one intangible
which was all that much chicken oh
that's pretty sick
that's pretty good
and we get the key
and we get the guns and hopefully a good
card
[Music]
wait
did I get both I don't understand did I
get both I thought because of the other
one where I I only could choose one I'm
confused
I'm excited too okay okay I get both
okay okay good because I thought I had
to choose again
God damn it
damn it the game wants me to play shiv
but it's too late
it's rough it's rough it's rough but
and now I'm preparing I don't wanna
wait so if I get the last key in that
campfire now do I still have to go for
all the other upcoming
like stages
okay
I take the key now
we don't I don't with 44 HP I'm feeling
somewhat confident
not necessarily needing to rest
um
I'm about to
of Grant
okay
I think I'll upgrade deadly poison
because I need more poison
I need more poison
you have a lot of potatoes to get the
red key better to operate first and get
the key later to get more commas with
the upgrade
[Music]
okay
oh
what's up
potion down what is this a ritual cult
called potion kfp potions
uh ritual gained strength at the end of
your turn
Pike's additional damage to attacks I
guess we'll drink it
[Laughter]
[Music]
um okay
start with poison
dragon card oh
it's so quiet why is there no bgm
o
oh no
that kept me that can't be waiting
[Music]
it's weird I was still started still
sleeping
[Music]
oh four times
six is 24.
now it's
18. baby
[Music]
18 18.
uh
oh sick
court
for only four okay okay
[Music]
should I I should I need to be careful a
little bit so I will play one block card
are you winning Kiara so far yes I mean
the deck isn't looking ideal but
[Music]
it do be like that sometimes 10 damage
oh okay
[Music]
I mean that actually that's pretty
meaningless
[Music]
I couldn't discarded the burn oh yeah
that's meaningless
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah I just spotted by this Garden
it's like that other car that will just
come back and um
ah but if I just it will come back
anyway but if I discard it at least I
don't take the damage
[Music]
anyway
we'll be fine
[Music]
now we're doing poison baby
I can't block the berniever right
[Music]
again discard oh he's also blocking
it's worth one
oh I can't block it is it
wait then if I can block it then it's
better to play a backflip
[Music]
foreign
I'm blocking it but since I have one um
energy left I might as well discard it
oh well same results though
same results
this is the same result right because I
would have blocked it
because I'm gonna lose the block anyway
hmm
that's nice
when does that happen huh when did I get
him so far
[Music]
seven times two fourteen
foreign
[Music]
will get healed after that anyway
and we can we can
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah yeah
a text potion and
person whenever an attack deals unblock
damage apply one poison
hmm
I'm not impressed but it's a poison card
[Music]
it's not that good
skin made a freaking Flash
it doesn't seem so good but it's better
than nothing maybe
is for hybrid poison shift oh oh
that makes sense because like we have a
proper poison build you don't really do
much damage more much attack on your own
um thank you
[Music]
whenever you play a card game oh
you're holding on the squad all none
Attack cards
no definitely not unload
freeze also for shift builds
after the image is good for final fight
but unnecessary
okay all right let's go for that I guess
just like this one
there are additional two cards at times
you can draw one more original card
gain energy at the start of your turn
you can no longer gain gold no
all enemies start coming with one
strength
[Music]
play Snake
wait what
but then I get one last card
huh
draw one additional card there are two
additional cards
[Music]
ah turn
comment ah okay
can't read
welcome to the city
is there burning one here too no I guess
because we only have one key left
that that down so we're afraid to go
wherever we want
there's shops double shop here
do we want to double shop we have a
little money
and then could go to the boss through an
elite year
question mark
[Music]
um
need to trim my dick
[Laughter]
[Music]
laughs
[Laughter]
Jojo
I didn't even say the last two letters I
didn't say them it sounded like it but
then I didn't say them
I want to say deck it's just too close
to one another
it's too close
oh man oh God
I'm crying
oh God
hello hello hello uh
[Music]
now what now I need to
oh God damn it
[Music]
so uh let me play a card okay so this is
one of those cards that I want to play
right in the beginning
were
they really want me
to play shift what the [\h__\h]
what's going on
what what
[\h__\h]
free
the free cards
look at those blocks
hey he's down
but yeah I'll give poison to him
[Music]
yeah he's almost dead
yeah yeah maybe I mean someone said
there's a like a a hybrid
deck
maybe we can at this point aim for that
but we already skipped so many shift
cards too
[Music]
uh okay he's dead uh
-huh I already have enough luck
see how I'm not even like thinking boy
or talking I'm just
playing those cards baby
foreign
[Music]
well we're already rejected and Venom
and uh
catch the tiger by his toe I don't
remember the rest but it's you
congratulations
oh speaking of crowd crowd
crony was Advent calendar Tanto uh in
charge of last night did you see it
and before that was fun and crony they
made cookies it's so cute
I was hoping that someone would do
something like
like that similar so very nice
[Music]
seven
fun seeing what they come up with yeah
actually you know I really do expected
or or even hoped for just everyone
recording a simple 30 second message or
something like that that's really all I
was hoping for
um so I'm really glad that everyone is
doing even more than that and becoming
creative and so on
[Music]
what do we take
Next Step
it's upgraded and free
[Music]
play Dance
back flip
running half back I'll go for back
something all right all right all right
free damage
[Music]
so okay let's go shopping
another noxious fumes huh
what do you say chat
foreign
additional copy of a card in your deck
um
shows a power card
[Music]
tactician can be good
this car is discarded from your hand
gain energy
I guess I have a bunch of discarding
cards but
the tornado bottle tornado how about
card what's up what would be a power
card
wait a power card that's not in my deck
or at any power card
[Music]
any
oh it is one of my deck oh
start each comment with this card and
then I would choose noxy's fumes for
example
hmm
I don't know if that's it
[Music]
what
oh but also could do it of after image
they're both cards that I would want to
play in the beginning
so I'm just going with this card in your
hand
okay okay
and now no money left oof but there's
already a shop waiting for me
yeah
we don't have to go there though we
don't have to
all right
[Music]
got the ship one again
and I'm not gonna do it now because the
block that I would gain from it
wait what am I talking about
not getting blocked from it anymore
I ought to win oh you're right
because
the poison
[Music]
uh-huh
oh wait oh yeah
he didn't take my poison
[Music]
10 damage you want to do 10 damage
no I say no
[Music]
should I get the shifts
okay you see to survive yes I will
survive
and Phoenix
foreign damage
[Music]
not anymore
so the videos have been very good I
think the one that's coming up tonight
if you're gonna like very very much
[Music]
um I'm inspired by it how everyone else
has been also doing their best and being
very creative
um
yes it was already kind of spoiled so
I'll just say it I might be involved
again
but because of that I was like what can
I do what kind of video
should we make and then I thought of a
fun game
and honestly that game that I thought of
I mean it already exists but
um
I was still thinking
no um
I don't know
I was thinking
it would even work as a stream so I
might even use that idea that I use for
the whole year and admin calendar
to make a stream out of it
eventually
but he'll he will die right okay
[Music]
they just don't want me to play a poison
run
[Music]
bad RNG for once usually my on stream
runs have good RNG right
[Music]
I don't really have the money for the
shop
not even to discard a card do Shield
there's another shop up here
so I think I'll I'll go to the enemy
hello uh what was it with these ones
which one do you fight first what is
recommendable
iron Jesus on his lunch break yeah
Catalyst yeah you remember
the Mystic kill the warrior the Knight
the Healer wait which one
Chad
Mystic okay okay we'll build Mystic
first
[Music]
upgrade
foreign
[Music]
music in this game is really nice it is
but it's also kind of always the same
[Music]
well it seems like Chad has very split
opinions on who to kill first
and
hmm
oh
I don't need to block
[Music]
man
what do I do with all this power
what do I do
LC race does a lot of damage
to worry about it
he'll die soon enough
this card this card it's a part
I feel so smart
and discard
[Music]
this guy
comedian oh so funny
and
[Music]
I don't like this
I don't like this very much
[Music]
apply
some more poison
weaken him
prepare myself
and gain nothing out of it
[Music]
even alone is useless but night alone
can hurt a lot
[Music]
I should have used the upgrade potion
maybe or anything really
[Music]
never mind we're going for the Healer
and he's going down so
at least he's not attacking this turn
either so I can focus on attacking him
[Music]
he's only doing one damage but increases
attack damage but no no no it's good
it's all good it's all good no need to
worry
free damage some more poison
you guys are just too worried
no need to worry so much
no free card okay
[Music]
oh that was it that was my artifact oh
that's the first time I see it working
oh well
[\h__\h] it didn't even get to attack me
really
[Music]
um
no poison
[Music]
um
what the [\h__\h] we're still hoping we're
still holding on
to the possibility
of getting a decent poison card
foreign
hello are you from the cult that I had
that feather from
how's it going how is cold life how's it
treating you hmm
wait let me drink something how about
dicks
because there's already a lot of
upgraded cards
yes
um well wait do I have oh yeah
a little bit too late but
example sure to get the energy potion
over here who's there also a better
Target
but
what's your problem with birds
wait I barely have any block
five fifteen but I get another five
block right okay what do I
[Music]
do it I didn't I didn't
I'm confused
should have maybe drunk and drunk into
portion
[Music]
thank you
don't
[Music]
want some playing Block cards
um
[Music]
all the days again oh well
sometimes it must be GM I hear meows in
the background and when I started
playing this game I always thought it
was my cats
I've gotten used to it and it can't fool
me anymore do you also have this
sometimes of bgms I think something is
happening in reality but it isn't and
you're really confused about it
really
[Music]
it
yeah it's really not many relics is it
um
science
hey yo
[Music]
but we had to give up on one because we
chose the key instead so
that's why one of them is missing
wait my chat stopped Let me refresh it
welcome back chat
one beat him in Pokemon sounds like a
phone ringing
that was a video in the game that at
some point made a sound that sounds like
just like someone opening your door
opening
that's creepy
Northern Craftsman macros has a part
after the first course it sounds like my
mom shouting at me through my headphones
what
now I have to re-listen to that maybe it
also sounds like my mom
that's weird
foreign
[Music]
ER is working again
I think right yeah
[Music]
it sounded sounded like my mom shouting
at me at one point and was it also North
from Cross
[Music]
I don't know if I should replace it
99 vulnerable
oh [\h__\h]
finally why did you keep me waiting so
long you know we're testing me right you
were testing my strength but now you
found me worthy of receiving you finally
thank you thank you
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
um
I guess we can upgrade
we can survive 41 HP is all right
random enemy four times
ah finally
finally
shall we go to the elite
[Music]
minions
cute
uh what after image
she knocks his films
backstab and he did
[Music]
oh
I don't have oh
[Music]
there you go there you go there you go
oh I could have also drank the energy
potion oh the fault is fine
[Music]
it's a bouncy boy
here we go
I don't bounce
it all went on the same one
oh
[Music]
here it comes oh wait she gets more wait
a second do I have to take down the big
boy first huh
no he won't do the 25 damage wait what
comes first the poison damage or his
damage
poison right
poison first okay
[Music]
and I do have to take down the leader
right
time
[Music]
thank you
I will die if I don't kill the minions
you kind of have to kill them all at the
same time
[Music]
on drink a potion and then uh
uh six damage wait
he loses 6 hp I don't think I can kill
either of them
free
no I can't take down either of them
[Music]
oh okay but hey we blocked everything
all right yes
oh you're ready has so much poison on
him
offend
I might have to drink the ghost potion
okay well see it's good that we still
have that
maybe if we're lucky we'll get another
one
eventually
[Music]
no
oh wait ah they're dying anyway okay it
was really just about him but he's gonna
get some new minions right away is he
oh it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
it doesn't matter let's go
[Music]
Elite down
foreign
Relic
[Music]
that fits what I want to do
finally final I think all the the aren't
Jesus as we said was on the lunch break
and he has finally arrived he says sorry
that he's late
but he's here now and he's gonna do his
best to bless us these cards are not
looking so good but um
free
lunchbox
just because of the beard
or your skip
we got 16 cards
okay
the bend and poison
[Music]
think we might need to remove a card
and then we could still afford
this one
let's remove them
I'll remove a block
before damage all enemies twice
yeah
it's not my luckiest run that's for sure
but I think we can still make it
left or right
no matter where we go
[Music]
I don't think I can go to that Elite
because my HPM
let's let's go here for now meet
a healing Relic if uh Facebook at or
below 50 at the end of the combat he'll
drop it
[Music]
I am below but right now it won't do it
yet
foreign
should we go here
this path
oh wait 31.
that looks good yeah skip the elite um
damaged
wait oh
the question mark was never sharp oh
[\h__\h]
exactly as much money as I have and it's
the only thing I can buy isn't this
destiny
no
okay well it's I guess it's free nothing
happens
a free something
so
we're gonna arrest
or we gonna sniff
or we gonna recall
first okay
this is
[Music]
look I think I have to go to church next
Sunday
every time you play free attacks in a
single turn game four plug more of a
shift Relic
but okay better than nothing
um
[Music]
we'll make good use of it oh
the library oh you come across an ornate
building which appears abandoned a Blake
a plaque that has been torn free from a
wall is on the floor it reads the
library inside you'll find countless
rows of Scrolls manuscripts and books
you pick one and close yourself into a
chair for some quiet time gonna read
Lord of the Rings
she's one of 20 cards ready
do we have something
poison stab
foreign
[Music]
Cloud apply for poison in two weeks to
all enemies
yeah that looks better than the others
Maybe
okay
all right all right all right all right
all right
fascinating
and
[Music]
don't have money
should I go anyway
it's no battle battle fight
all right
we can't hide no much longer not much
longer
bouncing flask
[Music]
nicely evenly spread
and I get a free card I did get a free
nice
[Music]
the same
you know what I'll drink one
[Music]
I don't want two of the same
um
[Music]
what strength stays right
strength stays over the
whole combat I think
[Music]
unfortunately lacking some block
but oh well we do have a healing Relic
so we good or maybe maybe I can I can
attack three times in this turn oh
[Music]
no I cannot that's that's all the Attack
cards I had
um
so these ones are whatever
oh oh I didn't see I only had one energy
left oh well that's fine then I'm
blocking all the damage
he does at least
all right
hey yeah
we're dead
you're dead
money
that's a little bit of a troll isn't it
but okay I mean two two
[Music]
it's upgraded I'll just upgrade the
other one as well
don't take
start off your turn drawing cards yeah
[Music]
and now we're in front of the bus
[Applause]
42 HP
recall
you wanna Recall now
don't see you
I still have one more whole like level
for we're crawling right
okay today's my birthday happy birthday
even if we can recall just next turn
after the boss like immediately
Maybe
I just wonder
with 42 HP is this gonna be rough
what kind of boss is this
because I would like to upgrade the
other flask
and not flask whatever that was
crippling cloud
champion
okay
[Music]
all right pretty Champion Boy
music bugged out
here we go
to Victory maybe I should do some some
squats and stuff to do some damage you
think that might help
[Music]
Oh
I thought I had one more energy I'm so
stupid
[Music]
foreign
enough HP
are you feeling sore from yesterday oh
actually
no
my shoulders feel always in pain so
not in particular not
um I mean
presently known maybe because I took
good care of it yesterday I took a long
hot okay not that long I took a decently
long hot bath and stuff
[Music]
good potion
caught up home
um
[Music]
okay 18 damage is quite a lot uh how to
dodge in a row
and then bouncing glass for crisping
crisping crispy had a crispy chicken
last night that's where that came from
and
seven poison and two weeks to All
Enemies free poison four times
have fun
[Music]
a bit more
a bit more block
I'm also about this anyway with so much
HP I think we're good then we get healed
anyway yeah let's do some bouncing
[Music]
foreign
um
next
[Music]
it's not gonna attack so
well
yes
people have a free shot futile week what
we clean
what what what are you saying 18.
fine school
[Music]
okay that's enough block
and here's some poison yeah
[Music]
that's cool
18 Again
nothing wrong
neutralize
[Music]
poison good stuff good stuff hey I'm I'm
barely getting help from you guys not
complaining
doing way more on my own
just because I need an introduction you
know to
all the characters before but I know
what I'm doing more or less with poison
um
he's dead
he's dead you've done it now yeah I did
it wait two teachers
did he reset my poison how did he learn
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no problem how do I get the more poison
one times two
[Music]
hey you remove my poison I turn on my
incense
it's only fair it's only fair
[Music]
okay
calculator you can't remove that try
removing it or I'll do you a favor I'll
take you down like this
it's a little bit less painful I'm dying
for poison perhaps is it
is a die die die
tangible
what's with all the shift cards
burst sister and your next skill is
played twice
is the poison card a skill
nice okay
well not the snack on my hell no remove
two cards from your deck
and gain energy at the start of your
turn you can no longer rest at
restaurant no I want to rest
although we do have the poof
I don't know cage
who wants to get into the rib cage
which one of you guys
which one
aren't you guys too chunky for the
purpose
[Music]
looking a little bit chunky monkey
hey
[Music]
you dead no why because of the boss
we just worked out with you did you
everyone
um
I'm thin chicken don't fry me
calling us fat
chunky it's a good word
it's a positive word
too tiny for my chunkiness all you would
win an early campfire yeah I'm thinking
so too
[Music]
they're all at the same spot kind of
they all are
[Music]
maybe maybe this one because it's got a
shop and now I got some money
[Music]
so cute
man
I wish I had more energy
hey these guys
[Music]
we're playing are we playing Zelda right
now what's with all the fairies in the
bottles
change that Genie in a Bottle song to
vary in a bottle and I'll be the singer
of it damn
true Paul moose
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] my block
no block no block but we have two
problems
[Music]
okay we'll be fine we'll be fine
oh first hmm should have done that first
maybe huh
[Music]
now oh
it hits
man Poison's too good
[Music]
first is good strength is turning
exhaust
[Music]
okay skip don't like that card
all my incense is working right in the
beginning I wonder how much damage you
would have done normally
[Music]
he probably won't attack next turn
so
I don't think I needed the Dodge and
roll
well
oh he does
how did you know
[Music]
I got covered I got covered
oh
my God and
[Music]
and
I'm blocking everything
I play this game a lot oh they always
have the same pattern they attack these
ones attack every round maybe this one's
the third round that it attacks me in
wait oh
it's hard to burn
s
[Music]
there we go
it wasn't even necessary to burst it
nice or bunny
go back to sleep
yeah
[Music]
looks like a skin
managed to complete the highest
Ascension of Ironclad using defense
build you mean the block build
[Music]
what's the highest
what is this
someone didn't rip out the weeds
[Music]
20.
oh oh so it doesn't go endlessly I
thought it goes endlessly
[Music]
act four is impossible about lots of
luck and survival oh we're going to act
four right normally it's free acts but
this time we're gonna go to act for it
right
[Music]
you can mod it higher no as long as you
recall the key no hurry we won't forget
about it also oh thank you what
thank you thank you all ill for the for
two pinkies actually
[Music]
no no no no no you didn't do anything
wrong
don't worry don't worry
[Music]
I'm gonna play something twice
we played Dutch and roll twice
then we get 12 block
at least
[Music]
oh
you know what I'm gonna use it because
this one's a little bit of a chunky boy
[Music]
in a little bit
it's time for my taste oh thank you for
the membership skipping it's holiday
season
gifts and everything oh so nice
it's the season of Love and
Understanding Merry Christmas everyone
oh did I not already play this kind of
card no
[Music]
we poison four times seven poison and
victory
I forgot which does not stack right we
can't
in terms of 25 goes to 50 or so long it
doesn't but it just
goes on for more turns
[Music]
every day
holy [\h__\h] though why is my HP so low
what happened
incense working
[Music]
um
only black cards I'll use dark and roll
because then I have Vlog next turn as
well
[Music]
take 10 damage is that blockable
holy [\h__\h]
it is blockable oh my God
didn't notice
ah well he's dead
[Music]
do I have to block the constricted
though no right oh
I didn't have to [\h__\h] I thought it was
already whatever there's a card in your
discard pile and return it to your hand
[Music]
it costs zero nice
head leg swing
somebody said we need block like in the
fourth Act
and 14 block is pretty good
um okay I'll take it
we've been so picky with cards so far I
think we can afford it
[Music]
um
shop and
campfire everything yeah because I
wanted to go to a campfire
ah
no poison card what is this climate
reward screens now contain colorless
cards the first time you lose HP each
combat draw three cards
start each combat with one strength or
remote card
[Music]
deal eight damage
at the end of freight turns deal 40
damage to all enemies
this
[Music]
all right I'll get rid of the defend
the end of your turn retain 10 cards are
not discarded at the end of the turn
[Music]
draw cards until you have six in your
hand
all very good for a shift
I think
removing blocks of square yeah but we
just can never Block cards so I think it
evens out nicely
then we get the bigger block easily
yeah I don't know about the rest
[Music]
as if I have no energy
go
save our money and we'll take it
elsewhere
oh
potions I already got somebody
[Music]
no I'm not even I don't even want to
give up my fairies
we could replace liquid memories
when we have fill all your empty potions
lots of running potions foreign
[Music]
slots in total that would be nice for me
right now
are we only gonna be a losing
it's okay
well then we might as well use up a pull
move sometime soon
purposefully well maybe not maybe not on
purpose but oh my God look at my HP what
the [\h__\h] I don't even have the courage
to
recall right now
because I want to rest but
in theory no I have I kind of have to
rest
[Music]
I have a Healer I like yeah but only 12
hp
it's okay we have fairies worst case
okay okay
[Music]
um
uh okay
no defense what the hell
[Music]
there goes the first pair of bottles no
wait he changed his intention
oh
oh he changed his intention no problem
oh no oh no
he's gonna debuff me
but didn't yet
[Music]
I don't feel cursed yet
thank you
[Music]
what
oh what he put a curse in my deck
[Music]
I don't see it
got a funny friend in my deck
[Music]
what I don't see it am I blind oh check
your deck on top right
[Music]
here
oh
it's my it's my roommate my switch uh
roommate
[Music]
a parasite if transformed or removed
from your deck lose free MAX HP
[Music]
what first
refund
you got to keep the Chromecast Ultra
what's that
thank you
you you seem very unhappy with that game
whatever that game is never heard of it
big oof
thanks though thank you
um
damn it that's two that that's so
expensive
he will change intention though right
when I attack him
[Music]
but uh don't see a way of normally
attacking him anyway and isn't except
for the strike
foreign
blocking we want to die once we wanna
all right if you say so
what a phoenix mindset
I have learned so much from me and I
have learned from you all but I don't
think he will be able to kill me
unfortunately
[Music]
it's not happening
instead
[Music]
not dying is an optimal
what you say jet
skip
[Music]
thank you
okay while I healed a lot my soul and
uh
uh no prepare here
and no I forgot what that card was that
makes me get blocked from everything
oh but I might want to do this one
because they're all attacking
I will weaken these words
[Music]
I think that's all right
I'm at least somewhat protected
bullying this is
[Music]
don't worry don't worry we got the
double fairies
I'm not gonna just let it happen like
that though
not so easily
[Music]
discarded
describe this card
ah
[Music]
ah it worked I used my fairy
I used my theory
what's the new one let's turn your next
card let's play twice
[Music]
no one's attacking
maybe I should have played that Quest
that would have killed it but almost
everyone
all right all right all right
oh don't worry
I'm fine
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah right this one's a spiky boy
should have just let the poison happen
[Music]
reduce the cost of all cards in your
hand to zero
bullet time saves his bullets and punk
boots and bullets and Bulletin
[Music]
quit
wasted a lot of potions oh wait what
oh let's buy one quick because of that
sloppy playing there I didn't realize
you know the fairy go bye-bye too
[Music]
it's okay we're lucky we can't get no
fairies don't worry
we can drink the entropic Brew ideally I
want The Relic for the potions now
though
[Music]
it's not a winning run anyway huh
have you guys not learned a lesson from
not believing in me
about things huh
yeah you're dead sorry huh
[Music]
again every time you play free text in a
single song gain one string
another
shift Relic
[Music]
they don't believe in me unbelievable
they don't believe in me how
unbelievable
[Music]
do we want this we can get a good card
foreign
[Music]
yourself losing your way as the walls
and grounds seem to inexplicably shift
before your eyes the constant Whispering
voices in the back of your head aren't
helping things either
ah
don't like don't like this one
[Music]
this would add one curse man
Madness for flask
run this can work when you guys can make
everything work hmm
which race not lose another free MAX HP
[Music]
this is a tough choice
not free we have no more health
[Music]
I would heal and later remove
yes maybe yes it's just one card right
not too too
I can't afford another remote
true and it wouldn't happen this time
but it's just one card
it's innate what's innate
[Music]
need good openers
okay
[Music]
it does the cost of a random card in
your hands and zero this comment
if it reduces one of my two energy cards
to zero then we save one energy
but we would mix two cards in Our Deck
oh well
at my HP but this this
temporary well this is Max imum but even
for temporary right now we're in a
little bit of a pickle alcohol Trace
of pickle that we're in
the big pickle that we find ourselves in
thank you
I'm not risking any more tiny fights oh
be good
could also be bad what are those options
I don't even know this is money this is
a treasure this is healing this is
removing a car this is damaged and what
is that
curse okay anything but anything but the
curse on the damage please please please
please please
[Music]
it didn't even have to rest last time ah
okay okay okay okay okay
now I regret resting but who could have
known
[Music]
who could have known we're back in the
game
14 times 3
[Music]
Sprint [\h__\h] maybe
um playing Dodge and roll twice
foreign
[Music]
Dodge right okay oh some people say
cloud but
ton
[Music]
damage
thank you
[Music]
all right and I block like half of it
oh my instance is working
[Music]
if I play burst I can't play crippling
or bouncing
[Music]
oh I got the duplication lotion again
I told you
[Music]
okay
I can just end it right I'm scared now
to make another mistake but I I can just
I think I can just
[Music]
up well it's okay we have a potion here
not mistakes learning opportunities I
like your way of thinking so positive
prep would help okay
[Music]
so we're right in front of the bus with
40 HP
do we want to rest
because it's a tough boss right okay
okay almost full HP here we go
what was his thing again let's just
what's his thing
something about time whenever you play
12 cards
it's your turn okay I can always only
have maximum 12 cards this is like a
really annoying boss if you
um play
look
look deck now
traditional coins just turned reduced to
cause your whole cards in your hands
play this now
ah it's not 12 in a row it's just 12 in
general oh yeah
[Music]
anything here that we want to do
strength potion Allen and poison potion
[Music]
no strength why not
okay
poison
doesn't count for its time warp so
that's noise damage that we're getting
there
five times three fifteen fifteen fifteen
uh five flow two cards six and six
maybe dodge and crippling
[Music]
cloud
y face reveal how much depth did you
create
uh well I kind of died twice myself but
I had my fairies keep an eye on this
counter
hmm
backflip
Dodge
[Music]
foreign
four-plated armor
[Music]
we converse something else now rip
what do you mean rip
I mean rip
we mean rip
[Music]
oh it
twelfth card
yeah but that's not a ramp
[Music]
yeah but I won't die
um
[Music]
okay
well
counter is reset
this boss ends a lot of runs I haven't
watched him once before but I think we
did well
at that point
um
[Music]
the strike and the neutralize
all right so we can poison him we can do
bouncing and poison because we don't
need to block anything
[Music]
good amount of poison
wait is it at free uh three more or is
he ad free
[Music]
thank you
nice and tangible timing oh yeah
yeah nine more cards okay
[Music]
close up all cards on your hands with
zero yeah I'm not really necessary now
oh I got so many Dodge cards though I
think I'll do backflip
to get
[Music]
um
oh oh okay
foreign
[Music]
well oh I got this strike
I can't do
anything else
unless I get a free card from the back
flip I I can't travel for God again
try to reset
should I
oh yeah the block for next turn
you're still 12 check the limit okay
hmm
okay perfect
calculator
what is he gonna do use a buff
[Music]
and turn
why
ah he will heal to half
[Music]
percent
I only have the who's 100
my God okay and also the poison was
cleared as well
why is this zero
what is bouncing plus zero
oh that one was from Snicker oil
um
okay now I can do normal again right
I don't know if I should prepare because
it will just up the counter
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
gives us a chance to get another block
card that we can use
and we still have points but we didn't
get it
we did not
[Music]
uh
we can neutralize him if we get
neutralized
from Fred
but two we go for the double right
[Music]
wait I can use leg sweep too okay
okay okay
I could maybe get bouncing flask
[Music]
I could try to get bouncing flask
should I
yeah no yes
don't be greedy save it for next year
okay really
[Music]
she won't do the buff again right he
won't heal himself
to 50 a second time right that would be
that would be
[Music]
we can burst the bouncing
or
bullets
um
[Music]
thank you
oh so let's do some damage
oh go for full block
I think strike we want to do some damage
because I'm at 22. two damage I can take
oh wait we get the block anyway what am
I thinking
now
okay ah
did he just reset
he just reset right okay
[Music]
nice
nine times three let's
neutralize we can also prep we can prep
flies
[Music]
backflip first
foreign
[Music]
okay this will hurt a little bit
chocolate
[Music]
but he'll die next turn yeah yay
but at least we made it this far
at least you made it this far
[Music]
well
here we go here we go
this is where it normally ends
until now this is where it always ended
and you kept asking yourself what are we
doing is it really worth it
I don't
you prepare your daggers
I might just attacks not enough
we shouldn't attack we should use the
poison poison the heart you ask yourself
have I been here before the heart pulses
louder and louder as your Consciousness
begins to fade a sudden burst of energy
emanates from inside you jolting you
awake the heart Retreats upwards a large
door is revealed in its place
foreign
the ending
I thought it would be like you know a
long one like the other ones
[Music]
the first time I see this was that the
fireplace is here and not there kind of
bothers me
at least we can upgrade something
I wonder
[Music]
crippling what does gold time do oh it
gets cheaper
I have one crippling or bullet time
[Music]
your next two skills are playing
um
[Music]
after image you're gonna need it
oh this is stackable huh
yeah no catalyst
never got that card
maybe they sell it to me in the shop but
I have no money
[Laughter]
oh
this is so difficult
choices
of bullet would be good
well
okay first
[Music]
let's say you can backflip first
ah backflip to draw on the more cards
yeah we had that um situation before we
had where we had bullet and backflip and
I would have wished to play backflip
first
but it
but no if we have if we activate bullet
and we play burst
[Music]
they're both they work like
and think
your deck is small so you're gonna get
it no early no matter what
you know what let's go for Birds they're
both they're everything's a good choice
but we have to make a choice
now I have no money
[Music]
thing
but I don't think I want it
you don't you don't know I know
ripped
I'm writing your name down if I win then
I want a formal apology
foreign
[Music]
is it always the same boss
probably right
[Music]
please please be kind what the [\h__\h] is
that
oh I'm in the middle
[Music]
uh you guys have to help me with this
one I need a I need a good chance to win
so I'll take as much help as I can get
oh intangible it works right in the
beginning
read
surrounded oh recip more damage if
attacked from behind ooh so first we
have to attack him
[Music]
right use targeting cards or potions to
change your orientation oh I can I don't
I'm not fixed in that position
[Music]
back attack
well no worries this turn
no worries for this turn
I have no
potions right now
um
[Music]
get the films going up
and
backstab you
what do I have in here anything free
only one card I don't know my last one
come on give me alchemize
[Music]
how much damage do they actually do oh
birdie well I don't want to turn my back
on this one
oh
foreign
[Music]
but I can play this one anyway
okay
[Music]
oh yeah right no cards but that's okay
that block is good seven times three
four
wait
no
no don't don't I can't think anymore
okay first Dodge
next two skills are played twice oh
that's fine
we don't want to turn our backs on this
one
[Music]
you don't even get healed after this one
right yeah bye yeah
I got bullet time again
three times two oh that's a week and
week one at least wait wait 48 holy [\h__\h]
but that's uh with me
uh turning my back on him
[Music]
um
I don't know what other car to get rid
of
[Music]
oh guys I should have played this before
prep
honestly what the [\h__\h]
deadly poison okay
[Music]
okay another time
foreign
or save it save it okay
use it
don't drink
I'll drink it I'll drink it
Burns
oh they're both not attacking
this is our chance
[Music]
um
okay we got the burst we can play
noxious films twice
and
first and back flip back flip of course
should I
burst it though
[Music]
your skills oh it's the power oh
and maybe
[Music]
should I double
then what else would I double
whatever but that doesn't really help me
I think I'll play a backflip now
so now I can double bouncing
[Music]
I could no wait let me play prepared
first
and discard the burn
I got another burn
oh I don't have the energy for it oh man
should I wait
we poisoned all
I still bouncing
person feelings no no that doesn't work
together
it doesn't work more long-term rally
than plans
wow
we can at least still like
strike them
[Music]
okay no problem
they're dead
now right
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's like 50 50 again
foreign
[Music]
did we not have anything better to
upgrade
than a strike in a neutralize
Maybe not maybe we didn't
oh you know what we didn't okay
I feel like a different Relic it might
have been better but okay
here we go
[Music]
Invincible can only lose 300 more HP
this turn oh okay
I don't think I'll do this much whenever
you play a card take one damage
[Music]
okay on just one but that's interesting
because the the card that we got gives
back free damage every time it gives me
damage right well that's blockable okay
[Music]
foreign
how it attacks me and with how much
though
[Music]
discards this card and
oh yeah instance burner and we have that
too it will help us
[Music]
Next Step okay
ow ow
[Music]
I'm so scared
what is the skin she's one of three
random skill cuts through your hand if a
class should I play this too
or save it question two
um
[Music]
say for nice and well here it is but
can't free but save it
[Music]
oh
I have done analyze I wonder
oh wait what can
only those two ones are is that because
of the poison already doing some damage
40 50. oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm so scared
thank you
[\h__\h]
but this car is drawn no one
in it
[Music]
it's 12.
four damage caltrumps none of your
attack deals for damage back okay
[Music]
this card well it doesn't matter
right
[Music]
mm-hmm
don't discard it
[Music]
oh oh no
oh
my wife
hey I thought I will draw it again
anyway
[Music]
she it had a barrel you maniac oh my God
chill the [\h__\h] out
[Music]
well this will hurt
this will hurt
[Music]
feeling damaged back at least
hey we got 20 inch P left
and he's not gonna do a bath
[Music]
I failed as hard 10 times
10 times
[Music]
the next debuff oh but he's gonna use
above another people
a drink oh I guess I can just drink it
whenever
[Music]
okay what is X
let me lose x x as much as energy I have
apply x-week exhaust
my all of my energy okay I don't see why
we will use it now
[Music]
um
gotta do some poison okay I have started
to believe that I will lose this fight
anyway
there no one
[Music]
what
I don't understand
[Music]
well because it's permanent
well
[Music]
come on
we're losing this anyway
we're not gonna win this anyway three
times twelve
[Music]
and he took one energy away from me all
right
[Music]
oh oh [\h__\h] I tapped out
oh
[Music]
accidentally imagine it's the game crash
now
[Music]
do you think we even have a chance
if we restart it
[Music]
the deck from the beginning you know the
orangey just was not so good the deck
was just not so good there were cards
that we were missing and eventually we
just took whatever came our way
[Music]
um I should have had like a different
one of the decks I had in my previous
runs
[Music]
I don't know if I Really Wanna
save scum
hmm
because I I don't feel like this is the
deck to do it God damn it
okay we'll do one retry
[Music]
um
I feel like
oops oh my God why did my game Crash oh
no
how did that happen oh the hearts Doki
Doki was just so strong
just once I don't think it will help but
just once you know
[Music]
um what did I do in the first turn
preparing them bullet time right
[Music]
and then I think I got rid of backstab
and strike
[Music]
oh
should I use a skill potion now
[Music]
we have I think a different
a different choice this time right it's
I mean or is it the same I remember
malays and the crippling Cloud but
adrenaline looks new to me maybe it was
the same I guess it's the same
[Music]
um
actually I see it I definitely see the
value of adrenaline
[Music]
the energy would be good and gaining the
cards would also be good
maybe we try with adrenaline this time
[Music]
I play it now
in exhaust
foreign
[Music]
what do you mean
should I just go for the voices
or
normally there's no chance
[Music]
I don't know
24.
[Music]
foreign
I think this this we are doing
differently
[Music]
can I discard
wait let's move if I discard this it
will come back right okay
foreign
[Music]
wait first burst to alchemize
and
the bouncing
[Music]
we got
artifact yes and fire potion
um
kind of lame potion
please run away at least
throw it at him
eat
and drink
[Music]
a boy
any heart surgeons in the chat who can
help me out with this one
three times twelve
[Music]
T
like
wait
um
[Music]
what if I
um
it makes no sense unless I maybe get one
more cool card from preparing
[Music]
next time
I wouldn't wish for a block cards
yeah Survivor will have been helpful
[Music]
better than strike room strike
is this my end
yeah
[Music]
as you saw you shall reap
well
it's okay
because
this wasn't a good deck but I think with
even with the deck that I had until this
point I played well
um
I tried my best but yeah I I as you guys
say yourself so many of you have failed
the heart so many times anyway so if
even you guys failed so many times then
you must really need a banger deck
it's hard
yeah
[Music]
nice try they didn't help
um
disheartening
down we've challenged it but we have
failed
it's it do be like that
I
will not try it again because I have
many things to prepare off stream
like the stream for tomorrow where I
showcase counter side for you guys
um
and actual oh [\h__\h] I have to also record
if I can
yeah tomorrow yeah tomorrow very early
stream I think it will be very rough
especially for PST it's okay if you
can't come but
uh if you want to see more of the
countryside
um
stuff collaboration and I recommend even
watching the archive what time I think
it's like 9 00 a.m my time or 10 a.m 9
A.M or 10 A.M
GMT plus one
[Music]
uh yeah don't mind if I do
the counter-side screen press is very
high oh I'm not buying it
I'm being sponsored
[Music]
well yeah that's a game soon no I can't
do anything about the price of course I
can't
[Music]
sorry but hmm
I'm sorry
but
it's kind of like me judging judging by
looking at other gacha games that I've
played
normally when I purchase a skin in a
gacha game it doesn't come with all of
those extras
yeah and it also doesn't come with new
voice over so it's not just a normal
skin
it comes with a lot of cool extras yeah
[Music]
but anyway you don't have to get it but
you have to at least
check out the stream tomorrow and then
you can just watch me have it and watch
me check it out
and then think about
think about it
take a moment and think about it
I'll purchase for Obama thank you
we still play Pokemon tomorrow
um thinking about it
maybe
but total a little bit stressful Maybe
I'll think about it
I want to
maybe but maybe we'll shift it I mean
there's no stress with Pokemon
apparently
because
um we got perms for a long time
um
and then because I probably will need a
nap afterwards anyway
having to get up so early yeah
and I need to plan out some things for
the weekend because I have a special
weekend coming up yeah
yes
and maybe if we delay Pokemon one more
time there's a chance that there will be
maybe another bug fix coming out before
my next Pokemon play proofing stream
yeah anyway thank you guys for helping
me with slay the Spire I'll read some
super chattels go to office and but
everyone who's leaving now thank you
anyway for being here I'll see you
hopefully again soon we'll try again and
unfortunately that we couldn't
unfortunately that we couldn't do it
this time
that was free Alice not gonna add
another three hours to that yeah
okay here we go
Oh Oh wrong wrong wrong wrong
this is the one
it looked like I was just gonna start
something with my hot glue gun
[Music]
the main part of the stream is starting
yes I guess so for some of you guys
to hit
up
to hit pedal
gingerbread house
I wanna eat some gingerbread
I want to eat Christmas cookies and
stuff I need to buy Christmas cookies or
make some myself I kind of want to make
some myself with so much effort huh
maybe at least once before Christmas
cookies
baking cookie stream well I did one last
year I did those uh Crescent Christians
Chris Christian shaped
um vanilla powdery uh Christmas cookies
that we like making in Austria very much
vanilla I did those last year those are
so yummy they didn't turn out perfectly
last time though
it's not the ideal
um
ideal vanilla Capital could have could
have been better
to just buy the ones in the shop maybe
um
okay
BTM on ah Christmas cookie why did I
talk about Christmas cookies now I
really crave some Christmas cookies
maybe I go buy some after stream
[Music]
want vanilla kit for now
you know they crumble so much but I love
the crumbliness about them
same here
[Music]
linear algebra homework wow good luck
brownie or fudge making stream oh no no
I never made brownies before
brownies is just one thing that
everybody makes but I never made them
um
[Music]
that was a really good too
you should try them what
I mean uh brownies try I should try
making them
they're pretty easy right that's why
everybody makes them oh
[Music]
not very Christmassy though
hmm
[Music]
um
but where did I leave off last time
I started catching up
you know
[Music]
let me see
did I
stop at Advent Reef
and next is baby I think
they're harder to perfect than cookies
though really
cute loose
[Music]
baking decorating handcamp stream for
sure I don't know if I have the time to
be honest
Christmas is very soon
if I can I'll do my best to
no
something about it
yeah I'll try
you are my angle
easy to bake
I wanna try
they're forgiving I'm gonna cook mine
last night but put it back in the oven
and they turned out fun
[Music]
a cute angle oh wait there's barely any
super chats in the amalgus
foreign
[Music]
which is the clip that he made is longer
than the whole collab kind of I think or
at least the same length
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
over an hour clip of all point of views
from this Among Us collaboration
collaboration
[Music]
but it's really helpful because it makes
you understand so many things that were
going on
because I'm I don't know how you guys do
it I'm not the type of person who can
watch several streams at once
[Music]
I don't know how you guys do it
so stuff like this is really helpful
afterwards
[Music]
don't ask me how I watched all povs I
don't want to hear so many voices you
know
how can you even understand what's going
on when you hear so many voices
except I miss a lot um
[Music]
it would be good to watch them the clip
makes me feel crazy yeah
I have to admit I watched yours as a
vlog oh wait
wait watch live huh
[Music]
follow most times oh yeah maximum two
but even that honestly I can't enjoy
that so
usually one at most for me
[Music]
those people switch to someone
is so unfair you know I keep on playing
among us because even as a even as a
crewmate I think it's fun but you
honestly question
what the [\h__\h] is going on when everybody
else it's always
a tool
[Music]
at this point I'm so sick of it longest
now I think I need a break again
[Music]
we had a couple of among the streams
recently so now I need a break again
it's enough it's enough for another half
a year or so
I know this we are among us now but um
huh
[Music]
well I'm not gonna be the one who plans
it out that's for sure if anyone and Ian
wants to play VR among us maybe I'll
join but
not gonna be the one planning it out
that sounds very tiresome
I don't know I have to try it out I
guess but
um
foreign
[Music]
keeps on wanting one thing to give it to
her because she always gives it the way
so easily and then she always follows
her personal
um Revenge lust
so that it's so obvious when someone
dies that in the previous meeting she
was like angry at because they sussed
her out
oh who could it possibly be if that
person who was testing her out is now
dead and then and then and then you you
suss her out and she's like yeah she
just she's just admits it
ah
it's funny it's very funny but she's not
it just that good thing imposter so RNG
give it to someone else please but yeah
crony being so funny and so honest is
funny I did tell her she shouldn't give
it away so easily I even gave her the
benefit of the doubt right remember when
I said my little chromey crummy you
shouldn't
maybe maybe it wasn't her
everybody everybody give crony a chance
maybe it wasn't her why would she do
something so obvious right everybody
would cuss her out so maybe she didn't
do it
[Music]
um
she's she's so honest and innocent
[Music]
my favorite was when she became an
imposter pet just hanging out
imposter pet what do you mean
[Music]
so I don't get imposter wow now that
just hurts
do you have to say it so directly
oh
[Music]
ah you mean okay because we kept her
alive yeah I am
[Music]
indeed indeed oh well anyway uh tickets
thank you for ordering the emergency
meeting keychain I gotta use it on your
keys the gamer Creek
takashan and TD Bank account
[Music]
that's it for a more goose
and then we have Pokemon
[Music]
Pokemon
this one dance
you bought it minutes before sales
period and why did you forget or did you
have to wait for something
and then or did you forget and
remembered in the last moment
that was lucky if that's what if that
what was the case um
[Music]
seven streams
that's so bad like it's many streams but
they're all they don't have so many
super chats I think so no worries
[Music]
too pure and Angelic to be an imposter
yeah yeah the Halo is proof so true so
true
thumbnail is misleading a real Kotori
will plead to be captured not running
away ah so
anyway it's just a normal kfp chicken
um
it's a chicken and has been at kfp for
one year minimum
[Music]
got a lot of imposter even though she
has a Halo
it's a different kind of Halo it's not
an angel Halo is that that's a different
name it's not a Halo it's an onion ring
[Music]
I'm back from my us vacation I only have
to catch up with the votes from this
weekend so that's manageable anime NYC
was fun and I'm glad I could be present
oh
you were there too I belated
congratulations for the whole talk
anniversary to you as well thank you
thank you yo anyway NYC was really cool
with that
um it was kind of like a panel but like
smaller
because it was at a booth space
and I really liked this way because I
was able to hear you guys pretty well
and I was able to see you guys pretty
well
um and it felt kind of personal and cozy
and and and so many kfp were there he
made me pretty happy and you guys
it was so cute the interactions were so
cute when I would say something like oh
do you remember this and that and then
the kfp is in the crowd they're like
yeah yeah yeah yeah
nod and yeah yeah I remember that
I don't know it's like we had a
conversation it's cute and it made me
feel relieved to see
so many hardcore key of peas there
help me out for a dad joke it was just
like I was watching stream
um
motion mentioned
it was cool to be there internet was bad
over that spot though oh
[Music]
bad reception huh
these live things are fun to see even
just for Clips y'all
I hope we can do it in this form again
but it wasn't called cooperation with VR
chat so
it will probably not be the norm but it
would be nice if we could do it sometime
next year again
[Music]
next one is just full VR jet it
you mean with you guys in VR as well
nah I don't want that I want to see your
real faces
make it happen business woman can wow
it's not on me it's not on me
what is that unusual uh
um
[Music]
something I use when you guys are have
become
um immune to the usual room seemingly
immune
[Music]
but we all look like chickens yeah but
no you all are unique chickens you may
think that you look so similar to one
another but that's not true I want to
see I want to see how fluffy your
feathers are and how big your butt is
the fluffy butt
uh how chunky you are how big your cute
eyes are the googly eyes
yeah oh that reminds me
I have to buy art supplies
all that stream the member stream that I
want to do
[Music]
somewhere like this
okay
I put it in my schedule so I don't
forget it
it's gonna be cute yeah I'm probably
gonna do some I'm gonna create some of
those things that I said I will be
making uh beforehand though because
otherwise I think it will be too much
work for one stream and yeah I think it
would be good to First do one on my own
and then get a feeling for it
and then I already know what I'm doing
and I'll be faster during the member
stream
sealed
I mean it's mostly members in here
anyway but
were you going to book
hurts everybody who doesn't have a
membership to get one you don't want to
miss this street no don't hype it up so
much I mean it's a cute idea but I don't
think
I don't think it will be
[Music]
that's special
I saw something in the schedule that
makes me wonder
what he's he's
[Music]
well don't worry even the non-members
will see the result of the members
stream eventually
you follow the whole life English Advent
calendar that I created have you guys
all been following the whole life
English eyes on calendar
I think tonight's episode and tomorrow
you definitely want to watch as a kfb
calling an episode because it's it's
worthy of being called episodes
[Music]
hmm
it's really so much more than I than I
expected thank you
[Music]
I hope gouda will do a continuation of
her little thing I want to see the
sequel
I asked her to do a sequel
maybe she will who knows
[Music]
it was so cute
she's so good
I wonder if all of that was mostly
ad-lib so good
and thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you
let me
[Music]
thank you
hot dog
[Music]
Lily the Unicorn Christmas thank you
soon thank you
[Music]
um
can you be panicked when you announced
goodbye declaration
so I left to buy milk at the corner
store to calm down kfp
[Music]
ASAP
here
chickens
fresh milk
milk
goodbye declaration isn't that two years
ago and not one year ago
feels like two years ago at this point
[Music]
I guess it's one and a half okay it
feels like two years I know it wasn't
summer though
happy birthday oh hey it's two times in
a row actually
happy birthday
the astrophysics remix is so good you
should
work together again
a long shot I know
thank you for all free remixes slow
[Laughter]
foreign
night and he will think oh I totally saw
that coming I made that happen I
summoned it by saying
you should work together again
[Music]
thank you Slowpoke I'm happy to hear
from you again
yeah he's a psyching oh oh oh he's
psyching
I didn't realize
thank you moose
all my Emojis no message so I'll just
give you some heart hands look look
these are for you wow
thank you also cute cat in your profile
picture is that your own cat
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the pinky
beat your quick boss Chad is already
starting to root for iono just like
Corona and Pecos Chad did I'm not with
them oh thank you the social artist yeah
yeah everybody was
deporting iono
kind of rude not gonna lie
[Music]
but thank you for the Super Chat and
thank you for staying loyal and
supportive
you'll know it's cute but I prefer
Daniel thank you yeah
thank you
can't believe all those trainers
oh well well everybody who's saying all
these nice things now was probably on
iono's side back then in the Stream
[Music]
you're lucky that I have a bad memory
and I don't remember every single one
who was on the iono's side
foreign
excuse me I was always on your side
really
man probably not
I actually lost a Yono in my place what
did you go to early or
how can you lose a fight in Pokemon at
all ever
[Music]
that almost feels impossible
sorry for the roast
foreign
[Music]
beat me twice no way
did you go with 20 levels under level
though how
actual skill issue
you don't follow God's favorite strong
animals yeah yeah that's the only reason
I would understand
um anyway
[Music]
the Unicorn Christmas Duncan counting
chicken 47
[Music]
um
thank you for collabing with me Kiana
let's battle I'm ready to lick and Kick
Your Flank and thank you for the Super
Chat Electro King
I appreciate all the support you have
given me let's battle shut up go away
you're not supposed to prank people for
super chats in my stream
I'm the one thanking people for the
super chats it's my job don't take away
my job
[Music]
um
why did you change your name
I know exactly who you are why don't you
change your name so weird
causing chicken
[Music]
oh membership
[Applause]
thank you Mama
well then well done
[Music]
you can make it to my member stream next
week then check out the other members
only content too and check out the the
wallpapers
um
[Music]
my beloved
how could you I thought you loved me in
the foreign
[Music]
explain yourself
very big in file size be careful
[Music]
why why okay no why
are you hiding where are you
I saw you before where'd you go
[Music]
rest in Portugal
where's the Portugal
he's an ionos chat is she streaming
right now
it's [\h__\h] overlapping with me even
though I'm her senpai
[Music]
unbelievable
flashlight
[Music]
stop streaming over me
again thank you soon
all right
you don't know you sound so fake
friendly thank you showing the resiline
thank you for the pinky here's a donut
for my own I mean kiwawa
[Music]
you sure about that Rosaline you sure
you're very sure no more Corrections
needed hmm
is your final answer
oh you better bring it better be
it better be it was a close one now
[Music]
laughs
who's you know you don't know you know I
don't know you know
[Music]
comma
what would you say I'll take a potato
chip and eat it they're dramatically I
think I already did that when I first
received the Super Chat I wish I had
potato chips right now
[Music]
today's been two years since my first
Kiara's room oh well you remember
what did you remember they should join
the membership right in your first
stream and that's why you'll remember so
well what
[Music]
I'm so happy to call you my Aussie and
to be part of kfb I love you
quinoa also it's been two years and I
still have no idea what I do at work
could you please tell me what my job is
ah
now I searched my YouTube history a
while ago oh
okay okay
cool what
[Music]
could
I'm stretching right now so how about
you are the chicken stretcher
chicken stretcher
you stretch them before we make them
into nuggets
[Music]
it's it's good also not only before I
make the internet but also before they
start work
yeah you stretched chickens
it's important to stretch before and
after work so that you don't get a
um
[Music]
yeah rough muscle sore the next day
I know there's a lot of fancy words for
it but I like the word chicken stretcher
on its own
um
but if you want you can change it into
yoga instructor or so as well
stretch there next
yeah
what did it what
was it so wrong sounding
hmm
wise words of tip
I'm not going to push but not the wrong
way to put it right
anyway
[Music]
so thank you for two years of your
support
two years is a long time a lot of people
already would have gotten sick at that
point so or earlier so thank you very
much
foreign
[Music]
to get the chicken stretcher
come Sunny down
[Music]
why is there so many hearts
what did I say ah about not leaving
[Music]
yeah
thank you for the pinky a well-deserving
head Pat what did I do to get a headband
win the fight
I don't even like I had pets maybe I did
something bad and you wanted to you
wanted to annoy me with the headband I I
outsmarted Chad
as I always do
thank you I'll take it this time
just once I'll take the headband here
you may have Pat the head
get it on do it
[Music]
have I been padded well thank you
apparently I'm smoothie now
I wish I was smoothie
Blackford Connecticut in Phoenix
[Music]
Payday for me today and I'm going to
waste the Super Chat to demand you get
some rest now go take care of yourself
foreign
[Music]
thanks for thinking of me I'm resting
soon soon
not yet
[Music]
okay
I love those emotes I love them
the peaky one is so cute too and thank
you thank you for thinking of me so kind
sweet
scroll down cushion
yeah I don't think we have that Phoenix
thank you soon you mean extension
that's Pokemon for y'all
[Music]
oh next one is pretty short too but
there's a lot of Reds and pinks what on
Earth
why
this one part four this is like that
this one this fumbling implies that I
chose the grass starter which I didn't
but that one was the closest to my face
I had to cut off the other starters so
sad
it looks like a lot
I was just in the start actually why
why was there a rush of Reds and pinks I
wonder
I finished something big
oh these are all birthdays
um
[Music]
Tracy thank you for the red super chat I
can't believe it's already my second
birthday in kfp time really flies I'm so
fortunate to have such a great group to
be part of as well as a very talented
hard-working and caring OC to support
love your boss keep being your awesome
self thank you happy belated birthday
tune Tracy
happy birth to you
happy birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
I was sleepy
sorry I hope your birthday was great did
you did you treat yourself to something
nice hopefully
and eat something yummy and get some
presents maybe party a little bit if
that's your kind of thing
[Music]
I want to see all the best please stay
healthy and and stay on kfp because I
need you thank you for supporting me and
spending your birthday with me
love love love
[Music]
it's done now I should mention it's also
my birthday today this year was really
good to me and I'm hoping the same for
the next
another birthday also happy belated
birthday to landscape m
wah because he was really good to me
nice well
I hope you didn't use up all your luck
hope next year will be great for you too
yeah
I hope all your dreams come true
thank you for supporting Kiwa being part
of keep feelings and thanks for being a
great campaign employee
happy birth in your shoe
um
[Music]
very much once again
gracias oh how do I say you're welcome
[Music]
uh in Spanish espanol
de nada Aya
should have known that heard it before
[Music]
he
um
red Super Chat there are two things I
want to say together the first is thank
you for showing me an interesting stream
and the second is
what what
[Music]
just a happy Emoji I don't get it
like a cliffhanger
okay
the second is
hmm
oh well I'll take it as as the second
thing being I make you happy maybe
thank you very much for watching more
streams and supporting
um
[Music]
let's have a test ooh what day of the
Advent calendar will just be read on and
how many become Burns will there be so
far since this won't be rightful while
how are you feeling today thank you
hopefully better than when this was sent
yes oh yeah I remember when this came in
uh and I already read it at that point
but no now there's there has been
[Music]
reading again
anymore but yeah I'm also feeling better
thankfully I'm kind of tired now though
and I want to eat something yummy
foreign
I think I'll end the Super Chat rating
after this one
Randy Duncan
if you could be a Pokemon between these
two would you be a mortise or a Blaziken
maltes
shortest Giants thank you
currently in Vienna on holiday anything
you recommend doing while I'm here well
are you still there are you in the chat
right now
it's been a while since then sorry I
couldn't recommend anything
foreign
[Music]
already left oh no what did you check
out how long were you here did you have
fun did you eat good stuff
I'm stuck in the country waiting for a
reply
imagine imagine
just staying as long until I answer
[Music]
thus the interrogation begins yeah I'm
curious
did you check out the Christmas Market I
hope you did
you better
I was there for five days so lots of
palaces and ate lots of good food okay
what about Christmas Market
come on come on
[Music]
you this goes to so many Christmas
markets yay okay then I thank you
you thrived
it is the most important time apart if
you go to Austria or Germany I think as
well during this season a must is
Christmas Market
don't want to think about how much money
I spent
it sounds like you enjoyed it I'm happy
to hear that yeah successful trip
thank you for
Trio it's not a very popular choice
um for travel I mean it kind of is but
at the same time it isn't not as popular
as like I don't know France or England
or whatever Italy or Japan obviously so
thank you Austria is so beautiful
and me too right
yeah I love Christmas markets I want to
go to another one just went recently on
on Monday I want to go again
[Music]
go again get those roasted almonds
and the other yummy food okay
um
[Music]
thank you
I'm beautiful Australia beautiful
because I live there
wonder how much you can stock up on
those islands
and I think that I was always thinking
they should sell them all year round but
at some point I did see them on the
lowest lowest lowest shelf in the
supermarket so I think if you look for
them they do sell them yeah they don't
need to be fresh after all
um they can be packaged normally to be
sold in a supermarket and yeah I did see
them I didn't try the supermarket ones I
wonder if they're good but I don't think
they would be bad
[Music]
ah I'm tired
there's some other places I'd like to
visit first look look the priorities
lost right is not very high on the
priority list of people it's kind of sad
but I mean I get it
I kind of get it but yeah
it's a nice place nonetheless
we have nice beautiful buildings and if
you like classic music then it's kind of
a have to go place
but yeah
hmm
if you like Sound of Music you gotta go
[Music]
snow in mountains yeah if you wanna go
on like a winter holiday
[Music]
I should just lay down on the floor on
my bean bag right now my stinky bean bag
I just I can't stop stretching and
yawning
stinky yeah that thing has been stinky
since I received it it stinks like
plastic so bad I thought it would go
away after a while but it didn't
I don't know how smoothie can tolerate
it she likes to sleep on it
don't know how she can tolerate it
oh oh stinky but at least it doesn't
like make the whole room stinky anymore
it's just when you sniff it it's
definitely stinky
can you wash it what no how do you wash
uh like a one meter no two meter long
bean bag
think what's stinky is what's inside not
the outside
um
I mean it definitely adapted to smell
but it comes from inside I think I don't
think it's the cover
for deodorant spray or something I guess
so but it doesn't really it doesn't
really bother me because I'm not the one
really using it my cats are using it so
as long as you don't sniff it directly
it's
it's totally fine
anyway
um Schneider thank you for a red and a
pinky finally a reborn chicken it has
been one hell of a month end of October
I got told that I lose my job due to the
company closing early next year but now
I've already gotten multiple offers with
a decent pay rise there let's go your
streams helped me a lot and I can't wait
for the coming jrpg Marathon still
hoping for more Yakuza and maybe
Catherine oh definitely at some point
I'm pretty sure about that yeah
well congratulations
I'm slapping my thighs for you yay
yay
congratulations
so it ended up being a good thing
things that seem bad at first
you know if you give it some time might
end up being actually good developments
in your life
um
[Music]
so I'm excited for you I hope that
whichever job you chose or will choose
will treat you well
and that you'll be happy there
um
donation for supporting me for a long
time
and I wish you all the best
scooter
[Music]
Africa
soon
what rockruff has an orange Evolution
but it requires to build its own Temple
and to evolve it as the sun is going
down
evolution
[Music]
oh
pretty oh there's also a red evolution
[Music]
that's very different types of
evolutions
or the shiny one is blue
the shiny one makes everyone blue
night form
foreign
[Music]
does it get different like attack snow
right a different type also no right
still same type right
only remember two from Sun and Moon it
looks like that's free
[Music]
same time
ninth one is dark
stats are different oh
it's cool
[Music]
nice
Pokemon
[Music]
Knight form stands on two legs yeah yeah
spooky
spooky spooky intimidating
[Music]
um
Ghost Monkey Junction
[Music]
Oreo shaking crispy chicken funds oh I
didn't get the Oreo shake yesterday but
I was so tempted because I saw they have
a new Oreo shake on the menu
you know there's no more Oreo shake that
I love very much and then there's the
Oreo shake that um is like overall like
chocolate as a base I never tried that
one though and then the new one is
caramel
so it's like kind of like yellow
brownish color
with Oreo bits in it
I want to try because I really like
caramel I wonder how strong the caramel
is
at least in my Burger King there's um in
Austria I guess there's caramel Oreo
shakes down I need to try but I already
you know ordered a set with an iced tea
so
but yeah I had crispy chicken yesterday
I I
um rewarded myself
I after the stream even though I was
exhausted I
um
changed out of my mocap
and by the way it was mostly the shirt
that I wore underneath that was soaked
so not much let's do this okay-ish but
I'll have to watch it at some point
yeah you indeed and then I put on some
warm fluffy clothes scarf hat everything
because it was [\h__\h] cold and was late
I went to
I went to a Burger King
and got myself
crispy
chicken but the fries kind of tasted
weird they tasted undercooked somehow
on that day I don't know why but they
were perfectly salted
could totally go for another one today
[Music]
of course the flattest it always comes
with lettuce but I added an extra tomato
because tomatoes they put inside are
often very tiny
and barely cover the whole Burger
so sometimes I add extra tomato
they ruin the fries they are still
edible but they definitely tasted weird
breaking fries aren't as good no but
this time they're really in tasted
differently I always get onion rings do
you get five onion rings
[Music]
is that what you get
Mr chicken's over here kind of
disappointing chicken is whatever isn't
very crispy what the [\h__\h] that's
impossible but I did notice I think I
said this before
uh I think when I looked for crispy
chicken in Japan they had a burger that
was called crispy chicken but it didn't
use the same breading it was more of a
like a normal typical like fried
chicken patty breading and not the one
with the cornflake like breading
that makes it extra crispy and that's
[\h__\h] lame they need the the cornflake
I don't know if it's really complex
probably not but they need that they
need that breading because that's what
makes the crispy chicken a crispy
chicken I know what I'm talking about I
know a thing or two about chicken
burgers hey
[Music]
oh you didn't like it
enough
yeah there's 100 there's differences
between European Burger King and uh
American Burger King and Asian Burger
King and so on
[Music]
yeah there must be difference you guys
don't seem to like it much when you're
from us oh
I recommend
[Music]
I mean honestly it's obviously not the
best burger place it's still like a
freaking fast food Burger chain but the
crispy chicken
it's so addicting to me it's it's so
addicting
here no way ah uh makes sense Europe
probably pretty much the same as ours
[Music]
pop ice oh I got a triple boy someday
thank you nine months of membership
thank you
[Music]
papa is the goats Papa's the best all
right wow this one's really popular
go to your fast food do they have it
everywhere in America or only like west
coast East Coast or so
[Music]
okay I see over here used to look great
to your punkle so
I don't go to KFC ever actually so I
can't really tell
mostly East Coast spread around well
everywhere huh
next time I go to America remind me that
I need to check it out okay because we I
already had what was it called in and
out
next is Popeyes
[Music]
it made me curious do they have good
chicken burgers or more beef burgers
[Music]
oh wow it all looks like chicken
oh they seem to focus on chicken ah
chicken noodle oh wow wow
oh is there any Popeyes in Europe
foreign
[Music]
wait there might be one in Spain
successful European launches in the
United Kingdom Romania Spain and
Switzerland gotchi
oh
interesting
maybe I'll find one in Europe before I
find one in America
Spain vacation
but it's probably in a city in Spain
where I don't really want to go to like
um
let me see Pop Eyes Spain
[Music]
oh what there's one Valencia I've been
there before and Barcelona and Madrid
yeah those are I mean Valencia wouldn't
go again because I've been there before
and the other cities I don't really
want to go there because they're like I
feel like they're like parties it is
Madrid has beautiful
um
beautiful city
architecture and so on as well but I
don't know
or assessment well
[Music]
maybe I'll check it out anyway at some
point I think I'll still at some point
visit
one of those cities at least
Barcelona or Madrid
but cool they have quite a bunch of them
I'm surprised they don't have one in
Germany then
[Music]
oh wait there's so many
well there's also one in Granada and
I'll
always
there's actually at least two in
moderate
free Vigo Cartagena there's so many wow
Spanish people love Popeyes
[Music]
damn
foreign
[Music]
let's go
yeah why was I anyway
[Music]
maybe somewhere here
did so much I could have been done 20
minutes ago
Spain but this is okay most of the time
you go there and they don't have half
the menu available
mine never has spicy chicken yeah
because it's here right in front of you
just kidding I'm spicy Phoenix spicy
Phoenix spicy Phoenix
[Music]
cat food spicy balls yeah what should I
get I want cookies
um something lunchy
[Music]
oh
I have to prepare for tomorrow and
hopefully sleep early
um
but I think I still should also cook
maybe because I got some meat in the
fridge
all right then thank you guys so much
for watching today tomorrow little
sponsorship stream
um
let's look at all the goodies
hasta
hello bleep yes
[Music]
Pokemon I think about I think I'll move
it actually yeah
since we added a different stream
and I need some time anyway
might as well move it
[Music]
can drink very delicious chicken beer I
had that but without the beer
foreign
[Music]
schedule a little bit for the weekend
you know why
thank you
what was that about moving ah moving the
stream I guess
um the the Pokemon one next week
[Music]
thanks for watching and in Germany
thank you very much
[Music]
had fun unfortunately we didn't win but
I had fun
bye bye
Gonna Fly Away now
[Music]
foreign