[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
have a great night
[Music]
show
s transmission
[Music]
hey
ladies and gentlemen and takodachi's
deadbeats chumfords
teammates kfp why did I pause before
teammates I knew what they were called I
wonder I feel like they're alligator or
not investigators yeah investigators
teammates they have like different yeah
it's kind of hard yeah
yeah it's a little bit confusing a
little confuses or teammates like like
which one which one is it that's okay
though it doesn't matter it's cool
they're all welcome we're all the same
in the Hat in our hearts yeah yeah yeah
yeah
everybody equally special important hi
I'm your GM Marie calliope
the Reverb is on now again need the god
voice for Just Another Second hello well
you guys have waited and here we finally
are it's time
for the finale of myth Breakers
yay
it doesn't even have to clap yourself
anymore
yeah wow I'm gonna leave I'm Gonna Leave
it to you guys at this point I'm Gonna
Leave it to you guys to take care of
that because I'm already it was a
mistake to tell us yes
drinks
yummy oh let me just Chuck it down well
what is that drink of mine uh it's a
fancy little like kfp milkshake that I
picked up from the kfp
chicken Shake yeah oh it looks like it's
really yeah chicken Shake
is there is there like what chicken yeah
the chicken shakes
them liquids they have to stay in in a
form a katachi
chicken tenders sound really good right
about now but um
yeah I already had a little
a little wheat kale chicken wrap today
of chicken
right now
named sponsored by KFC
yo welcome yeah yeah delicioso
everybody okay thank you so much for
coming here thank you very much for
Gathering today to finish to finish this
fight to finish this series that we
started together towards the beginning
of our time together in whole life it's
a series very near and dear to my heart
and so I'm really glad that we could all
come together to really put a concrete
conclusion to it because it didn't feel
right to just end it myself something
that we kind of created together
um so I'm very excited
Kelly yeah hey you're you're you're
your book moves now I know how far we've
come
over
yeah it moves yeah why is it ending
though the crowd may ask
um well I think all all good Adventures
need to come to an end
um as you can see all of us you know in
our time in Hollow have gone on
incredible adventures and like done our
own done our own things and stuff like
that it's just hard to keep up these
days
um like doing something that's weekly so
from now on though I won't stop being a
GM I think I still want to do one shots
and that certainly isn't exclusive to to
people that haven't played before so
like if any like couple of you guys ever
want to join into a game Etc that I'm
doing then it will be open to you I'll
be doing different ones various groups
of people
um
you know I'd I'd like everybody to you
know I was thinking I'd like to do
shorts that involve you know people that
have like collabed with each other
before
um just for chemistry reasons and stuff
like that
um so that's kind of like a little
requirement that I have
um but it'll be cool uh you guys can
like sign up for different ones in the
future uh the bgm is so loud I pull it
down
but it's banging though come on you
can't deny it is you can't deny maybe I
want it all the way up so in order to uh
kind of get you guys familiar again
familiarized again we went over all of
this in a little recap session but I
just want to make sure that everybody
here like really really knows I'm gonna
recap the recap for us I need to make
sure you guys remember your characters
let's make sure you remember your
characters and I think I remember the
lore of my character but but but how to
how to use stuff and um
well in terms of rolling things um I've
decided for this finale it's really
going to be mostly home brew
um except you know rolls are pretty easy
you know you've got your sheets it's
just like some simple some simple math
you just add some dots together and do
simple rolls but we're not going to be
too too much of sticklers for rules this
time just because you know it's the
grand finale and I want to focus on the
role play aspect
yeah so let's go ahead and remember
Tiara really quick kiwawa that's your
character that is indeed mine yes she's
behind you right now in a kind of stand
form I included everything
out staring at me
many bad experiences
um
your time oohu was kind of gone
somewhere yeah true we're scouting the
area to help you yeah useful and never
coming back occasionally woohoo
hold on oh so TR is basically just um a
cute very spirited bird Handler she's
got a sharp Witch she's got a sharp
tongue you made a lot of enemies like
you made so many so many that I can't
even tie all of the plot threads with
all of them because there's too many wow
well I mean everyone must be ruthless in
a world like this understandable I I
definitely I understand it you know you
gotta you gotta be ruthless and if we
had more sessions I would make you deal
with every single one of them
um but this alas uh the session is over
so it looks the season the series the
series is coming to an end
um so it looks like you're getting off
scot-free
[Laughter]
that's okay it's kind of cute though
it's kind of endearing
um yeah so basically uh you had like a
little run-in with one of your with uh
your brother actually yeah
you met him and learned that he was
running a hunter conspiracy that robs
people essentially he became a thief
which is not great yeah and he came to
rob you guys him and his crew they're
all using these special masks gifted to
them uh by an unknown being we don't
know who it is but it makes them strong
and agile and turns them into dicks like
really mean people
yeah did I notice already no you learned
when they tied you up remember they told
they tied all of you guys up in the last
session oh yeah inside your home
yeah it's cool I can remind everyone
tied up or seeing people tied up yeah
yeah okay yep yeah so you were tied up
with watoto as a matter of fact when you
met again with your brother and not only
that but the family members of all of
the other members except for Yule were
also there
oh yeah that was fast
even your family's safe you'll you're
the only one with a normal family oh
okay they didn't touch me okay
no they love you
all right let me crank this down just a
bit yeah all right um so speaking of
fuel you'll be all right the resident is
hired scientists oh yes very tired
College goer yeah you went to a frat
party once it was not fun
when it was a very rough description yes
yeah that was the time all right
um but essentially you became uh the
assistant to the professor who was
always doing these weird experiments and
never really told you what she was up to
yeah yeah she was after some fishy [\h__\h]
very sus uh but you don't help it oh
yeah
yeah I mean you were just doing what you
were supposed to do as as an assistant
to the professor so I mean but you never
really did figure out what she was doing
in her lab
yeah yeah but you really just want to
nap the only thing you really care about
is useless
honestly you'll is planning something I
can feel it yeah
you'll be all right
but you always really kind of just I
don't know you'll sounds like someone
that I know in my life a certain a
certain Taco that loves to sleep
well it's just your imagination all
right whatever you say
whenever you say you'll be all right
Now we move on to scout oh Scout oh wait
does it work
[Music]
you were ready for that here let's put
on some some country bangers really
quick for the background let's see
where's we're the country bangers I have
them in this playlist I was waiting I
was saving them up uh here we go
okay I wanna hear this wait no this is a
happy song I mean Scout could also I
mean be represented by a hat that is
happy and Country
I guess
all right
you know what oh Scout oh Scout it's so
special
so Scout is known for solving her
problems by taking her pants off I guess
alarm only looks like Kyla now I can't
unsee it
oh alarmingly very similar yellow red
Countryside version of Kyle yeah and she
is pumpkin pumpkin version backwards
pumpkin version wow of our beloved
blacksmith Kyla that makes perfect sense
actually yeah maybe maybe Kyla is yeah
Kyla's inspired you're calling her a
bumpkin no no no I'm just I'm saying the
design the designer
she was she was just inspired wow myth
Breakers really has had quite the
influence on hololive anyway continuing
onwards Scott has no last name but it's
just pickle yeah Scout from belt buckle
that's it she's uneducated please be
gentle with our daily spout yeah she
requires a patience it's not the
brightest but she has a really sharp
look
she can make her pants do anything for
her she's a country girl and country
girls gotta do what country girls gotta
do even if it's the wrong decision yes
even if it is you know burning down
um a haystack that is Sheltering
children which is a thing
yeah during the beach carnival Mission
you're like can I roll morality I'm like
what are you talking about
oh my
um quite literally yeah that's the
reason why we're breaking up this group
we can't handle each other's ethics and
morals anymore yeah and it's just too
much disagreement yeah it's not the best
mix
so it's time to part ways I just want to
sleep man yeah
I don't really know what Scout wants do
does any of us girl do you know what
what Scout wants what does she want what
does Scout wand is that like a just in
general yeah just in general like I
think she just wants experience inside
the farm but she just doesn't
she doesn't understand it's like
releasing a somebody who grew up really
sheltered into the real world for the
first time yeah
true yeah why are you say he's one you
chat
she want money
her family is broken her sister is like
it's all chaos and so she's really happy
money can fix things money can fix it
yeah
everything much about money yeah true
enough but I mean I guess it could be
useful anyway we hope that Scout finds
what she's looking for without burning
down more bugs and more odds with
children say a quick prayer everyone
is
especially Chihuahua I feel like you
guys have some good news
Chihuahua
got a nickname now too huh yeah to match
you I want to match you yeah watoto is
um a special little entity I'll go ahead
and put on the watoto theme which is
great because when you play this track
on YouTube in the comments section it's
just people talking about watoto
it wasn't a really popular track but
this is
just a just a little a little guy just
just doing lots of those things
um hates the government really hates the
government loves watoto family
um wants to take down government with
big secrets and uh fine family but
actually watoto found family watato
found the wasato clan and they had
joined Chihuahua's brother's crew of
hunters that Rob and steal from people
but it's not really their fault the
watatos are good people it's just they
they got the masks from some mysterious
being and they kind of turned the people
yeah PGM too low now
for real I listened to yeah
please boost it up bass boosted Water
Theme
um but yeah that's the watoto family
um and uh once again meet them and
um they said Son don't be stupid like us
um you know we made we made a deal a bad
deal so don't make any deals with any
space insects or whatever but ah oh yeah
yeah
space lizards space lizards space
lizards face wizard lizards but we all
remember that watoto made watatos still
has a little bit of a baggage in
watoto's pocket
yeah always creeping over your shoulder
always creeping over your shoulder ready
to strike at any moment yeah the worm
you know what the warm is
no I wear them in her pocket
like a real worm entity
[Laughter]
I don't think I ever understood it
wasn't the natural worm oh my God what
are you squares I don't think I have a
garden
yeah
it's a worm well even as a worm I would
try it because if it fits in your pocket
then it should be small enough but why
is it aren't like dragons and lizard
cold-blooded
oh it's I think it's just a symbol from
the worm entity which like moves on my
hand and it's like
ah yeah I've been marked it's a token a
token of of um it's like an IOU that the
worms
a what an IOU
was a while you you don't know what an
IOU is
so an IOU is like he owes you money
I thought it was being witty
I got it
wait and I owe you
anyway okay
God if I make a joke and you play that
freaking Cricket noise
I swear to God
um now the last thing we need to discuss
before we really get into this is the
rolls
um nice and simple quick and easy I'm
gonna be doing the rolls just because
I'm just not gonna make you guys relearn
how to do that [\h__\h] so what you guys
need to do for me though is I sent you
guys I sent you guys your character
sheets and you will need to tell me what
your numbers are for things like
Athletics plus dexterity Etc so let's
pretend uh a watoto is uh running away
from the government at top speed I will
do my goal all right what's a toad what
is your Athletics plus dexterity
it's uh
uh you got this two two two okay that's
right is that both of them combined
yeah all right so I roll a two D ten
and let's see how many successes I get
so greater than eight
uh you fail okay so the government
catches you and takes you away to
government prison no
no all right
um
gorgeous session that was fast you can
you can go sleep or stream now
um yup thanks for joining uh we'll have
to go to jail forever we podcast I'm
just kidding I'm not gonna let you guys
get off that easily we haven't oh no the
Suffering The Suffering I have suffering
in you
so
now we get serious
the bgm is stopped and now I take us
to where the scene begins
which is in the bar
oh I'm gonna do a little previously on
okay
previously on myth Breakers oh
the team
was chilling in the bar they had been
doing uh many different missions for the
guild for a while now
um The Myth Breakers as myth Breakers
little quests like going and subduing a
ghost or chasing off a werewolf or a
vampire and things like that right
um until they heard from the boss that
some terrible threat was coming for them
and so the boss traps them inside of the
bar and made them basically try and flee
as an escape room sort of deal a forced
escape room
um Chihuahua Tiara was too smart for
this and used to trigger some kind of
button that accidentally locked down the
entire bar
which made things difficult for them
however
however that exact same time there was
another actual real threat entering the
bar and they used sleeping gas to put
you guys to sleep
oh finally finally
the sleep you you crazy nap time let's
go let's go congratulations you got what
you were looking for you
um but you guys wake up and
you are tied together uh Yule is tied to
scout uh Tiara is tied to watoto and the
assailants make themselves known various
members in green masks yellow masks and
a red mask
um they are robbers they take you guys
to the Vault and they steal all of the
money and offer you some of it but first
they tested the bonds between you guys
so for example
um you guys had to play a game of ally
or betray in which uh you could try and
get some of the money but the person you
were tied up with would be killed in the
process
ah
however yeah all of your bonds survived
all of you turned out to have close
bonds and be friends impressive
however they did take all the money they
took all the money because of that so
that kind of sucks
um and now
and now effectively
effectively there is um
there's no money
at all
but you guys did manage to untie
yourselves thanks to now remember these
masked figures
um we're actually led by Kiara Kiara's
damn it Tiara's brother uh Tiara's
brother who is in Egypt
um and had found a mask that granted
exceptional power uh he took that mask
all the masks from Egypt took them back
to mythdon and assembled a crew of
hunters that became thieves basically so
your brother's essentially a thief now
um great yeah very nice
um what a weird job Choice yeah man well
he went a little power hungry with the
masks and ended up actually crossing
paths with Scout's parents and watatos
parents who also joined in the thieving
Guild
interesting
um they took all the money and they left
um but not without kind of alluding to
the fact that these masks were given to
them or at least to to Tiara's brother
by some unknown mysterious entity well
in Egypt who that is we just don't know
um but the story left off after uhu
untied all of you guys you guys are
still in the vault and all kind of just
standing there having been untied last
you heard though the boss of the guild
Lady M had been shot you don't know what
happened to her
[Music]
and gives you money
okay cleaning up that means we're next
oh God
do we want our money back or what it's
up to you
at this point you guys are standing
there in front of an empty vault
there is no money for the organization
it's all been stolen by the thieving
hunters and you guys are left there
standing alone
honestly it wasn't even ours to begin
with so I don't know
if we gotta do
oh well the righteous thing
oh well
I guess we'll go after them
should we find the lady who got shot
oh yeah she uh
where where would she be in the
well since you guys are in the ball we
look
you guys are in the vault and there is a
bar on top of you guys
um it looks as though the emergency
lockdown is kind of stopped you know
there are no metal doors everywhere
anymore uh-huh
so what do you choose to do
we'll go and check at in the bar okay
see if maybe
or is it the perception
would you like to do a perception check
uh when you get to the bar or do you
want to do it yes okay
okay uh uh all righty go ahead actually
let me look around and around the Vault
see if there's anything empty yeah sure
all right what's your perception rule
yule
uh
uh okay it's wits plus composure
what's three composure four so seven
okay that's right you had kind of the
cracked perception rules I'm remembering
yeah yeah
okay two six
uh you find twenty dollars
left in the vault oh nice nice
twenty dollars left over
um and you see also that um
the thieves the way that they went out
they kind of like
close the door behind them it's not
necessarily locked though
um you do know you do know that that
door you notice a sign above says Exit
so it leads to the outside
um and uh I would say in terms of what
you hear
um you can hear some faint movement
above
oh
yeah
footsteps or just voices or unknown not
high enough perception to tell you
okay wait the vault is under the bar
correct
oh okay
no
no worse I I do I do feel like there's
someone above us I'm not sure if we
should oh go and check let's go check on
her
wait is there a security room
would you like to roll to perceive
sure okay what spots of those perception
rules
what's plus composure
six okay oh
let's see what watoto gets all right
that's a 10 which means we re-roll again
I know there is a way to Auto reroll I'm
just not gonna okay
that might be a good time to do the auto
reroll I'm just not
uh so you you glance around and
interestingly enough there is a little
door that's kind of got sort of um like
oh
a window to it that has like some wire
over it and like little little diamond
shapes and above um it says cameras
oh
so there is that you guys want to do we
could check the camera oh I didn't know
there was a camera room
let's go check
yeah you can see you guys enter the
camera room take a look around
and you see well automatically you can
pretty much just tell from the camera
that lady M you see her there with the
the lady that your boss she has brown
and pink hair kind of changed in the
middle of in the middle of the series
there so it's broken
um she's crawling on the floor
with a trail of blood underneath her
maybe we should go fast
which room which room is that yeah you
take the stairs to get to the main main
bar it's the main bar okay she's in the
main bar you can see on the cameras that
no other assailants are within the
building
oh okay we gotta go fast walk fast up
a little speed so quick you guys speed
up is she dead
I don't know Scout she does have a lot
of blood beneath her in a trail I guess
you could ask her if she's dead
would you like ask her Scout
Scout does healing check perception roll
all right let's help Jake okay
you want to check how much health she
has all right so uh you guys Rush up to
the bar the main bar area
um the lights are kind of flickering the
electricity is kind of shot uh the
system has been shocked a little bit so
Scout you rush up to lady Madam M and
you decide to do a little health related
perception check which I will go ahead
and modify a little bit so let's do your
wits plus medicine
oh we might be in luck at two uh plus
three five okay five all right let's go
listen come on
that's a that's a big ass there oh three
yeah oh my God
okay that's three six that's four
successes so far
okay that's four successes four
successes to check how Madam m is doing
uh on the floor you kind of turn her
over
um and give her a thorough look down it
looks as though she's been shot
um
in the stomach but like not quite near a
vital organ you can tell that she'll
probably survive the bullet is not very
big the hole itself is decently small
she wasn't shot with like a shotgun
obviously did it goes through her or did
it go in and stop it wait wait and it
stopped
oh no oh okay take out the bullet yeah
you can tell she probably will live
through this but she is she is a she's
Lucid but not making a ton of sense she
kind of mumbles a bunch of [\h__\h] like you
[\h__\h] idiots
I have I have the skill first date does
that do anything
uh sure can I can I help her anyhow yeah
sure thing so we're gonna keep this
extra simple since it's the finale go
ahead and tell me what your medicine
plus wits is
uh four all right
please one success all right okay um so
you know enough to like make a basic
extraction which she doesn't like lots
of screaming lots of
um and you know how to cauterize the
wound
um okay there are like heating tools
nearby
um and so you are able to do it's good
enough and you you put a bandage on it
you find like a little Band-Aid little
first aid kit put a Band-Aid on it it'll
be fine
and at that point she's kind of able to
get her [\h__\h] together and she she like
after all the screaming looks at you
guys and says
oh God they robbed us didn't they
um maybe we got 20 bucks
but 20 bucks left I know 20 bucks sorry
about that yeah that would be split it
yeah what did she see though does she
remember what did you see what did you
what do you remember lots of mass
[\h__\h] with guns they were strong
I'd never seen them before though I
don't know who those guys are
that they have masks on any Tails any
animalistic qualities oh like like fur
and like like anything no they did not
have pills their bodies no we know who
did this don't we yes well it was no one
else it wasn't any other assailant it
was our family okay I was checking if
there was like the same people
it was your family yes my brother got
some masks and build the created a thief
Guild or something like that at a
watoto family possessed by demons wow
wow what should we do so buy that by
that extension of that you know what I
would make all of you owe me
considering that it's family and
Family's debts get passed on there was
not um none of my family and that crew
okay
thank you hey we will get back what
we're what we've been stolen
oh forget it I don't need the money to
be honest I think this is a sign a sign
from God
it looks like
I mean I mean I don't know it's just an
expression what was the money needed for
where did it come from originally from
all of the different missions that you
guys have been doing we've been storing
up here of course you get your cut but
there's a much bigger amount of money
that comes from that
look a huge cut
I mean it's just how business goes well
is there a contract I don't remember
signing a contract about the cut
do they really have to get back
the money that was stolen yeah I can
give you a contract she says if she
pulls out a pistol it's kind of too late
now eh pistol you want a contract you
want to make a contract
well I also pull out my Chris my my
pistol oh gosh come off it it's not that
dire
ah look here's the thing
essentially our organization has no
money it's not that big of a deal but
think of it as us going bankrupt in
other words you all are free to go
oh okay bye bye
thanks
yes you are here by
released from the myth Breakers
that's it
you have a son yes he's he is eight and
he's at soccer practice I feel like they
should go to the hospital yeah for
soccer practice yeah it's a Flesh
Wounds
next if what happened to Big by the way
oh Vic oh yeah the vampire Prince
sure I haven't seen him in a while to be
honest I heard that he got some other
job at a school
oh he's gone thank God Anna can scout
say something yeah what do you want to
say Scout watched a lot of videos
growing up uh in my my crime fighting
videos usually if they're trying to kill
people they'll go for the entire family
do you think your son's in trouble now
Madame m
oh
rise get kind of wide
I mean he is he is a brown belt in
Taekwondo so I think he might Brown is
not good enough or not even a black belt
oh
I need to go pick him up
um all right I don't think you're in any
any shape to drive ma'am are you gonna
go pick up my son for me
I mean we can go together not for free
I'm pretty sure your son doesn't know
what we look like
if we if we take a van or something you
know might be suspicious people trying
to pick up a kid into a van and I don't
think that's really smart
got any family you can call
ma'am no it's just me taking care of my
my eight-year-old son
who's the father it doesn't matter
your business
[Laughter]
he's right it's none of your business it
doesn't matter I'm eight years old he
can walk I guess
yeah that is true
you can run his first around Anna
look if you want to go ahead and drive
me over to the the soccer field you can
drive me to the soccer field
all right let's drive her to the soccer
fields make sure you know just okay
I mean she's she's the bleeding lady on
the floor we can't just leave her she's
just threatening to kill the arrow wow
sure I'm sure she didn't mean too much
harm okay she was gonna let us go this
is the least you know we can do help her
get back with her family
yeah as long as we left the bullet in
should we fine I guess but let's make it
quick okay all right all right I'm sure
I can drive quick don't worry okay all
right all right before you leave she
grabs a bunch of the wine bottles in the
cabinet just puts them in her purse
let's go
cherry
all right all right everyone get in the
car roll your driving you
uh my drive is three okay
and I also have aggressive driving skill
I'm not sure
if we can get to the soccer field on
time okay are you gonna try and like run
over other people in in order to get to
the soccer field on time nah maybe speed
a little bit but not running over people
gotcha
before we go I'm taking all of my items
that I own just saying I mean including
my walkie-talkie okay as long as you've
been keeping track of your items I have
attractive yes I have many friends don't
touch the 20 I'm keeping it safe okay do
we have to specify I'm taking all my
items as well
let's see well here's the thing is I
certainly wasn't keeping a list of them
so if you want to go ahead and just yeah
you have the list okay you have your
list so if you guys want to go ahead and
tell me what you take
it can be pretty much anything you gotta
think about it though like you gotta be
careful like you have to take things and
after this you can't go back and get
more
okay I'll take two bottles of water okay
from the bar
uh I'll write this down uh my cell phone
of course okay
um
did I have any weapons does that have a
taser or something I forget you had a
taser I believe okay I'll take my Taser
yeah
um
and uh
uh
oh and my phone charger can't forget my
phone charger of course
surely I have a phone charger on me yes
and uh
uh yeah okay that should be it okay
twenty dollars or is you holding the
twenty dollars
I'm holding the 20 because I found it
okay I'm keeping it safe until we get to
McDonald's yeah gotta save for the
Mickey D's
all right how about you though
I thought don't take a battery from
every remote and item
okay a little rude but sure go for it
and watoto take handmade Arsenal okay
gotcha oh yeah you are quite the The
Crafty one aren't you okay handmade
Arsenal
excellent lots of bombs and crafty
things how about you Scout what are you
taking
uh I'm trying to remember I think Scout
I think I had excuse me I think I Scout
had a like a really well made pickaxe or
something really good and a dagger I
don't remember she had a bunch of
weapons you have a dagger I remember
maybe a match okay or something yeah you
can bring the matchbox and some uh so I
guess we'll just call it you wanna bring
an extra pair of pants maybe
no I mean it's fine I got two legs on
this one
yeah and what have you got Tiara what is
your list well well so um
I got my uh Phoenix pendant I got I'm
bringing I mean I'm not bringing all of
it I guess I'm bringing the pendants the
combat knife My Revolver my
walkie-talkie and my phone
um
uh a poison bottle okay a lighter a rope
okay I'll take duct tape and zip ties as
well and I don't know what it's useful
for but I got an enchanted mirror okay
gotcha and and I'm bringing the bowling
Snips Enchanted sniper rifle that I have
never used until now
yeah bowling bowl and sniff yeah oh yeah
yeah
abused or something yeah he was like
he's a fairy that lives in the Hedge and
hunts humans all right sniper sniper
rifle now do I have to like specify or
like buy a munition for the revolver no
we don't do ammunition in this series
okay good
okay unlimited unlimited ammo my
favorite type of game and I mean I got
the hair pins in my hair still that's a
six hair pins okay six hair
let's go okay then what that will take
them don't forget now yeah of course who
always comes by okay and what do you
want to take
uh alcohol all right you got it which
kind yeah
a massive explosion if needed I see not
for drinking but for creating creating
big bomb okay and maybe drinking while
creating true true
just a sip
oh whoops okay great so you guys are all
loaded up into the car and um you
actually got one success so it's a
decent drive you know you did succeed
um yeah in making your way over to the
soccer field and interestingly enough
the address that that Madam M gives to
you Yule is actually the same address as
your local College
huh yeah it turns out that
the eight the eight-year-olds are using
this soccer field for practice
so you've actually been I thought for a
second I thought sun was a genius you
know being in college like soccer it
could be
you roll up and you do see that the
eight-year-old is playing with a bunch
of 20 year olds
all right what what as he moves across
the field you see that he kicks the ball
with ease he's Swift very quick scores a
goal all the adults dropped their knees
what the hell man
whoa
yes suckers
yes unfortunately your kid have super
speed or something
he's just very gifted
are you sure you're a human or your son
there's no way an 80 year old can play
against
you're 80.
80 80.
eight-year-olds although you said 80.
you said sorry sorry hard of hearing
sorry you know what maybe he is 80. it
just looks eight
okay I never know in this type of world
who could say
who could say she does say no comment oh
if if you really wanted the answer to
that that would give you too much
information about the father and I'd
prefer that you just not know
oh you speak the father
no absolutely not
oh yeah disgusting
oh you're turning off the car oh sorry
I'm just getting really nauseous right
now thinking about anything like that
with Vic understandable I would feel the
same mother
almost as if you summoned him the car on
cue
exits the college building with a broom
in hand oh hey hold on a second I look
like he's here he's here oh hey guys
what's going on Tiana acts as if she
doesn't know him and looks away
no
how you guys you guys want to go to
McDonald's instead
unless we dropped off the lady let's
drive quick quick quick
wait wait no hold on a sec
okay there we go quick question can I
have that broom you're holding on to
oh yeah sure Scout what you're gonna use
it for I don't know I just want to hold
on to it
I think you fly
no oh like a witch made of wood though
it feels real sturdy
oh okay Scout yeah sure here here you go
I don't really know what you're gonna do
with it he gives he gives you the broom
thank you very much have a nice day just
holding on to it
and then Scout got a broom
you will as soon as you start thinking
about going to McDonald's with the team
and just forgetting about all of this
because you know Madam m is kind of
sauntering out of the car you know
waddling towards her son who's now
kicking all the adults in The Shins
she's like Timmy hey Timmy
Timmy stop shut up mom
you're so lame
little Timmy please Timmy I can't
mommy's wounded mommy's morally wounded
Come on
Mommy Mommy she shot to me as she kind
of Waddles toward her son you'll you
actually get a phone call
oh
yes I'll take the phone call
hello this is Patrick
you hear
a familiar voice on the phone a voice
you haven't heard in a long time
hello there yule it's me hello
don't you remember
it's the professor
yeah you're cutting out
oh oh sorry realistic
sorry
don't you remember you'll
it's me
professor
oh
well doctor have you been
I've been
very that's good
I've been that's good I thought I'm
waiting
for you
for you you'll
are you ready for
ready for ready for what
you'll turn on the speakerphone
okay I turned on the speakerphone
forever outside the college right now
I've done it I found a way to save the
world you will
you are saving the world I was
all of this time I figured out what it
wanted
and I created something magnificent
what what
I want to share it with you you will
okay this is a stranger nature so uh um
welcome meet me
I mean I guess I'm or are you at the are
you at the at the lab I'm kind of nearby
I can drop by if you want
yes I'm in my lab but
you're going to need to go underground
there's an underground
there is go to the Challenger's closet
the Janitor's Closet all about the Metro
okay bring everyone
you know but
wait how do you
know about
more what do you mean by everyone
I've been watching you so patiently
watching all of your adventures you too
are serving my same goal
and thusly I think it's only important
that I invite you to be a part of this
oh it sounds like a cult meeting
you build a flux capacitor sir
you can say we'll go with you we'll be
there with you I know well I guess if
it's with everyone it we'll we'll get
through it right don't forget let's go
I've given you many many A's in the past
I think I've earned those A's and also
the paychecks for the TA that I've been
doing in the lab
um your work has been a little slow
they stop sleeping on the floor by the
way
well if there was enough time to
complete the task you've given me and
and
okay
you before we go this person we don't
even know this person is it are we
walking into a trap or something you
think there's a chance at all I don't
know the profit has always been so
mysterious experiments
I don't know but the whole part about
saving the world is kind of
suspicious yeah you know I've watched
enough shows to you know know that it
can go right or wrong either way so well
it'd be five against one I think we
should take him we should see at least
what he has five we're taking four I
can't count no no no no I mean we have
to go to the janitors cool guys I don't
know where that is hey hey Vic do you
know where the genres cause it is well I
have a janitor would be a pretty exact
janitor if I didn't know where the
janitors closet was I mean I mean it
happens right Vic could it take a circle
lead the way yeah sure I can show you
around
okay all right all right
yes because we parked the car let's
follow and go for the closet meanwhile
you do see that Madam M kind of waves at
you guys and says um
hey um I'm going to the hospital and
then we're moving
okay moving okay Florida we're moving to
Florida no one will find us nobody will
come after us there greet the alligators
my mom I don't want to move to Florida
all my friends are here he looks back at
the adults whose Shins
all right all right you guys go ahead
and Waltz into the the school which is
well it's summer break right now
actually
um which is the main reason why uh the
field is being used by others at this
point in time however it is it does
still seem to be a team of adults so
that part's a little strange
um but um but the college itself is
closed so you know Vic explains to you
all you know I was actually just doing a
bit of cleaning around here inside of
the school
um you know for summer and whatnot but
what what exactly do you guys want to do
in here again what's the deal uh work
I'm visit I actually go to this school
if you remember I'm just visiting the
professor and the professor kind of
asked if we could uh I think we should
tell them everything you will tell them
everything he's an alibi if things go
wrong we'll have somebody on the outside
all right what did you say
wants me to visit
uh and and the lab but we gotta go
through the underground which is
apparently accessible from the Janitor's
Closet I don't know which genres closet
but you know since you're you are the
Jagger of the school I thought maybe you
know you could possibly know where
that could be oh we actually have 25
janitors closets oh man exactly yeah
is there any one of them that you find
very uh interesting or
not so sweet I mean something
interesting that happens in any of them
any people walking in a lot of uh closet
often
oh let me see any of them got a book
memory check I mean let me try to
remember okay it says as he rolls a
memory check
come on Vic
a matter of fact I actually think I do
remember something like that
um there's there is one closet that I
like to go to
um to like watch you know usually it's
my break room I like watch a bunch of
break room yeah I just chilled sit back
you know smoke a vape watch some uh some
television you know
um and there is a draft
that I don't like very much you know
kind of kind of kills the vibe you know
the wind yeah
yeah let's let's start from there why
not
okay follow me
following yeah yes chat he Vapes he's a
vapor he's a vaping boy
so Vic kind of you know casually leads
you guys
um into the Janitor's Closet and it's um
it's like a very kind of
how do I say it's um
it looks cozy but it's like empty and
you know there's like a sink there's
like um a little chill area you know it
doesn't actually have a lot of cleaning
stuff in it weirdly enough it looks more
like a break room than a Janitor's
Closet aside from the you know the odd
mop here and there
um but Vic says yeah here it is I need
me to do anything else
uh no we'll we'll take a look around and
see if this is the one I guess it's a
perception check to look around can you
ask him where that draft was coming from
oh
oh yeah yeah Draft before he goes if he
could just point it out yeah uh yeah
let's see
um the draft
over here that's weird it used to be
right over here I remember because you
know this is where I sit to like chill
and it really killed the vibe uh you
know with the draft and whatnot I really
couldn't focus
yeah hated that draft
um but I don't know
um you can look around here on the the
right side of the room
all right I guess I'll I'll look around
now hidden door reception reception
check I have a bad perception you guys
uh seven right
seven days
what do you see with your special eyes
yule
about four successes
all right so pretty much immediately
you'll you are able to sense the draft
um coming from the corner of the room
and interestingly enough
um you see a small crack in the wall
right behind where the the super dinky
1970s TV is
um it's very faint and it looks it looks
like you definitely would not have
noticed it unless you unless you looked
really hard and there isn't any draft
coming out of it anymore interestingly
it seems almost as though somebody
realized that this this crack in the
wall was here
and tried to cover up
we try to uh open it or break it somehow
guys yeah guys time
it's perfect
pickaxe no you know how hard I couldn't
like knock on the wall or something to
kind of get a feel for how thick or
there's like a wall like yeah what's it
yeah button or anything you knock on the
wall and it seems like it's very thick
no button inside it seems as though it's
been resealed by someone from the inside
oh
big pic as though someone wanted to have
sealed in there
sealed in there is it
can we see if it's like is it drywall is
it what's behind the do you know what I
mean like yeah what kind of rock it is
material what is that is it even I don't
want to smash a pickaxe on something
that isn't even smashable oh true yeah
that would be really bad for your
pickaxe all right go ahead Scout and
tell me what
um what your uh let's just do a typical
um a typical wits and
um let's just do wits and compose your
perception I think that would be best
yes four okay perception check for
Scouts
okay that's one success and then okay
all right one success
um you can tell that it's not brick
um it seems to be
a bit less tough than brick whatever is
behind there not quite drywall not quite
brick so I would
like plywood seems more like wood
hmm
yeah it seems like we could throw what
Toto against it that should work
Mass traveling quickly at the wall
he's quite throwable a little
tick
uh tv antenna
okay okay and uh watoto take a battery
and smash
oh
we watch the TV on
is there a TV in the break room is this
something we can bust through
it's on Teletubbies
oh who still plays Teletubbies TV
okay light battery acid on fire okay
gotcha okay you want to light the
batteries that's gonna be a crafts roll
it's going to be wits plus crafts
oh dear
five all right I have an Alchemy skill
oh Alchemy
um let's see that apply here Alchemy is
making stuff out of yeah I guess that
would that would make sense I'll go
ahead and I'll apply it
all right two successes
um you create one vial of battery acid
and you have exhausted
the battery unfortunately
um you've had to use all the batteries
that you collected in order to make this
all okay if you have one vile of battery
acid
does anyone have a lighter
I do oh yeah you did bring a lighter
if you don't want to use your lighter if
you fluid oh true it's just one time
turning it on right it's buttery acid
blow up
um that's a great question hold on I
don't know how that works I think it
just like eats through things that it's
really acidic right
see no battery fluid can evolve
flammable hydrogen gas when exposed to
Metals this seems complicated very hard
to extinguish is it going to catch the
whole thing on fire if it's wood what is
this building made we're setting the
whole school on fire
we have upgraded lighting okay
we look great
okay all right yes it is flammable
okay wait battery acid explodes when it
comes in contact with water one what
saliva is water
okay
battery acid on whole okay on the the
crease in the wall
okay you spread the battery acid now
what do you choose to do
wait I have I have a bottle of water I
can use a little bit of water it doesn't
explode that way
yeah all right so you ex you use one
water bottle okay now you have one left
okay
and maybe Scott should throw one of the
matches while we're standing outside of
the room just for sure yeah that's true
I'll give you guys I was gonna say I'll
give some of my matches and they can do
it it smells dangerous no no hey people
to carry this uh match into the room
into a small room before with no windows
hahaha
wait what do you need me to what are you
gonna make me do this seems dangerous
it's fine
just stand here in the door frame while
we're standing behind you and throw this
match at that little you know that thing
there oh yeah how's your aim Vic
um let's see I'm really good at cornhole
amazing
okay perfect for the job yeah
hold on can I hit my vape really quick
uh sure okay hold on one second you want
to vape now
yeah
I'm a little nervous right now you know
you guys are really looking at me funny
like I get this really strange feeling
from you guys okay we can look the other
way you know yeah I don't know about
this you guys are gonna have to
someone's gonna have to roll persuasion
to persuade Vic to do this I have
persuas
ion social skill all right what is
actually pretty weak but it's um
gin plus expression
all right
there
you do not succeed in fact you almost
fail in fact I think you do fail
ah oh yeah well then I'll do it I'm out
you guys sorry about that I just uh I
feel I'm gonna go Vape outside can
someone intimidate
oh
you want to scare him into doing it
I have one intimidation I have two okay
very intimidating one day all right
intimidation plus expression
uh where's expression
you can also use manipulation for this
one it's above above oh I don't have any
just intimidation two okay I have
expression and intimidation okay
so let's see
um then that'll be a minus one so also
so you can only roll um a one which is
dangerous
can I try persuasion and kind of
manipulate persuasion okay you want to
try a manipulation persuasion roll yeah
so that's a three better than the one
come on all right intimidation is always
an option if this doesn't work okay uh
same number
um which you know now Vic is really like
about to leave he's like actually I
think
actually I think I'm gonna smoke my vape
on the other side of the field uh Scout
do you have a chance you have a chance
to be less intimidate him Scout let's go
we'll give it a try
expression plus intimidation is three
okay
uh it's a critical success
oh nice
she rolled up her invisible sleeves
um so what do you say to Vic Scout
something [\h__\h] I don't know I didn't
think it is okay you can fewer words is
fine too you can just tell them to get
over there don't give him give him a hug
or something afterwards
about breaking his Vape
okay uh oh you do do it do it or else
ah okay fine
buddy God she doesn't even have to say
anything in particular she looks coldly
it's those it's the eyes
okay fine
all right uh stand back ladies he holds
the match
um and says do you want me to throw it
what do you want me to do
watoto spread battery acid all over wall
and crack so yes throw okay I throw now
what's the order of you guys standing
behind Vic
oh God that's the order
um
just need to know GM reasons
be pretty far away I mean
because we knew it was dangerous going
in yeah we're kind of standing on the
other side of the hallway
the pictures on the doorway okay okay no
problem all right
yeah anything for you tiara
he throws the match and all of a sudden
there's a huge boom
um and everything feels hot for a second
you guys feel like your skin is being
ever so slightly scorched but because
because Vic is the one that's kind of
you know taking the brunt of it
um you guys mostly turn up safe no
damage really worth mentioning
um Vic on the other hand is on the
ground
um he's not dead because he's a vampire
and whatever he should be fine but he's
definitely not conscious at least the
wall is open
okay good well since he's not conscious
we don't have to deal with uh anything
now with him being himself step over him
carefully you can't can't breathe
chemicals from fire
um I can't hear
what role
big boom now big boom true we sound it
does eventually calm down though
thankfully okay but it is it is a little
bit difficult to hear however what to
tell you what you are correct
um about the chemicals there are yucky
chemicals around here what do you guys
choose to do
run fast
all right is that how you guys would
like to handle old breasts okay
old breath and run into yeah oh
Scout puts on the goggles she has on her
forehead okay
cool you have goggles all right
everybody I'm gonna have you roll
um an Athletics dexterity rule to see
how quick you can get through the gas
um except for scalp because of your
goggles I think you're probably fine
so let's start with Yule you'll what's
your Athletics plus dexterity
Athletics and dexterity okay three three
okay
here we go
um that's not what I meant to do hold on
for roll three D ten greater than eight
uh zero successes okay so
um as you run through the the smog and
chemicals you'll you do um unfortunately
not run quick enough to really stop from
breathing in some of it
um I'm gonna have you take three
bludgeoning damage
don't worry I'll keep track of your
health over here so bludgeoning so there
are three different levels of Health if
you guys remember there's blood lethal
and and um Mortal or like um you're
gonna die damage right yeah um so
bludgeoning is okay bludgeoning is just
a slash
mm-hmm okay Yule is just a slash three
slashes okay um eventually though if you
get lethal those will turn into X's
um okay and you just you really don't
want to get the the worst damage which
is
the Mortal damage but you'll be fine
probably unless you're happy
um wait you said you'll be fine
[Music]
hey hey hey I like that yeah it's pretty
sharp yo what's your health by chance
the one you gave me had six so I don't
know if there's an updated one okay
gotcha we haven't really we aren't
really using exp for this series just
because it's a bit short
um but that's okay uh let's see next up
we've got Tiara are you ready to run
through the smog hell yeah I got six ooh
those are Chad numbers right there I
like it
okay
um yeah I don't even really need to
reroll this 10 but you're oh yes to say
four successes you're fine yay you're
absolutely A-Okay all right well it's
until your turn what's your Athletics
plus dexterity two okay oh
[Music]
sadly watato uh you take similar damage
to Yule
um it's three bludgeoning damage what is
watoto's health
uh eight eight okay you're you're a
sturdy one so you should be fine okay so
all of you do manage um to get through
eventually to get through the the wall
and uh you find yourselves in a totally
different area an area that is
completely unlike
this area or the previous area in that
it's much darker
it's much older
there's something off about it
in that it seems like a place that just
isn't visited Often by humans but you
know that that can't be true if the
professor is back here
Colleen yeah
St strg
just so you know that's easy and OBS
if something's like oversized when you
put it into the screen and you press
Ctrl plus F control immediately like
adjust it to your window size oh nice
okay
Patrol control
let me see I see gotcha thanks a
Chihuahua you're welcome so you guys
enter this brand new hallway who would
like to roll a perception check
okay the good ones
okay what are your numbers yule
seven okay
let's see what you see with your special
eyes four sixes
so you you immediately notice that um
this place well it's old as hell it's
decrepit but someone has definitely been
in here you can see in the dust on the
ground there are still Footprints subtle
Footprints here and there additionally
scattered in between the footprints are
twigs and leaves
oh I remember these twigs and leaves
Professor had me fetch them well that
one day really for what
I don't know
figure it out huh I did not sell any
cookies
maybe in another world
no cookies I don't know I see footsteps
Footprints I feel like we should go
follow it maybe it's the professors
what do you guys think okay yeah
all right
what's the footprints what's the
lighting in this area it's dim but
there's some flickering lights of
electricity
um from lamps in the ceiling that are
just barely working
lights
well everyone uh be careful it's a
little
weird here but hopefully nothing too
dangerous what and slowly make our way
down the hallway
all right
you guys make your way down the hallway
further and further
and the hallway seems to stretch on for
forever
oh there we go
until finally doesn't like this
finally you roll up
to a little area here
now let me see is this the music that I
like nope that's not it
is it this one
nope
um that's okay
doesn't matter
so you find that you are in something
some sort of it feels like it's becoming
more and more like a lab
the further that you go in like not just
a research lab but
something something horrific something
like like out of a horror game or
something like that it's oh no it's
spooky the walls aren't just rusted you
you can't tell if it's rust or blood no
no
something's smeared Scout's getting
jittery
wall no no no no
sniff
all right
um You smell iron
perception roll please all right what's
your perception I'm so sorry
oh oh oh which plus what is it uh
composure composure that's a four okay
Scout rules two successes and then one
re-roll
all right with two successes
um what are you choosing to to see what
do you want to focus on in particular
here Scout the walls okay looking for
looking for teeth I'm looking for
anything I'm looking for anything that
could be just like the the the living
tunnel that I got stuck in all right so
you look closely at the nuts and bolts
in the wall
and they seem to quiver ever so slow
but
almost as though there's something bad
feeling about this
I think we should go back
or are we too late oh and do we want to
call out for the dog maybe I mean boys
Dr oopsie Dr oops
it echoes through the Halls
in our response you just hear a low
grumbling noise from the walls
okay check if there's a signal on my
phone
sure thing you look at your phone
and it appears that the reception it
doesn't look very good
I mean
uh I guess I could still try to call
Dr oopsie
all right
you attempt to give Dr oopsy a call
and interestingly enough it does manage
to go through but only for a moment
well
Dr oopsy
hello hello
can you can you hear hello
see I think we're on the way but I'm not
sure if we're this is the way there's
like a weird hallway with some blood
looking things on the wall am I am I
going the right way come on speaker he
won't hurt you
oh he won't hurt you he's on our side
perfect
o can go first okay
Eve all right we're on our way I think
we'll be there soon hopefully and just
like that Dr oopsy's voice is gone
feels as though it's being sucked into
the darkness
before you well the Dark Hall stretches
onward and onward and you can't see
anything about 10 feet ahead of you
mm-hmm
uh do you advance
my total jog
all right let's I guess we're advancing
going
follow what Toto
all right you guys follow watoto Down
The Long Dark
ever stretching onward hallway
seems as though it has no end
until finally you arrive at what looks
to be
some kind of
well it looks like
a very large heavily plated door
huh
the outlines of it seem to almost wiggle
as though dimensions are being
changed and worked around them
interesting should we not yeah knock
okay
okay you knock
no answer
this guy
is there a lock on it perception check
all right sure thing
what's your perception Well mine's
really bad free okay
you never know
uh no success
I'll do perception I'll see if there's
anything you'll see
all right yours is seven seven
oh my God okay it's my cousin everything
all right success is a critical success
um you see that the door has a lot of
traffic oh wait never mind that's five
never mind I can't count okay you go
ahead it's fine yeah five successes so
you see
you see that wait maybe it is six one
two three four five six okay it's six
it's six ah I was right okay so it's a
critical success either way you see that
the door has a large wheel an Iron Wheel
uh stuck to it
and it's not particularly Rusty it looks
that with the proper amount of strength
you would be able to turn it and it
looks like it's the only mechanism on
the door
all right I've got no windows though I
don't know what lies ahead
remember Lefty Lucy righty tighty wait
turn it low right oh I have big strength
and okay Athletics
okay I have physical activity it's gonna
be strength it's going to be strength
plus Athletics
I have that yeah that's six for me okay
oh
all right okay Sierra you grab the wheel
firmly with both of your hands and pull
unfortunately it sticks fast and it
looks as though someone's going to need
to help you
someone is going to need to assist you
okay I can help
all right you keep turning uh Tiara and
Scout joins you on the door uh Scout
what is your strength plus uh athletic
not Athletics yes athletic strength plus
Athletics three all right
it's not much
all right together we strong yes the two
of you manage nice managed quite nicely
to make some progress on the door
um Tiara at first you know you kind of
pull and then Scout grabs two of the the
handles on the wheels kind of like a
pirate ship handle
um and and she pulls down and then
suddenly it gets unstuck and begins to
turn in the correct Direction ever so
slowly and the most awful screeching
noise rings out through the hallway
[Music]
[Applause]
on your ears
oh yeah I loosened it all right
you loosened it
and finally
the door opens
do you enter the room
yes I love that screeching emotes man
that you've got
it's so good the screeching emote oh
yeah
yeah it's pretty good
and very slowly but surely
you enter
into the dark room
so this one's really dark
this one interestingly enough is not as
dark as the hallway that you were just
in in fact okay
there are green lights emanating from
several areas in the room the room is
quite wide oh
and you begin to hear
the sound of something
a being a large being within the room
boom being
some kind of instant boss fight no
perception
I'll roll seven
surely
God damn it all my time
that luck runs out I'm telling you
it does sometimes
can I do something with my dangerous
sense
sure
um well see with your danger sense I
would have I would have let you know if
it was truly dangerous right
so you're okay for now
okay okay but you'll is used to working
in the dark that's why I see very well
in the dark
suddenly you see before you
behind the glass there is something
alien
something you've never seen before Oh
it looks something like uh
it's very long it's got please no
Metroid Prime
huh
almost as though it has multiple limbs
no couldn't be limbs you it must be
it must be next
next
put hand on glass
you put the hand on the glass and
suddenly
a long
tentacle presses against your hand and
you feel a connection
it's the worm
the wire like a tentacle
oh
Big Worm
something long
and you hear a guttural noise as though
someone
well to you Walter toe it just sounds
like a greeting but to the others
sounds
horrific
it sounds like the worst sound you've
ever heard
what is the thing is this an animal
you can't tell can I do animal can
you may do animal Ken plus expression
all right that is a four okay
can it hear you through the glass
all right with one success you are able
to determine that this is not an animal
this is something
animals animals have some some level of
Consciousness to them this thing
this thing is it has no no conscience
did we hear the last conversation you
had with Dr oopsie on the phone we sat
on speaker or was that not yeah I'd
assume you guys have heard it okay yeah
yeah okay I was on speaker then because
you remember he said that it don't worry
it will he won't hurt you it won't hurt
you so this thing whatever it is is not
a bad thing
I mean that's what he said but you know
with experiments like this you never
know how it can go wrong I mean it says
it doesn't since since talking to the
animal doesn't count it doesn't have its
own
thoughts
you want to attempt to speak to the
creature
okay
you will need to roll your expression
Plus
socialize plus two
and how many
you have zero for both of those
yeah all right well you still get three
well plus two right yeah
okay
all right
with two successes
you are able to somewhat make sense
somewhat of what it's saying to you
only watoto can hear this however
so here's
well first it doesn't just speak to you
it wants you to speak first what do you
say to him
big long worm
are you dangerous
it is almost time
time for what
time for the Reckoning you're Reckoning
what
the worm says time for Reckoning what's
happening what
what is Reckoning worm
laughs
I will finally receive the present that
I have been promised
the worm is gonna get a present oh at
Christmas time I know I don't think it's
Christmas yet what what what's the
present
what kind of person is
the present what no
no
it's not the present you're a present
for me
oh
this kind of holds flustered it
hold on a second
coffee hold on
oh oh just didn't the doctor say that he
found a way or so to save the world or
am I mixing up things out of you are
correct you were right this thing is
supposed to save the world let me ask
like I don't know can we look around to
see if there's any like signs of Dr
oopsy or anything
um let's see uh one one of you guys can
roll a perception check one of you other
members
how well is your perception
is that with dexterity
that's a four okay good I'll take a look
around
all right with one success you notice
that there's one other door in this room
oh
and there is a bright light coming from
the window it is approximately near the
end of the large capsule
um but what you realize
um is that there's there's something
strange going on here the window in
front of you you realize it actually
might not be a container
it might actually just be a window
can we look beyond what where the worm
is to like where it is
um the glass is very fog fogged up oh
okay you can only see a basic shape
I guess we can walk towards the door
because we still got a plenty of Dr
oopsie yeah where is he where's that guy
yeah
walk towards the door okay
you're going to need to roll another
strength check to open it because this
one also has a similar lock or similar
can I help all right would you like to
roll to assist uh first of all Scout
uh
uh if if she needs it all right there is
a way that you can assist in this so
Scout what is your initial role what is
your role for strength plus uh Athletics
uh three okay
all right with one success that adds one
dice to Tiara's pool
noise
okay so seven now now you have seven
dice
come on surely oh
so big
finally just nice all right so with the
combined power of you two ladies
extremely strong muscles
um Scout you kind of you kind of uh
bring up the the bottom part and tiara
you grab from the top and Pull and once
again you hear that terrible screeching
noise
and as it screeches you hear a horrific
roar coming from from the inside of that
room as the door itself almost kind of
forces itself to be pushed open
and it opens up to you
and we see
and
you see
we see something horrific no oh
a sight that you never thought that you
would see in your life
role of perception
like graduation papers
all right okay
because this is a new room
one success one success oh
um
it's big
Dr oopsie is there it's real big and Dr
oopsy is there oh you see
in this room you suddenly realize why
that window that you saw before wasn't a
window after or wasn't a capsule after
all no container because this creature
the big large thing behind the window is
not contained at all but rather
is free still in some chains but
otherwise free and out in the open
a horrific creature that you've never
seen before
this
what is this could this be
could this be
the worm
you see wait it's a thing Lee heads
three heads on this large being that is
chained to the ceiling
and before the creature stands a
familiar being you'll
it is
a doctor wait wait wait wait logic uh
we'll check because I don't understand
we saw one being first behind some
window and now we see another one behind
the door which one is the one on the
picture
they're both the same one it's the same
yeah
but the window was like a giant room it
was not like a
like a container it's like a it's like a
window yeah correct yeah yeah oh
yes
yes with this large being before you
with bright green eyes and an unknown
substance dripping from the mouth
doesn't look like something that could
save the world at uh what the hell we
should get out of here doctor
when you say this Tiara as soon as you
speak Dr oopsie turns around previously
she had been standing before the being
with her with her arms spread open as
though speaking to it as she turns
around and you notice that she has one
of those masks on her face one of those
glasses
done
that's right she looks at you and begins
to speak with a sort of fervor that only
a mad woman would speak with
I have done it I have found a way to
appease the Beast you'll
face what have you done
this being it's been creeping into our
society it wants chaos it wants
destruction but I have befriended it I
have while you're talking I'm taking
steps back and and getting my sniper
rifle ready okay
take some shots at the yeah just in case
just keep on talking keep on talking
okay
I have created what this thing wants a
world to take over a pocket Dimension
you will I was creating
a fantastic place
a world that this thing could be God of
don't you see how brilliant it is
how
it's quite simple really
I figured out how to copy the dimension
that is known as the Hedge
and create an even larger world for this
thing to govern
and therefore
he will stop coming after this world
isn't it fantastic
sounds good
however there's something missing
there's something missing you
what's missing
humans to govern
all of a sudden you guys begin to feel
very strange
all of you can I no your your hearts
begin to race as you feel your skin
crawl
and you realize that
there's something fishy about this room
you're done
I'm saving the universe
can I try to take a shot
sure go ahead at the doctor oopsie's
head
yeah sure all right so you you may roll
Firearms plus dexterity what does the
violin sniffs and Shadow sniper have
like extra you know yeah it has plus two
oh
firearms and dexterity yes uh okay
what's Gunslinger again
a gunslinger oh boy
Gunslinger let's see
perfect I'm all in favor of this but
what if it ends up making the Beast
angry and then I'll take the Beast up
next oh gun store means you can fire two
pistols
and pistols can we can we can you aim
for the mask maybe the mask is yeah yeah
I'll take it so I'll go for the mask but
okay sorry one more question uh all
these things the marriage they seem it's
been a long time are they even maybe
useful I have subduing strikes loaded
for bear and human prey is any of this
useful let's see
I don't think loaded for bear is gonna
be useful here but let me check
how close am I to Dr oopsie
let's see
here okay yeah these merits those merits
do not apply sadly damn it okay well
then I'll just take a shot with the plus
two and the uh Firearms is four okay
plus 632 so six plus two eight it's an
eight roll okay
two successes
eight okay wow oh
okay so you managed to aim a shot
directly at Dr oopsie's mask and you
fire
it whistles through the air and
eventually reaches it connects with the
mask and the mask explodes after doctor
off of Dr oopsy's face easy you see many
pieces however you do also manage to
Lodge the bullet directly into Dr
oopsie's cheek unconscious
[Music]
I'm happy with this results
I need to finish my paper [\h__\h] that
all of you at this moment hear a mighty
Roar inside of your minds inside of your
own brains
the being says
come to me my children
you will inhabit my world no I refuse
all right everybody I'm gonna need to
you to roll a composure check
the closure just composure straight
composure
all right oh no we'll start with yule
with one success
all right you get one success
all right
you start to feel yourself slipping in
between Dimensions you'll oh no but you
at least are able to recognize what is
happening to you
and that's when you realize that Dr
oopsie has already done it
in fact
the door itself you notice something
kind of strange about that door as you
fall to the ground you fall to your
knees and then manage to glance over at
the door that you entered through and
you realize that opening that door
triggered some kind of mechanism
oh a mechanism that started a large
machine
the room is a machine
all right Scout roll your composure
two
Oh Boy Scout you fall to the ground and
you slip away
goodbye no Scout
[Laughter]
all right Tiara what is your composure
all right one success you too also begin
to slip but you are able to recognize
that you are passing through dimensions
oh
watoto
what's your composure
three all right
oh my Lord oh
with two successes watoto you watch your
friends fall to the ground
um and you you watch their bodies kind
of
it's odd it looks as though they're kind
of fizzling out of existence they're
leaving this realm and now it's just you
and the large being in front of you the
enigmatic dark shadow looks directly at
you with the beaming green eyes
still drooling
my child
you must join them you have a mission
no I will save them
you do that water though but in the end
chaos will reign forever
want to make a trade
another trade
before you know it you two are now
passing through the dimensions but not
in the same way as the others uh this
time you know you travel very easily
their traveling is very painful but it's
not so difficult for you
and just like that
you guys begin traveling through
the in-between
oh
for a moment another dimension oh no you
see a light on the horizon as you feel
your body's traveling
speeds that you didn't know were
possible for Humanity
100 miles per hour no a thousand no one
million miles per hour through eternity
and past Dimensions you feel your body's
becoming rendered
and just like that
when you open your eyes
no
you find yourselves in
well
not really that scary of a place at all
just a bit
strange a forest
a large Forest yeah yeah that sounds
it's purple and blue and seems to be
seems to be full of
bugs that don't seem generated by this
war by the human world
flowers premium things that you've never
quite encountered before
where are we the Scout wake up or
Scout's still asleep
oh you wake up all of you slowly begin
to come to your senses where's the Beast
gone
not in this Dimension from what you can
tell you don't sense the Beast
watoto
you are alone in this tranquil yet Eerie
forest and interestingly enough Dr
oopsie is also there on the ground still
passed out
got him
now can I hit him with my broom
do you choose
I'm going to awaken Dr oopsy with my
broom that I stole from Vic all right
are you keeping that thing
uh it's in my
holster yeah
my blacksmith holster yeah the same one
as the pickaxe it's a little harder just
stick it in there you know yeah
I'll go ahead and have you roll um let's
have you do
um a weapon a strength and weaponry
check
I'm not gonna I'm not trying to be beat
this person I'm just you know okay
accuracy uh Weaponry is one two three
four strength is three a seven wow okay
a mini beating right there something no
I'm not trying to beat machine awake all
right well with two successes you you go
ahead and accomplish your goal but you
you kind of you know since you're trying
to do it softly but you know because
it's just it's only two successes you
kind of you kind of whack the [\h__\h] out
of her um and she does take a couple
bludgeoning
um sorry
she coughs up a bit of blood
oh I didn't hit you that hard come back
well you don't think the blood is
she did get shot in the face so okay
yeah it's cool you didn't do that
somebody else did well I had to free him
from the mask and I did that doctor
oopsy are you okay wake up
ah you I have I have failed you
I'm so sorry I get an F
no
you were always my best student
I just I thought I was doing what's
right I thought I could create a world
to to make to make him happy to make him
leave ours alone but
but I don't think I think he's going to
take both now
um
do you know where we are or how do I get
out of here is there a way
not I didn't create a way out
but great it doesn't matter he's on his
way anyway he
would be on his way
who he
the new yeah that Creator God of this
world
I suppose technically I am the god of
this world because I created it but he
will be its new ruler
and now but with you humans here
he has beings to torture and play with
oh [\h__\h] whoops track change beings to
torture and play with
all of you I'm so sorry I don't know how
to get you out of here
[Music]
well we'll find a way out uh
we always do you created this world
right what it what how like some sort of
is it like a material world is it a
digital world I don't know is it a
simulation something it's another
dimension similar to the Hedge
have you been to the Hedge before
yes hola possibly possible
I I created a special technology that
could copy the Hedge
I copied it and made some modifications
of my own but there are no humans in
here except for you
couldn't you also add humans or other
creatures
I thought
because you four are
strong you could keep the Beast
entertained for a long time
well
I'm sorry you always said to mind
always said to you know plan for
multiple possibilities in every
experiment I can't believe
you went against your philosophy
like I said I wasn't in my right mind
maybe another whack with my broom you'll
be in your right mind you can get out of
here I suppose I deserve that
no
now if you help us
I mean is it is it impossible to create
or copy humans
Etc
to
take place in this world you know
I pondered that but
it didn't seem possible
I I suppose if we did manage to get out
of here we could
we could try to to copy yourselves over
but but what if those copies have their
own Consciousness then we'd be dooming
them to Hell forever
doesn't seem like there's a clean cut
way out of this
we must kill
worm the Worm but that's impossible it's
it can't be killed it's a it's a being
of
Eternity
a Three-Headed Beast that cannot be
quelled
um
steal it
that could be possible
the pig worm
if we I suppose if we did manage to lead
it into this world it is on the way
after all ah
if we found a way to escape perhaps we
could exit in time to destroy the
dimension with
the worm in it how big is the worm I
thought this thing was huge how are we
going to sneak out with a big giant worm
I mean the big one will be stuck here
and we're the small one the wormhole
Wormhole truth be told the being that
you saw
in the lab
was merely a servant of the worm
corporeal being a copy so to speak
of its body see the worm is is more than
just it's more than just a material
monster in the world it's
like I said a creature of Eternity
we can't truly kill it but perhaps
perhaps we can seal it and as soon as Dr
oopsy says that suddenly you sense a
strange glitch
oh in this dimension
everything flashes red for a moment
and you hear what's happening booming
voice
come out
it's time
huh
that's not quite what I wanted this is
the one I wanted
there come out to where first time
it's time time to play humans
Hmm this world
this world looks like [\h__\h]
why is it so beautiful
I can change that
oh no is it just weird that's not like
big
sorry I control
there's a little
deeper
oh
[Music]
yes chaos
okay so that's hard to understand chaos
thanks for repeating that big word
I mean I hope you all are ready
my humble servants who will help me in
terraforming this world
what happens if we're not ready
well the the voice does not respond to
you after that and suddenly before you
know it
you see a large being appear in front of
you
suddenly the world the world begins to
change around you it begins to lose its
color
in some areas a deadly red in other
areas completely monochrome and a dense
fog permeates
flora and fauna begins to die off at a
rapid pace and suddenly there is nothing
left but desolation
and a large figure looming in the
distance with two hands and then a third
hand
oh okay
it's it's
The Hash Slinging Slasher
kind of correct okay kind of correct
and just like that you guys realize that
you are being slowly tailed but not
before
you witness a sight most horrific Dr
oopsy looking up
at the large being drops to her knees
and says please spare us
we've made a mistake
my liege if this world is not to your
liking I can make a better one well just
please let us out
oh he's gonna die she's gonna die
you watch as a large booming voice says
you may dispose of her
doctor
and before you can do anything a large
hook
penetrates the center of Dr oopsie's
heart and raises her up to the sky as
she vomits blood
the blood spatters beneath her making a
most sickening noise
before
the hook drags Dr oops
sorry every time I say doctor
drags the doctor drags the doctor toward
its face you hear a horrific crunching
noise but you can see nothing
the sound of Bones cracking and flesh
being consumed
and the figure begins to advance towards
you
I think we should what do you choose to
find a way out
one Toto will flip over rocks to look
for a hole
all right
um
all right role perception what's your is
that your turn you guys get one turn to
do something oh what do you guys want to
do do we get a perception roll or does
that not count uh it'll count as your
turn
oh no okay
I wanna fight
you want to fight the being I want I
want to shoot
all right you may take a shot
um
yeah my Snivy
all right
with two successes you managed to hit a
shot with it what appears to be the neck
of the creature and it gives you no
response it does not seem as though it
has been hurt or damaged in any way
okay
um maybe we should just
can I can you can see can I look around
to see if there's any way to escape
all right sure that will be your turn
okay perception big all right seven
three successes oh okay
all right with three successes you do
see that there are some some brambles a
bush nearby
um that leads very far down and you
think that the being might be impeded
having to walk down so many rocks down
the cliff
you realize that you may be able to
outrun this thing if you have the
appropriate Athletics role
everyone look there's a there's a way
out of here maybe maybe we can outrun
whatever is chasing us
oh
sure well I can probably outrun it don't
know about you guys
I don't mean they're not I mean it's
worth a try for everyone I think okay
maybe actually may not be I won't attack
rocks
all right I
I I rolled the running thingy but I
while watoto is looking at the Rocks I
pick water up and take water to with me
you take water with you well I kind of
like grab his hands and drag him along
no Rocky time you may do that but it'll
be a minus one okay oh no all right so
what's your Athletics plus dexterity
uh six all right
six
all right
gotta go we gotta go all right with two
successes you just barely managed to
skip over to the cliff and you move
quickly around the Rocks um and are able
to make it a decent way down but not
quite all the way just yet we'll need
Scout and Yule to roll their Athletics
and dexterity or find another way
to scale the cliff
uh
I already have the three I don't know if
it'll be worth it all right remember you
may use any items if you can think about
how to use them creatively
I mean I only have I mean
uh could I possibly use the water bottle
to like how far is the
the slippers what huh 10 feet away from
you
ten feet do you think I could like toss
the waterfall and then like turn on the
taser and then like throw it as well so
I could try to like electrocute it and
somehow that could work but okay we'll
need to you will need to have a good six
a good level of success with that in
order to do this you will need to use
your
you will need to use your dexterity and
wits
oh that's six okay I think that's more
worth it than my running okay
with three successes okay you managed to
you don't really know if it's doing any
damage to the being to this this warped
version of the the hook of the worms
World
um you don't really know but you do
notice that you have managed to stop it
it doesn't make any noise it doesn't it
doesn't um fall to its knees but it does
stop for a moment which gives you enough
time to to run so both you and Scout you
may add plus two to your Athletics
dexterity role nice okay so that's uh
that's a five okay we'll start with you
huh
I thought I was looking at me menacingly
for not letting him look at the Rocks I
don't want to flip Rock no Rock no no
with two successes uh you do manage to
get to where um
to wear Tiara and watoto are now how
about you Scout Athletics and dexterity
plus two
uh Athletics dexterity plus two so be
that would be four but I have my broom
is there a way I can like while I'm
running wedge it into the ground and use
it to like launch forward an extra bit a
little bit yeah just to get myself I'll
take the whatever damage I get for
falling down but okay that is gonna give
you two bashing or two bludgeoning
excuse me two bludgeoning damage which
is fine there's just two slashes so all
right
um then I'll I'll give you I will give
you a plus one
does iron stamina Merit affect this at
all or no no I would not say so here
okay so that'd be of five then with my
broom with your broom okay thank you Vic
thank you Vic
all right it's one success
two successes all right so the whole
team is caught up together down the
cliff scaling down the rocks and
thankfully because of Yule's trap
um it would appear that um the being is
just kind of you know leaning over the
cliff watching you go
um almost as if to taunt you the the
Warped version of the hook the worm hook
if you will holds up the dastardly hook
with Dr oopsy's body still hanging off
of it uh
can I do something what would you like
to do
uh I I don't remember where I got it
from but I have this Enchanted mirror
right I don't know what how it works but
maybe can I like
do something with it
um maybe pointed at the monster or knock
on the mirror and ask the mirror look at
them if you want to talk to the mirror
um I wanna I wanna do a pers but is that
one one round if I just do one thing
with the mirror correct the rest of the
team will proceed down the cliff so you
can use it or you can get the safety
first it's up to you
we're past the cliff right so like yes
it would catch up with me if I do
something else but but running correct
and watoto distract the the
sure what would you like to do
dance
I want to throw my Molotov cocktail okay
go ahead and roll for me your dexterity
and let's see
we'll do uh decks and weaponry for this
one
where's the no house bro the molotov
cocktail
uh I only have two dexterity and no
Weaponry but I have survival luck
a survival walk awesome good okay can I
take the take the molotov and throw it
for watoto
sure
let's just do crafting of the yeah all
right so you want to do crafting
yeah have you actually so you haven't
made the molotov yet correct
oh oh well I have the alcohol and then
we have the match all right we just need
so first you must do a crafting
dexterity or crafting wits excuse me
witchcrafting
okay uh it's five and I have Alchemy
okay
um
hold on a sec
you know what it's the finale I'm gonna
let you use alchemy
zero successes
um
cocktail will not work it will not light
up you don't know what you did but it's
a dumbass it's not gonna work
sadly yeah you you try and get it to
light but it just won't work you don't
know if it's something about the air or
something about your crafting but it
looks like this one's a dud
well
um I'll point I don't it might not do
anything but I'll maybe a little blind
it hopefully I'll point the mirror
the monster okay but be very pointless
okay do you do it in any particular way
to try and catch the Light
yes okay then I'm just gonna roll a 1d10
for you and we'll just see what happens
how about that
1d10 to Blind the no nothing happens you
hold it up you hold the mirror up to the
Beast who just kind of tilts its head to
the side
and proceeds down the cliff following
you
[Music]
um
it was a valiant attempt
could have been something
um you realize that the cliff is getting
steeper and steeper and it seems as
though it's leading into a dark ravine
should I take my pants off now or should
I wait
you think they'll help you
they usually come in handy somehow make
a slingshot
I use it as like a like what like you
know like in breath of the wild the the
flag like a pair of shoes yeah the
glider yeah the glider glider pants
do you think it's scared of Fire
you're not sure
it didn't seem is it worth it
it got stunned with the electricity hmm
but I I no longer have
water or you know
I can reach we do have matches
you can flick matches at it
you're gonna light your pants on fire
and throw it
would you like to throw matches at the
being
can I throw one sure testing all right
dexterity plus let's do wits because
it's in the Heat of the Moment what's
index oh dear that's a four okay
not too bad
like three successes
um
your aim is good enough that you do
manage to to flick A Match Into The Eye
of this this Wormhole and you see one of
the eyes go out and um you do hear a
large grumbling you don't think that it
particularly hurt the being
um but he does he does uh fall to the
ground
um as though trying to to nurse a
wounded eye which gives you guys more
time to Cascade down the cliff all of
you may roll Athletics plus dexterity
plus two thanks to Scout's match eight
for me okay uh
five for me okay so we'll do all right
eight and then five eight to ten greater
than eight
all right you make it down the cliff
um Tiara
and greater than eight
all right one
okay
um you will you make it down the cliff
next up was it what is it five five
well that's until you make it down the
cliff Scout no one
oh dexterity end and um Athletics
oh um
four yes
okay
okay you make it down the cliff people
successfully escape from the beach
[Music]
click make do oh nice and Quick Escape
and you do feel as though you have
sufficiently gotten out of Harm's Way as
you enter this dark ravine
um it's very hard to see anything in
here until you realize that there are
some small beams of light off in the
distance oh
walk towards it yes would you like to
walk towards the light
yes scene
yeah okay
you walk ever so slowly towards the
beaming light and it seems as though no
matter how far you walk
it doesn't get any closer
oh I point the enchanted mirror at the
light you want to try and catch the
light on the mirror yes oh take out his
other eye
I mean we don't see the Monster now I
think oh yeah yeah there's no immediate
threats around you at the moment
thankfully
it's just you guys in this Ravine full
of light and you can hear your own steps
Echo around you it's almost as though
you've entered a completely different
plane
of existence within this dimension
I still want to do the mirror thing okay
yeah
um let's see so go ahead and roll for me
uh once again dexterity and wits to try
and catch the light on the mirror
oh okay dexterity and what's this time
[Music]
foreign
okay
this mirror must be good for something
all right two successes oh so as you
hold the mirror
um and try to have it catch the Light
once you do for just a moment uh catch
it on some some ray of light
um you realize that you're hearing an
internal voice
outside of your mind but the voice
itself isn't saying anything in
particular rather it's a question that
just comes to your mind
where do you want to go
well
home
home you think of home
think of home all right to my sister
yeah or back in time to before or no
okay
time traveling Antics in my world of
Darkness I don't think so
um so
um Tiara since you're the one that is
kind of hearing this in your in your own
minds Mind's Eye
um
you think she'll share it oh you want to
tell everybody what's going on yeah so I
just I you know I did the thing and um I
I heard a voice in my head asking me
where I want to go Anna
oh
I don't know if I'm going crazy either
but maybe I should answer
what would you answer oh hold on let me
try it yeah okay I'm gonna go home
all right now as the light catches
onto the mirror you see what is
a very faint
faint vision
of uh
the city streets outside of the
homestead bar
but it's very faint it doesn't seem as
though the light around you is is
sufficient enough
um
[Music]
have more reflective things or so I
don't know
you all has her phone with flashlight
yeah I have my phone can I use the phone
that's kind of a mirror sure if you'd
like to you shine a light onto the
mirror
still just doesn't look like it's enough
in fact it feels almost
in impossible
would anyone like to roll a perception
check perhaps
perceptioner
all right counting on you all right
all right with two successes
um what you're able to surmise from this
mirror Yule is that this doesn't seem
like the type of see the vision is
extremely dull it's blurry it's out of
focus but you recognize the area you get
the feeling that if there was a large
flash
something could be done here to make the
video how large of a flash you don't
know you can't tell just a large flash
[Music]
can I take a picture with everyone with
my camera and turn the flash on
sorry yeah sure you can try oh okay you
guys gather together for a picture
sure okay okay you guys gather and
everybody's smiling
um everybody's smiling and you snap
um you go ahead and turn you make sure
that you turn on the flash because
that's very important and you snap a
photo
ah
and just just for good measure you snap
a couple more
yeah you do many many flashes and sadly
it doesn't seem as though the mirror has
been all that affected there you go
something catches your eye
something about those pictures
see you took a couple of them
however the first couple it's just all
you guys in a casual smiling pose
together
and everything looks fine except as the
pictures go on you realize something
strange
something strange about
watoto
it's time no
no
it is time for your favor
if wrong your favorite
has come
what do you want from watoto
I want
you to be my servant
to do what
give me your body ah
I will take your body as my vessel
will forever be one
potato will disappear
water will live forever with me
as the governor of this world
uh you want to do flip rocks
no
oh no what turtle does not want
you don't have a choice
you feel
your your mental faculties slip away
from you as your body and mind surrender
to the worm Bound by the deal you made
so long ago what
dude
I was caught up the Hat I have a knife
can I cut it off
who's gonna kill
I was thinking making a few solution but
I don't want to lose I'll disrupt the
process I'll smack him with the berm
again disrupt me Christmas
somebody hit him throw him jump on it to
disrupt the process you watch as
watoto's body transforms before you into
a being of Destruction
what the [\h__\h]
water toes bones begin to break as
water's arms begin to change into
something something else
as this thing now
it's it's a it's a contract therefore
watoto may still try and get out of the
grasp of the Worm but it will be very
difficult
I believe
friendship
you want to use the power of friendship
our friendship well since watato is now
on the offensive and merged with the
worm
um whether whether water likes it or not
I'm gonna go ahead and put us in our
our little our new scene where we have
some tokens
oh
kind of parasite attached
you feel the inexplicable urge to kill
all of your friends
now everybody for the first time in a
million years let's roll initiative
so uh initiative is on your sheet you
have an initiative mod it determines the
turn order
so everybody will roll a 1d10 plus
uh their initiative one ah four four
okay all right one to ten plus four it's
under oh okay all right
all right so who just uh gave the the
plus four was that me Kiowa
all right tiara
all right who is next
by initiative mod is seven okay plus
seven
twelve okay
see was that yule
yes that was you okay
you
twelve
okay now
Scout how about you how do you I don't
have it written down how do you get to
your oh it's on the it's on your um it's
on your sheet the flaws it doesn't I
don't have it there really look oh let
me see I'll look for you
do you like add up
all right uh your initiative mod oh it
isn't there
um okay uh let's see
hold on math how did we decide the
initiative
right it's dexterity plus composure so
let's see a four or two uh two all right
four it's four
all right so Scout is 13. okay so that
is hold the second
all right I don't want to go first
oh yeah you don't want to hurt water
though all right
but watoto has plus three
resist or something uh plus three to for
attacking plus three to all of your
offensive
all right what is your initiative mod
um it's three but my numbers add up to
five oh gotcha okay then it should be
five and then plus three for worm
14. so you and Tiara are tired
rock paper scissors
oh yeah good idea all right this one is
for
warm Toto
five
is
this really what you want
don't know
[Music]
yes we're in Toto you can feel
you can feel the worm is is influencing
everything that you see and feel but
part of you really wants to break free
from this
so every turn all to resist every turn
you can roll a 1d10 and if you get a 9
or a 10
you can break free for that turn to take
a different action than what the worm
wants you to do
okay
so worm Toto for your turn let's have
you roll a 1d10 go go go
to your own hand you surrender to the
worm
no it's fun for this turn and this time
the worm is going to move forward
taking a step forward will also be a
turn there's kind of a little graph
before you
okay
moves closer next up
Sierra what's your move
does this thing have HP it does actually
sorry I forgot to show the health bar oh
okay well I'm interesting I had to make
a new one hold on hmm
all right
this bar right here
I only only I know the exact numbers but
oh I will adjust it accordingly oh okay
I I'll take a shot with my sniper rifle
okay
go ahead and run your Firearms plus Dex
plus two
uh uh uh uh
wait a second I don't know
oh I just noticed
honor of my firearms four plus six over
six plus two it was eight okay
all right
10 greater than eight
one
okay oh
you hit and you do one lethal damage uh
to worm Toto uh as you see the worm
recoil you also see watoto is recoiling
uh and the pain of your friend is
evident
[Music]
oh
when you when you hit wasato with the
bullet you can see for just a moment
watoto's eyes stop being red for half a
second but then become red once again
kill
[Music]
but that was quite good damage I see
how about you Scout what do you choose
to do
uh can I I don't really have any
distance weapons I have a dagger can I
launch a dagger you'd like to throw a
dagger
I guess so I'm gonna have you roll
dexterity and weaponry then
plus one for the dagger
I have
I can't see it I have like a a something
light
light a specialty in Weaponry okay
I think it's light light Weaponry oh
okay
let's see I don't know if that helps
anything but
let's see um
Henry oh I see I see
uh in in lighter weapons okay it's a
specialty okay yeah then I would add one
on to your rule for that
so that's five Weaponry plus two
dexterity okay
for my tiny little dagger all right
you've launched the dagger at the being
and watoto and you managed to do two
lethal damage
once again you'll see your friend's pain
I'm so sorry
but also I don't have my dagger now yes
your dagger is gone
it is launched in the Beast
it is ever inching closer to you
all right you will what do you choose to
do
I have I have no weapons no nothing
what do I do I think on your feet like
you guys
improvise
uh
I will see if there is any weak points
or anything usable
nearby perception okay you'd basically
like to do a perception check yeah okay
all right with one success one success
um so something that you notice pretty
quickly Yule is that the Beast that is
sort of like
taking over watoto is not simply like
um something attached to watoto's body
but is sprouting from within watato and
has completely taken over his entire
being
um you get the feeling that the only way
that you're going to be able to make it
out of this is by completely
neutralizing the threat and therefore
watoto or trying to reason with the
Beast and that in itself may be
extremely difficult
well
reason as in like talk right correct
okay
all right
I think
anybody have it since I have no
experience
you know might as well talk it out
yeah that's the best I can do yeah maybe
yeah with the talking we can do some
mental damage and get it again
all right so how do you choose to
approach this would you like to use
intimidation persuasion
ah uh persuasion okay
what total you can you can make it out
come back to us
speaking to your friend oh
tall
I don't know
all right use your what is your
persuasion plus expression
uh two how about manipulation you can
use that too
oh manipulation
what that manipulation is going to be
three okay
all right you try to reach out to what
to tell with your voice
um and because of that
um Kitty
cute
um because of that you feel as though
you really can sense that wasata is
still in there fighting and fighting to
to break free from the control of the
creature of this this dastardly worm
um because of that uh for wasitos or
wormtoto's next roll
um watato will get a plus one to the
dice pool
Break Free oh for Breaking Free okay
yeah yeah
it's a good damage okay it's a good
thing okay now wormsoto is next let us
roll to see if you can break free for a
moment and make this moment your own
instead of the worms for the 2D 10
greater than nine you succeed all right
because that's all you really needed for
this turn you may act of your own free
will watoto
oh
um
is there like a move set that the
the worm has that I could try to use
um yes the worm
has many different ways of affecting
people uh oftentimes using mental mental
tricks uh this this one this creature
specifically
um kind of specializes in in
manipulating with mental Darkness
um additionally some basic attacks like
grappling with um one of the three heads
sprouting from the body well
um and also summoning other creatures uh
to attack
oh no
those are the main things that this
creature will do
I don't know oh um
watoto always has a mushroom in it in
you know the pocket right yes
eat the mushroom
yes is this is this just a random
mushroom you pick from your pocket
it's a mushroom that has properties uh
to affect the mental psyche oh I see
it's a mentor fan ah it's one of those
okay gotcha all right so you eat the
mushroom
um
and uh the the worm does not
particularly like this what have you
done
what the toes strong mental
why did you eat that
hmm
water dolls
not weak to mushroom but worm is weak to
mushroom
that's right Wausau has that immunity to
mushrooms that is true
[Music]
thanks to you eating this mushroom for
the next two turns the worm will not be
able to do mental attacks against the
team
oh nice yes the worm is struggling but
because of this um instead is it's kind
of like when you enrage an enemy um and
they only want to attack instead of
doing status
oh no
so the worm will focus on attack but at
least you know your friends won't turn
against each other or you know harm
themselves Etc
so oh no all right next up Tiara what do
you choose to do
that is the difficult
decision
um
I guess I'll shoot again okay
maybe we can aim for like the legs or
something so it can slow down its
movements
alrighty I'll aim for the leg okay it's
an 8d10
uh yeah one question will power was like
what was that adding adding dices onto
plus three
one willpower is plus three correct oh
yes let me add one willpower to my
oh
eight nine ten eleven
um
that's a lot of room all right you want
a critical ah two successes so you do
about the same amount of damage as last
time uh you shoot two quick shots um at
the legs of the Beast and you managed to
take down one of the legs
um but the worm is still able to advance
um until you take out the other one
mm-hmm
when I shoot in text
hint hint uh someone take the revolver
out of my pocket
hell dear
all right Scout you're next
is that the plan we're taking out its
legs wait is the worm like behind watoto
like the worm is coming out of watoto's
body
oh okay and it's kind of wearing watoto
like a skin but also coming out of the
body as well a very horrific creature
at least
was that
The Whisper was I told to us or was that
I told you I told you you told me take
the weapon out okay
and I'm asking are we taking out the
legs I'll give it a shot I don't really
have any more weapons in her
unless I just take a step backwards so
okay so if you're going to shoot
um it's going to be firearms
plus
um let's see what we did Firearms plus
dexterity
oh wow I mean wait I add willpower it is
like me how many did you do you're not
you're not never gonna use it again
after all true I used one for free it
adds three dice
I'll add two willpower oh you can only
extend one per turn though okay one will
power all right that would be pretty
crazy though all right that would be
pretty crazy okay
with one success uh you managed to do
the job
you take out the leg
um
give you back the revolver here you go
good job team next up Yule what do you
choose to do
um
yeah
still talk to talk to you but with with
um with a willpower put all my willpower
into it all right we're using willpower
now
um so what is it is your persuasion plus
expression plus three what would that be
uh
it could be manipulation too right true
okay so three plus three six all right
uh no successes your voice
your screams cannot breathe your screams
cannot free water though
let you down
all right sadly for this turn watoto
cannot Escape
um Norm however the worm is um stuck in
place so can't really do anything at
this point
um besides try and and heal itself which
is something that it can do as an
eternal being so I'll have it roll to
heal itself nah
all right
pretty this is the lower roll one of the
lower roles of the the worm Toto
creature at this point so
all right
now what do you choose to do tiara
so are both legs taken out now
um one of them is back up
no
just
I shoot this leg too okay
all right gotta stop it and give it time
to re recover all right so this
particular rule is eight to ten correct
yeah
I think I don't need willpower for this
one all right let's see all right one
success uh you shoot it down just enough
nice all right
I have foraging survival skill
foraging and we're in a forest I'm gonna
look for mushrooms
all right sounds good foraging all right
um so let's see you're gonna roll your
survival and wits because it's in the
moment plus one
six plus one so seven
you can do math
yeah all right with one success uh you
look around and all of the mushrooms
here are extremely alien and not
familiar
um but you do manage to find one purple
one that looks kind of neat looks a
little similar to the one that watzuto
had so you find one mushroom one purple
mushroom
amazing okay
next up Yule what do you choose to do
uh can I borrow the revolver
okay I don't have it anymore
yeah okay
all right
what's the thing
firearm it's firearms and dexterity
and I'll add my willpower okay
so what's that so that's uh uh one plus
three plus e
seven seven
yeah all right nice pretty good
my bad where are you aiming oh I'm
aiming for the notawa Toto but like the
monster part going in the back okay
gotcha all right you managed to get a
really solid hit on the Beast um and you
don't necessarily aim for watato however
because they are intrinsically connected
you see is heard by this
and sort of flinches in pain
um and lets out a scream
a lot I'm sorry this is bad all right
wormsoto will now roll uh to regain
control
all right it's still a 1D
10.
rule I believe in what they're doing
to get past the worm this time and you
can feel it slowly crushing your your
mind oh [\h__\h]
the promise that you made to the worm is
just too it's bound for eternity
you feel like you can't beat it
you feel defeated
don't lose hope
[Music]
come back
Tiara what do you choose to do
um
wait so did the worm not do anything
oh
all right the worm chooses to heal
itself
all right next up Tiara what do you
choose to do
um
[Music]
do we do we see
lots of those hands you see his hands
yeah
um they're all distorted and mangled
they're all all you're saying is uh more
than one and more than two but both of
both of the hands are distorted and
mangled hmm
[Laughter]
are the legs restored again
uh no they're still they're still taken
down one is back up though he still
can't quite move very far
um
I will once again give give us some time
by shooting the leg again let's go
all right I remember I remember this
Rule now 8010 yeah yeah
okay with two tens of successes nice
yeah
oh my god oh hmm
Jesus all right wow that's a really
that's a critical success yeah let's go
all right you do a ton of damage to the
Beast yeah baby in so much pain
so cool for sure and at this point you
have completely blasted off uh one of
the legs of the creatures will not be
coming back
congratulations oh my goodness however
it's also you know watoto's legs so that
kind of sucks again
um but you know I'll roll you in the
wheelchair once oh God
What's it gonna take for me to
I have a mushroom what I do with it now
can I ask for my my party's help
sure
what do I do with this mushroom oh uh
you guys can converse in his mouth
is the mouth open it looks like it it
looks open on the beasts and then
there's lots of those mouths
is it open
screaming right from pain
so it should be open yeah it's an open
mouth
thank you
I feel like you can throw the mushroom
yeah what
what do I have to roll to throw this
mushroom it's purple if you want to
throw it really really good really solid
pretending like you're playing cornhole
because you you did that out back in the
countryside
um dexterity plus uh wits and then I'll
give you a plus one for your country
background
will my odds be increased if I craft
something I don't want to I don't want
to make a slingshot but I just I mean I
have a plus plus and weapon creation I
don't know that will take up a turn yeah
that's what else I was thinking uh oh
okay I'll do uh what's what was it which
dexterity plus one pumpkin power yes
so that's five all right to throw this
mushroom would you like to expendable
yes please okay one willpower all right
with two successes you do manage to make
the shot uh straight into watoto's mouth
the watseto does kind of have to chew
the mushroom a bit and initially
um
the the problem is the worm is really
really trying to get watoto to spit out
the mushroom
um so we'll see during the the next turn
if Watson
all right
next up yule
what do you choose to do
uh uh talk
I'll talk I'll talk this time all right
chew on that mushroom eat it
okay
all right go ahead and roll your
persuasion plus manipulation what is
that number
uh three okay and I'll use my willpower
too just in case gotcha
okay here we go
oh
wow all right
all right with three successes watato
here's your plea and because of this
success uh watato's composure check or
not really composure check um but the
check to have watato take the turn for
watatos self
um gets plus two dice so we're rolling a
three D ten but it has to be greater
than normal here we go you can do it
damn it
um he kind of spits out the mushroom
however however because initially you
did make you did make it into the mouth
uh the effects of the mushroom do still
kind of
they do still kind of take place uh
thankfully because it is a strong
mushroom this isn't just your regular
mushroom this is an Intergalactic
mushroom from a new dimension something
that's purple something that nuts purple
something that not even watch with those
taste buds know or recognize or really
know how to do it it is
a mushroom so because of that
um you have successfully incapacitated
the Beast for the next two turns
look all together use the power of
friendship now
all right how do you choose to use the
power of friendship to just stop the
Beast uh
I want to hold hands with the others
oh and talk
fencing
okay get out of your powers
you guys should sing a song yeah we
should sing a friendship song
what's F is for friends what is you guys
[Applause]
that's so sweet good song
all right
I'm gonna go ahead and just get you guys
like a little bit inch you guys just a
bit closer so it makes a little more
sense
okay all right um
so how do you choose to approach this
would you like
um to combine everybody's
persuasion and manipulation
if you girls don't mind yeah let's do it
one big turn okay okie dokie my
persuasion of manipulation together is
three
all right
I only have a one to give are you sure
this is a good idea uh you may use real
power if you would like yeah
we all useful power
if you would like to
I'll use my willpower then instead I'll
be a six I'll add six
okay
I mean okay I'll use a willpower that
makes it too okay no but let's break
down this is for one yeah so it's four
okay that's four will become the same
for me with willpower for four all right
I'll roll the fours first
um the power of song and friendship okay
well that's too bad free will set us
free the power free will set us free the
power of variable satisfaction
that's one success for scout
what is uh you'll want to roll
uh uh it's a six
[Music]
all right
God damn it I really wanted this moment
to be super enemy what the [\h__\h] you can
still keep trying
you can keep trying uh you still have
another turn where yeah that's true what
what's worm Toto is in capacity yeah
okay same same one what's the most part
I don't have many left but okay hold on
yeah I am looking at all you guys as
willpower I'm crossing them off on the
sheets the house will believe still and
the power I believe in power of
friendship yes
you guys should tell watato the story
remember remind watato of the stories of
you guys together
remember our times together our
adventures and and remember wanna play
more right
remember all the hotels were until you
saw the batteries out of all the remotes
think of all the remotes and still have
batteries you gotta take although we
don't see how to flip yeah rocks
together in the colored Fields there's a
lot of them
rocks
come back to us
you guys all together combined got five
successes
with the power of friendship you feel
your spirits
go to watoto
and you feel the warmth in your heart
spreads to
watatoso remembers the many memories
um that you guys have shared together
and watato rolls I'll add all of your
successes to watitos composure role to
break free
and with two successes with two
successes uh watoto is
able to break free from the Beast
completely yes
they separated
we separate
uh the the worm is horrified by by you
guys as friendship cringe and backs away
and says
you'll never know
you'll never understand
still looks pretty disgusting though
still still missing legs
we'll make it grow back with
um some magic yeah
for 10 years I'll push you in the
wheelchair we'll push you together we'll
carry
mushroom I'm sure it can fix it
it's very sweet
however the the worm still has plans for
you guys
um
and is now ready to ready to battle
continue the fight you want to change
your voice
no the worm was the worm is ready
to continue our fight
get like a turn number thingy initiative
uh no because watoto is really messed up
from all the things that you did to
watoto uh watoto will be last
okay last year on the nose bleeding out
what sorry
it's painful maybe now that Ina you will
doesn't have to talk about out of the
worm anymore and she could do some first
dating but yeah
yeah that is true
worm Karen worm turn yeah so Lotso so
essentially right now you are at
um I'm gonna go ahead and put you at
four lethal damage
from The Things They your friends have
you know they've been beating you
sleeping
I was just trying to disciples I thought
you like one Toto
Sonata
all right Scout what do you choose to do
in this moment
uh
but I don't have any idea
when I borrow this revolver I'm holding
yeah
or the pickaxe what am I gonna do throw
it at it you can run up to it bite your
pants on fire
true
I don't know if I'm gonna get close to
it
um you could throw the pickaxe
that is true you would lose it but you
could go grab it again of course
could I
position myself could I run behind it
yeah sure
all right here I'm gonna play another
song yeah yes all right you'd like to
use your turn to go behind the Beast
or
I could light the broom on fire and toss
it or that would take a turn
it would
okay I'll do it I'll I'll light the
broom I've got matches I've got a broom
still and I have weapon creation okay
gotcha so if you want to create the
weapon uh you need to use crafting
weapons
why Scout first
the Friendship chant was your idea
Oh I thought we were already in like
another turn
oh wait is that oh we didn't use any of
the other girls turns for that no oh no
okay okay oh
all right alrighty
set them on fire
so go ahead and roll your crafting plus
Weaponry plus one
oh
does this count as a aggressive light
weapon or no
um it looks pretty light I'd say it's
pretty light yeah sure you can
because it's crafting for Weaponry four
but both I have weapon creation and
light aggressively you can only use one
of those
oh okay well four four eight plus one is
nine
okay like crafts oh yeah okay
um are you kidding me if you're unable
to craft the weapon you wish to create
oh I'm stupid
very sad
um sad day it looks like uh you you will
need to uh attempt again if if you want
you didn't crit fail though so
you got this all right you'll it's your
turn what do you choose to do
I will try to stop bleeding on watoto
okay make sure doesn't die all right do
a medicine and wits check please what
are those two combined
four I also have first I don't know if
first date does anything uh first first
aid will not apply for this okay so
following bgm too quiet no my so my
computer's really overloaded right now
so it's like not playing the bgm oh it's
like it's like loading infinitely so let
me imagine yeah
epic boss music playing until I can get
this to play again
bring your
New York GM to work day yeah sorry guys
I'm trying to have it load but uh it
really doesn't want to okay uh let me
let me pause this maybe okay
um okay Yule what do you choose to do
uh I think he already rolled oh I did
you're right one success okay
um let's see you go ahead and heal one
lethal damage from watoto who now only
has uh three lethal damage
one leg is gone forever
unless
no it's definitely
it's definitely gone okay now what to
tell what do you choose to do in this
moment
uh um
[Music]
uh I still have my weapon homemade
weapon Arsenal which I think just
consisted of like a sound gun right oh
correct you did have a sound gun that
was pretty sick
would you like to stun the Beast
uh yeah I'll use some of them
I use the air horn setting
air horn said it you set it to air horn
and go ahead and I'm gonna have you make
I'm gonna have you use it as a weapon so
weaponry and dexterity for this one just
because it's a unique kind of weapon
uh okay
um dexterity oh uh I don't I don't have
any Weaponry but I have dexterity two
okay
so that'll be one unless you use
willpower that is um okay I'll use a
willpower okay 4D 10.
with the sound gun okay oh nice the
sound guy nice wow thanks to the sound
gun uh you actually stunned the being uh
this horrific nightmare creature
um and you managed to take down some
health and also paralyze
[Music]
and so thankfully
um
so thankfully uh the next turn will be
skipped
nice all right now Tiara what do you do
you have to kill it oh
hmm
I
take another shot okay
let's go let's go this time I'm aiming
for head gotcha you take a shot for the
head with two successes uh you managed
to pull off a pretty clean headshot nice
nice job
the creature roars
unhappy with what you are doing
very displeased
not very pleased about getting beaten
the hell up okay let's see
desperately trying to pull off some PGM
okay
um next up Scout what do you choose to
do
I'm doing it again nine all right let
the broom go power it looks like uh I
think you only have one more left after
this I'm not using willpower oh I got a
plus from uh weapon creation and or
aggressive light weapons
you're just that good okay wow three
see if it doesn't work once you can try
it again you successfully Craft
um
you successfully craft a hold on a
second
floor yep
you just gotta roll
wait hold on a sec all right so now your
broom is on fire and it's it's a very
Mighty fire and it'll it's going to do a
lot of damage if
if and only if
a sec all right I found a way to get the
bgm back okay
all right if and only if you can manage
to make it hit
hmm all right
yeah I found it hold on
did I might not like in the perception
world there's like it's the forest floor
correct
correct I'm wearing like a ravine thing
is it rocks uh you yeah there are well
there's a lot of rocks and a lot of smog
all around you
no grass no grass
should be seen there are mushrooms
there it is all right this will work
okay
all righty
next up we've got yule
all right
what do you choose to do
uh
uh Iowa
um
use the revolver
okay
all right you use the rev the revolver
go ahead and roll your firearms and
dexterity
how many will Parts I have left two you
have two left okay I'll use willpower
too okay so what's that number
uh so that's that's one four seven all
right
for the 7010
two successes roles are not on the
screen oh sorry about that here we go
all right you managed to get three three
successes nice yay turns out you're
actually a great shot you will be all
right
we'll be all right yeah and you make
quick Works
nice of the monster who does not really
have much health left at all you guys
think that you're really approaching the
end here
yeah it'll take us just a little bit
more what's it so what do you choose to
do
what Toto wants to ask
the being a question okay oh
yes the being is furious that you you
have completely
disobeyed me Watertown you will pay for
this on an existential and Universal
level
has barely anything left to lose
the the creature almost seems a little
bit impressed by by your tenacity and uh
and you're you who has such a strong
spirit and you don't give up watoto it
is impressive but you still you really
don't get any kind of coherent response
uh from the worm at this uh who is still
curiously trying to you're very curious
about you guys as a whole
um and you sense a bit of hesitance now
from the worm in um in continuing on
this fight almost as though
he's considering not doing it anymore
but not quite at this point
yeah the worm is still going to attempt
to bring you back
to bring you back by using a mental
tricks
oh this is where you end worm
oh
with two successes uh you begin to feel
your mind being drawn back to the worm
what's your composure
oh uh
[Music]
a three okay
all right
try as the worm does to bring you back
uh you are able to match the worm's
strength in mental with your own
strength of heart let's go let's go
yeah Tiara what'd you choose to do
shoot all right plus one willpower okay
so eleven
oh boy I love it
with two successes you have almost
you've just barely managed there's just
a little sliver left
one eight one HP in a dream I hate it
when they stay alive but what with one
HP yeah I love it when I stay alive with
what I treat
all right Scout what do you choose to do
you gonna throw your broom
um what what will I have to roll if I do
that uh let's see it's gonna be a
dexterity and I'm still gonna have to
make it be Weaponry for you but I would
consider it a light weapon
I'm gonna throw this broom all right
position so what's your dexterity
Weaponry plus one
six plus one seven plus will power is
when you want to use okay
yes
even eight you throw the broom with all
of your strength as though as though
throwing a burning javelin
one success
that's all you need that was that was
all that you needed Scout
nice and um before you know it
uh the worm has been
essentially neutralized however you also
realize there you know is a bit of
realization here that this is not really
quite the extent of the entire worm this
was merely just a servant of the Worm
but because of this
uh you you hear that the the Beast after
letting out another Mighty Roar speaks
to you not just you watoto but the rest
of your team and says
you are much stronger than I thought
I cannot have you in this world
if if I were to keep you in this world
I may suffer extreme mental damage
cannot abide being the God of this
creation
so I will take my leave
nice
however
I have only one request and you must
abide
and as and as the the creature says this
it grows very large and you realize that
you know this being is actually pretty
much untalable
um but
says I will show Mercy to you and your
world if
you stay out of my business
forever
what is your business
get away from the supernatural world
I'll never return
[Music]
and then you don't return to our world
that's it that is not possible I will
always have my hand in your creation but
um doesn't seem like a good deal
this is fine a burping logical here
if you don't get involved with us but
then you do something to our family or
anything around us it'll affect us if it
affects my family by doing something
else with someone else affects my family
and then affects me then it's affecting
me you're starting to really hurt my
head please
I'm trying to be logical
[Music]
tell us how to get out of here
yeah I'm about two seconds from changing
my mind
okay okay okay we'll get out of here
we'll get out of here
for one more request sorry
you dare ask for another favorable no
yes because you were so impressed with
us please please heal what total flag
give him some one of your limbs please
you don't you can't regrow them right
yeah I had to pay the price
you can try
I'm just like
being descended
my daughter will be back
like a Terminator
[Music]
this is just called the cool worm oh
I don't know what no no what doctor will
come back to finish the world
the worm stops talking
your time is limited worm
uh where's the exit
the worm does not respond to you
it's one important thing how do we get
out of here
the lights
well there's still the light
well the worm doesn't seem keen on
helping you get out so you may have need
to figure that out
if you knew how to create some kind of
large flash
large flash how about all all phone
cameras at once
the power of friendship okay I thought
those burner phone is dead
ah
it can shine light on the tinfoil head
disco ball
you want to try and make a disco ball
with the dough
uh okay no crafts crafts and dexterity
uh okay uh two and oh wait four okay so
it's four all right
uh sadly you cannot make a disco ball
gotta get light
what items do you guys have
I mean we still have do we still have
the Vodka you do
uh and we have the matches yeah like a
giant circle on the ground with alcohol
and set it on fire yeah you could try to
do that
uh go ahead and roll um whoever wants to
set this up another crafts and dexterity
roll
I already rolled it is okay
I have four crafts and three dexterity
what's Crafter
crafter sense is that a merit or a
specialty
it's us it's like written beside the
skill oh okay then that's a specialty
plus one plus one okay so seven eight
okay
all right uh you get the job done it's
not fancy it doesn't look great and you
pray it'll work
you're not sure there's a good quality
vodka
yeah not the best right you set it on
fire
yeah all right
with a great whoosh you drop a match
and the light becomes very intense
um all of a sudden
it is enough of a flash to kind of to
kind of brighten
brighten up the mirror enough so that
it's not really obscured it's it's
actually
it looks like it's in Focus now
however it's still just an image so
you've solved the issue of getting light
on the mirror but Sierra you feel like
there's still one more step
how are you going to have this mirror
send you home
my my my pendant
you know you want to try and use your
pendant
I guess how would you use it
um
um how about I how about you roll a
little perception check okay perception
check all right maybe the mirror is
dirty and you got to spit on it and
shine it
why
I have shed a tear
[Music]
um
I'll perceive I only have Fredo okay
let's give it a try
with one success that's right oh I will
give you this one hint
I'm thinking well you're thinking by
looking at it something on the more
permanent side
you get a feeling this mirror has one
use
but
we we break it do you choose to break
the mirror
um is there a return button if it
doesn't work no there is not you have to
take a chance
all right smash smash all right so he
wouldn't let me do this if this makes us
stuck forever right no it might make you
find another way out okay all right so
all of you guys stand in a circle Sierra
grabs the mirror and throws it on the
ground in order to smash it and with a
shadow it smashes
and nothing happens
and then one second later okay another
great flash erupts and the mirror almost
stands up on its own as you notice as
you it's less noticing and it's more
like you perceive holy and completely
all of creation of your real world
flooding into this Dimension and you can
feel this Dimension shatter and cease to
be
wow as your reality once again
once again completely
fills your surrounding almost like a
painting almost like like paint filling
a canvas or a bucket
it's almost kind of magical and
beautiful in a sense
but
before you know it within the blink of
an eye
you have returned
backwards we're back
how do we know this is the real
Dimension the right Dimension pinch
I mean would you like to roll perception
to find out
uh I can roll I'll look around
this is seven almost like I'm having a
hard time here hold on a second
these animated BG's man
it's raining
in the rain
hold on all right this isn't gonna work
um sorry I can't hear anything you guys
say whenever I play like media for
whatever reason all right oh
um I'm just gonna say you guys
all right
um actually let's put you guys here
because this is quite beautiful
uh you guys are not sent back however to
where you want it to go
um you are sent into the icy cold
mountains uh beside mifton
oh why is this happening in the
background uh in the icy cold
um mountains where there actually seems
to be an aurora borealis above your
heads
wow very beautiful
um
and um just like that
you're back do you want to roll
perception
yeah okay
let me guess you'll you'd like to roll
perception wouldn't you you very
perceptive players you're very
perceptive you
'll yeah no successes you just know it's
cold
yeah it's cold you know but I still work
very well you keep sneezing
slipping away
yeah
[Music]
you still you have three lethal so it's
not quite bad but you are bleeding what
tattoo needs warmth
oh
everyone gather around
thank you for fighting to get out of the
worm yeah you saved Waters you are the
heroes we all saved each other
[Music]
my cell phone is ringing
no we have reception here there's
reception in these mountains whose floor
is that
it's yul's phone oh I'll pick up the
phone hello
you hear a voice on the other end
hey you all hey did you guys ever finish
your mission
your number
uh how'd you get this number
oh oh oh I don't I don't know I just I I
just had it in my contacts somehow hey
we're cool and everything right I did
save you and like bring you pizza and
stuff yeah yeah you did you did yeah we
probably exchanged it then I'm I'm not
like I'm not weird or anything it's just
no of course of course not um we're uh
we're kind of stuck in the mountains I
think we finished our mission but um we
might need a little bit of a pickup you
know we need to block Vic because isn't
like a vampire so we're not allowed to
get involved in like Supernatural that
is true that is true
uh actually on the second thought wow
yeah yeah we're good
I can come
turn off the phone
um that is that is true you guys are not
allowed
um to have any kind of Supernatural
contact from here on out lest the worm
uh come back and destroy your lives
um ah however you do notice now you'll
you guys have service here
oh
it's called an Uber
needs to go to the hospital oh yeah
Hospital first we got a hospital to do
ambulances are expensive
you can split an Uber right but in the
end we'll have to go anyway right I mean
we're not necessarily in America where
the ambulances are [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
expensive maybe we're in Europe
actually you know this area
um you guys especially Yule uh because
your college did like a trip up to this
area for skiing it's really just a nice
Mountain next to mifton it's not far
away oh okay
um we can probably carry auto down the
mountains it's not too far to get to
town and I'm sure we can find some sort
of ride there what hotel sled
sled okay so if all of you guys want to
take watoto down the mountain all it's
gonna do um we're just gonna require
um a strength check from everybody
what's your strength
two okay
uh free yeah
okay
all right nice okay
hold on oops
okay and then
see how effective the carry is
okay Scout carry yeah very nice okay so
nice uh you guys do manage um to just
barely um
Carrie watoto
um you know he's not feeling what though
is not feeling very good
um but that's okay because you guys are
warm and you guys are doing your best to
carry your friend also watoto is very
light and small so thankfully it's not
much of an issue
um and you do remember you actually do
see a trail and you're able to follow it
just a little ways down
um and it becomes morning time
um morning time in this beautiful
mountain region it's very lovely
um here in the mountains and um and you
guys find
um a small it's not really a hospital
it's like a nice Clinic meant for skiers
that get into skiing accidents
um and there you are able to get watoto
the help that watoto needs and you guys
stay the night there at the clinic
nice yes so watoto have any uh extra
Dimensions based mushroom side effects
um no thankfully not not right now it
would seem
okay for now but who knows will grow
second brain
yeah second brain foreign
and we have some nice Alpine hot uh poof
what what
hot food no no you know an Alpine huts
on the mountains we have some really
yummy food oh Alpine Alpine oh yes
Alpine oh I see I see
oh yeah just like camping
we have one finishing meal yeah yeah you
guys do spend the night um in the clinic
together and it is very cozy
um and you know they it's not really
it's summertime so like skiing isn't
like really big like there was some snow
on the mountains but skiing isn't like
huge so they haven't had a lot of you
know skiing accidents so they're fairly
open and they allow you guys to stay the
night and you guys spend time by the
fire uh talking about
um the many Journeys that you guys had
together
um and recounting your memories
um of the time spent
and um lots of tell with some crutches
you're back on your way and the
following day
um you guys find yourselves heading back
from the mountain without a car
um but you guys do find your way to a
Crossroads
um by the mountains it's very beautiful
full of flowers and grass and um from
here on out you guys realize
no one's really telling you where to go
or what to do and all of you are kind of
able to choose your own Direction and
path from here
well I'll stay
I like the mountains ooh like snow
mountains because snow owl will stay out
so you decide to stay in like your homes
and your home in the mountain for a bit
yes for now I know and foreign
ers
I will I will write you letters and I
will write you DMS and I will do
anything
don't look at me never
oh you lost your leg because of me
it's okay I forgive you oh I'll pay for
a really high-tech wheelchair for you
okay I'll hold you to it
so what do you choose to do here at this
Crossroads next to the mountain
watoto has a plan
we'll find that Toto mom Toto
and watoto will start herb business and
what Toto will get a bionic Lake nice
okay no need for my wheelchair then
Noah
sweet
what do you choose to do you will hear
at this Crossroads
oh I guess I gotta go back to school and
finish my degree
or Masters I forgot what I was doing
honestly how are you gonna explain
oops he's not around I'm gonna have to
find
but
you know yeah you might want to get away
from that case you will
be fine that is a missing person's case
right there
it'll work out
yeah yeah and um how about how about you
Scout what do you choose to do
Scott leans down in the field and picks
one single blade of grass and puts it
into the corner of her mouth she reaches
down grabs her God pickaxe she made on
her journey slings it over her right
shoulder turns to look at the other
girls and says
it's been great and I've learned a lot
and I appreciate it but
I gotta go find my sister and make her
life for her and I I'll see you around
[Music]
GG
goodbye thank you
stay in touch everyone oh I'm so sad now
it's just good music though that's
pretty it's pretty emo emotional
um but as you guys um you guys kind of
give each other one final look
um as you turn away from each other and
all head in different directions
down the crossroads each of you taking a
different path knowing that someday
someday you guys will meet again
certainly someday and you'll keep
writing to each other and even though
life may change and even though you may
meet other people along the way
and even though those memories may get
further away
the four of you were friends
nothing will ever change that
that
[Music]
that is the end of myth Breakers
thanks
thank you
[Music]
dramatic end yeah yeah thank you so much
for our friendship yeah I'm surprised
what Toto got to live I was prepared I
thought it was prepared to die
just to let him know I was prepared to
to kill you for the gratitude
oh no
yeah I think everybody was kind of yeah
definitely definitely ready to do
definitely ready for that but um you
didn't want to you know no one no one
wants to get rid of well of course not
of course not
to live a happy life with an herb shop
with watato Clan uh
um yeah so we wish all of the characters
um good Journeys let's hope that you
will graduates College in The Tiara the
mountains with
um and that Scout is able to find her
sister and make a life with her far away
from their parents who really suck
um yes yeah those guys are the worst and
um the Futures are open for everyone
however they are not allowed to interact
with Supernaturals ever again so a lot
of the people that they encountered in
the past they are really gone for good
and less unless all of the ghosts that
are still chasing Tiara may come and try
to find her in the mountains and all she
can do is run in order to not incur the
Wrath of the Worm but but it's probably
fine right guys
it always does
so with that being said thank you so
much to you guys the players as well for
making myth Breakers uh what it was just
a really fun and exciting place for us
to like I don't know just fool around
and like play some characters and like
RP and stuff yeah
thank you
for accepting my crazy idea of let's do
a ttrpg it has been a blast and um and I
hope you guys get some good rest after
this and um you too
take a nap before the next stream which
is uh there's a whole live fighting game
out
I'm excited yeah all right well thank
you so much to the viewers as well for
sticking with us for so long for
believing in us and um
it's been quite the ride but everybody
you take care of yourselves and um we'll
catch you we'll catch you guys later
thank you so much thank you
take care and never forget the friends
we made along the way they were our
problems
you gotta you gotta use power friendship
uh with that being said I'm your Maury
I hope you remember me that would be
cool
um and yeah
[Applause]
thank you goodbye everyone
[Music]
snap those pictures
bye everybody
see you next time
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign