​​​ ​Kuh-luck!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahhhhhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why? Why is this happening?!​ ​​
​​​ ​It all started an hour ago.​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Camping?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. Let's spend time out​ ​​
​​ ​in nature for once!​ ​​
​​​ ​And look for a new HOLOTORI​ ​​
​​ ​member while we're at it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Camping and bird-watching?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​But we don't know any​ ​​
​​ ​good places for camping.​ ​​
​​​ ​No problem!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've done my research!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, research!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, where are we going?​ ​​
​​​ ​Here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, where?!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right! Let's get going!​ ​​
​​​ ​N-Now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take the metal bird!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, a plane?​ ​​
​​​ ​This just smells like trouble!​ ​​
​​​ ​I purchased this helicopter yesterday.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're not flying in this!​ ​​
​​​ ​No! No way!​ ​​
​​​ ​No engine? How eco-friendly!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, eco-friendly!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​And so, Kiara's helicopter​ ​​
​​ ​crashed on some island.​ ​​
​​​ ​Gwak-a-groodle-groo!​ ​​
​​​ ​We could've just​ ​​
​​ ​taken a normal flight!​ ​​
​​​ ​Waaah!​ ​​
​​​ ​The ocean's beautiful!​ ​​
​​​ ​Goes perfectly with summer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Quit chilling out!​ ​​
​​​ ​By the way, where's Kiara?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where'd she go?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara?​ ​​
​​​ ​Here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​It seems she flamed out​ ​​
​​ ​right as we crashed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why do you sound so calm?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kikkeriki!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's our phoenix!​ ​​
​​​ ​Glad you're back!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now help us out!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Even a fellow bird is​ ​​
​​ ​not allowed to harm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​She'd just revived, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​We could communicate in birdspeak!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! Nice idea!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cluck cluck!​ ​​
​​​ ​(You there, chicken!)​ ​​
​​​ ​C-Clucky cluck!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Join us!)​ ​​
​​​ ​C-Cluck! C-Cluck cluck!​ ​​
​​​ ​(A-And be an idol!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Talk about sudden!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cluck... Cluck cluck?​ ​​
​​​ ​(Will I be able to fly as an idol?)​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cluck!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Of course!)​ ​​
​​​ ​C-Cluck c-cluck!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Nothing is impossible for idols!)​ ​​
​​​ ​C... C-Cluck Clucky!​ ​​
​​​ ​(We'll back you up all the way!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Cluuuck!​ ​​
​​​ ​(I'll become an idol!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? It joined us?​ ​​
​​​ ​Can it?​ ​​
​​​ ​And that's how hololive​ ​​
​​ ​gained a new member.​ ​​
​​​ ​HOLOTORI's debut original song!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't forget to check the MV too!​ ​​