foreign
[Music]
thank you
this is
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
so I'm late hello
yeah welcome everybody and we are
currently on the Japan server because I
was spawned there from the last time I
was there I spawned in the in the uh New
Year's fireworks area which means the
last time I logged in here properly was
for New Year's which is almost a year
ago
a little bit and then I I had my Elijah
so I was trying to fly towards the the
you know the gate to go back to ianza
but I couldn't find it and um and
finally was trying to help me find it
through watching my screen but then uh
my eyelidra um broke right before the
ball and crashed I crashed yeah bamboo
Thicket and I just died right there was
a too high fall I guess and yeah now now
fauna picked it up right
yes I got all your stuff yay except for
a melon slice I can't carry it no
problem but um I still have to say
goodbye to the melon slice I still have
the problem though that I still can't
find use because I don't know where the
hell I am and I need food oh my god
there must be food here right
um
do you know your coordinates I'm at uh
the like a festival place right now wait
isn't this the fireworks place it's a 85
and it's where
huh
sorry what was the what are the
coordinates uh 85 and 85 x uh and uh Z
is 189 so almost positive
positive plus the positive okay
oh there is food oh so food I tick this
is all abandoned anyway interesting
hello
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no the adventure is
starting off strong we've had our first
step and we haven't even gone
well there will be no more devs after
that
sure okay I'm at the festival ground
where are you yo oh
hello
hi let's go here let me give you oh yeah
I even had a totem with me your stuff oh
I had a toilet with me but I didn't have
it in my hand I'm glad I didn't waste it
oh what do you mean waste
because I wouldn't want to waste it for
a stupid death on the Japan server by
breaking my Electro
because I wouldn't have died it was like
there's like we can have infinite
oh did you make a farm or something
it's at your house you'll have to check
oh really are you gifting people online
nobody logs in I had the same problem
like last year still I asked you also
people were already stopping to play
really
yeah thank you thank you thank you I had
all the stuff with me wow wow did I
really have all this stuff with me I
don't know I'm did I have to oh well
thank you for the diamonds I surely had
those with me
I'm good at gambling are you lucky
no but also I've never seen hot wings uh
my my lights were broken before oh yeah
well I have a farm that you can use to
fix it oh can show you can you show me
the world oh that actually I did that
unenchanted dishevel was mine if I could
have that one back the unenchanted shop
yeah I landed we made my shovel and I
think you still got some fireworks from
me oh yes
I'm also low on fireworks but we won't
be able to fly back now I have fireworks
this is series two I think one thing
your lovely members
all right so oh yeah what we're gonna do
today is prepare for the litter we're
gonna shoot some skeletons right to get
some heads
yeah but not the ones on my thumbnail
apparently I thought that you have to
get three normal skeleton heads and then
put some coal on them and then they
become black with their heads no black
or skeleton heads that would be clever
it's just because I was Googling
um like skeleton heads on Google for a
PNG and then I saw one which was like a
recipe like they were making it uh like
someone's custom yeah maybe that was I
guess that was fake I guess you don't do
that because of that I thought you put
one skeleton and you need four coal and
then it turns it black
it's it's hard to get a skeleton skull
though isn't it apparently I've heard
you don't you have to like kill it with
a Charged Creeper explosion or something
what
regular skeleton
a wreck the regular
yeah I think it's actually easier to get
the Wither skulls oh really
the regular River skulls we can just
shoot or or punch or whatever right yeah
do you have a a good sword
[Music]
really you just need looting three
blue thing free oh I have to check in my
chest at home
maybe I have okay if you don't have it
though I can I can get you set up
for free right
of course of course
oh there's an Enderman stuck there how
did they do that
oh
enclosed in glass
it's like a zoo
yeah have you seen oh we were talking
earlier about the ID server Kiara hasn't
been yet I have nothing yeah yo I guess
I was kind of waiting for an opportunity
for a tour
and that back then when people were
doing that mostly I guess we just didn't
happen you know
so I didn't go yet but I I know it's
very very very very very stunning I'm
sure anyone would love to give you a
tour Coco has a zoo in the ID server
that's probably much better than the zoo
that we have on the end well I think I
might have been taking us the wrong
direction what is this
wait is it this way
why is there so many chests
what is that this stuff is that
bam all the treasure on here
I left all my fish at home
you mean in the real game right in
Minecraft
in the real life that is Minecraft okay
I have some fish here but I'm not gonna
give it to them
sometimes Minecraft
they're so stuck here all right I'll
give some wait I shouldn't should I
these ones are already pets so these are
someone's someone's bed with my mind
being hungry tormenting like this I
might be hungry
where are you going
I fell are you looking at the
coordinates
um
yes
I think it's this way
okay
it's your dream to make the en server
look like this
thank you for it to at least like be a
smaller version of this in the beginning
and then you know one by one then this
girls didn't play so much anymore then
cancel joined with a new console yeah
also also didn't play for so long I feel
like and then rust came along everyone
was playing runs I found out were you
playing running a little bit though on
the Ian server
some members crony and Bae mume and me
have been playing Minecraft
hmm
when when when did you uh we played last
week
oh gosh I'm streaming
yeah
what
completely missed that
people grow up together what the hell
yes if you ever want to play just let me
know I can always make time for
Minecraft we could play earlier too at
least I can wait hold on I forgot to
write my starting twitch
okay I'll protect you in case there's
any monsters
exciting we have begun already a long
time ago why are you not here yet
question mark
uh you already missed the best part no
no no
okay and then
um
[Music]
for asking me
for the Stream
if you want what are you what were you
eating
how are you eating
the reason why I didn't want to tell you
is because I wanted to say it out loud
here I was eating
basically a chicken salad
oh what is the chicken salad to you
um it's in this case it was a in US
Austria we say back handles a lot
which is
um potato salad
um
with of basically like a baked fried
chicken
uh fillet kind of thing oh
um it's very special and then they also
make it with uh they add like sunflower
oh sunflower pumpkin pumpkin
seed pumpkin seed oil pumpkin seed oil
what am I saying yeah
and uh I just wanted to say that because
I've heard people call us
um chicken salad before Oh
you were actually eating
eating it eating the chicken salad yeah
yeah oh I see I see I see I see find the
distance
oh yes yes and I saw when I died this is
the bamboo you died in I think this one
over there that's so that's so much so
close to the portal so you need to close
them
ah I was curious because then
in America chicken salad is something
weird oh I guess like like wrecked
chicken made into a salad
it's like do you know
tuna salad like tuna salad sandwich I
was like where did you go yeah yeah yeah
oh it's been a while
yeah it's like that but it's like
chicken with mayo
[Music]
mushed up into a paste and then put on
bread ew ew that's weird like a sandwich
definitely very different from what I
was eating yeah
I mean there's also like a chicken salad
like a salad with chicken on it but like
I feel like when people say chicken
salad a lot of times they're referring
to like a chicken salad sandwich
well we need to try the Austrian one
someday
with the soy chicken
you can I guess you can have the chicken
salad without the chicken
it's so sad
oh
anyway we are on the Eaton yes
[Music]
so if you want to do you have um
I was gonna check out the on my my home
and see what swords I have unless you
haven't already read it and I just take
it from you
um I don't okay okay would you have
something you could borrow but it's
probably better if you have one you can
keep right
okay so
okay so do you why is this what what
what what the f what what what where you
go
listen minister
hold on wait what's happening
I had the same problem like this for
like a year I feel like what is this
what is this
oh my God I stopped I think
oh okay uh you'll want to go the other
way if you want to go to your house Chad
um
it was extended yes it's a whole Loop
there was construction and everything
look to like the other connects yeah
connects from Council to miss to PPP and
all the way back
[Music]
what happened oh there's so many cards
like last year oh last year
freaking carts
oh no are in there yeah I'll give you a
push
okay I broke one
I think this might have been movements
doing on the other side there were also
a bunch of cards that's why I stopped I
was able to stop thanks to them
apparently it was like six months ago it
feels like a year ago
just half a year ago
well well I was surprised by that
Improvement I don't know I don't I don't
think that Ian server needs to become
like the JP server I think the en server
can be its own thing with its own charms
yeah
we can always improve though
oops
okay
here I'm just gonna oh wait was there an
actual
one for the cards a box for the cards um
it's probably this okay there's all
kinds of other stuff in here too
yeah okay
um would you like to you know have some
tea at my place
yes all right follow me there might be
something waiting for you there ah you
you broke into my home like inside let's
say your cats let me in
wait is this where I left here oh oh do
you other house you mean probably the
other house ah my my new house that I
don't use
that's not new anymore either on the
bottom floor
oh [\h__\h] you wow thanks for everything
what is what's everything what did I do
for you
Kara you've done so much for me
like what has my stem pie and what
helped me out you've been hired me yes
we won't ever inspired you
one when I got to watch you I'll dance
for like 14 hours in one day that was
more inspired I think that was more like
torture but maybe more torture for me
oh
oh oh wow aha are you flick this is just
a flex you're just flexing on me oh
because my bribe for everyone to try to
get everyone to play
wow and the enchanted book is efficiency
uh-huh
damn
good thank you this is what I mean about
the totems though don't you shouldn't
you should use them wait so how easy can
you get them now uh quite easy but my
Farm's broken right now because I need
to fix it but okay
um when it's working it's very easy
oh you said you need we need what on the
on the on the uh looting three I don't
think I have that right now do you have
a diamond sword
yes I have diamond swords well we can
put to looting three on on your sword
okay wait wasn't there a maximum on
things you can put on there because um
there is are your swords did you enchant
them a lot no one of them has four
things but another one only has three
things so we might be able to put it on
there did you add the enchantments with
books or did it come with the
enchantments oh these are with books
okay those might be too expensive what
oh should I take one where nothing else
is on
um
let me see
maybe I have to oh you could this um
I was thinking about that one yeah that
should be good that one has good
enchantments on it too yeah I know yeah
the sword I got for working for a second
I'm really not doing much though oh
here's another token if it's too
sentimental though we can make you a new
sword no no there's a chance that we'll
die in the nether oh yeah I guess we
don't we also don't have to mend my hot
wings because we're not needing them in
the Never
oh yeah I can show you how to mend it
though I have to show you my farm
because it's very efficient
[Music]
anything else I need
um
we could bring fire resistance potions
but I don't know
huh do you know where the nether
fortress is
I think I've been there before but it's
been so long
yeah I also don't know we can find
anything
with the help of Chad we will definitely
find it
yeah I will just have to remember are
you bringing your totems
like one or so
um yeah probably okay the thing is if we
fall in lava it's like it might not do
that much well we could I thought you
were gonna say if we fall in love
if we fall in love we need the totems
save us from self-destruction
all of the fans have to be like
somewhere inside all right I'll bring
like two photos Now show me the show me
the hot wings place
the yes mending place we can take the
rail there too yeah okay
we could probably make fire resistance
potions at Ina's house
that way if we fall in lava we can like
drink one really fast and then
hopefully we'll be okay
you think it will be so dangerous
[Music]
when I was looking up the pictures you
know of the pinches I thought oh oh we
only have to fight skeletons okay all
good thank God we don't have to fight in
the Never
oh no but I guess we do have to fight in
the Never we do unfortunately
Kyla spends like all her time in the
nether she loves the nether maybe she
likes Dark Places
maybe spooky
no oh my goodness
is that just I guess that could be just
normal for her right
yes I think so she didn't possibly join
because she knew that we were here
streaming
it
like disappointed hey I'm not alone
um I think we can take some of these
potions you know said before that it's
okay yeah does one take maybe two fire
resistant potions okay I took two
I'll probably
um
be too slow to react to use them in time
but well if you have your totem you'll
have extra time oh and your armor might
help
okay
all right mending station
yes let's go on the rail
when are we going in the underground now
the you know the opposite direction
where I went yeah yeah we can go the
other direction
oh wait did I go the wrong way
[Music]
I might take some of this though damn me
and my mom built this I remember
maybe
one yeah didn't you make a really big
one
and it was too big and it lagged the
server and you had to make it smaller
what no no did I dream that
I don't think so
oh
like I heard that maybe it was someone
else's Farm different Farm
Chad do you know what she's talking
about
you like that happened
[Music]
that was around and like the very very
beginning I bought I I built I I have I
still have that Coop the chicken coop
and uh
I guess it lacked my game a bit when
being close to it
but that might also not be what you
meant
I think that was it oh
I'm confused I don't remember anything
well it was relayed to me through like
three layers of chat so no one ever that
happens it's like who knows what the
truth is
whoa
whoa we're going so deep
it's a roller coaster oh
did you have your cards oh no
I think this is it though
[Music]
okay whatever oh
I'm leaving this is how it starts yeah
it's disobeying me okay
that places so the beginning that I know
wait
BPP right uh no you want to go to PPP
okay we have to go further then oh
oh
I wish we could write one card did that
just come back
perfect
[Laughter]
it's like a little dog
[Music]
but this is not this is not well built
this if you have to have some stuff yeah
in between it's not
it needs repairs okay I got the other
one back there are plenty of projects to
work on in Minecraft as always
things to do oh yeah I replace the torch
oh maybe one more here
okay
um how do you go that direction I'll
just place it here and then push up push
up
we're at oh we could have just um
the lights are broken though oh yeah
right that's why we go there oh yeah
right
never mind we could not have
look look
the rail though get to show off all the
new stuff yeah
but in reality we're not taking the new
cap right now
where are you from
the new right is it all well maybe not
though this is old
yes
did you all dug together yes we did I
mean I feel like there was one member
who didn't dig as much because she was
carrying the camera and uh it was her
idea
I have not been digging this much
uh need food I need food
um
but then I I went uh straight because
you pushed me thank you what about you
though I'll be fine maybe just continue
a few steps further ahead
yeah I don't usually Ride The Cars This
Way
ah usually I go in the other direction
it's long this is a long tunnel yeah it
is we kind of need like PPP closer but
wait so you built uh
something like PPP or are we just going
to PPP
well it's near PPP I've been building my
forearms at PPP so it's like Farm
Central now
who are a farmer's daughter
picking up the farming job
picking up the pickaxe
to make sure every parent's dream come
true take over the farm so that it
doesn't get destroyed by history and
time yes yes yes some big corporations
knocking on the door yeah
trying to shut it down to build a Costco
but no we don't have Costco here
yeah do you have something similar no
something where you can buy a big box of
a chicken
big big bucks of like one thing several
things no like a huge Supermarket like
that no not really no no really no no no
I I don't maybe we don't and I just
don't know about it because like for for
Costco
you need a membership right to get
something
and maybe that's the same thing in
Austria and that's why I don't know
about it because I don't have a
membership it's secret top secret
um
yeah it's like a secret Club oh
I'm like the Mean Girls oh it's night
time
all right so we're not going up there or
maybe there's some food yeah not up
there is there two beds anywhere
ah
there's beds up at the top
two beds
oh I've never been inside the fishing
house
oh yeah maybe upstairs
go upstairs out here
oh there are nice we can sleep here not
quite our colors but no it's fun but
it's pretty cozy yes you smell good
fauna oh is Kyla here on the en server
oh [\h__\h] oh no she left she'll come back
don't go where's the fish where's the
fish no fish no one's going fishing
oh she's back
oh
okay we'll have to swim but I need I
think I need some food first otherwise a
little bit too slow oh okay I have some
oh
please
no what's your favorite sweets
oh I don't know I like every sweet
maybe cinnamon rolls or french toast I
can make
a saucepana I haven't made it in a while
though can you make it yourself
I do make my own French toast
[Music]
oh why are you are we just going
straight I think I see something very
tall yes this is where we're going okay
yeah you have your elytra
uh yes okay
what's your favorite sweet you just
kidding oh
no
um I have so many but uh oh man I have
so many like I should send you one of my
Austrian snack boxes
oh I probably can't eat a bunch of it
though
um are they do they have to be vegan the
snacks well yes I don't eat non-vee
things well then the milk chocolate
probably is a No-No right
[Music]
what about dark chocolate do you eat
dark chocolate
um if it doesn't have milk in it
sometimes even dark chocolate has milk
in it
yeah I agree it shouldn't but you'll
never know
okay yeah okay Doctor not really my
thing but
really I love dark chocolate I'm sure
there's some snacks that I could give to
you that are vegan especially like I
feel like over the past
five ten years
companies have been making more and more
like vegan snacks as well
so yeah I know you're not
German but I know that Germany is really
vegan friendly ah I've heard that yeah
yeah so it might be similar kind of
Germany I would love to
I recommend
Munich just because okay we have to jump
and then oh
you have to jump and then push this down
oh
um
so jump and click on the yeah
what the hell and then this is his sword
and this chest ew This belongs to the
farm so you can borrow this Farm hmm
that's like you don't like them the
fishies are weird as hell they're weird
it's the funny fish farm
[Music]
[Laughter]
just stand down here it's safer if you
stand here okay okay
um
and put on put on your armor yeah
mending on it
um the armor no just the just the hot
wings that I want to mend okay well
you'll want to get mending on your armor
eventually because the farm it does hurt
you a little bit
it does hurt you a bit but it's okay
we can get mending for your armor why do
I hit
um
what there's a dog
Olivia already died
could you like create such a torture
device
this is the Dark Side of nature
of an invasive species they're ruining
the natural ecosystem of Minecraft so it
must be done okay
standing
are they eating the Dolphins
probably they're evil these are evil
fish Kiara and you must kill them okay
where do I
know yeah and it hurts a little bit but
you'll be okay you can eat the fish
oh no that hurt my soul and my body you
can put on a chest plate if you want
you'll take less damage and you can hold
your elytra of course oh they're
probably going in The Hoppers aren't
they do I have to hold it in my right
hand I'll hold it in my right hand
Papa
no this is so sweet this is so scary oh
is it healed though
I think that took me way longer in PPP
do you see the power of this Farm
power of destroying nature yes ironic
because they're invasive species they're
the ones destroying nature
well good job fun on building this this
is pretty good thank you
oh I didn't even take damage although it
felt like I took damage
yeah it's best to use it with mending
armor otherwise you will start to
destroy your
um oh you can put the sword back in here
yes what here this one
they freak out
[Music]
don't worry about the fish don't worry
it shouldn't be it should it's FFF it
shouldn't be funny fish Falcon it should
be freaky fish function
I'm freaking funny is just a nicer word
for it
but you're right there are freaky fish
the freaky fish farm
all right
do you want to go to the Rain Farm to
see it it's not functional right now but
yeah yeah let's just get away from this
flap flap slimy flaps okay do you have
your electron uh yes
okay I think it's
I think it's this way
can you fly this way oh it's this way oh
go follow someone oh that's not it
is
you see it have you decided where to go
that's yes business is this what
I thought you build it somewhere else we
go to the top
oh no no no you can go to the bottom oh
oh so this Farm is not working right now
but
um I don't really recommend that people
use it because it's actually pretty
dangerous to operate so uh ideally I
will just run this farm and then other
people can is this where you get the
emeralds
yeah there's there's not too many in
here because I used a lot of them but
wow
wait did you bring any emeralds with you
uh oh yes I did 64 blocks okay that's
that's plenty
you can take more if you want no no no
no no no no no
this gets sent to the bottom
man I dropped a lot of good stuff
um yeah
oh
it's a health potion
oh and swiftness or speed
hold on
good job
thank you
okay now we can go to we need the
enchantment right yeah I have a trading
haul
which is
this why I always get lost I think it's
this way
oh yes it's this way
you made a trading Farm
I
did ask you also if you wanted to
make it in Phoenix 10. but where are you
I lost you
uh you're there
it's this way
this house
I lost you again I lost you again
where are you uh
where you just saw me a second before
um
buy the cake oh there you are yeah just
this way oh
so are you saying that Phoenix Sun is
obsolete
well I don't think it's obsolete
sounds like it to me fauna
did ask
if you wanted to work on it my mom's
crying right now for now you made my mom
cry
oh
let's see what this is it's not done yet
even so
it would be so unfortunate if a fire
would hit this house no
I still ain't removed all my signs and I
didn't put them back up yet but I made
fun I don't know how to get down there
um
I was just doing it weirdly okay so over
here I need to put the signs back up but
he has looting threes this is terrifying
fauna
everything will make is terrifying
scary look at them suffering nature look
at them asking for more space because
they're going insane
the only thing I can see is their heads
do they even have a body left fauna do
they even have a bunny she's the one
they deserve
for what what did they do to you they're
librarians
do you hate books so much you don't hate
books I hate them what did Librarians
ever do to you you know how you make a
book
have to chop down a tree wait maybe
there's vegan books
maybe maybe I guess maybe ebooks are
vegan books
yeah if maybe if you if you charge it
with solar power you are
you are the stuff you use for building
this is literally wood blocks of wood
the trees sacrifice themselves
who told you it's okay
they did
why don't they talk to me though phone I
guess because I'm not nature exactly I'm
convenient fauna
you you have your own you you know you
talk to your kfp employees they
literally say I don't hear your your
nature saying any word
oh this guy has looting threes
I need to chop up the emeralds right
oh yeah and you'll you probably I forgot
to get books so you might need to get a
book buy a bookcase to get books do they
have a book okay yeah you can buy the
bookshelf and then break it and it won't
give you books how do you break Emma
Roblox just chopping in your inventory
in your crafting table oh
oh like this is so touch nice okay
oh I stole it here oh no no problem not
like I really need that one exact block
okay hello sir
um don't worry I will
say hi later
um but for now
uh bookshelf.com
[Music]
yes yes the bookshelf you have the Play
Store no yeah you have to place that one
oh
there we go freaking the course of hmm
okay
I just needed one right do you need one
too
I don't need one okay oh he's about to
level up
good boy nice not that it brings him
anything in this says scary scary
sad world
[Laughter]
um and then do you do you want mending
for your armor
oh I think I still have some mendings
myself but oh yes I'll take them this
guy has mending
Mend My Heart
there's also a protection for here which
is also really good for armor
all right can I not get one more sir
oh he might only sell so many what for
the day okay
I'll put it on my chest plate and then I
have one more actually I can buy some
really if you I don't have any emeralds
though if I could borrow some emeralds
okay oh here oh
I'll give you these blocks oh and did
you run out of books actually I have one
more do you need okay no no no oh
here you go
hit the librarian
are you one of them or are you something
else
and I don't see any chickens down here
she that's that's because
there is this potato no no they're so
small they're like not on the same level
height level as the heads of these
people it would be like on the bottom
yeah on the ground
how about a trades for you know
um you and me kfp versus well what's
your whole thing called huh
name
time
I think I was I wasn't about it because
I was thinking maybe I should make a map
art maybe that's what we need oh yeah
but then you need also like a
construction logo
yeah maybe Kieran Coe
has a nice ring to it
also could I have more emeralds what do
you want did you want more mending uh
yeah yeah I guess so yeah yeah yeah
how many do you have how many mendings
oh I have one right now
okay
do you want any protection
uh you have protection here too or what
yeah part four is here
uh wait ah wait I can't I don't think I
can can put mending on them because
they're Unbreaking free right
uh you can oh can I okay some things you
can't combine I don't know what they are
um my diamond helmet has protection free
and I'm breaking free but my pants have
only Unbreaking free my diamond boots
have depth Strider free and Unbreaking
free and my uh oh my chestplate has also
protection for the Unbreaking frame so
not too bad right
[Music]
yeah better than mine actually I haven't
I haven't gotten fixed my armor yet okay
okay
so oh yeah okay okay so now we go to
enchanting top table somewhere
Yes actually it might have to be back at
the at the farm the funny fish farm
unless you have levels but levels levels
how many levels do you have of 24.
um
I don't know how many you'll need that
might be enough we can sleep here the
communal bed aren't even still in their
beds that they got nothing
no they have everything because of me
this Village was nothing they owe me
everything
that's quite some ego you have built up
there oh no
look at this I built this big house for
them
and that actually like looks really good
pleasing
thank you the sad thing is that
everything's happened downstairs in the
cellar in the basement
Anvil over here
all of the same space
here's an anvil you can put um
[Music]
real facade
okay oh
yeah I think I can do everything here
nice
we need a golden helmet right when we're
down there should I put mending on the
golden helmet no right oh no I don't
think that's necessary
okay
actually I didn't bring any gold
um
yeah
a pencil already pencil
I have efficiency five where should I
put that on why did you give me that
um that you can put that on anything I
think that was your gift
okay I am ah I still have that okay okay
um
[Music]
here's some more fireworks
father
wait do you have something like
um
for fireworks you need paper and
gunpowder right what's up do you get the
gunpowder from
your big farm over there nice
yeah yeah it also means gun powder noise
all right on the sword I was gonna put
what
a looting three okay
oh no I need some more levels for that
one
okay we can't go back to the farm okay
this one has voting for two expensive it
says
oh yeah the sword for the raid farm and
she's not there right now
and I'm the only one who uses it right
now
if I might take that one to the nether
because I'm
kind of I can I can go along to the
Finish if you want you can stay here
huh
you can stay there I'm gonna okay go
into the fancy fish farm
yes it gets a new adjective every time
somewhere
this one yes
do you have to enter from uh the the
weird stairs
no you can fly there oh
I found you okay but I landed in the
water do you have your totem equipped no
but I landed in the water safely
you know even with the totems I would
feel
I like the Subways I know you said it's
not a voice but I have this RPG mindset
they're infinite
[Music]
but all the all the good treasure were
both cherishable items I feel like I
can't use them
because then I don't have them anymore
um but you can get more
okay today today I will I mean today I'm
gonna do fighting skeletons I can't
really see us getting into such a
dangerous situation where um maybe maybe
I I think it's quite dangerous really oh
huh offering no help
do we need something do we I don't know
we were good
um I mean I only have one Elijah just
kidding
what if I lose my life actually no I
actually have a backup Elijah never mind
dad
because I I went Elijah hunting myself
when we first uh started
out but I didn't think I wanted 200 of
them because I wanted to leave some for
my colleagues
please
yes
I wonder if Kyle also plans to
take down the weather and I do like she
probably already has oh really
I mean I don't know if she actually has
but it wouldn't surprise me
what did I come here for upper levels
for levels
[Music]
foreign
is this healing is this healing
oh
[Music]
oh fire explosion she's offering
oh
this is healing
did you put mending on it are you
wearing it yeah
should be then I think I think yes I
think it's healing
[Music]
and my I guess as long as I'm wearing
this the level does go up but let's see
let's get the oh
whoa I got you know I was I was just
apparently killing one by one for a
while but suddenly I had like I don't
know 10 10 at once and that's where
suddenly I got 22 levels at once again
and Mom my armor is healed no I still
there now you see the power
I think I see it of FFF
uh uh yeah
[Music]
brain slow this goes
here
okay
now this sword is incredible don't need
anything anything else ever
I think I'm ready
okay I'm trying to get us some food
right now nice
and don't think we need food
I saw that um I saw a compilation
of you struggling with some never
portals because of Amish
yeah actually that it wasn't
or just because of army there okay the
server was actually broken uh hmm the
server plugins were not working properly
yeah something was iffy there yeah we
had to have the server updated
so it was updated
yeah I was really annoying and I made
them update the server just so my farm
would work I wonder if that affected
anything else too though because
um I don't know how how much that one
era
did but if it affected other things and
we never discovered it we would have
never discovered it without you you know
struggling with all those portals
wait so with the whole portal
recreating itself over and over again
like that was the bug
I've had that issue too but I don't know
if that was normal or not well it's
actually that can be normal
um
yeah it can be normal there is a problem
there was a bug with the the way the
portals link but I just I like I
researched a lot on how portals work
um they're not actually linked to one
another like if you build a portal it
doesn't necessarily link to a portal on
the other side it just sends you to the
closest portal of the corresponding
coordinates in the Overworld so that's
why you can have a situation where
you could have like three portals that
are linked which is very annoying yes
yes
that do be annoying it is very annoying
where are you
um I'm at the snowy Village
I have some food
now
my inventory is very bad potatoes
oh I got some fancy prismarine from
fighting those dudes oh yeah there's a
bunch if you ever want to build with
prismarine I think good I might want to
we're trying to bully her in Japan
oh oh oh you you probably don't want
that that's okay I just want to play
Minecraft anytime
I don't think she's really like
quit or anything Callie however you know
Kelly doesn't want to play Minecraft
anymore
sad there's some food in here oh
wow cookies stuck up some cookies
and bread and carrots one golden carrots
are
apparently the best food in Minecraft
but there's only 18
. yeah
more
you have them okay we have we have
infinite now that
18 is infinite
ah there's some outside here they must
freeze in the cold no no they're warm in
there is there a heater inside
yeah I need to check can you open it up
so I can check it you can you can show
me the proof right
okay
he's looking really worn down I do have
I made an iron form too it's not that
good though
[Music]
he is feeling the effects from your not
good iron form
[Music]
it looks terrible you shouldn't see what
happens in the iron farm
[Music]
it's not good let's hope no one tells
him so he doesn't start a rebellion in
the revolution
Kyle let's hope that no one poaches your
villagers telling them that there is a
better place where they can have their
own little houses and sleep inside them
and work with better working conditions
let's hope no one tells them I hope they
didn't hear what I just said oh they
sound very interested in what I just
said they're like huh huh what are you
very interested in that me
then when you want to when you want to
get any enchantment you have to run
around for 20 minutes clicking on
everyone to see who it belongs to I know
I know I know where they are you
normally and then oh yeah from for
someone who built it it's no problem
think of everyone else
[Music]
when there's something that I can get
from Phoenix and I'll just continue
going to rain extend because I built it
so
okay
[Music]
when I need looting for you so again
I'll come here because I don't think we
have that
you didn't steal any of my Villages
right
oh okay these are all born and raised
here I raised them from children for
Mommy for eign
[Music]
genderless really
well they all reproduce with each other
so well that's Minecraft logic
maybe even humans
what are they
they're illagers
now you're making stuff up for now I'm
not you can Google it they're called
illagers without the V
that's such a stretch fauna
it's real it's real
anyway Lois are we done
oh sure you're right Kyla did ask where
we are oh no
oh
sorry I didn't see your message we are
at the snowy Village
does she know which Noe Village you mean
I think so she was building with us
oh
she was gathered see all these shelter
boxes Muna donated all of these uh
neat
and Kyla gave us this glass oh
yeah that's a lot of glass
noise
you ever want to build here it's the
open collaboration
I want to make it like a cute Christmasy
wintery Village Christmas
yeah hello Ian Advent calendars
you may be some there in there too right
someday sometime possible I might be
also involved in the calendar
yeah
already wow wow no way wow so reliable
maybe sooner rather than later fauna
will be behind the door
oh Queen thank you partner for being so
reliable
well thank you for organizing it for
real Kiara you do so much no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no don't say
thank you oh it's such a good idea right
I was like wondering why don't we have
this like organized by the company why
why but then interestingly I saw that um
uh when like one day after I started
planning it which was like three days
ago or so
I saw that actually the Japanese uh Holo
Stars they have something like that
going on company organized yeah so I
realized oh I guess because probably if
I would have thought of this earlier it
probably would have been possible to
have it go through uh management and so
on it's not impossible
yeah maybe months in advance but this
way you know it also works I I bought I
bought a domain one
oh you're so you're so techy now yeah
I'm I'm I'm I can go to Silk Valley or
what's it called
yes
silicone yeah yeah yeah yeah I have my
own website yo I mean but honestly I I
did not obviously not code it but yo the
person uh who quoted it is a kfp who's
studying it however I'm just flexible
with my cave you know yeah
[Laughter]
it's crazy it's really cute it turned
out really cute thank you I'm excited
how's the second one gone up yet not yet
um it will go up in uh two and a half
hours I think
[Music]
so I mean we don't know totally don't
know who the next video is by but in two
and a half hours you guys should go to
Holo Ian
uh
and then open the second door and the
first one if you haven't yet yeah yeah
are we waiting for Kion on everyone yeah
it's cute that everyone can look forward
to a new video every day yay who knows
what they're going to get yeah who knows
indeed because I didn't uh I don't have
all the days
um filled up yet with participants but
just gonna have some repeaters hopefully
hopefully every day there will be
something oh she's here
snow
oh her natural habitat yeah
oh she's probably gonna bring like 500
potions right because that's her style
yeah yeah
it's not gonna be you two or five or ten
and Potions gonna be 50 or so
boxes one sec before tragedy
what does that mean take it drink the
potion one second baby
oh Kyle is so sweet thank you ah you
can't um oh yeah right you can't like
um
piled them right
so
thank you should we just bring the
shulker box into The Nether oh yeah
probably we can put some other stuff in
there too
oh yeah you have
actually well
the real way to do it is to like bring
um an ender chest and then put your
shulkers inside the inner chest
oh yeah that's what Kyla's telling us to
wait why do we need to why do we need
chocolate chests
so if you take an ender chest with you
and you put it down and you put your
stuff inside
then you won't lose your stuff yeah I
know that but aren't we just go in there
to get free skulls
yeah We're not gonna like need so much
uh space in our backpacks no
yeah but that means we keep our stuff if
we are silly die
um we could just not die
exactly actually I don't I don't have a
silk touch pickaxe right now that's
pickaxe oh you could bring should I mine
this one
yeah you can take this one okay and mine
is kind of full of nonsense you can um
put this choker box inside the Ender
Chest okay first and then mine it I
think
oh yeah oh god um
I love stuff in there too yeah mine's
also full oh I have gold boots in here
oh there you go what else should I throw
away
my iron nuggets I guess I don't need the
iron nuggets don't need the paper
uh
okay well
um I think I'm gonna go
uh to my home once more to like clean
inventory out and then we can go
okay okay
[Music]
I want to fly there oh do you know the
way I guess ah it's that life guys I
feel it a few times yeah
okay where'd you go um I'm behind you
okay
yeah it's just like this way
oh
wait how does she know she's listening
probably
um maybe one should look at chest
or two would be cool to have because
that one we have right now is filled
with fire resistance potions that's true
hmm
yeah yeah and I clean out my inner chest
and then no problem because we just
bring this how do I put
I want to put like
I need them pleating emote
with Kenya
uh wasn't it like this way oh that's how
we're the top of the tower isn't that
where me and Kelly jumped off
what's that present up there
fauna do you know of this present
the
present by the council area
um in the sky the red big gift with the
green bow
on the on the way to
um I think I'm getting lost
um
I do not know
s
[Music]
secret apparently it's a secret
I have a secret
who's made that
secret is that a Christmas present for
you maybe from someone else
yeah bye I'm lost
um
do you know the coordinates
uh it's near zero zero I think I think
that's near where council's area is you
probably know the way from there right
so yeah okay
uh
uh okay this way
really far how did that happen
I think if you just travel like um
Northwest oh I see something I see
something oh my God
let's buy hot tomorrow right I mean only
hatima could have built something like
that what on oh yeah kept going if
you're at hatchimal you should I think
from hajma you want to go like
a slightly South mostly West what on
Earth
is that her Hogwarts I think she's
building Hogwarts oh maybe it looked
like a castle a church or a school
yeah yeah
she's been working on it
she streams usually like right before I
go to sleep so sometimes I watch her
when I'm about to go to sleep
watch her build
do you know how to check which direction
you're going if you push F3
just if you look at facing is this like
a facing west in the second block I
should be there I'm here I found it okay
okay
so and then we go through the main level
portal or a specific one I think the
main one like close to Ina's house would
be
yeah I probably won't go in there yeah
I'm waiting for Kyla right now okay but
you wanted to get stuff at your house
right yeah I'm I'm there right now I'm
gonna clean out the chest and then
I'll wait by another portal for you
[Music]
this can go this
this can go this can go this can go
[Music]
um
told them come with me
oh there's a bucket from
oh was that the one that
has a Japanese brand probably from the
the Summer Fest
most likely
are you gonna fight them with your sword
or with your ball or so uh we need to
use the sword because it has looting
three ah yeah okay okay because
otherwise the drop rate will be really
low
okay okay
makes sense and do you think we'll get
it pretty quickly but I heard that it's
2.5
um
0.5 percentage of chance of getting it
should be way higher with looting three
I don't know what it is it's something
like 20 I think maybe we'll get it in 10
minutes but then at least we spent
um one hour through exactly even get
ready so
this is also preparing you got armor
better armor right you can use that for
the Wither yeah I got golden carrot
Source we want that for the Wither
mm-hmm
a friend of this
I'm so slow brain is so slow for now
what's so so brain brain yes brain snow
me too
slow brain
I always just throw everything into a
chest and then Chad gets mad at me
you need crony in kilinko
that would be a good combination of me
and crony have different skill sets we
have a history in Minecraft though we're
kind of we're kind of Minecraft enemies
oh
I like that that's spicy
it is spicy
I like The Arrow anyway
[Music]
I think here and Co is like we used to I
used to work for bunkeroni Co
but I we had a we didn't part ways they
only complete so now now I have my own
Kieran coal oh but no no hard feelings
right
only in Minecraft
so I don't need to bring my shovel right
oh yeah you don't probably don't need it
no X ever maybe the pickaxe that's it
yeah okay I don't want to lose anything
yeah you could bring like a a worse
pickaxe too you don't have to bring your
best pickaxe
all right ah I'll keep the flint and
steel
[Music]
um
so slow so slow faster faster Chihuahua
no worries I'm still still waiting for
more presents from Santa Santa Claus
oh it's oh crisp it's December it's a
it's something it is I can't believe it
November is already over yeah when does
for you really like what do you need to
feel like the Christmas season started
the first of December or something else
um I don't know unlike December 10th I
had the desire to put up Christmas
decorations but I didn't December 10th I
thought it was too early but I wish I
would have because now I'm kind of like
oh I don't want to put them up if I'm
going to take them down
so soon anyway
so
actually pretty late huh that you get in
the Christmas Moon
yeah I think usually it's when I'm like
when I go see my family
oh
thank you Carla you got it yes
okay and she flies away
I have cleaned out my chests
and
um yeah
okay
um I'll come to you then
okay me too at the portal Maybe
and I'll give you some sugar boxes
courtesy of Kyla whatever did you bring
huh how many did you bring
quite a few
it's always Overkill
I know
she's so cute
um
hold on I'm flying I cannot sleep while
flying
skill issue
you're right
Pro Minecraft player would have no
problem or a pro flyer
totally me even though I am
hot wings
and that's because of the hot wings in
there and it's just not optimize
standards anymore
okay well there you go hi
oh my god well
too
what did you keep some in your inventory
too yeah I kept some okay I'll put like
we really don't need that many but I'll
keep some they will be useful for
private use
yeah yeah that's what I was thinking for
you I don't know how many you have
well well now I have a lot more
[Music]
um
I don't know what to put in my Ender
Chest oh shoot I don't have silk touch
I would have this wait can this break it
I don't know if this could break it just
can't break it
oh don't we just need one end of chest
girl
uh yeah probably I guess so I have that
one already I placed one extra yeah and
I can't pick it up because
the right one
oh
there we go
thank you
[Music]
yes I think so
um
we probably won't fly right yeah and I'm
not breaking bringing anything to fly
okay
[Music]
all right you have your fire potion
you have your totem in one hand oh
um
why should a shield is a good idea yes
me chilled we have skeleton shoot
little wood
four times
[Music]
uh help me Chad what's the rest of the
lyrics
[Music]
I think that was about right
foreign
do we need milk
do we someone said oh for withering oh
for withering we'll be fine just
remember to eat yeah especially your
golden carrots do you have any wood oh
not right now how much you need
um one two three four five blocks okay
five planks oh planks okay I should have
some somewhere
and
me and Dad I'm not ready for my shield
oh you're making a shield
yes do you have a shield
um no only my own but I got planks
you said five five
five yes I think it's five
I'll give you I'll give you six
I got more than that but six
it is in case we weren't right and you
need actually six
how do you throw things in Q There you
go
thank you
with full Enchanted armor and gold
carrots you don't need milk yeah
seems so weird oh wait this is not how
you make a shield oh my way I do I not
know how to make a shield
oh I don't know how y'all
anticipated that
Shield we need iron too I think you need
iron yeah one one yeah yeah I had some
though chunk of iron
take more totem no no no no no no no no
where do I where did I put the rest of
my totem still
how many totems are you bringing phone
yeah uh three okay well let's go
okay what's a kid my inventory
just throw it all away
throw it away
en Seaver is very excellent weight and
trembling fear well I've read this
before haven't I
said who was that
okay are you ready I'm
cold
I don't know it's
it's all yeah I don't know how to get to
the Fortress
I think it was that way first of all
right chat Maybe
this seems like the right way I think I
took a screenshot at some point
um
let me see him
North and then East this is East
and then North
wait let me see a screenshot this way
and left I think
I feel like I took a
a screenshot of it before but finding
that now might take a while hmm no this
this way
you think so yeah I think it's this way
this way this one okay okay yeah yeah I
think I remember the last time I saw it
I was some
close to it and and I needed to be
rescued because a pig was on a one block
road a big peak you know
and I felt threatened by it wasn't it
like there I think
and then someone came to rescue me
because I think I had nothing really to
protect me and then one block Road you
know having that big pig push you over
and fall into the lava is just not gonna
be very bad
okay should be
should be somewhere
yeah here and then left
it would be very nice Road right there
there's a lot of stuff here is that the
left path
probably I think I have been here before
I think I got blaze rods here
that's so spooky
are you not saved me oh yeah I could
have been Ina because like
I was like hello can you help me you
know
[Music]
her knight in shining armor yeah
yeah good old times
see so much can happen in Minecraft
is this the watch
excitement is this the way
I don't remember this path to be honest
thank you
oh oh oh I kind of continues weirdly
here
you still behind me
yep okay I'm here
wasn't that far away hmm
they can be pretty far
oh
it's cool wow
oh oh there's enemy but I I have gold
I even even stepped aside oh
goodness it's the Fortress
wait where no when you look straight on
to the right
um I can't see because of my settings oh
I think I'm pretty sure that's the
Fortress I have to go down here I think
bye-bye so scary oh so scary oh so scary
oh it's so scary oh
we should have brought a boat
do we need to take the other scaffold I
think we need to take the other one I'm
scared
your potion if you're worried
um
how long does it hold on
for eight minutes oh we have a lot of
them so you might as well wait where are
you going um I'm coming back up
oh this is so scary already
glad I drank it
yep and then just gently at least you go
first so in case the scaffold land is in
the lava then you die first and you can
tell me before
potion I'm not dying in any lava I'm
glad that I I did the one job of leading
us to The Fortress yes yes one thing
that I did besides all the things that
you did
yeah I was planning to eventually doing
it myself like taking down the glitter
but uh and then I would have done my
research and all but you know fauna
you're so much into Minecraft so just
leaving it all to you now my dear little
kohai
oh of course yeah
someone has been here before
wait be careful there's like
a lava block there oh oh that's time
surviving yeah are they gonna like
immediately greet up attack us there
um
oh I got tea nice man just seems to save
so far yeah okay should I place push up
here blocks I totally forgot to bring
blocks we can destroy some of the
countries oh there's okay
where you can also take the thing about
the wither skeletons is there three
blocks tall so you cannot block them so
they cannot go down the hallway because
they're too tall
well tell me when you think there's a
good spot to put down the chest
oh do we need to put it down and the
chest well yeah
I feel like yes only the energy
coordinates uh I'll put it here
it is
happening so you remember these
coordinates for me
take a screenshot saplings
oh oh yeah I guess torches the Torches
block their spawn
just dark in here
okay well everything is
in place
I don't know where exactly this spawn
usually I just like run into them okay
and I don't want to then let's run
around
spooky oh my God I have a different PGM
for this I don't know if it will really
get this dramatic but I have dramatic
RPG danger music here there you go do
you hear this chat
I love it it's been a while last time I
used this I think was when I was um uh
taking over the what's it called the
forest mansion
oh you did that yeah I did it alone it
was fun alone whoa it it was very
dramatic like a forest Mansion did you
do it before
um I've done it yeah like before
hololine oh oh this is dangerous time to
do it again oh my God that is dangerous
scary
oh
keep your inner chest with you this
divorce right do we need to go up
hmm
don't baby
oh other stairs here oh are they
fire resistant so oh yeah okay
I guess
yeah I'll pick up I'll go pick up the
under chest
bring it why am I bringing it you don't
need to bring it you can just hold it
okay
oh I went upstairs
I'll see you hello
um I'm getting rid of torches because I
think maybe they only spawn in the dark
oh okay
I don't know if that's actually true
scary scary
a bowl I left it somewhere I could have
shot that thing
um it's okay if you're a fire resistance
though because their shots won't hurt
you okay
but they will hurt you if you like touch
them so
I'm not so brave
there's a magical suspicious door
and the weather skeletons
is there a specific point where they
spawn in the Fortress or just anywhere
biomes that are better than others
um
because I think it's just because other
mobs won't spawn there so
um do I get a curse when I try to
destroy some of the Fortress
no
what is what is this what is this
oh I guess we just need to keep like
walking around
and we might see them eventually I feel
like I always see them when I don't want
to see them
now that I want to there's nowhere to be
found oh
[Music]
where are you and he's outside the
Fortress oh
side
outside uh don't worry about me too much
though
you can look for one two I think oh no
there's piggies
don't worry about it
foreign
[Music]
I see you
I'm making a staircase for this guy
because I don't want him to fall off oh
[Music]
guys I'm so friendly right now oh he's
not watch out watch out
yo what's up
oh
I'm good I'm good I'm good
already yeah do you want it the Looting
sword is insane yeah what
what's up
oh oh my oh my oh my
heroic
stop it
potato fry there's three of them now
yeah just make sure to drink another
potion because you're so probably going
to run out soon oh ah one minute does it
stack if I drink it before it runs out
uh it'll refresh so you can drink it
before it runs out
[Music]
oh I don't see anybody
um maybe
you look this way I see one
oh
he's not even looking
I got him yeah but no school no school
can't get lucky every time
I'll [\h__\h] toward my heart
my heart Pitch Black
oh there's this one over there
how do we go there a black heart and
soul
it's the emotori inside me
get over here take it down fall down
take him down
bye
ouch
um
oh he didn't drop a skull did he
oh the first one was so lucky I know our
expectations got set too high when we
I'm so lucky the first time yeah the
next one will be it's the next one
Shirley
I kind of wanted to get like six though
sixth one so we get him twice a month
yeah
oh there's one it'd be nice to have more
beacons for the server I think
oh on the beacons
yeah
oh sorry
normal potato fries
why is there so many they all spawned
before there was only one
yeah
their Blaze runs are pretty useful
though hmm
fancy fancy
when we go up here see if there's
something up here
[Music]
oh there's a normal skeleton
why is there a normal skeleton
wrong Dimensions but he
good you shot me
all right well now I'm going to look for
some of them
me too
um
there's one oh don't die don't die
you're done so long
[Music]
I'm okay
the skeleton like that oh
hello there's a pig and a skeleton oh
aren't they friendly
no
um
the pig's trying to flip me out ow
l
[Music]
he's strong this pig
I normally just kill them with a bucket
of lava
why is there so many
I haven't gotten another school
oh wait come on that's already a good
amount
one out of three no no oh no school
but many Blazers let's go
oh I should put it in the chest ah
you're right oh yeah oh there it is oh
yeah you should put the skull in the
chest at least safe
nice checkpoints
I'm gonna try to break for a few
foreign
[Music]
there was one over here
hmm
where'd you go oh there you are
ow
you saw me
no sorry I'm talking to the skeleton oh
a Wither one or a normal one wither one
I don't know
show them who nature is
that's right
uh
don't underestimate Ninja
in Phoenix this should be like your
natural habitat fire everywhere yeah oh
I'm totally comfortable with this
situation yeah not too hot
It's gotta be hot
but to be honest I like
um cold environments too can you ski or
snowboard
no I've never been oh you have to learn
yeah I would like to try it it's very
difficult it looks easier than it is in
my opinion scary it is scary I crashed
before when I went skiing with Cali and
Hokkaido remember your story yeah it was
terrifying I really thought I was gonna
die not that that would be a problem
because I'm a phoenix
laughs
so yeah but still it was still
terrifying
yeah I would be scared that I would like
run into a tree
yeah that's almost what happened to me
yeah but no there's like normally if you
ski somewhere there's like a you know a
big area of you know a big road
Snow Road with no trees in the way but
yeah if you lose control hi you lose
control you might crash and that's
indeed very scary
hmm
so I have to start in a safe place until
you feel like
you have enough skills
oh is there I heard something there's a
pig up there
can't reach him well as long as he stays
up there we can be friends
you want the
you want this meat
is so meat he was just his friend
bullied me earlier so I'm getting
revenge
well where are the weather things now
I've been running around up here for a
while can't find them I know
maybe I need to turn my back on them and
then they will pop up again
maybe they want to play hide and seek
well it's like
oh when we did the the hide and seek
around that's the first time I did that
I didn't know that you know it was so
easy to do I thought you needed a mod or
something yeah it's pretty fun I hope we
can try it again sometime I don't know
if people actually like Among Us I
genuinely had fun
but of course like too much is of course
not fun like doing it once per maybe two
months or so
it's fine in my opinion
[Music]
but because I wish everyone got a chance
to be the Imposter yeah
apparently I should have oh I should
have um
like reopens the lobby a few times so
that helps with the bug is there really
a bug I have heard that before I don't
know if I believe it but um
hi hi
please do you need help yeah please help
did he drop something no schools oh
oh I panic man
oh skulls what the hell the first one
was so lucky I thought we were gonna
easily get them all in the short time I
already opened that up sorry the delay's
not been there don't fall don't fall
okay
I hate when that happens when
the first try you just get lucky and
then yeah
expectations
can't follow up on them now we are just
suffering
um
at least it's not so unsafe in here it
is like hard to fall down somewhere
mostly
yeah
oh apparently it's ah it's five percent
oops probably with looting three
okay I'm not part of it not being too
easy
I wanted
I wanted sex
but now that seems like that seems
ridiculous
yeah let's not do that
we'll be here until Christmas
so I'm about 1 in 20 then
huh
I don't know how are we going to split a
beacon
amongst everyone
what Beacon was for what speed running
speed
um or like mining I feel like mining is
the most useful first one Hello friends
no skull uh
and how um how fast the reach of the
beacon
um I don't think it's that far hmm
Maybe
I know 100 blocks or so honestly I don't
care so much about the beacon for me
it's just the experience of taking down
the weather oh
[Music]
where are you guys where are you
I guess like the beacon it could be a
communal Beacon though yeah so that
people can borrow it when they need it
when they have like big projects to use
hello
oh what did you find
a skeleton who has no skull oh no
because if you ever need to like mine a
bunch of stuff out then the beacon will
help a lot
because it can allow you to like insta
mine things
never need to like flatten something in
it sounds good oh you have a flattening
area
I can see that would be very helpful
there
if we ever do have you like thought
about doing
um en sports festival
because you're also quite into Minecraft
I think that would be fun but
I don't know I feel like a lot of Yen
members don't play Minecraft maybe they
would join for the sports I don't think
so
they would no you don't really have to
play Minecraft
you know like if I think even Cali even
even Kelly would participate but at
least you're like to build it
is a big issue I don't know how they
managed to build all of that so fast
with like what three or four members
yeah they're really coordinating though
in ID
oh yeah we can get ID to help
doesn't that take away a little bit from
having like
yeah no it's not doing everything only
help
yeah you need to do us ID server tour
yes
yes I'm sure anyone would be happy to
show you around
[Music]
it's really incredible I've seen like
screenshots and videos a little bit I
think yeah they aren't doing Justice
either it's like it's like being in like
Disney World when you're there
I think um Japan server is also very
very incredible but probably like in a
different way Japan server the stuff
they built it's like it's a bit more
chaotic cute and chaotic and fun stuff
while ID just feels seriously impressing
structures yeah and like everything an
idea is like coordinating too
like I think they planned a lot of it
from the start
school
I'll open up here oh there's nothing
here
I've seen people say the en server is
like the countryside and I think that's
I don't think that's anything to be
ashamed I don't think our server is bad
it's Charming it has its time especially
you have to consider for the most time
it was just five members and then you
know now even now we're still not that
many we're just ten
[Music]
it's not that many members
I think it's a cute server oh I see one
in the distance
how do I get to him
oh
there's a pic oh no that's not a pig
I was kind of scared
Maybe
oh I'm scared I'm scared
do you need help
um no I think
oh
making stairs
are they is he still up here huh
what I saw him here he was here right
yeah that kept happening to me too I
would think I see them but no I really
saw that might be around somewhere where
did you go oh oh there he is I'm scared
oh I have the high gun I have The High
Ground come here
and you have a cool sword does he know
where I am
oh where did he go maybe he's inside
it might have been me
because you're running away that's so
sad follow me follow me you need help oh
I need your mental support
like I saw him up here what's going on
and then I saw him down here it's not an
illusion I'm pretty sure and then he
went got one
maybe there's two
uh no school no school no school
sad
[Music]
you're not even spawning The Fortress
like he was walking on the on the
mushrooms what the hell
Just Dance Again oh but that's hard to
reach because there's love out there
fauna do you want to go to this one
sure where you know where I went
um on the roof
but I
I will try to make myself noticeable now
here down here I'm too scared to fall
down but there's one
um over on that bridge you see him do
you need blocks
no I have blocks okay okay I'll leave
this one to you
or maybe you can start just stop the
lava somehow
I got it I think oh
oh he's so scared of you he's running
away he's running don't run go get him
go get him all right he's he's been
cornered oh now he's got courage to come
back
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
yeah skull
no oh no there's a pig here I'll come
back oh no there's a pink
okay okay okay I'm coming
big scary Pink scary
don't fall down
I won't fall
very safe
I'm not safe
you're safe no you're safe no
oh this guy yes he's bothering you yes
yes
but then he pushes so far far yeah
he likes to flip
oh nice nice
okay all my boots are about to break oh
no I should have healed them uh the
golden boots
yeah
oh I hear
oh oh big white boy oh he's angry
we're not here for you except for
skeletons oh there's one oh
okay
back up in a safe space man
what the hell
I guess this is why they recommend you
find fortresses in a certain biome
because it can increase the spawn rates
because here I think like the pigs can
spawn
um because we're like the forest so was
there more than one Fortress per Nether
or is it just one yeah there's like
infinite oh
well I think we'll we'll find it here
eventually
fun it can't be that difficult to find
two more
right that's true
this look
spawn rate seems slow
fighting them is no problem
does he know how to get to me no he
doesn't
uh I'll get to you maybe uh
oh oh he's so confused this is so sad
his AI is so confused
okay so I took down the place here let
me make a pop
um
don't hit me from over there can you hit
me from over there please don't hit me
from over there
Mom this is scary oh here
this is is this enough yeah bye
whatever
you got this
oh he might fall down into lava if I do
this though
oh are you gonna give him a pathway I've
been making one but now I'm too scared
to put the last block there
okay nice oh was that too tall for him
that was too tall
yeah we can do it like this are you
ready yes I'm ready
hi
oh nice no score let's go
I'm so much coal though I even my
[Music]
mom makes me
so rude rude I he wanted to come to me I
helped him what the heck
I mean it's obvious he has a skull so
why doesn't he just give it to us
oh
we need to we need to help him
like his body
I agree upon a third TV show that you're
watching right now anything okay
I'll pick the baby
when the babies ran away
um I've been watching or I watched
Breaking Bad oh and then I've been
watching Better Call Saul what better
call soul
yeah Better Call Saul is like a spin-off
a Breaking Bad oh
breaking back if you want that's the one
where the Malcolm in the Middle dad is
in right yeah
completely different character yeah
really is it really or is it is it maybe
really actually him
I did like um amalcum in the middle
episode where it's like him but he's
like waking up from a dream
and then it's like Breaking Bad was just
his bad dream I love milking the Malcolm
in the Middle dad I just recently
re-watched the whole mackum in the
middle like from season one to last
season
oh I like that show too
yeah yeah but I guess I need to watch
Breaking but how is it like like what
what genre is that
more serious right yeah well actually
people say that it's a black comedy
which it kind of is it's just a really
really dark comedy yeah I would say
mostly it's like
drama Thriller
dark the other thing is I don't like
frillers that much
[Music]
um
it's not scary but it's thrilling
yeah you might not like it though I
might not like it there's a lot of Gore
I don't know how you feel about
core
yo should we take down the other mobs
that are here just so we can spawn
something else
um I don't think once we make them too
mad I think that'll be too mad and don't
be mad forever
okay I better not touch them
oh
yeah oh no
have you angered someone
no I just killed the baby and I feel bad
now maybe can we please do something oh
really first one are you watching
anything right now
I'm always watching something but I'm
gonna finally start watching the newest
season of the handmaid's tale
oh it kind of freaks me out but it's
it's good and I hate it at the same time
yeah I read the I read the book but I
haven't seen the you read the book damn
cool
the whole book
it's not sure
it's only like 200 Pages or something I
think and he never wants to show though
no the show is terrifying like I think
it does the book a lot of Justin too
yeah you have to you have to watch the
show the most season last the most
recent season is season five they've
brought out a lot and it's really high
quality but every episode like after
every episode I need like
a break because mentally I can't
freaking take it it's too much yeah
I understand that yeah I wonder if they
like
I bet it's new material the show right
it wouldn't be just following the book I
don't think I think I think it's
following the book properly I haven't
heard many complaints about it being
linked I feel like the book is pretty
short though I don't know if they could
make something oh they definitely are
dragging it out endlessly though so much
out of it yeah they're really squeezing
that lemon
they really are like for many seasons
Ella's been getting
um okay are we ever getting out of this
[\h__\h] or what is it just like one does it
fall like one character oh one mainly
but you do definitely hear about the
others
um um and some of them have really cool
glasses actually one of the girls that
you learn about
um is being acted by Rari from Gilmore
Girls Alexis Bledel
no
[Music]
um the one with the old ladies right
now
[Laughter]
the young looking pretty mom and her
daughter raising her daughter alone
is it like a sitcom or like a drama not
a sitcom I think but like um because
there's no like laughing tracks and [\h__\h]
but it's funny and and and it's cute and
there's some romance and a little bit of
drama but I don't know what what how
would I describe it why did you not
watch
I don't really watch comedies or
anything most of the time no but I think
you would like it
perhaps perhaps
[Music]
getting wrecked by the Peaks
oh no my boots are already gone oh
I only have my helmet one in terms of
gold
it's okay
I will survive
one way or another
is Gilmore Girls It's like a comedy what
is it it's definitely a comedy but it
also has like a lot of sadness and drama
and cute and romance like you know all
kinds of stuff and you know so like
splice of Life yeah yes yes that's what
I wanted to say yeah it's nice of life
kind of
and it has a lot of Seasons so you have
so much to to binge watch if you need
something to binge watch
I have a lot on my list right now
there's a lot of animes coming out that
are really good oh you're still you're
still deep in the anime hole
you know watch anime I used to watch a
lot of anime let's see Andrea also
um no anime from like 10 years ago or so
um I know some how about zero not Skybox
no I don't know
[Music]
I know it of course but I haven't
actually watched most of it you
have to watch
the whole series All Seasons you have to
yeah
I mean it's funny but it's not like
mainly comedy I would say it's about
um
about putting as much information in
your head as possible in in one scene
that's yeah that's how I felt when I
watched I watched a couple episodes you
really have to pay attention yes yes yes
yes
they just have a lot of dialogue um but
I freaking love Pokemon about dog that's
like my favorite anime
you like it you like Central yeah
[Music]
yeah
it's the crazy one with with the snake
hair eventually kind of a spoiler though
does she have glasses
oh no no that's that's
um uh you're talking about what's your
name the one who turns into a cat
um
what that sounds cute yeah
I like a real cat
what's her name again the snail girl
ah um and now I'm forgetting all the
names what the hell
um
she's adorable
he's so cute yes with the big backpack
oh hello hello oh it's so cute hello
hello hello I got him about uh no skull
at least I found one again and by
killing him that means we can we can
spawn a new one maybe
yes more please kill some Blazers Maybe
there's a lot of places yeah
the wither skeletons
um
what kind of shows
[Music]
sorry sorry
uh Pig did you watch Umbrella Academy
yeah I like them but the world I don't
know what what was my did you watch the
new season yeah I didn't oh I haven't
seen the new one yet I found it was kind
of ridiculous
um some parts of it it's high quality
and all that but for some reason
I already forgot what my exact words
were when I gave feedback about it but
something about it was just like
please did you feel that way about the
first two seasons as well or just the
third season I think
I may have partially had those feelings
in several episodes also in on the other
seasons
but the first season I think there were
reasons why I
absolutely
was disappointed but it's still worth
watching I would say
yeah I really liked the first season
first season was was decent yeah yeah
[Laughter]
okay I'm
gonna film the one not help
are you okay okay
welcome
no no skull why
questions
you get that one oh you need that one
take it take it
I got it I can take him
rip his head up
ah no no school
so far oh
ah
please count for us what happened
[Music]
where was the one oh yeah we can look at
our stats page
um
is that me dying there's just that stage
oh I see one of you dying
[Music]
just don't die when you're looking at
this test oh where are those stats I
don't know how to
uh go to the escape and then statistics
and then mobs hmm
oh
I've got this before
wow I've killed a lot of zombies I've
killed almost 1200 zombies
oh but that's totally oh is it from the
rain Farm is 8 000 vindicators wow
oh my goodness 20 000 pillagers almost
then wow
so I saw one over there wow
where one could do this
is he upstairs chat
it was upstairs Ryan
oh yeah yeah there's upstairs
I feel like Kiara if you like to watch
shows you should watch Breaking Bad just
to say you've watched it because many
people say it's like the greatest show
of all time
they gave me a stone sword
s no but that was lucky I guess to have
two at the same time
If Only They gave me two skulls
man I panic but I think Discord cuts out
my Panic so you didn't hear it oh yeah
probably
oh man but I I have a theater responding
a bit more than before
yeah maybe
um never give up
wait it's almost damn
it's been we've been looking for yeah
looking actively for like maybe one hour
where is everybody
so dark
oh well a new room
new room and
stairs
I found a new room at least more rooms
to run around and check out yeah I don't
even have like a path I'm following I'm
just running randomly that's a long path
can they spawn in here too chat
so the Fortress I think is looking at
the ground
um
probably as long as it's um there's not
torches
oh yeah no no one's ever been here
before it seems but now that's uh that's
it hmm
I don't I don't feel like they would
spawn here
Target acquired
targeted quiet take him down for now
he's coming to me oh
no skulls slacks
it's [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
come on
come on is there looting four and five
two no
point five two
that's definitely looting two
oh no I forgot I don't have boots
anymore guys really angry oh maybe do
you want to go home once to get some I
don't know
should have placed one ah wait actually
isn't there I think I just ran by gold
spawns here right you can make it I saw
some gold here let me Farm it for you
but I only have silk touch actually
oh that doesn't work right you can bring
me the book okay and I can unsilk touch
it it's awesome
gold oh will he be mad
I think
oh wait do I have one in the under chest
wait I think I do actually I think it's
also almost broken though
I'll wear it for now
I hear I saw some goals
um
it's hard to reach
oh
there you are
[Music]
maybe you can mine it yourself then
yeah I can okay so mining
what was that one no you're going the
wrong way I don't know if you'll reach
there but I guess you can take some
different gold and have that doesn't
have only the same gold
there's just some quartz here though
don't need corn I think
huh don't need quartz
yeah I don't need quartz
which is pretty
yeah it actually is pretty useful too
for Redstone
but I have some I think they have a
favorite uh
Stone uh gem in real life
I really like uh opal opal what color
does that have like rainbow rainbow
wanna yeah that's pretty there's like
pearlescent kind of oh an opalescent oh
I see one
[Music]
what's your favorite do you have a
favorite gemstone I like them well
they're all pretty but of course
Diamonds Are a Girl's Best Friend right
that's true no skull
yes yes I hope his drops didn't burn in
the fire
that would be unfortunate oh I see one
whoa
well there's a couple ones down there
oh oh where oh my actually just two
oh I think like you're riding quite a
few
yes I think if I open a P1
it's funny
stupid stupid
dummies yeah dummies can't reach don't
die let us kill you
don't get don't forget to call kikiwa
so I I make you stare can you come now
no no
um
oh there's one where I just was
[Laughter]
ah
I gotta get it
one more
[Music]
Chihuahua is going to collect all the
skulls yeah they all came from like the
ones that I started attacking
you know you know which ones yeah I've
Got the Feeling to give up
oh where is
oh
oh chest
and they didn't even touch me this time
because I was attacking them from
above
all right scroll is safely placed in the
chest
Phoenix luck yay
where could this one be oh do I see no
just blazes
um
I'm gonna turn on my hitboxes so I can
definitely not miss anything that drops
um Pro Gamer
oh I dropped that
I'm so shocked fauna that like you never
saw the shows that I shot someone
Gilmore Girls like what what about
wait I think mommy was the one who
didn't see it but what about you did I
ask you before about Lord of the Rings
oh yeah I haven't seen it either oh my
God why I have but it was a long time
ago and I don't remember it I chat today
when I was a baby was it I see one was
it hurt oh mermaid does I said I want to
watch it together with because it's
impossible that they haven't seen it
before
because if it's her and moment and
I have two people to watch that with I
think it was yeah it was mommy oh my God
what the hell it's probably because
villain mermaid it must be Zoomers and
I'm just a boomer but even if uh
Zoomer thing to not watch Lord of the
Rings maybe it is no I'm a boomer too
I'm just I don't know I tried to read
the books but and I don't know
I I have nothing but respect for Tolkien
but his writing style is not really for
me you know okay yeah then you should
watch the movie
it's easy to comprehend yeah that's true
uh no school what's cool thank you for
the call it's like wait Cole ah
not Santa but I think isn't it Krampus
the campus
yeah couples and you know the the dude
that looks like Santa he's called
Nicolaus and actually I think it's on
the 6th of December we have the Nicolaus
day and
um you know Nicolas here comes with with
the campus the evil evil compass and if
you're not a good if you're a good child
you get like an apple or something
boring like that yeah that's not even
that good
yeah but if you are bad then the compost
will hit you with uh whips and and we'll
pick you up and like throw you around
it's really scary they come into school
they literally raid schools
it's terrifying dude can you imagine
what they look like have you seen them
before I have I think what have you do
you know like The Binding of Isaac
the game I know the game but then no I
don't know what you're talking about
though oh there's krampuses in that game
and he he is like a goat head oh yeah
yeah they have the big fairy they they
wear like big big suits fairy suits and
I mean not not you know those fursuits
scary scary in the modern era modern
cramping no no no no no no no
and then they come and rate schools but
also like in on the countryside they go
to like they have the Krampus runs where
just a ton of them will run for the
streets and then there's like always
these normal people who stand around the
streets like just because I guess they
like the the adrenaline of maybe being
punched in new face and still stuff and
and they think it's funny so they just
wait there for their Destiny I guess
oh I see two
um it's amazing it's so scary doll
have you heard about the the Santa the
dress is in White and the Santa the
dress is in Black what no
they say
that originally there were two Santas
one dressed in white and one in black
what what and
the Santa dressed in black was evil
like you say probably you said this
kidnaps kidnaps children and one day the
Santa dressed in white had enough and
murdered the sand to dress in black and
that's why he has a red coat is
oh I said I'm sorry from a movie or what
[Music]
yeah it's probably a game
I don't think it's a real story but it
should be
it sounds like it could work with you
yeah your Krampus you know
but some some people mistake the Nicolas
for Santa but he's a very slim version
of Santa
this could be evil Santa who brings
Krampus
oh well he's supposed to be the good one
but maybe maybe that's all just a fusade
yeah
Krampus and he lets him do the evil
stuff while he actually also wants to do
it no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
he's a good boy
but he shouldn't just bring Apples and
those nuts because um
I think children deserve something more
than just yeah chocolates
it's Christmas you know
yes I mean it's not really Christmas but
it's close enough
Nicholas and apparently it was the fifth
not the sixth
I make mistakes so does that mean the
Krampus are coming again soon when I
hear no Bells they wear like big
cowbells and stuff so you can hear them
coming normally
what's going on are you getting some
Withers uh mine killed some and I have
no skulls
need our new one
ah well I got I just got one recently
and that has to be paced and balanced
you know
I'm still looking for them but no no
luck but that's normal oh God
one over there I think
okay I can do this
you got it the pigs are dangerous and
shields help though
okay it's dead
everyone I keep thinking I see a skull
but then that's just because the lump of
coal yeah
this was correct okay
cool I thought it was school but it
wasn't really cool
maybe maybe oh yeah no way the Winner's
Garden
okay now he's already taking some damage
oh did you see it
yeah I see
what
the Labyrinth of stairs now
they're manipulating our work here
this one will drop it
no
I'm starting to think that I might be
Unlucky One of Us oh there's one over
there
oh and we built like some stairs over
there the parallels Bridge
oh yeah yes yes you can go there again
precarious Bridge you go there and I
need you to go
I'll go
I will watch you but you're the one who
has the good good job
I don't like that tap if you build a
better path I would go
oh
at least I'm watching maybe my presence
will
it's going in the lava no I'm not scared
what if he knocks me off but you have to
fire potion though you can it doesn't
hurt you that much right
yeah
well is he okay
oh wait but I don't want the skull to
die in the lava yes
all right all right
oh and
nothing
oh there's some gold now going over
there though I think there might be
another one oh
[Music]
good luck oh no that's a pig just a pig
oink oink oink oink oink oink oink
I was feeling so ambitious at the start
of this I was like oh we can get sick
get to drop that idea quickly
I know
I thought we were set with the Looting
oh but as long as the other pigs don't
see it right oh no never mind they don't
really seem to be angry at me on it
maybe maybe I hit the weather
no it wasn't over there
they sounded angry for a second but
maybe you're okay
40.
a life honor
hello
see that one I thought I hit him but I
guess he doesn't care
oh this is Kelly here
oh my gosh you're right
well there's our three skulls don't die
don't die yeah
it just turned off
um
but we're done now
yeah
oh I want more I want a six that's fine
we can look for a while more no longer
I'll come back sometime okay okay you
know the way now yeah it's not too bad
that's all we needed right the skulls
what what else is there
to make the wither we do need like Soul
Sand I think but I have some okay it's
not hard to find
all right
other than that um I did want to get
like Smite oh enchantments
come on drop drop it
I didn't drop it oh
it would have been my luck is pretty
good but not that good yeah wait
actually I just realized this is your
karma your luck Karma because well you
you I'm sorry you lost your shiny in
Pokemon
yeah I saw a few post on Twitter I
walked by it it's on stream and then you
know I bought one and then I walked by
another one and I was thinking while I
was walking I didn't say it out loud but
I was thinking oh that looks a little
bit different but I didn't think
anything about it because they're both
very bright you know
[Music]
after that like a while after that while
I was fighting the next mob already a
few meters away uh when Chad was saying
oh that was a shiny but it seemed like
they meant the one that was fighting
they didn't even mean the one I walked
by but the one I was fighting before
that was not of shiny but yeah then
later on I checked and I checked the
archive and it was of course too late
anyway even if I had gone back by the
time they told me it was too late but
I'm so sad because it was the The Ice
moth and I think that Pokemon is really
pretty
it's been nice yeah I'll go pick up the
Ender Chest
do you want to put it since you have the
other ones okay
we did it
and actually you know what time wise
it's pretty perfect yeah it's almost
midnight here it's pretty good I like it
the balance time balance all right the
the stone swords I'll throw them away
I find it interesting to use the stone
swords they're so weak but I guess they
match their look
yeah their arms are strong wow
or what oh wait so this one oh we still
have so many portions you know what I'll
drink one I'll drink one because if I
fall and then die that'll be terrible on
the way back
goes in here
wasn't there I think I placed one more
uh
of those chests in the other entrance
place oh yeah I think I saw shulker
around there somewhere oh my God
helmet oh damn mine broke too hard oh so
we're both without gold now yeah oh
oh we'll be okay though I think
oh
we just have to get back yes
okay I think is it here
uh-huh yep
oh scary scary scary scary scary scary
scary scary scary scary scary scary
scary scary scary
oh oh my God the Strider
it's all good oh wait there's a lot of
pigs
[Music]
what do we do I'll find them don't worry
bam I'll beat you back up
the Striders they're stacked on there's
so many people they're so cute
oh Pig ah oh that pink
I think it's this is safe though okay
let's go quickly
pigs don't know how to use the
scaffolding my God
they would break if they tried to go up
on them
I cannot support them
oh
well when will we fight the Wither
um
maybe before Christmas
yeah I think we can manage to do it
before Christmas oh oh my goodness oh
watch out watch out watch out watch out
watch out watch out okay
oh God
oh there's a pig at the top there's a
pig did you die oh
my place where your stuff doesn't drop
eh
don't die
I'm being shot at and there's everything
is here oh no oh holy moly where are you
now
I'm on the scaffolding oh
did you go all the way to the top is
this little pig there um yes
there's still a picture
are you even higher than me right now no
I'm below you now what when did you get
there that's so scary I fell I fell to
the bottom what
and I died but my totem saved me oh
oh
see you have to hold it uh but you know
what I'll put it that actually scares me
so you learn learned my lesson
and
can I build here to the other scaffold
but how do I build from a scaffold I'm
really bad at building from scaffold I
don't want to fall off I'll kill it okay
these too far
hey
[Music]
somehow he pushed me off I think I went
too high on me oh okay was it this way I
think it was that way oh yeah
oh
um
it wasn't useless
um you did most of the prep for the prep
but in the actual action I think I was
not useless thank God yes you got all
the skulls
I got the Lucky Sword the lucky hit
[Music]
if you ever need more you can always ask
me I can accompany you I know it takes
you along
I'll come with you I'm your lucky charm
you are
finally my Phoenix lock came back to me
I know yeah this is this is your karma
you had bad luck and now you'll have
good luck yeah have you found any other
shinies no I don't think so
the mass outbreaks yet not really no I
mean I've watched some videos to see how
people do it so I might do it maybe
I'll try next week but I don't want to
do it after I'm already done with the
game because I don't see any meaning in
getting or shiny when they're not using
it you know so if anything there's like
any tournaments though left or right ah
that way because we said left right left
yes so now it's right
um
there's also you can get a shiny charm
at the end of the game
but honestly like the people encounter
so many shinies even without so I think
in theory it's totally like possible I
have shiny hunting when I had a mass
outbreak and I found one after like 40
minutes or so 40 minutes or an hour
which one which one it was a Fido
yeah you should be using them yeah it's
also cute but the
shiny color doesn't make him look that
different no it doesn't actually because
I evolved him and then he's just like
different
just a caramelized dog
all right panda
foreign
chest for now
yeah that should be fine they're safe
and cozy in there yes oh the do you want
some of those potions or should I also
keep them in the
River the river attacks with fire too
doesn't it
I think so I thought it was like
shooting fire
it does I think he shoots like withering
glass wow okay wait does it show
he has explosions I don't know if it's
fire
[Music]
um
not just a weathering effect he attacks
with explosions so that doesn't count as
firearm okay are you like blast
protection would be good we took like
what how many two two potions from or
four from Inna
oh yeah yeah we could return them yeah
one four was it
oh we have visitors oh
hi we've been sleepy we were in the
weather and then I go to sleep
quick quick
terrifying Awakening they're still here
but they're burning burning in the sky
okay
I'm gonna put them back where they were
before and she will never have known
that something was missing that we've
been here
[Music]
I love her house I love the glass Taco I
know it's because her house couldn't buy
it but it's like so good yeah it's been
for some stage and some history do you
see you look looking literally at his
story honestly this area where all the
myth houses are is so nostalgic too hey
that's why I like the Ian servers yeah I
agree
maybe I will play some more Minecraft
now that you know we have the weather
thing going on I don't know what to do
after that but at least now we have
something to do I just need you know I
don't really like building farms and
stuff that much
um I find that a little bit boring
um as a stream at least for me because
like I don't know like I need to think
so hard and plan just place blocks don't
want
so if it's adventuring I'm always in
yeah I want to Adventure
yeah I think Bay also wants to go on
adventures
hmm I actually I should check out how my
frogs are doing though before I leave
are they still they must be still alive
right maybe they multiplied by 50 or so
but today
that I guess they don't didn't they eat
them slime slime balls but not much I
thought that was amazing you were going
to make them eat fireflies but then like
they had to take it out of the game
because apparently in real life it was
like poisonous butterflies yes yes yes
yes
that is true I know that from froggy
Wawa
she likes them anyway but you know she's
not supposed to eat them eating like
food
actually if you guys want to know what
frogs can eat
I made a frog
um food or food for frog snack fly tier
list
uh or a froggy Mama made it on my
channel
a while ago
but it was quite informative because I
was literally like froggy mom was giving
really really informative information
yeah about like normal flies and all
kinds of flies what flies are there I
don't know look at that oh
god dude flip and flop oh they go like
quack quack oh wow that was a big jump
oh sick nice jumper do a flip flip get
out whoa
whoa he's having fun oh he's living his
best life
I'm happy I want something to happen in
a tiny glass cube but
have you ever thought about getting like
a reptile pet like you know frog is this
considered the reptile it is right
they're amphibians amphibians that's
what I mean that's what I mean have you
considered it
about getting a turtle because I have
Turtles but I don't I think I don't
really want any pet that I have to keep
in a cage just
um I don't know I like cats I'm good
with just cats yeah but it's not like
you know a frog would want to be running
around your whole apartment floor
I think he's happy in a place like this
it'd be like I didn't I don't know I
feel like there's not as much into it
we're talking with them you know you
can't really snuggle a frog a frog
doesn't really work you can kiss the
Frog
yeah but they probably don't really want
to because have you asked them
they look they look like they want to be
kissed
I don't know maybe no I like a lot of
reptiles and amphibians are pretty
standoff well snakes definitely want to
cuddle fauna
snakes snakes wants to give you a big
old hug
they want to squeeze you I love you
they might just wanna
well yes
respect you
tie you up
yeah well Frog's cute I I'm I'm so
planning to get a aquarium at some point
um but now like I'll I'll be traveling
like to Japan for like a month and so on
so if anything I want to get it after
that otherwise you know I can't enjoy it
but I'll still be paying for it yeah I
just I feel like I'm kind of too lazy so
lazy because it's a lot of Maintenance
yeah you like clean the tank you know
yeah I was thinking the same but I found
the service uh in in Austria that like
does it for you oh yeah you can choose
like what you want the aquarium to look
like what fishes you want inside with
plants what design what size and so on
then they come and install it for you
and clean it for you they come yeah they
come like two to like clean it clean the
water like change the water and they
take out the fish that are dead if
they're running dead then we'll place it
and also you don't even have to even
feed unless you want to but they have an
automatic feeder and stuff so I thought
oh my God this is perfect because I want
an aquarium but I don't want to travel
that comes with it
so I'm planning on getting that I I
looked out their their choices and so on
I'm excited
for species I'm gonna get feces and I'm
also gonna put in um what was it called
the blue the blue it's not a crab it's
more like um I wanted the crab but then
the dude said he had uh what was it
called similar to a crab
[Music]
a crayfish fish oh yeah it's like
stunningly brightly blue
so beautiful it stands out so much you
know in in German when I said I want the
crab in German it kind of a panel
apparently is in German similar to a
crayfish so yeah I don't know if I can
get a crap I love crabs but I'm getting
a crayfish yeah crabs are cute have you
seen the video of that person who bought
a lobster at the grocery store and then
raised it as a pet yes
yes yes I have
that was fascinating I've seen a lot of
those kind of random ass YouTube videos
with stuff like that
I've also watched I don't really like
lobsters that Munch like as an animal or
is it because an animal
that cute
yeah yeah and I don't think they're cute
either but you know what I watched also
a video where um a Korean guy he was
like uh I don't know walking randomly in
the nature and he found like a little
tiny not really even a stream of water
it was just like a puddle of water that
was leading to a bigger water body and
there were like a lot of tadpoles caught
in there
and he wanted to help them so he caught
a couple of them brought them home and
then raised them into frogs and brought
them back because like tadpoles so many
of them die in nature without making it
into frog stage because there's just too
many of them and then stuff like that
happens where they end up in a little
puddle but then the puddle disappears
and they just you know they dry out and
also they get eaten by other animals so
everything it's a hard life for tadpoles
but yeah he gave he gave he took some of
them home and then the rest that were
there he helped them go into bigger
water and then he raised them and made a
whole documentary about it it was so
cute he's a tadpole hero yeah oh so cute
yeah and I love those kinds of videos
[Music]
um
we should raise a frog from a real one
okay
but you don't want to interact with them
I've kissed a frog before when I was
younger I just feel like the frog
doesn't really care you know it's like
with cats you can tell that they love
you but like a frog I'm not even sure if
a frog really can loving it doesn't
matter it doesn't mean you have to teach
him love if he doesn't understand love
then you first have to teach him love I
don't know if they're capable who
understand love stop pounding the frogs
they have so much potential they're
swing they're cute they're cute
you can perceive them as cute
and then the big frog ones they're funny
but the tiny frog was so cute I only
want love you have to love them
I don't know why I'm giving frog so much
love I feel like I'm being manipulated
by Froggy Wawa Spirit somewhere probably
toxoplasmosis yeah
all right I'm leaving this place it was
nice seeing you again flip and flop
thank thank you for letting us in
an enclosure for frogs or not yet no I
don't have any frogs oh my God
yeah well if you ever need
um actually I still have tadpoles if you
just want to go the easy route I I can
give you a tadpole
so have them I don't have a place to put
them yet I only have the best models are
still living in a bathtub
used to live ah the poor axolotls
oh well well let's go back I go back to
my place I guess or you should take a
picture
can we put the heads on our heads
is that possible can you maybe we can
then we can take a picture with them
yeah
does it count as a helmet good idea
this is what does it count as a helmet
you can I think so yeah you really can
oh let's go we can dress up
nice good ideas cute
[Music]
and their chest don't oh yeah that will
pose in front of the gate
yes yes yes yes yes oh hunger how did
you figure out where to fight it too
yeah we are going for we know about the
easy way but we're going for the more
difficult way
yeah with so many of us if we do it like
in a small space it will be dead and
well I mean when Council fought the
Ender Dragon it was also something felt
it may have been anticlimactic
yeah because we traveled so far but then
it was
yeah maybe pretty fast I heard that your
fight was very
chaotic because of certain members
IDE will be worse oh it's harder
well
[Music]
but we're both Pros you know
okay so picture time do you have like a
um like one of those filters on or
oh I should turn mine on I should turn
mine on too you had them up okay let me
see
um whoops was it in video settings no I
think it's video settings oh really
I have shaders here
um does this still work
hang in the never it would have been way
too dark so it was good why are you so
good for the nether oh
I'll take my armor off
[Music]
don't hold bread okay uh
look at us
[Music]
we did it high five fauna
good job high five
yeah
I'm glad we could do this together Sonia
yes thank you looking forward to the
weather fight it will be very dramatic
[Music]
a big underground Cavern I feel like
that would be a good Middle Point okay
so he's writing it out in the open that
way we can contain it a little bit um
yeah yeah so it won't just fly away okay
do you think we have to fight it really
far yeah from anything we've built
because it can like completely destroy
no problem we'll go super far we
couldn't even do it like out there in
the midst hour so
yeah yeah yeah I have a I have a railway
that leads on a ice way that leads all
the way to the mess have you seen it
before my man song
yes I have we can do it somewhere there
underground yeah that would be good I
think okay nice
thank you guys playing thanks for your
good luck no thank you for preparing and
thank you guys for watching ours thank
you prep work maybe the next or the next
week after so we can do the the actual
fight sometime before Christmas for sure
if you guys wanna see more of fauna
if this is too short for you guys if you
like if you're like oh I'll miss fun
though so much that was just like it was
it was nice but just so little bit more
would be nice then maybe
right fauna maybe in 50 minutes right is
it 50 or is it more like 24 hours and
15. oh
what's something else really oh then you
are okay okay okay I'm yeah you could
it's because you too like gave me the
videos so early
let me see it
let me look at that it was supposed to
not be but it is ready if it needs to be
it's right I couldn't even switch it out
let's see the I have a I have a
a file that is connected that will
automatically like update at GMT plus
zero oh oh no it's not maybe I should
switch it because now I already kind of
teased it
oh no sorry guys no fun not tonight but
we will now understand that it will be
soon okay someone just as good yes yes
everyone everyone's good I didn't watch
your video yet even though you sent it
to me because it's so in private
oh yeah it's nice I wonder I wonder what
you did in your video just chat with you
well who knows what else who knows who
knows you guys will have to find out by
going to hollow Ian Dash and advent.com
but yeah in any case in 50 minutes there
will be an update so uh oh we even uh
the site now um there's been a couple
updates ever since it launched we keep
on trying to improve it um now there's a
counter a Time counter that will tell
you so you don't have to look up the
time zone
um and then there's a function now you
don't have to refresh the page yourself
if even without refreshing the page
refreshes itself
um you don't have to refresh it by the
time the counter is at zero yeah that's
the workable of a Harvard Harvard person
yeah
you'll be so so skilled so talented
so overpowered and I can't do [\h__\h] what
do you mean you can't you you planned
this whole thing yes I'm the brains of
the operation
and you're the brains of this operation
fania
better I don't know about that
all right let's uh put the put the head
back so that we don't lose it all right
right what if we wear it what if we get
one more of the skulls and then we wear
it when no we need two more and then
just to mock the Wither we wear them
when we fight
yeah maybe I'll get confused oh yeah my
friend or a fool interesting
I never met whenever before you must be
friends or yeah if we can if we can be
the double-headed winner usually they
have three heads but if you stand
together like this oh yeah
I forgot about that
um
we're twins we're twinning okay guys so
thank you guys for watching good night
good day thank you bye bye and uh in
German we say our our Founders then
bye bye guys
foreign
[Music]