[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
Ki sorry for the wait
oh chunky
wonky that was me K
wa oh no I want to say k to myself oh no
I want to say to
myself wa I HT my cat too
yay KY chunky wony of the p
end of the
future dark magic yeah it's
magic oh yeah right normally I play this
with full screen
so how you guys doing where do I I think
ah
normally
normally well first of all I'm too big
yeah
uh left or right what was
it me yeah I think right cuz I was kind
of like
covering the
pictures eventually oh there's hair in
my
mouse I need big a waa H starting twist
TW twist starting tweet spell ah
indeed that has also been
forgotten doing
I you mean all
right I don't understand what you're
saying quote
starting
[Music]
now
okay okay okay okay okay did you sleep I
slept I oh my God I oh I slept quite
well in fear
quite undisturbed by
Kos but I had again nightmares at least
until the first time that I like woke up
in a more uh proper manner and then I
went back to sleep after going to Idol
meeting but in the nightmare I had one
of those nightmares where I was being
like chased and um like shot at again
what cha being chased was is more like
common of a nightmare for me but being
shot at was quite extreme uh with
a and I was trying to fly away flapping
my
arms uh it was it was quite um
terrifying and I realized eventually
that I'm in a
game and I would just have to like exit
the game to get out of this shitty
situation I found myself in many many
close to death or whatever situations um
but I kept on clicking on exit game on
the menu and this and that and I just
couldn't leave the game I just I just
couldn't uh it didn't work it didn't
work alt f4 didn't work nothing worked
and I was getting so so so so so
desperate
[Music]
[Laughter]
it was uh yeah no like being chased and
all that like a matter of life and death
situation is quite common for me but it
being a game is pretty rare I think I've
had it before but it's rare and then you
just can't find a way to leave the game
even though you know [\h__\h] [\h__\h] this is a
game but I don't know how to get out my
starting tweet didn't no it did it went
through I even see replies
yeah then I went back to sleep and then
I had better
dreams what was it I don't remember what
it
was but I did have better
[Music]
dreams what it was chased by an
indestructible tank what the [\h__\h] tank
aashi kiar was it
me funny how you only remember no no no
no like legit there's not nothing else
to remember a lot of the time it's just
yeah hi you
bu you were chased by a tornado in a
dream that could happen IRL too right
that's like more likely than being
chased by a
tank [\h__\h] that's the scary
reality next time you have to defeat
them all I I I don't know I I think in
this case I was able to kind of lowy fly
with a lot of effort but I couldn't use
anything to like fight
back wait that reminds
me yeah I'm like like lowkey remembering
my other dream that was really weird too
really weird really weird dreams pissing
me off
will you appear at Japan Expo in France
yeah yeah we just had an announcement
and I didn't know about it either until
the announcement
so uh at the moment who knows I don't
know um but nothing's nothing's certain
let's just say like that thanks for the
pinky thank
you whole life is coming to Paris party
party Paris
h no who knows who
knows you know I don't know can't really
say anything at this
point
H I would feel more comfortable not
dreaming anything at all
yeah Will W EUR truck to the
[Laughter]
event that's funny that's kind of
funny at least EU Bros going to win for
once yeah I mean honestly Japan Expo is
big
but uh and I've been there before a few
times
but
Europeans there are people from all
kinds of countries at Japan Expo but I
feel
like most of the time they don't really
go out of the way to travel to Japan
Expo just because it's like the biggest
European
convention I feel like
even doomi is getting like more of
a common
destination for non
Germans but Europeans to travel to like
you know there's
like there's so many more yeah well
maybe now now for sure like there will
be more people coming from outside of
France I suppose yeah but I think most
of the time
Europeans just go to the conventions
that are in their country which sounds
very reasonable especially for maybe
Americans where even in America if you
only go to American conventions even
that can mean you travel huge
distances but
um yeah in Europe it's not even such
huge distances but it's more of a
problem of like
language is completely different you can
go as a German even if you speak English
you can go to an Italian or a French
convention or Spanish convention and you
you don't have an idea about anything
that's going on in the panels they don't
speak English I mean maybe sometimes
with like uh International guests
there's like English panels and then you
will understand it too but generally
it's not built for you right
so that's the bigger problem I think
compared to America you may travel the
same distance but they speak a different
language there
you've been dreaming about the
anouncement te for the past I know I
know I remember that KP even had like
French KP even had uh hashtag going on
for me to bring me to to Japan Expo yo
that was like one two two years ago or
so it's like how a lot of doam guests
are German dub actors so if you don't
watch German dubs it's like well yeah
but that's like nothing to complain
about German conventions want to bring
you know German guests not not German
international guests too but they want
to bring guests that are like relevant
for the German crowd and yeah that's the
same for like whatever Italy Spain Etc
so I get it but it's like that explains
why traveling far two different country
for uh you you know do you understand
what I'm trying to say what's my point
do you get it what am I
saying wish I could go to Japan X is
already for the to weekend yeah when is
Japan
Expo Japan Expo
2024 it is it the same
weekend it's not no it's not it's like a
week after or
so it's a week after
right oh
anyway we should play the
game we should play little game let me
open
itop let's play the cutest game again
cutest Game of the
[Music]
Year ah the music
oh
man I'm already feeling
[Music]
happy this gamer will last as long as
yako are no no it
won't yeah I don't think so I don't my
controll
it there we
go these are my people
yes it's been a week my happy place
indeed Mommy
Maybe Mommy I mean pretty certainly
mommy but you never know there might be
a
Twist but probably mommy she's just like
dark her everything's like dark about
her her eyes her whole Aura is just
dark we need to bring her back to life
maybe then she's my
mommy this game is long to
underestimated not all she's she's a
she's quite she's a mommy right she
maybe not my mom mommy but she's a
mommy wait how am I going to where where
where am
I when am I
straight maybe like this
okay okay uh I did not have time to do
anything did I press the right button
yeah I did not have time to to to do
anything uh but somebody wrote something
to me that was helpful as a reminder of
what I wanted to
do let me check my likes really quickly
to find it again a yeah pikao thank you
for helping
me uh we'll start with trying to get
Carrick uh a pet that KCK yeah that we
failed getting before it's like a I
think it was a bigger version of one we
already have and then we're going to go
maybe find the rage horn because
peekaboo told me how to get the r horn
you're welcome thank you did you play
the whole game now I know who to listen
to when I'm looking for uh
advice yeah you did oh my god let's
go uh yeah let's go outside I think uh
we have no training
sessions
so what
I go outside touch some grass
yeah let's touch some grass new motion
mention what peekaboo is the new motion
for this game if that's what you're
saying uh so let's go to the lava C I
wonder if I'm strong enough though oh
heyo what are you guys doing here
camping they're literally camping
like you know what I mean in two
meanings two meanings of
camping you [\h__\h] get out of here
here's my turtle my turtle will destroy
you alongside this thing that we're
going to find the bigger version to in a
moment and oh yeah let's try this it's
hard to
see like I see this right and it's
like hard to see I wish I could like
move the camera a little bit or I wish
it would show me on the top right who
it's actually hitting like I want it to
like blink people
[Music]
people is this just like going to the
middle one or or is it going through the
for everybody I don't
know yeah I know who is hitting first
but I don't know
[Music]
who who are the others it's hard to see
from this
angle uh if I if I start with you okay
it only goes to the middle
this one mhm this one I think it always
hits three
people
[Music]
oh
speaker
speaka cutie
[Music]
PTI speaka wait hello I'm so cute I kept
on getting Spa's stream in my recomend
commended today but I had no time to
watch speaka
wait she did h no
[Music]
way okay wait if it's if it's speaker's
Heavenly cute voice I kind of want to
hear her sing like sleep talking next
time can you sing sleep talking you
maybe don't know it it's from my
album please sing sleep
talking some sometimes
I think it would be gorgeous can you
play it with your piano y y I love
people who can play the piano like how
do you do it you're so
crazy okay it was like this okay n
n this cute game would suit
[Music]
you
pink cute cute as hell
[Music]
well isn't today the first non- collab
public
stream since
okai for
me is is
it don't listen to what what do you
mean yeah this face with pinky oh we got
to talk a little bit about ofy then cuz
I I already talked a bit about it in my
member
stream
but got to talk more about it okay so
where is this where we are in the in the
cave if you continue exploring the lava
area and the cave at the left
side the lava
area
okay yeah listen listen to the waa
don't listen to whoever said that listen
to the
wa always listen to the wa talk
[Music]
yeah I mean it's it's interesting
ah 16 hours into the horns
shees thank
you thank you for coming by to ofai I
hope you had fun wait is it past here
peekaboo what I'm looking for did we
make you proud yo you you didn't make me
only proud you made me
like I don't know it's it's
crazy
because
I I I think I've been to way bigger
conven as a guest
right then ofai I've performed in front
of bigger crowds but somehow this time
it
felt like so real and it felt probably
because it was so crowded in such a
compact
way
uh it it it just felt so intense
yeah and everybody was so into it
everybody was so into it like
maybe if we performed in in bigger
venues before and often it like it
wasn't only me right maybe if it's like
a panel with other members and we just
sing one or two songs then a lot of the
fans are there for for the other panel
guest or whatever as well which is fine
you
know um
um and certainly in this case a lot of
the people a
lot certain amount of the people in the
ah in the audience
were not necessarily only there for me
right
I uh assume so woohoo wow
wow puzzle
lener but but it still felt
like it in that moment it felt like like
watching the footage of it how you guys
chanted it felt like you guys were all
there for
me and and and and it was just like a
big wow moment for me watching cuz like
I'm I'm going to be honest I didn't
really hear you guys at all I was just
imagining when I was actually performing
and then I watched the VOD and I was
like damn you guys were so loud and you
were singing along so much and oh my God
it made me so
happy it made me so happy and I it
didn't hit me this hard ever before I
think which is weird because I've been
at in in bigger venues and all that left
or right
peekaboo both is interesting cuz we
haven't explored
either left
okay I wouldn't know how to solve this
anyway
M angry Bulls room
ah 6,000 oh that's uh I think
[Music]
easy wait what
H how much how much how much xp did I go
into
this
huh what ah 109 okay that's uh not a
good
start and
that's to I'll die
[Music]
again we got a oh the the the puzzle ah
let's go to auto save
[Music]
point recently watching
small watching can change the whole ER
yeah
so yeah I would say the audience was a a
big reason for why
this hit me so hard and why why it was
so great in the first
place y'all it was amazing and I I was
really really nervous about
everything
because I I knew beforehand on the day
of the off guy as I told my members
already wow I knew that my 3D was going
to look really scuffed
because I didn't end up being able to
use the program that I thought I could
possibly use which would have improved
the live feed of the motion
capture um but with our Holo app and the
accents combined it it just looks really
[\h__\h] and it's kind of embarrassing to me
to perform like that but it's okay
uh after the
[Music]
rehearsal I I was like the most nervous
oh [\h__\h] I forgot
healing I was like the most nervous um
at the time of the rehearsal I think I
was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] and
then I
saw a few acts before me and they were
all such great singers I was like
well well
hopefully I can make up for the lack of
insane singing skills I'm not a bad
singer but not as good as them but I was
hoping I could make up for it with just
my my presents and my uh dance and
scuffed dance but
still and and I know I know how to Hype
up a crowd I think so
uh I suppose my
Charisma is something I've got going for
me
let's use the shield
Stone okay he's still I think instead of
half HP he does like a little bit more
than the third
[Music]
now which is okay we'll figure it
out I got the
rist yeah now let me Focus for a moment
uh do I need to heal I think I don't
need to heal do I but I could do a magic
Shield
or I can also heal a little
bit I can do both uh what was I going to
use I was going to
use just a small one no it just a small
one for
now fite this light up I have so much
energy in the room yeah there was so
much energy in the room man but can you
imagine
I I wrote this uh to oh my God I almost
said different uh I wrote this to Mint
um we had like a we were we were
chatting quite a bit over the weekend um
and she's really sweet and really
supportive let me lower the
bgm
[Music]
uh and I after the performance I asked
her like mint was this was this good was
it awkward was it was it okay and and
she told me yeah it was amazing and all
and I told her oh thank God because like
I felt really uh like if you think about
it the situation I was in is really
awkward
like it was like 7 a.m. right 700
a.m. but like basically middle of the
night for me cuz I stayed up the whole
night for this 700 a.m. Wawa in her
motion capture straps and headphones on
so obviously if you just stand next to
me you don't hear anything it's just
silence and I'm dancing awkwardly
singing
awkwardly in front of my computer
looking into my
monitor like the thought of that is so
awkward I don't even I didn't even hear
you guys which makes it more Awkward for
myself to but imagine you're just a
bystander standing next to me and
watching what I'm
doing someone's just like I'm just like
singing in front of my PC dancing and
flapping my flapping flaing my arms and
looking so
ridiculous but on the other side of the
world that translates into a really hype
like the absolute opposite a really hype
concert with cheer like without cheering
and and and actual music and everything
and and all that like it's crazy how the
yeah the magical V tubing and internet
and live streaming translate a really
awkward situation into the most hype
thing
ever basically imagine you know do you
know the remember the do you um without
music but with like squeaky sounds
parody video that I uploaded
it's kind of like
that oh
man uh yeah it just felt so
awkward but then I watched after that
what after I I felt like this awkward
about it I watched the Vlog the whole
thing and I was like okay I feel okay
now I feel good
now this was good oh he's okay of course
he's resistant yeah makes sense but he
still did a lot of damage wow
mint yeah mint sent me a lot of sneaky
pictures I mean I think she also
uploaded a lot of them
woohoo he had two turns Hey
yo
uh let's do a shield again because [\h__\h]
I can't heal uh-oh
uh-oh I can't heal just not with the
bird okay
okay wah brain uh proud need yeah strong
one like aged frog mhm oh that means I
can't attack that's
okay terrifying approach what was
that what was that enemy strength oh oh
it keeps on
increasing ah okay he buffed himself but
didn't attack okay okay
okay now we can use magic super
explosion which doesn't take up a turn
right
does it oh maybe it does the other one
maybe doesn't take over the turn cuz
this this one doesn't and I think the
arrow also
doesn't
um just in case Magic Shield and
this should be
fine
yeah we'll survive for
sure oh okay yeah we're fine I like to
cute
cute okay he's going to die
now let's just hit him with the
arrow than the red
chant gosh we got the rage horn
yay y the bull has rage quitted the
game with this we can make uh I think a
pretty powerful step
even though I think we just upgraded our
stuff recently at the end of last
episode should I fight
these why
[Music]
not thanks for the membership gift yay
thank you I appreciate it thank you
[Music]
oh this
one oh I thought it was optical illusion
I thought it was hitting
more Ah that's not bad that's not bad it
all you missed the item with the
bull
what
what I got the item what do you
[Music]
mean got go to work okay hope to see you
again
sometime have fun good
[Music]
luck okay they're actually not getting
another
turn nice
[Music]
let's do these ones
too I'm late don't worry about it I was
also a little bit late
today today I I used my running machine
again for the first time in a couple
days but the the days before when I
didn't use it I was still like
physically active I would say like I
felt quite uh exhausted doing some some
stuff like carrying heavy [\h__\h] and um
cleaning everything blah blah
blah
you
so I think not too bad also like off guy
off guy was quite the workout I was
quite sweaty after off
guy so I think I have a good excuse to
not use the treadmill on the offy day
right
you were able to rest after off guy yeah
when when I tried to sleep after the off
guy I noticed my body was like hey yo
why are you sleeping in the middle of
the
day I did get like still I I fixed my
sleep
schedule right after all good all good
we're back to
normal we're back to
[Music]
normal wait what why am I going back
he is this name different now no why did
I go back no no reason why I go went
back okay now let's go should I go over
there I don't even I don't even
understand
this this one this one's like whatever
let's just walk through
it how much did you run today not much I
didn't even have much
time I really didn't do much but um I I
I I ran more than I walked I would say
uh cuz I wanted to I I was like I got to
work on my stamina this summer is
crazy zigzag oh on top of
ah should I
kaboo should I go or is this for like
later cuz the game isn't telling us to
go there ah you also went there man
there so many of you guys went to offy
wow I'm
impressed should
I how does it work
again you could try but later would be
better oh okay good
good good good good
good uh sorry I'm like so distracted cuz
I'm trying to
tangent but yeah I
did uh some um training and some
cleaning before the stream and I
showered washed my hair you know I
trained my hair like this is a real
thing it actually works uh to only like
you only have to wash it like once a
week or so hey maybe even like if you
want to stretch it and you don't go
outside even after 1 and 1/2 weeks it's
still not really it doesn't look greasy
it doesn't really feel greasy
either I used to have my hair get greasy
and all that really
fast but once I started working from
home uh where's the other thing that I'm
looking for Carrick peekaboo do you know
where Carrick
was I'll continue in a moment I need to
know where to
go yeah if you wash it too much it it
overproduces oil and if you stop doing
that for a while the mines is it on the
right
side hey what you can do that
in in this m no that's a pudding cave
why do I keep on going back to the
pudding cave makes no
[Music]
sense let's teleport home and then
teleport from
there yeah so I used to like need to
wash my hair all the time like every
second day or so but once I started
working from
home
I I you know less need to look good and
like go outside and I started this so to
say
ritual of not washing my hair so often
and it's it's so worth it I think it
makes your hair healthier and uh you
save more water and and shampoo cost and
all that
[\h__\h] really recommend it really
recommend especially if you're a woman
and you got like long hair then I think
you want to aim for that because
you will have way less trouble with your
hair I
[Music]
think yeah overwatching not
good anything like you know your skin as
well not just your
hair where where is that
bastard I need to capture him H the tell
to go to the end of the mine okay okay
okay you're so smart I my brain is only
working at 20% capacity right
now I need your help tell me what to
[Music]
do yeah yeah yeah yeah dry skin if you
have skin problems you might want to
think about maybe doing less for your
skin rather than too much
uh oh combat log ah
tainted is it a tainted no it's Ki he's
not even on the list
though oh
kico kico no Kik kic he's not on the
list I thought this would be helpful
let's go to four I don't know
M it's a side area
H yeah I guess so did I already go like
too far it's the last
one cling bad sheets often yeah that's
probably something I should do more
often uh that
[Music]
is probably one thing I should do ah
here it
is m
M all right 3,800 okay was our problem
that we killed it last
time
[Music]
possibly
okay I guess I'm just not going to bring
out my pets or should I maybe in the
beginning it's okay
don't do too much damage
girl okay okay okay okay
okay oh no baby against mommy sorry
Mommy sorry
Mommy and we're already passed half of
its HP
dismiss dismiss
Miss
dismiss maybe just a free orb flame
Circle okay I feel like I'm playing
Pokemon like really carefully getting
the HP
down oh ah ah don't kill me
bro bro I had you
okay
bro I've been saying bro more often
these days don't know what's wrong with
me what is wrong with me
H do we have a only MP recovers over the
course of several turns I guess they
want you to use that Magic Shield more
often I guess I'm still
good I'm about to influence
bro yeah I don't think
[Music]
so
no he's not
ready which is concerning let's dismiss
my pet
one free orb flame
Circle we got to be careful
though he has four free free stacks of
fire okay how do we do this again magic
slab individual magic
circle mind control circle come on come
to me get into your
ball say a lot too not sure if I picked
it up from her hey that was
easy y now the small one can be replaced
by the big
one
easy time to go
home now we can continue with the main
story cuz we did those two
things
y oh wait wait a second let me check
what I need for the
weapon we want to how does this work
again
evolve ah okay ah oh my God I can really
already evolve it I just need another
dwarf Golem Essence
[Music]
easy
easy back hill Golem cave easy easy
should be
easy maybe I can even just uh
sleep and you get it for
me which one other oh wait it's not here
is
[Music]
it what was it
dwarf
uh what no
no I don't want to AutoCraft it undo
undo the
AutoCraft there we
go there it is dwarf Golem grass
[Music]
we just need a few
ones small smaller smaller
[Music]
Golem is it in the pudding
cave
no the is it is it is it is
it is it
here
uh left
cave there's just so many choices here
these
ones quick
hunt clear
crystal at least I can quick hunt them
okay we got
[Music]
one we got another one which is already
enough I think but let me just just get
a couple
[Music]
more we got three more
yay ah this one I have to fight normally
oh well what's north of your house
anyway don't think the game ever sent
you I feel like I went
[Music]
there all
right that should be
good a turtle was there no I don't think
they mean where the turtle
was there's like another path next to
the turtle
place okay let's
craft was it
the just make
two what did I make
two oh it's
happening w
we have more spikes and
stuff magic storm hurs a massive sphere
of concentrated magic at the enemy
causing a wide ARA explosion or is that
another one of those special attacks
let's go let's nourish it
again was it even worth nourishing it
beforehand if I then evolve it I guess
so but I'm I nourish it to the max I
think did I I hope so
[Music]
okay yeah without as long as you
have ah ah ah if it wasn't nourished
fully I when I evolved it I would have
had to add more
Stu or
what I don't
[Music]
know you have to n to evolve yeah seems
like it okay okay
[Music]
okay okay cool that makes us even
stronger I feel like we're already like
in terms of Staff we're like too
powerful we shouldn't already have that
one well maybe we should cuz the enemy
was pretty weak but I feel like I
wouldn't have it if I played it without
you guys um anything else we want to
craft
uh yummy yummy yummy
[Music]
yummy could make some
bombs but no already have a couple
[Music]
ah ooh I got to go fight
that thing again sometime if possible to
get another rage horn to make this
booster
[Music]
Circle but yeah it still seems like
pretty difficult to make anything out of
these besides the first one
[Music]
only your pets
what all these damage upgrades are
useless because later in game you only
need to defend since all enemies one
shot you what only your pets will do
damage
what
what no
[Music]
way pets hard heart carry in this game
what doesn't feel like it at all right
now you for
[Music]
real sticky bom
no it's not one guide peekaboo kind of
agrees with it you get more op Pets As
you progress in the story
[Music]
okay wait five
fork we can make it we don't have it
yet yeah oh my God
what Five
Forks five
fork let's go
[Music]
okay uh how do we put this on
again
[Music]
uh this
one yeah is a for fork lightning
Circle and we just replace the four fork
with the five fork right
e
okay then let's train and sleep
[Music]
once not even on Max on difficulty is
that true you will out damage your P I
would think so but we'll
see and what should we
train maybe
HP all about HP which is jumping I think
was it
jumping I didn't pay attention no it was
swimming how how's this work ah ah okay
just dodging oh swimming
[Music]
exercise do I stay up okay oh this
should be fine no
problem got to get that perfect bonus
easy easy easy
easy pieber is a better swimmer than
me so
sad perfect right right
or wait wait I was supposed to touch the
flags
no I thought I was supposed to dodge
everything and if you think about it
that way that I did it perfectly
[Music]
no I was wondering why the bar wasn't
going up but I just thought they they
determined at the end I don't know no
way
no no that's so
[Music]
dumb no
way no way I can't believe it that's
ridiculous um
man
no
unbelievable okay oh yeah we're still
human I just
realized and where where does the story
want me to go right now
[Music]
uh is this my main quest right
now seems like it right investigate a
Rua temple location hint a temple no
okay
[Music]
yeah we've been there before I guess now
we're going to go
[Music]
further which way though which
way should we
teleport to a like where do we where do
we go
[Music]
which
way oh I can quick hunt
them hey
yo okay that's good what was this
[Music]
again toss a
coin toss a coin to you Witcher
[Music]
plenty a valley was it a valley of
planty toso coin to oh let let's look at
the oh yeah right what do you
eat what do you
eat I would think I don't have it yet
[Laughter]
the last one I choose let's
go tail sting Fire's electrical energy
what are you a Monteray what the [\h__\h]
okay cool wait let's give him one
more and another one yay maximum
affinity
coolo beig
[Music]
can you go there
thanks what
now wait never mind we can just jump now
what what
[Music]
what oh crabs Herman
crabs right let me find
them did we find no we didn't fight them
before W look at the what the [\h__\h] is
that in the back some
Dragon
[\h__\h] let's
go let's [\h__\h] go let's [\h__\h] go
let's [\h__\h] go let's [\h__\h] go yeah
oh oh yeah okay no problem
uh I guess it costs a lot to summon the
big one
[Music]
w wow
wow wow e
Superion
sheh more SM
hero and I want to use I want to try the
five fork lightning circle on
you
wow nice that's pretty
[Music]
strong he did 338 damage versus his big
one that did a
th let's go
looking crap W what's wrong with
him he's
beautiful he's beautiful have you never
seen a hermit crab before and Y what is
this elf and ring a bracelet that makes
you slightly lighter when warn oh M
interesting is that how I get over
there or do I get faster in
general what does that
mean slightly lighter
[Music]
uh aha uh more
agility how do I get over
there no access to the water here
[Music]
I don't have a way to get into the water
I
think not from there the dragon is too
strong I thought
so yeah we got to go
here of
course I'm ready ready for what
[Music]
is
this
insides that's that's funny because that
sounds like something I would say like
it's weird phrasing somehow is it not
also in Japanese just said I'm going to
throw
up or it's the pp I yeah makes
[Music]
sense no
pulp which sounds almost like
Papa which probably is what where that
comes from that word is it no maybe
not or is
it
Papa maybe it
is is Spanish we say papa it does oh
well there you go huh
[Music]
I don't want to go
back I got to grow up
[Music]
encro M
Ribbit
[Music]
Ribbit and
croan e
[Music]
memories of the past I tried again to
remember what I saw at the great Gates
of the auroraa temple I was scared but I
pushed through in the memory the pope
was taking power from my mother the
power must have come from the aimard
amulet
I need to tell
Anna let's go to
[Music]
Anna I guess we go home
first yeah for sure that's a pope yeah
looks very
popy Dopey
popy
uh uh uh an
uh uh wait uh teleportation
to mine entrance yep yep yep I remember
I remember on my roof no no no no you
might think
so it's not that
simple that is just my imagination and
yours too
apparently at least we share the same
kind of
weird oh
there's pie but there's no mama
[Music]
why oh isn't that what we saw last time
where we participated
[Music]
you're jealous to being almost killed by
the
[Music]
dude igned
again thanks for the
[Music]
MCE
for every time I hear Justice I want to
say
Jud but with
[Music]
Justice wish
do you know how to make
pie it's been a month already oh wait
are you kind of a newcomer welcome thank
you new Warriors have started to appear
in lak they might attack Anna when they
first see her I must find
Anna uh location laak
Forest
uh uh where is that again is it
here that's the
village
oh oh now she changes automatically good
good good good good good maybe I can get
there for here hey
yo are they like getting rid of the
barrier oh I can just walk
through
he ha found the
forest and
[Music]
oh it's him
again no don't jump
Alfredo you and me we can be amazing
together chicken
alfredo no really
jumped
alred it's not deep enough you can
literally stand in
it oh well yeah the armor is definitely
a oh help what do you what you expect
what you
expect mommy I'm also looking for my
mommy
same where the [\h__\h] did she get the
fishing pole
from what the
hell because I have a mission
I want to make chicken
[Music]
alfredo and that you did
I'm
[Music]
don't make it wor
pberry try to kill
himself give him a break man give him
some
cake
[Music]
am
foree girl
[Music]
well by the way I already know noticed
this in the previous stream but I didn't
want to like bring it up cuz I thought
maybe if I restart the game it's fixed
but do you see the effects of when I
walk I feel like it's like a wet effect
but it's always happening I don't know
if this has been there since the
beginning if it's on
purpose you see
[Music]
it doesn't matter
though I think it's grass but it's white
it looks
like it also happens on the bridge so I
feel like it's just like a
bug
yeah it's like
everywhere I think it's water being
kicked up but it's just continued to
stay there but whatever uh what find
Anna still uh where could she
be
Anna does this it's still a forest so
she could be here
right oh this one's so big big
fight you guys remember how I uh told
you in the member
stream now I'm telling you uh separately
in the public stream but I talked about
it before that I moved like twice
without really talking about it
and after I moved like that first
time it was like right after I I lived
there for like a year or so
approximately right and I had curtains
back then and then I moved and I was
like man I just recently more or less
recently installed like had my friends
help me install curtains now I feel bad
if I asked them again so I like kept on
waiting especially cuz I lived in a
place where I was like really high up
and I what didn't feel like I really
needed curtains anyway so I just lived
without curtains for like 1 and 1 half
years or even
two and
even now the past months I didn't have
curtains either and I felt like damn I
really need curtains now I have finally
I have finally have curtains and it's
not just you know the good thing is not
just
that people can't see me anymore let's
go but I was using um what do you call
the the things that go down that are not
[Music]
curtains what do you call that
again in English blinds yeah I was using
blinds but I wanted curtains right I
just felt bad to ask for help cuz it was
a pain in the ass last time I did it in
the first place that I lived
in what the hell is
this but now I finally had it done uh
two days ago two days ago yes no yeah
yeah two days ago on my day off had my
friend come over and help me uh not
everywhere not everywhere there's
curtains yet cuz it takes so much time
we did curtains and we did shelves
it's a lot of work man especially cuz
like the curtains got to go on walls
that are really [\h__\h] thick
concrete it's really bad it's so loud
and so thick okay I don't think I'm
supposed to be here
oh yeah know
[Music]
okay are you telling me to go back
yeah yeah drilling into concrete it was
fun huh very fun last time we kind of
failed and then my friend was like I'm
going to bring like a better drill so
that we can get through better and even
then it was kind of
rough oh these are
weak aim heart's barrier
he that might be a
[Music]
what never
mind never
mind I don't think I was supposed to
fight
them um damn where do I
go but yeah not just like the the lack
of visibility to the outside that I'm
celebrating but it looks so pretty
because um I've been like trying to
decorate
my uh living room to be like you know
green gold dark green and gold and you
know partially like black gray and so on
oh we're watching this again
[Music]
and and I had these uh dark green
curtains really thick ones laying around
ever since the first time I moved hoping
to use them again
sometime and they have this like
uh what do you call that fabric that
looks really
[Music]
soft velvet yeah they have this velvet
look
really really beautiful curtains so I
bought golden curtain
rails double curtain rails and I
realized oh just buying the instead of
the actual rails buying just like the
the the
poles will make the installation so much
easier so I went with the poles golden
curtain po
with fancy ends to
[Music]
it yeah art de go let's go Aro and so
the the golden curtain poles they have
these um velvet dark H dark green long
curtains on them now and and some of
course some like light white uh little
bit sefr curtains behind them and it
just looks so much better now every
everything my my living room is just ah
it feels like it's all coming together
beautifully I love
it
m brass gold or gold gold M just gold
gold I I don't know mostly the golds
that I have in that room are yeah just
like basic gold
gold obviously not real gold where the
[\h__\h] are this where's Anna Let Me fight
these maybe behind
here maybe behind
here wao what that's how this works oh
how
fun you see this
guys oh okay but now it only hit
free
interesting
interesting geometry let me look at this
[Music]
again
uh another time where I wish I could
see it from a different angle okay with
this one it shows different
lines let's see this again okay it only
hits him
huh now maybe I don't like this Fork so
much interesting
though yeah it looked like it would hit
everything kind
of wait one second let me
[Music]
boom
head yeah it's like a brightish gold
yeah it looks so pretty it made me so
happy once it was finally up and and and
we put up some
shelves um oh hello did we fight you
before yeah we put up some
shelves above the sofa like wall shelves
wall shelves are so good they save so
much space and they look so
clean when they're put on the wall
directly ah so nice I have so much more
space to put things
on cuz I was running out of space oh
there it
is I was running out of space but that's
where we came from but I guess it wasn't
triggered because yeah that's where we
came
[Music]
from now we're not done and we have like
uh yeah a few more curtain uh poles to
attach the to the wall and like two more
little
shelves yeah I did Alfredo I guess okay
yeah you got to do him and then you got
to go back so I came from the wrong
direction I suppose
[Music]
but I just wanted to say it's so nice to
have curtains again for the first time
in like two
years oh it ties the room together so
nicely like it's it finishes the room
especially if it's the last thing to be
put
up oh man I want more curtains I need to
finish the rest when I can blinds are
kind of bland so I get you it's not just
that it's like for my blinds it's either
up or down but if I have like at least
the the the seethrough
curtains closed then I can have privacy
while still letting in some light and
that's kind of what I I needed yeah I
would feel weird not having curtains for
two years yeah
um it's yeah like I said I don't I
didn't really need it in that previous
apartment because I was not visible to
others I was up quite high and uh there
nobody could see
me thank God it was very reflective
anyway how did the Sun that always wake
you up uh yeah that's something that
bothered me too oh I remember actually
because I I I I I didn't feel like
asking friends for help with curtains
again because it was such a pain in the
ass before but I really wanted to be
able to darken my rooms I uh at some
point I bought you know those like
really weak poles that you can extend
the rods and and you don't like uh drill
it into the wall you just like hope it
holds up by the
sheer like yeah a tension rod to sheer
tension yeah like a shower curtain yeah
yeah yeah like a shower curtain one but
it was actually supposed to be for like
kitchen windows or so for like really
really thin lightweight curtains and I I
thought I hoped it would
help so I put those up at least in
my yeah in my bedroom and in my working
room and I but my curtains my curtains
were really heavy because they were
really thick ones and it would hold up
until you moved the curtain then the
tension rod would often just fall down
and yeah it it didn't work well at all
it didn't work well at all but I'm not
doing it this time this time I'm getting
everything done nicely yeah and I'm not
waiting like a whole year to finalize
and feel
comfortable with my living
space and it really changes a lot living
in a half finished Place versus living
in a pretty much like finalized
Place
yeah makes me happy makes me happy I
want to put a lot of stuff on my shelves
but I bought a lot of boxes from Ika I
think they're going to come tomorrow and
I just wanted some boxes so that I can
uh so that it looks a little bit more
clean going to put them up the shelves
yeah yeah many many boxes I spent oh my
God I spent like 130 bucks or so on like
boxes any kind of boxes more happiness
please
yes finally a correct pronunciation did
I say Ikea Well normally I would say
Ika normally I would say that
EA yes cuz is
correct I would think so
oh oh
I love the glow on
that actually
cool
[Music]
I let's
go wo it's a hot air balloon now
what explosion
[Music]
witch
yeah sorry girl I can't hear you so well
from up there can you speak louder the
bgm is really loud
too who's playing the bgm so loudly hey
where are the speakers we're trying to
have a conversation
here imagine your whole life just having
constant bgm going imagine being a a
game character always having to listen
to
this be
funny
funny that's one thing they have to deal
with this these game characters can you
imagine living a life like this damn
girl you live like
this uh someone CL free to two
[Music]
W music is constant PGM you mean wa on
demand at least you know you're in
trouble when the yeah right and I also
will know when I'm okay yeah this is
pretty shitty ah like what is this angle
I can't see who it's going to
hit I could guess
but
uh like
um wait now I see wait actually I'm so
dumb wait wait did we never did I never
notice the question
marks it's not really question marks
it's it's
her wait there icons now were they
always there
[Music]
I never noticed they were glitched
before
ah yeah that's what you guys meant with
the UI being glitched why is it not
glitched today h maybe because I'm
playing full screen
today was I not playing oh no because
the game actually I think it actually
started on the right screen I didn't
switch it to a different monitor yeah it
was misaligned okay you can't be you
can't be Kiana dot dot now I know you
wanted to be like Kiana dot dot why the
[\h__\h] did you not know this until now it
was always there but you guys also have
been telling me it was
[Music]
misaligned okay well only
two I wonder if it hits less people is
the damage it could
do like compared to five people will it
then be contained within these two
people
h i
wonder no change so like if I'm hitting
less targets it's not worth it is that
what you're
[Music]
saying oh I can choose who she's
bombarding
uh
maybe Justice or
Justice
nice you can yeah can
focus can I not the not the Fireballs I
[Music]
mean I mean for example the the Thunder
I should heal a little
[Music]
bit Yeah the the the the the the Archer
I still have to destroy his Tower right
but when
I shoot him it shoots his Tower first
but it doesn't show us how much HP the
tower has
right cuz he's I hit him twice and he
he's still at 150 but I think it's
hitting the tower I just don't know I
don't know I don't
know how much it's
doing hidden
HP
man it's more targets the better usually
yeah
Thunder slunder what are we
doing good
[Music]
damage very
nice liia
down very
good only Justice is stand in what is
that true ni your name why is your name
Justice you sounds so
dumb
ah who who dropped that
there
Anna I guess Ka
what if Anna is Ka have we ever seen Kaa
and Anna in the same place eh
[Music]
illusion magic or more
like will all make
sense
[Music]
eventually
for
[Music]
fore for
you knew it then why why did we like get
out of it so in a such unstylish way
it looked more like you guys
[Music]
fell you can't boss pberry
around pberry is a woman of her
[Music]
own
Mommy is she peeing onto the
stone Maybe Mommy was poppy after
all
[Music]
Mama pie
ingredients don't think I think she got
[Music]
lost
for okay that
[Music]
b fore
look at the gorilla sleeping peacefully
in the
[Applause]
back
monkey
a can we go somewhere else to have our
fight I don't want to disturb this happy
monkey
[Music]
for
Fore
[Music]
for She's So Mean
easy yes point it out pberry roast her
[Music]
harder oh
I got stronger but you're the same so
you suck I'm amazing you just suck you
keep on
[Music]
sucking don't worry I got
plenty maybe she'll really be sitting on
my house roof for now from now on yeah
let's
go but my house is kind of
[Music]
small wit houses small smaller witch
houses why
[Music]
all right we have said it we have
pointed out that we think we are her
daughter what's going to be her reaction
[Music]
M
but it's not replaced it's just us is it
not
[Music]
a mommy sorry Mommy sorry Mommy sorry
Mommy for real for real man the title is
so
accurate oh bye
baby hi
bir do
something a
man
[Music]
a bye oh she
came sorry
daughter
[Music]
Mommy
foree
[Music]
foreign
speech no
[Music]
hug by
wait you're the one covered in scars not
[Music]
us Pie's head is so
huge foree
[Music]
but what if she is mle like we don't
have proof that she's
not right there's still a
[Music]
possibility maybe they'll still reveal
it at the end and for now they're just
like going to make us think
bondage that we just have uh you know a
fake mom now I don't know
ah look how happy she
[Music]
is
for it was quick
[Music]
yeah but why don't we move in
there fore
[Music]
did even the bird is nice to
us feeling bad probably
[Music]
put a pillow under my arms maybe that's
going to help with
the like I've
noticed the past
weeks
good um that my arms get really sore
from putting them resting them on the
armrest
ionically
ironically the fck
[Music]
pillow why armrest so [\h__\h] for resting
your arms
[Music]
I had one job yeah no not
slouching not
slouching sometimes
[Music]
is
name I don't know like a Turkish name or
[Music]
so Banana shap W actually doesn't sound
too bad and banana
[Music]
is Turkish for wait is it oh it
is
wait that's so
funny I feel like
as we I hear that kind of like accent uh
a lot in Austria you know so and I hear
names like that a lot in Austria so when
I say it like also
it just sounds so Turkish to me no way
it actually
was did you forget about our Narnia
watch I mean no
but did the movie ever tell us that that
was like a a Turkish name I don't think
so L is like bro uhhuh really
[Music]
the movie Never tells right yeah we
didn't know I didn't
know Turkish Delights oh I wanted to
tell you when I flew to Thailand I flew
through uh asemble right I told
you there was I went into the into the
business Lounge right and they had a lot
of nice food right I didn't eat any of
the main dishes but I I was looking I
went I walked so far to finally find the
like sweets
desserts and they had a lot of different
Turkish Delights and I I think i' at
some point in my life had a Turkish
delight before but this one had like so
many different ones I wouldn't even be
able to tell you which one's which um
Turkish delight and um uh uh baklava
different kinds of Bak laava I guess
there's a lot of different ones of that
too not just the one that I would think
of
normally I tried a lot and I must say
there's for me personally it's very HIIT
or
Miss but very
interesting I think mostly the the Bak
laava was very Hit or Miss for me cuz I
don't know maybe it wasn't all
Baka is actually Greek what what for
real M what does it taste like a lot of
them are very nutty and honey
honey uh based I
think
yeah I don't know some of them I like
some of them were like very very
me but they had so much choices nice to
give a lot of different things a
try hi honey oh
I'm kind of glad that that died
off thank God actually you remember
there was a time where you say literally
nothing and everybody's like hi honey
and and make you say
[Music]
it
[Laughter]
yeah uh my father would never
die did anyway power to protect it
doesn't matter if I'm not mle because
Anna has cap CED me as your new daughter
anyway a oh captured accepted sorry uh
we're not in pal world we can't capture
humans or witches I protect her from now
on I should go to meet aand at a r
Temple and ask him how to increase the
power of the blessing uh oh try creating
a magic circle five orb flame
Circle well I just created Five orb
Thunder Circle I don't know if I can
make the flame
[Music]
Circle um uh what would I
need this one I remember we got before
and this one I guess I used up to many
uh
peekaboo where do I go for this one
again is it the cave to my
left flock fly oh yeah flock
fly ah the swamp
okay okay okay
okay okay wait do I have a teleportation
point I guess
not
[Music]
no just SW okay to the right but like
the closest right and I got to go
on
[Music]
you like these
the the FL flame pouch was that from uh
like a big frog not just the random
small ones
right wait am I in the right place I
wait now I remember it was ah not you
not you not you
um wait let
me what do they drop I wish it would
show the big one yeah
I wish it would show what they
drop but it
[Music]
shows here right ahuh
ahuh what was the other thing that we
needed this one ah okay for this one
I'll have to go into the fire
cave but where's the big frog
[Music]
oh I can't I don't
know
where's you got to let me
through oh we're already on the other
side well I'll fight you
anyway
M
aha 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4
[Music]
5 wow okay
cool that was neat we're back where the
piranas are beautiful uh come come here
come here let me ride you can we just
like can I can I run faster
somehow hey hey I don't need it I don't
well that was easy I didn't need
[Music]
anything
s fly a
FL take this maybe not worth it but
whatever oh wait he dies so fast let's
[Music]
go he dies so fast a to the
yo H speaking of a to the yo wait did I
get the item do you guys remember on
Twitter we saw something I retweeted
[Music]
oo I got it okay
we could go just straight
home we're getting a Yakuza live action
and yeah yeah yeah people pointed out
there were Yakuza live action shows
before but I think this one will be like
way more ambitious and and like you know
High budget and more like you know maybe
maybe cuz Amazon is making it
so I think it's going to be good
the question is just when the hell is
that going to come out 2025
2026 when they announce it now I guess
it could still take a long
time oh wait did it say
October oh I guess it did say October
well
then that is so
[Music]
soon all right I hope it's going to be
good
man I'll have so much to watch in the
summer
finally what's the first thing that's
coming
out what will be the first
thing October is in the fall yeah that's
so
soon fire stone
House of the dragon two two weeks for
real oh finally man I I remember when I
finished watching the first season and
they were like uh next season in like
two [\h__\h] years I was like bro am I
even going to be alive in two [\h__\h]
years how the [\h__\h] can you make me wait
so
[Music]
long man
like this is going to be the longest
weight of my whole [\h__\h] life man
stop a little dramatic no very
realistic I'll respawn
[Music]
yeah it is really long it really is
and I I think I had the sameish feeling
for rings of power and Wheel of Time all
of them One
Piece One Piece
[Music]
why going to be eight gr episodes eight
episode and wait they release what one
per week how did they do it I don't
remember one per
week is it one per week
we need twopiece yeah [\h__\h]
man every
[Music]
Sunday yeah I think
um in
Austria it's going to be like a little
bit delayed
right and I don't even remember remember
what streaming service any is is there
any austrians here who
know what streaming service
was I think I have
to buy it or so I don't
know we don't have
HBO bro guys America is not the only
country in the world Americans be like
HBO
du [\h__\h]
HBO HBO is not like all over the world
[Music]
oh is it Sky again oh
man [\h__\h] Sky I don't have
Sky I've been watching a lot of videos
these past days um I I don't watch the
Jimmy Kimmel show but um I've been
getting a lot of I got one
recommendation and now I get a million
of them of those videos where Jimmy
kimel's team interviews people on the
street uh of like what is it Hollywood I
don't know
um where they ask like Americans they
stop them and they give them like stuff
like for example they show a world map
of the whole world right and they ask
like name any
country any
country and they some of them couldn't
even find America but some of them would
even say like Russia is America or
[Music]
so it's so so so so so embarrassing and
I don't worry I don't think I don't
think you all are like this I can't even
believe it I can't I could not
imagine and then uh one time in one of
the interviews they're like okay name
any book any
book nobody could answer but of course
they only cut the ones into the show
that were funny and didn't have an
answer of course right
right um stuff like that or or oh yeah
yeah yeah the funniest things are when
they go in like uh te telling them about
the most
ridiculous unlikely news they make up
some news and they ask them did you hear
about this and everybody's like yeah
yeah yeah I totally heard it so for
example one of them is like um so
president so and so uh and a
certain northly
country that shall not be named you can
guess have made a pack and that certain
norly northly country is now part of the
us as its
51st state or whatever and have you
heard of this what do you think about it
and and they're like oh yeah yeah I
heard about it and and it's it's not
cool and blah blah blah they believe
it and what
a certain northly country in in Asia
guys is what I'm talking about it's so
nonsense not
Canada yeah it's just like why why not
just not just stuff like that but like
really the most ridiculous things and
these people will just pretend that they
heard the news and then they ask like
how did you where did you hear this and
who did you watch the news with and
they're like oh yeah yeah I think uh I
think I just heard it on the radio or oh
yeah I watched it like yesterday uh on
the TV with my with my little brother or
whatever like they even do you actually
think you like are you gaslighting
yourself or are you just making things
up for the sake of being interviewed and
wanting to seem like you're up to date
with things I would say so right but
like don't you feel so dump for
pretending just say no I didn't hear
about this are you for real
it's so funny
though why are they lying bro and then
there's some some cute ones some funny
ones for
example uh there's
like there's like uh fathers and there
Sons or daughters and they're like they
ask the father if they know anything
about their children like their birthday
or their schools teachers or their uh
middle no their eye color even one
father didn't know his daughter's eye
color no I don't think they're scripted
maybe some of them I don't know but I
don't no I don't think they're scripted
I just think they they deliberately
choose the worst of the worst ones which
are just the funniest ones no no they're
so
realistic no there's no way the dads
yeah the dads don't know anything the
dads don't know [\h__\h] that's just
realistic
that is just realistic
though and then at at some point um they
asked the mother like basically the same
questions that the mother knows
everything about the
[Music]
kids no no I don't believe
you whatever even if it's scripted I
feel like it's a some of it is a a a
realistic rep
presentation of what these people would
say most like
nrip well of course like the way they
relay like their news and whatever and
their jokes interviews prescripted but
those straet interviews they they seem
really
real they seem really
[Music]
real no I said the i i the uh like some
of them are really
[Music]
like when I see them I'm like nah
there's no way that you guys are like
you don't know this stuff like no way
right I I am not thinking after watching
these things
that you guys wouldn't know where to
place like I don't know Australia on the
map like point at Australia and be like
is this
Africa I would hope so I mean you tell
me do you think do you think that every
American can tell you all kinds of
random countries and continents of the
world and and show you on the on the map
where it
is do we no right
yeah so to a certain extent it is
realistic I would hope that you would
know where Australia is though I would
hope now Australia for sure you got to
know
[Music]
right sorry I've been tanging and not
attacking Iris didn't know where
Australia is oh no okay wow I name a
country
[Music]
H I know
countries the number one
country is the
[Music]
waa then name one make one well of
course I can name I can name many
countries Greece Spain Italy Australia
Japan China Singapore
Philippines Canada I can name a million
ones turkey you want more you want more
wao whoo whoo
whoo quick name five
women I'm just going to name whole life
members Malaysia and
champ I I I I didn't save one country so
I totally forgot about their existence
[Music]
man
funny but watching them be so unable to
name any countries it really made me
wonder if I showed
a map of the world to our
beloved
American uh or North American and
Japanese
members will they be able to answer a
lot
or I
mean no gooda I actually think she will
not suck at it
you know what we're going to kill that
thing
again oh it's a it's almost
back and I honestly think I didn't
mention ID members because I think they
would be pretty good at
geography I think they would
be something tells
me they would be pretty decent at
geography just don't think about
kobble don't even think about kobble
my what your
rope don't don't don't don't mention
that that is a special
case
[Music]
uh maybe maybe one
day you know how gooda did this IU
smarted than a fifth grader show that
she like put
together maybe one day I'll do something
like
that and I'll it it will be mostly like
geography
based had a question like that to whole
talk oh hello uh a geography question to
hold talk name any
country they're just going to say their
own country name one besides that
uh
uh I oh you know what I should do oh
okay I have a good one I have a good one
I should give them a map of the world or
maybe do them a favor and give them a
map of Europe and have them point at
wherever they think Austria
is oh that's going to be so sad but it's
okay I wouldn't even it's Austria is
small and there's a lot of countries in
Europe I don't I don't really expect any
non-european to know to like be able to
place it on a map but it would be cool
if you could at least have the knowledge
that uh Austria is in Europe
and that it exists and maybe even though
it's Capital cuz it's it's pretty famous
you just got to put one I I think just
many people know the word Austria and
the word Vienna but uh maybe they don't
automatically put it together you know
they they think of it as two separate
like words I don't know that have no
connection with it I don't know
[Music]
I need to make a number map of America
yes see I don't I don't you know I don't
know anything about the states I don't
know your States I don't know where they
are um so wait I should have [\h__\h] I
should have I'm so
distracted I should have I should have
brought out my pets Oster is my favorite
city like there's nothing
[Music]
embarrassing
about not being able to
place Austria on a map if you're not
European that's I wouldn't say that that
is something to be embarrassed about
it's just funny because if you're
talking to an Austrian if you're working
with an Austrian like
me then I I want to know if you know I
want to know if you know where I I am do
you know where I
live give it a
try I want you to give it a try maybe
you know just to get to know me more
maybe that's the
purpose have you understand where I'm
from
and and at the same time you can learn
something
new isn't that that
[Music]
wonderful I know it's fire resistance I
just don't really have much more
powerful things I think the Thunder
attack is not going to be so
efficient on its
own with with just one
enemy could be wrong but I don't
know setting myself up for this no I
wouldn't be disappointed I would just
laugh and be like okay now you know now
you know and now you can visit me now
that you know where I
am you're always welcome to come visit
me you can make no more excuses cuz now
you know where I am did I get the item
again I would hope so did I get what I
wanted anyway yeah I think
so answering all of my questions
now Austria really I don't expect people
to know
because we're so small and we don't have
like such a memorable shape like Italy
for
example and yeah I wouldn't be mad if
you don't know where Austria is but you
should at least know that Austria is not
Australia the boot yes the boot
beautiful city thank
you also shaped like a chicken leg no I
always say it's shaped like a
schnitzel I am proud of my snitel shaped
country
oh okay let's go home let's try to be a
little bit more focused and productive
that's the first hurdle yep I knew austa
because of soccer are you sure we are
one of the most
insignificant
participants so much so that we are
often not participants at
all in like soccer leagues and stuff m
[Music]
we're always missing in the
party FB
FB we are in the EM this time when's the
[Music]
EM o o
let's get more buff this time this time
I want to nail
this okay I got to get the flags
right
oh okay number two ow [\h__\h] no what wait
what's going
on I dodged so perfectly last time
it's
okay no I missed
no
[Applause]
no I'm never doing this one again never
again I'm setting myself up for
failure who saw that
all who s that all
[Music]
I was going to craft something was I
a I remember this one whoa suddenly I
have 65
shees sheo
[Music]
mhm MH
MH
[Music]
okay I don't know bring me whatever
what I wasn't [\h__\h] talking America I was
I was giving you the benefit of the DB
saying that was really funny but I don't
believe you guys are that incapable of
naming countries and
stuff I'm giving you the benefit of the
doubt I'm just saying for sure there are
people like that I believe it it's JK
okay okay it's JK m m mwah mAh
you're too
[Laughter]
kind I'm somewhat capable I believe you
I think the people who are watching my
stream are generally just by I don't
know being here you guys seem smarter
than the
average
person
[Music]
there I might be wrong but I think you
are I think also also just by watching
me you would know more about Europe by
now and and you would be able to name a
few more country maybe you learned more
for watching
me you definitely know more about
Austria since watching me than before
watching
me so I made you smarter smart baby
smart South Island uh what where
where are we
going
[Music]
down down
here believe in yourself chickens with
ason find ason but they're not s they
would say aru Temple if
they thought he was here ah I walked
right in his ass
Ohan you surprised
[Music]
me didn't know what a dandle was before
let's go I told you
something dandle dandle is one of the
cutest traditional outfits to exist so
you better know
[Music]
it might be lying to you
stop saying as like
this
what is that not how he would say his
own
name the sharks sharks are roaming
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
yeah you can't take down this Lion and
the witch
together no
chance spr was their St War
too oh in your
ass this setup makes me think I was
supposed to arrive from the temple the
Temple's
[Music]
insides let's do
it what a question about NE they just
used the German
[Music]
word interesting
she's scared of
me wait my pet still behind
him staring at his ass
[Music]
why can we go into the ship
too I have to talk to
I have to talk
to go away go away now go
away
okay my beautiful lion he's so
[Music]
pretty yeah they are kind of reasonable
for a
change I'm surprised we didn't have a
fights just
now oh yes the other day I was nearly
killed by a very strong
Warrior isn't that fun
[Music]
piece of cake for me or should I say
piece of
[Music]
pie yeah she's so
chirpy for pie Berry it was just another
Tuesday so
[Music]
true
wow wow
[Music]
really wait which garden statue the one
where I died in front of those
free thingies the aim heart thingy
[Music]
okay I do wonder what that was Temple
trial I must pass a trial to develop
our's blessing into the form of a
lightning bolt I need to find the
ceiling Stone in the East wing of the
Arora Temple and request a trial
East
okay let's
go oh it's even showing
me the
direction yeah I knew I was going to I
was going to go here I knew it
[Music]
oh maybe Channel some Channel some magic
into it try to hit it with our funer
whatever oh never mind it
[Music]
worked ah
oh and he's not one for a small
talk no time to waste oh
7,000 let's do Shield
Stone wow a little bit scared of what
this uh alua has to
offer let's bring out the turtle and the
big boy
[Music]
I wonder
should flame orb Circle thingy let's
go
o oh
easy n that's no
problem oh oh yeah you took a lot of MP
let's do something about
[Music]
it let's take this Power
Stone oh easy I got a crital we got a
freaking
crit ah he missed let's go counter
attack
[Music]
my pets didn't even attack I feel like
well they probably did but it felt like
they
didn't I might be too strong for this
[Music]
whoa it's
beautiful now maybe you know how I joked
before about how we're able to use an
arrow and a bow to shoot down those
bunnies in close to our home but we
can't use it in the
battle so maybe now we're able to do it
besides the aru's arrow attack so like
more
often like an actual
weapon I changed my class into Archer no
more which from today onwards I am an
Archer I had to pay
real money in the cash shop to buy a
class changing
scroll I think in many mm RPGs you kind
of have to pay for
that range
Master that's range Master's not
Archer is
it I'm Archer class now yeah Arcane
Archer
that's a thing in other
games oh that's so cool that sounds
really
cool her voice yeah I feel like the
other characters have better voices like
even the cuty
[Music]
ones DD has a Mystic oh really in DD oh
Nar
[Music]
not rise up voice
beloved
oh oh wow a r lightning bolt AR
lightning Bol has been added the old AR
ARA has had its cool down reduced and
its power increased oh so we can use it
earlier now
okay that's me after getting off of my
treadmill my legs just don't work
anymore
[Music]
me black
Joe I get it that's how I feel am
[Music]
yay is literally what that
said it translated to that at least
trust
me uh okay I have to find
again oh he's right there
[Music]
hiya my as
Li I think I know where it is
[Music]
well we got to try we wake him up
yeah yeah the lion PL mhm we already
stumbled into
[Music]
it hell no he's not going to join me he
likes living in freaking Australia
[Music]
H I'll think about
it oh more lands
[Music]
they seem pretty genuine about
it
okay okay what's first a
shipwreck
oh oh that's
funny am I
back the moment I said like I was
looking at the chat and I was feeling
like oh it's kind of dead I was like
guys are you dead and that very moment
after I said that I saw my OBS kind of
dying losing its connection for a
moment I manifested it yeah I I killed
you
no we both died if we die we die
together it seems
asked me to keep an eye on Livia because
he can't leave the temple himself liia
seems to have gone to a ship break on AR
okay so we have to do that
first oie
[Music]
doie here my swimming practice is paying
off just not in
the in the training mini game sadly
[Music]
there we go that's what I want give me
more of
that it's our Romeo and Juliet moment a
beautiful
oh maybe it
is all righty let me
in okay okay you need help
[Music]
huh knew it you need
help leave it to me
[Music]
oh yeah for sure yeah strong Minds what
do you think it is and n n h November
re's favorite
month that's your only month where I
feel like you might be able to do it
[Music]
Bros but besides that you should leave
it to
me foree
[Music]
friendly Savage true though true being
treated but like [\h__\h] by all these
Knights for years and
years can't just do a favor to them like
that so easily especially when they're
so desperate about it let's get
something out of it pie ideally
[Music]
piey oh to purify small AMS of dark
magic
[Music]
p
no uh Insignia only given to commanders
each Insignia is engra of a unique
design Livia temporary why ah to show
the knights that are inside that like
heyo I'm here to bring you to
liia or or it's a sign to finding others
[Music]
okay
H but I have a feeling we'll be
[Music]
fine wait I didn't put it on
yet do I have to manually equip
it was it automatically equipped
maybe it's just like optional
anyway but we should probably put it
on right we should probably put it
on yes I am M Commander
[Music]
liia
interesting for some reason I've been
asked to investigate the wreck instead
of Livia there's a large amount of magic
coming from the wreck that's it's
probably what ason is wey of let's
see
uh yeah we are not wearing
it but we could
U magic resistance
8% maybe instead of the strength
Fring dark magic destru as an additional
skill
[Music]
okay
oh what's that behind the
door backstab they will backstab us what
no what do you
mean what the [\h__\h] is
that may said
it what
[Music]
oh I can't go that far
back door
exhausted from killing all the monsters
in the ship and then capture you
what what she's so evil what she I
thought she was nice
is
[Music]
man bro is hiding behind the box I can
see you you are not just a box and I
know it can't fool
me
ah six
turns this one's still should ah okay I
think this one is now one turn earlier
cuz I think it was three turns before
but the new one is six turns after the
combat starts
she oh wait oh it's
AOE
oh big big F AOE ball what are you doing
there bro oh you're hiding oh you're a
real one he's a real one that's why
you're hiding there and you're not an
enemy wait I'm trying to talk to him
there you go
no don't worry look at my
Insignia just pretended to be a box
[Music]
yeah I'm so nice just a
box investig shipwreck cabin the warrior
found that the Shipwreck claims to send
something among the crates investigate
the crates in the Shipwreck cabin okay I
mean I was doing that anyway
[Music]
oh no
[\h__\h]
and
oh okay well this is very visible to me
even if I'm not looking at the
[Music]
icon shees this one's so [\h__\h]
strong maybe also thanks to our new
staff he yo look there's a nice paper
that we should check out shipwreck diary
page oh No Just A
Box come on reveal yourself to
me you're are not just a
[Music]
box and and
sco oh he forgot
something ah the
key but I also want to go down is it for
here oh oh it's not
okay
SK he he's he skipped
out of here I don't
know SK
why oh there's another
one maybe I'll read them maybe
[Music]
not oh my
God and you guys are telling me that
I'll be weaker than my pets one day when
I can do
this are you sure
[Music]
door I feel super strong at the
moment oh is there nothing here
huh there's a really tall bro over there
can we like destroy this together no why
wait what I can't fire a freaking cannon
in here
I guess I'm doing it
though go make it
boom what do you
mean what do you what do you
mean get a Canon Bell Oh I thought like
oh not okay okay
okay
[Music]
ah what do you
mean okay there we
go I came in like a
cannonball and now I'm going to shoot
you
down with
[Music]
myall
for the
spring how did he get so tall
though he's unusually
tall
2,800 what a
joke thank you for the Super Chat yeah I
remember you from the meet and
greet I really had a good time at a meet
at the meet and
[Music]
green I want to do more
oh
nice should have maybe chosen the one in
the middle
actually that
[Music]
reach brain empty moment let's just do
this I mean I could still just bring
another pet out but I feel like it's
[Music]
unnecessary GRE that was really like a
one time only thing pretty
much I think it was just the one time I
did it
[Music]
right and then I wanted to do it again
but it was a no no
yeah it was too good of an
[Music]
idea I swear to make to want to you got
him [\h__\h]
should have waited until the final boss
the final door that I open
[Music]
yeah let's just end her
quickly she's done it to herself
let's just leave her
[Music]
there I agree
but wait what about the treasure chest
come on no you can't
just okay we have a reason to go back
inside anyway cuz of the last key that
we
got okay so because I am
strong that makes you realize you
shouldn't have tried that's that's just
a
[Music]
that good
idea nice also I'm not giving her back
her
things I don't want to I don't want I'm
keeping them
[Music]
no mercy next time stop [\h__\h] around
with me I'm so done with your
[\h__\h] I'm so
done oh there
okay that's interesting the ones above
didn't uh spawn yet but these ones
respawned because of the stones
oh dangerous synesis recipes
oh Danger us you say now it's even more
isn't
it even more than before I didn't even
heal I
think my sneeze jump scary
what stop cussing my mom's
watching really sorry Mommy sorry Mommy
sorry Mommy Mommy sorry as my title says
I'm already apologizing ahead of time
for my title what else do you
want that's
funny oh she
[Music]
they're curing
too he told me to
die kind of
[Music]
mean nice
okay now you better stay
dead oo 10,000 gold and a high power
ball
bomb sensitive to impact making
difficult to carry and handell
a and 7,000 gold can I not take these
Stones all right if we would take them
then I guess we wouldn't be able
to take take down that Knight anymore in
the future he yo who who are you I think
I saw him before did I
not I like I like how oceaniz this ship
has become look at those
snails
cute
Ean I'm missing one diary
[Music]
is he the one that was in the fields
like sleeping
first what are you doing
here
[Music]
for yeah the LA one
is what I've been
collecting bro they were lying around so
obviously on top of the
boxes open your eyes Lazy
[Music]
Boy
for
E understandable
yeah and then she betrayed me stabbed me
in my back or she tried to at least
and then she stabbed my
[Music]
bag you should mention
that or is this assuming that I went to
talk to him before
was there a possibility that we could
have talked to him
[Music]
before she did she
did indeed she did we could have known
if we would have talked to him
[Music]
earlier oh oh I see something inter
behind that door but wait
there's which door to go into
first no no no
no
ah okay what did I do with
that I could read it but I don't want to
I want to go in here first ah wait
there's another one
one
H all
righty
oo just got another one
[Music]
I was wondering if he was going to react
to me taking that
one no show me your face
[Music]
looks like
f let's
go let's go 9,000
ooh almost over
9,000 yeah that's a little bit
concerning let's just whatever take
agility
um so I wonder how much damage he
does yeah 9,000 is one of the strongest
enemies we've had so
far
and oh they have the same power these
two nice but this one's weaker but I
feel like we should do
this okay okay all right what you going
to do what you going to
do that's it n you have more more than
that to offer
right let's do something
extra he's got to have
more one of his turns is like blinking
red that must be something
special A's arrow is
[Music]
ready let me just take some
MP recover MP 80% recover 150
[Music]
MP recover 300 let's do this
one PE PE PE and we get another turn
this doesn't even take up a
[Music]
[Applause]
turn counter attack yeah even that
attack it was better than before what he
did before but it's still and we get a
strategic
crit I don't know let's hit him with a
swing just for
fun
[Music]
maybe oh it did the
trick
wow we're so
strong okay so he will arve because of
the dark Stones would it sounds like we
should maybe think about just removing
the dark Stones down there
but I guess that is not an option for
some
reason she came
[Music]
in is she going to kill my Ste steal my
kill
[Music]
spee
fore like
[Music]
playe
fore
[Music]
fore fore
spee
[Music]
foreign
for
[Music]
Fore foree
foree spee
[Music]
fore
for Fore
[Music]
you just ripped off that
stonee foree
[Music]
do you guys know this
song it's pretty Niche and
[Music]
old I don't
remember it never happened it's like an
accident outside of
work ins
[Music]
work makes sense
not no way you're still going at
it Sav you guys
no I may be a witch but she's a
[\h__\h] yeah but you a
[\h__\h] what's worse
huh
true or maybe she's just she's trying to
let us go without losing a face
that's why she sent them
away
right you're letting me go
[Music]
right yeah yeah yeah
okay mhm she's letting me go she's
pretending to have been beaten by
me Redemption
AR good for
you good for you
liia I would have been living at you
otherwise
[Music]
nuts I'm I wasn't done let me go back
in they keep on kicking me out
[Music]
just put on a pan face some Doo eyes and
go
pleas can I have your credit card and
social security number aim heart
please please aim
heart I need it I need
it otherwise I will die
[Music]
please oh another Wade thank you for the
Wade
[Music]
than if I can find aart like I did with
AA maybe I can ask them to cure Anna's
illness if aart grants me the power of
the amulet I can surely cure Anna's
illness I should ask Anna about the aart
temple but first I want to look in to my
yeah I want to read these pages
shipwreck diary page
one I didn't expect this to
[Music]
be thanks for the membership
gift this is dark Warriors proud the
Shipwreck they appear to be corrupted by
dark magic from Warriors who died during
the Spring War I intend to investigate
the Shipwreck over the course of 5 days
for maximum of 1 hour at a time the
source of the dark magic must be found
as the pope
[Music]
commands my subordinate nson has lost
Consciousness and his body has begun to
turn on an ashen color I specifically
told everyone not to spend too long
inside something is wrong has nson
already been poisoned by dark magic the
other members of the team are not doing
well either it looks like I'll have to
continue the investigation
alone
okay I hear strange Whispers put this
speed aure of dark
magic but dark magic could never tempt
me I am too
strong there's nothing that this body
and mind blessed by the pope cannot
overcome even though not
November yeah he's been through
it no issues he
wanted I woke up to find the SE severed
heads of my team lying on the ground in
front of me did did I do this I can't
find any of the others either
oh
no random heads is not a good
sign the search has been a failer and I
have lost myself no I L myself before I
even arrived here the blessing of
physical enhancement was only a curse
that fueled my Hunger for great of power
which is now consuming my reason all I
can do now is lock myself in here and
hope that no one comes to this
place but we did and we have ended your
misery
[Music]
now now hold
and uh I want to go
back
yeah
no wait that was a number six oh
oopsy
ah I'm scared what would Livia think
would she be living she saw metic weak
Warrior who allowed herself to be
seduced by black magic a coward relied
on physical
enhancement I would rather end my own
life before she finds me I hope she
never
[Music]
does
kuso
okay we're going to go back inside
because there was still one
pretty interesting looking
enemy eldri
radiation I don't know where you're
getting this idea from but maybe it is
maybe it
[Music]
is oh
is there something to pick
[Music]
up bro they kick me out of this ship so
many times when I
actually need so much more even another
page
bro uh wait where's
it's one diary now
huh
where ah
here how I wish I could see your face
again Livia Just One Last Time oh that's
it shouldn't have opened this book just
for that one
sentence I made I made a book I am now a
book
publisher I kind of am
am I
not think I
am maybe I should even claim that I
wrote
it or not that I wrote it but just going
to take all the money for it and keep it
to
myself yeah hope it will sell
well um all right
oh wait do I
even I don't even have the key for this
I guess I'll get it from
him
Ethan probably has the
key after I give him the book where
could he
be is he in those fields sleeping again
do you
think my book now y
yif my final form
fif
um well we got two training sessions
let's
[Music]
train and
going to do
this okay this one I
know should be okay
clockwise
X
counterclockwise X clockwise
[Music]
perfect oh achieved successful practice
three times adding stage two to the
difficulty of this practice you can earn
more bonuses by challenging
yourself just in this game in
[Music]
particular
interesting perfect bonus
%. yay now let's sleep
[Music]
pie pie pie p pie pie p pie pie pie pie
Bye by
by those those dust thingies are so
cute let safe for once
oh yeah and I
think we could switch out the accessory
[Music]
again don't really need this I think
generally maybe I'll give myself the
agility when do I get this one uh combat
XP oh maybe at the next level up
maybe let's change outfit by the way
this one we haven't worn it
[Music]
much so cute okay uh I want to
go
[Music]
to here's
fine I'll check if I can find even
y are those new enemies over
there I'm famous
man just real fun we should show
ourselves come
on she just [\h__\h] bed him
[Music]
immediately she's so terrifying look at
her smile
oh
got f for XP yeah I mean if you actually
go through life with an exp
bar and the only way to level up is
doing stuff like this you
know I mean I mean
I
mean what are you supposed to
do I know these are not new enemies but
we haven't fought them in a
while oh they have dark magic too so now
actually I guess that
uh bracelet or whatever that was could
have been useful here
[Music]
too but are too weak
anyway just going to farm a few of them
oh yeah this one becomes
be all
right dark magic Stone I feel like we
might you know need them maybe for
crafting cuz we
haven't fought them and picked up these
items in a
while but that's not what I came for
he heo
oh that's new isn't this also
new idle business
regulation wait are you like role
playing or is this just like a funny
coincidence that you are sending a Super
Chat like that to me
[Music]
I was missing the role play yeah hey yo
why did you not
die so why this is
new wait now they even took out one of
those they're like looting raiding this
dungeon who physic
[Music]
heo limited is time limited based on
stage oh okay then I should do it
earlier rather than later okay before I
run into some other stuff
but okay let me see if he's there where
I think you might be making time doing
Fitness Studio work you guys how do you
even how do you
even I can't be longer on a treadmill
than
like like if I'm running maybe 10
minutes nah probably just five let's be
realistic how do you guys do
it um here
[Music]
quite impressive guys I must say
exercise bike if I had more spa space I
would totally buy more equipment I would
love a bike like
that I feel like I could do that longer
than
running for sure it's more comfortable
too Ean peekaboo tell me where is Ean or
anybody else who played it is there a
hint on where he
[Music]
is
are the warrior area in the village oh
okay
nice here
[Music]
he's
imprisoned
fore don't say so
loudly they're going to hear
you he's
nice why are all the girls in this game
so
mean to the
[Music]
witches what's with this ratio
mhm nice where're so nice we are nice to
people that are nice to
[Music]
us are you going to read it bro
Battleship 2 gets a few more sailers on
board the large Golem sank and Transit
up are being loaded onto the battleship
meaning there is no way to destroy the
barrier inside the temple requesting
additional support for one large Golem
from
[Music]
thean infiltration corpse we can offer
you one fighter platoon blah blah blah
blah blah
blah w
[Music]
you missed this in your first
playr entire second
for I wouldn't replay a game just
for some small thing that I miss
[Music]
missed it
to but you didn't replay it
right
diary but diary in the end didn't matter
write the pieces of paper
[Music]
sorry
Mommy that skipped on its own when I
skip one while it's Autos skipping it
will skip the
nextage the next next message like
immediately
automatically what did he
[Music]
thank
you thank you I'm excited to check it
out I hope it's stronger than the other
thing that would be
fun I am a troubl seeker and a
troublemaker oh I can't teleport here
huh you can give the diary to Livia H
just next time I'll meet her I
suppose back to the ship for the fourth
time for real like they really force you
to go back there more than anything else
ever
[Music]
um did she even acknowledge his current
predicament kind of right she did she's
like what what
what I wasn't really taking it in what
they were talking about but she
[Music]
did she did point out that
he's in the Shell I think
[Music]
that's uh close to everything that I
took
[Music]
him
nice yeah he doesn't care
much he's just chilling he's vibing
you guys should let me quick combat you
already we're wasting all of our time
I'll even get exp from these
fights makes me mad makes me
mad what's
that I'm sure whatever he drops will be
something for something
cool right
there was something in the deepest Pine
of the r after all most of the dark
magic upstairs must have been absorbed
by this thing it wasn't say after
all I see so this is the dangerous magic
that asan was swearing of it must have
originally been a human its form has
changed tremendously you what what
you're telling me that this monster used
to be a human it has been absorbing dark
magic for so long that it's original for
form is completely
unrecognizable it's gone beyond the
point of simple insanity and is now a
much of itself why while I'm voicing
black Jo why am I squinting my
eyes getting in character
40,000
run oh
you think I can do
it I'll
try H attack is weak okay time to take
out the
trashi wow you said weak uh that was
almost half of my HP
bro I think I got to dismiss seed Spirit
to get the other
one okay
um
[Music]
yeah got to play smart and buff myself
nicely I
suppose all right [\h__\h] I guess it would
be good to have the purifying necklace
on for this fight okay if I if I die
once I'll put it
on
yeah
okay okay missed ah counter attack let's
goooo nice nice nice
[Music]
although wait I can use you already oh
okay oh I thought I already used you
last
[Music]
turn this is going to be rough I think
it's going to be
rough just 12 more hits like that oh
there nothing now but now we're getting
the strong attacks like aru's Arrow
which doesn't take up a
turn yeah let's go
[Music]
and next turn we're going to get the
crit so that'll be fun as
well do you think I'll survive one
attack for sure right especially if I
have the Magic Shield on
although yeah that
takes yeah maybe damn
it you know what I'll triple swing
instead I don't
know I no I need a little bit of MP left
over so that he can drain some of my mp
instead of my
HP
okay okay fine we're fine we're
fine okay we got crit we got
[Music]
heal I I might go for the we have so
many of these I guess I can take one of
these cuz I wanted a bigger heal anyway
[Music]
I'm going to put on a Magic
Shield it's crit time is this even how
strong is this anyway 350 is this even
strong should I just go for a normal
fire ball or
so I guess it's it's probably strong
decent strong right
[Music]
math is hard it's just it should just
say clearly how much damage it's going
to
do what is all of this it's great for
AOE
[Music]
oh and it doesn't consume
okay okay yeah yeah yeah yeah big
critical nice
oh yeah so if you don't run out of
MP no okay it doesn't stay I thought it
would stay maybe uh the Magic
Shield
okay oh he gets two more hits before I
get another turn so we want to protect
ourselves for
[Music]
sure but this seems doable yeah we're
going to be all
right wait do I is that agility thing
did it burun out
y y
b I can't I have to
heal that's rough I guess I could choose
not to attack and take the agility
potion or wait ah if only I had another
AR's
[Music]
Arrow yeah I'll take an agility thingy
though oh yeah I get I do get to attack
uh before he
attacks twice yeah good good good
immediate effect and we got the bolt
Yahoo m
[Music]
but what if I wait until next turn to
use
this cuz next turn I have my
crit I think I'll do
[Music]
that that will be the first time we're
going to see that
super
powerful okay
[Music]
uh okay it's crit time does this take up
a turn yeah it does I guess okay that's
fine here we go are you ready for this
watch this
[Music]
nice nice double
nice double
nice hey to the
yo the
[Music]
Y nice
nice nice
okay okay we're so
close yeah is oh my agility is gone
again isn't it wait that really barely
stays up
[Music]
huh should I take I should take one more
right it's free turns I think it's gone
right I don't
know wait I didn't take my shield I
didn't put on my shield oh well oh well
ah I have have to I have
to
uh
ohuh I thought he what just
happened okay
crit crit
[Music]
yeah
wait does the
strength now strength doesn't increase
the magic power I suppose we need a
potion for that but I could also throw a
bomb in this turn and then use my crit
but the bomb won't use up the crit
right cuz I was going to attack after
that too
I don't think the bomb would use up the
crit would
[Music]
it but maybe I don't know it's kind of
weak anyway but we should use them we
have so many of
[Music]
them uh I really hope this doesn't take
up my
turn it shouldn't because the healing
when I choose a healing item or whatever
it also doesn't take up a turn
okay it cral on its
own okay let's
go how much or
[Music]
okay we can take oh yeah he stole my kid
I was going to say we can take him down
next turn he did it for me there was no
next turn whatsoever
AO oh
Shield absorbs a large portion of dark
Magic's attack power and consumes a
percentage of MP if you do not have
enough MP your defense rate against dark
magic drops significantly what what what
what
what oh
so it's only good if I fight against
dark
magic or what good for yeah dark magic
[Music]
bosses
maybe
Nar maybe even the final boss
well we did it we did
it you you're not here yet
sad that was a big long
fight I like it I like it more of that
please wouldn't mind
more I'm just going to teleport hor horm
horm Anna's house okay
can we make something with our special
item that we just
found what was
it this thing giant dark I'm sure I I I
I saw that in one of the
recipes oh yeah we got to look into this
like forbidden what was
it d dangerous General
General ah we could
make these out of the smaller ones ah
oh I can also make the ones that you
need for this
[Music]
one oh do I need them for anything else
you I'm just going to make it because
why the hell
not now I got
two two dark magic Stones giant ones
wait yeah two okay what I do with
[Music]
them uh this is not the this is oh this
is interesting though minus 19% total MP
cost of magic it doesn't use the big one
this uses the big one but I don't have
the other things this one I could make
actually interesting
inly I was worried I already used up all
of the smaller ones but
no that sounds good finally something
new cuz we've been
using wait ah no no uh no oh we can make
this we've been using only this one so
far which is 10 plus plus
10% total MP cost of magic 110% power
boost so we'll just uh switch out one of
them
for one of these I
suppose and
[Music]
thenuh what are
these what are these lava
eye I don't think I can get these yet
right maybe
soon oh I
[Music]
were these
permanent yeah they were
right can make a couple of these
[Music]
oh oh I can make a new
armor the high
crabber is it better than what I have
surely right ah wa increase agility
minus 15
what it says increase but it says minus
I'm
confused
ah my current one gives me more agility
I
guess I
guess Aus it's heavy I should say
[Music]
decrease you can train that Comon for
heavy armor to reduce CU not should be
should we
[Music]
maybe these shoes look so nice these
ones I want
[Music]
these Okay so
aha I don't even I don't even need the
big Mar magic stones for evolving this
damn it I shouldn't have used them all
up to make another big
one but I also need lava eyes which I
still don't know where I can get them
from what do I do with my big lava uh
big dark magic stones that I
made I didn't see any use for it
[Music]
keep them for later I guess so
yeah okay uh train train train train
train choo Cho only one well we need
[Music]
agility yeah lots of
plus
three there's nothing that really
focuses on agility this one gives the
most oh we haven't played this one
before let me practice it this
time
[Music]
H ow
what oh I
see out too early I guess aha this kind
of reminds me
of
the fitboxing with Hats amiko game that
Coulda played I was watching a little
bit of that when she was streaming it
and I was thinking maybe I should play
that too with my accent
so that was so
funny I didn't watch too much I had to
go to sleep so I watched like just uh
like the beginning of it she did get
into boxing eventually
[Music]
I don't know it sounds fun because you
can box along to some vocal
[Music]
songs get ripped with mik oh actually I
don't know why I did this but somehow
cuz I was in the I was in the kitchen
and I was watching good on my iPad and
then she started boxing and somehow
somehow I just joined in and started
boxing the air in the same Rhythm as her
I was like trying to play
along I don't know what got over me to
do that what prompted me to do
that I was boxing along with
[Music]
goba Okay g
woo wo I'm so ready for fit boxing hey
y gamer alert we w we
W
[Music]
nice sleepy
you think the CH were doing the same I
doubt
it I
doubted I doubt they were moving their
arms along to the
Rhythm okay we are going to go to Anna's
house
[Music]
oops e on
a to the desolate Hill oh misty eye on
the mountain
[Music]
below watching oh Anna not here again
what
[Music]
I just noticed her house doesn't have a
toilet maybe what maybe she was really
peeing when we when we saw her the
last I mean if your house has no toilet
inside I guess you got to go
[Music]
outside I mean the ouse or maybe she
does have an out
[Music]
house I have a bad
feeling can't wait to tell Anna about my
plan but where is she could she be in
trouble oh yeah she's definitely in
trouble
[Music]
definitely she's in danger
we got to save
[Music]
her behind the door bottom left what
what that was the entrance though oh you
mean Oh you mean the outside yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's what I'm
saying oh
[Music]
happy to see her she's funny
nice it's that old dude right oh no it's
[Music]
not thought it was that old dude who
always in the
village
[Music]
for
foree
speee what a hero I'm going to fall in
love
for
foree
[Music]
speee
for we got to save her ass let's go
[Music]
wait they swim so slowly even though
they're swimming into the direction of
where the water seems to
flow that was
funny all right how many can we get one
two three
[Music]
four and that one is the best for now
I should have brought out myet damn
[Music]
it I'll eat a warm p
although I feel like summoning the pets
at this point is a little bit
unnecessary let's do a double swing on
the
Archer get another
attack let's
do oh we got Arrow AR Ru as Arrow
already but I'm not going to use
it I have mercy with these
people she says while burning them alive
[Music]
a he died from the
aftermath he did the
math oh there's
more is someone going to save me now I
don't need to be saved though
they
admitted moment
TST your body is that a like an actual
good advice if you're in this
situation interesting that was no big
deal anime
logic
no damn it
I I'm if I was going to take that advice
and just
die wait wait
wait pink hair white skin it all washed
up she's so cute I love the pink hair
what I'm here too and I'm going to see
it oh no oh
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
oh
for misunder understanding
Corner they changed the art too I was
wondering if they
[Music]
would but it's the same art just like
lit up
[Music]
basically understanding Corner are they
not doing it anymore is it gone forever
[Music]
for doesn't happen every
time there's not so much
misunderstanding yeah I remember like I
heard in the beginning uh because it was
so
popular they they you know wanted to do
it more but they couldn't come up with
so many Miss
understandings but everybody expected a
misunderstanding Corner each
[Music]
time must be rough man I was offering
some
misunderstandings I was offering him but
not not directly just on stream when I
said oh here's something for the
misunderstanding
Corner we're trying to make yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I guess so they would
like be like oh well oh that's a
misunderstanding and that's a
misunderstanding and that's also a
misunderstanding making a
misunderstanding out of everything even
the smallest
things kan's companion seems to be B bad
badly not baldly no no badly injured and
I'm not sure she'll make it up there
safely uh I should search for Kana and
her companions in
the oh they went in without me what wait
what
what what I just with
them what
happened why' they run away from me
[Music]
new teleportation all
time wait they can use it too
[Music]
thanks for the
membership thank
you I want to go up but I also got to
check out the altar do I have to
activate it I don't
remember ah there we
go I should follow Kaa wait is it that
way or
up probably that
way no oh bundle of teleportation
talismans a stack of Palms sized papers
with elaborate teleportation magic
circles drawn on
them okay we'll figure that out at home
probably oh
oh I can walk on
these oh well there's nothing here
[Music]
though me I'm the best Austrian of
course I
am thank you I
agree oh okay okay this means
nothing there is nothing here but I just
needed it for the piece of my mind I
needed to check it
out this corner
[Music]
too yeah they should have put an item
somewhere up there
[Music]
you don't have to say his full name each
time just say
Crown don't do him that favor
[Music]
do you even have to lay low if you just
take off the makeup and all that she can
just walk around normally
right you think people would would
recognize her if they don't recognize me
with makeup
[Music]
but she needs to
be doing her fee thing otherwise she
can't live oh a
key what key oh Matt's Garden passage
key not page for unlocking the iron gate
to Matt's Garden I actually don't know
what you mean with
[Music]
that okay I'll I'll go there too
Hana gave me a key that will unlock the
iron gate to her home the passage TR is
located next to the entrance to the L
first mine I should open the passageway
and go to ka's
house uh next to the
entrance uhhuh can I go take this
too
[Music]
well I even changed while I was holding
on to the
Rogue I called that skill
insane skill can you change clothes and
put on your makeup and
everything like this while you're
holding onto a rope
huh I doubt
it okay wait
uh
h ah
[Music]
hello how you doing
what can I use it as a pet like the
other
[Music]
pets
interesting this one's name is dwarf
4 it's great for concentrated strikes on
a single enemy if you use your magic as
a power source oh hey don't SC
that this is backpack spider good for
taking on multiple enemies it has free
missiles and his backpack Each of which
can go off a different Target what do
you think
[Music]
guys I can get both yeah but not now
right wait there's a little air balloon
up there zein
cute spider kind of cute
spider spider cuter you think so this
one looks kind of like
monkey but
okay oh I got an achievement
[Music]
no oh I want to
help and we keep on destroying
[Music]
them
for d
[Music]
mhm that's [\h__\h] up
indeed had too much knowledge and he was
being used for
it he still is being used for it I guess
[Music]
h
maybe he's not a bird
[Music]
[\h__\h] corrupt as hell
we should go together
[Music]
what if
we're no never mind I'm not going to I'm
not going to come up with another
ridiculous theory that is never true my
game theories never seem to be true even
though they're so
good yeah what if we're related
[Music]
but they we don't look a
lot makes no sense guess
[Music]
sounds hot oh my
God we're not watching B right now
[Music]
okay once a signal flare is shot at an
enemy Kaa will unleash a peanut shark
towards its
[Music]
location for
my brain is so empty
[Music]
today existing
today I'm just letting it happen
[Music]
I keep on Zing out
she using
me chat will warn me of back
yes please but I think she's not going
to backstab me
anymore not
[Music]
her I'm going to get everyone on my side
that blonde backstabber
too she likes me
wait if I'm grown up then I guess she'll
also be grown up we're going to see
grown up Ka is at some point too
long and grown up
oblivia oh the realization hits
that tiny little milk boy oh okay he
looks bigger in the picture but still he
looks like
a like a [\h__\h] milk boy I don't know
what that means I'm more interested in
the girl behind him which is probably
me that is 100%
me 100 million
per. a small magician witch
girl that is uh mostly covered up in clo
so that we can't see her
clearly uh it's one 100% me oh okay
finally a waa Fury that is going to come
true it's pretty obvious though isn't it
wouldn't you guys think of that too
because yeah there he's using her yeah
yeah yeah easy easy easy milk toast eat
milk toast is good but I haven't had it
in a long time milk bread by the way not
just toast most
bread no spoilers here ma'am it's just a
[Music]
assumption hey I'm just excited that I
saw mle
mle in Japanese means look at her M
there's moo look at
her
look in Spanish me is like I see
oh
interesting is
well it's probably got to do with Anna
[Music]
no no no way eh I don't know what you're
talking
[Music]
about
foree oh no
Cy
[Music]
POS hello
rich I love the character design of that
witch over there
I love
it
D no not because of the white hair
everything oh no don't put the attention
towards yourself like Dad you sussy
bucka don't ask me
[Music]
can not feel my
magic I am literally Jesus look at what
I just did
[Music]
okay they're all like oh
I love their
reaction okay bro
[Music]
you're
&m he's not
&m I want to make some Eminem joke I
don't
know but I don't know any of his songs
[Music]
do we know when Anna lost midle wasn't
it earlier than a year
ago do we
know
ex
CX if you open your program on your
desktop
cuter My Stream will
[Music]
open I am the executor of cute
yes I can't even say that so confidently
cuz I'm not like that cute
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm
right
here but I'm
[Music]
disguised what really happens when I
opened the
program he
is that my chat window
opens it's not a joke so I can't do
butons
it's
true now marry
me I thought I thought we got to a good
point where maybe you would say
[Music]
the duality of kfp
man that's okay pieber is cless just
like I
am thanks bro for telling me
Jo like ja right
now
oh does she
it does she
know oh no she doesn't okay
[Music]
you have to talk like this from now
on don't think too hard about
it oh
no oh
no
[Music]
pberry
for I've been here a lot girl I'm
[Music]
fine that Pope even healed meia
roll the one on
Deception
yeah yeah
for why do I
[Music]
have
demen for
[Music]
hi hi hi hi hi
hi let's just go
[Music]
what
I I thought you would let me
go girl
who she backstab me again
yeah I guess not because you're too weak
for
[Music]
it can we use I don't know our robot or
I don't know
shees
[Music]
girl can we just teleport out of there
come on let's
go not probably
not not that easily
[Music]
a no jo no we killed black Jo
no okay okay okay
imagine collateral damage
[Music]
oh she's worried about me she's she's
being a
[Music]
little you know you want to help me cuz
you know you like me but you're
conflicted with your
feelings understandably
[Music]
oh I didn't notice that
fore
she's a good one the moment I saw her
character design I felt
it yeah we're going to turn her to our
[Music]
side we have pine
indeed we have pine and we're feeling
Pine what we have pie and we're feeling
Pine damn it mess it
[Music]
up she gives up let's go
I'm already pretty decent at
[Music]
it no I believe in magic
but but but we live in a
society that tells you as a warrior you
have to kill and hate witches but was
always like that was it probably not and
you should just live by your own
values rather than somebody else's
values that are
being like brain wared into your brain
[Music]
as she still has
it we're we're [\h__\h] no way we're
blackmailing
[Music]
her no way
bye
[Music]
Barry I'm going to ruin your whole life
it's going to be so miserable I'm going
to ruin all your chances to do
everything that you ever Dre of doesn't
that sound
great
[Music]
psychopath pycho
Berry think we might be the bad guy
[Music]
yeah no
oh oh
[Music]
true this is
called power harassment yo we're using
our power to harass this Warrior
lady but it's okay it's okay we're doing
it for a greater cause and she deep in
her heart also does not want to hurt
witches
so uh calculated strike observe the
opponent's weaknesses for a few turns
before delivering a deadly blow the
power of the strike can be boosted by
the characteristics of the sword h
[Music]
fore
for was it needle
[Music]
foree
damn
[Music]
foree ah
black Joe still chilling on the
ground now we know that his bottom is
white oh wait we already knew that it
just I think we already knew that I
guess yeah his whole belly is
white never
mind ah so much story today lots of of
yapping
[Music]
damn I think I'm not going to play much
longer though because I need to
cook and I'm just brain empty
[Music]
today so this N I just
feel I knew that if I would like go on
my treadmill before a long stream I
might be kind of tired and that might be
the thing but I still wanted
to you know do something I didn't want
to I didn't want
to because I knew I would be too tired
to do it after the
stream I kind of want this game now it's
so cute it's really nice please go and
buy it and play it do it do it do it do
it do it yeah I got to keep up with my
exercise I need I really we need the
stamina there's so much stuff going on
in the
summer oh my
God I'm already
terrified you bought it on switch You'll
Play it after Paper Mario yeah speaking
of Paper Mario I I've completely stopped
watching dendo playthrough after like a
few episodes sadly because I also just
kind
of I didn't find
it uh I didn't like it didn't really
yeah I don't think I would have
uh been very into it if I streamed
it it didn't grab me
no I think I think it's probably the
battles because if you don't play it
yourself and then there's so many of
those battles it's just boring I
think maybe playing it myself would have
been a bit different
I'll give it the benefit of the doubt
because yeah I was just watching him do
a lot of battles and it's like it's kind
of
[Music]
lame you bought the game today o well
don't worry I also was not very focused
I'm
very drained at the moment
moment doesn't have
Gino I did like that game yeah that
Mario RPG game that we played that was
totally
mying but yeah let me save I think for
today hey yo what happened why am I not
wearing an
armor what
happened I crafted one but I didn't say
that I wanted to take one one off and
then not even replace it what the
hell what the hell game I didn't notice
that at
all also should I put this on or
[Music]
not is it good to just always wear this
is there a a con
to put this on even when I'm not
fighting against dark magic I think it's
fine right
[Music]
it's just that if I'm out of
MP my defense rate against but that
doesn't matter then if I'm not fighting
against dark
[Music]
magic okay okay no
downside good good good good good
[Music]
good let me save
again okay
[Music]
yumy I feel so low
energy I feel like a
zombie rest early tonight we do have a
short stream
tomorrow would you guys be okay if I
just read super chats
tomorrow I think
tomorrow probably it's going to end up
being a little mini
K uh
yeah with special reveal and special
announcement
but it's going to be relatively short
and that's fine then I can read my super
chats
[Music]
yeah no it's not
2.0 it's not 2.0 no no no no
a set list I don't have a set list
planned out at all that's what I'm going
to do tomorrow the whole day before the
stream planning it out practicing and so
on you will see it's also not
accessories it's not accessories
not black text and white backgound no
it's not that either can you sing some H
songs again I think I will
mhm and maybe I don't know maybe some
vocal songs I I'm going to check if the
K app has anything interesting for me
[Music]
now I got to check it
out didn't suggest anything
though new 3D outfit bro I wish
I
wish if
[Music]
only the games I've been requesting
permission for still no reply
D
sad there's this game I wanted to play
with Gooby ball I'm still waiting for
permission and then there there's
another little small oneoff is game I
think it's kind of a one-off game kind
of like I don't know frog detective but
it's duck
detective I've been waiting for perms on
that
too just waiting and waiting and
waiting small little cute game there
something about a Salam
I love
salami yeah quite short I know I know so
it's going to be a one-off
game okay sorry I
am zombie Wawa zombie waha I'm zombie
kind of tired tomorrow I'll have more
energy I
think because we're going to do
something exciting too yeah I'm all
indeed oh way messaged me back by the
way she confirmed it was because of
bakar the reason they did that on stream
they've been inspired by
it oh for people who don't know
yesterday we watched as our members
watch along we watched n monar which has
that famous toothbrush scene and then my
chat told me that waya and all did that
before on stream when I was questioning
if it would be a good off collab idea H
and then I looked it up and I watched
the clip and I was like oh my God I
wonder if they did it because of b
monoat or if this was just a random idea
from them but yeah seems like it was
back in when we got Daddy
inspired very good what does that mean
that waya likes Pak
[Music]
monar I think so
she
must yeah Ollie
said why would they want to do that
randomly I don't know I honestly don't
know but never underestimate ID members
yo they do funny weird
things hey it's
ID okay
guys and
we
[Music]
say Little Smoothie update before I
go that
bit today
today today
when I woke
up I was just chilling chilling in bed
for a while with the cats the cats were
by my side and then I
noticed I noticed some wind swooshing
sounds I'm like hey
yo and then I get up and I walk to the
door and I see smoovie has done it again
Smoothie has jumped up and opened a door
once
again she has done it
again she has mastered the element of
wind she hasn't done it in a while and I
normally really I haven't really locked
but it's like she knows what the one
time when I don't have it locked she
knows it and then she'll go and
try yeah she's she's not to be contained
or controlled by
me Tri Lo cat
loocks it's okay I was amazed by her
skill not letting her lack of fum stop
her she's a amazing she is
[Music]
clever
yeah she's so
sweet yeah and today today both my cats
they chased out a spider I've noticed i'
I've been getting so many little tiny
spiders way more than when living in an
apartment way above the ground now now
that I'm on the ground I get a lot of
like SP
speeda I just I stood up from a chair
and I I walk towards uh the exit of the
room and I see a little spider on the
ground and I was like but then I was
like kada you can't be shocked it's just
a tiny ass spider it's not going to hurt
you but then smooy comes in I'm like
smooy look look I pointed at the spider
and then she sees it and then she kept
on like pushing it pushing it pushing it
and the spider kept on going towards the
exit towards the window very good very
good and then and then she kind of gave
up she lost focus and gave up I was like
smoothie is kind of too nice to bugs
I've noticed I need chunky wony for this
generally smoovie is less terrified of
things like loud noises and so on but
chunky wonky M when it comes to bugs she
likes to like ruthlessly attack them and
play around with
them yeah so I brought over chunky wonky
and she smacked that
spider several times and she got like
really excited she got a big kick out of
it it made her Zoom get some
doomies she smacked the spider a few
times and then she went like and then
she zoomed out out of the
room so cute but they're a good team
together spiders will help your
garden well yeah I guess so I don't I
don't mind them in the garden and I
guess even like with not just spiders
but also other weird bugs coming in the
spiders maybe will eat them but I don't
know I'd prefer them I prefer nothing at
all to be in here they can all stay out
please just stay
out or I guess they could
also be a nice toy for chunky wonky and
smoothie free toy free exciting toy
no money
spent good entertainment for
CatOS those poor
spiders says the
Australian well you guys like spiders
over there even though you have the most
terrifying ones I'm glad I don't live in
Australia I guess yes because if my cats
were to smack a spider in
Australia then the spider would multiply
into 1,000 tiny little spiders and that
would be really difficult to deal
with that would be terrifying that's a
skill that only Australian spiders have
austral are I don't know why I'm saying
it like this today I'm saying a lot of
things weirdly today H that's a wolf
spider wait that's an actual thing
though I was just
joking what do you
[Music]
mean what do you
mean what what do
you can a wolf spider multiply into a
million little spiders oh yeah cuz Okay
I see a picture of a [\h__\h] ton of spiders
on top of the big spider is that what
happens yep
B what what what what what they like
what they
kagin oh it carries its baby oh
my sorry the
pictures go oh okay I'm I'm just going
to go like oh man this is like like not
good not doing good things to me right
now
[Music]
I'm going to me I'm going to
meu I have appetite yeah I just don't
have the motivation to cook but I have
to in German Miss that's and I love you
guys byebye see you tomorrow I hope
you'll all be there it's going to be a
special
one and on Sunday it's also going to be
a special one two special
streams in one stream in one week
y bye
bye love you
guys w w wah W wah
wah wah Super Chat reading tomorrow I
promise
[Music]
birthday dinner tomorrow is it your own
or someone
else's happy birthday if it's for
[Music]
you your dad's ah nice ah that reminds
me I'm totally going to forget this
other otherwise so let me tell you now
can I tell
you just one meet and greet memory from
off guy maybe that chicken is in here
there was a there was a one meat and
greet oh we're still back there was one
me and great person who told
me that they got their dad to watch my
streams
like somehow their dad is like pretty
like into it
too that's why I tweeted it yeah that's
why I tweeted that dads like me too not
just moms and I was like it is your dad
like a nerd or like into that kind of
stuff um but no it was just
like yeah just me and oh yeah I think
there was some kind of connection with
like German
uh I
think they they have some German roots
or the dad speaks German or the dad
lived in Germany before or so something
like that and and that's why in
particular uh I think I remember they
said that the dad likes when I speak
German in my
streams I was like what this is kind of
embarrassing but at the same time I'm
glad that like someone who's not into
this kind of culture and like anime and
all that in general like someone really
unlikely right to
be interested in what I do and and so on
and
me now both dads and moms love
me German Channel Revival
we talked about this before I said
before that like I feel like I I I want
to I don't know like whatever I stream
there I feel like I could stream here
too somehow but I you know blah blah
blah I don't
know what German
Channel yeah oh yeah say say you were
also at the meet and greet if I'm not
going completely Bonkers right now with
my
[Music]
bra you were there you were
there we're so nice to meet
you I want to meet more of you guys more
kfps putties come and meet me when you
can if there's an
opportunity
okay I am awaiting
you h
one
[Music]
day okay now I'm going to
go I hope you get more chances to meet
kfp this year well we're already halfway
through the year
though I don't know about meat and
greets
but you know one way or another I'll see
you
what another YY Yi profile picture
owner
stalker yes mle why mle who's talking
about
mle yeah I watched a clip about crony I
was like what what do you mean crony was
at offy what she was she she's not
what what the [\h__\h]
what under cover croni like guys do you
realize you could have like been
standing around her all the kfps who
were there did you think about that you
could have been in the presence of the
one and only
quason did she see you I don't think she
probably would have avoided I don't know
I don't think she she would have yeah
also cuz it was really late and she
talked about like going drinking and K
with her friends in that clip so I feel
like she probably didn't spend that much
time at
[Music]
ofai
mhm she was literally stalking everyone
what she could be any of us even me she
could be
imagine she showed up at your fan me
that would that would have been funny
that would have been indeed very
funny I got to check out the other clip
thenon she's everywhere right now she's
in Poland she's at
ofai man look behind you she might be
behind you right now
like the
Undertaker scary scary to think about
it she's in the walls okay I'm going to
go I said I would go I'm going to
go
bye-bye Al Z
[Music]
by the way I don't know if you guys
noticed if you were at the meet and
greet if you could hear me so clearly I
just want you to know when people take
pictures and say cheese I thought of
something way better even before in
other meet and greets you guys just got
to say k Kitty cheese I'm so proud of it
because even just Kik key makes you
smile
Kik key alone would also be fine but
I've been saying Kik cheese every time
when they stand next to me to take a
picture KY
cheese
[Music]
remember it rolls off the tongue it
totally does
[Music]
H it
does I used the chef head in the med
gr no I
didn't
ah I think just for one
person yeah just for one person I think
yeah
[Music]
yeah oh yeah cuz she was in
Cosplay and I was wearing my casual
outfit but I was like okay for us to
look more alike each other you know what
I'm going to do I'm going to put on my
hats only because I can do that with my
casual outfit yeah I said just for you
you guys saw that
picture oh that was Mai oh mie
cute you're here
[Music]
A
C I was so
honored uh ghost I got an update what do
you mean what are you saying this like
what
[Music]
please elaborate on the hashtag or
whatever
[Music]
bye-bye got to
go what do you mean on this what wait
what oh okay bye by
bye-bye what like an official one not a
fanade or so
[Music]
wrap it
up it was an official firw up there what
they're like they're like me they're
like I'm out of here I'm leaving I'm not
updating this off anymore this company
is dead and then they come back and
update it just like how when I say A's
in and I come back for another
[Music]
tangent that's a
special connection I feel it's
fate this doy fate
[Music]
mhm okay bye