[Music]
foreign
I'm spazzing out in the corner of your
screen at like two frames per second
oh you're watching my stream Kelly yeah
I have it pulled up I have everybody's
pulled up oh guys
[Music]
welcome to the hashtag cod in 4k Diablo
Cola yes
that's that you have as well it looks
good thank you I'm a fancy sorceress yay
sorceress nice who who's everybody what
is everybody playing as
good question go around let's go around
Ring Around the Rosie okay yeah
all right
first okay fine I'll start okay fine I
will I will begin I will begin all right
so more put some of my character's name
is Morp uh morph is uh she thinks she's
a skeleton she's just really weird she's
a necromancer
um very skinny and strange and toxin
third person morph talks like this
more bits morping time it more Bluffs
pretty lady speaking of pretty lady
let's let's go to
Keandre keonder
don't I look pretty because I put
um the I used the trends more good
whatever it's called
the specific cloves on top of other
cloves that don't look so pretty so now
I look super pretty
looks cute I like Callie I'm so glad
that you are joining us a necromancer
yeah
but now I'm realizing you guys can't see
the skeletons which makes me really
really upset actually morph is sad you
can't see her skeletons really don't
they show up maybe when we leave town
maybe I hope I'm not sure I'm sure they
do
okay who else does we have Kyla right
next to me as well okay let's go what
are you I am a druid I don't know how to
play the drift but let's just let's go
carrying just like a brick probably
building a house yeah what is that a
brick let's go let's do something wrong
let's go Cali actually wait you might be
building a house with Cali right because
Cali has a really normal pickaxe on your
back how you doing okay let's go more
blacks pickaxe
whoa wait corny you look like crony what
you really look like girl names I
changed my
outfits that's very nice
what's Chrome you playing what is that I
am playing as a rose
okay wait Rogue you have you have two
swords or what
uh I have like a bow and oh I guess I
have two swords yeah
I can't I can't go that fast how do you
go that fast in a circle
I'm playing on a controller oh okay okay
plays on PS5 oh wow
oh okay so I'm I'm a sorceress I chose
the the special thing is the day do you
guys know what I tried to reference in
my name
[Music]
um
Andre
no no Kendrick Lamar
Kinder Egg
no yandere no not because you know I saw
uh I was first trying to recreate myself
but it didn't work so well and while I
was creating the character I realized oh
she's looking kind of like Game of
Thrones character Miss Andrea
hashtag
we all kind of have our own colors here
yeah like I got purple
macaroni has blue
macaroni and then well as red and Kyla
is kind of green I guess if you look at
the hammer but for now brown is also
good you'll surely get greener Greener
and Greener
ogre color
yo I haven't played in a couple days but
uh my current goal is the campaign quest
for level 10 the tarnished luster and I
thought we would do that unless you have
any other ideas it's fine I'll just
follow anything
follow me and fight
s for fight
fight yes me and the skeletons warp
skeletons let's combine up
but you hear the other ones but no uh
game audio one second
[Music]
Sun check Sun check everything's fine
right
one two three
yeah yeah yeah hello okay all good all
good okay all good all good nice nice
thank you thank you how about now
I think we're here
game bgm now I'm
I'm Latin
loud more song there's your music take
off my helmet so you can see I'm scared
okay we're ready
oh you can go to the
future cab instead of like oh really
I want to go to the Wardrobe together
everybody yeah let's go girls gonna
dress up I love dresses
girls yes it's okay I'll just wait I'm
reading the skills right now it's okay
just ignore me it's okay we're done robe
oh cool okay is it safe to show
um the the group screen where I invited
everybody in it's okay
I should be fine it should be fine look
at this we're looking so cool Kelly
looks like she is she needs sleep
so cold that hair that's Libby
if I can do unequipped look but I'm
still equipped with it right
I drew it
play and Drew it you need help can we
let's see I'm trying to so unequipped
look but that doesn't mean that it's
unequipped correct
oh
I forgot how it works crony you help her
ah so you got a wardrobe
and then you can just like uh go to the
Head section and then
it just says unequipped look
oh okay cool and you just choose that
yeah yeah
cool I'm ready to go okay what did you
change yeah
because I want to look like a skeleton
more wants to look like skeleton hell
yeah I feel like baldness looks so good
in Diablo I know right I can stick
[Music]
wait why is no cap
maybe you can reflect light on your
forehead and find like a new skill to
attack with whoa nice idea yeah use my
head as a mirror you you use morp's head
as a mirror yes
you must clean it all the time I've got
my shiny my shiny cloth good the shiny
cloth
[Music]
uh
difficult it's like down in the east
can I track this okay good it good
I'll follow let's go we're gonna kill a
bunch of guys let's go love killing love
killing people
with the ladies murder with the ladies
ooh murder sleepover
damn it we're going in a circle okay
girls night out in the circle yes
running in circles not accomplishing
anything let's go ladies that's right
that will change where are we going
to
uh what's it called actually you can pin
it though
pin it for you guys yeah
just right click right click on the map
so we can follow oh I did oh why is SEO
skeletons
are here
yeah
do we share items or does like everybody
get their own drops no um yeah
that's what Chad told me
she just wanted to make sure
yeah I'm not ready yet I'm not ready
I'm already kind of like
struggling to see where everybody is
because now I thought this person
belongs to us oh
hey more says you are not invited to
this party can we kill them
you are not part of our group
cool me
cool Mean Girls let's go
hey no no others no Outsiders allowed
I think sorry we're super quickish of
like how am I going to have in the group
yep
damn bossley we're the Mean Girls of
Diablo
you can't sit with us
yeah
yeah yeah yes we are you cannot go to
hell with us exactly you can't no you'll
go to heaven and have fun there yeah
yeah
Super Evil ladies but also not really
evil but just kind of mean not eat mean
is good uh there we have even
yeah you guys want to go even even even
let's go let's go
morph is here
more do something you're more abusive
okay
let's do something
is
it not too loud for you
it's always the Battle of volume
yeah oh you guys don't like that
let's change it in a second a little bit
I I I feel like I'm taking away
everybody's like
item drops but but hold on
[Applause]
oh level up completely
no no not level up that was just a quest
I thought that was a level two I got
excited wait maybe it was I'm level six
now okay new ability yeah
increased light oh no I did have a level
up too okay not so Target
Park
oh that's what it is okay never mind
pick up gold hold on
hold on hold on okay I also will change
volume Goblin what does this villager
have on
[Music]
mental stability
yeah all the traps are mine yay it's
like Christmas
[Music]
yay
yeah nice young ladies nice girl first
together Diablo game right yeah I've
never played diabolo before how is that
so far I love it
yeah I'll probably end up doing a 12
hour stream this week what
yeah it's too fun oh yeah a little too
addicting hey
once you're in the Diablo
um whatever you're not getting out
there's no way back
I tried to stop playing the game because
I had to go do a recording and I was
like all right time to stop and then I
spent like five minutes trying to stop
the playing the game and I couldn't stop
[Music]
yeah
yeah blue
you bolo
are we already inside no okay
we're all playing on tier one right yeah
okay I am too
probably Kyle already privately plays
the other one right
yeah it seems all right
Kayla so you already finished the whole
game or
uh the the main campaign yeah
but how long did it took you to finish
the main campaign
oh I kind of forgot how how long was it
guys I don't know can you help me
asking for her has no feeling of time
anymore wait what do you mean by tearing
yes
three stream three stream they say three
stream
how long
yeah
30 hours I wanted to I wanted the game
to be longer than that
okay 40 to 50 yeah they say 40 to 50.
not bad
thank you
pyromaniac over there
what you okay
you good all good all good I'm just
cleaning up on my knees
oh cool yeah
as I said we're steamrolling the server
surprised what explosion
[Music]
I have to go up here for the quest okay
do you girls have to go there too or is
it just me no I think it's uh
let's see
[Music]
you and that nuisance of a child both oh
are we going into the mines
mother and
you guys hear me yes uh
okay yeah did you see the conversation
of the NPC or yes
okay okay that's probably not necessary
oh I think I skipped it
oh no problem okay I marked the location
on the map so
[Music]
Ebola time
we're just playing some video
[Music]
well maybe not everybody knew you didn't
know that did you care a man I feel like
I heard it before yeah it just makes
sense
yeah yeah oh we have Diablo Pizza I
think in in the oven
I think there's Diablo Pizza which is
like really spicy
or like Diablo hot sauce yeah I feel
like I've heard of that before oh yeah
yeah it really really is the really hot
hot sauce that sends you literally to
hell wow you could almost die that's
Diablo hot sauce right oh that sounds
fun
get that skeleton Captain skeletons
thank you
I'm gonna
I'm so Madness
all right I have to pick up all the gold
now clean up clean up okay
skill point maybe this one it was
medicine right here okay strangers
stranger
oh morph is nice lady
nice skeleton
warp is nice skeleton lady
I have to
ah
I'll take flame Shields
let's see I'm reading I'm reading
reading skills I don't know um
I also don't know what I'm doing with
the skills
I never know what to do
okay
shut up let's go
what should we do right now
or decomposed The Necromancer is kind of
cool
I love necklace was really nice yeah the
character is kind of cool
but somehow the what is that
the all of the scale is kind of confused
me
go for it
oh you talk already
I'm talking now but oh I think us being
in the group messed up the the cutscene
how much of the game have you played uh
well I guess I already played this part
so I don't need to see it I play it and
the beta I played like
wait how much do I play end of act one
got some work done yeah this is your
first one playing the main game
uh
uh uh I played uh last week or so one
time
um but before me and crony played Diablo
2 resurrected right yeah it was fun I
hear that's a while ago Debbie say that
one's really good like this one and then
at uh that's pretty close when I was a
child my mom used to play Diablo one and
two I suppose and I was watching her and
sometimes trying to game uh myself but I
was always too scared of everything oh
thank you never get that's the the first
little boss so
I was just like wandering around always
I mentioned this time I'm playing it
properly I mentioned on stream I feel
like I understand why you like it
because it's not too scary for you
because I know you don't like scary
games oh maybe now it's not too scary
but but it definitely was yeah although
I saw something and I think that we're
maybe still gonna see it I don't know
I'm confused what happens when but like
the blood ritual stuff and all that that
everything's scary
Define scary what is scary like
how much scary is scary everything is
scary good point no
life is scary life is scary true
that one I agree
life is scary yeah the news will die
oh
it will
please
what's going on
look there's just a lot going on that's
fine more cleans the battlefield I'm
excited for boss fights I want to see
how yeah we can kill a boss
Arrow to my heart
until we go what why why I have no no
Mana
no mama
will
what more character are you playing like
uh what else
sorcerer is better apparently according
to some people but you know I'm a
phoenix I gotta be a fire saucerer yeah
I wouldn't believe it if you were an ice
spider
is great
yeah yeah I feel like in most other
games that I played like MMORPGs where
you have the choice between Fire and Ice
Mage or swords or whatever usually the
ice one is always like super weak
um
like ice ice is more like for status
effects and that's why people go for it
but fire is just like more physical I
think like well not physical it just
deals more damage in my opinion
well think about it
if you freeze someone like you can just
they can just get unmelted but if you
burn someone they're like that's like a
piece of their body that's gone
yeah but I think it's good this is the
absolute balances did so well that you
can play Ice and still do good damage
I appreciate that maybe I sometimes
some other time
but not this time
I mean you can't believe it through it
I was considering playing a druid in the
beta but everybody was saying that the
Druid was like super weak yeah
everyone's super difficult
did they not did they change anything in
the balancing yeah
anymore like it's the build
it depends on the build I think
okay yeah
Kelly you know it's cute you have five
skeletons right yeah and I just stayed
behind a little bit one of your
skeletons stayed behind with me
what a gentleman that'll be thank you
for staying with Wawa what a sweetheart
that's the dead beats for you making
sure nobody gets left behind this way
it's just so that I'm not alone and
scared in the dark
oh except the fight's coming to us
yeah these are two weeks we need
stronger opponents I know we're kind of
we are really steamrolling yeah
okay now
let's go
wow the best
yeah we could go to tier World tier two
if we wanted to I think we might need we
probably should at this point
can we do it while uh chat can we do it
while we're in the middle of the game
maybe we need to finish the quest first
we need to get to the finish some quests
like complete some quests to go to the
here too yeah but it's not that hard if
like from one to two
okay
I think I'm already on tier two yeah
wait then wouldn't we not be allowed to
play with each other though
that's a thing I'm so confused about
that
IDK
we're gonna no whoa whoa what's that
skele dude thing
yeah if we play with others we following
the the host world so if it's like
playing in here one so it's like
transfer all to tier one yeah okay so I
would have to change it okay why am I
running up Don't Run Away
come on
scaring me to run away past Chihuahuas
is still deep inside of you saying no
too scary it's okay
you play
yeah we can just go back to kyoka yeah
oh wanna do it now probably we can just
open the portal
oh okay finish the mission first we can
do it in the middle of the dungeon too I
mean we can do that like
okay okay whatever you guys want to do
yeah because it's gonna be like uh more
XP too right
true enough yeah so we better do it now
how do I get out of the
uh dungeon map
uh do we just teleport out or we just
need to press t hold T ah yeah
it's been a while okay
here we go did we leave someone behind
so everybody want to kill the Shad okay
no girls left behind no no ladies all
right now let's let's go to higher a
higher levels
how to change uh you need to go to the
wait the statue uh
this one the world here would the world
appears that you oh ah
wait is the is the green one you yep yep
yep I'm the green one
[Music]
um
which
is
what do you need
okay
use this one
oh this one South pitch this one
wait
why
huh
wait what
what happened with the Discord can you
guys hear me
uh
yep we can okay
where where where where do they go
but others not
but
oh
they hear you what
okay let me let me just restart
hmm I didn't know what happened
I don't know what happened
um
it's really weird but the stream is fine
right
the stream is fine
hmm
I don't know it's very funny after
it's very funny because because after
Kiara say like no girls left behind and
then suddenly it disconnected
um I cannot go I cannot go back to the
I cannot go back to the Discord though
this is like really weird I don't know
the Discord silly connecting
connecting and connecting and connecting
and connecting and connecting
region issue hmm
maybe maybe maybe maybe
um
I can accept that
[Music]
can I still see
them moving
[Music]
it's it's really weird it's like
reconnecting to Diablo 4 but I can see
the moving
oh
Nani Kore
no
no no no
I'm collabing
but I'm not collabing
help
Left Behind foreign
I'm so sad
um
get self-help yeah I really need to get
some help
wait um
connecting connecting
wow so bad
try to use isp2 um I can do that
maybe my first ISP is like rejecting
International
[Music]
uh uh connection or something like that
probably no
[Music]
hold on
the stream gonna be like disconnected
for a while okay
the stream gonna be
disconnected for a while wait wait hold
on let me let me hear away my l2d first
and then let me pull out
okay
okay be right back
okay okay we are back we're back
are we back are we back
we're back we're back oh no um
this is kinda bad
[Music]
um
oh no uh
wait wait wait wait wait wait
um
that is so cool
so they just kind of popped out of the
ground
are those your little pets your pet
snakes nice oh my God that's adorable
oh but I can respawn them elsewhere
the silent chest do we need a key for
that I want this silent chest yeah can't
open it sadly but I want to open it can
we buy a key chat you know it I'm sure
you know it oh Kyla okay oh welcome back
hi Kayla I changed back the connection
glad to see you all right okay I think
someone need to invite me back
oh you're all flying yeah I'm still in
the loading screen
[Music]
so many there was a problem logging in I
cannot do anything
[Music]
the ID curse
I was about to say whoa
whoa let's go QR let's get them
hey
oh I'm going to die no no no no no no
rattle them boys
everyone dead
including your skeletons yeah I'm just
cleaning up the battlefield real quick
okay I'm muting my eyebrowservices
so I'm not bothering them morph is clean
freak but I'm trying
I'm trying I'm just oh there's some
level 48 dude here that's a strong guy
maybe I should what are you doing in new
barrier huh I should and noobs only
the uh probably
wants to take all these maybe because
another game of blizzard and Big Empty
right now
writing I don't know
am I am I getting Ben maybe I'm getting
banned let us know when you're ready
yeah it's okay it's okay
you guys want to check out the Stellar
while we're at it oh seller yeah that
sounds fun what's there nice dude I have
no idea
okay okay
yes invite me now or
oh no no no no it's okay I'm I'm still
um trying to fix the battle knife okay
take your time yeah
[Music]
it's fine
okay
anyway Kayla true
yeah yeah so it's okay it's okay uh
you've seen it all you've experienced it
all
yeah well stay strong did I just got bad
or wet I don't even know what's
happening
there's a problem logging in oh no yeah
oh that's it
this looks nice these all look super
good yeah
nice loot ladies was a small sign
bigger than mine at least
okay leaving the cellar okay
like a wine cellar right Carrara
I don't drink wine what what's that wine
cellar yeah yeah he said he had a seller
you said yeah to sell her I'm just
asking Hey where's the cider ad though
where's the cider Brewery
that's what I want to know where's the
cider Brewery
I just want to know where this is yeah
we're the mini drink he's at a wine
cellar I'd only put iced tea there I
think
I think I'm in oh really okay
you look good okay
maybe we can invite it says you're not
in the game yet what I'm in game
maybe it takes a moment oh wait now
invites
okay
let's go
[Music]
uh try to catch up with us it's okay
it's okay I'll just teleport
okay we're having a party right now
viscera everywhere
these guys are nothing they're chumps
I still feel like we're kind of
steamrolling yeah yeah yeah we're still
doing pretty good I'm glad we changed
tears
it's good night's more like a little bit
more challenging now a little bit
I I didn't totally just almost I feel
like we're fighting stronger enemies
it does feel like it yeah but I already
got a level up so the EXP is flowing
I'm close to Loveland I'm excited for
hard bosses
yeah
I wanna do the the act one boss but I I
guess we probably won't get there today
it's okay
who run in a circle
I
tried to look for Monsters I can't find
it works just following you
when you follow follow we're gonna run
back to the
um it's okay I'm here here I see Kyla
I'm here wow let's go
[Music]
yay let's go
also you guys finished the what is that
the the story the first story The the
dungeon oh no no we were doing like a
Cellar like a random uh okay okay
there is an event below
okay yeah we can go get some new
skeletons
we need to wait for a moment it will
spawn here I think I don't care I'm
gonna change my skirmishers okay
defense skellies
oh
inspect the ancient Oberlin oh here we
go
let's go
Bring It On Us
okay
do we have to stand on this place
you have to keep standing on it until
it's as long as you can it's already
it's already done it's already done oh
it's already done yeah they're like um
an orange circle until it's gone and
then it's uh
yeah yeah
oh okay yes
[Applause]
I want to see some some stats on who
does the most damage me too do we get to
see that no it doesn't say no
what I want to see more wants to see if
she's actually helping
you have the power of five skeletons I'm
sure you're helping I guess so that's
true Shield skellies
my Defenders
Lightnings tornado
[Music]
Welcome To The Bone Zone
uh
classes did you already play
uh uh I played uh sorceress and
Barbarian before
barbarians
using magic sounds fun we still got some
different classes to go yeah sure true
that's true
you can do yep I wanna try it all crony
Club yeah true yeah music magic seems
fun in this game in particular
games like this I just I just like to
keep a distance from the enemy so I'm
usually like some kind of Mage class
yeah or a Healer and usually a Healer I
feel like you'd do good with Necromancer
too because Necromancer has a lot of far
away stuff yeah yeah
my I I like my sorcerer
was like a hang sorcerer
oh
but inside of a necromancer I would like
to be a nickel mantis
that eats you up
they have two forms they can be big
scary cats or they can be small kitty
cats that you can pet
e
Dude where's this that sounds amazing
right yeah I know right
forget the skeleton deadbeats I want I
want skeleton cats
wolves
wolves or they could just be regular
cats that's fine too
oh Kyla careful it's fine I'm calling my
wool holy [\h__\h]
yeah
hell oh okay you're back up oh it would
happen oh
what do you flexor
they're coming
I'm not flexing
[Music]
not just a casual Flex it's all right we
forgive you yeah it's okay thank you for
forgiving me casually arrives in a
Mustang
uh this way okay
okay
[Music]
now we are going to oh okay oh where do
you have you have wolves now I see the
yes of the Wolves I'm calling my wolves
oh that's cute
oh cool so Necromancer isn't the only
one that can summon some friends to help
yeah
true the wolves are super cute though
you want to have you like I can
you know
I'm thinking about it now when I was um
trying to choose classes for this one
you want to play drugs like
yeah but like I thought the Wolves were
just for a show like in the character
selection because I didn't mention
anything about somebody moves
just an image but okay hmm maybe next
time
maybe next time there are like 10 slots
yeah I mean that's the reason that you
can keep playing dialogue again and
again right so you just need to complete
the main campaign first and then after
that you can play the Druid after that
yeah let's try different characters it's
true it's true
dude
left or right left
we're back in the mine yeah
I think we'll blast through it again
yeah hopefully because it's not a good
feeling okay you know everything again
but we didn't get so far anyway that's
all right it was just exp as a warm-up
yes
preview yeah
Palms away
example
oh crony something spinning around it's
almost like a crony copter
Too Perfect
just like spinning
um
[Music]
I think we really need more moths
this is like
to Leo for us no this is planning no no
no no no no
I want the bitrate to suffer it's too
bad I can only do World tier two I'm so
sorry nice
it's not your fault
I'm just saying
she already played everything this is
boring no no I'm not saying this is
boring nah this is fun
it's not fun for her it's nothing having
the worst time in the world right now
you can tell
yeah exactly
no guys please help me now
we're just pulling your leg you're fine
yeah you're just hanging with the noobs
no but no you guys are not carrying the
boobs
you seem a little too uh Pro but I guess
you know we can include you no you can
hang out in our Noob squash yeah
I mean My Level is the lowest I'm the
newest I'm the most new so yeah
a full blade
bring in the bars let's go boys
okay oh yay I'm so excited I love these
fights I want the floor covered in
viscera for me to clean up
is that an evil laugh yeah
yeah okay
look at that guy which is not so evil
after all
okay I got I got frozen I
like stuff you killed the boss too fast
it's mine that was only a mini boss
it's not the big big boss not yet yeah
why would your mother
like that crony are you gonna
um uh play with the same character in
your like other streams or are you do
you have separate characters
uh I I have a necromancer oh like okay
cool yeah
what about you is this your uh I was
gonna just play with this character
um and then if if the group ever like
feels like not playing anymore then I'll
just continue playing this character
what I was gonna do
sure but I cannot see us like finishing
the whole game together I doubt that we
can make time so often and yeah yeah
especially because I want to play
a lot of times where not everybody is
available so I'll probably beat the game
on my own as well I'll be available
after time by the way
of course
we weren't referring to you we knew
already
when is she ever not available
yeah yeah
sign up with your like potential to play
so many games for so many hours I feel
like
I'm surprised you're not or are you are
you playing Zelda tears of the Kingdom
oh that's the reason like I mean I need
to choose between the Zelda and the
Diablo back then yeah yeah because I
know that if I I just cannot uh play
both myself
[Music]
I think for some games that I cannot
have the time to play I'll just watch
others to play
I think you can watch me play okay sure
sure
yeah I'm almost done I'm almost done
though with the game yeah yeah yeah yeah
there's members to uh playing Zelda too
back then yeah
I saw you were almost nice nice nice
yeah but I'm trying to stall now because
the game is so good I don't want to
finish it yet we're really grinding on
it for a while there yeah like nine hour
streams but that's nothing for Kyla from
for Kyla that's nine hour stream is like
a three hour stream oh silence Kiara
silence you're still the marathon come
on now give me that both of you guys are
insane people
what are you saying you're also the one
that do like long streams no no what do
you mean no you guys all do long streams
yeah yeah
we all grind in our own ways I guess
you're all guilty all right well
guilty as charged is that how you say it
yeah yeah
I don't know streaming it doesn't feel
like a chore to me so I mean I don't
know it's just kind of fun I don't
really notice it
not anymore at least
how do we get down there I guess we
gotta go this way we need to go around
you a ladder
wear ladder
sugoi
so technology
technologically oh
they should look at Germany and use
Germany technology
put an elevator in this weird ass
dungeon
um something happening are we opening
the door no I don't think so I think we
just need to go this way
okay oh you'll think we're going out no
no no no
bring on them let's go
please complete no reward received you
have completed this Quest right okay
well all right reward received sadness I
mean I've already completed the quest so
wait we are going out it
no you got the wrong way ah
I have to talk to the dude yeah we we
need we need to wait for the NPCs
oh gosh those days I made the same
mistake I also did the same mistake
makes me a little yeah
do it again no no no no no we just have
to go all the way back yeah that's like
just a shortcut
[Music]
I got my girls
oh oh only one person had to talk to
yeah
um ah there we go completed by the
crownster
now we're opening the door aura
[Music]
okay no
oh everybody's dead sweet there's one
that's still alive talks a lot do you
have any money oh yeah
over where this guy talks too much okay
who did this
people
yeah he's super dead now
jump jump oh well not super dead enough
girls are you coming over
oh you guys already yeah
I I don't want to skip it but yeah
okay let's go
it's okay I already saw the stare at the
story oh you guys want to see it it's in
my Beta stream chat if you're curious
about story
oh yeah let's out mommy yeah
they're all watching I see
yeah we all know Lilith is hot okay we
get it are we watching the cutscene
I mean I skipped it I don't know I'm not
pressing anything I'm afraid if I press
Skip and then you guys gonna be skipped
oh no no it's not it's not oh really
yeah there's a symbol that shows that
someone's watching okay then okay next
time maybe I'll launch
Mean Girls play together don't you even
worry about that
yeah Mean Girls sleigh
crony yes I wanted to ask you something
yes would you maybe consider
um sharing some of that cake with me
hahaha
it's not she's in desperate need I am in
desperate need
but it's still like nothing compared to
your cake and that's just not fair
I mean it's it's can't help what you're
born with
yeah I mean I mean I got to deny it I
can't I was gonna say it's not that good
but you know it is pretty it is pretty
good question for you to sit on and
stream for long hours
oh wait I was gonna try to kill
Kyle yeah Kyla just turned into a band
yes really why did I miss that why why
are you throwing your skills to me yeah
closely
okay okay so so no cake for me is that
what you're saying no I think I think
you should ask again for them to like
buff your buff your cake I feel like the
buff that I got uh was the first and the
last one there will not be any more
Buffs what
this is
it's not fair
I it's okay I'll make up well make up
for it with um my dance moves yeah yeah
you could probably get another like you
know outfit
where there is more cake butt pads
in the new outfit but be like oh I don't
want to be able to see the butt pads or
notice that they're butt pads but there
are butt pads in the skirt or whatever
yeah for in the shorts
well uh as far as I know they wouldn't
change like you know the butt size just
because there's a new outfit
but but you could still ask for the pads
though like yeah like they can't really
say no because those are real things
yeah well I know Kpop Idols use it yeah
exactly
so maybe it's a tribute
to K-pop Idol butt pad
you know when I get down on the floor
you know yeah ma'am I need some butt
bags
[Applause]
for one million dollars but you know
even the insurance it's just not not
enough it has a use do we need to climb
down I think we need to climb down
has anyone talked about the talk with
the whatever sign is that like in the
corner of the room
right now I see now I see a quest mark
thingy
okay okay okay
nice thank you more yeah Morp says no
problem
place to trap nope
[Music]
million dollar booty million dollar
booty
crony did you know
that your mommy is next on my list
she's going after all the hollow moms
what do you mean
what do you mean what I mean well you
know you know that I'm I'm very popular
with homo moms but the thing is that
your mom is kind of special to me
because she's a hello project otaku just
like me
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
she she will maybe adopt me you know
because she she she's into Idols I'm
into Idols I'm sure she wants a daughter
like me you can have a sister
is my game glitched you guys are submits
now
you're just all about in the back what
happened
no you guys are Frozen at the gate oh
really I can't attack enemies
no froze bro you cannot move
I mean I can move no you're standing
standings still yeah I think you're
having like a
um a network
issue a DC maybe ah
um
yeah if I leave the party and come back
do I do I have to start over or is it
okay it's a good question
I mean it's okay
um there's gonna be like a portal that
you can teleport to us later on
okay yeah no worries
okay
progress is based on party leader well
that's good news hey it's okay okay let
me get out of here
yum yum
it didn't no I'm not this this owning my
papa but I mean one can have more than
one parent right
Mark is yes
why are you girls dying what oh no it's
because of like if we go further and
it's not in the range it's gonna be like
we're dying
[Applause]
I
where is okay we can't we still at the
door okay and can we just need to go
around we gotta run all the way back
all the way back yeah I'm wearing all
the way back
kind of far away I'm a little further to
oh no nothing changed anything changed
yeah let me see
um let me try again to just leave
okay
did you maybe just restart the game
completely yeah maybe restart the battle
net I already start the game
let's wait here let's not go too far in
case she has to walk all the way no no
it's fine uh the portal can be like
teleport to
I'm okay
yeah yeah
luck is not good tonight
[Music]
that's what matters that's the fun part
you know about collabing there's like
issues the club is endearing
now let's morph back into parties yeah
I'm in yeah hey your party campaign
state does not match with the party
leaders you'll be making progress in the
party leaders campaign okay yeah now to
teleport to you guys you need to go to
the
um the Waypoint they're like there's
gonna be like four portals just hop into
us
okay teleport to oh crony yep okay
macaroni oh okay
morph is on the way okay yes ladies
the team's all here okay let's go
speaking of macaroni
last time I was in America I had my
first ever macaroni and cheese
what'd you think how was it was amazing
yeah I knew you'd like it yeah it was so
good but the portion was so big I could
I only eat like half of it I swear it
was huge I tried my best
better to share
American portion yeah what the [\h__\h]
American portion please they are too big
I feel like it's better to make it a
shared plate
yeah but it was so good I want to try
making it at home
yeah it's pretty it's fairly easy to do
is home cooking
um don't really know how
mac and cheese tastes like yeah
even the inside you've never had instant
before no voila
what I thought everybody over there eats
mac and cheese all the time
Maybe
maybe not me or maybe not I'm gonna ship
you a bunch of instances I'm gonna ship
you a ton of instant Kraft mac and
cheese oh I did instant ones good too
again
yeah
they're decent if it's not as good as
like The Gourmet stuff like stuff you
might get at like a restaurant that's
for sure
but what the [\h__\h] still pretty tasty I
mean I think it depends on the person
and not in excess of course oh gosh
pill finder
that guy's annoying
oh yeah
yeah I got
um Kiara's birthday present it came in
today
I saw something on the Internet and I
thought you'd really like it what yeah
you're getting me a birthday present yes
just a little thing I hope to ship it to
you and make it in time for your
birthday but I don't know maybe you'll
never use them but I thought I don't
know I thought you can give it to me in
in Japan
oh yeah wait wait wait Chiara is like
I was trying to kill an enemy and went
in the same spot where I was putting my
mouse at suddenly something appeared and
I accidentally clicked yes oh no but
like what's the leader what was that
anyway here let me maybe we can invite
you back if I the leader now is crony
okay yeah you're the leader now Oh no
you're joining uh you're about to be
transferred to the party okay transfer
now did I miss something
you're all fine can I can I delegate my
host to you just just leave the party
just leave the party
just leave the party just leave the
party uh right click okay on your yeah
and now and now it's gonna be me okay
I'm leaving the party no no okay
[Music]
I'll be the party leader that's fine
I'll be the party leader everybody else
come back okay I'm inviting the others
back into okay
I'll be the party leader on my powerful
PS5 just leave it to me
I can host
okay I I need to catch up on you girls
okay now I don't see anyone
are you guys gotta teleport to Me Maybe
yeah I don't know
I'm confused take up teleport to town
first the [\h__\h]
okay
yeah we just need to talk together
I mean I mean you can just go
yeah just go to the portal oh
it's gonna be easier
okay
hold hands all right I'll wait for you
guys
okay coming
what was that thing that popped up on my
screen anyway
did you see it
let's go
yeah
yeah sometimes like the leader will do
something or like
a character will do something and then
if you decline
it's like join in it'll kick you from
the party
um
oh okay some cutscenes what
I don't know
it's just not in here oh I'm still here
um I was gonna say no way no way
ready yet yes RIP and tear decompose The
Flash
kill me off like that
I'm still in the game let's go
I I could still hear from boys
it's because I am here no way it's all
in my head oh my goodness
oh boy I'm not gonna fall for it I
should have teleported what have I done
you can still do
it
get the shaman
you're gonna revive everyone
oh no dear oh dear oh bother
oh joy oh you're almost here
I am almost here and I'm gonna die no
don't you got this you're not gonna die
Pro tips don't die
just don't yeah just you don't drink all
the potions
I'll come to pick you up
yeah it brought a whole party I thought
you guys would like the experience
points
oh hell yeah
hi
okay that's it that was not so bad there
were more I guess they lost interest
oh I see them
are you taking care of them yeah yeah of
course yeah what kind of what kind of
party host would we be
your Uber is here crony
yeah getting the Uber
oh whoa thank you
no
nope nope
big boy
down here it's okay finishing the
dungeon
is crooking me
okay no
gotta clean the battlefield gotta clean
the battlefield
oh a succubus cool tornadoes nice nice
nice little thick
not ready
[Music]
Uber
okay okay
[Laughter]
I hope I feel years coming off of my
existence
every time you say that
cute
[Music]
boys leaving so many bodies around guys
I have to clean them all up
thank you they've had enough of me chat
already I I guess next time I'll play
alone no no no no no no
no don't do that no no alone
all these terms you know where I'm
learning them where
well chat
whole live and through everything I'm
doing that's connected with whole life
you know
oh
my education is thanks to all of you my
condolences
oh yeah
ouch oh
some advice and don't worry you can
leave the corpses they're useful for
other skill abilities
oh like what necromancer of advice I
don't really understand
I mean I don't really see another use
for them is the thing but if I if I do
see a use for them then I can understand
I just kind of like to leave a clean
battle yeah oh wait okay I understand
now because I I I I know that skill the
corpse explosion skill is absolutely
insane you will oh that one's pretty
handy I like that one I haven't seen
that yet if you get to it in the skill
tree choose it and then whenever you run
around and you press the scale all the
corpses all the dead enemies around you
will like explode and do AOE damage yeah
it'll be like fireworks yeah I love that
that sounds amazing God I love
necromancer
they're so Nifty yeah
hey
ouch
this dungeon is very very long
I'm making good progress though yeah I
think if we finish this it's already
quite an accomplishment
lights
my dragons are so cute I hope I get some
fan art with my dragons
your little Hydra heads yeah
[Applause]
around
and Cali will play skeletons yeah wolves
and and Kyla as as oh Kyla with her as a
wolf
really and then crony with her
chronicopter Souls
yeah actually wolves might be a better
idea
companions
I can be your companions though who are
your companion we're all companions you
want to be my wolf wow okay ready for
mobs maybe maybe not like that
what do you mean not like that what do
you think I said
yeah
I'm drawing it right now
I better just kill all of this mobs then
think about that
it's okay
yeah they're definitely taking a lot
more time to kill which I appreciate
yeah
I think it feels better idea that we
changed yeah I didn't want to do it
alone but as a party
um yeah yeah
it's a [\h__\h] chaos though it's nice I
love it we did it
[Music]
the boss might be a bit harder now might
actually kill a couple of you well
looking fine let's go I can't wait
and if you die from the boss like just
so like a respawn a thing here nothing
great question no idea but hey not
knowing is part of the fun yeah right it
really raises the snakes but as the
ritual started already here or what what
your voices dead priest
oh no she's just talking next to me okay
she's just a little freaky
it's kind of long a little bit it's just
drawing fan art I have your back lady
we want to watch this costume this one's
pretty cool oh whoopsies I kind of
skipped it already
your hands are so funny where is
everyone oh yeah there they are
[\h__\h]
hey why aren't you guys moving oh
because you're watching it all right
it's fine I got it
enjoy the cutscene I'll hold down the
fort I've done this battle before you
see stop but okay okay you're fighting
someone yes Mother stop you fighting
alive
I'm good don't worry about it I got my
skeletons
she awakened me magpies I saw a magpie
blood ritual the other day on YouTube
okay I thought you were just gonna say I
saw a magpie and I was gonna say oh I'll
make my blood ritual oh
it's a bird right yeah it's a birthday
just to collect things I believe right
it wasn't the blood ritual I guess it
was death ritual
they were crying when one was like dead
and all the magpies were gathering
around and going like
oh they're warning oh yeah oh hi I'm
here now we're fighting now
what what's uh who are we fighting eh
we are fighting the mother
wow yeah she's really pissed right now
okay wait I I I'm never gonna look
blinds again
if I'm missing all the action no no no
no I wouldn't have skipped it if I had
known that there was gonna be
should we fight the health spawns and
all that over here yeah that's probably
a good idea she's immune yeah
gotta kill her her demons
all right
okay come on get him oh
get the hell spawn yeah okay that's fun
nice
let's go
nice soup don't worry I got potions
oceans for days let's go
yum yum oh
you want some of this you want some of
this you want some let's go I did not
mean to do that like this oh yeah these
are some big boys
all right it's getting a little tough I
like it yeah this is fun
Lord
oh God I should focus on one skeleton
where are you at yeah that's usually a
good idea
oh the pit Lord is pretty scary
oh it's a spicy meatball
come on
[Music]
potions
do we have to kill enemies in order to
make them spawn or his one yeah
close
I'm gonna start thinking Portugal's
original song Hitler really likes me he
will not leave me alone
that's fine I can be a distraction
you're the chosen one the bait in the
chosen one yeah you're the chosen one
[Music]
[Applause]
but my HP was struggling yeah
me
as I was protecting you
everything I don't know are we skipping
I have no idea
I'm not skipping it because I feel bad
that I skipped at the first time
blessed blood okay
beg if you need to oh we're gonna see
the problem
I'm going to finish it
meets me in the Mr Woods
there's Australian people say pravar
ES
no no
if not
okay I'm done watching please leave me
okay okay I'm done all right me too okay
me too
there's one Team Quest complete
we need to go back home
we can just teleport right
I cannot I think so we need to go back
yeah oh okay we need to go back
all right a little walk in the park
let's get going
make sure to walk and leave a one line
or hold your partner's hand
yeah
my hands yes ma'am like some ducks okay
like a conga line
oh hi
nice
more enemies more exp very nice
I'm just gonna take balloon
Goblin nice yeah I'm little Goblin I
can't help but more physical no I'm a
loot Goblin just just I am in general
I love Gathering Gathering things
I get it we fired though
okay
waste ah this is where we accidentally
left before yup
where is it
okay we need to go there to find near
Rail
oh I had dead beats down
down you go
is this like the I don't know like the
the deadbeats that try to sign up for a
job at Cali's place but like failed so
they get mad yeah they Rebel Revenge
anger beasts
where did Carla go it's okay just come
here
we must hold hands or walk in the line
no my hands are just that long
dude are you like Lucy or something yeah
my answer is just flexible and that long
it's amazing I forgive
but not again lady not again I like that
name I'm sorry no traitor Beats
Trader beach sounds like a merchant name
I know like Trader Joe's or something
the trader Beats from the Trader Joe's
full of bus in 10 minutes I don't know
if we can join the world boss
just getting no need
I'm Invincible oh nice
nice do you guys want to join the world
boss
level 35 yeah level 35 Plus
um
we can take them we can take them no no
yeah we can yeah
it's it's there it's like a
okay
no it's like the level 35.
oh yeah I'll do these four of us yes if
you combine all our levels it's way over
35. was that how it works
[Music]
okay oh is it a time thing never mind if
it's time then forget it 10 minutes and
10 minutes we need to just go as fast as
possible today but actually I can do it
if you you guys really want to do it I
can just you know really because I can I
can go with my horse and then you guys
can teleport there if you want to try no
no no no no okay
one time when we're higher level we'll
do it okay yeah
okay
then we can do it confidently probably
why you're so enlightened
oh I touched a shrine
oh nice I didn't see one I was enchanted
I was blessed with like a momentary
boost
yeah yeah
several of those and they all have like
different oh I see here's one artillery
Shrine
we attack faster in summon holy arrows
holy arrows
that sounds fun okay we need to find the
neural yeah my arrows
check out my arrows I'm sure she's
around somewhere
chest
okay
[Music]
I love the music in this game it gives
me light Skyrim vibes
yes music is good
I don't know Nero standing somewhere I
found her before somewhere here but it's
been too long I don't remember
[Music]
um
there's a chest here nice
though
chest though I want chest though
oh no the trees
I don't want to hurt the trees the trees
are good people
trees are on people cure they're good
people you're not yeah
they're good trees but they're not too
cute is what I'm saying
wake up
they're good people
they have a soul I know it's been a long
time wandering these woods but you gotta
stop mistaking trees for people
I mean the trees that we know is not
moving
so maybe it can be people
oh oh yeah yeah
right right well yeah all right ladies
whatever keeps you sane
okay
oh oh
there hey it wasn't a person it was a
stone
darkened Holt
hello welcome it was snowy
it's very cozy I like it I love smelling
games we're getting closer to Santa
Claus's home with everyone yeah I want
Christmas to come already this
please let's enjoy the summer a little
bit no hate summer summer sucks Summer
sucks I agree
whoa
[Music]
what's the cheapest cell though I wonder
if I've been good or naughty this year
I'd say good
maybe your chat can answer that
well they don't know me yet they don't
know like who
does someone know you better who's gonna
be the judge I know me I think I've been
pretty good and if Santa's not gonna
give me anything that's fine because I'm
just gonna get my own gift
a very good way of thinking about it
very salty no that's not salty what do
you mean
I I couldn't understand it I can
definitely like I don't need Santa's
help to get me what I want I can just
get it myself it's a real girl boss
attitude and I appreciate it let's go
yeah thank you
no problem girl
why are we fighting Phantoms again oh
It's a Spooky Forest
why why are we going back and forth
there's a leader here but none of us
know who it is
I was just looking at my inventory it's
fall I want to sell some stuff yeah my
inventory is full too actually yeah I'm
gonna go back
we can teleport to the city yeah yeah
yeah yeah we could do that okay okay
let's go
[Music]
kill shad
quick teleport break at least it's not
as bad as in like Diablo 2 when you had
to go and sell your [\h__\h] after five
minutes of fighting all the time always
inventory full it's uh uh it was so um
it was typical though it was like the
charm Point somehow
yeah
diabolo hey Bolo
let's Salvage all of them
oh I got some really nice new items
actually dang are you selling them or
are you
um salvaging salvaging okay both
cool
[Music]
all right
um junk common
junk junk
can I not just sell these guys because
these like I don't need the the looks of
these I'm gonna go to my wardrobe
because that's the most important part
I should actually carry
this
um
this is
why not they're so hot yeah that's what
I was thinking
this do I have a stash in this game yet
because yeah of course fire of course
yeah okay is it by the Wardrobe yep okay
let's have a look at look
okay
let's buy something did you do it
through it question is important
fashion is pretty important
[Music]
what's this
whoa oh this one is so cool oh no it's
so expensive expensive
[Music]
oh
Kyla probably has yeah
I can I can I can give you some yeah no
way no way look you're giving me in a
light trash no
yeah
so kind
I just saw something in the store that's
like freaking expensive I don't need it
I don't need it
my my chat tells me not to buy things
yeah just dollars because you can just
uh pick him up
you just stunned
uh
apply look
you still won the gold no
no
I am done uh doing my things
okay
which which
uh what am I which teleportation thingy
am I using
we can use any hours yeah
this is the winding Wing one I guess
winding away yeah yeah okay
okay
me too back
back
no Moe's not streaming my TV today
I figure I figure three is enough I
figure three is enough yeah because it's
not like we have vastly different povs
so yeah yeah okay oh heavy scythe
that seems like it could be good oh
brutal heavy sight yes for the Grim
Reaper
oh
yes very nice beautiful oh
there's a scary Red portal here
oh we should go in that looks like fire
fiery portal oh yeah
where are we in hell
the dog speak ing to us it's
a wall you big wolf I guess the big wolf
saying actually meow meow meow I don't
know how you guys know about the lore
but it's looks like Mephisto
who are you Mephisto oh
my bloodied wolf I see
why are you here this wolf saved me in
the mountains
but
are you watching the cutscene I'm
watching oh gear
box always oh this seems kind of like I
anti anti-hero character
it is Fluffy yeah
wait
can you pet the dog
that is the important question with
games these days no
it is
if no petting then [\h__\h] game
[Laughter]
okay I have a question Kiara did did I
ever actually ask you to step on my back
or to just crack my back because I don't
remember asking you to step on my back
no you you did you did remember in the
studio you laid down with your face on
the ground when we did the pretty uh the
collab
okay on the ground and you were like
can you step on my back and crack it the
way that I ask people to crack my back
is I breathe in and then I ask you to
push down as I breathe out but you're
supposed to use both your hands oh yeah
I was I was too weak oh didn't you crack
your back before Kelly yeah yeah we've
cracked each other's backs but with our
hands
successfully damn yeah
what the [\h__\h] why is it just me and
Chihuahua now nah because we're still in
outside of the portal yeah yeah let's go
is it back cracking time
foreign
I would also like to get my back cracked
but that that the way you do it Cali
just scares me I don't want to hurt you
oh that's okay I mean whenever people
give me massages they kind of do a
similar thing so yeah but they know how
to do it and I I could possibly kill you
and when I do it on a long time no
as long as you don't like you know crack
the neck
I think it should be fine unless you
want them to rest forever then you can
do that
I don't remember you stepping on my back
qo because I would have remembered that
because whenever I go to get massages
they say can I step on your back and I
say no you can't
oh really yeah oh
no you cannot do that
you wanted me to crack you back so you
were on the ground I remember that you
definitely used your hands you know
I don't know how it feels like
my noodle house yes you don't know how
it feels like I've never gone anymore
but why yeah we should go
I know yeah I'm afraid that I will get
addicted to that because what I know is
people say that you know like once you
try it and then you're gonna get
yeah
we will always want to get get a massage
once you did it once yeah it's good for
you especially if you stream a lot you
know yeah
I think they'll probably like massage
you and be like holy heck your back is
so stiff what is wrong with you
like a tree
okay don't you feel back pain ever Kyla
not really not really not really yeah
wow what kind of chair do you have oh
yeah very nice chair right
that's a few good ones which ones can we
like Miller
[Music]
yeah I have a Herman Miller too oh me
too
it's just like um normal gaming chair
though
yeah even people say like the office
here is better or like long hours right
yeah
if you stream like 10 hours do you sit
straight like properly the whole time
not really not really most of the time I
lay down
my fears know about that like I I really
and then like usually my voice
somehow change a bit into like very very
calm one that's the time when I lay down
yeah I can lay down and play game oh you
recline yeah
yeah that's one good thing about gaming
chairs is that you can completely slide
down I I've fallen asleep while doing
what
it was like a bed like a gaming chair
bed and like it's like a desk set up so
that it's like a desk on top of a bed so
you wake up game and go to sleep oh I
know about that
uh-huh uh-huh yeah I don't think I've
seen that one
no that doesn't sound amazing you'll be
bedridden for the rest of your life but
the bed sores Chad are we starting what
foyer
oh okay
I think I'm frozen again oh really oh no
everybody's jogging in place skeletons
included or maybe it's because of the
Cross play you know
um
which is really too bad but let's see
I'll just leave
it's okay
oh Kiara's the host again oh yay oh it's
back look at this beautiful Circle I
feel like if I talk to this mirror it's
gonna like tell me who's the prettiest
of them all
yeah we all know the answer
well okay
in this game
my hot lady I mean look at her she's I
mean
I mean this is true but yeah okay
outside the game do you want to save
benefits what what are you saying I
didn't say anything who is the prettiest
of them all crony no I don't know I
don't know I just think it's a
no-brainer
foreign
[Music]
you're too pretty for that
I'm feeling kind of my face is turning
red onions
transform
wow you're like Chopper I'm not ready
yet
oh no I'm not ready yet
I have to kill it it's an enemy no don't
kill my wolves no no
no no no
[Music]
how many wolves can you summon two or no
oh
my dress I don't know oh
that's kind of cool I think four is the
max though I'm pretty sure oh really
okay yeah
[Music]
do rose only have the Shadow Ball
floating around you anything else
they just reduce damage
uh that's
getting received
okay I'm sure you have something better
maybe in the future
you know I kind of doubt that let me
take a quick look
Wibble is that question towards me or
towards crony you [\h__\h] if you set
your first enchantment no why am I stuck
at this dark screen it's okay
[Music]
I have nothing I only set up traps I
have no companion what is the screen
I've never seen it before press yes this
River can be used
what do I do with this
to unlock complete sorcerer Legacy
Legacy
you have to do quests to unlock
enchantments
you need to finish your priority Quest
oh oh the projects too early
[Music]
let's see I restart my PS5 oh
okay
I'll see eventually
from Level 15. shh
oh I have a quest that came in when I
turned number 15. well that was within
today so I couldn't have done it
questo
where do I see my quests again
press J
J why is it not Q
because Q is potion right ah right yeah
so it is
ah priority Quest oh sorcerer the legacy
of the Maggie this one you guys snitch
off collab I really want to do off
collab but yeah yeah I want to do in an
off collab I don't know I want to do
like um you know board games I really
want to do like more games
I'll bring a I'll bring a typically
German one oh maybe everybody can bring
a board game from their own culture yeah
yeah
we need to get perms yeah yeah we need
we need to win it yeah
that's a good idea oh my God
I think uh connecting to diabolo for
services I think I might get in
that's okay too do you know this um like
it's similar to Jenga do you know this
game where you have like a lot of really
thin wooden sticks and then you let them
fall on the table so they're like all
like a yeah yeah I know it's like a mess
and you have to like you know pick them
out like in Jenga without making the
other ones move I think yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
I've played that that's a fun one yeah
yeah let me join your party
I think they had some colors on them too
and depending on the color it even gave
more points or you had to get the ones I
don't I don't remember the rules anymore
old memory unlocked yeah very nostalgic
very nostalgic
children's games you're back in the
party let's go
well I'm very far from you guys
[Music]
um
there's no portals here
wait I'm gonna hold on let me go to
Cabbage wait hold on nope no they
appeared right as I went away
yay I'll go find you guys
I wonder if all necromancers are doomed
to be patanko wait now crony stream dead
what
what is happening
she's not talking to us so her internet
died
on a weird night I'm the only one so far
who didn't have any kind of issues yet
there she goes there she goes
I'll be back sometime
but it has been it has been two hours
yeah yeah true it has been two hours too
yeah yeah I was gonna say crony sleepy
from from morning Maui sleeping from
night time yeah next time we can play
when it's like morning for me and then
it's better times for you girls I think
except for yeah Kyla said it's any time
many times good for her that was always
good at any time
anytime anytime yeah maybe next time
actually 5 a.m for me four different
time zones here right yeah yeah
yeah
yeah but we just we'll just we'll just
go in a circle everybody suffers
sometimes sometimes such as the
dying somebody Stoppers
I like it though it's fun
next time it can be me
oh you wake up I'll wake up I often
uh need to fix my sleep schedule anymore
what time is morning for you guys like
oh
so so what time you say normally like 11
12. oh okay
oh yeah what about you
I I don't know it depends it really
depends I wake up
um whenever I need to
yeah yeah you don't sleep much do you I
sleep I see I sleep better yeah I
already tried this conversation with her
Kiara I sleep I sleep that's more
and by the way I don't think we can play
next week because I don't have time next
week maybe the week after yes okay it's
okay
yeah we'll see how it works out
yeah I don't know what happened
Ronnie where are you I at least I at
least want to say goodbye to her yeah
at least we need to know we need to know
what happened at least right agreed
isn't the concept next next well that's
just one day
that's not gonna block my whole wink off
foreign
let's see um oh what was that
yes
[Music]
traveling quite a bit come over here and
Stand By Me and and and uh okay and if
we stand in a triangle maybe we can and
pour some blood on the ground maybe we
can summon Chrome okay
that's a great idea
chronic
I feel like you're not putting in enough
passion into the summoning
my salmon
I feel like I'm alone in here you know
and this like witchcraft thing you know
I don't know
sex thing
ah crony sent us a message oh she did
open Discord Do You Wanna Say Goodbye
NBC
it's been two hours anyway so
a little piece out should the need arise
yeah
and I I want to say bye bye the crony
somebody worked at least yeah
we did that one big dungeon so that was
pretty good I feel good about it
um
oh
I think oh okay
something I guess she got she got sick
of waiting for her
I don't know if we leave right I don't
think we can continue it later on from
here you know
yeah
hello hi I'm finishing it with Kayla
hi hello
hi Connie
and welcome completely under I love this
internet I
sweater crony it happens to the best of
us yeah it's okay
sorry about that
no worries
that's all good
switched internet recently and I think
that's the problem I talked to them
looks like I need to talk to them again
well the trail
talking to people I must wait a moment
yeah it takes too much energy
when do we go what the [\h__\h]
well no I don't want to force anyone to
stay but if it's true what Kyla says
then I would probably finish it at least
with Kayla
[Music]
um I think we are halfway
but I mean I don't know um
are you planning to do like a solo
Diablo no oh okay no okay that's not
really okay
then we just need to split around this
then it's okay
we can spit around this
one is good or maybe or maybe we can
split we can just split
like one go to the left one go to the
right ah okay yeah
I'll go right bye-bye okay just make
sure you don't die
I'll help as much as I can but if I DC
again that's probably curtains for for
more for tonight
okay
Stay Alone
um
oh
I need to come and help out my skeletons
can't help you
hi thank you
yeah
finally splitting up oh no no they
shouldn't you never split the party
rule number one of tcrpg crony is here
in spirit
ual support
no worries oh my God I'm out of potions
it pulled me over to him
hurry up skeletons what am I paying you
for yeah
they gotta get to work what the [\h__\h]
Callie I know right they're just not
pulling their their weight
holy [\h__\h] again
um
let's go honey if you do you think you
like um be back you don't have to force
yourself but
if it takes too long don't worry about
it
oh it's just uh
yeah they
Mother of God
are you on your phone
yeah they they told me to uh just you
know stick around for 10 minutes but I'm
pretty sure it'll if dream will be done
in 10 minutes so oh no wonderful I
should not have switched service what
was I thinking
ah
why did I switch
by the way
yeah the bus is here so if you guys can
oh yeah
we're almost there
yeah I I
nice it's okay it's okay it will take
some time I thought you said the boss
plastic
[Music]
let's go
no more Leroy
I was I never ever had to use it in the
proper context before I'm very sad so
now you finally there
hey girls know where that's from I know
I know yeah I know the reference
World of War cool Leroy dragon
for the block craft when that Meme was
happening
yeah from the Hearthstone
it is very classic
I will call you now Leroy Kaila nice
Jenkins yeah
okay
I'm just gonna slowly decompose you and
have my skeletons hit you with their
Shields
foreign
what's that mean I think it's a name in
general yeah yeah
so who's Harold
who is there any meaning of Terror ouch
it's kind of like a dorky name oh I'm
sorry there might be some Heralds in
chat
that was rude
connects with a office worker I think
sounds so serious
ly
the beautiful name it's it's the name of
a smart person which is why I said kind
of to kind of Dork meat
so weird how certain names just happens
to them
you know real smart
you know some names you feel like they
only fit adults but then how do the like
they were children
yeah yeah but did it feel weird when
they were when they were joking kind of
crazy to think about it like I can't
really imagine a challenge
Daryl
Daryl Daryl yeah Daryl
I can never I just can't imagine a child
named Daryl I hear the name Daryl and I
think of a guy in like a business suit
the coffee with like in the break room
hey Daryl what's up
how's the workload go no you know just
the usual filling out forms it's cool
Daryl hey you know what I'll talk to you
later
grab a drink afterwards I like the name
Daryl doll I like it maybe because I
I've never like met anyone before in
Austria who's who's got that name
oh
Daddy
are you girls like gonna
teleport out oh yeah
use that teleport but there's still like
there's still the campaign quest in
inside no but I oh yeah
I'm not even moving I I okay I spawned
there after the portal
taking like different portals maybe I
don't know I don't take any portal oh
that works too
I didn't see a portal they're a blue
portal um outside that room
I am blind
okay I'm always Blended
this Ledger was written it was next to
the box and theories created
first Necromancer cool that guy's cool
that's my leader no oh
but it can still work there must be a
spell in this book we can use to bring
my money
because at this point I skipped so much
story that we have no idea what's going
on yeah I was gonna send to it in my
other stream so no worries I'm still
so far ahead of this
okay I think it's done
yeah yeah it's done
Quest is done okay let's go we can just
teleport back Yay good job let's go
well done team wow oh
streaming stream fun stream
oh there's a giga chat here
whoa Giga Chad what's going on
somehow I feel like that somebody who is
a fan
well that was really fun guys thanks for
inviting me to play
yeah well thank you so much thank you so
much for inviting me too
oh yeah but no no um no pressure that we
always have to be for but it would be
nice
I wanna play until next time crony I
already said it next time we can do it
the evening time for you
a morning for me we'll figure it out
daytime can we yeah yeah afternoonish
thank you for inviting me to no no
problem I think I'll read some super
chats actually because it was kind of a
short stream yeah I think I think me too
yeah
[Music]
thank you
have fun okay thank you so much peace
[Music]
hi
we're back hold on I think I think I can
go back to my first ISP right
so that the LCD can be up
okay hold on
the stream gonna be
um the stream gonna be down for a while
but
hold on let me let me
leave the game first because it's gonna
be disconnected
okay
[Music]
um
okay
be right back the stream gonna be
offline for I don't know um one minute
be right back
okay
okay are we back are we back
um
wait what
hmm
the Diablo is not connecting so I think
I need to just change the
whatever the screen maybe right the
screen the screen
the screen just changed this screen
okay
merge screen no no no
why we need to change the risk no no no
no don't
um
wait let me setting up first
ah
okay uh maybe just change to this one
but I don't know
not like that obviously
if it's like this it's gonna be like I
don't know hold on
ah
[Music]
uh wait I think it's the wrong one
wow it's double
it's all double music
what is double music
okay
[Music]
why I'm so big
this is not right
[Music]
we
said
sit
[Music]
why I'm so small right now
whatever
the hammer actually needs to be like fit
into the box
nah it's fine
it's slime then whatever
Hammer not food it's a flute hammer
okay
okay so I gonna start from the SC first
foreign
okay
uh Jordan and Ryan for Mommy it's real
blessed no no falling asleep get some
help for mommy no mommy mommy
fee faction have fun Chronicle Kiara
Kali thank you so much thank you
and then
and then Yama bro what is what is yamabu
doing suddenly
ihongo
it's okay no worries
um
wow nihongo
break roll even better Yama bro
very nice
[Music]
thank you so much fifaction for the pink
so fast thank you thank you thank you
and then hello hello
foreign
[Music]
that's actually the reason why I uh why
I
played a electric Druid just because I
want to play
uh this kind of the same one not really
but yeah you know
it's a different class but it's kind of
the same like the element
of it so yeah
um
Kyla played Dre literally she bear with
me yeah true
true
are what a sight I'm happy I get some
help get some help oh who knows oh is it
about the cake one I just I just got
literally no comment you know about the
Cake part
because
I don't know I just
I'm just confused what what to say about
the cake
it's just like I know
but yeah
uh
so for you even though I'm not watching
when you do live on game it's okay thank
you so much as I'm hero hello hello
nice fight thank you thank you arigato
and then
don't be root cannot be like that
without back pain yeah I mean no no I I
don't wanna jinx it but I know a lot of
people that sit
um for a long time on the chair
gonna be like I'm having like a back
pain or something like that yeah I know
I I really know that it's a very serious
thing
for all of the people
out there
um when they cut the back pain it's
really painful I know
it's like unbearable pain yeah
but luckily I've never felt anything
like that but I just don't want to jinx
it and I don't want to
ever got any back pain so please don't
but yeah
yeah
that's why
that's why yeah I've I've I've never
done any massage in my life that's true
that's 100 real
but I know you know like um
uh Mama Ella also
uh not the type of like getting massage
person so yeah um
but since
Papa Ella really like massage so since I
was really really like
a small child
I know that Papa Ella always like say
that this is how you massage this is how
you do massage to other people yeah so
uh back then when I was still in school
I tried to massage
um
my uh what is that classmates right and
then and then they uh say it like it's a
certified uh
very good very good yeah yeah yeah
so probably I need to probably I need to
test it my massage skill for other whole
ID members probably yeah because I
really want to get that certification
that certification of
um
best
massager of whole ID right yeah yeah I
really want to I really want to probably
next time when I can do like um of
collab or maybe just like any any
anything
together maybe
I can try to do that yeah
yeah yeah because because I was like um
got a lot of trainings from Papa Ella
back then
mm-hmm
very nice
the other members don't know no no no no
I haven't got the chance yet maybe next
time
maybe next time yeah
maybe maybe the Holo ID gen one
will be glad to have a free massage
service
right maybe
Maybe
Sala
foreign
[Music]
let's go
very nice
Indonesian word let's go let's go
this is
[Music]
foreign
yeah yeah yeah
yeah but right now it's just YOLO it's
okay
[Music]
very nice
and then
nice
Terminus your spirit box for chronic
crony are you with us
you're good
cannot be like that at all
and then I succeeded I passed into
college
thank you very much for your
motivational words it really means a lot
for me also thank you for promo thank
you so much thank you so much for the
updates
congratulations
hmm
Fifi table trick great run fun times
with the ladies good luck on the next
train thanks hey thank you so much thank
you thank you
very good thanks for the collapse so how
straight
quite tanky even though it's still like
level 10 I can feel it like I can feel
like it's quite tanky and I don't know
why but I feel like
why is it like more tanky than the
Barbarian that I played before
or maybe it's because
why is it lagging the l2d nice or maybe
it's because
um
the statue of Lilith probably
because before the stream started
yeah before the stream started I was
like um collecting the statue of Lilith
and I already uh
uh got
um
all the first four already done
the fifth one the last one I already got
like 15th yeah so it's like
um
like 20 less than 20. yeah the how is
that one it's like
uh uh less than 20. and then it's all
done
so yeah it's kind of if you feel like
why is it like um level one but it's
Stronger Yeah it's because of the Lilith
statue I think
I I I also can fill it like the
difference
so yeah
and then I think after this I will con I
will
complete all of the statue because it's
super easy it's gonna be like um
less than 20 more so yeah
I think I'll just complete it tonight
yeah all the extra stats and skill
points yeah ah it's gonna be like
80 plus 80 all stats after
completing all of the Statue of Lilith I
think I think right I think it's plus 80
all stats
if we can manage to
get all
hmm
then
foreign
ER almost zero
gito
almost zero
yeah I think
um the reason why I thought Alias so
hard last time I think it's also because
of that like I got almost zero of
statue of Lilith not even 10 I think
it's just like very bad
but after all
yeah
but after all I feel like
uh
uh I feel like yeah it's just a normal
color right doing everything in the hard
way first so in the hardest way possible
it's not in a hard way in the hardest
way possible because why not right yeah
foreign
[Music]
but
to be
available
really really helps because it's like
plus 80 all stats so it's really good to
complete that I think
um
[Music]
I forget all characters yes
true true
[Music]
Lucas is
yeah
the the statue of Lily is
we need to find it but there are a lot
of guides already
well mine sorcerer's damage
um
golden reduction yes yes yes
you owe 100
something 160 is it 100
100 I don't know
wait let me let me let me check it
um
photos that deal of
[Music]
um
Diablo floor
yeah yeah 160.
exactly 160.
I think I'm right now I'm let me check
let me check the picture first uh
[Music]
picture picture
the however is
however it's 34 right
I think I have
34. yeah 17 more 17 more and then I'll
be all done
it's gonna be like taking only
uh an hour or less I guess
[Music]
dungeon we're gonna do the dungeon we
need to clear all of the dungeons for
the points too right we can do it like
just on stream
[Music]
foreign
yeah
and then straight to our stream wow wow
I know right
and then
Andrew
[Music]
no no it's malam actually what's
midnight Midnight midnight it's midnight
thank you thank you Andrew okay so drill
our sorceress thank you for draining my
life before by the way
[Music]
you guys you guys know what happened
did you guys what happened before the
stream started
[Music]
okay so I was playing I was playing
Diablo's from
three four four pm I think three or four
pm I don't know
and then I was like catching up with the
study of Lilith
right and then uh I saw the clan usually
usually I usually I didn't really talk
in the clan unless unless
um I really need to talk about something
or awesome thing and then I was like but
but I but I really read all of the
conversations in the clan right
and then after that I saw someone say it
World boss in 20 minutes and then I was
like oh no
can I uh can I join the world boss like
I'm still under level and then it's
still like very hard for me to even
fight the mobs uh but I really want to
try the world boss um the T4 World boss
and then
and then after that
um no no not the sibling no no not the
sibling someone in the clan someone in
the clan saying like World boss in 20
minutes and I was like oh no and then
and then the dinner time will be like
coming very soon and but I really want
to try like it's gonna be like my first
ancestral items maybe like even
legendary items if I can get uh if I can
defeat the boss right and then hmm
I was thinking like hmm what should I do
what should I do what should I do and
then after that
um I wait until like I waited I I I
still kept silent I still kept silent I
said nothing and then after that like um
10 minutes 10 minutes before the world
boss I said like
uh no no no I saw I saw someone I saw
someone said like uh one slot four P
four World boss and then I was like
this is it nah
uh
this one this one and this one this one
and then I was like
let's go
this is it and then I was like invite me
please
and then and then they just invite me
after that ice and then after I joined I
said like
uh this is gonna be my first world boss
in T4 and I don't know maybe I will be
just like died you know like got one hit
and then like hmm and then and then they
said like uh it's okay uh just don't get
hit and then I was like yeah yeah I will
I will just stand um outside of the area
and then after that it start at first
ice at first
yeah and then the boss is like
90. the level is 90 I think
yeah yeah the the the level of the boss
is 90.
and then I was like still 64. yeah I was
64. and then
after that at first I just uh
stood
outside of the area like the outside of
the bus areas it's like very far away
but I but I mean I wanna try the damage
right I want to try the damage but
actually actually honestly
it's not really that painful so
um
so
yeah I mean
I survived so after all I just got
closer and closer and closer it is yeah
yeah and then I mean
it gave me damage yes but
it's not that bad it's not that bad
[Music]
it's not that bad I didn't die I didn't
die I didn't die like the lowest the
lowest uh the lowest HP that I got is
like half HP so all good all good
and then but yeah maybe maybe I gave no
damage that's always probably so
um and then
and then yeah and then after that
someone
in the party
say it like
the items
are not good
right and then followed by the other one
like yeah same with me and then I was
like checking my items and then I got
two ancestral
I got two legendary ancestral and it's
and one sacred
um legendary and then and then and then
and then
that's actually yeah and then and I and
then I and then I say it right I say
like I got this this this and then and
then they replied me they replied me
like
uh I don't trust you and then I was like
oh okay and then I you know right the
the Diablo can like link the items so
that um it can be appeared um
on the chat right so I just I just I
just click click click I just click all
of that all of those three items and
then and then
and then they just say like oh she
really got
it
legendary ancestor yes even the even the
unique I I think I got the unique unique
ancestral
unique ancestral and
what is that again I don't know I click
I click all those three I forgot but
yeah there's like even
um unique unique ancestral yay
absolutely
but no worries no worries um
it's not suitable for my builds no
worries but I mean it's just like um
I got that much luck so yeah
hmm
yeah
yeah but ancestral unique summer sacred
unique oh
ancestral unique summer sacred unique
satulagi
is
and then the
what is that what is that called
the Box
we cannot open it until we level 80
right
so yeah
[Music]
I got all this awesome stuff but meh
don't need it yeah can you treat in this
game would be nice to try for something
uh
we can trade but not the
legendary one
not the legendary not the unique one but
we can
um destroy it we can extract the
legendary aspect and we can treat the
aspect yeah but yeah I mean it's still
such a waste if we do that I feel yeah
true if you're sure you're gear is match
with your gameplay I will I will I will
do the upgrade later on probably after I
reach um level E key probably yeah
foreign
[Music]
nice
yeah I did not think on the world boss
I just like yeah do whatever and then I
didn't die and then I took the party
luck
let's go
the fact that you got all those super
rare items and cannot even use them is
just pouring salt in the wound for
reference Like You Stole kinda
Kinda Yeah I know
but I mean it's okay it's fine they do
this right
it's really funny I mean I mean when
when I when I
fought the bus when I thought the world
boss
well I didn't even get that
great items
but when I did nothing
I just got a very very very very very
rare items so yeah
Jonathan Ryan thanks
um
ancestral
[Music]
same no no no good items
I don't trust you
if if if you don't trust me then
yeah let me just pour the salt let me
wrap the salt in your face
right
on your face right
[Music]
I mean I mean I was I was I was trying
to be
considerate but yeah
random
there's nothing
that is
foreign
[Music]
malicious compliance
is nice
very good super good very nice
later when I went later okay later when
I did my solo stream I will I will show
you guys what is the items even though I
even though it's not suitable for my
build I think I will not um
get it away probably and yeah I think
after this I gonna Salvage all of the
items first like uh from
the previous one yep because it's time
for me to change the items into the
ancestral one right so yeah I think I
don't need all of those items anymore
foreign
rank on
grengan
I mean I already I already took all of
the luck and
I'm not even using it
[Music]
what do it what through it
so you're going to self then lost
um
it's okay then I will I will always try
to do the world most um
later then
[Music]
okay very nice
if it's a WordPress your Nick it might
be a very rare item usually the Bus drop
a really rare item
if you're lucky enough
so yeah
[Music]
just maybe maybe just don't get a party
with Kyla probably
that's the tips
[Music]
oh see I really want to be your
classmate I get to copy your homework
and get a massage what a deal wow yeah
true yeah
male escape on my way join again fifth
so I can get Kyla massage and get some
hair I'll get some help
uh
what is that uh
Jonathan Ryan Bobo mine sorcerer damage
can you see nobody by the way thank you
Andrew oh I meant how do you say
midnight in IDR uh
middle middle middle is actually
h
Milam but usually we don't say
usually we just say
absolutely yeah
yeah
don't even Congress passed the tea for
world word boss what word boss boss boss
that
not World okay word boss word boss that
have a lot of words
nice then even nice
work boss yeah maybe we need to like do
a typing competition to fight the boss
is it World boss
but it was
um
then I think that's all for the essay
let's check the social bus
[Music]
uh hello maester I used to play the
piano by the ear but it was horrible I
think I prefer to play with my hands
[Music]
and then
us I say
thank you so much for the 69 La isina
Texas
you can do it
I mean
I don't know if I still have some luck
I don't really have luck that's why I'm
taking Irish People's Law but good luck
but
you cannot
take back your luck
you know but still good luck
uh-huh
that's a mouthful for a native English
speaker have a good night and see you
tomorrow or today gonna work now yay
good luck with your work
[Music]
so we got new luck and you take it again
kinda
foreign
[Music]
and
what flavor of bubble tea can light a
campfire in the wilderness
this is defense
and then interview whoa
so many many many many many
important days
Good Luck Good Luck Good Luck
good luck let's go
keep fighting
me
thanks Ella for the 4K collab it was fun
as expected even though we had some
problem good night I mean
they are no perfect
things in life so yeah
the problems are just like
making it
fun more fun so yeah
[Music]
let's go
okay I think that's all for now
I don't want to
Roll Along the Stream
and I think this is Wednesday right yeah
I think I will be streaming from let's
say um
morning but maybe it's not gonna be like
morning morning as in
[Music]
eight o'clock no no it's not gonna be
like that maybe we can start like nine
or ten
[Music]
uh
uh my mind Minecraft
can be
[Music]
I played
I played um
wait what
gurus gurus birthday stream is tomorrow
birthday birthday birthday stream is
this morning
what time
what time is it
foreign
[Music]
a.m okay okay no problem no problem I
thought uh yeah I just don't want to
like Clash over
it's okay
happy birthday happy birthday
happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday happy
birthday
[Music]
and before you go quick tell me a D4
plus I don't care which and I'll mean
them when I get the game in a month
[Music]
I really I really want to play Rogue but
still got no chance so yeah
[Music]
it's fluid in our hand what it slowed in
our hand wait
a
minute
[Music]
your model holding something in hand
yeah it's a flute it's like a customized
fruit
[Music]
okay
I think that's all should be done
yeah I think she'll be done
then thank you so much I I after this
what
my plan is
um I will
complete all of the Lilith statue first
yep
and probably I don't know any hell tight
I don't know but um if I'm doing hell
tight in the key for probably I'm gonna
die oh yeah Hells I do it in the T3 and
then just go back to claim the items in
T4 right
have a good night thank you so much have
a good night too Andrew okay I'll be a
room thinking lion happy birthday girl
yay let's go
not a good stretch to be honest yeah I
mean if we if we play in the T3 right we
lost all of the EXP too
so
that's actually not that good what can I
do now is actually
just grind first probably until like 70.
yeah I just grind until we reach 70 and
then we can just do the tea for health
time
but yeah
just party and do even in T4
just party and take all of the luck
right
yeah right
[Music]
yeah that works yeah
very nice
that's what happens either way
I really need to go
and thank you so much for having me atsu
Iden
idea
see you in the morning bye bye I think
on
[Music]
foreign