K welcome to one of our KY test kitchens
yay I am your T Takashi K and I have
asked our safety department to prepare
this very professional training video we
will start with your uniform then K's
experimental Service delivery devices
and finally prepare you for service so
you become one with the
bucket everything here is completely
normal of course take it away narrator
thank you Teno say hello to h47 74 who
is definitely not a chicken and we'll be
helping demonstrate your new team member
duties and he definitely meets all
Health Department criteria first the
standard issue kikiki apron a cheerful
colorful service apron and kfp colors
with adjustable tick ties and many
useful Pockets made out of 100% thick
cotton canvas given to all kfp class HD
members this apron this a apron oh my
God you bird bring I'm not on the hat
yet tjo he's doing the thing again chill
relax calm down okay I guess we're doing
the Hat now your stylish cotor hat with
cute feather and Wing adornment it's
designed to keep your Sparks Al light
and turn the dark of your shift into day
keep your sweat and Fe I mean hair out
of the food you may notice yourself with
a statistically significant increase in
compliments and confidence levels while
wearing the kikiki
apron well look at you little chicken
that apron looks amazing on you yes
slate you'll become a heart Challenger
of customer service with increased
confidence while wearing the kiky apron
our research division is still trying to
determine if it's the apron or a side
effect of having somewhere to put your
hands during awkward conversations and
remember any items that mysteriously
appear in your pockets are strictly kfp
property don't you dare try to keep them
and to complete your uniform here's your
team member pin our pins feature
state-of-the-art identification
protocols to ensure ER documentation
when if incidents occur if the pin feels
warm to the touch it just means that
you've shed your feather I mean that
you've grown a as as a team member and
don't look behind you our Signature
ceramic bucket bowls are designed to
hold 32 o or about 1 liter they offer a
highquality dinin experience that
prevents Health Department violations
from occuring management would like to
remind team members that any old paper
vessels are to be discarded after using
and not washed and reused no matter how
much money it saves you may notice an
uncontrollable desire to listen to and
dance the Teno songs while handling the
Chopsticks this is clearly a feature not
a bug of our manufacturing process's
unique injection mold patterns remember
the Chopstick made me do it is not a
valid excuse for impromptu performances
during service hours and is grounds for
being sent to the usual room and now our
special Shadow resistant kfp soup spoons
Now with an anti-slip hooking technology
to prevent them from falling into bowls
quality control would like us to
demonstrate proper handling techniques
notice how holding the spoon by its
curve produces the perfect parametric
equalizer for singing while cripping the
handle is optimal for interviews and
podcasting incorrect spoon orientation
may lead to frog and throat incidents
that require emergency response but wait
before you go to make the ramen you need
to be able to prepare the toppings and
sides next we'll introduce you to our
signature premium Maple and walnut
cutting board marketing wants us to
emphasize as versatility as a shakery
board and elegant wall decoration the
distinctive Shield shape that bears a
striking resemblance to Teno own shield
with integrated handle are for culinary
purposes only according to our research
division's very insistent memo monthly
mineral oil treatment is essential to
protect the board so that it can in turn
protect you the standard operating
procedure in case of agitated Arcane
inclin customers is to raise the cutting
board up like so and hide yourself
behind it notice how H 4774 is properly
positioned board is Def ing those
metaphysical projectiles excellent work
h47 our fire insurance covers fire balls
now that's right fire boss thank you
Teno and now the centerpiece of your kfp
test kitchen equipment the kikiri knife
your signed Kiri represents the Pinnacle
of culinary engineering this 8-in chef's
knife features a custom Phoenix Feather
pattern Damascus vg10 steel composition
with a signature fiery orange Co offered
alloy veins the handle Bears a striking
resemblance the Teno sword hardened to
61 HRC for an edge retention and kagi
that quality control enthusiastically
notes beats the cluck out of common
knives let's observe the proper
technique in action notice the approved
pinch grip method impossible efficiency
rates are completely normal and expected
or you'll be sent to the usual room and
remember special techniques that can
only be activated upon yelling the name
of the technique are strictly prohibited
the resulting collateral damage to
kitchen equipment and eyebrows is
excessive and entirely un but it's so
cool let's do it it will definitely
attract our customers too en are you
sure about this what are you the
[Music]
chicken no definitely not a chicken very
well do You observe how h47 S4's motions
mimic that of a hotori even creating
after image mirages from the speed of
his movement please note that while
highly unlikely a fever Knight of retro
respective sleep talking can produce the
Sparks required to ignite your Kiri and
yourself please fill out the respective
extra Krispy incident report forms if
this occurs now you're finally equipped
for the most important part of your
training preparing our signature chicken
Pyon Ramen it's rumored this Ramen broth
gets its richness from being perpetually
boiling since before 9000 BC and it was
reported that it was so delicious and
nutritious that it prompted a love Rush
from customers that created an
unprecedented pile of incident reports
start by admiring the gorgeous potential
on the P the gorgeous artwork they
contain a unique blend of flour
including ginoa and are dried not fried
so step away from the fryer quality
control has made the claim that the
traditional dough rolling processes for
this should be impossible especially
when real conu is involved research
division has simply called this a skill
issue 3 to 5 minutes later when the
noodle texture is done to the customer's
preference of softness empty the
flavored packet contents into the bowl
but not the chicken skin crumbles
secrets from Michelin Star Kitchen were
used by our research division achieving
what quality control describes as
scientifically impossible levels of
delicious flavor if customers ask how
much nutrition this contains you are
only authorized to inform them that it
contains 25% of each vitamin and mineral
and other nutrition facts like the 37 g
of protein and the 8 G of fiber you are
not authorized to elaborate on how that
nutrition came to be then top with the
pure Phoenix Tears Aroma oil finally
sprinkle with the chicken skin crumbles
and oh no
and that's enough training for
today oh we seem to be experiencing some
technical difficulties please bear with
us nothing happened no one saw anything
someone cut the feet cut the C feet
let's go everything's fine let's go to
the uh the the usual room come with
me yeah thanks for watching forget this
happen and make sure you're a good
chicken or a team member yeah you yeah
you you know what you need all of this
merch bye bye bye bye bye nothing thanks
for
watching little
[Music]
be you're Gooden