[Music]
so
my
[Music]
hello
i
am
and i'm here to tell you stories
yeah but uh excuse me i am
not very energetic
uh currently the heat is melting me
i am trying to survive but i feel
like the heat is drowning drowning
draining me
um
yeah no i don't have ac because it's not
really a thing in austria
oh my god kill me
it's so hot i have the the fan on and
hopefully it will help
yeah finally see in europe i don't know
about all of europe but in austria we
just
it's not normal to have ac in your
apartment normally like you know
i wish i had also because like
ugh i live in a in a decent apartment
and i would i would hope that decent
apartments come with ac these days but
they don't
um
ac isn't the thing in the uk as well
yeah i know uk i kind of get it it's
colder than here
but austria
gets
heat waves in the summer we get it gets
[\h__\h] hot in the summer you know
would be nice to have ac at least in
like more expensive apartments
yeah i can't okay all right
don't tell me to get a window unit
whatsoever
already talked about this i can't
i can't
like getting one that i install
like the the proper one that you install
outside
is
construction that you know
goes through the outside walls and that
most likely would not be allowed
by the landlord and then
those things that you don't need
construction for the window units
they would be too loud way too loud for
streaming and i mean i could set it up
maybe in other rooms but maybe but
it would be nice to have it where i work
because i spend a lot of hours here
not having it where i spend
most of my time besides my bedroom
in front of my tv
uh yeah it's okay my fan
helps for now
and besides that i guess my
my strategy is escaping austria into
countries where there is ac
as much as i can until suddenly surprise
oh summer is over
so i'll be in korea
and they definitely have ac
so hallelujah bless bless korea
[Music]
foreign
uh yeah i guess i'll be outside a lot
yeah but at least at least the hotel
room and all that and the stores
all have ac
not even every store here has ac
like okay some some stories but not all
of them
but okay at least that's something like
most most stories like
i don't know super i think supermarkets
yeah have ac
here and uh
i guess like i don't know clothing
stores i think normally have i seen
yeah
but the apartments know
it's tough
so it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
yo
people are really slow when it comes to
upgrading to ac housing yeah i don't
know is it that expensive
or why why don't they install it here is
it so expensive of water i wonder
i guess people just really want to get
the most out of you without giving you
anything for it
i recently i feel that so strongly
like people just
want to
use other people
so much
so sad
and get nothing no they want everything
but they give nothing
goddammit
well well well that's how the world
works yeah got dark so sudden
[Music]
but um i'll try to um i mean to be
honest when i
woke up and actually already yesterday
after the karaoke stream i didn't really
feel like streaming today that much but
then again i was also like
staring into the void
of sana
and um
also just generally not feeling it but
uh i was like
well i'm like so
so hmm i feel so
not here i feel like i'm not existing so
i couldn't do anything so i guess i was
like okay whatever let's just
let's just
do something
and and pass the time
yeah
um
so i'm gonna talk about my trip because
i have a lot to talk about anyway i took
so many notes
um the foreign cheek i don't even know
what that means anymore i used to know
i forgot
one of those days yeah one of those days
one of those days
[Music]
um
yeah
but
but i mean i don't you know i'm gonna
talk about italy but
it's okay we're we're staying in contact
with san anna
and if you look up to the sky
you guys can
not quite
see space but
you know it's there you know it's there
right we know and we know it's there so
you look up then you see a blue blue sky
but behind that blue sky is a
big big beak
big big big
big
big big big big big big
big big big big big
big
space
even bigger than that
incredibly big
[Music]
um
it's like god she's looking down upon us
protecting us
from another
crash into a planet into a big thing
thingy she's protecting us
she'll dodge it
she's you know the good thing is that
you know
we we're like
on her good side now
meteor yeah
we're on her good side now like she's
got to know got gotten to know us
and she hasn't gotten to know
any
other living beings on other planets
like i wish she told us was there other
living beings
but as far as i know they're not
so
we managed to get her on our good side
and that's a good thing because she'll
protect us like if there is anything
coming up you know to destroy earth
anytime soon she'll be like oh can we
like
let me just move that with my with my
pinky let me just push that away with my
pinky
cause i got some cool people on earth
got some friends there they're kind of
nice so let's let's protect them
she's good
[Laughter]
[Music]
but eofy is here okay
she's here
so that doesn't count
[Music]
and dinosaurs now i wouldn't say she
hated dinosaurs but she just didn't have
a connection with them
no no particular reason to protect them
from a meteor
[Music]
yeah
why why would she have i mean you know
she's just for her it was probably just
looking at someone stepping on an ant
[Music]
if you compare it this is the equivalent
of a human stepping on an ant her
looking at immediate meteor crashing
dinosaurs
it's not a big deal to her
at that moment
[Music]
yeah so
anyway
i want to do a little recap uh of what i
told you guys in the stray stream
because maybe some people didn't watch
it
[Music]
and because i'm gonna talk a lot i'm
gonna
uh
pre-prevently pre pray
preemptively
take a fruit candy
ah uh-huh oh
um pure peel hot okay one thing i'll say
i will take credit
for the
song choice of pure pure heart and
hajima lindin you may know how dimalin
in sanne's
birthday concert a birthday
graduation concert
because
she was asking
uh oh yeah she was asking um like oh
what songs should we sing well any any
any
any recommendations and i was like
you know i had
uh i had um
um
i was in that moment i think i was in
the k on mood because i think i just did
my unarchived archived karaoke at that
moment
um
and then i recommend it
peel up your heart
because i felt like it had vibes
that were fitting to that
um
occasion
[Music]
the whole you know
girls from the same school singing a
song kind of also graduation vibes you
know school graduation and all that
um
[Music]
yeah i thought that one was really
fitting and
yeah so i recommended that one
and then i also
i was like sorry sorry and you don't
have to you don't have to
um take this song at all but i i just um
remembered another song like i went
actually i went through
so many songs i was like oh this could
be good this could be good but then i i
figured oh i sang this song before
can you put me upon me as you may know
hanji
i sang it before in my stream
and i thought that was also really
really good
not only lyric wise because the lyrics
are also about going away and saying
thank you to everybody who's been with
you until now
and moving on
um but in a happy way because the
instrumental that's the second thing the
instrumental was very uplifting but
still
emotional but uplifting and kind of
happy it gives you a positive feeling
about
the graduation
so that's why i chose those two songs
and i'm glad someone liked them
and went with them
yeah yeah yeah i think they were good
songs that fit perfect to the occasion
oh i didn't do the lyric distributions
that's uh kelly did that
kelly kelly did that
so yeah i'm taking credit for that
it was really really really beautiful
and cute
uh how everything came together
yeah
it was really cute oh man those those uh
small council
models counselors models they're also so
adorable oh my god
so good that they came out before so
that they could use it for the concert
the the movements and the expressions oh
i just love how
sana's twin tail twin tails sway around
so adorable
yeah
so
well um yeah sadly that's over and
happened too fast but uh we have to
continue doing our everyday
lives things
and that includes
um
streaming for you guys i don't want to
put a picture um
eden exile are you watching this
i wanna
i want this picture to to be put in one
of those frames and put it on my table
this picture
[Music]
i i'm waiting for
i'm waiting for an
uh a thing
please
waiting for an addition
thank you
anyone can do it dope i guess so
honestly probably
cute
okay now it's story time
now it's story time
italian
italian mamma mia number one i saw you
in the pray chat saying will there be a
mamma mia counter well feel free to
count it
feel free to count it
[Music]
remember this music i used it before
it's really good
one yeah one ban
[Music]
if this wasn't such a kind of like last
minute uh
change of mind of what i wanted to do
in terms of streaming
today then i would have uh
maybe made some comics but instead and
at least you know i'll at least write it
down
maybe oh i have an idea
i'll write down some notes
to have an outline
on stream i'll write it down here on the
on the screen
wait
um
there was that yeah yeah yeah that can
be useful
[Music]
okay
let me get my notes
hi
i'm gonna
write some stuff down
okay
here we go
[Music]
i want to pick a
screen color but it doesn't select it
properly
oh well
[Music]
okay that's fine that's close enough
actually happens to be
the opposite of that
okay
so recap
uh
last week
last week right last week on
first day
last thursday
kiwami goal
[Music]
remember i told you
ah reason i went there was because
uh a while ago
on the
6th of july
kiwama
birthday
pretty close to that
uh
2324 so was supposed to be remini anime
convention in women in italy and i
already heard about this a long while
a long time many years and i always
wanted to go kind of and this time it
felt like
since i'm doing my
this
this during this birthday
no friends
no friends around
no sure
so i celebrate it with you guys only
sad
but i was like oh oh oh so let's
celebrate my birthday later on
how about we do it in remini at this
convention because i googled
google google say
remini
this date
yeah
and friends will i was like let's go
let's go
[Music]
wait do these notes even help
[Laughter]
maybe not
maybe at the end if you read all this
you'll just be like questing my question
my question like
and i said let's go
[Music]
yeah and um
it looks like me taking notes in class
how i write down notes in school yeah
yeah
life is being controlled by google
always always has been
so
i was like let's go my friends are also
like yeah let's go why not it sounds fun
like what the hell
um
so we decided to go and i i pretty
quickly booked my flight
and hotel
and um
i was i was um kind of looking forward
to it but then
more and more and more i was like i was
getting busier and busier and busier
with birthday preparations and other
things that were going on in real life
and made me incredibly busy
and then i was kind of like starting to
feel like i don't even have time for
this but oh well
and then at the same time
like about a week or so before
this happens
one week before
we find out
we've been bamboozled
bamboo zoom
no corn
bench no convention
bamboozled the big bamboozle happened
now let me no one change the phones
actually
[Music]
i don't know what is this and i don't
like this one either whatever ah
[Music]
as i told you guys in the stress stream
for sure
there we go that's that's okay
as i told you guys in a straight stream
like we found out that like this anime
convention
in rimini in italy
it kind of like had some big drama
that
[Music]
ended up resulted in the convention
splitting into two conventions
back to back on two weekends
yeah
uh and i mean
the first one in the first week where we
didn't go to was kind of considered the
real
convention
and a lot of people went there
apparently
but but then the one that we went to
that actually is the first date that
shows up when you look it up on google
was the one no one went to
and when you go to like the instagram or
so of that convention in the comment
section you can see italian people
commenting in italian like oh whatever
big drama don't go there it's not the
right convention
um
whatever you don't speak italian you're
not gonna pay attention to that and
not gonna translate every single comment
because like well why why would you
and you wouldn't know
so
and also because i didn't
you know i could have probably gotten
the information if i told you guys on
stream beforehand that i'm going to
rimini
but you know obviously for safety
reasons i didn't say
but if i said it uh you guys could like
i'm sure some italians in the chat could
have warned me about it
yeah unfortunately i have to be
secretive about these kind of things so
i can have some privacy
um
well well well
two
conventions
one good one bad
[Music]
so we went to the bad one and then no
but the thing is like before one week
before we're like oh [\h__\h] what did we do
and i was like i wouldn't mind
canceling
because i'm busy anyway
and
yeah
and but then my friends were like oh but
we need to kiwawa without you it's not
fun
and we want you to do to be there also
we can't cancel because
where we would lose a lot of money
if we wouldn't go
and i was like okay
friend
friends want to go
i know but yes
then i went
[Laughter]
so
yeah
but you know i was like well hopefully
it will be worth the stress
hopefully
hopefully maybe you know it could
be actually good um you know good
vacation
because i'm stressed anyway maybe i can
turn off my brain and just enjoy my time
there
um
yeah
no but yes
yes
so okay
is this the point where i stopped
telling you guys no i told you about the
flight too i think where people clapped
but i think that's it right
oh and and the scissor
the scissor i think i told you about the
scissor
yeah
about the flight
yeah i did okay flat
fly people clap
clap
why
stop clapping it's not not worth you
clapping not worth an applause
it was a really short flight and then it
lands and people clap like crazy like
like they just heard a
lady gaga concert
and then they clapped again put a person
on them on the microphone
like he's lady gaga or something
why why you club
but okay i'm not really that mad about
it okay but i'm just saying
it's stupid
there's no need to clap
so hmm
okay okay here we go here we continue
and we arrived we arrived in in rimini
safely
and
uh
[Music]
pretty much
uh
the airport really small okay airport
pretty damn small one of the smallest
airports i've been to
um small airport
and uh we were in a group okay actually
uh two of my friends rbf and bff
they also were gonna join us but they
went uh in in different
different
they joined joined us later by
a train
[Music]
[Laughter]
they joined us later by train but at
this moment i was with other
actually other rpf and uh
not much of an rbf though
i'm not renting that one that much
because
he doesn't want to help that much
whenever i ask for something
for help he wants money so
[Laughter]
he's a bit of a greedy type but um
so i don't ask him much for help yeah uh
but uh
the other like his his girlfriend really
cute
and she's she's actually the one that i
told you about who um downloaded uh
valkyrie connect and like grinded
so hard
uh got my character to max level and
always use my character she's the one
yeah
that's that's another one of my friends
yeah and she was also there
so yeah my my friend group we went
together minnie
yeah
simp
i wouldn't call her a simp like she
doesn't really uh
watch my streams as far as i know
she keeps herself updated on like what's
going on i guess and what i'm doing
but i don't yeah she doesn't watch my
streams but she she likes be tubers in
general
so anyway we arrived at this small
airport
and
we're like really chill
like oh no stress the moment we walk out
of this airport we're just gonna gonna
go to our respective hotels and chillax
and then meet up again later for dinner
but
we
walk out of the airport
and
there is
no taxis
and then
i also i open my phone
and i open uber my uber app
and it says
no uber
what what what what what what no [\h__\h]
way no
no
not over
you can't take uma away from me how am i
supposed to go to places without uber
[Music]
i was like okay well no uber is fine
let's just take a normal taxi but there
were no taxis either
um and we had so much so many suitcases
[Music]
i looked it up and apparently they have
uber
in like
uh
three cities three cities in italy
according to google
in the big ones like rome
and
venice maybe
who have been so reliant on uber in the
past years
suddenly not having an uber we were
completely like
stunned at what to do how to get to our
hotels no uber no taxi
it was hot and we had a lot of luggage
and we didn't really want to deal with
public transport you know
[Music]
yeah so actually we weren't the only
ones who were standing outside of the
airport entrance
there were like a lot of other austrians
there standing and waiting for a taxi to
miraculously arrive
um
how to travel
yeah how can we exist without uber
please what the hell more uber please
yeah
uh
so after waiting for like 20 minutes
outside
we saw
like taxis started to arrive like two
two or so
but we didn't take it because i i i
didn't even try to take them because i i
felt bad because the other people were
waiting longer than us so and and then
we wanted to take one big one together
so we just waited until the others
uh
i did until the other austrians
got their taxis
uh
there are taxi apps though yeah but the
thing is like
we didn't know about any of those
um we looked at there was like some kind
of board
outside
that listed um the fairs
uh from the airport to specific areas in
rimini but nothing
nothing like not even taxi numbers were
written in there they wrote taxi fares
but no taxi numbers but then at some
point
i photographed the taxi number that was
written on one of those taxes that drove
by
but don't worry we eventually got our
taxi and
my friends were like
uh
let's tell this taxi driver
our several various hotel
names and have him
drive
to each one of them
and let us out one by one and i was like
already
dreading that because
i had a i had a gist
that this taxi driver would not speak
english
and would be very annoyed by the idea
when we can barely communicate with him
and make him like stop in so many places
oh yeah oh yeah
i i knew that he was gonna be pissed
and
so yeah he arrived and
thankfully he at least knew
without us even showing him the address
where all the hotels were that we wanted
to go to
um
yeah so there was not much that we had
to do
but he did indeed not speak english and
he did indeed seem like a little bit
like
um
he was a little bit annoyed by us
[Laughter]
um maybe
[Music]
we uh
uh eventually we got into the taxi
and then yeah he drove us to the hotels
and then
yeah i checked into my hotel
uh-huh
but yeah no english
oh my god
no english
at the in the taxi but in the hotel the
receptionist spoke perfect perfect
decent good english so i was relieved
and i i checked in my hotel room
actually
i i had like a three star hotel room
which was totally fine you know it even
had a pool and all that which i didn't
use
but um
i was actually i was trying to find like
better hotels but
they were literally only i felt like
there were only
three-star hotels and one big
big
this big grow hotel but that one was
booked out too
so the only hotels that were available
were like two-star freestyle like really
small hotels
but it was totally fine like i
i was
i was satisfied with my hotel room yeah
yeah
oh good oh good was a good hotel
breakfast was decent decent breakfast i
i noticed one thing uh
italians seem to like
sweet breakfast i i could be wrong
but from my experience from hearing what
the other
friends hotels offered in their
breakfast and what my breakfast offered
they really like sweets oh they do yeah
can't confirm nice
yeah cause there was a big um
i had to say there were there were more
sweet things than non-sweet things a lot
of like cakes
uh like not like super creamy cakes and
all that just simple really simple cakes
um
like what what would you call them
oh yeah and a lot of pastries yeah
um
oh my dying venus
danishes no not necessarily danishes
mine just had a lot of cakes i don't
know what coffee cakes i guess so
italiano
i was i was happy about that to see that
because you know i like i like enjoying
a sweet breakfast
every day
so i would usually i would
take some pineapples some watermelons
and some some of the sweet pastries
for breakfast while i was in italy
yeah
that made me happy to see it
breakfast
breakfast sweet
yum
okay
ah but that was actually me already
jumping to breakfast uh before that
uh wait a second
uh
let me
think oh yeah okay so
uh we said we're gonna meet for for
dinner but i was so hungry and and also
no i at first i really wanted to eat
like a like a big ice cream puffy so i
went out
alone to check the streets for some ice
cream ice cream i wanted a big buffet i
didn't want just one one ice cream cone
and i wanted a perfect
so i i walked down there's this it felt
it felt like a main street
because like most of the restaurants
were in this one street in one line in
one straight street line
so i went down that street and uh
because like my hotel was pretty much at
the end of it
and i went down the street and it was so
hot and the further i walked the more
hungry i got so i gave up on the ice
cream because i couldn't find any any
parfait style ice cream
uh and it was already like late late
late late lunch or
early dinner time
and i couldn't wait for my friends
anymore so i went out to get some some
small
uh
yeah
food
and i sat down in a in a restaurant
that had like a
appetizers i guess
okay okay
and they had appetizers and so i ate
those to fill my tummy and later on my
friends they were like walking down
the street and i don't think they were
even looking for me but they i was like
oh hey yeah
yeah look at me it's
here i am you found me surprised so i
sat down with me and they ended up
having something small too
yeah
yeah just a little snack but i noticed
one thing
remini must have
so many austrian and german tourists
because
there were a lot of restaurants who had
which had like okay not a lot but some
of them some had even german
menus
uh yeah we hate them hey
i'm one of those come on
goddammit i see some people
we have more italian viewers than usual
don't hate us
it's a touristic um touristic city what
are you gonna expect i would say
i don't want
germans but austrian tourists are fine
yeah
austrian tourists we're fine the thing
is you know there's a direct flight from
austria to rimini
so
yeah when i was walking down that street
i heard a lot of tourists speaking
speaking german like pretty much
everyone that looked like a tourist
was speaking german
[Laughter]
i think i think besides the italians
everyone was german or austrian
um
no
tourists
all german
yeah they all spoke german
this seems like a hot spot for austrian
vacationists hmm
which was funny
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
maybe a cab driver spoke germany no i
don't think so
oh yeah oh yeah uh also all the
restaurants in that street they looked
so nice like they were all like really
cutely decorated and
fancy and pop hip hip
hip and poppy
like i was i was at this one restaurant
where i had the snack that
uh it was like
it had benches that were covered
in a louis vuitton
a pattern but then there was one big um
writing that said
what was it not real or fake or
something
until the waiters were wearing uh shirts
with the louis vuitton logo but then it
also said fake or something like that
so i was like what's going on here
it's your yeah is this a loud is this
legal but i guess if you
write it there that is fake and not real
i guess i guess it's okay
yeah but it had a lot of fancy
decoration and all that kind of cool
place
and the waiter was really nice spoke
perfect fluent english so that was good
yeah the
fancy restaurants
cute decoration
yeah and then when i was sitting before
my friends came actually no no wait that
was already when they were there yeah i
got a phone call
while my friends were sitting there
i got a sudden phone call
guess who
mommy
mommy called me suddenly
no no mommy mommy mama tony suddenly
called me and she the thing is like
because i kept it secret that i was
going to italy uh
i don't know i didn't tell her that i
was going to italy i just kind of
happened you know i felt like you know
it was
not a big deal so
i didn't tell her beforehand so she
called me and i i don't know i guess she
just wanted to catch up but i told her
mommy i'm in italy right now hi
but um i didn't i didn't hang up you
know i said i'm i'm in italy eating food
with friends right now but you know what
we're not in any
so she um started
she started to uh talk a little bit with
me
and
she was like oh we're in italy and i say
avi mini you know remini and she's like
oh yeah i know remini
and you know what she said
the moment she heard that avenue knee
she started this whole tangent
about how
mini ocean
is poop
um
she did not and i'm sorry guys she did
not have anything positive to say about
rimini
um
she loves italy
but nothing positive about i mean she
said that she went there like centuries
ago
um
and uh yeah
the thing is like i
i just arrived and it was you know nice
and i didn't have any negative feelings
yet but she
uh so i didn't quite understand but she
told me oh yeah sorry ocean
um it's it's like so dirty
and there's like so much fecal uh
bacteria and there's so much poop but
she didn't say it like that she she
didn't say fecal bacteria she literally
said
it was so confusing like i i didn't know
what the hell she was talking about but
she was like saying that
um
because like back then
um back then maybe it's not like this
anymore now because
um
people's butts are more dry and i'm just
like question my question my question
mark
but she said yeah back then you know the
like the whole
you know there's a lot of poop in the
ocean and i'm like what what's what
[Laughter]
huh
and uh because of that i guess uh a lot
of um
[Music]
what's the green stuff called again in
english
uh because of the bacteria a lot of um
alg
uh
algae yeah algae a lot of algae like
builds and then blah she said it's a
this is disgusting and the water is so
hot like really really really warm and
it's just ew
ew ew mommy was like ill
and i'm just like
i'm just like
okay mom thank you
thanks for letting me know
good good to know
thank you soon i'm i i i don't know what
to think now
so
i think then we went to dinner
and i think
the first night i think
i think this must have been this
i think
it was somebody asked in the chat before
but we got
something called i think it was prd now
so
the funny thing
when we met up with the friends again i
was like oh you know for dinner i i
wanna
uh eat something nice and they were like
no like all of my friends they were all
like no we don't have money i don't have
money i'm so [\h__\h] broke we're all
broke and i'm like okay okay we don't
have to go like to a really really
really really fancy place
but um
i don't want to eat you know the
equivalent of
uh like a really cheap uh
kebab
you know in austria if you want some
cheap street food you get a kpop which
is yummy and has like a lot of you know
veggies and all that in it it's great
but i said since i'm here i want to eat
some you know
more proper food you know in a
restaurant
yeah and i was saying like i don't
necessarily want to eat the equivalent
of that here
now the funny thing is we ended up
eating piadina because one of my friends
wanted that
and after eating it i have to say it is
kind of the equivalent
because
and that eminem was fine it was yummy
and all that but the reason why i'm
saying this is because it's cheap and um
look
uh
okay i got a really simple one there's
more
varieties that are more
um
you know they have all kinds of stuff in
there all kinds of veggies like zucchini
and uh or you can have meat like roast
beef in it and so on
yeah this is a famous place in remini on
the street that has
so many different pia it focuses on this
it's like although although what i what
i have i think that's a little bit
different they had like two different
types i'm not sure where the difference
is
um
yeah
it's
yeah yeah my friends got the prop i know
i got okay calzone i am my friends got
the piadina though
but it was very similar i don't i didn't
really see much of a difference
what
let me look it up again so it's just so
that i'm not using the wrong word
piadina
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah my friends got
the piaginum
uh but it all looks like kind of like
this
quesadilla no no no no quesadilla
not going to leave me
i don't i went for a really simple one
because before this i had like a little
snack as i told you so i wasn't like
insanely hungry and i just wanted
something
smaller
uh so i went with the simple one but the
other the other one's got some fancy
ones that looked really yummy and i got
some bites too and they tasted really
yummy like the like the roast beef
version and all that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
so
nothing against it and i just find it
funny like i say let's not eat uh some
something too
simple but it was yummy it's okay
everybody enjoyed it so it was yummy
yummy um
[Music]
actually i think
my friends were so excited by it they
even like ordered seconds
yeah
where where is my where's my are here
okay so we ate that kind of stuff
in this one big big place
on the street
uh
where's my note
here
okay okay okay okay
that was the first dinner but i heard
that remini is kind of famous for
piano pianini whatever
uh so
i would say that's wrong it's probably
wrong
is it from my minion i'm not sure
um
i don't know if that's true
no okay
wrongini
it's something super simple yeah it is
it's okay though
um
[Music]
something after dinner uh
i took a while um i got i got back to
the hotel
and
no wait before we went back to the hotel
actually
my friends really really really really
wanted to see the beach go beach
but it was already like 11 pm
um but they wanted to go so
i was like okay i guess like all right
my my foot you know i had that wound
and i really didn't want to already get
sand on it but
i was like okay i guess let's try let's
try to not get sand on it
uh
yeah and keep my sneakers on i guess
so i went with them and it was really
dark already but we found a nice spot i
guess we didn't see [\h__\h] it was so dark
it was so dark we saw nothing
and i thought my friends were crazy but
they went into the water because they
were already wearing swimsuits and they
went into the water and they said it's
so warm and i'm like what at 11 pm are
you serious
no lights yeah no lights it's really
dark
yeah it was warm at 11 pm
but uh the thing is that that's ocean
that's just generally warm because it's
that kind of ocean yeah yeah cannot
explain but you know
ew no not you warm is good i'm happy
about the fact that it's warm
[Music]
i like it makes it easier for me to go
in
don't have to be a [\h__\h] about it
[Music]
i think on the way to the ocean first
uh we walked by um an ice place and and
i got myself some ice cream finally
and they had
like i got two scoops i got one green
apple scoop really yummy and the other
scoop because they had it i was so
fascinated they had
kinder country ice cream
candle country is like my favorite
chocolate
yum and kinder is originally from italy
you know so
it makes sense yeah they had kinder
kinder ice cream came the country
specifically
with the cereals
so yummy
that i was excited about that so then we
went to the water and yeah we checked
out the
water a little bit
um
yeah then we had some weird my friends
brought up some weird gacha talks i
remember that
they talked about a certain gacha
and the character that
has
insane amounts of
lewd
loots
mate
and i'm like okay
cool
because they're like they're really into
that gotcha they all play it
every day
and number one number one yeah
apparently it's the number one character
but now the character that has the most
amounts of
blues
between like any other anime character
ever
anyway
yeah
anyway so then when i finally
went back to the hotel
and i noticed holy [\h__\h]
this place likes to party because my
hotel was like so close to the beach
and so i could hear the partying from
the beach
they were like blasting loud ass music
after midnight it was like 2 a.m or so
at this point
and
but thankfully i was i was tired enough
to sleep anyway i think i did my space
too
my twitter space before i'm not sure
anymore the timelines confused me but i
did my twitter space and then i slept i
think
yeah probably or i did it on another day
no i think i did it on the first day i'm
not sure but no no maybe i did it on
friday when did i tell my twitter space
you guys remember
was it friday or thursday
[Music]
it was the first day right
it was friday
oh
[Music]
i thought it was the first day
okay it doesn't matter
i just noticed yeah it's uh the walls
are thin
really thin and it's really loud so oh
my god then i woke up in the morning
friday
friday awake
loud [\h__\h]
they were so loud oh my god like oh i
guess it was like a checkout rush or
something but this these chicks in the
room next to me
first of all they kept on like
the doors of the rooms were so loud
every time you close the door i think
you could close it quietly too but they
would just like let them fall
to like shut like boom really loudly and
they kept on doing that and i heard them
like being really loud like talking as
well and she could continue sleeping
eventually after like an hour of that
[\h__\h] continuing
i finally fell fell asleep because i
think they they
they left i think they checked out or so
and then i finally was able to sleep
again oh my god so loud though
god damn it those doors i mean i
understand that they probably don't
realize how loud they actually are
because if you're the loud ones
then you don't really hear
any noise from the others because you
are the loud ones everybody hears you
but you don't hear anything else so you
you don't realize
how thin the walls are and how much the
other people hear you
so i forgive you for not knowing
i guess
but [\h__\h] loud
yeah
what they gave us the cutlery
everyone ate it with cutlery
let me get rid of that
picture now
okay
so
eventually eventually i finally woke up
went to the breakfast which was sweet
nice
and then i was impatient so i was like
you know yo everybody i'm going to the
beach now um
and i'm going to try to get us some you
know some umbrellas some parasols and
some sun beds and so i went there alone
okay i went with my
with my
floatie
floaty the one i think it's the same
that i
got in the maldives i think
could be
i brought that with me really smart
because i was like i'm not gonna buy one
here super expensive last time i brought
the one from the maldives back to
austria and then i brought that one to
italy smart
yeah
so i brought that with me and i went to
the beach and i was like hello scuzzy
excuse me
and
somebody who speaks some italian
yeah
no yeah
i don't speak italiano
so there was like one dude who was like
it seems like he did all the giving away
of the
umbrellas in that beach
he spoke okayish english but not really
[Music]
not really though so we had some
communication issues but i said
uh i want some i want some some beds and
umbrellas
and he then you know told me oh if
you're that many people
i can give you this big one somewhere in
the front
and uh sewn so many beds and i'm like
okay
but he tells me it's like
a 10 i think it was like 10 euro
per sunbed or so and i'm simultaneously
because my friends are not there yet
simultaneously i'm trying to communicate
to my friends on our group
that you know it's so-and-so and is that
okay for you
blah blah blah but like most of them
didn't answer
and i'm you know trying to
figure out what to do but you know the
guy he's like
being annoying kind of pressuring and
i'm like oh [\h__\h] sorry give me a moment
and my friends don't answer yeah
and i'm i'm trying i'm trying to
organize something but
yeah
[Laughter]
now i don't think it was a scam because
he did have some kind of list of prices
behind him
on the wall
that uh seemingly had those prices
i think so
um
so i think that's okay and like i didn't
mind the price but you know my friends
said they're all broke so i i didn't
want to make any decisions for them that
they were going to be mad at me later
but eventually they finally answered and
gave me some kind of a yes so i went
with it i got them
and uh
yeah then
i was like hopefully my friends come
soon because there i was sitting under a
huge
huge umbrella wait uh
um kiwawa go get
uh parasol
and vince
for it for all
and then i was
alone forever
because nobody came i waited for like
one or two
hours
for some friends even i waited three
hours some came earlier
i waited so long
and nobody came and you know
ah
it was one second let me let me let me
show you something
let me show you something
they took their damn sweet time it was
already i don't know 12 or 1 p.m or so
ah
i want to draw something
for better understanding
[Music]
okay
now can i show this on the screen
[Music]
okay let me see
um
[Music]
you're not really supposed to see that
that's not what what my
photoshop shows right now now you see my
goddamn
don't look at that
[Laughter]
my thumbnail ps dance
oh look at that
[Music]
no that's not a diver where is it
why is it
maybe maybe paint is better because this
doesn't really show it properly
[Music]
go with paint then
okay how about paint
paint
[Music]
okay uh
layering
ah let's put it
i don't know let's put it here i guess
well
layer it here
ah
okay
sorry
so i was there
and here then there's
here's the water
water
and then there's the sand
okay
and then you see that yeah
and then uh so pretty much in the front
he gives me this
big
square
umbrella yeah
and he gives me like some
some seats there
and let's just say there's some in the
back too but let's just say i'm chilling
here okay
kiwama
kiwama is chilling here waiting for her
friends to arrive all alone and you
would think you would think i have a
good view in to the ocean right now
right
um
right in front of me
like this
looking
not to the ocean but just looking
towards the other direction
[Music]
is these ladies this italian old ladies
italian old ladies
sunbathing when i say old i would say
50 60 uh topless
and
enjoying the sun no problem with that
but it's like right in front of me
like literally one meter
away from me
and i was like oh they surely will like
move their seats a little bit right when
when all of my friends arrive so that we
don't always have to look at this right
oh but no they stayed the whole day
sunbathing their private parts
um
well
well i saw i saw a lot that i
did not need to see
[Music]
[Laughter]
i want to look at the ocean but all i
see is these
really really really
tanned
[Laughter]
oh man
yeah and then you know i was chilling
alone in this like relatively awkward
situation and then you know who walks by
[Music]
know who walks by
uh
a chinese lady asking everybody on the
beach
guess what she was asking
it's a game now
yeah okay some people got it
[Music]
she asked everybody
and i was like what
massage
cause i've been to a lot of beaches
so far in my life in different countries
but you know and there's always like
vendors who sell like stuff
overpriced like jewelry towels floaties
ice cream whatever but never had i ever
come upon somebody who's selling
massages
it's over here in italy
oh
you know what i have
absolutely no problem with that i was
actually like
i was like
hell
yeah
i was like hell yeah okay actually that
sounds good
yeah the price was okay too
um i think it was 25 minutes for 20 euro
which compared to massages in the city
it's yeah the normal price i would say
so i i was alone and waiting and had
nothing to do anyway so i got myself a
massage
and uh yeah she was a really good really
really really good massage
massage therapist massager
her massage was really good i was really
satisfied
yeah what a deal no i think it was
really good
yeah but they wrote zero communication
like she couldn't even tell me 20 euros
she wrote the number into the sand
like no english from her side no italian
from my side so yeah we had some
problems communicating but what you need
to communicate when all you need to say
is massage
yeah massage hell yeah
it was freaking good
hell yeah
yeah
um finally at some point
while i was being massaged
my friends started coming in and uh yeah
started taking seats
um and we started uh like putting
sunscreen
on and you know i had my hundred sp
always i stopped writing in my notes
wait i need to catch up with my notes
old lady is
getting
naked tan
and
and then there was a massage lady yes
speak yes
i'm so happy she was there i actually i
really wanted a massage anyway so it was
a perfect opportunity and then later my
friends came and then finally
we went into the water and the water was
it didn't look dirty
like i thought it looked fine i've been
to dirtier beaches before like the one
in l.a
sorry la
sorry
and the sand was was golden and clean it
was really hot the sand was so hot we
were like always running uh when we were
walking on it we would always run
because it was really [\h__\h] hot you
would burn your feet literally
um but the water was also really warm
and it looked it looked fine you know i
didn't see any like garbage floating
around in algae i also couldn't really
see algae floating
around uh so yeah it was fine in my
opinion
and uh
yeah one thing i also found funny is
sometimes
i also saw i never saw this before the
beach
sometimes
in the sky
there were like little planes
flying
with some
with some big ads
yeah they were flying by but uh
they had like big
[Music]
big
ads in italian on there and we were
looking at it and probably a lot of
other austrian and german
tourists at the beach were looking at it
but i think we all
had
no idea
what that meant like okay cool you're
advertising on this tourist beach but
could you maybe add something english to
it because
no idea what you're trying to convey to
us
yeah it was really loud but yeah funny
funny ads no idea what it means but okay
cool
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah later i would go into
the water
and i would i would constantly
i would constantly like a child
use my floatie
oh hi
this is me
[Music]
wow my heart is so beautiful i would
constantly be in my floaty because there
was comfy and low effort yeah but the
water was really shallow but i still i
still wanted to be in my
in my cute floatie
yeah
naked obviously just kidding i had
something on
something i surely had something on
and then you know my friends they would
like push me around and then then and
yeah they would hold on to my floating
when it got
too deep
and yeah that was just always in my
floating and sometimes
sometimes that would be
it would be
i would be like
yeah
like this
[Music]
but
i had problems going from this to this
so
a lot of the time
um
[Music]
a lot of the time
i didn't get my second leg out and was
just
it was just upset why is it like this
now
it was just stuck
and i was acting like oh cool oh cool
this is exactly what i wanted yeah yeah
it's exactly what i wanted i wanted to
be in this position this is perfectly
comfortable
oh swimsuit yeah yeah yeah
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah
yeah eventually i got my leg out though
i figured out how to do it properly yeah
i got the gist of it again
it was fun and then then my friends they
also used my floaty later when i was
sick of it
my floating was so popular i'm so glad i
brought it
floating popular
good
choice
[Music]
and then
uh we stayed like really long and you
know we meaning the convention itself
usually is in the evening
and uh let me take another fruit candy
it's usually in the evening and and
around the evening like maybe around
five six
seven pm the like all the cosplayers
they would come to the beach and you
would see oh convention
but
so we were looking forward to that uh
my nan you know at around i guess maybe
6 p.m or so
we saw
some cosplays and we were like oh my god
is it happening we were getting really
hopeful that there were actually other
people besides us
going like too remaining for the
convention
but it was only seven
seven cosplayers
or so
so
it was
on friday it was like seven on saturday
it was like five on sunday it was like
no one
so
yeah
[Laughter]
very very very sad
no convention vibes at all but to be
honest in hindsight i
kind of
preferred it this way
because it made me feel more
more safe and private i guess
yeah because then i knew that no one
knew me
because there was only normal people
around no convention people
um
anyway
then i changed into something into
something cute in the evening and we
went to dinner
um we had some good italian food
i think uh which day was this i have
some i have food pictures of course
but which day
also let me think actually was this
ah
i think it was on the same day
uh wait let me see actually i have pic i
have dates on my pictures um
yeah it was on this day
huh
um
one story i forgot to tell
on this day you know when my friends
finally arrived one reason why they came
late
was because uh
you know
they wanted to get a watermelon they saw
a 10 kilogram watermelon somewhere in
some supermarket and they were like
wouldn't this be fun to eat
at the beach and i agree with that
watermelon at the beach amazing
but
can i like
delete this yeah
hey
my friends
huh
my friends you know
super proudly
arrive
with this
big
really big watermelon
and they're like look i got this huge
watermelon and i'm like
cool
how are we gonna cut it did you think
about that
so
what they did bring
was a lot of a lot of these paper plates
and
plastic forks uh plastic knives
like a hundred of them
but no real knife it was just one of
those white plastic knives
and i'm like this is gonna be a disaster
this is gonna be super super super bad
we're not gonna be able to open this
watermelon
but then
they put the watermelon
into the sand
okay and they start
they start
working on the
on the watermelon
[Music]
with the plastic
and i'm like you guys are so stupid
there's no way that this is going to
work
well turns out
it actually worked out pretty easily
surprisingly i'm like what the [\h__\h]
but with just
two plastic knives
they cracked open
the watermelon
quite successfully
now i will say that it was still a huge
[\h__\h] mess after that because we did
not have forks
i think yeah we only had knives did not
have spoons but you know we could have
spooned it out there
no we had nothing
so
we then got these
uh
paper plates with like little chunks of
watermelon
handed to us
with a lot of watermelon juice
everywhere
and i was trying to eat that with
guess what a plastic knife
yeah they brought the metal no they
fought a little bit further they got the
plates okay if they didn't bring any
plates then it would have really been
even much much much worse
but this somehow worked out and um it
was really yummy so
i actually have a picture of the
watermelon
uh
there you go and i took a you know
there's a [\h__\h] wasp there too i'm
assuming now that this is a wasp
good sound yeah
it looks like the one in my other
picture
look at this high quality picture yo
and you can see how messy the watermelon
actually no at this point it was
actually pretty clean because at some
point we we got it to
a nice shape and then um i would just
slice i got a good technique at some
point i would slice off the pieces with
the knife
off of the watermelon until it was so
flat
yeah
yeah yeah it's a pretty good picture
like yo
that was a zoom three times zoom or so
the watermelon is crisp
[Music]
you guys are idiots there's no way that
we can open this watermelon like this
i must say
i respect
the hustle they did it anyway
i doubted them and i laughed at them and
they did it anyway
respect
later we went to dinner and have some
pictures
of the food
[Music]
for example
oh my god this is
huge what why is this what why is this
this way
oh it's turned around okay
uh
oh
let me turn that
[Music]
like this
here you go this was a starter um it's a
tomatoes
on oh oh yeah bruschetta brusetta
so yummy
that's one starter and then we got a
different starter too
[Music]
mmm this is similar but it's with um
not caprese
or what's it called blazer
i guess it was cup laser yeah let's just
cut blazer i'm thinking of something
else
really yummy buffalo yummy yum yum yum
yum yum
yeah lot of tomatoes yeah the bread was
super crunchy
so bacon chicken and then like i got
actually i got a really really really um
simple dish
[Music]
i got a simple carbonara so i didn't
take a picture of my kaminara but um i
took pictures of my friend's foods that
looked more delicious mine was delicious
too but their pictures looked their
their foods looked better than mine so
took a picture of their
food this was some kind of gnocchi
with some meat
yeah oh god it's getting crowded here
thank you and this was
uh
some some some pasta yeah good pasta
this is just some of the foods that we
had
very good good yummy but i must say oh
my god bruschetta oh
bababi you're so good
we're only at five huh you thought i
would say more
oh no i didn't need any pizza on this
thing
so
oh
let me write down
water melon
with plastic
knives
wow
impress
yeah they surprisingly managed to do a
good job at it
noise
okay okay i'm continuing oh
[Music]
oh was that on the same day
what
[Music]
was that on the same day
i guess soon
really
what
i'm getting confused by my nose but okay
so then after dinner
we walked around we got ice cream again
and
uh
yeah
yeah nothing
nothing much happened then that just
went to the hotel and then sleep sleep
soap
and then it was sunday
sunday
i stayed by the way from thursday to
monday
yeah
so sunday
sunday
sunday sunday
i went to the beach again i was like
confident you know i did this one day
before so i can do it again i'm gonna
get the big umbrella again that everyone
was so happy and satisfied with
so tom i went with my floaty i went
before everybody
else again
and everybody else took their sweet time
again
so i walked up to the dudes the same guy
went to the same beach
and i'm like uh please
umbrella grego
rejo
and he's like no no no no
no
no no no big umbrella and i'm like why
why
and he says oh sunday
many many people very popular day you
have to reserve umbrella
since the day before
and i'm like hey yo what how would i
know i didn't know oh my god but i did
take a look and yeah every big
every big parasol was taken
by peeps
so there were no more left and i was
like trying to discuss you know once
again i was trying to communicate with
my friends
like what do you want what should i do
should i get several smaller hi dana not
as good as your drawings
definitely not i'm just
just scribbling
um and i told i i was like trying to get
them to tell me what they want to do
because like the dude was also like i
don't know
i would that's the day when i was like i
wish i could haggle because
on the previous day
um
you know it was 10
[Music]
euro per
sun bed
but not really like partially like i
guess the price was because of the big
umbrella
and also the placement where where you
get
uh the
the in which area you're placed
and
then on this day
when he was then telling me he can give
me
two small umbrellas
with a couple of sunbeds
close to the beach
i was like yeah two two small umbrellas
it's not gonna cover it i think we're
not gonna all be under the shadow i
think and he wanted the same amount of
money though with
less sunbeds
and less shade he wanted the same amount
of money as the day before for the big
umbrella so i was like
makes no sense dude
i don't know what to do but like i felt
pressured and and
they were like you know they looked so
adult
and um
yeah
they looked so so confident
so i couldn't haggle i felt like i
couldn't haggle in this situation
yeah
so i was like okay i guess i'll take it
because finally after a while i also got
some replies from my friends again but
yeah
it was kind of intimidating and
uh i wish my friends were there
at the moment but they came again later
and then
um
oh
yeah so the thing is
um
i was
i shot let me do anything i was
i was sitting alone again
i was sitting
oopsie all right
oh [\h__\h]
i was sitting
i was sitting here okay
and then a little while later
two of my friends joined
and here is kiwa
[Music]
just hanging and then and then a friend
come mm-hmm
and another friend come
and they start you know uh uh
talking to me and i'm like really
focused on them
looking this way
and and and then and then and then and
then and then you know what suddenly
happens
by the way this day was really windy
suddenly
friends
come from
the other side oh yeah no massage lady
was there every day asking everybody for
massages very very very very
pressuringly very pushing me
but but but friends
surprise me from behind with
with
[Music]
a big big cake not a beef no no not to
the pizza but we have a big cake above
the cake yeah
they suddenly come from behind and they
all start singing happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you
and i'm like what what what what what
i always wanted something like this to
happen to me
i never get surprised like this
so they come over there they put the
they put the
the cake there and they tried their best
to light the candles but the
the wind kept on like you know killing
it but they even had the the sparkly
ones that go
for a few seconds
and then it's over
but they also had like
candles
that said
17.
[Laughter]
uh
the number 17
um
and i was very happy about that because
that's obviously accurate
[Laughter]
they did mention that they did not have
any other numbers
that was pretty much the only numbers
they had available that's why they ended
up buying them
but i liked it i liked it because you
know i'm totally 17. yeah
oh yeah i guess they could have put it
like 71. why would they do it why would
they do that i'm 17. of course they put
it like one seven not seven one
no
that would be rude that would be
inaccurate that would not be the truth
and we want the truth only the truth
yeah it was a it was a strawberry
cheesecake and um
oh it was kind of frozen inside so it
was like an ice cream cake but that was
perfect because it was really hot and it
was not so frozen that you would like
lose your teeth on it it was like like a
good good amount of frozen
that actually worked out pretty well
yeah
it was perfect it was really yummy i was
so happy it had a lot of strawberries on
it and and they let me have the pieces
with the most strawberries on
because yeah you know birthday time i
was i was allowed to be um
greedy so i got the pieces of the most
total bunnies
so
that made me happy
to get like an
afterwards surprise
birthday cake from my friends yeah
thank you friends thank you
and then
of course the massage lady came by again
at some point so some of my friends got
massages
me too actually i got another massage on
that day
uh
yeah and no
no we were just chilling in the water on
that day
let me update my
my notes here
huh
oh
one of my friends is listening to the
stream and corrected me
and yeah
i guess they had all numbers then why
did you choose 17 because i have 17.
there you go there you have it
uh wait
save
oh cause it's more funny okay
wait so um
surprise
okay
yum
yum yum yum yum and basically the rest
of the day we were just chilling we were
just um enjoying the big big big waves
cause on that day this wind was so
strong so the waves were so big and we
kept on jumping with them and i got i
got so much water so much disgusting
ocean water into my nose and my mouth
and my ears and everywhere
uh
like this one was way more salty than
the maldives
water and way more fishy
so
but i was disgusting at some point i was
like okay i'm out of here because i
think if i take any more of this ocean
water i'm going to throw up
yeah
so then i continued to chill people
played with my with my floating again
and then later we saw as i said
later in the evening we saw about five
cosplayers on the beach that's pretty
much about it kind of sad and
disappointing but still kind of fun
and then
we went to dinner after
i i guess i changed i might have changed
into something cute again
and then
we went to dinner but uh
um
so i did i did the following
i was wearing
i was wearing some
so here
here kiwawa feet
this is kiwa feet okay
i was wearing some sandals
okay
and they had
they had some whoopsie
[Music]
they had some platforms
and um
because i walked a little bit in the
sand in them
i had a lot of sand
in there
and i was like let me just let me just
wash this
uh so
i when i arrived at the hotel
i let the
shower
out the outside shower
wash away all the sand okay i [\h__\h] the
sand
and i thought this was smart i thought
you know
this was good because i did this before
and the the sandals might be wet for a
while but it's okay it's kind of
refreshing it's hot outside anyway
so i was like walking a while with these
kind of squeaky shoes now
because every time i walked it made this
like a little bit of a squishy sound
and then we were walking on this busy
street towards the restaurant
for like 15 minutes or so
and then suddenly
[Music]
suddenly
it's my foot
suddenly uh wait how was it it was like
kind of like
this
suddenly the soul
completely lifted itself from the top
part of the soul and it was completely
hollow inside
suddenly
the whole shoe fell apart
yeah and i couldn't walk with it anymore
i could not walk with it yeah all the
all the the you know the wetness itself
was fine but the fact that i was walking
so much with it right after and kept on
like you know
the suction the suction with every step
you know the sounds the squeaky sounds
it made like the
black squeak
eventually
created enough suction for it to rip off
the whole shoe
off of the top part
yeah
so i was like [\h__\h] this is so
embarrassing ah
[\h__\h] did everybody friends please stop i
i i my shoe broke [\h__\h] i'm so [\h__\h]
so
uh my my best friend i sent her on a
mission because there were like you know
all kinds of shops in between the
restaurants there were some shops that
sold like some some beach clothes and
some some beach shoes you know those
flip-flops so she she went there and she
bought
flip-flops on me and she said these are
the best ones she could find
[Music]
it was blue flip-flops
with some really tacky butterflies on
them
they did not fit my outfit at all
because i was wearing a cute red dress
but whatever
but the thing is like i i realized this
is maybe not the best thing either
because if you recall
my feet my one of my foot
okay this is my foot
and
the reason why i had that wound to begin
with was because of one of these shoes
but this is really the only easy choice
you could get at that moment
but my wound was exactly here
that's where you would wear
the flip-flop
so i was worried that it would open it
up again
but it was okay for a little while
yeah i didn't wear them for too long and
i tried to walk really carefully and i
had a band-aid but you know the band-aid
would like rub on it too so
not so good
worst spot yeah
normally normally i when i wear
flip-flops oopsie i always get like
blisters here and here
where it rubs on those parts
but this time i had it here and that was
that was tough
it's right now
i still see like the aftermath but it's
basically healed thankfully
yeah anyway
that was the that was the shoe disaster
mamma mia mama mia
said it twice for good measure
ah
shoe
broke
flip flops
let's go
yeah
okay
and then we have dinner
uh oh
on this day you know generally all of
the restaurants that we went to pretty
much were recommended by uh to us
by
people
who went to the real remini one week
before
like um some other austrians who are
friends with one of my friends
and um and they made like a whole list
of like 20 restaurants and ice cream
places and all that
also marked on the map like really in
detail
basically wrote a whole book about where
we should go and all that that's cool
that's cool actually it was helpful
um but sad that we weren't there the
week before
[Laughter]
so
anyway
uh
one of the places places that were
recommended and that seemed to be really
famous and popular was a big restaurant
called bounty you should look it up
rimini bounty and it's pirate themed
[Music]
now this is just one view i didn't get a
good shot of the restaurant but inside
it's like a like a like a pirate ship
inside and then outside is also pretty
cool like maybe you see the girl the
waitress
she's dressed they're all dressed like
in a you know pirate attire
really cute
yeah and then there you see behind the
waitress there's a live band they had a
really loud live band
they were like doing some rock songs and
stuff
uh in their own rendition it was really
loud so it was really hard to hear hear
one another when we were at the table
trying to talk with each other um but
besides that it was really cool yeah
um
it seems like yeah a big place when we
arrived
uh
i i went up to the
to the
lady to the pirate lady who was
assigning tables and i was like hey we
have no reservation
but with so many people can you give us
a table and she's like
uh no probably not sign up here and you
may have to wait at least 40 minutes
could be one hour it could be two hours
but yeah if you really want to do that
go ahead so because we weren't sure what
to do
we just signed up and we were like maybe
we should go somewhere else
i'm really [\h__\h] hungry though i just
want to go somewhere to eat i don't know
if i can wait for so long
and then we signed up
and then
we were like you know kind of like
trying to figure out what to do but then
suddenly
after like three minutes of talking
even though the waitress was talking
about it like so negatively like as if
we had no chance suddenly we get
contacted hey your table is ready after
three minutes
what
what what oh my god we were like oh my
god this is for real this is real holy
[\h__\h]
yeah it was real we actually got a table
so [\h__\h] early
someone must have literally just left in
that moment so they cleaned up the table
for us and yeah we got this big table
outside and
yeah with the live music and and then
and then they um they have other food i
guess but they mostly uh focus on
burgers they're famous for their burgers
and they have different types of burgers
like normal burgers and then double
burgers and then they have anglers
burgers and then they have wacky burger
and so i was like hell yeah you know
what i'm gonna get the wacky burger
he'll walk you burger
it doesn't really you know look special
it's a bit difficult to take a picture
because it was kind of like in a in a
wooden box
not on the table and not on the plate it
was on a wooden box and so it was hard
to get a proper picture and it was like
on the side covered in these fries but
but it was really yummy it had a proper
tomato it had salad in there and it had
the wagyu patty
now i will say
it's like i mean
it wasn't like
insanely insane incredibly
like surprisingly delicious it was
definitely delicious and i'm i'm glad i
got my walking burger but the thing is
you know i'm the only one on the table
who got the vlogging burger
and the moment i got it the moment my
friends heard what i just ordered they
were all
aiming to get a bite from my tiny baby
wagyu burger
and the moment it arrived i felt i felt
their their looks i saw i saw them
looking at my burger spent one one
friend specifically who's watching the
stream right now
yeah
when i when i took a bite they asked
like oh
how how is it how is it you do you want
to buy it from mine kind of like
hoping that if i take a bite from them
they will get a bite from mine
[Laughter]
i i felt it i felt the
ah the stairs and my burger and i was
like you know i have a really small
tummy and
it's hard for me to finish foods
and and this too this was so much it
doesn't look like much i know but it
wasn't a lot for me
and then i i was getting closer and
closer to being like really full but i
didn't i didn't want to give away my
whole burger you know it was the most
expensive burger on the menu so i wanted
i wanted to really get the most out of
it but at some point i was like okay i
can't i can't do this anymore
so the last few bites i i gave one bite
to every friend
and they were happy
they did say that uh
what was it
the
the angus one was really good too
the vacuum was a little bit better
but
it's not like a
like a overwhelmingly
overwhelming difference
like you're happy if you got it if you
got the angus
um burger
but the wagyu it has like a special
something
um
[Laughter]
but everybody wanted to eat my bird i
was trying to keep it the secret that i
had to vacuum because i knew i know it i
know
but the burgers even even though i
struggle with eating the whole thing
it's still a small
a small food right relatively small see
i only had one patty
so if i gave all my friends a bite i
would have not much left but i gave them
some small bites at the end
i'm gonna protect the burger
so yeah
[Music]
about the live music at the end they i
was surprised like you know i didn't
know these people but maybe they're like
kind of well known in lemony or so
because at the end when they were done
with their
uh with their set
there were like
three
three or four
women young women standing there waiting
for them to like
clean up or pack everything away and
they were like trying to take pictures
and get signatures and all they had they
had groupies
they had groupies what but when they
finished i was like
i should get up on that stage and sing
no not girlfriends it seems like most
fans yeah
yeah yeah
anyway
that was that was a really really good
dinner not very italian but this place
is just really really well known in
remini i think
and it was a cool experience yeah very
piratey ahoy
pirates
nakamimo
[Music]
they're very popular oh well one one
thing that is special about this place
is um
like uh they they bring this these huge
jugs or something like uh of draft beer
put it on your table
and
i don't know how to explain it so it
actually sounds special but but it's
like uh
see here table
and they put these
huge beer thingies there
even though people so small okay maybe
not that small
wow wow
a pog
[Music]
oh wait you didn't even see what i was
drawing
you didn't see what i was drawing oh
here it is
that's
this is
this is supposed to be the
i don't even remember what it looked
like
yeah okay that's a little bit too big
ah
yeah but that was nice and i got really
late and then i finally went back to
lo lottel
yummy oh i want to eat this burger again
it was actually really good
i'm glad we made it inside because um
that was one of the places my friends
really wanted to check out definitely
find bulga
yeah hotel i know i learned in school
hotel
[Laughter]
and then oh wait actually i got a creme
brulee i love creme brulee and i saw it
on the menu so i was like
what the hell
what the hell let's get the creme brulee
here
wow
creme brulee
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's already been two hours but i'm
close to the end of my story and then
we're going to read super chat those
because i need to catch up
last day
last day science should be
monday
uh okay
so last day uh i had to check out really
early so i also had to go to the beach
early
um also i stored like everybody's bags
in my hotel for some reason
because then later on we would go with
the taxi from my place
instead of picking everybody up everyone
just like went into the taxi on my place
so we went to the beach
and then on this day there was barely
any wind
oh and this time we actually got even
less some beds because we were like have
most of the time nobody's even using the
sunbeds so we don't even need that many
yeah so we saved some money there
and we we
went into the water as always as per
usual and
uh because the waves were so calm i got
to focus
on the soft soft sand and i've noticed
one thing
when i was
[Music]
touching
when i was touching the sand
in the water
i noticed
sand sand sand okay and then
water water water water water water
water water water
i would notice actually even though it
feels so soft
there are
a few like shells
here and there tiny ones
and then my hobby for that day was
picking them up
between my big toe and the small one
next to it
bringing it up out of the water
and then looking at them
it was hermit crabs
and i would like
[Music]
okay they were not that big
okay so i would i would hold them in my
hand i would be like yo friends look
look i have a hermit crab because it
will like peek out
it would seem like a little bit
and we would stare at it and then some
of them would like move a little bit
they would be like what the [\h__\h] is
going on
what why am i outside of the water and
they would slowly slowly come outside
and then at some point they would go so
far outside that i would like scream and
i would go like and i would throw them
away back into the water because then i
actually freaked out and was really
scared of them
and then i kept on repeating that i kept
on picking them up and i kept on
bringing them out and i kept on staring
at them and
calling over my friends and we looked at
them and then it slowly came out and
then they came out so far that they
almost touched my hand and i would go
like
actually not only me all my friends
around me we all
screamed together because apparently
these tiny tiny tiny crabs are so
terrifying they could eat us up and kill
us
yeah
very very very violent hermit crabs
yeah and i keep them kept on throwing
them back into the water and picking up
and throwing back into the water
and yeah i was really harassing them
this is literally harassing them sorry
i'm so sorry but i was so excited about
them
cute hermit crabs
i've only laid a new you know we had
this whole hermit crab moment in the
maldives
yeah they must have been really confused
[Laughter]
kiana wrestling the ocean equivalent of
grizzly bears exactly bears yeah
really terrifying terrifying sea
monsters
there was one crab just one crab that
just stayed in the shell and didn't say
hello at all it didn't come out at all
it was really shy
i don't know what was wrong with that
crap
i was like this [\h__\h] i'm not gonna say
hello to her she already threw so many
of my friends into the water so
violently
no bully please
it's new yeah
yeah
it didn't want to be thrown well i did
throw him in the end anyway
okay yeah it was cute the peaks were so
cute
it was really chill really calm on that
day so we also i would like float on the
on the water with my back we're gonna
chill massage lady came up i came again
too
said hello every day
um
we even made like appointments on the
previous day with saying she would be
like oh why not you here tomorrow and
then we would be like oh we're here this
time so find us and then
she would find us and give us massages
yeah
good lady good lady i wish i wish all
beaches would have
massage ladies running around
because that was actually really a good
idea like you go to the beach
to have fun and to relax
and i would most
well
i would definitely prefer buying a
massage over like a shitty
necklace that is way overpriced
it's a bit risky to get massages on
beaches
uh
i mean if it's like a
like like this old chinese lady
i don't know i don't see why it's
dangerous
if it's like some creepy person i'm not
gonna
say yeah i guess but that that lady
should seem totally fine
hmm
yeah she got good business with our
friend group yeah i think so too
uh so actually
uh after that beach time we actually
left kind of early uh
on that day oopsie oh
left kind of early on that day because
it was really hot due to the lack of the
wind on that day the hotness was even
more
apparent
and
i was suffering but wait let me write
down uh
i made the crab
hi
bye
hi bye
[Music]
it didn't update
what it
where'd it go
oh did i write too much
i might have written too much it just
kind of just stops there how about if i
do this yeah okay
that works
hi bye hi bye
i ran in the room
incredible
so and then and then yeah so we left a
little bit early uh to have lunch before
our flight like a late lunch or like an
early dinner
and there was one restaurant that i
already wanted to go to
on the first day and but you know we
didn't go there on the first day because
i couldn't convince them enough and then
on the second day i also couldn't
convince them but the thing is there was
this restaurant that i walked by
and it looked really really really cute
because it had so much cute decoration
and and i really like the vibes of it it
was mostly seafood but i so thought you
know i want to go there even though i
don't like seafood there was this one
big table that was big enough for all of
us that had
swings as
the sitting
swings
and i was like this looks so nice it has
swings and like um
um like a like a like curtains around
the whole thing and i was like i wanna
go there
the whole time just for the experience
of sitting there yeah
and yeah that's where the cute waitress
was yeah
so finally finally finally finally on
the last day
i could convince my friends to come here
luckily when we went there for lunch the
uh
the table was actually empty and have a
photo so you will understand why i
really wanted to go here
this place
also is next to so much garlic
yeah it's dreamy it's cute like every
seating area was like nicely decorated
but this one was special in my opinion
um
yeah
so i wanted to sit there all the time
and finally finally we made it there
and
uh it was [\h__\h] hot on this day and so
it was kind of suffering because you
know we were sitting outside
no ac
but
the food was really yummy and then there
was this cute waitress i kept on like um
talking to her because like they would
bring us a bottle of water in the
beginning and they didn't bring any
glasses so i was like
i went i went up to her
uh because i just saw her you know
waiting some other table and i don't
think she was supposed to wait our table
but she was just the woman i went up to
so i was like can we have some glasses
and
and i noticed oh she doesn't really
speak good english so i brought her over
to the table and i showed her that we
have no glasses and then she she nodded
with a smile and then came back a little
while later and brought me the glasses
but in the meantime i figured oh you
know what it would be nice to have some
ice cubes because
it's [\h__\h] hot so i said in italian
italiano and said
[Music]
she had this cute smile she was like oh
this girl's trying her best to speak in
italian
i was so proud that i was able to say
quebec
and my friends they didn't even
understand what i just ordered so i felt
pretty cool
i sounded so fluent
yeah and then she came back and then she
brought me the cuvetto di gianto and i
was like mila grazia and she laughs at
me again and then she puts down the
cutlery on my table and so she places a
knife on my right side and ah no no no
no she places a a fork on my left side
and i i pick it up and i say [\h__\h] it
and she laughs at me again
she's probably funny i was like a baby
saying words and then i pick up the
knife that she puts next to me and i'm
like oh i don't know what this means
anymore i said that in english and then
she figures oh oh oh she probably wants
to know what it means so so with the
biggest smile she says coltello and i'm
like
and then she laughs
yeah cute moments i really liked her
i kept on trying to say
italian words to her she was cute she
made me happy because she was smiling at
me um yeah when i saw her being happy i
was happy too
[Music]
and then and then finally for the first
time after arriving in italy uh i
finally ordered a pizza
it was really good
i wanted a simple pizza doll because it
was such a hot day
and i didn't want to have a too
complicated pizza i felt like normally
normally i like my pizzas to be like
complicated
but on this day i felt like something
simple will do
so i got this
uh it's not exactly a margarita
um
but it's um
yeah it's with bugatta borata in the
middle which is a little kind of like
mozzarella
and cherry tomatoes it was so good
[Music]
yeah surprisingly no coin surprisingly
no tuna i know i know i know
but sometimes simple is best i get that
hmm was so good but they also they
served um
like my friends uh ordered cabonara and
they served them in the craziest
dish
i wonder
is there any people who like to remedy
and know this restaurant and know the
name of it because
um i have no picture of this
but
um
i want to show i'm sure that if you look
up the restaurant you find
you find the carbonara plate i'm
guessing they serve all the
all the pasta in that
plate which is not really a plate
i mean there's something written on
there on the left picture
but i'm not sure what's
what it is
oh wait coconuts
this is coconuts
because
they're on the bottom right on the menu
placement thingy this coconut dot it is
that the written let me look at that
coconut springy
oh
that is
not it
[Laughter]
that is i guess some company they work
with some club
some club or something
[Music]
really
i can't find it
the place is called cheats
really
[Music]
yeah
yeah that's it
i think it seems so
oh oh oh oh oh oh
[Music]
let me
try to find a picture
of the way they serve the carbonara
they have so much seafood my friends
also got seafood and it looked
disgusting
partially like they had some kind of
like big crab and it looked disgusting
but no way the carbonara here looks like
i know it this this this could make my
ah
it's not the perfect picture but
oopsie
where'd it go
wow oh yummy
mamma mia it looks so yummy
oh wait
that's a good picture
wait wait where the [\h__\h] did it go this
website is [\h__\h] i'm on some kind of like
review website
[Music]
where'd it go where did where did that
picture go
and i think my friend sent me something
friend who watches the stream
ah
[Music]
it's just a restaurant
i'm here i found a good picture
okay
[Music]
this is how they serve the cabonara
in a huge
crown
[Laughter]
and it's kind of hard to eat out of that
it actually here it looks pretty flat i
think it's the white uh angle lens that
they use in this picture
feels like it's a wide angle lens
but it's it's much like higher
much more high
and it's really hard to eat out of it
because you have to like can you imagine
you have to lift your arms to get in
there
no no i was joking about wearing the
crown but in the end nobody did
we all forgot about it
now i should wear it
new crown
i'm totally wearing it
okay so i was really glad to go here at
the end on the last day before our
flight it was yummy i met a cute
waitress
happy happy happy
yeah and then let me see my notes
yeah at this point i was actually happy
to leave because i felt so hot and the
weather was so humid actually
surprisingly humid
i didn't think italy would be that humid
it's been a long time since the last
time i was in italy i used to go so
often when i was when i was younger with
my mommy uh but yeah it's been a long
time so i didn't remember it being so
humid
um
so i was happy to leave at this point
and then we went to the airport
and
finally
rest around of my dreams
cute waitress
and we went to the airport
and it was
it was
a ghost airport
[Music]
why why you say oh let me tell you why
where's the picture
i didn't save the picture
i sent it to genma
here it is
he spooked
spooky
this was the airport
on our departure
the main entrance hall
it had
about four
check-in desks
and uh pretty much four gates four
flights
there was two flights on that day at the
point when we arrived two more two more
flights it was pretty early still
so empty
yeah but we also boarded or like checked
in kind of late actually after getting
past the security there were you know
austrians going home
quite a lot of them actually
um but yeah that was just right before
the gate waiting for waiting for the
flight
so
empty
i was shocked i found you know oh my god
we gotta be early at the airport you
know that we don't miss the flight but
then i arrive and there's literally like
no no waiting line at all no person
waiting to check in their bags
i was done with my check-in in like two
seconds
and then yeah waited for my friends and
then we boarded the plane the plane was
you know one of those
budget airline planes it was cheap
and small
and but yeah it was all good at this
point i was just happy to go back but
you know what i noticed
when we arrived
they clapped again
[Music]
when we arrived back in austria they
clapped again and i think i now have
my
result
of my studies
i say
that europeans like to clap when flying
with budget airlines
yeah those shitty small budget airlines
why because those are more likely to be
boarded by um people who don't travel so
much
i i is is what i've picked up so far
so it's for a lot of them it's their
first flight in their lifetime or it's
like the like one of the few flights
they had in their lifetime it's very
special to them and they're excited to
go to italy or whatever yeah they're
just really excited they're really happy
so everything is like super
fascinating and special to them so they
land after a one hour flight and they're
like
let's go
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah
that's my that's my theory
because it never happened to me ever
before
on a on a long distance flight
never only these little budget plans
um italian people do that no matter what
type of flight it is
i see well i was actually like so tired
i fell asleep on the flight normally i
can't i can't fall asleep so fast but in
this this this situation i was so tired
i fell asleep and then
suddenly i am awakened by applause and i
i look over to my friends who are
sitting like in the row in front of me
uh diagonally and they they were looking
at me because they knew what i was
thinking about applause in their
airplane they look at me grinning
smiling
and i look back at them like really
tired
and angry linus
and i'm like huh [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
stop clapping at once
[Music]
in the end i must say it was successful
a very successful trip even though um it
wasn't you know how we originally
thought it was going to be at all how we
originally wanted it to be
but it was really good because we had a
lot of fun we never like had a vacation
trip like this before before our whole
friend circle
i went you know to vacation with my best
friend before like the spa vacation
but all of us together it was like a
school trip that was nice and um
yeah we had fun and everybody got a
sunburn except for me
even though usually i always get a
sunburn but this time i'm so proud
i did my best i i put a hundred
sunscreen production factor sunscreen on
me
before swimming and after swimming i was
very careful
yeah all of my friends got a sick
sunburn and then they put curd on their
bodies afterwards
yeah
yogurt and curd and [\h__\h] to
to yeah it's a home remedy home remedy
no roasted chicken you mean
yeah fire proof
yeah
so now
um i have a funny aftermath story
remember what my mom said in the very
beginning
now i thought the water was fine it was
warm it felt it looked somewhat clean
it wasn't as clear as it was the water
in the maldives
yeah i will start the funny i will do
the funny
cause i'm not done with the funny here
comes the real funny you know my mom on
the first day she calls me and says
as you see on the notes here she says
remini ocean is poop
and i'm like yeah okay mom bye like
whatever whatever you say it's no idea
what you're talking about
why why are you so negative mom
now uh three days after i arrived back
home around three days or so
my friend sent me a news article
and i look at it and it's it says
remini and a lot of other beaches close
by of other cities close by
all the beaches are closed
for being too dirty
with fecal
bacteria
[Music]
[Applause]
what
my mom was right all along
apparently so many beaches in that area
including the one that we went to
were closed
now just a few days ago
i don't know if they're still closed
but yeah they tested it
the authorities tested the water like i
guess they do occasionally
and
apparently there was too much fecal
bacteria poo-poo water
yeah
um
which was apparently confusing to the
people of remini because right after
they did their test
they did their own private test the
authorities of lemony and their test
turned out fine apparently so there's
like a drama about yo yo the beach is
totally fine it's okay it's not dirty
you can go in
yeah but i find it so funny my mom was
right in the end but i mean you know
it's like the water was okay it was fine
yeah and i don't know like it was a few
days later so i'm not sure if that that
shouldn't have been the state of it
while we were there but i don't know how
fast
this can change
i'm not sure how how fast the ocean
water
the state of it can change
hmm
yeah yucky water no no
it was okay
uh
it was it's fine
it's probably fine but
it's funny
um
yeah i mean i don't know is that where
it came from i guess so that makes sense
but hmm
[Music]
don't know i know about it
water is like in the maldives
oh mamma mia
it's so bright
oh what hasn't it italy that's in italy
you have such a beach in italy
mamma mia
oh
it's not on the big italian island it's
on
small
smaller island next to it
it looks pretty it should go sometime
yeah it's an island
[Music]
i heard about it before yeah yeah
so that
was
my
italian
travel story that was supposed to be
a big big
crap
vacation in the beginning because we
were all like negative about it like oh
it's going to be [\h__\h] because it's not
what it's supposed to be
we got scammed into a convention that's
not a convention but it ended up being a
really fun time with my friends
it was a nice vacation i actually got to
relax and chill and have fun with my
friends
and um yeah
that was nice yeah
got some good food too
[Music]
had fun in the water with my friends
yeah
it was a good experience even though it
was very stressful like during going
there during a stressful time where i
felt like i should be home working
uh was pressuring but
um that's okay
yeah before returning to italy ask us
for advice
thank you alessandro
thank you
yeah made to make the best out of a bad
situation exactly
hope you can go to proper convention
next year
i don't know if i would go next year but
um
i don't know
now i went to remini once so
kind of want to go to lucca sometime but
luca is also feels a little bit
intimidating
because like luca is a famous convention
in italy that's known for being spread
throughout a whole city and it only
happens like starting from the afternoon
into the late night
and it's just the whole city is a
convention basically but it feels i
don't know just the thought of it is a
little bit intimidating but i need to
check it out sometime
um so anyway thank you for listening
we're gonna read super chats now because
i need to i need to catch up and uh i
did my story i did i'm danny with the
funny
sounds wild
yeah the italians you know they have
wild conventions they're all in the
evening it's kind of chill
in the evening and they have beach
conventions isn't that so cool
because you you know what it means to
have beach conventions
you know what that means
swimsuit cosplays
[Music]
yes yes
yes many many swimsuit cosplays
[Music]
yeah okay so i will know
i'm done with the bunny
uh
oh yeah wait
news
poop water
that's the
last thing i would write on my notes
[Laughter]
mommy was right all along
okay
[Applause]
okay i'm gonna get rid of that now
[Music]
now we need super tactile
i need a third fruit candy holy [\h__\h]
i think my throat is really [\h__\h] up
man
talking streams like this
kill my voice even faster than you know
gaming streams i talk a lot even in
gaming streams but at least not as much
as in these kind of streams
um oh well
okay
um
well
i have to read i think everything's
starting from monday
or so
[Music]
um
oh
so there was a super chat reading did i
have super chat on learners oh yes i did
but did i finish the super chats from
the super chat's reading
i think i did because i i remember being
like completely caught up
so then there were super chats from the
kfp 101
i think maybe that's where i start and
the director's cut
[Music]
i think yeah you guys say director's cut
but i think we're missing the
uh kfp one-on-one video super chats as
well
okay
[Music]
hey this is what we'll be reading
is not much let's go
god of amiibo thank you soon
hope to visit italy again have been
since i was a kid glad you had a good
time thank you yeah you should go if you
live in europe why the hell not
italy is so close
easy to get to
a bit more expensive than like greece
and spain i think but
um italy has nice places wait one second
how about bgm
we called this back again
okay so god of amiibo says
um
it's my birthday today how kind of you
to make a video all about me on my
special date since i'm extremely
hysterical yoga
jokes aside i had a request i already
wrote a number on my employee card so
can i ask you to verify the number 52
love your tantrum of course i don't
think it's taken so feel free it's yours
it's yours all yours 52
god of amiibo is yours enjoy the number
and happy belated birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday god of amiibo happy
birthday to you
[Music]
[Applause]
congratulations sorry my
congratulations came a bit late
i hope you had a lovely day
and got a lot of congratulations from
your friends a lot of well wishes and
all that and your family
um
yeah stay healthy
and stay in kfp
and then you'll be happy forever
thank you so much
[Music]
had a relaxing day
i hope you ate some cake
birthday you have to eat cake
looking for the top donkey showing cruz
duncan
what is it this time
oh holy one i had hoped to greet you in
your previous visit but the line of your
worshippers and adores of your recent
deeds were so massive that it took two
weeks to be able to offer my prayers
my previous visit oh
before i went to get the frog right like
in the same stream when i prepared to
get the frog
i thank you oh patreon
bird of phoenix then for your continued
protection of our village and enriching
the lives of your faithful mayhem flames
of life burnt bright everlasting and
beautiful
oh
jeff
it's so nice to hear from you somebody
who actually respects me unlike these
chickens in the chat ah this is how it's
supposed to be
ah thank you jeff
thank you so much
i will come
and bless your village again sometime
soon
yes yes see you there
please take care
and uh protect the village in my name
until i'm back
jacob's monkey thank you vengeful bubba
for now getting pets from kiwawa danke
should
justice for bubba dancer violet's secret
name
there were four flowers in the flower
laying on the floor
wait wait wait wait dog food was a red
one thanks for the twitter space and the
tweets you're too sweet boss hope the
foot is better today
oh thank you that was my first proper
twitter space so far
before that all my twitter spaces were
uh my cat's purring
[Music]
which i think is
the right way to do a twitter space
anyway
yeah per space
but yeah i hope you enjoyed that space i
was just talking about my foot the whole
time
thank you very much mwah my foot is
better now yeah it's all fixed also now
i don't walk on sand the whole day
anymore so
it has time to heal
in the open air
properly
[Music]
patsy duncan spanking him thanks for the
pinky i said both kinds of yolk
i didn't expect this from you throwing
me under the bus like that what the hell
you don't mean it like that right
right
you want to be on my good side no
we're not kind of a call we're not a
cult
we're not
no
um
oh i said it before doesn't matter
doesn't matter you need to know
when to
repeat the things i say and when not to
repeat them
you should know
when i did an oopsie and you should know
when i really mean what i said
you have to be able
to
um to assess that on your own
[Music]
m next up is a director's cut
all right there's
[Music]
wait it's only two
on my side it's only two
oh yeah i think it got turned off
because of stupid automatic
monetization thingy from youtube
um recognizing something that we have
permission for anyway and then it turned
it off
[\h__\h]
this [\h__\h]
scott thanks for the pinkie and duckling
thanks for pinky both of you
the only super chats for the director's
cut
so sad
so sad youtube why do you do this to me
why
sky says director's car this will be my
third time to watch this concert oh
however i will still enjoy it besides
the original song i love four blood the
most oh that's the world has a guilt
yeah four blood it's just such a good
song it's so cool
i'm glad you enjoyed it
it's it's just oh my god it's so good
it's so good
[Music]
thank you for watching it skye
thank you
for your support
i hope you enjoyed the director's cut
the other one is from don cooter who
says only kiara could make perfection
even more perfect
yeah
yeah so for me
the way the director's cut looks like i
am
i am satisfied
[Music]
i think it turned out really well
yeah thanks a lot
for waiting for it very patient kfp
[Music]
um nani stanley
ah
okay so now we have the stray super
chats
[Music]
straight straight
where's the other foam nail
[Music]
ah i saved it in a different folder
today is the 31st yeah 41st by the way
oh that reminds me oh yeah
you guys were telling me that the the
wallpaper for the members only
uh ran out again which is so weird
because i'm like pretty damn sure that
when i was uploading it again
i um made sure that it's like available
for another two weeks or so
uh but for some reason i guess it didn't
take that setting
let me upload it again one last time and
have it up for like one day
i mean i think like you guys all
downloaded it already but whatever
uh let me do that now because it's the
31st cell at least in my country
and then tomorrow you guys will get the
new wallpaper
july right it's the it's the birthday
one right
so these two
oh wait it can i can only do seven days
oh
well then i'll delete it myself
can i
oh well
um i am
[Music]
dry
members wallpaper
[Music]
tomato
okay i'm gonna upload it on the
community board once more
i'm really a bit more than one month
away from two years of cuava oh my god
apparently
holy [\h__\h]
two years
whoo
wow
in my whole life i i rarely have
continued one job
like that long
but i guess i didn't have so many
jobs in general over
yeah i'm just i'm just you know i'm 17
so
hmm
i couldn't have had that many jobs
uh
july
wallpaper last chance
[Music]
if you haven't
that should be fun okay
okay it's uh it's up now
if you don't have it yet go get it
[Music]
okay now
now
straight super chats
we'll stick with you guys for as loving
as we can what as long as you can but
you're gonna be loving too right
you have wallpapers i can download wait
you don't know you really don't know how
you like saying it ironically
sarcastically
uh like two or three months ago i
started giving out some high quality
wallpapers that i commissioned
from artists
and and they're like the clean version
of it
is always distributed to the members you
didn't know
don't you get notifications
wrong link and no
should be the right link
hmm yeah
that's the right link
[Music]
and it's on a community page for members
only post there you see
uh
dalia every month but like after one
month you can't get it anymore so you
should really check
um
you should check every month
about the wallpaper
yeah they're good for your pc your pc
will feel better if you use it
and i use it for the
monthly schedules too but
the public only gets to see the art
with the schedule on top of it so the
clean version with no schedule is only
for members
so popcorn yes yes i'm excited too
i'll see you there
thank you my sweet chicken
okay and then uh wait wait my brain is
slow slow slow slow brain tomato
a stray thumbnail here
pinata
[Music]
okay
oh yeah you have to click matome
download though
just click some obvious button
you know i would use like an english
site but giga
gigafile has you know the function of
getting rid of the data after a month
while for example we transfer that i
also like to use
the maximum is like shorter than that
not a full month so i would have to like
go back and like get a new link and all
that and that sounds kind of annoying so
i like to use giga file
normally
thank you very much
thank you
very very considerate
okay
[Music]
foreign
my eyes
when i started reading the red one
i i saw something in the corner of my
eye
let me have their birthday
they want a job title
happy birthday belated birthday
job title foreign
what are you good at
is there some special skill you have
some experience or so
help me help me
[Music]
yeah
he watches a lot of my vods
shouldn't all of you be doing that
shouldn't there be a given i'm currently
watching all of kim alvarez does that
count
he's good watching passports what the
[\h__\h]
what kind of like skill is that
first of all all of you should be doing
that second of all
like that's not not a skill it's just
like you doing something
ah
um
how about archival
kfb arc archivist
yeah
just watching my boss is not a job it
should just be your your default
lifestyle to get
to like from the catcall just be just
basic
isn't that cow carrot
i guess oh but it's not like it's his
official title
um
yeah yeah go with archivist
enjoy
and hope your birthday was nice yeah
no i'm the slave
oh come on cow carrot
i'm i'm paying you i think
and you enjoy your work no
hey at least at least i i i put my whole
tangent about italy
into one stream
aren't you happy about that
yeah for the kfb 101
stuff
i i i leave it to gemma so i don't know
if he actually got the money but i think
he's getting paid that's what i'm saying
well if you didn't get it then let genma
know
jenna is taking care of that
[Music]
no
it's because i don't do the paperwork
[Music]
no
anyway
uh pawn thank you for two pinkies hi
kenneth welcome back i'm so happy for
solar popcorn i can't believe it is
happening recommendation maps are almost
done and it should be up at viva lakia
website first week of august i'm glad
that you um put it on the
on on the on the website so it's easy
for me to find again thank you
also i found out that one million dance
studio i know them i watch their videos
korean dance group with 25 million subs
they already have 25 million subs holy
[\h__\h]
do dance lessons also private maybe you
should check them out it is in the
website i only wish you to make fun and
exciting memories while you're in korea
love you and can't wait
ah
maybe you guys don't know um
it's a a dance studio that got extremely
well known and
in korea because they blew up on youtube
uh with their choreographies
and they got so popular that i think
it's kind of hard to get in there now
probably i would assume so they got so
famous like they are also like on tv and
they make choreographies for the biggest
k-pop groups and all that
they blew up
incredible
i mean can you think of any other like
dance studio that has 25 million subs
incredible
i don't watch them so much anymore these
days but i used to watch like so many of
their videos
oh yeah lovely
yes they are tv level famous yes yes yes
i would say in korea
everybody who's not like 60 years old
knows them
everybody who watches youtube you know
[Music]
i don't know i i feel like you know they
they dance so much like hip hop style
uh if i would take a lesson there i feel
like i couldn't keep up
but actually it sounds like an
interesting idea maybe i'll look into it
um
i remember sometimes in their videos
sometimes you would see
you know mostly it's koreans dancing
there but sometimes you would see like
one or two foreigners
in the in the dance lesson videos that
they upload
and they really stand out
oh dear kewalo would stand out oh dear
uh
thank you punk
[Music]
hope you had a wonderful and fulfilling
break i'm researching for my next recipe
video and wanted to ask if there's one
dish you would like to master what would
it be
would it be okay if i made a video
tutorial to help
thanks
if you think you think you could master
it and want to help me
i'm the owner of kfp
i don't know
what
[Music]
something i don't know how to make that
i wanna
make
i can't think of anything specific right
now
[Music]
i mean i would like to learn how to bake
some like dope ass
cakes but
that's baking
huh
trying to teach kia how to cook root
exactly
[Music]
oh oh oh he can bake too
all right hmm
[Music]
now we have to challenge him with
something more difficult something
really difficult
like no you know you know
he says he will master it and then teach
me then we have to make it something
really difficult
something really challenging
[Music]
the
the most difficult recipe ever
doesn't have to be a cake
[Laughter]
um
come up with some stuff
guys souffle nah
basic that's basic cooking
[Music]
risotto a nice risotto you know what i
really like to learn how to make a nice
risotto but
um
i guess so but no i mean i mean i made
arizona before
i feel like i don't need his help to
learn how to make it
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i guess okay
but a result with no mushrooms
um
i don't
[Music]
know now i'm thinking too long about it
the ultimate pot roast
it just makes something interesting
this makes something interesting and
impress me
why are mushrooms because i don't like
mushrooms and every time i look at like
an italian place menu
which has risotto even if they have
three different types of risottos
it always has mushrooms
[Music]
always there's like three types of
risottos two have mushrooms in it and
the third one has seafood so i never
ordered the risottos even though i love
risottos
[Music]
yeah anyway impress me
yeah i'm back thank you for welcoming me
back so
kindly thank you
what is that cute art in your profile
picture i want to see the big version i
don't recall
i don't recall saying that in big
where is it
goku
i want to say it
have i seen this one before
it doesn't it's so small i'm not sure
you have to show me again
show me
i actually liked it already
show me again
thank you
[Music]
speaking german to me
wow tai chi
[Music]
impressive
thank you i am back tai chi
thank you for always being there
welcoming me back
[Music]
function
yeah taiji spoke in german even
impressive
luna shine krone thank you
congrats have been invited by seoul
popcorn with bait and joe i can't go
there because of my work but i wish you
have a great time in south korea also
i'm looking forward to your collab with
navi mama so much
yeah we already did one we got along
really well so i hope that in person in
korea we'll also get along well
[Music]
sean r thank you for the pinky hey buzz
with all the frog love i've heard from
you
i was reminded of a short game on steam
you and the others
should definitely try to get permission
for it's called frog fractions and it's
a trip anyway much love and have a nice
day
oh
let me look it up
[Music]
crochet that looks like a kusoga
that is definitely a kusuki
way too long
[Music]
but
overwhelmingly positive because you'll
get
top tier coming yeah
it looks like a remake from the one in
atari
uh
huh
huh no cow is less of a crystal getting
this what the [\h__\h] how dare you
okay oh
i don't know about this
the game game of the decade what the
[\h__\h]
rock fractions is not about frog
fractures
what is this what is this game
what is this
you don't understand it's amazing
but it's not good at selling itself to
me
[Music]
the less you know the better
i'll think about it okay okay okay
the thing is i actually did want to play
some frog related games
so
okay
note
frog fractions
uh pudding channel thank you soon
i couldn't send a super chat for your
birthday until now your 3d concert was
amazing this past few months have been
pretty rough but i always can count on
your streams cheer me up a bit you're
always right always working so hard
thank you for your content beloved
kiwawa red
you're still right write red at the end
of your super chats even though i don't
even need that anymore
thank you
thank you dakoma
for also always supporting me with your
pixel art is so cute
and you also i every time i end the
stream afterwards on twitter i look and
i see your tweets especially after kind
of orca streams
dakoma is always going crazy on twitter
it's really nice to see that positive
energy thank you
thank you please continue supporting
kiwawa no cheating
kiwawa number one
okay
i see you working for other people i saw
that
i saw that
what came out of a priority
okay
[Laughter]
sorry i'm confused because of uh what's
written in the super chat
i can't it's stan's dad someone offered
to buy a super chat for me because
toddlers are expensive but it's sad's
second birthday today we're still around
he loves kotori and he calls you kara
but can kiki was the best
what he knows my name
oh my god he can say my name
oh my god
the baby is able to save my name
he has a full head over there wow
wow
you mean a full head of feathers right
easy mistake to make
cara
hello cara
it's close enough
that's so sweet thanks for the update
thank you no sweet to hear that and yeah
i guess you know raising
raising a family i'll definitely
expensive
i wish you all the best
yeah greetings
from all of kfb thank you for stopping
around and raising your
son
with
my very very educating
content
[Laughter]
for the pinky
can you be
[Music]
no worries
thank you thank you for the pink super
chat and popcorn yeah i'm excited
it's i would say
all thanks to a certain pong
who kept on pressuring the convention
telling them i wanted to be in in their
convention and then they also got bales
on board
yo can't be so strong
i'm glad i'm really glad
looking forward to it i hope i hope i
can
it was a boat oh yeah i think you guys
told me something like that
but you know someone has to start it
um
we voted for you tantra man yeah
thank you
i'm so honored you know navi mama also
told me
uh you know that i have to be careful in
korea because i'm so popular in korea
and i'm like it
like it's like are you for real like
what
can't be that
much
[Music]
but
i'm flattered what
yeah
no way
[Music]
i'm not a superstar in korea no
no way i don't believe it no
no i mean yeah
even like the whole cafe thing seeing so
many people lining up for the cafe is
shocking to me
because i guess like a lot of the korean
fans watch um clips mostly
so
i mean i still have a lot of them in the
live chat but it's like they're not as
apparent as
they actually are
yeah
so there's way more than you think there
are
um they also have like you know
different media they don't really use
twitter they're like chilling on naver
so
we don't really hear much from them
try to summon them
[Music]
where am i korean bros they're sleeping
they're probably sleeping but some of
them are here some of them
some
hello
3 a.m
i want to uh next week i wanted to do
another duolingo korean stream
oh yeah ah now i remembered
right i forgot that i wanted to do that
and then yesterday i was planning out my
schedule for next week
and i needed one short stream and i
couldn't figure out what to do now i
figured it out it should be duolingo
all right let me put that in
link go
oh
duolingo that works yeah
nice it's a good time too because i
wanted it to be early in the day because
like later
next week i have two days where in the
evening time i have some crunchyroll
stuff
so i can't stream in the evening
and if i stream something before that it
should be something short that's so that
i also am available for like preparation
later
so it needs to be something short
and now i guess that's perfect
[Music]
okay so next week duolingo korean
i know it's not the best but it's
basically the only
language learning
application that we have permission for
so i don't really have any choice if we
want to learn something we have to use
duolingo
well last time i checked it you know it
was all right it was all right
scheduled today dropping yeah i could be
i'm pretty
done with it i think
oh
it's a squiggly mustache oh dear
thanks for the pinky
log free three weeks since i infiltrated
kfp fiery chicken boss found out i'm a
taco and ordered her chicken to rip me
apart
my disguise was holding up poor gym was
a good sacrifice for my survival must
stay alive for mamaena
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
i don't like the fact that you're
narrating this storyline
i should be the one narrating it if
you're not rating it you could be like a
dungeon master and say hahaha i took
over kfp funny
it's my my place now my store now my
restaurant now no no no no i say
froze dice
oh
haha we found you
we found you and we're ripping you apart
and we're making fried chicken out of
you
a fried taco sorry
huh
oh that was so easy
and i will let mama ina go
no no no no no no we're just taking care
of this one rebellious taco who thinks
he's smarter than me
oh no no no no no
i am under control you should know that
by now
maftin eight thank you dark attack thank
you for the red super chat thank you
thanks for always putting in the hard
work to keep kfb motivated educated and
entertained please remember that we're
all proud of you and happy for you
[Music]
the director's cut of your concert was
as polished as promised glory to phoenix
over lady takanashi
thank you so sweet
i guess i am keeping you guys educated
yeah i teach you guys about idol stuff
i love music and
some stuff like oh yeah my my tutor's
obsession actually today before the
stream i watched a movie because you
know i felt like
so empty so i was like what can i do i
guess i'll watch a movie
and i watched a movie about um it was in
the 1400s um about um
a queen
of the north
uh uh what is it what was it
margaret
um
the movie is called margaret the queen
of the queen of the north yeah uh who
was queen of
uh
sweden norway and denmark
no we're not talking game of thrones i
know it sounds like it but no no no it's
it's a about an actual happening but
not much is known about it
they burned all the documents so it's
kind of a mystery but
the movie was actually pretty good
yeah the all the actors were like danish
and swedish and
so on so
yeah
uh
and all the like the soundtracks were
made by
scandinavian people
[Music]
um
everything was created
by
europeans scandinavians and that's
pretty cool like for that i would say
the quality was pretty good hmm
yeah and it was interesting to learn
about that because
it's close to the tutor's
timeline
a little bit before that
a couple centuries before
like 100 years or so before
yeah
yeah yeah um interesting actually kind
of shocking uh
but
yeah
you guys should look into it
i don't want to spoil too much but
there's you know there's this queen you
know norway sweden and denmark back in
the day
they had like you know
they are ongoing wars all the time and
then there was this one queen who
uh got them all together into one union
and that was incredible like that was
the first time in history that these
countries finally were at peace
um and she kept them at peace for quite
a while but then there was an issue with
her son
like she had a son but was like killed
or she fought it he was killed and then
after like 15 years or so he
he comes back uh but she already adopted
a different son to take over
eventually
um and he comes at a very he shows up at
a very very
difficult time where they're trying to
make a union between them and england
marry the sun to england
england princess
blue
and then they're like oh are you are you
really my son like she's not sure
um
she doesn't want it to be true
blah blah blah we don't know if he
really was the son he was in the end
burned alive
uh
and the documents of the whole
you know court case were burnt with him
so no it's violence
so we don't really know
if uh it was really him
um you would think that in the end the
queen had
the
um like she knew it in the end if it was
him or not but even if it was him like
in the in the movie the consensus what
that was that it was really her son but
she burned him anyway because
she did it for the country you will
understand if you well i spoiled you so
much so
i'm sorry but you will understand if you
um
watch the movie
yeah yeah normal family stuff yeah
totally yeah i was shocked though
proceeds to explain the whole plot you
didn't stop me
try to stop me harder
you in the chat you can't do much you
have no power over me
[Music]
ah it's kind of [\h__\h] up if it really
was like that that's hella [\h__\h] up i
mean i understand her decision i guess
because because can i explain further
the thing is that
the adopted son
was lacked by
all the countries but the real supposed
real son
um for some reason
uh i guess because of his heritage was
only supported by one of the countries
and if she would have taken him back
then the whole unit union would have
been destroyed and there would be war
again no more peace and she didn't want
that so in the end she was kind of
forced
to even though she fought that was
actually her son after all who came back
after being held captive by the germans
for 15 years and tortured
and she finally fought oh yeah he's back
and he wanted to run away with him but
then she realized oh [\h__\h] the germans
are coming i need to protect my union
my adopted son can do it alone and then
she's like oh [\h__\h] it's [\h__\h] and then
she watches
her son being burnt
alive
next to her adopted son
and she did it for the union
yeah
and then you know actually something
good came out of it because peace
continued for quite a long time
i spoiled the enemy i did
yeah uh sweden left the union first
after
a while but
uh denmark and norway stayed together
for
a long time for like 300 years until the
1800s which is really cool and that's
why they have a special connection
yeah that's why the scandinavian
countries in general have a special
connection and that's something i didn't
know and that's fascinating to me
fascinating now i want to know more
about the history of scandinavian
countries
denmark and norway sitting in the trees
hmm
[Music]
interesting right
no real story time
i'm really i am into them history i
don't know every country's history okay
so shut up but i know other things that
you guys may not know okay
you know things i don't know i know
things you don't know
[Music]
i'm sure there's also things you don't
know that you would feel stupid about
when you were told about it
yeah
there's a [\h__\h] ton of people in japan
who are told about mozart and they
didn't know who he was
and i thought oh mozart everybody should
know mozart
so don't even get me started
food signs
then there's a lot of
support there's a lot of history in this
world we cannot know everything
okay and i'm trying okay maybe maybe i
was taught before and i forgot okay
don't judge me for not knowing something
you do if you feel so smart don't you
feeling so smart huh
you don't know everything even
do you know [\h__\h]
no you don't
[Music]
anyway
so continuing
a gym thank you for the pinky
[Music]
i'm
i'm going to take your weight chat
being a little [\h__\h]
you go look in the corner
look into the corner
reflect on your words and actions
you can never be smarter than kiwawa
your boss okay
[Music]
yeah of course i'm blaming the whole
class
this is what you do as a teacher
enjoying the corner huh huh
you like it you like it down there
and now you know what it feels like
being called bottom left
didn't feel good
[Music]
it's very angled
okay i'll i'll continue now
so jim said oh jim i'm alive squiggly
mustache you little [\h__\h] i faked my dad
to drop your card and it's time to send
you back to the void
oh
now the storyline is going where i like
it to go thank you jim
don question that sounds good
continue please continue
i know it's all for danke she can't be
that good thanks for the pinky i heard
you're really bad at impersonating cats
and you can't even make cute purring
sounds for 30 seconds straight is that
true
you know i can do that you know exactly
i can do that
[Music]
no i can do it
don't fall for it
what
[Music]
prove it i've heard so many times in my
streams
yeah but like
it's reverse i don't want to i don't
want you to control me i will not let
you control me right now right now i
need to be in control
these people in the chat they think they
have a hand over me
if that's how you say it
now you don't i'm in control i'm not
part of your system
nah
i'm gonna take your super chat at this
chat i'm gonna throw it to the ground
into the corner
stay there
not ever thank
very sweet thanks for the generosity
i want to give you a heads up i will
have huge expenses backing up and going
to have a hold of my pinkies oh okay
don't worry about it thank you
soon
thank you
thank you thank you thank you should try
um the normal super chats once
talk to me don't hide behind those
stickers
you can use words
maybe you're shy but
you should use your words so i can talk
to you thank you very much for the
support though
rest
i'm
currently not really interested in rest
yeah but yeah thanks for asking
christian crayon lancashire and pepsi
maxwell the first time
thanks for the pinky
oh thank you thank you
yeah i enjoyed my trip thank you
the director's cut was perfection the
original was already absolutely amazing
but you somehow made it even more
incredible i'm already on my ninth free
watch i will never stop re-watching it
you really are the best love you always
and forever
oh you know you will stop re-watching it
one day when i'll bring out a new
concert vod
then you can watch that forever and ever
and ever and ever and ever
more than 15 times now oh my god
you you will end up knowing the
choreography by heart yourself if you
keep on watching it
when i watch someone's choreography a
lot of times even without trying to
learn it i still kind of pick it up so i
think you will pick it up too
valkyrie
[Music]
oh i have to go work now i enjoyed
watching the fun broadcast thank you i
think yeah it was already like 6 00 am
for you
did you like change your sleeping
schedule you just sleep after work now
and then watch my stream
during the night and then go to work
i mean i guess it works if you need to
make it work somehow i guess that's that
that works yeah you bought it
wow
i think i saw you in the chat now too
yeah
[Music]
yeah i mean yeah you gotta do what you
gotta do if you wanna watch kiwawa
streams
at least you're getting sleep i hope
i hope
say another sleep schedule
no not silent oh you just change it up a
little bit it's still a sleep schedule
it's just scheduled at different times
[Laughter]
ah now let's just you know sleep at
different times
what what does that say
[Music]
i'm gonna sleep during the day okay so
he does seem to sleep during the day
smart
that's actually smart you know all my
korean fans should do that and my
japanese fans too
so that's all that's
on
[Music]
just do it like that
easy
learn from kiwa take control of your
life
i bring you guys back now but you better
be good
no teasing chihuahua
this is my happy place you can't tease
me
here again brandon duncan for the pinky
wait so the entire game is about the cat
that went inside and wants to go back
outside accurate
yeah
that actually is really accurate it's so
typical
i love that too
that is the whole big meaning
of the game
[Music]
9527.90.1
thank you soon for the red super chat
have a nice day thank you you too
thanks for the generous super chatter i
appreciate it hope you enjoyed the
stream
and
oh now we're done with strain
[Music]
we're done with straying
korean class
okay okay okay
where's the thump nail
what
i saved it in the wrong place again
why do i keep on doing that what
no where is it
i'm blind
okay i'll just download it from here
[Music]
yeah i watched the cover yeah from
amen navi mama
i was so surprised what the [\h__\h] i
didn't know that was happening oh my god
and there's a song that i really like
too
you are
[Music]
stream back in april
april she told me like she recorded it
like a year ago or so
because i dm'd her i was like what the
[\h__\h]
and she's like i recorded that like a
year ago
holy [\h__\h]
let me turn on the lights is super dark
in my room
oh
[Music]
yeah maybe she meant april last year
could be
i don't know why you gotta ask amit
jonker's just peeked into the room hi
donkey monkey
you're waiting for me
i'll be done soon
navi mama did tease it last year
i didn't know though i was so shocked oh
my god
it was really cute
it was so cute
[Music]
thank you for serving at a time when
there are a lot of koreans thanks for
the consideration yeah
yeah yeah you're welcome i am a person
who can cookie yomu
so
and when i whenever i do these kind of
streams also like snack box streams i
like to be considerate and do it at a
time that makes sense for the audience
you're welcome
yeah
thank you for watching
oh but this should be the time when you
should be sleeping right normally now
now that
you changed your sleep schedule for me
sorry
i keep on changing my stream time i'm
not like those streamers who always
stream at the same time slot i'm sorry
i know that would be like convenient to
always know oh she's she always streams
on that day during that time so
so she's gonna stream at that time again
today
but you know i like to mix it up so
so that a lot of people can watch
whenever
[Music]
it's always a mix
but it's a certain time window where you
can expect me to stream right so usually
i start at
i don't know 3 p.m my time and then
i don't go longer than midnight these
days
thank you
satisfied
k
f
p
[Music]
um
i hope you enjoy your trip ah thank you
i think i will enjoy it i'm already
super excited
i'm i'm not so excited about the flight
because i booked
once again economy
i just went for the cheapest fight i
could find because i wanted to save
money i don't know why i do this but i
just don't think it's worth it spending
five thousand dollars on a [\h__\h]
flight
i just
don't think it's worth it unless you
make
millions and millions and millions of
money
i just don't think it's worth it
no
um
for a couple hours yeah
yeah yeah yeah business
long distance business class is usually
like around five thousand
five thousand to six thousand
dollars
yeah and i i don't see the merit in it
like
just for 12 hours like what
if you're gonna sleep most of the time
anyway even if it's painful
i feel like i don't know
what i
want to consider if it's available is
like premium economy
for longer distance that's like
you know when a normal when a normal
flight is like 800 to 100
then the premium economy is usually like
to 2600 or so
so it's like in between
uh economy and business but
i already think that that's expensive
but
yeah kitty kitty that's something i
would consider
why spend all that on the flight when
you can spend just spend more on the
trip itself exactly like for me it's
like
the money
i would spend on the business class i
feel like makes more sense to spend on a
on a nice hotel
because in the hotel i feel like i spend
more time
and then in the
in i mean it depends what kind of trip
it is like if it's like a resort trip
like to the maldives then you spend a
lot of time in the hotel
so then you can spend a lot of money on
a good resort if it's a city trip then
it still doesn't really matter much
just get a cheap hotel i guess
because you're gonna spend a lot of time
in the city anyway
but yeah i think it makes more sense
to uh book a nice hotel
then a nice flight um
yeah even though i mean i wish i if it
was if it was a bit cheaper if business
was like three thousand not five
thousand
then maybe i would consider
maybe but even then
no no no
um
[Music]
yeah
i just don't think it's worth it
it doesn't have the right value
to try it once with experience yeah
you know what would be nice
whenever the gates open up and
uh whole life brings myth over to japan
i am hoping
that we get blessed with
business class or premium economy
please
please cover sam
i mean i feel like it should it should
be
doable
please
anyway i'll report back to you after
having a broken back uh because of
flying with economy
again and again and again
[Music]
oh i just buy right away i don't really
wait for prices to go down but i at
least with this trip
i would i like clicked the option
flexible dates and looked for something
cheaper
because it didn't really matter when i
would go for me
so continuing
thank
you
um
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat it
trying out all these foreign languages
yo
so educated well
thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
foreign
very cute
story manager that's me
i'm still so [\h__\h] though i wish i was
better i want to impress my korean fans
but
yeah it's um if it was back in the day
where i was still going to school or so
i would have more time but now i work
full-time so more than full-time
i want to learn more but i haven't given
up on it so
it's a it's a whole prog process
so please wait for me
um
they're easily impressed though i'm not
impressed myself so
i need to work harder need to improve at
least until popcorn i want to be able to
say a few things
i will learn some phrases
thinking thank you soon
stay on the ground i will try fighting
yeah
thank you you're doing great sajni thank
you assassin
[Music]
oh there's a long text in korean
uh
[Music]
so sweet thank you
they went to the cafe
the collaboration cafe and they enjoyed
the food
and they wish me lots of fun experiences
in korea
oh
i will do my best to enjoy it with navi
mama she's she's trying her best to like
um you know try to
make the things i want to do come true
so she's helping me
very sweet
i'm glad i have her on my side for this
yeah
yeah she's so sweet
i i hope she will like me when we meet
[Music]
thank you
very useful korean yeah yeah yeah i hope
plans to have a nice day in korea thank
you i'm sure it will be great oh
i'm excited to eat lots of yummy food
and and see the beautiful
scenery of
seoul and meet the nice people
and see the collaboration cafe
yeah maybe play some dress up
and wear a handbook maybe maybe
yeah
i don't know i need to do some more
research on what to do or just read what
you guys told me to do and i'll rely on
that probably yeah
yeah
i'm still still not sure about going to
that bath house though
[Laughter]
probably not
think about it i'm still thinking
[Music]
if nami invites me
no i wouldn't be too shy i don't want
navi to see me naked
no
no i can't
yo
yeah
hope you enjoyed it i think also a lot
of nabi mama fans were happy to see her
streaming again
yeah
thank you so much for
watching jiwon park also thank you for
the pink superchatto
thank you tencho for showing this big
interest in korea and korean also nabi
mama and kiwawa are
[Music]
that is correct yes
you are correct
yes
but at least at least the
thank you so much
thank you for your love and support
okay
we're done with that
and korean class super chat does okay
next though
mm-hmm
[Music]
next one is really not much because it
was from alice fiction
[Music]
special did you watch the stream guys
you need to watch the ball it's a short
one i probably most likely won't be
streaming tomorrow so if you miss me you
can watch the vlog yeah
um like i reminded her like a while ago
i think during the off me offline
meeting
and she didn't know what i was talking
about she was very confused she
completely forgot
uh yeah i reminded her once but i don't
know i don't want to pressure her so if
she wants to do it she can let me know
that's okay
which comes first mk batsu okayana
concert
[Music]
very surprised to see you in that stream
thank you i'm sure you will be so good
at it
good at what was it about the game
oh yeah oh yeah
but thank you thank you for the red
super chat and i mean i saw that she's a
v2 boy now too she has a vital model
it's also very very very hot
very sexy ah about the voice acting
maybe
oh i wonder if it's about that
ah she's so sweet thank you so much mwah
and looking for the top thank you
thank you
thank you everybody
and now i think there's only the super
chats from today
[Music]
and then i'll eat lasagna
i want to eat some lasagna why does
youtube keep on logging me out these
days what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
i forgot about that because it's not in
the list oh
[Music]
can i read them next time i will read
the ones from today now but can i read
the united ones next time because like
the ones from today i want to read
because some
some super chatter
super chatted thinking that i will read
it today so
okay
and
[Music]
italian
thank you for the rest of the chat thank
i love how hard-working and dedicated
you are love how thoughtful and
considerate you are love how creative
and funny you are i love how dorky and
goofy you are
i'm not talking goofy
i appreciate you and everything you do
maybe i'm overly emotional
ow right now but i need to say it more
kiara i love you
i love you too
you're so sweet
ah emotional
no i hope you feel better now i mean
being emotional it's not necessarily a
negative state of feeling but
i'm guessing you were a little bit sad
because of sanyanya
yeah i hope you feel better now kiwawa
is here to make you feel better
all is good
in the arms of kiwawa
love kiwawa yeah
thank you
for the sweet sweet caring
flattering words
for the pink super chat consider this to
be an extra big tight hug oh
i love you yeah you're the best oshie
someone could ask for thank you i'm glad
you think so oh everybody is so clingy
oh
so clingy yet so cheeky these chickens
be careful be careful chickens
the cattle
yeah
we only have one kiwa
protect protect kiwawa
thank you navida mitti
and very fluffy hug
sarah rob thank you for the pinkie and
potential evansell wants to tell you
that he loves you very very much i know
so much so that he hides his all she
loves but soon that he acts yeah he does
but you deserve to know the truth so
here i am to be his courage you're his
oshie and he couldn't have another
i know
that's
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
i know his true feelings
it's okay
you can't hide it well
yeah it's too obvious um
it's okay no need to hide it be honest
to yourself
be true to your feelings
what same
if you received a super chat you okay if
we spy once and was caught by mummy
sorry i'm being held here i'll never
spying anymore if i could go back i'd
like to draw for the kfp
translate i always love you no [\h__\h]
way that definitely means something else
i don't trust you
let me translate that by myself
[Music]
actually i'm secretly on vacation with
new maze fans what
what
i mean that's kind of tt but why are you
lying to me
it's trying to make an excuse why he
can't go to work and he's trying to hide
the fact that he's on vacation
and now the excuse is that he's being
held
captured
no way
you know what happens with liars
their pants will be on fire
set them on fire guys
set this lying chicken on fire
well enjoy the vacation sounds titty
thank you
berserk night dead or alive duncan
thank you now you see bubble bubble more
often these days sergey silai thank you
for the pinky kiki look at meat until
now i am a crunchy juicy bucket ready to
serve and be served and one time become
a small phoenix yay
like a hybrid phoenix yeah
thank you for making our lives brighter
and being the core of such a wonderful
community as kfb lady kiwawa you're
welcome
oh bucket
oh you look so yummy give me a taste
give me a bite
thank you for your support please
continue supporting
phoenix forum coming soon
[Music]
reports from the mines of northern chile
we had snow we had dust
we also had summer like heat
oh i'm doing good right now i signed an
indefinite contract with my employee but
the one the one with kibawa is also
forever ps your new hair 10 out of 10.
ah thank you
i know this hair is good isn't it it's
cute
i love braids yeah
[Music]
but yeah be careful in the mine
snow sounds fun though especially right
now where it's [\h__\h] hot here
[\h__\h] summer
well then
one day i'll either get ac or i'll move
to a country where it's called colder
thank you very much or i move to where
it's hot but also like right at the
beach that would be nice
i want to live
a vacation
that's just my dreams though um
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
and i really appreciate appreciate her
efforts
not only towards me
but towards everybody's success and i
respect her i'll just kind of repeat
what i said i respect her
as a
as a colleague as a friend and as a fan
but
um
yeah it's not like i really want to
marry her or whatever
he's just regret so closer because she
actually tries to help me and she
worries about me
and she's just there for me more than
anybody else
in the past couple
weeks months
and that's just you know i really feel
that and i appreciate that
i'm someone who
when i am
have a friend that i really appreciate i
show it very
[Music]
openly and very enthusiastically
yeah
and when i say i love you to someone it
doesn't mean like i want to have um
sexual intercourse with you
it means i really appreciate you being
there for me
as a friend
okay
it's like really no need to think too
much into it i just i just really also
you know i feel like amen deserves that
um
appreciation
i want her to know she's appreciated so
i like to make it very clear
okay
hi
[Music]
my
oh
[Music]
uh explained
the
what happened
i guess
why why like the question was basically
how i
became so close with ame
that it
turned into uh you know us being
apparently married according to amen
um
so so social yes yes okay okay okay
[Music]
almost married to all of myth
god damn it
she did sing a song about you in twitter
space what
when
what kind of song
yeah yeah yeah just being openly
appreciative i think there's no problem
with that
[Music]
you asked me
doesn't know exists
huh
when
[Music]
what
but didn't she sing
gura does no eggs or did gooda sing army
doesn't know exist or the other way
around
two weeks ago
[Music]
oh my god
what
[Music]
i'll have to look into that
okay uh
mk23 thanks for the rest of the chat you
know what you are right jumping to that
hot bubbly pool did help me get a tan
way faster than any studio
and what do you think tencho how did i
look anyway it was uh wait it was a 10
10 of the 10 to experience and i can
only recommend everyone to do the same
you look
so beautiful you know that tan
from the fryer it really brings out the
color in your eyes
and the color of your blood
it's just all
glowing absolutely glowing
beautiful beautiful
congratulations
gives texture yeah it gives you this
this beautiful skin texture too
yeah
i like it it makes me want to touch you
thank you so much for being a member for
so long
[Music]
i'll do another member stream
the week after next one the week after
the coming one so you know one week in
between
[Music]
thanks for supporting me
thank you oh thank you
i'll check it out
uh
yeah yeah yeah
if it doesn't uh
get drowned by my other twitter replies
[Music]
in my dream i saw attention
and i worked in kfb
no that's reality that's not that's not
a dream
no no no no
i think this is usual room usual room is
not bad no
no
no that's just normal every day no
you're confusing some things
no it's saying korean kfb stuff will go
to bed now
how how i did not give you permission
but okay i want you to be healthy so go
but that was not a dream that was
reality
maybe you're thinking reality is the
dream
[Music]
confused little chicky oh no
thank you for coming by see you again
soon i hope
nikon
comes
thanks for two pinkies comes on nida
after the poop story the food story
tantra doesn't care if he offers summer
vacation and bonuses to employees
what a night eve living chicken
you really think i would offer summer
vacation and bonuses to it please huh
i offer summer vacation and bonuses to
myself
that are provided by you thank you very
much kfp
i love you
even when i'm on vacation bonus is super
chat exactly
yeah yeah yeah you can go on vacation
but then wherever you're going you have
to work at that branch
in that place the kfb branch in that
place
how about that deal
deal
mwah ball
rappel thanks for the red super chat
attention kim i was over the weekend in
netherlands now i'm on my way back home
i definitely miss you and kfb can't wait
to be back home and listen to your
italian experience mamma mia i'm excited
my phone has low batteries so take this
tube and see in the stream thank you
that sounds fun
i want to visit the netherlands too
i hope you had a great time and had a
good offline time
yeah enjoyed some
offline time some touching grass time
touching buildings time
yeah thanks for remembering me not
forgetting about me from fro nice to
have you back even though your phone is
dead now
i'll see you soon
skipping the sneak shots thanks
[Music]
oh it's nice to have someone
representing europeans and whole life
glad you were able to enjoy my country
denzel maybe next time try sardinia if
you want to see clear waters like in the
maldives i will
i didn't realize italy had such a
beautiful
beach too but i guess this is like a
smaller island smaller islands always
have like moist beaches don't they
yeah
thank you thanks for watching my streams
from italy
allen iverson thank you soon
and the gaming crew thank you
spanking helen thanks for the word super
chat sorry the convention didn't work
out look glad you had fun on your trip
but the kids were glad to have you back
oh yeah definitely
yeah
um i missed them a lot too
but yeah
the convention it was really unfortunate
because that was the original reason we
went or we wanted to go
but
in in hindsight as i said i think it was
actually better this way
yeah
because um
i don't really feel so s like
[Music]
it's just not the same anymore as it
used to be going to conventions
i i get very like nervous and paranoid
so
i always feel like watched and
um
like i always need to be careful and all
that
it's just i don't feel so free anymore
so in hindsight it's probably better
this way
yeah yeah yeah yeah
um
yeah
it's okay i mean i've had my fair share
of conventions before whole alive
and now i get to enjoy a different side
of conventions you know being there as a
guest
like a special guest like a performing
and that's really cool too i i do miss
going there like as a normal person
with my friends and enjoying it normally
where not everybody knows me
i mean even before like people in the
community knew me you know but um
yeah that was kind of different so i
it's nice to be able to see both sides
and who knows maybe one day i can go
back to being a normal convention
visitor with when i'm like 40.
when i'm like 40 i'll go to conventions
again and no one give will give a [\h__\h]
about me right
we'll see if i still even am interested
in it at that point
[Music]
23 years
yeah exactly because i'm 17 now
um
especially them did they give you a kiss
manchester general is done
[Music]
very kind of you to think of my
director's cut thank you
hmm did you see did you see all the all
the differences all the changes i wonder
if you noticed
i totally get that if you only watched
the original once and then the
director's cut once that
on the first
watch you don't notice much of it but
yeah
okay
why am i possibly reading it in
german oh
say
six
seven it sounds so similar see been
seven
[Music]
eight
nine
donkey
point
yeah a lot of things that you will miss
if you don't watch it side by side yeah
we're just fine like i'm not asking you
guys to watch it side by side
unless you're really curious about what
changed
what is this i'm curious what this
superchat says make poetical me
i love kumi
oh i watch kiara's broadcast today i
feel happy to be with this fun youtuber
kiara i hope you have a fruitful day
while enjoying delicious chicken thank
you for working hard on the show today
feet
chicken
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for watching hope to see you
again soon
i'll eat lasagna afterwards though
probably
wiki tunes thanks for the pinky
i don't get excited over celebrities but
i fangirled so hard when you liked my
art collab it was a huge honor boss also
i'll be moving back east to the us
oh
you mean from way from where from
from the uh
from pst to est or what
they'll be around more robson again i
didn't get to say it before but happy
birthday
i'm happy if you come more often again
and also yeah that was really cool it
looks amazing
texas for five years ah
okay
welcome back to the east coast soon yay
yeah east coast is probably a little bit
easier to catch my streams
oh
thank you so much
thank you
for continuing to support me
even when it's hard to watch me
thank you
beast coast
really
thank you
[Music]
a month ago i was still a waitress i was
happy i quit but today that changed
[Music]
and i understand why you why you're
saying you're happy you quit like a
normal waitress job but
why did it change
oh my attention is an emergency i wanted
to listen to your hits on sparks
comrades on 500k on spotify and they've
found there's some old lady who's
credited to the sakana in their slow
shook honestly that doesn't sound like
it's a year ago that sounds like it was
yesterday
huh
oh because i'm into waitresses cause i
flirt
oh i didn't flirt with specifically her
because she's a waitress i didn't flirt
with her at all i was just trying to
flex my italian and i was happy because
she was laughing in it
doesn't mean i'm flirting
anyway yeah slowpoke
that doesn't sound so old
that's like i feel like i just released
sparks like a month ago
what the [\h__\h]
seconds
a little info i learned airlines
apparently make a loss on all economy
tickets they rely on business in first
class to cover the difference and the
economy to fill up the empty plane with
people
what
really
i feel like they would make enough money
but maybe you know the the fees for like
landing space and
and maintenance and all that i guess
could be very expensive yeah well
i don't care you're not gonna guilty
trip me into taking business class
hello it shouldn't be that expensive
reason why budget airline is so keen on
all the little extra
not a whole dog
well again you're not going to guilty
trip me
if you want to be a budget airline
you're going to have to deal with budget
people
i'm not part of your system
eh
screw business class hell yeah
they think they're cool
sitting in there really comfortable
seats that turn into beds
[\h__\h] you
i deserve good sleep too
i deserve a healthy bath too
[Music]
i am budget people
bathroom bags overrated no
i need healthy back
budget backsmith
i'm good with getting seats of extra leg
room oh
yeah i don't need those
but
i want more reclining
and i like to have a window seat so i
can lean my head on it because if i
don't have anything to lean my head on
when i fall asleep i constantly like
fall to the front i never fall asleep
never i need to lean my head sideways i
don't know how people do it how do
people sleep without leaning their head
on something
that's why i wish you know when i travel
that i wouldn't travel alone all the
time because then even if i don't have a
window seat i at least can lean my head
on the person's shoulder next to me
same same
practice like i use those those neck
pillows and they don't really help me
either
[Music]
on some planes you can fold the sides
yeah i tried that too it helps a little
bit but still not quite
it needs to be a bit bigger but i'm very
happy very grateful for planes who have
that in economy
the size that you can fold that actually
is a nice feature
say something to union
huh
oh wait is it was it
or something
[Music]
i forgot i didn't remember most of the
things now my mama told me but i
remember juggling
um
[Music]
yes
that's why i jumped into the fryer girl
yeah thank you anybody
don't don't don't
okay
let me refresh one time
the kotori emote is just so good
the threatening aura
too good
high attention seems like you'll be busy
in others of cr expo your trip and
whatever you girls have to do for the
second anniversary coming up i'll put
that's in september
just wanted to say good luck thank you
thank you
yeah i mean i think
see our expo
currently
it's just fine now i have to record some
things for it but
now it's fine
just getting the coming weekend behind
me and even that it's not going to take
up that much time so it's alright
but
yeah the korea trip also
i mean i'm i'm definitely gonna try to
stream on some of the days in my hotel
room so you guys won't be completely
alone
i have plans for going to korea in
august i hope tantra merchandise is
still available during my time oh
i mean i saw someone tweeting at me
today
that they went today and they got
merchandise from me so i'm sure you'll
get something
you may have to go early though
[Music]
yeah and i hope that the things that ran
out of stock i hope that maybe they'll
get some restock um
yeah
but i hope you find something
enjoy
enjoy your trip to korea
yeah they'll still still have some stuff
definitely
[Music]
the duck points from my oh my gosh
stairs okay so whatever
[Music]
thank you very much
who knows maybe we'll meet in korea
you'll see a phoenix walking down the
street and you'll be thinking damn she
cute
that's my boss let's go
okay everybody i'll see you the day
after tomorrow i'll go have a lasagna
now and then i guess i'll make my
schedule for you guys because you guys
go crazy if i don't make my schedule
so yeah just wait i need to eat first
lasagna takes a while in the oven if i
feel like it maybe i'll do it while i'm
waiting
no
and then you'll see the new art for
august i was
my fingers were getting tingly because i
wanted to show you guys the next art
[Music]
i did ask this time
uh a korean artist i was looking through
kiwala fan art hashtag
uh i was looking for korean artists and
looking and looking and looking and
looking and looking now find one i found
one and uh yeah because you know i
thought oh i'm going to korea maybe i
should ask a korean artist
to draw something
it's not someone like super super well
known but i just found
him in my fan arts and i thought oh the
art is good
yeah
[Music]
there you go
yeah yeah yeah a lot of good korean
artists using the hashtag i wonder if
some of them cause like they don't
usually use twitter i wonder if some of
them upload somewhere else and i don't
know about it
maybe i don't know about it
they upload it on neighbor do people
korean friends do people upload fan art
on on nava
where do korean artists usually upload
their fan art
[Music]
maybe pixip yeah
i mean if they draw
like
hololive fan art i would assume that
they make a twitter account
for the sake of
getting them to see it
hmm
yeah artist i can see that artist would
use twitter
because a lot of other artists use
twitter so for the sake of connecting
and all that
fix it and fix it oh if any of you guys
hang out on pixiv because i don't really
look on pixiv and you see a fan art
that's not in my hashtag because they're
not on twitter show me
if it's something good
show me
[Music]
um okay now i go eat
please have a nice evening a nice night
everybody
see you on tuesday
thank you love you guys hope you liked
the story of my trip to italy
[Music]
good night
um
bye
meow meow meow
[Music]
do
oh wait
i forgot to say it
oh oh oh sorry i was like
just already looking at um
mentions on my work discord
[Laughter]
um
but you know you know it already every
time i say in germany we say something
else you always say afrida sin don't act
like you don't know it but okay
it's for for completion's sake
sorry i noticed you though
[Music]
i always notice you're dreaming
do
[Music]
you