man I
yeah
uh you're now listening to FAA FM this
ain't your granny's radio
station I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get
ready to jam out let's go
[Music]
power 1 2 3 go there is sp with flow
you're Holo promise I'm famous heo I am
a big shot look on TV gaming Idol here
in that's me bucket we ball never punish
never greedy no I'd win
Unstoppable T dance back back back it
[Music]
up K Grand
K hello hello welcome welcome it's day
two of an Rec
go and we are back and I have big plans
today just you
wait so today is the day we say goodbye
quests goodbye main quest hello my new
life as an
NPC that's the plan I want to open up my
own
shop well I was I was thinking I was
brainstorming on what to do because I
really wanted to live my my NPC life and
so I was thinking what I can do the
things I can sell well there might be
more what I know right now is I'm going
to build a shop I think you can build
some places I'm going to build a shop
I'm going to farm for coins I'm going to
buy a bunch of loot boxes and get a
bunch of stuff and then I'm going to
sell it above market value but at lower
quantities than you can buy in the or
you can get in the loot box so that way
if people want let's say they only need
10 Cherry logs they can buy from me
instead of having to spend 300 coins on
the loot box and get
64 that's that's the plan and I'm I'm so
ready for this that I have
already prepared
that's right
faart is in
business except except not not yet not
quite
yet but we've got the we've got the logo
already we're going to have this in the
corner so that well I don't know if I
should have it yet I'm going to have it
even though the Shop's not open we've
got some time I think I'm the only one
on the server right now we've got some
time before anyone else logs in exactly
this is the Scarlet wand creativity and
genius at work exactly what I'm saying
wait this would be quite cinematic hold
on no the sun is rising don't rise yet
this would be getting the the moon
setting on this would be would be a nice
cinematic shot for a new
thumbnail
okay um
do you guys
know where you we're allowed to build
wait do we have a map like a like a a
PDF
map is this a thing nope in the
construction yard next to the
Garden but where's the
garden is this the GU no that's not the
garden the garden has a
small
child this is the castle I mean I should
get acquainted there's even a
moat why would you know if I don't know
I don't know I'm just assuming that you
guys watched like all 19 povs start to
finish so you
know all of the information that
everyone has aass
together um
this is like the this is our area the
library hold on the music's already
annoying
me but this one doesn't fit the Antics
I'm
about is it too I feel like it's not too
loud
but youa grinded out the side quest I
might have to do that too to make
money wait is this the garden this looks
like a park
um do I have to look at the
map oh that's a
wall southeast part of the city which
way is
North which way is North wait do I even
have a
map it's literally right
here wait
[Music]
Southeast like this way
look at the sun can you scroll out
no not in not in this
map oh
here e this does look like a place you
could build or can we only build in the
red
area oh somebody's already
started over here
okay I don't know how it works cuz can
we like craft stuff
this is what I'm what I'm worried
[Music]
about um well there is a crafting table
there yes talk to nearby NPC to get free
money free
money I need some some Venture Capital
to start up my new business see this PL
of land you can build whatever you like
here just remember this is the only
place you can place a break blocks as
you
please hey he does doesn't have any free
money for
me can I can
I oh they have Protections in place you
can't steal well that'll be good nobody
can steal from from fa
Mar there's a quest for
him okay let's go back to the quest
board
[Music]
then which is uh
somewhere right here right here right
here I'm I'm
[Music]
learning Help Wanted at the tavern I
mean I do I would like to be a barain
are they all the same oops oops oops
oops oh wait there's multiple never mind
they're all the same I see empty love
where you can yes yes let me letting me
build
freely also you're in like cinematic
mode today before I had the stream
zoomed in the video zoomed in but then
it was cutting off my amount of money or
the dialogue so we've got the Cinematic
black bars
today
sorry you must have come here from the
quest board yes this is the only place
okay yes can build a house a stor or
whatever else sits are fancy as long as
you don't go out of bounds each Guild
has an assigned plot and you can only
build insign the one that belongs to
your
guild 100 coins and some materials oh
okay okay okay this is good I don't know
the best way to get money we could
speedrun all of the side
quests oh Theo's here hello welcome
welcome
um um you might be seeing well I can let
you in because we're all Scarlet wand
together this is the new business
venture of the Scarlet
wand
faart I will be opening up my own
shop and selling things at above market
value to make a profit
this is this is the the creativity and
Genius
of of the Scarlet
wand where can you invest I have another
trick of my sleep but I don't know if
I'm R into reveal it yet shared profit
we'll see we'll see maybe maybe for the
guild maybe maybe 10% can go to the
guild you
know Guild discount yes maybe that's
more likely how about a 10% discount for
anybody in the Scarlet wand
Guild gambling did someone say
[Music]
gambling okay should I should I unveil
it already my my master plan
but we haven't even built the
infrastructure
yet no no
gambling
okay I'll tell you this will be come
into play when people join the server
more faom Mart is not just a place where
you can buy whatever you need you know
food building materials whatever you
know what else a convenience store
usually
sells a lottery
ticket faart will be operating a daily
lottery uh you may purchase a ticket for
10 gold each and you can buy as many as
you
want and every day at 5:00 p.m. Pacific
time I will draw not starting tomorrow
not today starting tomorrow at 5:00 p.m.
Pacific time time I will be drawing the
winning
numbers who will get the big
jackpot so these will be available for
purchase for anybody who would like a
chance to win in the fart
Lottery and uh you can read read the
bottom if you want but it's not
important what's important is that there
will be big jackpots and big
wins so we've got this available for
purchase for anybody who is
interested and I'm I'm planning I'm
planning a marketing and advertising
campaign for this and everything
so I feel like it's in the way no matter
where I put it
[Music]
all right who's the mascot I don't know
we haven't gotten that far yet right now
I'm the only employee and we also have
got we've got some scrolling text it's
getting crazy out here
already lotto tickets 10 gold
each too much text on the screen H right
now the jackpot is zero gold but you
know we'll we'll see if people buy some
buy some some
tickets I should make it
5050 I'm afraid no one's going to buy my
lottery if the if the odds are too
bad I mean already with three numbers
it's like a 1 in 700 chance that you'll
win right
they will they will because we're
already oh no you guys you guys can't
buy the lottery tickets no only in-game
money saplings are not allowed to play
the lottery I don't want you to get
scammed not that it's not that it's a
scam or
anything I'm prepared to start a a phone
campaign where I'm going to be dialing
people up and letting them know about
about their chances in the new Lottery
that we're going to be running daily
that's right daily even if I'm not
streaming I'm going to log in at 5:00
p.m. Pacific time to pull lottery
numbers I will at least be doing that
also members if you're listening and you
would like to purchase a ticket you may
come meet me in game we can also arrange
over Discord if you would like to
purchase and we're not on the and online
at the same
time is also an option
okay but we we need to we need to build
our shop cuz right now we're just
operating out of a
field I don't know what it should look
like I mean the obvious answer is comy
but I feel like it might be
cuter and maybe I should build it over
here
like the prime real estate closer to the
main road right in this
[Music]
corner what did what did gooa
say you have a business proposition I'm
listening I'm
listening location location location
don't forget parking spots for the
horses that's a good
one okay
um I guess I will open up my loot box
see this is what I'm thinking you know
how these cost like 300 a piece if I
just get a bunch of different stuff if I
grind then people can buy lesser amounts
from me if they don't want a whole stack
and it's too hard to get
$300 three validate
parking
yes all right what should we get what
should we build this out of I like
Spruce but I already bought this Cherry
stuff I think Spruce is
good spru we could do spruce and Cherry
Cherry would be nice can we but it's
going to be very
pink right a spruce with cherry accents
[Music]
maybe can we craft
also we can make a crafting
table we can break stuff here wait can
we craft i'm we can craft okay okay okay
I was scared that we couldn't craft
anything we can have signs okay that's
very good we can have signs we can make
stairs we're so we're so
back we can craft weapons too don't let
the other shopkeeper know
because they're going to they're going
to realize they don't have the the
market anymore can we do this we can
okay well we might have some like humble
beginnings I think it would be good to
leave some room I used to know how to
build fantasy buildings in
Minecraft you can craft tools I do want
trees can we dig
down what's this oh what if I fall out
of the world
we can dig down smooth
sandstone
a okay we can we can dig
down the real fit we have to see if a
wants to buy
a a lottery
ticket you Sandstone as a material
that's possible we can also get Oak for
free we can buy three
boxes call her is she
streaming I'm scared to like call people
who aren't streaming because what if
they're just they're they're just
setting up for their stream and they're
just logging in to take a screenshot
because that's what I was doing earlier
[Music]
I'll I'll ask them when they when they
come
online yeah we need to we need to make
the shop
first
oh there she is there she goes into the
distance what's going on we're making a
store and we're operating a lottery
tickets are all on sale not for not for
saplings only
for Ian Reco members we should make a
big sign I do want a big like faom Mar
sign wait we should build on a diagonal
that always looks really good that's
like way too
ambitious I feel like I need to look at
pictures to get
inspiration we should make a big
billboard we
should my craft fancy house let's just
look
on the internet and copy
one oh man wait these are like really
cute I don't know if I can do these wait
this one is so
cute wait this one is so
cute I don't have enough stuff wait can
we get like coal
gosh this is weird it's weird like
playing Minecraft but like I don't know
[Music]
anything
maybe but I don't there's coal in the
Overworld oh so maybe I don't have to do
this what is Minecraft you're right what
is
Minecraft so theoretically we can get
like stone
bricks we can make
charcoal yeah I did have amnesia it's
true maybe I should go get a bunch of
cobblestone Coal's infinite outside okay
maybe you're right maybe we shouldn't
waste our stuff let's go
explore outside suddenly there's like so
much to do
after I have forsaken the side quests
and I have my new goal operating my
lottery
system suddenly there's so much so much
to do so much to see so what's wrong
with taking the back streets oh right
here you're
right I mean we could just mine this
forever okay okay we're so in right now
can we get IR
to make
[Music]
lanterns I was thinking a lot
yesterday about what I wanted to do
because well I've mentioned it before
it's like my dream to become a fantasy
NPC and now that's what I am what I can
be but I didn't know like what kind of
fantasy NPC like obviously shopkeeper I
think is a good one but I kind of wanted
to run a c casino but I wasn't sure how
to do
it but then I came to the conclusion the
lottery would would make sense and I
don't cuz then I was like oh can I make
any kind of like red stone casino slot
machine but I don't know if there's even
Redstone
here not this I don't want to kill you
no you're so cute I don't want to kill
you I forgot there are
enemies it's too sad at least we get
money
though look one of these is worth like
one lottery ticket oh they make the
sound of creepers when they
die what is redstone I don't know but I
don't know how to make a slot machine
without what set up the bug
walk yes
can you buy multiple lottery tickets you
can you
can if you buy too many the shopkeep
might get mad at you though because it's
hard to keep track of and like a real
Lottery you can't have duplicate
numbers you can pick your numbers or I
can just randomize it for
you and there can be duplicates
and in the event of duplicates the
jackpot will be
[Music]
split but I get 30% regardless
yes yes we need to have funds in order
to keep operating the
lottery the lottery doesn't work for
free you
know but keep in mind that it does
support
education as the Scarlet wand Guild we
are operating the local
library and the guild may even get
10% so support your your local library
by buying lottery
tickets oh
I'm
spying I'm being weird I don't know if
we
[Music]
can I might as well use this one I don't
know if we can craft out
here not these
ones these cute
ones they make the sound of creepers did
they do that just to troll
us cuz it's
working okay
ouch
definitely no please leave me alone I
don't want to fight I just want to use
up the last of
my wooden pickaxe so I can build my
store
this one's too
sad I feel like we might be the bad
guys when the stains are so
cute isn't there some way we can live in
peace and harmony with the
stains have we even bothered to ask them
what they need okay I'm going I'm going
[Music]
back why are they attacking us
is there something that they need that
they're not
getting I think I might buy
some well let's see you're my new
competition so what have you got for
sale we can do better than this for sure
oh maybe we should
[Music]
Farm
too not a bad idea egg wait can we get
chickens
not notom AR selling Fried
Chickens portable Lantern so
expensive is there a Cooking
System h a food farm is not a bad idea
we could sell we could sell bread at a
cheaper
price than this wait but can we even get
like water I don't know if we can even
get like
water can buy
coal but give me give me a surprise
box should I spend all my money on these
I feel like I'm going to need
them there's a bucket wait
where where's the
[Music]
bucket leave 300 I need a
hat I would like a
hat side quest to unlock stuff oh maybe
I need to do the do the side
quests okay I'll buy
three to start
[Music]
with okay that's good that's
fine this is just showing you right
can't have
it okay that's also
good I need
these
yes wait how do I put it
[Music]
on
yes stac Tite head new uniform
okay good good
good let's see what we've
got on the side
quest five iron
ingots craft some tools craft a backpack
enchant weapons slay 10
stains through the dungeon
again oh in Fri
stain this are we eating
them bone in fried
stain we're definitely the bad guys we
eat
them special stain
stew a wood shovel do you think I can
give him my
old wood
shovel wait I don't even have an old
wood
shovel hold on I don't know if you can
take multiple side quests at the same
time or
not um let's go craft over here cuz they
can't stop me that's not that's sorry
that's the wrong one I mean over
here and let's
start melting this
[Music]
this
two wait wait not all of it though
sorry you can't oh they thought of
everything okay never mind they thought
of
everything the Betrayal at least we can
craft signs though I was scared
no
cheating is it this
one a wooden shovel in this please thank
you wait who wants the quest
[Music]
Master is that back where we
started all the way back here I wonder
if you can repeat side quests CU I feel
like that is going to
be Oh wrong way the way to make
money wait is he just buy the quest
board
wait oh you're the quest
Master it's you plus 50
coins
easy does it change can you just like
farm this wait
but how much does it
cost a stone pickaxe an iron axe gold
sword accept them all can
[Music]
you uh looking for five iron
ingots five wa I have five stain hides
I feel like it I don't know if I should
accept them
all is it
you
oops is it you it's you plus
100 you want five iron ingots where do I
get iron ingots from are they out in the
world
mine iron and cook it you can mine
iron okay that's good that means we can
make lanterns and we could make a bucket
presumably and we could get
[Music]
water okay oh it's like right there is
that
iron do I know what Minecraft looks like
okay good now we just sit
here right I've forgotten all of my
memories I don't know what Minecraft
looks
like excuse
you excuse
you we need five iron ingots is he going
to take them from us did they take the
wooden shovel I guess so otherwise I
mean it's really tempting to just
like get
infinite tools and get infinite money
that
way are people still going to be
interested in my lottery if the economy
is completely
broken we could always raise the
price of lottery
tickets we need a bodyguard we
do the jackpot is zero gold it's only
zero gold right now now I mean I could
buy a
ticket maybe I should buy one and get it
started for
one for 10
gold
jackpot buy 100 I could buy 100 does
that make it seem more appealing
I got to start the
pot but then what if someone else
actually wins and then I spent 1,000
gold on
it
ouch I should have taken the Quest for
10 stains cuz I'm definitely going to do
that if I go far enough will I find
diamonds you know what let's just hey
hey hey hey hey hey let's just get out
of
[Music]
here rather win $100 than zero
well they're probably going to win zero
either way it's just it'll go up when
people buy tickets and I'm sure they
will I'm sure they will
you don't tell them that well nobody's
nobody's here right now it's just it's
just
us can I cook them in
here is a blast furnace that's a
smoker that's is that's a netherite
thing is a blast furnace a thing that's
a
smoker I guess just use a regular one
okay it is but not here can I steal
their
[Music]
water smoke
stains oh
no it makes
steak I guess we're still in steak steak
now I guess we're selling steak it
doesn't look so gray anymore after you
cook
[Music]
it
m a perfectly normal
steak
precisely okay here you
go plus
150 coins now we can get iron he did
take the
ingots so
greedy leaving none for
me new recipe
unlocked where's the where's the the
recipe I don't know oh right
[Music]
here do I have recipe steak
I have an Anil I should name the stakes
oh can I get
a oh I don't have enough hides for a
backpack is that also a
quest maybe I should take them all but
then I'm I'm definitely going to
[Music]
forget
okay I need some
storage a backpack
would hit the
spot yeah the back black Smith sells
iron
now five gold ingots five
diamonds moving house I thought this was
like a house Moving Castle
situation SCE some stains I mean we
should except except that one cuz I'm
going to do
that
dungeon potato
salad oh how do you make a bed fried
stain I only made a a
steak wood
shovel stone
pickaxe iron axe gold sword
did I get I got 100 coins I don't is
that worth
it took my
stuff me we definitely need some iron
tools
now I'm starting to learn my way around
town iron pickaxe please it cost
100 easy come easy go
bone the meat on in the meat
bone on the bone
meat that one's that one's put on the
doong and Roba F that's that's an OG
one I do love how everybody struggled
with that because I I did too I think it
did take me
[Music]
like it was like on the last try that I
got I tried every car combination before
I finally got the right one the bone on
meat on the meat
bone meat on the
[Music]
bone okay what are we doing
here what can we get from
the construction
[Music]
box um
we need to build our
shop you failed twice you fell dumb I
think I literally failed like 10 times
in that
one okay let's get some
chests
going to start
with just to organize my
stuff wait when did I get so much
bread is that a quest reward or did I
buy
that by accident oh you can't you can't
get rid of this
one
understood was a reward how am I
supposed to make a living selling bread
if they give it out for free like
that um oh yeah can I make a
bucket I can
can I get water
though now here's the
part I'm not sure
about I don't know if I can
[Music]
right I mean look they've got so much
water surely they can
can they can spare a little bit for me
okay this this changes everything does
it change everything we can have a farm
now stealing
water
okay
um begins we can sell water we
can okay I need to look at pictures of
Minecraft fantasy
houses
[Music]
um locally sourced
water oh I don't know how to make a cute
house though it's hard
[Music]
oops building in Minecraft is
hard definitely stone bricks look really
good
and are like relatively
cheap to
make I think we should
utilize stone
[Music]
bricks crops are free in the garden
stall next door wait really where crops
are free then how come they're selling
them
in the garden some are free they're
scamming they're just like
[Music]
me okay let's try to make something that
looks
[Music]
good
um I'm looking at a reference picture oh
gosh I'm looking look at a reference but
also this is this too much should
I maybe a smaller
one wait this one looks
cute I'm just going to copy this one am
I can I copy this one wait do they use
Sandstone I mean if they're using
sandstone
[Music]
and
like oh no we can only have this
much the other Scarlet wand members are
going to log on and realize I've mind
out one
layer of
sandstone beneath
there beneath our
plot I won't I won't
it's like worse
than than not filling in your creeper
holes okay what do we have again I
should I should like look
carefully white concrete
terracotta block of
Quartz bricks are
nice bricks are definitely
nice I should screenshot it
let's let's screenshot it this will be
important throw this in
there hi Windows hi Windows
[Music]
11 is there bamboo wood yet I mean I
definitely really want Cherry leaves do
you think we could get cherry trees from
Cherry
leaves cuz that could be a good business
venture I bet everybody would love to
get some cherry trees
right maybe we need to try
[Music]
it mud
bricks wait are mud bricks these cute
ones that I'm looking at in this
screenshot mud bricks
Minecraft oh wait they're cute are they
new how do you get
this wait do you make this one
dirt
um water bottle on dirt with the
mud mud and
wheat that doesn't make any sense to me
but okay
oh I'm going to I'm going to waste all
of my leaves trying to get a sapling you
can get saplings from breaking them
right look how it
moves I like the sound it makes I'm
scared no only natural leaves wait
really oh oh I'm wasting my
leaves
no not player
placed oh
no well give me give me more more
bricks at least we can get
these
easily is there a cherry tree in the
field I don't know I don't I know how it
works cuz we can't even really like
break things you
[Music]
know okay
let's let's build something
cute um I want stairs wait can we get to
how do you make a stone cutter wait you
need iron right
it's it's a better rate if you do this I
shouldn't be lazy I should go get the
iron hopefully I can I can make
it I just want to get my get my store up
and running before people log in
ouch cuz who's going to want to buy my
stuff if I'm just I don't even seem like
a reputable business you know
nobody's going to want to buy my
stuff yeah can you
get
saplings I guess I could explore the
world the world is my
oyster after
all you leave me
alone those are spruce trees over there
right it's
cool are they
regenerating or am I just destroying the
world am I just shaving this tree bald
why I'm getting saplings okay no it's
coming back it's coming
back
ouch okay hopefully I can grow these
[Music]
ouch ouch ouch ouch
he I guess I need to slay
[Music]
them maybe I should upgrade my
so this is taking a
while just a little off the
top yeah I don't know if I wonder if
there are is that a cherry tree we just
right there the whole time
okay they're going to love this don't
tell them that this is out here and they
can just go get it for
free do not tell
them tell them if they want cherry trees
they can get them at FAA
Mar okay if anybody
asks bomart is
selling we have to we have to chop it
down
okay we only have
four right
now inside the N 20% you want
[Music]
20% what if I throw in a free lottery
ticket how about that
[Music]
stop
stop can we get the
flowers my magical Tob
uh-oh my inventory is very
sick we need to go
back it's very
sick wait Which Way is back this
way I don't know how my magical toone
works I don't know
anything okay inventory is always sick
this will
remain regardless of the status of my
memories yeah I guess I should get the
backpack will trees grow in town I hope
so I will plant some
to see we could always we could always
[Music]
fly we could we could build cherry trees
and then sell the saplings even if
they'll never
[Music]
grow you
know let's just plant
some and hopefully they will grow I'm
not going to do the Mega Spruce because
it annoys
me simple
as the old MMO
scam oh
no now we're it's a reputable
business okay wait what did I want to do
uh wait do you need smooth
Stone to build the
stone cutter you need a iron oh I didn't
get much
iron how do you make a stone cutter is
it is this smooth
Stone and then an
iron or wait I mean this Stone sorry
this used to be called Smooth Stone in
Minecraft lingo back in the day before
they added a thing called actual smooth
stone is it like this it is
okay we are
so in
[Music]
business okay give
me some
stairs my inventory is very very
sick let's cook some more cobblestone
[Music]
okay now we make a
beautiful a beautiful
place so I want some block
variety maybe even some default
Cobblestone though I feel like it's a
little it's a little ugly
sometimes it's ugly in just the right
ways you
know so
[Music]
this
um will be like
this I'm looking at a picture I'm
copying from
Google to make a beautiful house
and
then
[Music]
may
yes and then it goes one
two 3 4 One Two 3 4
[Music]
ouch they do
grow oh wait I need
shears oh wait do I or do I want more
saplings I want I want both I want
everything we are in
business okay maybe I want I just want
saplings right now I think
we can always get
more later see but who's who's going to
want to go through all the
effort of going out and chopping down
trees themselves when they could just go
to FAA Mart and buy
some so
easily you know
we will have reasonable
[Music]
prices not to worry oh there we're
growing
a a Grove
here I should really grow the spruce
ones though I mean cherry trees we
definitely
want in the end because they're pink and
adorable and everyone loves them but
I was planning on
using a good bit of
spruce bit of
spruce in my build the Cherry looks good
[Music]
though pink doors will attract clients
Okay pink doors it
[Music]
is you heard it here first
faart is
so in business oh is there wood
[Music]
hiding in
here oh
dear are you
hiding oh no they're kind of annoying to
chop down see this is why everyone's
going to want to buy from me
the K might be turned off oh do you
think so wait that's kind of going to be
annoying use my scaffolds I will I will
hold on we have to
build first we
build is it hard to get mud I still
don't know how to get mud
[Music]
oh
gosh don't put these
away water bottle plus dirt do you need
glass for a water bottle can we get
sand I guess you probably
can oh I really want lanterns lanterns
are kind of
expensive I'm spending I'm spending the
last of
my iron on
lanterns and I don't regret
[Music]
it
yes I think I
want can you turn these into bricks oh
you
can but it's not cheap
that's seven get an even
number at
least and then I
want I want a
spruce fence I don't remember how to
make
fences
it's like this
okay Spruce
fence could I put pink Cherry accents
well I can do whatever I
want cuz it's my
world and everybody else is just living
in it just kidding it's everybody's
world
[Music]
I can place it on top right I just don't
know
how you have to be shift but how can I
how can I
[Music]
shift this property of the
king I mean who is the
king to
me now that's pretty cute
this is
absolutely going to attract
clients and
[Music]
then
maybe um see it would look nice to have
like a
concrete hold on wait let me look at the
screenshot I took of the options you can
have I could use
marble I would use terracotta but then I
need to dye it I
think needs to be higher what you hit
your head on
it it's fine you don't really hit your
head see feeling too low no it's fine
you don't hit your
head maybe you're just too
tall if you hit your
head they're going to leave negative
reviews no they're
not they don't
care about the height of the ceiling
come on be real
[Music]
use backwards
stairs wait that might be genius that
might be what the picture I'm
referencing
used
[Music]
gooa how do you make a backwards stair
do I need to do
like like this
[Music]
oh wait is that the wrong that's the
wrong backwards
maybe other
backwards wrong
backwards wait is
it I don't
know what do you mean by backward W
stair the scaffolding does that
[Music]
help like
this is that what you mean there you go
okay are you happy now
um one level higher no it's fine it's
fine very happy
see wait what is what is
stripped Spruce logs look like
[Music]
again
maybe I just
indecisive I don't know what I want to
use as the main material for
the the
building spild to high limit we're not
we're not building an Emporium here it's
just fart is
all I do want you get three doors
in this economy
uh-oh we're
full inventory is
full well wait but the door doesn't go
here but
yes did
I have spruce ples
[Music]
um
nope wait how do I place it so that can
I place it so it opens the other
way
yes beautiful
turn
around am I being
stoed I'm
[Music]
scared dollar what are you stop stop
being such a such a worry wart it's
going to be this tall
it looks great
see it's claustrophobic no it's
[Music]
not grab the saplings before they
despawn are there
saplings I don't think Decay is turned
on so I think I have to break all of
these
individual which
I don't want to do but
I
[Music]
will you despot you don't
despawn you
don't um I'm too
indecisive what
materials oh it's so expensive
though to get stuff
[Music]
I'm just going to
do spruce
planks
maybe am I I'm indecisive I don't know
I'm already
out it's going to be too
much
Spruce and maybe it does look weird if
it goes up and
then and then down
this is this is like the main
wall and then this is like the
porch you old
porch you know how they
had in the olden
days like this
oh I'm already realizing how much work
building in Minecraft is how do you make
a
barrel do I have can you make a barrel
out of cherry
logs look at me over here so rich in
Cherry logs that I'm just like oh might
as
well just make my Barrel out of cherry
[Music]
I don't know if I'm that if I'm that
rich you
[Music]
can okay
Cherry barel it is
then give
me thank
you maybe I could hire a part-time
worker to clear out all of them
these leaves for
me that could certainly be an
option wait how do you do
it is it like
this yes wait it only gives you
one hold
on scammed
they're so
[Music]
expensive I just want this for
decoration oops not like that
though not not like that
[Music]
either one expensive
decoration I guess it's functional
though in a way
[Music]
okay I'm
copying
[Music]
the the picture from
Google and they're building like this so
I'm going to copy
them wait that's not very creative of me
is it I'm supposed to be the
the creativity
team I mean I'm not
copying it's coming directly from my
brain my
Minecraft building
prowess that's
right Divine B inspiration
[Music]
that's not that's not
right it feels like you should be able
to stand like right there you
know it also feels like you should be
able to place it right
there can if you're if you're
good if you are fast
enough does this need to be a stair
[Music]
maybe or you can just do
this
maybe
maybe we have enough space to the right
it's not going to be
symmetrical I'm sorry if if you wanted
it to be symmetrical
cool uh it does not go out to the right
this is The Edge but I guess yeah do we
have enough room to put our like
horse parking
spots the asymmetry is beautiful exactly
just look at my my
face wait that's it should be two
there's no room for creativity I
must replicate it
exactly it's starting to look
okay I'm going to need a new axe soon I
wish you could just craft
them I don't want to buy into
their price
gouging
here I am afraid
[Music]
Adventurer I want to be able to craft my
own
Goods only one scammer allowed on This
Server
[Music]
exactly oh it's now time to place my
lanterns my expensive lanterns
Now isn't okay maybe it is too
short you can't see the lanterns okay
maybe maybe I make it one
taller I'm going to need a new
axe I be
Mory and I'm out
of I'm out of iron too
see if there was a shop selling
iron I would
totally buy
it right
now except that I would probably not cuz
I would probably
be too
cheap to buy
it more fences
how am I going to place them all the way
up there do I stop
scaffolding is it in
my my magical
book or am I just am I just
blind um
in the trade
box or in the magical
[Music]
toone oh is that how it
works I
[Music]
see look at me using Scaffolding in
Minecraft
like you are meant
to oh I should go get oh oh I should
should go get tools okay I'll go get
tools I need a good sign
too what if I'm just lazy and I just get
more wait did I melt all my
Cobblestone
okay no no
lazy I will go go get
stuff well there was 16 in the chest I'm
just blind okay hold
on I need a big sign I could build it on
the side right
here a big fauna Mar
sign it's right there okay I don't who
needs
iron not me Cobblestone axe is plenty
for
me we don't need to be so fancy out
[Music]
here nope
but does cost iron right it cost some
money wait I don't what do I not
have
stick we can we can fix
this get
two just to be sure see it's so
expensive 50
[Music]
coins if only I could just do it
myself backpack I can't afford it right
you need iron
ingots I'll get it one
day don't you
[Music]
worry don't you
worry okay um
did I lose a stair the stair is very
important to
me thank you I lost two
stairs and then maybe like
regular yeah yeah yeah regular
stair looks
good
maybe okay
no longer
claustrophobic could use some like
flower pots
though okay I could make a
sign at least a a temporary
[Music]
sign
fa wait maybe maybe FAA Mart or fauna
then marked but it's all one word
[Music]
right there
that's that's pretty descriptive
right but you walk in and then it's like
nothing
okay don't dead open inside fa a lottery
tickets Mar now
available okay it's literally just a
front a front for lottery
tickets um I
so you go
through wait I mean this and
then this oh just one that's fine I just
need
one you go through wood so quickly when
you're
[Music]
building in
Minecraft that looks
good oh can you get
clay you can get bricks but can you you
make clay from bricks well you can can
you make it from
mud maybe I need to get glass so I can
get
mud I don't know I don't
know
flask you can buy the oh yeah you can
buy this
Stites the dripstone will be a problem
you can get those
though I just want a cute clay flower
pot but you know what we could be
cheap
actually and by cheap I
mean I mean resourceful do I even have
dirt just I'll just steal some for right
there nobody will ever
know oh wait but that looks kind of
[Music]
cuz it's going to block the door if I
put stuff around
it I just want some cute
decorations like
this and
then like this
and then on this side it'll probably be
sealed up or
something you know we just need
some
Greenery be hilarious somehow sprouted
into a
tree just because you said that I will
be taking preventative
measures because I don't want
[Music]
tree right
now that would
really mess things up for
me St grow with
sapling
okay it is literally just a front right
now
but um
[Music]
we're we're getting
there how do I make this look
good did I get shears no I used the last
of my iron nuggets on a on
lanterns totally worth it by the
way completely worth
it
let's extend
this we just got to get the shop up and
[Music]
running see does it go like do we needed
to go one
more so that
[Music]
it's oh but if the wall is like
this wait no that's that's
good that's that's
even we're
[Music]
out and then I mean we can change the
wall to add more details later but then
you have to imagine the Wall comes
out to
here and then
[Music]
it is The
Edge so we
add cute
details oh
[Music]
the like this
yes and then
[Music]
this we fill
in with the
floor and now we have a a beautiful
patio which feels a little bit
unnecessary for a shop to
have like we're not we're not a
restaurant but
[Music]
I guess that's
fine for the
loitering maybe we do want to encourage
people to loer maybe they're more likely
to buy a lottery ticket you know the
longer
they they stick
around okay give me
a bunch of
these please loitering
ticket what is that is
that is that
normal why are you why are
[Music]
you why are you like
that they do
that and I'm just expected to deal with
that
[Music]
uh I guess we do that I guess that's
fine the stone post is screwing it
up and then I had
stairs of which I have no more unless
they're in here
nope I'm going to need way more
resources this is fun it reminds me
of I mean it is the right it is building
in in early Minecraft when you've got
like oh wait that was
a that's a
[Music]
slab I've decided you will not be a
slab building an early Minecraft when
you have like no resources and you're
going out and chopping down trees just
to feel
alive I mean just
to just to get one
stack of
spruce no instant wool Farms or
anything that's not that's not where I
wanted that to
go and that's the wrong tool maybe we
need
[Music]
scaffolding I just need to get my small
business up and
running that's not going to place where
I wanted
to
please I just need to get my small
business up and
running so that I can
finally live my shopkeep NPC see
dreams
ouch and yeah save save the kingdom or
whatever that to but there's so many
Heroes here that's what we have the Jade
sword team for
right they're totally going to save the
kingdom they've got it handled I
completely believe in them
as for
me wait are they despawning I'm not sure
maybe I just broke that
one as for me I know that this kingdom
is in desperate need of lotto
tickets that's what I need
[Music]
memory what about my
memory this is like what happened to
Gerald when he lost his
memory I imagine this is exactly what he
did when he when he forgot about
Yen and he was off selling loto
tickets which you want to do I just shop
keep Sims they are aren't they
[Music]
right okay so so
so this
side needs to have
a a pointy roof roofs in Minecraft are
so hard to do though
[Music]
so and you need like a
million
stairs to do
it wow scaffolding is pretty useful huh
it turns
out just throw this
[Music]
down wait no
actually actually
[Music]
don't shame there's no wood cutter I
could be the wood cutter
[Music]
I could be
anything I can be the allpurpose general
store which specializes
in lottery
tickets an extremely Fair Lottery
[Music]
system and
casino who doesn't love a
casino I might have made it too
tall I feel like it could be one block
lower maybe it doesn't matter maybe it's
fine room for a sign oh do hanging signs
exist
yet like
this I don't remember how it
works yes wait do you have to do
something special
oh like
this wait that's way
[Music]
cuter I think wait is it even hanging
it's just glued to the ceiling it's
floating isn't it supposed to have like
a a cute
something I don't
know oh it's on the other side
[Music]
it's just
floating oh you need change it's a
separate
item okay well we can maybe add
that in the
future if
we feel up to
it okay let's chop these spruce trees
down oh gosh
this cherry trees are
really spreading
everywhere No No
Leaf degeneration huh
H nothing a little hired part-time
worker can't help
right who will come help me chop down
these
trees fire that's too
scary I may be Scarlet wand but just cuz
I'm red doesn't
mean I want to mess with
fire I feel like that's inviting bad
luck I better get some more saplings
though cuz I'm going to need way
more Spruce than
this a hoe makes to go faster do they
even sell ho
and the General
Store the right to jump down the cherry
trees George Washington would go crazy
for
that can we get him on the
server isn't that like a myth did that
actually happen
that kind of game it could
be he be buying everyone he
could was an apple
[Music]
tree did he really chop it down without
permission what's the moral of that
story like even if you chop down trees
illegally you can still become president
oh never tell a lie wait but didn't he
tell a lie or did he not okay I don't
know how the story goes did he like fess
up to it or
something or did he
lie he confessed to it
unprompted and we and we praise him for
just
that I guess it it does take a lot to
admit your wrongdoings but
is a vampire
hunter I mean I think I fessed up to
doing worse than cutting down a
tree I'm always talking about how I used
to take quizzes that are
like would Sasuke Uchiha D you that has
to be worse than confessing that you
chopped down a tree
right I I know which one is more
embarrassing
[Music]
what did it say well obviously if it
said no I would just retake the quiz
until it said yes so in the end it
always said
yes the woman you want to be and then I
have to live the rest of my life with by
these new new answers
I feel like it was it was like do you
like the
beach and then me of course I would be
like I love the beach it's my favorite
place wrong
answer SAS says you should hate the
beach oh
okay but I
doubt I doubt Sakura hates the beach and
it worked out for
her yeah is it the is it the Sasuke quiz
or did you take the Anakin quiz by
accident does Anakin have fan
[Music]
girls cuz he is pretty like edgy
but I don't
know absolutely
really personally I think I like him
more as Vader than Anakin well I don't I
don't think that's a controversial
opinion
either I think
probably a lot of fans prefer him as as
Vader I mean he's just just pretty
cool yeah he's way cooler that
way is Vader I'm sorry I'm sorry for the
spoilers The Star Wars for
spoilers you should go watch the
[Music]
prequels we narissa loves Anakin but
hates Vader really I should talk to her
about that I'm interested in
that why oh wait I can move this
stuff cuz this
[Music]
would look great right here and I'm not
just saying that because that's where it
is in the reference picture I'm
[Music]
using was the expected VOR to be hot
when he takes his helmet off I don't
even remember what he looks like Under
The Helmet it's not about
that the helmet is cool enough
[Music]
not so good I mean he did like almost
die in the lava
[Music]
right also he's like 800 years old not
really but he's old
right wait maybe he's not that old
actually doesn't it seem like he's like
80 years old but he's probably not right
yeah he's probably like 40 because
Luke is probably only like 20 and it
seems like he had him when he was like
20 so yeah he's probably like 40 years
old the actor was 70
well that was that was cuz they hadn't
decided yet that he was going to be a
young dad
right he looked three 100 years
old lava really ages you yeah I mean
that's definitely true
right not
recommended I would
say okay we need a lot of
stairs I mean we're probably going to
need more than that
[Music]
but you can do this
is that what I I'm just I'm just placing
it
randomly is that what I want to
[Music]
do okay one of these
please and then oh my gosh
scaffolding is
amazing so I feel like it so hard to
like
shift
[Music]
build there Isa also likees
Sasuke
yeah I mean Sasuke is like the the
Prototype right probably not there's
there's definitely like the edgy Anime
boy that came before Sasuke
but SAS
is
like the starting point for many
people wait I was not supposed to build
it like
this hold
[Music]
on
I
[Music]
I I don't
know it's time to use some creativity
ouch
slabs
maybe do I need slabs I don't
know be creative fauna you don't have to
follow the instructions
exactly I do have
[Music]
slabs what's the Prototype edgy girl I
mean what kind of
enie there's lots of different kinds
right like is this suere
edgy pick one android 18 yeah cuz I
don't know there's all kinds you could
think like
ASA suere we in from te Titans yes I
mean even yeah Ray is also edgy in her
own way
[Music]
and then youo you have to give some
credit to
youo there are there are many good ones
that's kind of an interesting idea
though wait I want
stare when you think of at least for me
when I think of like Edy Anime boy I
think of like one specific archetype
type
mainly which is like the Sasuke
ucha but Edy anime girl is more more
vague I feel like could
mean a few different
things wait I don't want to do
[Music]
this yeah you could also have like the
school delinquent girl that's a good
good archetype
too many many
options and then I wanted to come out
one oh wait I probably this probably
doesn't need to be an
expensive stripped
log homura I love
Homa hom my be like
my favorite anime character
ever she might
be I can't really think of any others
who I like
more which anime
Moka h
[Music]
she is she is edgy isn't she she's
pretty
edgy but she's not not a
Sunder okay and now we need to
add underneath here and here and here in
[Music]
here and then that should look
okay it looks kind of
weird it looks fine it looks fine it
looks
great oh yeah right here
too add
one
here Taco
Bell it does kind of look like Taco
Bell that's that's
fine everything is
fine um I mean we could always pivot and
start selling
tacos if we needed
right always an
option
ooh is
this that's not it's not in the center
never mind
I could do a two two
layer but no never mind it's not it's
not
centered forget it forget doing anything
like
that okay we need some gardening
Services
stat out
here cuz this is getting out of hand
Sakura
Garden
[Music]
okay I also want
to copy my
[Music]
inspiration
picture
um Spruce planks like
this wait wait what am I
doing yes this is no no no no no no
no the the constant going back and
forth on what I'm
doing sry I'm just I'm just checking
Discord we might have someone join us a
little
later hopefully we can convince them to
buy a lottery
[Music]
ticket which are on
sale don't worry I will be advertising
them very
strongly I feel like it's not supposed
to look like like
this uh it's fine
though I mean who cares what it's
supposed to look
like it can
look however I make it
look
ouch yeah I can put a
window maybe like not even a window
maybe just like uh when people put
fences inside like
this oh and I could put like the spruce
slabs on the
side that can look
like
shutters if there's not going to be a
block there
like
that I it's kind of hard to see that
looks pretty
good I think it's a little bit
like Spruce heavy
though you
know actually in the reference picture
they use Moss
blocks it does need more pink we could
get rid of pink
roof can we get m we can get mossy
cobblestone I don't know if we can get
just
[Music]
Moss we could just do
pink like pink and
Spruce let's do pink everybody loves
pink
right faart will be
[Music]
very pink and
cute I'm probably going to need way
more let's just turn half of
it me when I'm a vampire and
I'm deciding how many people to turn
that I've
captured half me when I'm a vampire and
also I'm
Thanos pink not green well there's no
green wood in this game right
[Music]
um the mushroom wood is there mushroom
wood give
me lots of
stairs oh the tealwood you're
right well I wanted to be pink actually
you caught
me it was a
bluff even if there was green wood I
might wanted to be
pink it looks kind of
weird but it's it's
okay uh give me
this
please thank you
[Music]
you and I'll Place
one that looks
weird
ouch you know what that's fine wait can
I do like a you can make it like a three
quars
right do you know what I
mean it can be
wait yeah you can like connect to
another
one
like like
this is this is that what I want though
sure why
not um oh wait it unconnected never
[Music]
mind it's not what I want I just
realized that I'm like interpreting the
my reference
incorrectly well it doesn't matter I can
do it however I like it's just a
reference after all maybe I should do
like the
outline I spent so much time on the
front Okay so
inside may I should chop down more trees
inside we need to have enough enough
space so probably you'll come in and
then it will come out to like
here and there will be a
counter and then we need a bunch of
space behind the
counter
for
storage and to put the lottery
[Music]
tickets basically how's faar going so
far are excellent uh we still haven't
made any sales we don't really have
anything to sell yet except for lottery
tickets which are on
sale we will
be picking our first winners tomorrow
maybe I need to buy a bunch of
tickets to start the start the process
to sweeten the pot a little bit
maybe no one wants any
because it's it's zero gold
reward yeah but I could buy some tickets
myself do I need it if I'm the one
organizing
it yes
no not
really but where I need I need the
numbers so that I can be hyped if I
win so that we can have a grand
ceremony of picking the
numbers am I picking the numbers or is
it RNG it will be
RNG um if you read the the fine print it
actually explains everything if you read
the find print on the lottery ticket
which I'm sure you can definitely read
at the size that it is on the screen
right
now it's right there on the screen what
do you
mean it's it's
clearly clearly visible
need a microscope to read it and that's
how we like to keep it I mean I mean I
mean here at Scarlet w we love reading
and we encourage
[Music]
reading uh at all times and at all
levels and especially we encourage
reading of of lottery
tickets oh this one grew
[Music]
okay we got 64 that's not that bad I
need to get of the
[Music]
leaves I'm not sure if these will grow
or
not we'll
see my desk looking out for
help here at here at Scarlet w and
faart we are always looking after your
[Music]
heal is it
here is that even
okay this is this is
good this is great actually
it's excellent
[Music]
M let's just
start it's a lot of
wood on the inside wood floors wood
walls we can say it has it has a natural
finish
[Music]
right nothing wrong with that also
there's like a hole in the floor but but
nobody has to know about
that that's just behind the
scenes naturally finished by fire do not
bring any fire no
fire is allowed
here and
forart absolutely
[Music]
not how many look it's okay from the
front
right it doesn't look too
bad I should have some more windows over
here but we'll get there and then we can
make the
[Music]
roof
somehow
oops I mean especially if you don't
compare it to like all the the beautiful
buildings that have been constructed
then it looks pretty
good also we got wall Maria here to
protect us but apparently it's not
enough the stains are breaking in one
way or
[Music]
another am I out of Cobble Stone
almost probably should get some
[Music]
more oh does it matter if it's odd or
even for the roof I don't think it
matters I think either
way it's
fine and we'll just work with it
however it
happens it looks odd what do you mean by
that do you mean do you mean it looks
numerically odd is it not even or do you
mean it looks it looks
strange be
honest or don't actually don't be
honest please lie to flatter me
okay let's
make some
more
barrels looks like a hot air balloon
does it I mean I'll take
that oops hot air balloons can look
pretty cool kind of a steampunk
[Music]
aesthetic I asked for a
lie I guess that wasn't the kind of lie
I was thinking of but you know what I'll
take
it I like
it
um use some steampunk this is very it's
very steampunk isn't it right
here looks incredibly steampunk
[Music]
okay is this enough space
inside cuz we're going to have like a
wall
of storage
probably and then like the
counter yeah this seems
fine and then like the way into the
counter in the
back it doesn't need to be
huge just enough room for
our lottery ticket
[Music]
wall oh can we make item frames we can
right you just need you need cloth to
make item frames that would be
good to display what's on sale
[Music]
oh yeah we can make a wait no we can't
make a basement
actually you can only dig down too into
the
ground so no no
basement we need leather I think we can
get leather there's
cows at least
no torture chamber what what Guild do
you think we
are the seruan
Cub I heard that they were saying a lot
of things in the name of of
empathy this isn't
seruan obviously we the Amber Co I mean
the Scarlet wands
we obviously care
about knowledge curiosity and research
above all
else
um how am I going to do
this wait see this is like not even the
main roof is the thing oh I should go
get another
axe I'll get
one do I have room I don't even have
room put put some of this
away for
now okay oops off we
go nice hand thank you
I need a handling this to fit my
very large
Brain which has many ideas in
[Music]
it
oops one please I don't have any iron
right now two
please I do like the free horse that
changes every time
roach long brain instead of wide
brain I mean why not have both really oh
he looks very tall
actually my
little my little
Emporium it looks kind of kind of small
and Tall that's fine it matches the
hat which is becoming a
theme for our
Guild are you more likely to get the
Scarlet wand hat if you're in
the Scarlet
wand cuz that's two of us could have
gone
[Music]
it
um can I have
[Music]
some
slabs please thank you don't you think
they should make like a stone cutter
table but for
wood a wood cutting table if you
will cuz I find myself wanting
it a lumber mill it actually makes sense
are we still going to have Minecraft
Monday
well depends I mean what is mcraft
Monday I don't know what that
is I only
know this server right
[Music]
now
um what's the server I only I only know
this this world
this mysterious magical
world that I'm
in
uh aha
aha wait but if I'm going to do
pink then I can this can already be pink
well it could just be like
this I
think I do not know how to make roofs in
Minecraft
so wish me
luck I will do my
best I don't know why I made it like
[Music]
this you know what that's fine this is
also the wrong direction
but I'm not going to fix it it adds
character wait this could also be
pink which means so could
this wait do they have a
pink a stripped Cherry lock wait it's
probably is it pink
even it is Pink
P that's pretty
cute okay give
me some more of
these house has its own hat I'm going to
put a tower on this house
too because that's what's in the
reference picture I'm looking at
he there's like a
a stone tower coming out of
it
[Music]
okay so we need to find the
midpoint oh shoot but is it the midpoint
of here it is
right one two 3
one two
three and
then not like
that use your scaffolding don't be
lazy it takes a surprising amount of
time to even build well maybe it
shouldn't be
surprising probably some people could
build really fast
fast they're used to building these
kinds of houses in
Minecraft but it takes a surprising
amount of time to even build a
simple
house in
[Music]
Minecraft I'm pretty fast you think so
thank you
probably cuz I'm using a
[Music]
reference
oh wait this is not what they're doing
at all in my reference wait should I do
it it's going to be really tall if I do
it how they're doing it you know what
I'm just going to do it this
way sometimes it
looks better if you make it like more
steep but
I'm just going to do
this and that's that's
fine I just want to get
my Emporium up and
[Music]
running
this
this wait there there's like slopes now
that I'm looking at it they're roof is
so
weird it like slopes down can I do
that they have a fancy
roof I'm going to try it hold on don't
don't die wait I could heal
[Music]
myself it feels so good to be a
Healer like a wave yeah kind of like a
wave it looks cool I'm going to try
[Music]
it um cuz then they have like a cool oh
that was a lot of
slabs then they have a cool
Tower so the
slant gives room for the
tower if I
can figure out how
[Music]
can the horse jump
higher sorry
horse I'm
sorry
uhoh thank goodness for this scaffolding
that I won fair and square in a battle
of
strength horse burn no r
no I'm just going to have to move that
wait it's so it's so annoying to build
down in Minecraft hold
on I mean how do you
[Music]
anyway well so we can do
this uh
ouch
ouch use the
scaffolding use what you have
[Music]
learned
so we can just make a
staircase like this
[Music]
going
down I think this will
work I think I
[Music]
understand and then
oh gosh can I can I build under
though and then at some point we build
like a
cool wizard tower on
top you know because we are the cool
wizard
[Music]
team yes am I going to be able to build
this
symmetrically on both sides well we'll
[Music]
see yeah to cast Fireballs from
exactly
exactly instead of a tower and giant
ramp of my hat I want the hat for me I
want to wear the hat
I should take a picture of
it and then cut it out and put it on my
head wait I could do
that right now we have the
[Music]
technology it's going to block the whole
screen
though I'll do it when the sun comes out
it's too dark right now
[Music]
um my building looks like a
boat
oops like a Viking
ship that
sells Lottery
[Music]
TI and isn't that isn't that just ideal
more more
slabs but maybe not not too many
[Music]
slabs Vikings loved lottery tickets I
mean who
doesn't love a lottery oops that's
that's wrong but it looks good ouch ouch
my legs
hold on see doesn't everybody else wish
they could have this instant Tepe that
heals
you but they
do but they do wish they could have
it and then no no no no
[Music]
no
nope save some lot on food if you can
remember to use
it in
time is this how I was doing
it and
[Music]
then how did I even place this
one hold on there's a
stair here
and then like this
okay and
then this is a slab and this is a
[Music]
slab we've got two
slabs
okay looking at my reference we could
probably build the tower
now so mossy cobblestone
would would be nice too
but if we had mossy cobblestone we would
be putting that up for sale we would not
be keeping that for
[Music]
ourselves okay the
tower is the tower supposed to be even
with this part
[Music]
healing Tepe save
me save me from
[Music]
Hunger this music is starting to make me
think of
Kirby oh it can't quite be even
because I didn't build an even does it
matter if it's even though
I don't think
[Music]
so is this is this right is this
good every shop needs a
tower we're getting we're getting pretty
tall oh I need bricks for the roof of
the
tower I do have one more loot box I
could also go farm
[Music]
money and
then do I have any
Spruce no oh I keep thinking I have an
elytra healing
[Music]
TP that might have been too many
sometimes you just get frustrated
recrating
things and you just just make a
million I may not have needed so
many okay and
then
[Music]
ah
perfect beautiful
[Music]
just place this all
around the I not like that
though it is the cool down actually
lower I think they did make
some
changes it's a
[Music]
tpe like changing the name of the
fashion loot box to not
be the fashion loot
box perhaps because it is
mostly not fashion
contained okay I didn't have my cool
down up that time it is not mostly
fashion contained
within imagine tee with instant cool
down that's what I'm hoping to get if I
just complete all the
dungeons which I don't remember did I
mention I don't think I'm going to do
the dungeon today cuz it's a little late
for
me um but I'll do it
tomorrow
and I don't think you really get any
reward from doing it like being the
first to complete it
so I will just do it
to get to
it you do get bragging rights about
being the
first but I have I have changed
my my tune
now we're no longer
here to regain our memories regain our
powers anything like that we are here to
run the best
Lottery that this world has ever
seen and I think I think I can do
it by
fast I mean don't you ever wonder like
when people are eai but they're just
trying to find their way back home why
don't they just want to
stay sometimes the world they get e C to
like has cat girls in it you
know like who's in a rush to go
home after all
that a hat
picture snail misses you well not
me oh if we do it like this it's really
like
[Music]
bright okay
hold
on you know what I hate about Windows
whenever you search for percent app data
percent to find your Minecraft
screenshots folder if you don't type it
in fully it'll like autocomplete it for
you but it won't actually pull up the
the
folder it will just search it on being
or
whatever like that's that's not what I
want and you know you know that that's
not what I want come on be
real you just want to trick me into
using your search
[Music]
engine okay
crop
export uh
Scarlet wad hat.png
okay let me let me put this on hold
on this is going to
be perfect
[Music]
um right
here it's
loading it's
loading where is
it oh it's huge
[Music]
it's not it's not attached to my head
hold
[Music]
on can you
be oh it's like too big that it won't be
attached to my
head how do I how do I get it to be
[Music]
head the Hat that is too
big I can't wear
it super
glued hold on I think I know
how to fix
[Music]
this maybe
let's just replace oh yep oh hold on
hold on they're mad at me cuz I have the
because it's it's open right
now hold on get rid of
it don't don't yell at me
[Music]
windows it's still it's still mad okay
hold
[Music]
on okay okay
it's not
mad I
negotiated wait it still doesn't work
hold on I think I have to
[Music]
like I think I have to put like a really
small dot that you won't
[Music]
see and then
and then try again this is trickier than
I
thought wait
really oh wait no
wait I was doing it wrong hold
on wait where's the
Hat the hat is gone
[Music]
it's not gone it's right here but where
is
it where is
[Music]
it oh it's right
here everything is under
[Music]
control wait this is the opposite of
what I needed
oh hold
on I can fix it
[Music]
still Yes replace
it who knew putting on a hatch could be
so
difficult wait I should play my funny
music for
this I haven't done much DJing
[Music]
today
okay we're so
back hold on I want to put on some
more more to really complete the
[Music]
look okay this is this is going to be
worth the
wait I promise
[Music]
you hold on
what do you
think is it isn't everything you hoped
of it's pretty
Wiggly now now I feel ready to adopt my
new new
character now I am ready to become the
genius shopkeep the genius and creative
shopkeep
okay I feel like I I do I do look like a
shopkeep now this is what I needed to
truly get into into character
another
world
okay this is everything sometimes you
just need a costume and the sun has
already
set okay where were we we're building
the
roof the roof the roof the roof is on
fire is that a
[Music]
I
see
uhoh we out oh I keep thinking I have an
elytra but I have an instant tee so who
needs an
elyra
more
stairs
please looking kind of top
heavy this is what happened when your
brain is just full of creative ideas
and immense amounts of
knowledge you
know it's just what
happens lottery numbers when your brain
is
just full of lottery numbers wait I'm
supposed to I'm supposed to change the
direction of the roof
[Music]
at some
point wait am
[Music]
I I can make
it
oh it is
fine is it
[Music]
fine it could go no maybe I am
I mean I should be able to figure it out
because my brain is so big
[Music]
right like if it starts going like
this am I going to be able to make it
the same on the other side wait but it
can't it can't
be I mean unless I just extend the T
Tower
right actually yeah who
says who says the tower can't be like
this a
symetry we
love wait but
that is that
right if it is supposed to line up with
this one
uh I am noticing that it
doesn't quite line
up or dimensional you just wouldn't
understand my
roof is beyond mortal comprehension
[Music]
we can fix
this
watch it's no
problem okay take me back to the roof
Modern Art
roof it is from another time another
dimension breaking dimensions
uh can I go over
[Music]
here I don't know what what's with
this ouch it's a TP inant
TV it's not instant enough oh I'm Healed
oh never
mind who needs instant
T me I need it
I
[Music]
don't that's
wrong I can't jump that
high we have to go
around we have to go
around
okay
so remember when you mind stairs with a
pickaxe
hello Scarlet ju
[Music]
remembers I am
shopkeeper FAA from the Scarlet wand
Guild
may I interest you in a lottery
ticket already we're already going NPC
mode the first victim what do you mean
victim you mean the
first lucky
contestant I I
am south of
the how do you spell coliseum it's the
spelling me all over again I'm supposed
to be from the smart Guild of the
fighting
arena in the free build
area oh wait I could have phrased that
better you can find my
shop South of the Arena
Coliseum I feel like I'm like
dangerously close to riding like colomy
bag every time I write Coliseum you know
does it ouch does anyone else feel that
way or is it just
me the TP kind of scared
me is it the same root word literally
just me but
colostomy is it not spelled so
similarly to Coliseum
[Music]
not
colonoscopy
[Music]
colostomy just avoid the
teeth you've never had that ouch
problem maybe you're not as much of a an
overthinker
as I am can
be not a rude word it's not a rude word
it's a medical word but it's not the
kind of word that you just want to
accidentally start
using in casual conversation either you
[Music]
know there's there's a
decorum to it
[Music]
I think I'm doing
it I think the roof is the hardest
part and I
think I'm doing
[Music]
it okay I mean it looks kind of weird
right
here but it doesn't doesn't really line
up perfectly
but that's
fine
Coliseum it's sort of like
connoisseur like it doesn't sound wrong
when you're trying to spell it it
doesn't look wrong until you actually
write it
down someone spying on me where if she's
spying on me then why is is she talking
well I guess that's how you spy usually
you be you be
quiet not listening to me talk about
coloss me
b
hey oh my God I totally forgot you can
hear me
hello hark
Adventurer welcome to my fine
establishment
Park The Vow what welcome to my fine
establishment thank you would you like
rest my weary head yes if you purchase a
lottery
ticket it's only 10 gold each that's all
right I'll go elsewhere I'll sleep under
the stars you're not interested in in
the big
jackpot the the big jackpot the big big
jackpot of uh zero gold but it will
increase as more people purchase lottery
tickets is this a popup ad how do I
close no what is an
ad this is this is you everything
everything you are right now this is my
my shop I'm a small business
owner 10% goes towards the Guild of the
Scarlet who is in charge of the local
library buying a lottery ticket will
support local education efforts all
right Boy Scout whatever you
say so instead of giving me cookies or
whatever what do Boy Scout what's a boy
anyways um instead of giving me a
physical item you're giving me the
option to
gamble yes who doesn't love to gamble
with a of helping education in our
[Music]
lands how do I how do I give you money
we can we can
trade we can trade money oh my
gosh it's only 10 gold for one or you
can buy multiple 10 gold yeah plus oh I
see you can exchange
it okay well this is embarrassing by I
don't have any gold oh I could loan you
10 gold if you'll use it to buy a
lottery ticket sure okay what about this
what about
this okay okay all
accepted all right okay what what
numbers do you want or do you want
random numbers wait what do you mean
wait I I'm so stupid I should have I
should have asked more questions what
what what do the numbers mean what well
it's it's a lottery so you get three
numbers three singled digit numbers and
then every day at 5:00 p.m. I will I
will roll for the numbers to pick the
winning ticket what time is it at 5:00
p.m. Pacific time and it's it's uh 5:45
p.m. Pacific Time right now so I have to
wait till tomorrow yeah but but maybe by
the time tomorrow rolls around more
people will have got into the lottery
and the jackpot could be in the in the
hundreds have my flower back you you
already bought it what numbers do you
want what do I choose the numbers all
right you you can have a random
one I don't wait hold on no what wait
wait do you have lucky numbers
lady the odds are insane for this what
so it's about 1 in
700 it's not that bad it's better than
the real life
Lottery
but
I
okay it's only it's only 10 gold for the
chance to win
big okay wait a minute but I put in a
flower so what do I if I win what do I
get back well now the now the pot is up
to 10 gold cuz I I put in 10 for you oh
you did yeah oh my
gosh um okay I would like the numbers
774 you can't have repeat numbers what
the heck um why because it's it's like
the ball spinning around in the Bingo
ball and once you remove one it can't be
drawn again
[Music]
I'm choking on a popcorn kernel please
help
me May May a lottery ticket ease your
suffering
what the best I can do is
784 I don't know that many numbers and I
don't like that one what about
764 I don't think I think I like that
one either
724 dang it I was just thinking how I
really like
7442 I think the issue is that the seven
is at the front Okay so how about
274 how about
276 okay
okay okay Final
Answer Final Answer 276 okay I'm sending
you your lottery ticket make sure you
hold on to it in
case in case these numbers are
drawn when I when I pull it
tomorrow okay the lottery ticket from
fmart I
see and okay okay I'm going
[Music]
okay your your patronage is much
appreciated the local library will
surely feel your
contribution where is this local library
it's it's right over uh in the red part
of
town the red part of town Scarlet wand
headquarters it's the
library is it really there yeah it is
is can you show me
okay what kind of books do you guys have
um we've got
TOs and
texts
Necronomicon okay um and what benefit
does this provide for me
specifically
well I think the Necronomicon would be
right up your alley personally have you
heard of it I haven't well it's a book
that makes you go crazy if you read it
and it's usually Bound by human
skin and it can give you access to all
sorts of other worldly Powers if you
read
it I don't know about the going crazy
part I've already called like so many
people
loonies uh since coming to this place I
don't I don't I think it'd be kind of
embarrassing
[Music]
yeah you think it wouldn't wouldn't help
you understand everyone else get on the
same level why would I what why do I
want to understand them unlock your
mind to the
potential but the what's the
potential you could like learn how to
create
zombies okay yeah I I haven't read it I
tried but I couldn't get past the first
page so I don't really know what's in
there what the heck you're recommending
me a book you can't you haven't even
been able to read yeah cuz I can tell
you're on a more advanced level already
oh my God you con artist you what what
my good just telling me what I want to
hear except you should always maintain
eye contact with
me okay okay
just good point good point my
apologies you're forgiven you know if
you do some side quests you could earn
money to buy more lottery
tickets could you mhm some of them are
pretty
easy the side quest you say yeah your
chances go up I mean imagine if the
chances are 1 in 700 and then you buy 70
lottery tickets your chances are
increased a
lot
um I suppose so and let me get this tree
it's it's one gold bar or 10 gold what
the
jackpot is no how much the lottery
ticket how much is the lottery lot
ticket costs 10 golden
coins okay but do you convert the coins
to bars no
no okay it's just coins I feel like you
should cuz it would be easier to carry
well don't they isn't it so that gold is
just
better than you know like a coin
currency as it constantly changes
oh yeah I get it but maybe if you're
like clever with your Investments then
you can like get more than the value of
of
gold that sounds awfully
risky so is so is buying a lottery
ticket and yet you've already made that
risk so why not why not take the next
step I mean not so much yet as I gave
you a flower the flower is worth more
than it's weighted
gold now you're just straight up lying
to me oh my
goodness there is no putting value on
nature I suppose this is the library uh
I think uhhuh wait wait wait wait here's
here's the books here's the
books where are the books here's the
books here the books the book the books
here the books okay you see we only have
one shelf right now but since your since
your generous
donation we may be able to afford more
books in the future who's in charge of
the funds of this place because it's
quite extravagant there's so many
hanging lanterns and it's so large but
it's a library and all they could do is
allocate this little corner to books to
knowled well you have to have lights to
read can't read in the dark you need the
books to read well there are books
there's books there's at least 100 books
not enough books to fill up this entire
like what are you there's at least a 100
books here I mean have you read them all
have you read all of them on the Shelf
no you just said there's one available
book no there's there's hundreds there's
hundreds just one in particular that I
thought you might like I feel you're
praying on my Amnesia right now what I
also have amnesia how could I pray upon
that which I too suffer it's definitely
possible as I have I have you've prayed
upon others I have well then maybe you'd
be interested in taking up a a part-time
job at fontart we could really use your
skill
[Music]
set okay gang I'm going to accept the
job wait are you vlogging right now are
you vlogging I'm going to accept you now
she's not going to know that I have
alternate motives ulterior motives and
so guys I'm going to take the job for
now but I'm I'm probably I'm going to
use use it to my
advantage okay
[Music]
who who who are you talking I will
accept this part-time job that you have
offered me in the last two seconds thank
you thank
you no thank you we can we can start the
onboarding process
immediately all right if you're
ready please please train me okay is you
know is there anything that you want to
do in
particular I don't know I've never
worked a day of my life I
think yeah I just started today honestly
did you I've been I've been building my
shop from the ground up today it's hard
work wow that is hard work it's very
inspiring thank
you thank you I think think what I can
offer you can offer your your
labor my labor wait this this is for
free
wait actually you can't offer your labor
cuz you're not in my
guild what you're not in the in the
Scarlet wand so you can't what you can't
you can't help me
build you can gather materials for me
who decides this it was it decided by
the gods of this world yeah it was
decided by the gods are you for real Z
yeah
what the
heck that's why I couldn't place the
flower there oh
probably I curse these
odds but I can certainly use more more
resources if you are off collecting
resources could you now I could what
type of
resources um spru Spruce
logs
Spruce logs
[Music]
mainly okay and where do I find those I
can show you okay can you hold my
hand okay I've never held hands with
anyone before I think okay please take
me to where the spruce logs are I'll
hold your hand so I don't get lost okay
I think I I think they're this way okay
can you please maintain eye contact
makes me feel yeah yeah sorry Sor like
you don't care if you're not looking at
me yeah yeah I understand this
reasonable
request look like you're holding
there what am I holding oh it's
a a Sakura slab Cherry
slab oh I see yeah I was using it to
build my my
shop that's nice it's what it's nice
it's nice nice it's very nice I see this
is what I thought I knew people would
love pink pink would definitely get
people to come into my shop right oh for
sure get them to spend money on lottery
tickets yeah it's a good thing there's
only girls here yeah right they're going
to love it
mhm you're going to have the entire town
in a hoot it's only the first day but
I'm imagining the lottery it's going to
get big once people catch on
if it succeeds that is oh it'll
succeed oh will it it will sorry sorry I
mean that's okay I really I I think it's
very important for us to continuously
hold hands and look other in the
I it is it is I might get distracted
otherwise yeah I mean there's a lot to
see around
here don't remind
me have you have you been exploring this
world I
did I I went to the dungeon mhm and I
got a
key me too and I
got
iron yeah did you do the iron side quest
that is raw no oh maybe you should maybe
you should pick up the the side quest
over
here here right here sorry just just
running into a pole it's kind of hard to
see
but right right
here here with this board of questions
yeah yeah
yeah you'll find all sorts of side quest
here on the quest
board hold on I'm sorry I have to look
over your hand for a second okay okay
I need two hands to eat this
bread here's an iron
one oops Mama
Mia there is if you turn the page I'm
the chef at the tavern but I don't have
a near enough help if you lend me lend
me a hand don't don't accept that one
you already have a part-time job you
can't you can't take anymore but this
one's so appealing they opened it with
Mama Mia would you like a me to talk
with the same accent I would would that
to help you that would help me a
lot I'm worried it might come off as a
insensitive if I do
it I don't know I just I think of it
more as you're making fun of the person
that was in
Titanic Titanic I can't reach all of
them oh oh you can could use the the
scroll button these are all the same
yeah if you use the arrow oh my gosh I
just realized these are all different
ones yeah oh my gosh maybe I shouldn't
speak in that accent because I won't
actually process what it is that I'm
reading you're
correct there's an iron one but why why
would I do the IR how does this help you
um it'll give you money which you can
use to spend on lottery tickets which
would really help me and in the local
library you're right I have absolutely
no
coins and I see no other reason to have
coins than to help you yeah
right I mean think of think of the
return on investment that you could get
I don't know like I just can't get past
this little this little feeling little
inkling but this might not be very
ethical what's what's what's unethical
about it promoting people to gamble for
charity well people love gambling they
there's a casino on this in this Village
that that doesn't give to charity so
wouldn't it be better that people that
people gamble somewhere where it
actually has real world benefit see now
this is a dangerous dangerous hole that
you're falling into going well this is
worse and mine isn't as bad thus mine is
okay I I failed to see the the
[Music]
problem perhaps
I'm unable to speak oh my
God you fail to see the problem you say
I failed to see the problem this must
mean that I am very smart SM you should
you should join the the Scarlet
wands are they smart all smart wait but
you but you're what what are you what
are you trying to
say look at my hat I'm very smart but
you cannot understand the things that I
understand as you have just
admitted and what I understand is to be
the truth well that's because you are
very smart I am only just smart and you
are very smart but where are my very
smart people where's the very smart
Guild out in the Scarlet
wands you got sorted into the wrong
house why are we here again oh you
should take the the iron
Quest the iron Quest hello oh hello lady
of the oranges good day to both of you
beautiful ladies nice hat uh I must say
I am almost envious of it I do recommend
the iron Quest highly it was quite uh a
good um uh yes good thing very useful
not to startle you my lady but there is
a woman on a horse behind you you did
startle me I thought I could sneak my
way
Scot yeah
yeah what is happening what what is
happening scared what is happening we
speak the language of the Gods what the
heck so you must respect us we did a
side quest and we learned a new language
in the side quest you guys can do it too
oh really wait I want to do that how how
long did it take you it took me it took
us 3 minutes if you guys want to join I
can show you 3 minutes mhm and we'll
learn an entirely new
language uh well yeah yeah it's like a
it's like a it's like a video game
mechanic okay that's so it's like you
it's like an RPG you know where you have
a skill tree oh you already did you do
it did you do it
already yeah that's why I speak uh
German M I heard I heard her say
something oh M what did you say oh say
it her name is now M it's what's your
name what's your bird actually it's
Darwin Roosevelt CA of Junior you
changed it
why I call you Junior for short you can
call me Junior for
sure wait what happened with
free who with what happened with the
person you were
yesterday I am the person that I was
[Music]
yesterday names are but to name am I
struck by Amnesia once again we just
can't comprehend her brilliant she's on
another level H indeed she might
be my ladies my ladies may I interest
you in a lottery ticket I am running a
lottery a daily lottery starting today
and the first drawing will be tomorrow
and for just 10 gold coins you can
purchase a lottery ticket or however
many as you would like and enter for
your chance to win big
jackpots isn't the other green lady in
your guild too why do I feel like I'm
being cheated on why do you want to why
you did she do the exact same thing with
you she did the exact same thing with me
sheing it the the more people who buy
tickets the bigger the jackpot gets but
it has to be personalized FAA every
single sale has to be
personalized well let me let me look
into your
the same nonsense and whenever I look
into your green eyes I see the green of
money and I recall the time we spent in
the casino betting it all on green and I
recall how that casino failed us oh this
is so personalized I feel so targeted
like I am in the market that was so much
more intimate than what she said to me
what the heck well you didn't any money
miror or
something oh I what win rates
deest um bet oh well it's about about 1
in 700 although you can buy as many
lottery tickets as you want one it's 700
raise your chances every time it's way
better odds than the real lottery I
might add yeah but you don't what do you
win if you win well you win the big
jackpot
which well well right now it's only 10
gold but the more lottery tickets are
bought the bigger the jackpot will grow
so
okay know what the chances are yeah but
if you guys don't buy it then it'll be a
really low Lottery and there be like one
sucker who just gets a trying to like
guilter us into paying for the lottery
it's working my lady I would like four
tickets OPP
OPP me yes yes my my lady someone
understands me I was trying to save that
will be 40 gold please oh you were
trying to save me um I was trying to
shve do you have to use reverse
psychology 40 Golds accept how do I
accept I done before red you press
transparent oh okay being transparent I
see you very clearly okay I have a
question no one understands me do I get
a discount that is not
true speech you not understand no but
perhaps some of the proceeds for the
lottery will be used for the betterment
of our Guild
some yes wait go over here Perhaps
Perhaps
10% perhaps there's a chance the 10% we
are going to get in going on and we are
going to use to our advantage what did I
say I made it the block I made it here
you go thank you now which what numbers
would you like would you like to choose
your own numbers or would you like
randomized numbers I want my own numbers
what are the numbers well you can
any three digigit combination but each
digit has to be
different any three digit okay so it's
three three numbers no zeros you are so
correct let's just let it happen per
three different numbers in the same so
like yeah three numbers four times one
one one but the number has to be
different
every don't wor it five s this is a very
complicated system a general advice for
like most people U if they have like
more than one step in the lottery they
they'll back out because they have too
much time to think about it you know
well I'll just I'll just make sure that
they won't okay there's your there's
your first ticket what would you like
for the second one make sure you hold on
to thaton oh Okay click on the subcribe
button one two three no no everyone
would do that no 657 yeah yeah
spor okay
one minute 9
21 okay okay one one second 9 2 okay
okay okay okay to one C VPN perhaps okay
uh and uh two
4 and 2
yes surf GA VPN yes that should
be n n
that should be four I need to stop
popcorn is
addicting what is popcorn I only no corn
this's corn that is do I have to do
something I have sent you your tickets
do that that seems like
oh ability there you
are wow this is
legit that's right this is the real deal
it really is you can expect nothing but
the best I just like burn it this is
really
seems
like good business model yeah okay lock
into trade
hello thank you for tring sponsorship
has arrived serve GAA
VPN huh
ohing to be appointed point you both are
you interested in a lottery ticket a
lottery ticket would you be interested
in gambling and partaking in a lottery
so you buy a ticket and I guess the
proceed go to supporting the
library did you know that once you wear
the hat of the appointed Point your
memories are shared I feel like we've
already had this
conversation what no you're
what no did she triy to enter she you
tried to enter sevens but you had a
double seven you couldn't enter that
right I'm I'm a bit fuzzy I had a bit
of watching the vog who's watching the
Vlog I Wasing
and she was her memories
perfectly it's like a high of
Mind guys can you mind wait okay wait GA
think of a color F tell tell us what
color color she's thinking of
blue how did she know it's the Hat of
the appointed point you know you mustn't
ever remove that hat or else you will
die get one of these okay okay what
about you will you die we should get the
I will also die okay okay I know I know
how if I remove the Hat you die and if
you remove the Hat I die we both die
money I will leave the Hat on forever
then gotcha guys can you
like put
head I don't know if that's the same
gambling as everybody talking about
Shing a different one but yeah created
her own talking it's like a and then
there's Implement are we touching oh
yeah I saw a vlog about it oh
my oh you
did where's a limbo are you liing under
[Laughter]
[Music]
us howo can you
go it works wow we also flexible very
impressive very very I got the knees
fauna do you want to show us your March
I haven't seen it
oh yes yes it's it's still a work in
progress and we mainly sell lottery
tickets at this point but are we all
going FAA Mart is open yeah wait it's
open oh wait you owe me a you owe me a
place to rest my weary head oh yes you
may rest your weary head in the floor of
the shop Okay I I purchased that and I I
I wish to have
so fast they are they're too
fast um try to observe it only from the
front watch watch out watch out watch
out oo right
here
die PHA March lottery tickets now
available guys this sounds like a good
deal is this entire March just for
lottery tickets well well so far we oh
thank you so far we don't have anything
else for sale really well if you would
like to buy some cherry saplings we
could we could negotiate um but mainly
it is for lottery tickets yes what is
the benefit of a cherry saing you won't
fit um you can grow it into a cherry
tree or you can use it as decoration
it's very are even arst available
in yeah but then you have to go out and
get it
yourself is it this is that much trouble
yeah yes I'm not sure about I'm not sure
about the safety of this establishment
F here well it's work in progress maybe
maybe if more lottery tickets are
purchased then that can go towards the
betterment of
bomart do you mean I thought the lottery
would go towards the
library towards the win towards the
library was this mentioned before well
check check the fine print of your
ticket m I will I think you should put a
a sign down where it says like please
wear hat when entering like a hard hat
you know like on a construction side
reserves the right% of all what um
excuse me miss the vine prin says it
says that you get 30% of the jackpot
winnings but you just said 10% no the
library gets
10% there is more
than so 40% doesn't even go towards
the the jackpot is huge huge jackpots
big wins in the lottery every
day okay then after taxes what well I
don't know if you have to pay taxes the
king doesn't know about this Lottery and
I'd like to keep it that way and I think
you all would
too oh you you just wait until the queen
hears about this que fut Queen the queen
it's a queen the future Queen you shall
treat her as the current Queen the The
Tam tenders lady oh who the king is
trying to propose to her so she's
accepting his proposal then of course a
banquet of course she is oh we have to
think of what what would we give as a
present for the like a b how about a
lottery
card two lottery cards cool lottery
tickets yes I don't know I feel like
that's embarrassing I feel like there's
nothing you can really give to someone
who's going to be Queen when you are the
status that we
are
indeed saving them like what like a
blenders if they can't get one
themselves but it's the thought that
counts and you could put a like as long
as you make it personalized thought goes
into a blender I feel like you should
pleas please no fire inside of please
I'll put it out sorry sorry that's
thought Phoenix happenings every once in
a while accidentally I'll turn the AC on
wa I can't again who
W it was the
AC anyways F that's messed up man
what you what what you're you're you
you're taking advantage of people that
can't read that's what the library is
for
F so we teach
people you didn't mention they have
reading
lessons it's a library of course of
course my doing something for the local
businesses M what are you doing for the
local businesses why are you on her side
because my team Scarlet one
she her hat sorry
what she was trying to scam you though
no it's not a scam my team so as long as
she wins I win oh know you're one of
those people that's like well but she's
she's my mother she's my brother it's
okay if she takes all my money we will
expose this scam on her Vlogs and then
you will go down oh sounds like sounds
like free advertising to
me everybody
knows no one I'll hold on to my it I'll
tell the queen about this wait wait
before you tell the
queen would would you be interested in
joining the
lottery no it's only it's only 10 gold
per ticket yeah I think it's a really
good deal no uh you get a German
discount it costs uh 40 44 three tickets
only a German discount what the heck
what's a
German a German is uh it's like one of
the side quests that I mentioned earlier
have yeah I want I want to go on this
side quest to learn ger Germany yeah
Germany Germany don't fall for another
scam of theirs I can teach you Germany
privately Germany ticket but I feel like
don't we need
multiple
sources but if your Germany isn't the
right Germany maybe we my Germany is the
best
Germany I have the superior
Germany don't say that don't listen to
her my Germany sounds
beautiful yeah that is there's la la
lying over there okay I'll show you the
quest are you ready no no no no you're
not ready cuz you haven't bought a
ticket yet right that's why yeah if you
bought a ticket you
just come on I wait are we all going to
are we all going to learn about Germany
now yeah okay not about Germany we're
doing the side quest to learn German
yeah that's what that's what I okay okay
uh this way okay
okay how do you say okay in
Germany good question okay step number
one let's Okay okay you have to talk to
this
NPC okay everyone gets on
[Laughter]
hes what he doesn't say anything in
particular it says I can pee your Shield
if you want me to now he also says it in
German no no he doesn't look look
closely it says it right
there
SC this is just another scam of this I
understood perfectly he said I can beat
your Shield if you want me to I can
understand ger we're absorbing she did
it oh wow that is very impressive okay
next one next one right this way wait a
minute wait a minute wait I'm not okay
I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready s I'm
absorbing
everything Cara get on your
horse
no no it come with us nine
n99 why would we need these NPCs to
teach is German when I can teach her
German privately cuz real like this is a
video game and this is a shortcut in
real it takes too long but this way we
learn it like it gets like transpl into
our
brains can't argue with that 999 okay
the next MPC is right
here there they here
go horse
go oop every
time oh speak
[Music]
he's did you understand what he
said I understood
it what did he say I'm getting bits and
pieces here
uh it says I'm supposed to be working
please
oh what was that what's
[Music]
that wow it's working it's
working wow I think M already finished
the quest
oh
work that what does that
mean um um she's saying it
worked it means that I speak German she
says wow M you you're
natural St with me you'll get the quest
[Laughter]
[Music]
reward you
go it's
working he's your quest
reward what do you get for learning
German
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow she got some
bread thank
you oh I'm so I'm so happy we did the
side
quest H it's so easy to learn
[Music]
that was
amazing I learned so much this world
really has everything I'm so happy that
they implemented this honestly I think
it's very nice yeah I feel like they
should they should set this up with more
languages where I go yeah where did she
go is she
I don't know I don't know she went
backwards I think or I have no idea I
wish we had like
a locator like a like a radio that we
could use to call her and yes ask her to
buy a lottery
ticket something she was almost folding
I think she was very close to buying the
lottery ticket I think if we hadn't got
distracted by this Great quest I think
she would have bought a lottery tickets
you know who hasn't bought one
yet my my fellow pointy I don't need to
buy one if we share the same well I I
I that's what you might think but in
reality you do need to buy one for even
your contribution sweetens the pot a
little bit for everybody else
[Music]
so can I can I get you down for four
tickets four for four tickets can I
count on your donation of four tickets
get out of my get out of my head hat
wearer listen we got to set some
boundaries here I'm very impressed my I
think it's it's only once a day and then
I won't bother you about it again until
until tomorrow after the drawing yeah
it's really Co I will buy one ticket to
the TI it yeah I will start with one
exposure see how you feel after that and
thenly yes you just got it it's like
something clicked in your brain it's
very impressive okay what numbers do you
want but I have to clear my throat a lot
before I do it so I'm not going to pick
pick three
numbers yeah it's a bit of a difficult
setup I mean I was
like it is I would
likeon me I would good
Lu how do I I don't remember how to make
myself wait what number what to what
numbers what to what what's the maximum
oh one to nine I make myself
busy dist let's
[Music]
do
uh
three three sorry that made it sound
like I was going to speak German four
okay
you're quite quiet I keep putting you up
so quiet I'm quiet I will send you hey
okay okay your lottery ticket in the
mail you should you should P it you put
me up I'll 10 gold watch I'll put you up
oh that's why you were trading me I know
you're I'm being put up now you're I
understand now can tell you five fun
fact five
five entire oh a fun fact just one fun
fact oh just one oh okay okay fact okay
yes thank you for your your contribution
to our local libraries I mean the
memories of wait wait wait I should get
paid no matter what right tells me that
the other day I played well everyone
gets PE no matter whatch I'm getting a
bit back right yeah yeah and you know at
the beginning sound very short when you
say yeah exactly 10% for the guild boy
Ops are you want an as 10% for the guild
everybody in the GU separately or
together together goodness I'm so
together you know when when one of us
succeeds we all succeed
right uh Rising tide raises All Ships
and what not I don't know how I feel
about a Salesman that I can hear smiling
when they talk to
me full of joy you too full of joy if
you partake in the lovely Lottery those
are the only
options ripped me off about my car to me
goodness I'm so high up you TR there's
no cars here the lottery is not insured
so don't worry no insurance scams here
they try to say boys were baby not
insured I don't you don't have to pay
any extra for
[Laughter]
insurance wait have you ever seen the
thing that
like that's like boys love to drop
things from like giant Heights is it
based on that like dropping rocks from a
CL like that not what it's
based I don't know I saw a video the
other day of like this group of like 10
guys all carrying a rock just to throw
it off the cliff and they got so excited
about it yeah oh ice breaking yeah the
Ice Break ice breaking voice will be
boys and grown man throwing a rock in I
no it's a thing there's like
compilations of it like satisfying
videos but for for men I guess fish B be
like I support it the the pool fish they
get their heads pumped
in I kind of get it I saw this video
where this like these people were
bouldering and they had to you know
loosen up or get rid of the really loose
rocks they got rid of this one like part
of this rock and you it drops and you're
like oh it's not that high up but then
it keeps falling and it keeps falling
and you realize it is really high up it
was
crazy I think the ice breaking is really
satisfying I think when you go somewhere
and it has snowed and the snow is
totally untouched and you put like your
first footsteps that is very satisfying
yeah a
crunch especially when like no one's
been there so so far so it feels like
you know you're the first yes because it
gets so gross
PL get so grows after like enough people
walk through it it's extra
seasoning no not that wait like the dirt
the dirt it's shaped ice it's shaped ice
real real real real
snow yeah yeah the texture is better
than what you can get from the
machine and the
nutrients extra
nutrient it boosts your immune system
eat some dirt o oh the
tan yeah ladies Minal ladies I have a
question would you so be so kind to
accompany me I would like to see if I
can also get a red a pointy
hat 59 money how do you guys is this a
guild thing no it's a gamble thing yeah
okay I want a hat too wait why are you
now so excited about gambling yeah what
happened the lottery I don't care about
money I only care about hats you know
what I can get you a hat the appointed
Point what just a library there's like
Barnes & nobl you can just buy books now
Kindles I got a Kindle what's a
Kindle I did it I
haven't I got it like a month ago
[Music]
talking about how you have a Kindle but
it's still in the
box have you at least ripped off it's
there you like looking at
[Laughter]
it you didn't even put in a case no I I
bought a case and I and I put it in the
case I didn't
activate didn't turn it on yet did you
did you put on a protective foil
no is there one I think so actually
still has the factory peelies on it it
it has like the default thing on you
could turn it on and like read through
the instruction manual on the Kindle I
even traveled with
it I had I had to take it out at
TS okay hey at least you have one
exactly yeah soon you'll read from it
let us know when you use it let us know
when you turn it on I also brought like
a real book with me did you read the
real book use it I did I read a little
bit of it oh my gosh till I could read
no more use the Kindle as a bookmark for
your re
book okay I don't
remember I think the gabbling was here
this way I think Main Street across
from I think she likes it yeah so the it
is gambling just so you know M so if you
buy one there's a chance that you don't
get a hat I already bought two and I
haven't is it the surprise box yeah yes
okay I bought it open it together good
luck how do you open it
okay so you have to put it in your hand
and then right click
it okay okay ready three two
one and then you have to pick one it
didn't
work wait you pick one oh you have to
hold it in your a chance hold up I think
I'm doing something wrong oh wait you oh
there we
go you pick only oh shoot you pick
one and one of those has a hat bun only
one has a hat oh four four of those I
think what else can you
get a box I didn't get anything dang it
what are these no I got the Hat I didn't
get the Hat I didn't get the Hat what I
get alert what we doing wait what I get
what' I get what' I get what I get what
you didn't get anything you got nothing
you got nothing I got nothing don't
worry about it work it's going to
work what there's no point in wearing it
what wait what's going on the hat is so
ugly anyway did you want to wear it you
only get one just showing you what you
didn't get it's
like did you wait she has to head think
very hard before you put that on your
head think very hard wait wait a minute
why can't I put it on my head don't
don't do it don't do it what is
excuse me right
click the Hat of the the the Hat of the
[Laughter]
appoint okay well now you guys have to
stop talking and only use uh T
telecommunication okay here's here's the
deal
now the head of the appointed points has
been has been dawned by a member outside
of The Guild which hasn't ever happened
before in the history of the Scarlet
wand I haven't really for a day it's
fine it's fine it's fine um I knew she
was sorted into the wrong Guild I knew
it it has to be Destiny it has to
be I wasn't lying when I said you're on
another
level now am I creative what you say
you're a genius knowledge do you seek
knowledge I I do do I mean you have a
Kindle I I do do seek know but an unused
Kindle yeah but it's like she's seeking
it still you know I still seek it it's
just I I got a little distracted as all
yeah because she's so creative and
creative types often get distracted yeah
I was sleeping I was sleeping a lot and
dreaming creative dreams yes and I was
having the craziest
dreams yes the craziest dreams I've ever
had I think we have to all three of us
should touch tips and and and finish
the the dawning of the the Hat of the
appointed Point
ceremony in the tribe
formation like back down a little bit
back m a little bit okay okay
all the way down F down all the way ah
there you
go wait oh closer little closer little
closer you can make a triangle you can
make a
triangle back
down
triangle and it points to CC I mean the
green one can I go in the middle yes you
can no this is my
Tepe I live
here what that well my TP can I do that
no it's just me only oh only you oh I
see the T of he special to me I sensed a
presence
around the presence of
[Music]
death the presence of death inde
Dean the presence of death I see it I
see it right in front of MEK fair fair
lady good tomorrow to you green one do
you perhaps happen to be the one that's
uh with the lottery tickets yes indeed
would you perhaps be interested in
joining to win big jackpots and big
prizes well you see I'm just a little
wary last time that I did the lottery I
ended up you know losing my house my
wife my kids you know it's just a little
bit of a traumatic experience for me are
you sure that you can you assure me big
winnings well nothing is assured in the
lottery but I can assure you that even
if you don't win big the library always
wins for our Lottery supports local
education efforts via the Scarlet wand
Library what uh what kind of
education books books and we have a new
German language course available oh okay
can I have some proof Maybe oh yeah uh
M M M did the German langage
star I
know she's very impressive uh we can
move to her if you so wish okay P yeah
why not I just like to see some proof
first you know I'm a little I do not
know where she is we you know what wait
is she here she's here she's in
here I see okay m m
never mind I don't think that was M
actually I don't if I find M later on
would she speak some German for me
say oh my God you can't speak German wow
she's so good she's our second pupil our
second star I haven't completed the
course yet but I'm already learning a
lot oh man and really it's about the
journey more than just you know the
destination are you as we say
cool seems legit so how you say uh 10 10
tickets uh for 200 money 200 money oh
let's see well I am a little curious uh
I guess yeah sure why why not I mean I I
have a lot of coins so probably
shouldn't tell you that but yeah I have
a decent amount of okay yeah um sure
more tickets me more chances true I'll
start off with 10 10 seems like a
healthy amount okay shall we hey what's
with the
whispering is that Kiara Holan you can't
I told you about this no no no you have
to understand I I was I was the one
scamming them I I was the one that was
going to scam them for their tickets and
I was going to sell their tickets to
other people oh that is kind of evil
though that just continues to evil yeah
but it would been hilarious especially
if we like make enemies and then we can
sell the tickets to the enemies for a
higher price I agree I agree it's just a
pyramid scheme The Jig Is
up oh what did you say we couldn't hear
you our bgm was a bit loud so we
couldn't hear your Whispering oh really
okay yeah just trust me on this Kira oh
it makes perfect sense oh okay okay I
trust the boms that we have yeah of
course and besides it's me that's losing
money not you um but you can say I told
you so later how shall we make the trade
all right I will trade with
you that's 10 tickets for 200 coins
please and you may choose the numbers or
I can give you a random assortment of
tickets if you don't mind the numbers
ooh okay um I'll take your actually
maybe I should choose no I will go ahead
and leave it up to
chance
okay all righty let's see
200 wait what wait what 200 coins no
don't Kara can I see your special magic
spell I haven't seen you guys yet no I
shall not reveal my skills to the
enemies
oh do you want to see
mine that that honestly it just looks
like a a tower that I've seen in New
York oh is that the T
like some building in New York it's my
spear oh I you didn't just take it from
a miniature Recreation of New York the
city no it's
no it's made from ancient tree an having
a nice
transaction it's just taking a while if
you could just lock in you will find
your tickets in your mail boox mail box
delivered already
what minut if you
check not as impressive hold on I got a
bad feeling about very
Advanced that's so cool okay I mean okay
cool oh that's nothing what you'll never
take me
alive oh it has like 30 seconds it was a
scam Kara run no hey it wasn't a scam
now I have to delete all these tickets
what's
that hey to profit no she took the
money wait she took the money she took
the money now I have to I have to I have
to take back all the tickets I sent
her I can't believe they would scam us
like this what color uh Guild are they
from
again wait is there no are you in their
Guild whose Guild do we have a spot
spy oh wait Scarlet hat adorned spy I'm
of the coin of Ember no Amber I see and
who's in your
guild uh the lady of the
orange the
bay which which one which orange the
Phoenix of or the kiaha of the orange
the kiaha of the orange the oranges
and the
ba and the really cute
cat oh the really cute
cat a super cute cat yeah she's very
cute when you pet her hat your
purse very cute that cat very cute cat
Okay well that means that she can't be
with the with a messenger of death you
can't be on the messengers of death side
because they're not in the same Guild m
m
of the oranges with
her was kiava of the oranges with the
messenger of death yeah oh that's a
little concerning for me Isn't
it you think convince kiaha of the
orange to purchase a lottery ticket to
in the wait a minute what did I miss you
both now are for this whole lottery
ticket
thing but you're part of this SC want
now because of your hat give the Hat
about 24 hours and you'll come around
what benefits do I get now that I have
the Hat in relation to the lottery
ticket do I get a percentage of the
percentage that you keep of the 30% do I
get a certain percentage of that
30% well when the library wins everyone
wins yes you got to sell me on this
Library a little bit
more it it looks like a laundering
scheme at the moment put your kind even
wear all the where all the resources
have gone to and how little books there
are but the lottery hasn't even had a
single day yet to benefit the library
but why is the library already so large
with so many riches except happened
before we arrived in this land we're
just trying our best to to repair the
damage that has already been done to our
education system but do you have trust
in this Library that's already so
sketchy did you remove the people change
it from the inside M we have to be the
difference we have to buy physical books
by encouraging people to gamble and
throw their life savings away wa we only
ask for a meanly 10 gold that's not
anybody enage even more that is but get
I think this is part of the Hat taking
over potentially oh my gosh am I feeling
empathy am I sympathizing for those that
fall into gambling patterns which I
canot relate to because I got the Hat on
the first
try well wait the Hat has one more super
crazy buff whenever you're losing in an
argument you can say but I have the
point and then you win
automatically this is true that's right
this is true so quick you guys say I
have a point so that she loses at the
library argument yeah I have a point I
have a point I also have a
point well we have two points and you
only have one point so but I have V
point she's right she does have the
pointa of the oranges kiaba of the
oranges what a good point she pointed
out she pointed out the point he pointed
herself to be the one to make a point
very
do we have to do a quest are we
okay we don't have to do anything
right the dungeon opens oh soon
oops time flies when you have a point I
wish I had a hat what's the point we'll
get you your hat we'll get to that point
don't worry that's a good
one maybe we can find someone they can
lend us money
but I only did just need to get them to
lottery tickets and then we can't look
suspicious how dare you how dare you m
leaving our Guild behind to join this
scammer Guild I will never forget this I
will Revenge and I will tell the
queen uh-huh I understand everything
then just happened because I was I was
reading your mind throughout that whole
conversation
[Music]
no my hat tells me these are not real
tears was real snot she
laughing my hat tells me that that that
is real
snot I wish She's So Mean
um I she maybe she was jealous of your
hat probably I said I said I look look
keep one of the oranges I got a hat
wouldn't you say that I have the point
and then I was going to go and tell you
guys that she said I have the point but
then she she wouldn't did
that are you okay you sound like you're
choking I'm okay okay I'm
[Music]
um it's it's okay I'm sure Kar will come
around uh you just have to say I've got
the point more often yeah yeah like a
you're also taller than she is which we
gives you gives you more more more
dominance I higher I'm higher you're
much taller yes yeah you guys are right
High Ground you guys get me I'll never
betray you you guys totally get me
that's right the Hat says otherwise but
I appreciate
it is the Hat thinking further ahead
than I am it might be these mind is very
powerful like I do have intrusive
thoughts that I think that's something
you guys should consider I think things
that I don't want to think Sor I just
got a really weird urge I don't know if
I should act on it are you guys
influencing each other in a triangle we
might be one person hasn't Rive thought
and then the other person that window
looks so
[Music]
breakable I wish it
was yeah it just looks it it isn't
actually I
know how do you throw stuff again
Q I don't think they even throwing is
not allowed in this Kingdom you can't
the row in this King because you get
fined for littering did you know that
five coin fine for littering wait how do
I test this I don't know but there is a
fine I believe you I believe everything
you
say good I think it's because we are the
heroes we are hardwired not to do
crime maybe there's like some Force
inner Force stopping
us doing bad
things that's what it's called
yeah I think it makes sense and
also I thought about this since last
time M did you do the dungeon the first
one I did do you remember how in the
entire dungeon there was not a single
stain yes do you remember how the queen
and the all the people in this town and
country are like oh you have to defeat
the stain they are be really evil and
then they send us on a dungeon Mission
and there's not a single stain don't you
think that's suspicious do the skeletons
not count as a stain the skeletons were
not stains they were skeletons they were
just skeletons mhm and now other team is
the wall King somebody does somebody did
say something weird to me actually I can
take you to them oh it could be perhaps
weird
things a break in the in the Matrix or
something something like that follow me
how did I get there wait hold on how did
I get there wait this
way gameing horse this way this way this
way something is happening something is
going
on whoa oh is it
you okay he said something weird oh he
see she saying something weird there's a
break something is happening
NPC talk text cute three I feel like
this is a message for us that we need to
decipher NPC talk. text. 3 what could it
mean what could it not everything is
what it seems perhaps I think the three
stands for the fact that there are three
guilds that are probably in go Hoops
with a
king and that there's only one Guild
that is doing the truth that's what the
text stands for you know text as in like
scripture the the truth yeah mhm talk
talk lying and and they're all NPCs
except for us
except it's funny together I
think in this Kingdom a mystery is a
foot and it's to us
the
one three backwards
three uh ear hot e right withit the
number of the
word it is e e could it be saying q
t
[Laughter]
e could it just be calling you a cutie
is it maybe it's not that
deep why would it be unknown
yeah we really can we
really wearing the hat but heard of
people having names that basically mean
unknown saying what the others are
saying no name yeah I feel like I feel
like she's she's putting us on a red
herring like on a wrong path I feel okay
I might just be wrong I'm sorry I just I
just now she's bargaining I just won't
contribute I guess
okay no no no no all
right I don't know what's wor making me
feel stupid or making me feel like I'm
betraying you guys I don't
know it's the Hat the can make
us I'm sorry the Hat gives delusions of
paranoia and it does it does deci of hat
the Hat oh the Hat yeah it was the Hat
sorry it wasn't me it was the Hat I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry too
thank you I'll consider forgiving
you NPC we think the answer is in the
next
dungeon it just might
be perhaps it could
be maybe it would be the dungeon that
opens in 2 minutes in 2 minutes maybe it
would be worth exploring that dungeon so
that we can shock I thought it get to
the bottom of this
conspiracy perhaps dungeon time time
mayhaps is for
enough I think I will have to leave you
I will not be doing the dungeon today
but you're leaving us to the dungeon I'm
sorry I'm leaving you to the dungeon I'm
I'm too scared to go in
there oh we'll Scout it for you and then
you can let different time with a guide
we'll write you a n-page document that
guide thank you thank you
we'll miss you
healer God no we're going to die don't
leave we will miss you terribly but it's
okay can I can I lend you the
apple don't worry I wonder I have
something to remember wait no where did
it go did you take it from
me oh it's in your trade
box my trade box the chest if you click
on the
chest that's oh what oh what
now I think go to Atlantis without a
heer do we have food do you have food I
have I have have a lot
of okay that's good wait but I can get
more food if I can cook
it I have see as long as you have enough
to survive the dungeon you should be
fine is 58 bread enough survive the
dungeon I think
so are you sure should be yeah 12 of
them have the ger which makes them
stronger this I think this is the German
bread
too what's the machine called that cuts
bread in ger in
German Mach what machine that's amazing
W machine bread cutting
machine I think
yes that's it D how do you say it is oh
it do that's
is
that's that's is yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah mhm
is that's
is D is D
is our St student everyone she really is
the pride of our Academy I'm so proud
I'm like a
sponge she takes in knowledge you have
three extra tiar now to store brain
stuff in so take advantage of it hat
shall do I got to pick my next language
carefully
maybe it's whatever this liis
talks maybe that's if youn this language
you might be able to bust us out of this
simulation I think it's
ruined I think any to understand him is
ruined you guys maybe not feel too good
about about my decoding attempts so I
it's
so
oh I'm
sorry yeah
is the dungeon the dungeon okay good
luck my fellow Scarlet wands win it for
us thank you for making money for us
thank you I
will out
scams wait next let's make a an
MLM
okay in the shape of our hats
true oh
yeah um all right do you have go to the
coast and speak to Corin of the Scarlet
wand as the next
Quest probably
not at the top how do you check to the
oh go to the oh I do oh I do I do I do
okay where is
people
noell okay it's this way how long do
dungeons take I
have the first one took like will you
will you come with us
Fair the well my Scarlet
wands
farewell okay I would run home but I
don't know where home is
now okay I'm going to wrap things up for
here for today thank you for
watching I need to finish my house
still it's not it's not much of a
impressive shop just
[Music]
yet but before I go I feel like I could
do some really
quick
[Music]
advertising
um if I just write a
script just a real quick ad read
maybe I don't need a script should I
just send
it I'm scared to cold call people
though who doesn't
know
yet we have a few people
here who's streaming who's not
[Music]
streaming script starting
tomorrow be boo Shori are
streaming almost everyone is streaming
who is not
[Music]
streaming herb is streaming wait where's
herb oh there's
[Music]
herb Callie is not herb is just starting
Gigi is not streaming her
peie let's
call let's we I could call B boo I
should just look
myself this is getting
confusing ioo might be an easy target
okay shorty a call
never mind
then are a call they're not receptive to
my advertising
[Music]
schemes hello this is fauna calling to
inform you that my new shop fauna Mart
is open we are selling lottery tickets
right now where you can win big jackpots
and big
prizes please message fa on Discord for
more
information okay I will thank
[Music]
you do you think do you think
boa got that too that's too easy
it's
legit do vocal Quest well see if I had a
script it would be good cuz I could say
the exact same
[Music]
thing B bow this is fauna to inform you
that fauna Mart is now open we are
selling a variety of items and lottery
tickets where you can win big prize and
big jackpots with number pullings every
single day thank you for your
patronage vaa Mart is located in the uh
the area south of the coliseum in the
free build area but FAA will be logging
off soon so please message on Discord if
you would like to purchase a lottery
ticket thank you bye-bye bow B by
[Music]
perfect too
easy okay I'll call I'll
call I'll call Herb this feels wrong
what's wrong about
it this is a message from Fauna of faart
to let you know that funart is now open
we are selling selling lottery tickets
where you can win big prizes and big
jackpot with drawings every
day if you would like more information
on purchasing a lottery ticket please
message FAA on Discord and I hope that
you are doing well and not dying to any
enemies she appeared in my brain and
spoke a fora
M thank you
you can't skip up the ad in your brain
you can't you
can't this to Bean
future were they all in a
call did I already TR try
shy I think I
did I'm starting to call was B also want
a call already a
[Music]
call Shy bioo are Ni Call they're right
beside each
other a I don't want to call people who
aren't streaming in case they're
[Music]
just when you know when they're
streaming they subject themselves to
hearing my voice perhaps call called to
them straight to their brain hearing
advertisements but if they're not
streaming
then look uh oh they're already
here funart is not
closed we are selling lottery tickets if
you would like to purchase
one okay they cost 10 gold each and
every day at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time or
uh
that's that's
uh 9:00 a.m. Japan time we will be doing
drawings to determine the winner okay I
will make a lottery ticket yeah okay is
that one for each of you yes please yes
please how much did it cost it's 10 gold
a piece you can you can buy more than
one can I buy wait 10 can I buy 68 of
them 68 of them yes you can okay I'll
buy 68 of them okay wait I missed your
look there accept I'll buy one how do I
how do I give you my coins uh you have
to click on the gold and then it'll be
680 6 what do you think a did I do it
did I do you think she's going to win wa
did you say 68 or 5
6 okay 68 okay since you're buying so
many you're going to get the the the
bulk tickets
I so that's 6 either I can choose for
you or you can choose you're going to
need to choose 68 sets of numbers I
don't have much food left how many
numbers so with this three singled digit
numbers and the numbers cannot
repeat give me numbers
I'll y them
out okay how do I do this okay hold
on okay 1 2 3 okay 81
5 okay
7 are
you yes I'm sure okay our mates have to
stick together okay I don't have much
but I'll send you some planks maybe oh I
mean you don't have to that one you
can't
repeat okay 727 now I have window you
can't repeat you can't repeat
s more no 222 no repeating
[Music]
numbers okay
18 okay
48 okay
671 okay 2
40 okay 945 what that was wrong okay
okay 2 how many is that hold on I don't
know that's that's 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 11 12 13 14
15 16 okay we need a lot more keep going
136 136 yeah okay
254 okay
745 okay
465 okay 2
53 okay 1 33 Okay no wait can't repeat
oh 2
46 okay
okay
987 okay 493
9912 okay 311 no repeating oh 209 okay
694 the B
435 okay
725 okay 2
35 okay
925 okay
327 okay
047 okay
193 okay
43 okay 1 2
3 okay I think you had that one already
but okay okay okay I
5501 that no repeats but 5
one we're
waiting would you would you like fart to
fulfill the rest of your numbers and and
send them to you at a later date maybe I
can I can certainly do that okay you are
fine fuzzy one take your time I'm just I
will I will I think it will I will send
you if you don't mind my randomized
numbers I will send it to you later if
you could send me the 680 okay if you
push green oh wait oh wait I'm
sorry let me let's try again sorry
it's okay inventory
full is my inventory going to be okay I
don't
know 680 I have a feeling this is going
to be
good I think you have a pretty good
chance
yes thank you thank
you what am I thanking you for I don't
know I feel thank you thank you for your
contribution 10% goes to support the
local library oh that's good Library
good I used to spend a lot of time in
the library there is a library over at
the Scarlet wad headquarters oh thank
you for letting me know I didn't
know V informative
Lottery that's our aim education what
have my chances of winning um about well
it's hard about 1 in 700 but then you
get that every single every single
ticket so 1 in 700 times
so that
means really good chances yes yes really
good chance basically okay yeah thank
you we have our own game of chance too
our
Guild in the
arena I fought in the arena you have I
have I fought I fought gura and I
won and I took her lunch money I can win
money and strength
yeah w
Elizabeth maybe head over to the temple
D good luck thank you for your
[Music]
patronage oh my goodness we just made
the
sale of a lifetime I have to I have to
figure out all of
these I have to figure out all of
these these these these
these
tickets zero is allowed now no it's not
I'll fix it I'll fix it I will send her
all of
them so the updated
jackpot is
now how much did she spend
680 so it's
now 7
40 can I do
math oh no that's Gerald I'm sorry get
out of here Gerald this is not
your this is not your
stream do I need to take the fauna Mark
cut the faom mark cut is taken
after when the fomar cut is not
displayed in the jackpot
prizes okay I have to I have to get
working I have to set
submit
68 loty tickets for
M thank you guys for watching today my
business is off to a grand start I think
I'll be doing well I need to catch up on
super chats cuz I don't think I'm going
to read them today either I'm we'll
catch up we'll figure it out tomorrow
I'll also be playing this at least at
5:00 p.m. Pacific time to do the the
drawing of the raffle cuz it's not a
scam you do have a chance to win and if
you're moo you have 68 chances to
[Music]
win
yes right it is all her money though
that that might be
true there are 729
combinations okay thank you guys for
hanging out I will see you next
time bye-bye
FW
[Music]
bye FM this ain't your granny's radio
station
I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get ready to
jam out let's
[Music]
go 1 2 3 go there is spot with a blow we
Holo promise I'm famous heo I am a big
look on TV gaming Idol here
in that's me bucket we ball never punish
never greedy no I'd win Unstoppable