[Music]
n
e
[Music]
n
uh uh
hi k
hi
darling why are you making weird
[Laughter]
noises sorry I'm
like uh I'm confused I'm I'm I'm still
in uh bed at the moment in my head you
know honestly same um so I get it I get
it second collab already so awkward
no no well it's because I I hurt kiwa's
feelings because I didn't marry her
first yeah that's honestly quite
insulting what went down there but I'm
sorry it's okay it's nice to see Ollie
happy you know every once in a while so
what are we doing today now
WEA some is being so so kind is to show
me around the en server I'm very excited
I've woken up in this spirited awayes
Minecraft area and I'm
scared yeah uh I I I I am I would say
one of the best poor Gods when it comes
to showing around thean server I was a
bit oh sorry I need to turn on Super
Chat I was a bit shocked uh to hear that
you girls didn't end up doing anything
yesterday because this was planned to be
you know after you already saw maybe the
the Japan
area um but you know it is what it is it
just means I'll be a to show the Advent
girls oh yeah you could show them around
if you remember so take notes
okay okay super jets are on now so sorry
well well well well we have two povs by
the way have n Isa streaming and Kiwa
streaming so I don't know I think we're
stay St stay together all the time but
know me too now who do I spy with my
little eye where is she you going to
come through
this weisa I only see your name tag and
it's already so beautiful I can see
yours
too wow wow this like a blind
date hi nice to meet
you should
we should we should we peek should we
peek no don't look at me so directly no
I'm shy it's time it's time to throw off
your shyness cast it away Koba Senpai
but oh no oh
no you're so beautiful just as beautiful
as the day I lost
you wait your your Minecraft avatar
looks so cute so pretty so pixell oh my
God so many boxes wow you're wow thank
you you're so foxy too I like your
little Cape no my my my what my cape
cape oh wait am I wearing the sports day
outfit right now no I'm not oh no I am
the the ID sports day outfit yeah you're
so cute oh my god wow your hair is so
long yeah your your black outfit it's
just oh so
fashionable so cool black is sling you
know uh wait do I I actually ah why am I
wearing this it
doesn't I should be wearing you know I
don't know did anybody make a Minecraft
skin of of your new skin yes they did I
wait let me let me see if I can find it
if you have it I can quickly change it
then we'll look better together yeah
yeah give me give me give me one second
it shouldn't take me too too long to
find it okay here here here here here
give me a sec I'm linking it to you oh
my
God oh my God he made he made all of
Advent too so we all except for shot
used him yesterday
oh what did she already use she already
used a different fanmade one oh okay I
thought maybe she just use a standard
Minecraft character we want to direct wa
how does work again I download the it's
just a PNG right you download the PNG
and then you go to the minecraft.com
there's a place to edit your skins
there hey I always do it in the just in
the game you can do it in the game mhm
like I mean you have to go to the
starting screen but
yeah one moment I'll I'll I'll leave you
okay I will stay I will stay locked up
here wait can you do it here too no
that's not it okay guys one
moment this is should be easy Minecraft
[Music]
launcher yeah Minecraft
launcher you can do it in the game
what no the launcher you guys mean the
launcher too right yet cuz there's a
skin thingy here now I'm going to be
walking in a different
skin uh RPG outfit did you get the joke
eh what
joke I'm I'm going to be walking in a
different skin I'm a skin
walker wow wow it looks so wow I know
I'm excited to see it oh okay all right
I'm logging back into the
game and then we're going to be more
matching you know what I'm actually I I
said if I collab witha I want to wear my
RPG outfit and I'm such a coward for not
doing it no not you didn't even know it
existed until just
now true I only saw actually when I was
scrolling endlessly through Twitter I
think I saw a like a Minecraft
screenshot of you and me together in
those outfits and I was like it where
where did they get that from NY
look at my
Senai look at her her cool
outfit let's let's take a look to them
resizing Minecraft window I love that
you can size the Minecraft window
however you like
[Music]
OHA you know uh Minecraft uh server
whole life server etiquette when
somebody logs in you try to greet them
ideally with their own greeting if you
know it it's it's often just like
something con with something of their
name oh my god oh
wow oh look at us we are so cute we
areah G screen too big is it are you
sure I don't think so I think this is
ideal ah wait never mind yeah it's n it
doesn't matter or does it matter no I
guess like it's so weird because this
layout kind of uh
M okay I will I will use this instead
we're holding
hands holding hands oh no that's that's
is that legal yes I can't find the other
one ah guys you will you will have
to
ah okay I
am resizing everything sorry you can you
can look at my
beautiful I'm checking you out beautiful
stuff new outfit let go did you see
amma's new outfit though I did it was so
freaking
cute cute right
little my cute Amelia Watson I love her
I'm sorry you have to hear that I love
someone else I I understand I know you
have other women you also
love much so okay well we uh are here at
the beginning I'm going to give you a
tour it's going to be a long one
probably let's go through
here bibity Bob left or right um uh left
wrong answer this
side you could if you want ride
afterwards here a little opinion about
the
server but the reason why I chose this
side is because we're going to go over
here okay to my Shrine that I built
before Oh I built it with M didn't I I
buil with M yeah M and M was quite
impressed um it's a typical Japanese
Shrine where uh I'm going to take
this it's a typical Japanese Shrine
where where where
uh we we are going to you know do our
visitation shouldn't come up here okay I
took a stick oh give it to
me there you go you took it you took it
from the wall right I threw it I threw
it at you I do a ding dong oh ding ding
ding do this work again oh yeah that
good job make a
wish I know exactly what you're wishing
something about marrying me how did you
know but you got to wait cuz you're
currently still legally bound to uh
someone
else no no unless unless you ask you
know do you know what this is no no it's
a omii okay so you push the button right
click take it what number does it say
one you
got congratulations that means you don't
have to put it up there because you only
put your bad fortunes up there okay I
see other ones up here that are one what
are people thinking uh they don't
understand well yeah they don't
understand because they're not being
Guided by Yours
Truly they didn't or they just didn't
read the sign because they can't
read I'm going to clean up here cuz I'm
the shrine
Maiden pretty Shrine Maiden Ki
waah ooh Crazy Love yeah unbelievable oh
I do holy [\h__\h] I love you you know
doesn't everyone at least know that
song but did you want no I don't
knowen some scenes but at the time it
was when anime it wasn't it wasn't
available for me to watch it at the time
oh but you know the song I need to watch
it though I I saw a picture of kanagi
recently and I was like [\h__\h] man I still
need to know what shows about it's so
cute unfortunately it never got
continued but it's still worth watching
it in my opinion so this area um was
built quite late in the um
second century of and in the don't run
Soo far girl St back
okay this year was built in the year
2000 this year uh this this area was
built in the year year I believe um
2022 um as a project for um connecting
our world with the Japanese world I
think uh and to impress them in a you
know a way that would make them feel
very comfortable and welcomed and this
big tower that you see on your right
hand side that goes all the way up to
the sky you know what that is I think so
it that is the S na na yes you can even
see the pl even see the planets that she
captured inside her balls yeah it goes
up really high it's really beautiful in
the night time especially over here we
have a little Bakery if you're hungry
this Bakery was built
by um maybe maybe also S I don't know
actually why is it sparkling here ah and
mind okay
careful so would you would you would you
like something out of the bakery we have
cookies we have pumpkin oh s also s
bakery I thought so cuz she loves bread
she love bread well no I feel like I
shouldn't take it of course you should I
took I took the free bread from here oh
good job oh oh from the sign girl you
got to stop taking things from the
signs oh okay okay yeah good good okay
I'll take I'll take the cookie then and
enjoy did you take it I I just say you
to stop taking things from where do I
take it from I'll the
cookie oh I see you take St okay I
understand girl it's not listening to me
no I was confused I'm sorry okay okay
okay no problem no
problem all right there's so much to
show oh my God this whole area basically
was built um you know during a certain
time here's a little picnic that's
really cute oh my
God yeah the Ian members tried their
best to get up to um Japanese server
level uh we got pretty close this is the
this area is the most beautiful thing we
ever built on the server um over here
is what is this this is new this this I
never went inside here what the hell is
this new it's a
farm yeah I guess so oh this this is
this is son's house what I never went
inside NY is actually really beautiful
in here oh my God is it for sale I guess
not I would buy it totally but yeah lots
of beautiful plants and then behind it
of course is yeah the tower well that
makes sense Tower should we go up yeah I
I want to it's going to be a little
little a little walk oh actually quite a
bit we should fly but you don't have a
no I can't
fly you don't you can't fly that is uh n
difficult well then let's just admire it
from below for now okay cuz I don't know
walking up there I tried it once what
the [\h__\h] are you doing
here leave my stuie
alone okay oh sorry I think that hit you
too it's it's okay I I like it so okay
um Let me let me go back into the middle
we should go in kind of in a circle ol
got right there was a zombie ol got
jealous you there's another there's a
wait run away fast because that's a
creeper and he's going to blow up
everything if he touches
you let to safety very good very good
okay how good are you actually at
playing Minecraft
um I've never played survival mode
really so I'm excited to start playing
it oh wow okay yeah I usually like to
build like Hobbit houses watching
YouTube guides so that's nice I know
it's so lame I'm so
lame no that's not lame what the [\h__\h] I
love I wanted to build a hobbit house
before but never really was I was always
too lazy well up here is the
onet dad I think mainly cie was building
but she may have had help yeah yeah
beautiful on she did a great job here
yeah it's steaming piping hot W just
like a real on I love that a decent view
to am tits oh Ena Ena built it too mhm
do you see am his tits I I I do I do
actually good view right yeah I thought
they were arms
um oh you thought those were arms but
then what's that that that she's holding
the sign with her ears I thought it was
on her head I thought it was
balancing it's okay it's okay over here
we have another little bath
open bath yeah yeah open air I guess
because this looks very open wow onset
in the snow narissa have you been to an
onset in the snow oh God oh God [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h] that
creeper no no no admittance for creepers
can he enter ah he's waiting okay no he
can't enter very good very very uh good
protection here and a nice rest area too
we could sleep actually shall we
yes
okay Minecraft um etiquette number two
when you want to sleep and there's
someone else in the server but they
don't know that you're trying to sleep
write z z z z z in the chat okay or you
if they're riding it and you're in a
position where you currently can't sleep
just leave the server for a moment
however if you're in the server but
somebody like in this area but somebody
on the other side like on the Japanese
side is riding that it doesn't affect
you so you can stay you don't have to go
to sleep okay mhm so over here there's a
bit more and I think there was a like a
hot hot room over here uh no this is
just oh wait there's just um meat on the
that's a that's a choice how can you do
this I didn't know you can put them on
the ground like that didn't
either where's the where's that hot room
down oh hot room hot room wasn't there
this hot
room it's an what it's an unlit
campfire you can put food on the C is
that a new f
thing or has that been a thing all along
because I didn't know about it what the
hell wow we should have slept over here
so we could have slept side by side yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I can't even though I've been
inside before I can't find the entrance
anymore whatever we have so much to look
at let's go let's
go are you are you you able to keep up
with me good good let's walk under this
beautiful arch of
plants and then over here we have some
playground that's really
cute what was your favorite thing as a
child to play with as in the playground
that's a really good question
[Music]
um I like to treat the whole thing as
one big obstacle
course uh so but I would I would pretend
that I was a ninja running away from um
running away from you pretending to be
an inja I was pretending to be a witch
always because my my Charmed influence
was too strong so I was like I used to
be on Rollerblades a lot uh with my
friends and then we would like roll
around the area and like act as if we
have magic powers and we would decide
who has which like I would have like for
example Pipers the other one would have
PR I love Charmed growing up
man oh that explains the CIS right you
and ninjas you have some history yeah
well Naruto may have been the reason why
I was doing but um what my favorite
thing so I couldn't use you know the
like the little bars that you just slid
down I could not do that uh little bars
ah those yeah yeah yeah I couldn't do
them but I really I really liked when
there were like platforms you could jump
to and from or like the rope climbing
wall type things you know what I mean MH
so I I like rock climbing walls yeah
yeah but those are kind of I feel like
they're kind of rare oh look at this wa
I want to take a picture of that oh my
God cute cheese come bit closer to me oh
my god oh that's so cute oh wow oh oh a
cute let's go howy Raiders oh hello okay
follow me we stop we're getting out of
the playgrounds cuz we're adults yes
okay oh are you
are you I just reminded myself you know
when I started playing Minecraft um it
was the first time I ever played
Minecraft when I played it on stream in
2020 oh my God
2020 and I was like so set on playing it
in third person you're crazy long time
but it just felt right to me and people
kept on bugging me about please play it
in first person please play it in first
person yeah eventually I changed but are
you in first person right now yeah
boring I know I'm so
boring good old times I just move around
well in that
perspective yeah yeah I guess mhm um
over here is a museum
ooh yeah please enter mhm free
entry um the watch 2020 until PR I don't
know I don't know what watch that is
specifically maybe I'm his watch kfp
first employee oh oh my
God flower from 2021 flower do you know
that Meme no explain it oh it was when
like Council was playing um Minecraft
and they were building something and
then um somebody just you know put a
flower somewhere I guess in the building
and and then crony was like flower but
she just said it normally but everybody
was like oh my God you say it like a
robot and so beautiful and then
everybody kept repeating it and yeah it
became a meme flower flower can you say
it like that
flower I don't know how she said can say
a bit a bit more robotic maybe like TTS
flower oh oh you sounded robotic to me
thanks to Minecraft beautiful thanks to
thanks to Discord I mean can you say it
again again flower oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah you should you need
to collab of crony at some point I know
I need to B her I need to be like
cronon call her quason she loves iton
okay here we have Shion and gaura Baku
membrane isi uhuh they they got a
membrane together I guess beautiful this
is Rip Pizza okay I don't know about
that s's first big big bad
big more fish this fish is unnamed
interesting we don't know exact exactly
where it came from this is a dead beat
um in a fortune cookie mhm that dead
beat in a fortune I don't know if it's
really a fortune cookie but somehow yeah
you know yeah yeah I see it yeah tiniest
dead bead scaled up um about uh 100
times for your um Delight please enjoy
amazing uh outside I don't know that
there's not really it's pretty though
it's pretty nothing nothing showcased
here besides water maybe this is water
that was captured from the hole that we
built in our first Minecraft stream I
don't know who knows it's gr bath
water ah oh it very well could be you
know all right let's get out of
here follow
me you know how to sprint right yep good
that's how I've been keeping up with you
this is watermelon house I think if
you're ever need of food like this is an
easy one to think of although
watermelons are not very good to fill
your stomach but there's like always an
overflow of watermelons so feel free to
take some you know I will take a lot do
it do
it I'll take is it automatically like
refill itself what's happening yes yes
you hear the the underneath
how uh it's like a a mechanism under
there yeah if you want to get deeper
into the Minecraft mechanisms this is
probably one you might learn it's a it's
a farm Redstone magic yeah never got
into Redstone
melons anything really you can you can
collect anything make a farm out of
anything really you know don't don't
look at him don't look at his eyes okay
never never look at Ender's eyes why but
girl you did you just look at that you
little [\h__\h] oh my God she never listens
she never listen I swear to
God my God stay stay stay I'm going to
take
revenge [\h__\h] what a waste I waste
the oh my God since when did they kill
you when you look at them I don't why
does she do everything I tell her not to
do try to not pick up all my items there
I'm I'm I'm coming right away I'll wait
I'll wait for you oh my God I didn't
have I didn't have my armor on and I
died even though I even used the totem I
was wearing a totem and the totem is
supposed to protect you from death once
and then it goes away oh but yeah he
killed me right afterwards anyway okay
so uh did what did you have in your
inventory besides watermel all the stuff
right here okay good here's uh more
watermelons you took a lot of
watermelons I'm really hungry I they
keep on coming back to me pick a mom you
need to you need to
move why I can't jaob okay one more okay
okay it went back to me that's okay wait
wait wait wait one
shower nice thanks
okay okay so yeah rul we've seen this
area now actually oh I still remember
this this area um is actually
where we would first spawn when we first
entered the the server when it was empty
and it was like you know let me put on
some armor cuz I'm in trouble when you
around
um it was uh yeah nothing was here only
trees and such and then from here um I
think the first ones were maybe me and
cie I think we started separately and we
would just um walk around through these
trees trying to find a good spot to set
Camp yeah M oh oh yeah oh yeah this this
tunnel exists gan's land tunnel but uh I
think it we we we'll check out ga's
house elsewhere come out
okay I feel like I'm running down that
endless Hall in Mario 64 you know what
I'm talking about the endless staircase
I love that
yeah okay are there currently any carts
here no
cart no cart
um fine we'll walk because I want to
stop in the middle anyway okay oh Burger
House oh yeah right who made the Burger
House again the watermelon thing was
made by Iris the Burger House I think I
remember that but I haven't made the
Burger House oh my
god oh you got to you got to like the
the best thing is to Sprint and jump at
the same time here yeah don't worry I'm
keeping up with you but there do be the
trees the
trees so this is the the train that will
bring you to the main area where myth
built all their
homes and in between we are passing
through several crotches
of I like that love that it's called the
pantu express yes it was a collaboration
of efforts of many people I
see but here I buil for some reason I
decided to build it here is my frog hat
you want to go inside my
house what did I call my God what were
their names uh oh my God they're so a
flop there it's there flip and
flop flip it
flop I think cute they're they are I
didn't know they were FRS in Minecraft
yeah they're relatively new
feature I went out to get them in the
wilderness and it was quite a quest
they're pretty rare but I actually ended
up finding them quite easily and then
you have to you have to uh breed them so
I breeded them I Brad them yeah I love
them and then these these beautiful um
leaves and everything all of these are
also pretty like new uh o yeah they're
pretty no can I put this
somewhere um
[Music]
no okay okay now carefully we go outside
by pushing the button and and then going
for quickly double door system for extra
safety for the frogs yeah don't want to
lose them yes I love my frogs I love
frogs I love frogs have I said before I
love frogs don't you love frogs too um I
actually do like frogs but I'm a little
scared to touch them like in in in
person oh I even kissed a frog in real
life before
I kissed the Frog and I liked it you are
froggy waa after
all whether or not froggy waa is me or
if they're separate entities is
something that you know is
very yeah so let's not you know's claim
anything it's not supposed to be me okay
it's my head Canon it's my head
Cannon fing wa is maybe my spirit animal
uh here if you ever in need for a bed
you can steal one from it's not stealing
it's like you know prepared for
newcomers to the
server mhm you have a band no light
blue is light blue your favorite color I
like blue the best blue is my favorite
color okay why is it not
orange you're you're you are my my my
orange thing that I like you are my
favorite orange than you oh by the way
this area was like built by Ollie Ollie
made it her quest for some reason to
make our area prettier and she very much
did she made this this whole like
rainbow bridge and then this entrance
over here with the with the flowers and
the water the Little Pond the path all
the pathing is made by her so cute I
made this ring oh to fight and oh
circles circles is yeah in kfp history
quite important but uh
not not important in in general uh
mystory so okay Carey will be mad but
yeah um not worth explaining I mean he
was a horse that I once left behind and
people have told me for 2 years straight
to bring him back and I was like there's
no way that Circle still exists and then
two years later I went on a search for
him in the in the desert like million of
miles away and he was still there so I
brought him back I love Inc that is
incredible yeah no how much you know but
like for Minecraft when you when you
lose something as long as you don't go
like as long as you're not close to the
area it will not like really load it so
you can even find what you lost like 2
years later here's my new sniffer look
at my
snier this is a really new animal what
is this thing it sniffs in the ground
and finds you stuff oh like like oh he's
kind of ugly I love him he's cute okay I
this is his adult form they also have a
child form which is a bit smaller he's
nipping me yeah his name is gooa
gooa yeah I still need to make him like
a a house a how long did it take you to
find this
thing oh quite a while yeah cuz I had to
go diving I think to like find an egg
and then I had to bring the egg here but
the egg finding the egg is like wow
difficult
M but he's worth it he's cute he looks
so
funny he's a funny looking guy here here
Nissa this is the legendary first home
of takanasi Kiara ignore that ignore
that Okay Legendary first home of takiar
and originally kifi our our beautiful um
first house that we built when we first
settled in our first Minecraft stream we
said this is the area this is where
we're going to build bu all the myth
things and we said we're going to live
together and we're going to do regular
Minecraft streams after that we we never
did regular Minecraft streams and she
moved out so that's that yeah very sad I
bet yeah my pre using this as my house
even though I built a proper house later
on but yeah I still stay in here meow
this is a cat this is a bed if you want
Marissa yeah please please miss you B
here and move
in you don't have to tell me twice wait
I need to remember how to play
Minecraft you can do it put it in your
yeah yeah yeah yeah I have a roommate
again
yay I'm roommate with my
S I see a future where I log into
Minecraft each time I see the bed coming
closer to mine for some reason I'm
wondering why what a weird thing to
happen so
strange so um I can I can make some
drawers free for you maybe I can I can
set up your own drawers maybe in the
future I I'll make you some
space it's
okay so oh this um this place isn't very
pretty right but you know it's very
functional but I ended up I built it I I
built a an actual house Kaza de
poo chicken house but yeah but I don't
use it but let's take a
look you have to press the button here
I'll press it for you come in come
in welcome to Kaz day
Bo I have a couch that is out of marble
very comfortable I'm sure TV we're
looking at a creeper uh explosion about
to happen a
kitchen makeshift kitchen tried my best
here
and then there's a second flooor press
button go
out good
job oh oh wait thank you for letting me
use elyra is this one good I think
so oh I don't remember that there were
emeralds in there no
emeralds
emeralds and some slime yeah and I I
never have slime when I need it second
floor is bedroom and and armor room mhm
please come in please come in in please
come
in okay good job this bed is not
functional we can only role play on it
what kind of role play would you like to
do kiala Senai the role play that you do
in like World of
Warcraft um yeah I have some storage
stuff that I always for about
here what the hell are
these what the oh these are Sher boxes
what the [\h__\h] cold sh
in I'm going to steal your stuff I'm
going to steal your diamond
sword yeah sure I guess probably won't I
probably won't know what's missing
so which one are you
taking oh cover her in
[Music]
diamonds [\h__\h] my reputation I just wo wo
that looks on you like um like a what do
you call American football um uniform
thing cuz of the shoulder pads being
huge on you oh my God look at the
bee the be yeah the be St no the be it's
not there on purpose it's been stuck
forever I didn't even do it that's so
mean of you you're just trapped I didn't
do it no I didn't do you what you know
what this is the ender dragon head yeah
I'm just storing it here yeah and yeah
this is a nice view from my
[Music]
balcony on the you know on the right
side we see a whole life sign with a ice
path you see the big bridge I don't know
if you can see that far I can see it not
not where it leads but I can see the ice
bridge that bridge leads to phoenixon
where we'll be going later o m and and
yeah well I'll show you everything that
you can see here because I'm very
knowledgeable especially about all the
myth houses and all that so let's
go that looks dangerous yeah it hurts a
bit but you know you you you should know
how it feels as an angel falling from
the sky yes thank
you okay down here is my neighbor Wilson
n n my Wilson she has this like really
dark bridge but then her house is still
so pretty and natural she needs to clean
off the front of all these Amazon
deliveries her front porch is
like yeah too much going on here Ora
Senpai tax this seems like it's from a
long time
ago could be
mhm come in she has very many animals so
if you have allergies then this is not
the place to be oh my God I don't know
what her problem is it's like uh what do
you call people who keep
things things yeah she's an animal
hoarder basically clearly it's crazy but
she built her house like a like a tree
um house
basically so at the very top you know
depending on the season she will have
different uh Tree Top but oh my
God she's um you know out of the myth
people she together with am she's like
the one who has like cool stuff like she
will she will focus on like potions and
other cool things while Amma will focus
on like red uh Stone things and all that
so yeah she has she's she has the cool
stuff when when you're thinking of
something that you need chances are Ena
has it maybe but that's more like back
in the day I guess you girls could
probably very much rely on Japanese
server all the time if you want up here
is her Observatory or so I guess
ooh there was an incident when her dream
burnt before [\h__\h] and since then she put
uh this glass over it to protect it
smart yeah man it really has history
doesn't it and the Axel too yeah she's
got Axel here I don't know why they want
to go into the corner I feel bad for
them they're they're looking for
something the brown ones look like
they're dying is that a normal color for
them yeah
exot have a wide range of colors yeah I
know but Brown not
blue brown is noral damn they look like
like
dehydrated they look like they're dirty
pretty it is pretty sakurama my soul in
it
sakurama okay that part I don't
understand did she help with this tree
maybe Chad you probably know
there's some people who keep track of
every Minecraft stream specifically
Minecraft yeah
really hatama visited ah okay okay so
she didn't know where are you I'm behind
you okay let's go down let's go it's
like they they they merged into one
animal okay we're leaving in a house Ina
Ina uh on her uh left side here we have
her farm for all kinds of animals I
don't think it's really being used much
but what she
really like one thing that she made that
really helped us on the server for a
long time was the wool Farm they're
pretty naked right now in fact what the
yeah you're looking for a specific color
just come back here and then check out
the sheeps and the chests underneath and
you'll surely find the right color this
is not all the possible colors as far as
I know unless she extended it recently
just a lot of
them yeah a lot of them there's still
some more possibilities I think there's
here some
Graves what the yeah all these grave is
here too so I suppose now that you're
married you're supposed to put your
grave next to her eventually no I'm fine
but by the time by the time you won't be
married anymore yeah I don't I don't
plan to die so good actually if you look
behind you now M and you look up to the
sky you see Sam
Tony that was actually um as history
says GAA G or actually might be within
Hol live English unless it's recently
changed uh the uh longest
recorded one-onone or
even not even one-on-one collab stream
to date in Ian it was a way too long
collab extrem to build this [\h__\h] how
long oh it's now it's now the second
longest 6 hours oh my
God yeah we were going a bit crazy
towards the end building this but is it
is a monument because of our
um song cover that we did IA on my
channel
beautiful yeah straight point of view
sorry we did lose our mind and wait I'm
should we go this is I think is it our
first anniversary
cake it does look like a cake now I'm
hungry it is I'm pretty sure it's the
first year cuz it feels like it was oh
no wait wait it's not first anniversary
it's a Christmas tree Christmas
Christmas tree Christmas cake Christmas
2020 oh my God that's that's even long
ago that's that's barely after we
debuted
it I'm num num num num num num we buil
that and and and the tree I guess we
decorated this tree beautiful it's still
standing still Christmas you know no
problem to keep up your Christmas tree
forever right yeah are you one of those
people
Kiwa sometimes in some years yes I see
in others I'm not can you not climb up
the Christmas tree like a
cat come down here at once Marissa Raven
Coss no I'm a star I'm a star Senpai
there a raven craft you are coming down
here at once now I'm counting five okay
wait wait wait I'm coming I'm coming I'm
coming I'm coming okay I'm here okay you
better not be doing that again okay I'm
sorry giv me a heart attack sorry giving
me a heart
attack um okay in the middle by the way
this is our uh never portal our main
never portal um we we could uh end up
checking something out in there too a
little bit later there's so much to show
oh let's go to house house my house I'm
I'm just chose a really really cool
extra special location in the water and
buil herself a nice little Cozy home
here it's a bit chaotic looking and and
you know she sleeps on the grass
basically but you know it's just her
thing she likes nature number one omos
oh she never picked up my frogs I gave
her frogs I am the number one amig
goling
jeez wait did she take like one at least
did I give her free why is this like
Mom she probably just wants to make her
own frogs or so but mhm oh man I can't
believe
it that is heartbreaking she took the
Moss oh I put moss and and frogs in
there and she only took the Moss this
Moss Enthusiast yeah she also has like
trees here which is cool yeah very
nature mous
nature the frogs are still waiting and
yeah she has like farms and stuff here
hidden this and that it's confusing like
's house is confusing me pretty cute
though yeah and it leads straight into
our T this is the famous
tunnel I'm getting PTSD wait no going
come back okay I need to put you on a
leash um this
tunnel and in whole life English and
whole life myth equal in that case um
first ever Minecraft don't don't come
back we're not going there yet and our
first ever Minecraft
collab gooda took the lead I think the
thing is like we were doing weekly group
collabs and um at some point uh it was
G's turn because I think we had it
always on some somebody's Channel um and
then it was goodas turn and we decided
to do Minecraft in this collab and that
would be our first Minecraft collab and
she decided we need to make a tunnel to
reach Atlantis
Okay and like I guess she wanted to make
it reach the the location where she
would build
Atlantis and
and and yeah without really knowing
which direction is correct this is why
the tunnel has um curves and [\h__\h] I see
uh we built endlessly for hours for guda
an endless tow tunnel I died a few times
um me and cie were probably falling
asleep a few times and and and Atlantis
is I don't know where it is though I
don't know um can we go look no no not
yet we're going to take the train in a
in a moment here's Callie's uh old
house you can come in yeah uh cie moved
out and then fought this hole in the
ground was a better place to live than
my wooden house that we built together
unbelievable
unbelievable uh and it like even it has
like see she has enemies coming through
here sometimes like it's it's just like
it's not even safe it's not even secure
it leads you to the tunnel like kind of
like a a ruin of the tunnel no come back
I'm just looking I'm just looking it's
not safe come back
here oh KY right I just saw her logging
out of Minecraft oh
funny thanks
Kawa she has her Mr seats but the thing
is you know she was she was uh she kind
of gave up on Minecraft um for a long
time I remember her saying she would
never play it again and then she played
it again though yeah so I don't know
what the current state is I think she's
just not very fond of it but she is like
she accepts to play it again if need
be okay oh yeah then then we were just
in am house but of course you you
probably noticed the big tennis racket
on top of it I thought that was a I
thought that was a magnifying glass it's
a it's a tennis racket please come on is
it really of course it is okay that's
the only thing that makes sense mhm only
thing so down here gooa house we not to
save
Bridge yeah uh she destroyed this is so
sad she had a glass tunnel
here this where we're going now that was
that was once a glass tunnel and she got
rid of it why so sad didn't she put a
lot of work into that man girl
girl yeah uh I don't even know if she
uses
this Play Still actively is this not
it's not from me anymore right yeah this
is a her her her Hood I
guess her shark Hood uh yeah Place very
very special as well
[Music]
mhm
okay did you read it yeah it's a kiss
from
FAA yeah but she's telling everybody
who's here to kiss
no what if what if we kissed in the gur
in gura's house tunnel in her basically
in her ear I
think thank you fa for that beautiful
prompt um let's see we could go back up
first she has GAA has like kind of
spread
her Estates across the server and it's
confusing because nothing is finished I
see yeah but uh oh yeah by the way I
forgot next to the Woolf f is the iron
farm if you have any iron there's
always nice yes there's always iron here
nice some might say you know for our
Farms there's always like a better
version on the Japan side but if you
want to be you know like me then you go
you go here and get the stuff here M you
know this is
um yeah I can't explain no she can't it
looks fun with my Shader though what the
[\h__\h]
freaky um this was supposed to be
something um that good made as far as I
know yeah she that was like a Revenge
project on P sire I
see but yeah who knows what it was
supposed to be
really from here do you see this like
hug building here what is that guess who
made that I'm I don't know that thing in
the sky mhm which Ian member would be
capable of building something so
crazy no one because it was made by
hatama really yeah she was building this
for forever oh my God and then she
jumped down
and she kind of died there um but yeah
she's she she left something incredible
behind and she's welcome to come
back yeah I guess she's you know I was
making a joke that guess who made it in
Ian um no one Ian gen zero but yeah
she's gen
zero um oh and from here we don't need
to go there but do you I don't know how
far you can see do you see
um something bright orange I do it has
like a o Oz Oz on the head M yeah that's
a stage I build with
nii
um I right you don't have fireworks uh
or like a um you don't have a I don't
have a okay um uh I'm going down not the
best path to choose but you know is
there a boat here oh there's a oh oh oh
K's trying to kill me wait that's you
that's you oh but wasn't there a
skeleton there is oh oh yeah I F where
did the skeleton go k he's killing me
no I'm trying to protect you I'm out of
the water him meeting some food I think
I saw a
boat or did
I is there one
here no okay
M where are we going not I guess uh over
there there is another cool farm I guess
and there's Good's attempt at something
let's just
swim just try to follow me we're just
going to go to gas gas thing and the the
farm thing we don't have to look at at
the
moment just sweam sweam swe do we have
any shaders on uh no not on my side okay
you you're pure say so minecraft pure
and say
so fresh out of the
out of out of the Minecraft bucket okay
ooh so where did you go good was
building something like
uh here oh where are you I'm swimming
there's a door there's a door with a
chicken oh don't go in go back up to the
L to to the to above the
water see there's
fireworks no I don't see them oh my God
why I lost her were you supposed to stay
behind me I was drawing I swim slowly I
see you I see you look
behind look behind I saw you I see you
okay this way okay I'm
coming come here come here coming
coming yum
yum just this is actually quite pretty
if only GAA would finish things this is
not finished right right
guys is actually quite
[Music]
pretty why is there an eye on my screen
returns an ie yeah oh I yeah it's uh it
has to do with what she what GAA built
here oh okay mhm so look at
these [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] what
the you little [\h__\h] how dare
you yeah not very secure in terms of
enemies she needs to put down more
lights um but this is this is uh yeah
pretty
Atlantis actually is it finished it kind
of looks like it could be
finished it's a yeah Atlantis
placeholder more or less let's here
okay I think it looks better at daytime
it's not finished okay well it probably
will never be cuz she abandoned
it but she got so far you know she had
like uh issues with getting like enough
materials for it so she got some
donations too and she got so far and
then she leaves it at Dan
GAA GA sen byai
why oh well I guess we could go this
direction I don't normally take this
path but it should lead us to
something hello me I think we'll go
we'll get to the side of Phoenix then if
we
M oh yeah shrimp shrimpy why did she put
them the
shrimp he's a big shrimp he's a big ass
shrimp yeah it looks nice looks edible
looks
tasty yeah she finished the
shrimp shrimp shrimp is finished oh and
let's see where are we coming out here
ah yeah it is it is at the side of
phoenixon yeah so here oh don't look
don't look I'm not looking I'm not
looking I'm only looking into your eyes
Kiara good good good we don't want to
repeat history um here uh Callie at some
point decided we should do uh like a
like a carnival thing here M so some of
the things we built you know together
with Ian um here uh let's find the
entrance yay
[Music]
yay it it's not you know ID or Japan
quality but it's CN quality build of
love you know um there's um a shark tank
where if you go inside on the other side
I can shoot and then you fall into the
water which is actually you know yeah
quite cool yeah yeah build of Soul
yeah yeah somebody would have to enter
from the from the
back and then I can try do I have an
arrow oh I
do let me let me yeah you sit on there's
some okay yeah yeah okay let me let me
let me get you into the water and you
need a little bath Madame yes I'm so
dir oh no she's
[Laughter]
drowning yeah that's pretty cool though
I think I would say yeah that's
cute in here was yeah Fortune tallying
oh that's got a fortune another Fortune
but this one actually has text on it m
so uh I think yeah you just push the
button push the button has descended and
you are not
alone no don't take it from the box you
have to take it from the button I have
the sheriff one again Sheriff blesses
you you get wait I'm trying to remember
how to get in my you are
illiterate oh yeah wow um that's nice
that's not very that's that's
not well you know you win some you lose
some yeah
yeah yeah I don't know I read it so I
don't think it was maybe correct you
know I think it might have been
wrong funny ironic behind that is the
unfinished feris
wheel oh my God I love Ferris wheels
kiaha s by oh yeah I love them too but
not if they're overpriced like in London
yeah [\h__\h] that this was supposed to be a
project I think from GAA and cie I think
oh man there's so many
what
the what what H why are what these poor
Golems they're chilling they're and
trapped what happened here they're
chilling supposed to be here why did
they all
how what what's I'm I'm florous it's
turning into an iron
farm they wandered in and can't leave
and they keep on I guess creating I hope
that one doesn't fall in that's so weird
I mean we could build them a way out if
we had blocks but I
don't yeah but uh it'll be difficult to
get them they're supposed to be in
phoenixon you know but it's okay they're
they're they're hanging out maybe we'll
help them out later this is a little
animal farm oh God impressive
yeah oh man zombie skeleton horse yeah
oh my go pet skeleton guy very
comfortable the oh the polar bear the
polar bear polar
bear this is a sheep
be it's a polar bear it's a polar bear I
mean if you don't know yeah yeah if you
know you know you know and if you don't
know you don't know mhm it's a slim
polar
bear
cute and what else there's a kfp
[Music]
uh over there a little little
kfb and another like shooting range
where you can get like gold pieces I
guess do you want to try it yes uh how's
this working is there like a GU do you
got to bring your
own uh let me give you a well let me
test it if it
works you're such a good shot does it
work though like I didn't get anything
thing I'm not sure if this is
working that's okay ah wait right this I
didn't I build this you're supposed to
toss eggs no I didn't build this but
it's like my style you're supposed to
toss eggs or snowballs not arrows try it
that's what that box is for okay well
I've got three oops uh yeah don't sh the
fox try to shoot the the one of the
targets how do I throw them H right
click I
think nice M try the left side
maybe H nothing's happening is it broken
it's not finished really yeah I built
something like this before in the
Japanese server oh well but in theory
you you did it so you know what you're
winning what your price is MHM my heart
oh my God my favorite thing W you w my
heart oh my God
okay I think you know we have enough of
this uh Carnival thing um let me show
you the most important thing on This
Server especially as you are a kfp mhm
this is important to you
specifically um Phoenix
[Music]
St famous famous Phoenix St come
in yes I'm in so let me let me explain
to you properly because some people
don't have this explanation luxury so
they're always confused but here's a
sign H straight you get back to Ian
headquarters or just take the ice Road
basically that's better left is the town
square with lots of Traders right is tto
is he even still here I think I by now I
I put him in this place this area is
basically uh unused it's being renovated
I see but the real phoenixon starts over
over this big wall I'm trying to really
separate it because I was like
renovating and I need the traders to be
in the right
places but Phoenix then basically oh let
me tell you though oh my God so
basically this was once a normal village
and then we went through it and it kind
of got destroyed like people um you know
automatically the the algorithm of
Minecraft is like sad it kills people
when you go through it and and then and
then and then and then I was like well
you know I want to I want to make you
know like a trading thingy but uh I want
to make a natural one you know so I
rebuilt this Village for like you know I
I I re rehabit it I revived it when it
was already dead um and yeah I kept a
very natural trading uh economy here
without putting them into prisons and it
went through several renovation stages
uh now is this is this is like built
together with my real life mother yeah
cuz she's is a Minecraft freak and she
we decided to you know um renovate it
make it prettier so now please jump over
here now you're officially in the real
fixon so there's beautiful beautiful
flooring here please look at the detail
on the ground W it's gorgeous at Night
the Lights are really pretty too mhm
over here is like everything that you
need in terms of like armor and weapons
and so on M like if you talk to them
they have names tetso is a big recommend
you can also trade um Iron to them to
get emeralds pretty nicely I see if you
need
emeralds and yeah I I named them so that
you kind of know maybe for some of them
like uh armor and feather falling decent
mining tools guy
Etc yeah try to make it as easy as
possible in with the setting Bob the
building tools guy decent mining tools
number two t all good man good man good
man yeah so they're supposed to stay in
here it it's actually a challenge to
take him out of this area it should
always be safe uh-huh then over here is
anything you need in terms of books like
uh
enchanting they are currently pretty
much enclosed in in this part oops see
they they they are supposed to stay
inside if
possible um try coming in with the
button yeah so we have we have sha
Mendes who has something for
mending uh we have the random [\h__\h] guy
we have re rip tide for
uh uh for Riptide that was a Riptide uh
all kinds of enchantments you just got
to look at their names and then yeah
posid
don't uh
Speedman akua crew what are you Z raid
yeah they all have like things related
to their names
M some some are important like there's a
silk touch guy somewhere I
think Buzz
Lightyear what's what's your name I
can't see sea Mendes a yeah silky boy
silky boy is the silk touch guy silky
boy you might need silk touch in the
future so remember remember what is silk
touch okay uh it's um when you mine
something normally if you mine something
without silk touch on your axe uh mining
tool um then it will um become sometimes
it when you mine it it turns into
something it it
wasn't but it with silk touch it stays
the same exact way you saw it when you
were trying to mine it you know what I
mean it's hard to explain I understand
it's hard to explain but yeah yeah so
this is that area the the people who are
not a literate are here and then over
here is the farming District
if you need food for example um always
yeah there's um I mean there's really
this this area even I don't use it much
but you could come over here with a lot
of watermelons and exchange the
Watermelons for more emeralds but
they're all somewhere else right now
these guys they're not sleeping let's
let's we should sleep
yes two I have one thing is like glass
for example if you're trying to mine
glass it will just break you don't get
it back but with silk touch you get it
back oh that's really really nice yes so
where's meel Lord did I is he in his
melon house I recently I recently
actually did fix this area a bit M um
and extended it to over here this cute
little melon house this is where he
should be feel free to trade in these
melons I even I even put some melons
here for people to trade and then I
revived this farming area this was even
you know in the OG Village this is where
the the farming area was so you're
bringing it all back he's M Lord look at
his prices he sells you he's like he's
got discounts right now do you see them
yes isn't that amazing mhm you can trade
for some some emeralds if you want
suspicious
stew I don't eat that
of
course well but I think he wants full
melons right yeah so you could combine
your little melons into one big melon
can you do that oh you don't have the
discounts oh he only had oh my God
they're making baby right now at this
very moment what the
[\h__\h] they even exchange bread what's
going on can you not make love over the
fence keep it up holy macaroni no keep
it up no that's too much love you know
no
this child will die
no now it's like separated from its
other parent it will forever be on the
other side of the wall I seen this
before Oh my
God can you not like I'm trying to keep
this in control right now he's having a
good time let him live kiaha
sometime damn okay wow well yeah so I
don't really use use this to get food I
mostly only use this to get emeralds you
know your Emerald
Farm yeah more or less it's not the most
effective one but it's the one that I
built so therefore I love it you know MH
um these Shula boxes they just have some
old tools that I was using when I when I
built this place so uh not don't
necessarily I mean you can take stuff
but um I might still need it some some
of these things
here um that's Phoenix 10 for you and
now we're going to go perhaps through
here just walk in and you'll be
teleported up upwards how do you do
that H it's um it's physics girl
physics and then we walk into the boat
can we both be in the boat yes it's so
fast on the ice you know this is so
romantic it's my favorite way of
transportation in this game beautiful
view oh my God it was very quick but
this is basically the shortcut between
myth Village and um get out yeah H and
phoenixon and then if you want to go
down you got to press shift when you're
on the water shift yeah and then just
walk on to the front can she do it yes
she's
sinking beautiful fully done yeah sorry
there's a little bit of pain infliction
at the end there it's got to be like
that that's okay yeah here are some
Farms that I actually own there's a
famous
one this is this
is kfp is first ever usual room I
suppose oh my God place is
famous I love the usual room it's it's
so
nostalgic people never get killed here
don't worry oh of course of course no no
no chickens are harmed here ever you let
one out cute good luck in life byebye
James bye-bye James come back when you
want oh wait I didn't show you the
actual kfb it's it's not a nice building
because this is one of the first things
I built but
M oh my
god oh hey this is recent somewhat
recent um yeah I'm I I built a kfp here
there's so many chicken workers and
chicken customers everything's chicken
here the food is chicken the customers
and the workers everything's chicken but
I thought you were a phoenix
kiaha yeah but we eat chickens of course
why would we eat phoenixes like I don't
have many this just me so Kiara fried
Phoenix why do you call it Kiara fried
Phoenix well just because otherwise I
would get some I would probably get sued
so I I see I
see and because I'm the
boss but it doesn't mean that we're
frying phoenixes
you know know well I mean if you think
about it it would actually be pretty you
know useful because you know phoenixes
can just you know you just
reform wrong this is what you're wrong
narissa okay correct me so Phoenix say
depending on the game or the anime or
the movie that they're in have different
you know lore settings okay what's your
lore setting
Kai so it's not a lore setting it's the
reality but yeah let's go with L setting
um in my case I am oh it's raining let's
take shelter okay I am the only Phoenix
in this Dimension left yeah um I was
traveling for Dimensions this when I
every time I died I I switched to
different dimension currently I'm
chilling here um I'm the only one in
this world and um I I can revive yes uh
uh I can try to stay in the same
Dimension when I revive but often I
would just switch Dimensions the thing
is if you Kill Me by eating
me that is making me incapable of
Reviving
no yes I don't like that that doesn't
work okay most other ways it works but
if you eat me it doesn't work so don't
attempt it you wouldn't want me to try
eating you evenly no I mean but I would
let you if you asked that is wrong so
many levels so wrong you can fry one of
my wings up it'll grow back Oh e no I
don't I don't like that no no Raven Wing
no Raven wings for you no no I don't
want to eat a part of you that's not you
I'll be inside your body
kiaha we will go into the tunnel now the
famous
tunnel so this tunnel has been extended
recently um there's there's uh AB
created a loop normally it's just starts
here goes that way and then ends
somewhere but I'm going create a loop I
don't think I ever did I ever go to the
full loop I don't know um but yeah you
take uh this
card oh God damn it well no go out we
have to remove it
first and then is there another one in
in there no no there's a silky pickaxe
though
oh and my what the wait um maybe one
over here yes okay you sit in the cart
now go go
okay and don't do anything I sit in
front of you cute cute cute and now we
go yes it worked oh my God it's like a
roller coaster it will take a little
while that's okay but I'll try you know
you have to imagine myth was building
this tunnel together history
is in these Halls um I died a few times
in the
process uh some doors here will lead to
little ruins where the girls were maybe
mining a little bit uh one exit also
leads to phoenixon it's another way to
get into phoenixon M where are you I'm
I'm still there I'm just a little ways
behind I got stuck oh don't worry I'm
coming okay um yeah so there's some
small smaller mines some bigger mines
here and
there uh but they've been pretty much
mined all
over oh upcoming is a place where I died
I think or did we already pass it oh no
is this is this where I
died it would be a sign that that could
be no no not sure ah this is it ah yeah
keep an eye out for a sign I guess too
fast to read it though
yeah died
here oh my God
yeah this is a long ride I wonder we can
make it faster with more Redstone
thingies
probably or we should replace it with
ice everything should be replaced with
ice in my
opinion but you know Amma made this rail
after we made the tunnel and like little
Memory Lane yeah it's history so it
should stay this way mhm and you know
I'm still very emotionally attached to
the Ian server in general mhm um so I've
been kind of like refusing to use any of
the
better um devices as in farms on the
Japanese side I just use what I have
here and I keep my house here and so on
like you know oh we can still go to the
hole yeah yeah we'll get
there um but yeah you you you you have a
home now in my house
so I would be pleased if you wouldn't
ignore the existence of the end server
completely now I feel like I need to
show the rest of Advent when we actually
get to play together I don't think I'll
be as good of a guide as you
but oh yeah there's still some things
that I haven't shown you I mean I don't
know if I can show you everything you
know also like for Council things I
don't know where exactly everything is
but you know we can try yeah so here's
where it would continue but I think it
just Loops back down here um yeah oh
another ender man don't look at him in
the eyes you can look at his legs but
not his
eyes so here
is PPP
PPP previously p property I see because
she uh built TT and Amma thought that's
nice I'll make a version for that in our
I server I see mhm and it's it was for a
long time our way of getting uh exp oh
we can go for the water here there's a a
level in between here for fishing M
People Have Spent many hours fishing
here just like in h cure
now um and then wait uh you can go I
guess there wait I haven't been here in
a
while oh yeah yeah I think we got to go
through here this water it's kind of
scary uh press space when you're in it
just space not going forward or anything
why is my thing so
laggy can you do it yeah okay I struggle
with it sometimes and up the
stairs this is very
unsafe yes it
is
scary go yeah go up and then
jump yeah you don't have to go up here
but this is you know the top like she
built it even higher
M but you don't have to go up here just
so you know um and then yeah this was
like I think we just went up there to
make it spawn more enemies but you don't
really have to do it now I guess you
jump down to the Axel to got to get back
down um how do we get out again we're
stuck are we [\h__\h] a
there okay let's go actually down um
back to the stair the
ladder
but you know Emma doesn't like this
place she's not happy with it so she
kind of also abandoned it I
think but there's there you can even
hear some cool music
here oh I'm
good over
here uh how does this look again was
there a
button
oh
wasn't there an automatic one though I
don't
know no [\h__\h] we changed it yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah we we yeah I knew we're
not supposed to press on it
[\h__\h]
uh H yeah yeah how are we supposed to
activate this
[\h__\h] oh I was already broke it two years
ago okay friendly it was messed up
anyway yeah it it made a tune I think
was it the Zelda tune
the 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 but how do you know that when it goes
low ah what smart girl
shees 1 2
1 two three 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 okay 11 12
13 14 15 16 17 at least we fix our
messes the demon of sound is in the end
the demon of sound surprise you thought
you was a demon of soup no no demon of
sound I fixed the last one 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 okay so uh did you fix these last two
or just the last one uh only the last
one
[Music]
okay 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 okay ah
with f fre you can see the note oh
really oh well uh so apparently the
zombie is supposed to activate it but
like I guess he decides when to activate
it on his
own but what if I want to hear it
now move
zomie he's like on the button right now
I think so he would have to move back
and on top of it again ah okay he moved
away okay maybe we can coer him I don't
think so but it's good he'll he'll get
there and then we will hear if we fixed
it
correctly tap the glass and we can't it
w
break Go zombie on the chicken chicken
lead the way go on the
[Music]
button go
go go I mean do do you have any of the
stuff to lead the chicken that the
chicken finds as
tasty oh
[Music]
wait not correct yeah they did mhm the
chest opening
sound we destroyed and fixed
it wow amazing I was scared but you
fixed it you started fixing it amazing
so here the way this works it's still
usable Amit just doesn't like it cuz she
says it's not so efficient but I still
like to use it sometimes
you okay uh so when you push the button
these mobs will drop down and then ah
and then you can yeah kill them and
collect the
EXP and if you have a a mending weapon
this is what you like to use to mend the
weapon back up cuz you need the EXP you
can walk around and some of the chests
collect what they're dropping so maybe
there's even something interesting in
there you know the the bottom one has
like golden armor that you need for the
nether for
example yeah also there's an enchanting
area for the for for the
books but F this is at least on This
Server so I like to use it cuz it's on
This Server U but fa made an improved
version of this she this is PPP made TT
and Fa made
FFF FAS funny or fancy fish farm FAS
whatever uh FAS that's isn't that four
far four FS FS faas fancy fish farm is
like four faas oh it's not there's no
fauna just SP a fish or funny fish farm
funny fish farm all right we can just
jump into the water here okay funest
fish farm is a little bit more difficult
uh to
access uh but it's more efficient so um
if I I I normally just fly there but
through the water here if you go that
Direction behind the PPP you will
eventually see some tall thing that's
where FFF is I see see it's it's spooky
though and you got to use a specific
sword and all that but it's nice when
once you need it then you'll appreciate
it and there's a there's a fishing house
and then over here let me show you my
biggest rival in this industry let's see
this also used to be a normal village
that was then destroyed
by the natural algorithm of Minecraft
mhm uh and then fauna oh good job Faun
made this recently into a prison oh for
villagers to serve her
needs I can't but it's it's very
efficient though are you okay yeah I was
stuck for some reason for a
second so let me show you this just in
case but you are actually obligated to
use phoenixon just saying oh of course
of course
so I think it's this way
yeah uh press shift when you're on the
that weird
thing F lives for efficiency yeah
efficiency but at what cost so she keeps
them here like you know in like one
space prison cells so that they don't
run
around yeah when you see you see what
they're selling very very easy to
understand very easy to use mhm
but you must please me so you will be
obligated to use Phoenix 10 okay
please yeah but she did a good job I
suppose at imprisoning people yeah um
well you know fa's fa is my ocean
Council so I might have to use both to
please both of
you well then do it in secret okay don't
don't let me see it when you do it okay
I won't make you jealous again kiaha
[Music]
sen oh well okay so so so so so uh let's
go back
to I guess the myth area cuz I got to
show you something there that I forgot
and then we could look out for some more
Council things um I know where the sauna
is um
I I
know ah I know I know I know of a few
more things I just have to run around
and be lucky to find
them yeah bunk I was never you looked at
him didn't I didn't look at him I didn't
look at him did I I did I accidentally
look what is the matter with him all
right you must die the good thing is he
can't go past that point uh yeah cuz a
certain amount of um yeah uh oh nice an
ie the the blocks like he's too tall for
them oh oh oh that was a that was a
specific an man you know sometimes
specific enemies are in specific
location this will be a lesson for you
basically for the future this was just
an experiment to show her for the future
so she won't make these mistakes um so
sometimes specific enemies are in
specific locations for a reason somebody
may have C captured them there um to to
be their pet or so um did you kill
someone's pet apparently oh no it's fine
let's let's run let's run he was Agro he
was fine it's fine so yeah I think we
should try to go go the other way
actually might be
shorter I think that's what the loop is
for right I would think
so yeah so if you see like a zombie
somewhere where he shouldn't be chances
hard at to
well well you know how do I even there's
no button
here I'm going slowly and then fast how
do you
move uh go like with the
w yeah that happens a lot it might stop
eventually okay keep on running after it
I got it I got it
okay yeah um oh yeah okay chat is just
attached to that one because he's been
in the tunnel for a long time and
everybody keeps on seeing him in streams
she's just been stuck I freed him from
his
suffering yeah oh she did to protect me
which means it was worth it a yeah kind
of probably I guess I did
that maybe I did yeah
maybe why does why does this tunnel make
me lag now what the [\h__\h] we are
lagging are you lagging too no oh my OBS
is
lagging stop lagging you little
[\h__\h] maybe my rander distance yeah
they're saying so basically he's gen
zero Andy like the Sora of Endy
world what I don't
know uh
okay nice oh I stopped oh I stopped
early I wasn't supposed to stop here oh
that's okay that's okay my carart just
stopped we run the rest of the path some
nice fresh air going on a nice jog with
kiaha
Senai I hate jogging me
too yes I like going for walks though we
walks walks are okay I guess if they're
not too long I have another mine cart
for some reason so if you found and
picked mine up you
can yeah I uh I I may have taken it um
but in the end we're just going to put
all the cards that we have in in a box
where it belongs no oh this was still a
long
PA I didn't know we still had so much to
go oh oh things just go back and forth
here um is this supposed to be I'm just
going assume that the fox is supposed to
be in here cuz somebody put it in there
knows let's not free him maybe it wasn't
supposed to be freed he's chilling there
he goes there he goes with his little
snoot oh he goes back and forth snoot oh
a lot of things are stuck here um wait
no let's um unjam this mhm wait this is
also is this the end yeah this is the
end cuz this cart is like sunken mhm is
this the sheep that will tell you this
is the end thank you sheep for telling
us thank you sheep still continues
though ah this is oh this is an entrance
to
buoni e what where are
we how do you enter it guys I don't know
oh
here I feel so illegal I don't have uh
passage allowance don't look at him
oh welcome to buoni a famous place um
because crony when Council man yeah this
wasn't holy [\h__\h] this this this was like
dly [\h__\h] man yeah
crony CR she went crazy she likes to
have things organized so she created
bunker Roni and she didn't want people
to know where it is and she didn't want
people to come in but people went in
anyway but she had everything so
organized and she had all these all
these things here yeah it was quite a
special thing from these Minecraft
streams yeah everybody you know I was
the only one who respected her wishes I
I I purposefully never looked out for
where her Farm where her whole bunker is
and I even now feel bad for being in
here let's let's get out of here then
she has a guest room oh
oh is it nice it's quite all right it's
just a single bed so
[Music]
tiny
nice and it goes
deeper oh yes of course it does oh let's
go let's see oh what is here on this
level there's like books enchanting
stuff some weird mushrooms mushrooms
cacti storage residence can take oh yeah
only residents can take ooh so organized
imagine imagine if if I could be so
organ this isn't an organized
though not a h oh
burner wow look at her do you think if
you were to build your own home would
you be like this organized beautiful
type or actually this is not really
beautiful it's just functional what kind
type would you be I don't know we're
going to have to wait and
see cuz I'm not some
stairs is this where does this lead
these stairs we're about to find out
exit um scary oh it's scary like it's
kind of nothing maybe she opens this and
then closes it off again maybe this is
the the Yeah the secret one that people
always try to dig into yeah that's
another entrance
uhhuh all right let's leave I feel like
I'm somewhere I should shouldn't be you
too yeah wait down or up
up okay we have to get past the Enderman
how do we do
it walk by him oh there's two even oh
there's
[Music]
three oh okay oh that's close it h
remember to close doors behind you in
general yes oh yeah okay this exit yeah
yeah actually good very good very good
up here I think there's a tree farm up
there
um I know you you might think you know
why Tree Farm there's so many trees in
this game anyway but sometimes I don't
know sometimes you need it
yeah um and uh this what was that again
um I haven't seen it in a
while this was chat will tell me in a
moment a creeper Farm oh this is
so oh it's not the one that I was over
always camping up
right yeah oh it's basically the same
thing yeah gunpowder does she have two
of
these no wait this is where oh wait now
I I I was able to um coming back figure
out where the hell I am yeah we we
circled back and this is a creeper Farm
I thought was the second
one yeah
okay um
interesting uh then we shall kind of
walk back
to the direction of myth Village [\h__\h] I
forgot to put back all the M well we'll
do it later we'll put it into the
tunnel
where uh you know you know the start of
the tunnel it'll be
fine be fine
okay so what do you think of our area so
far it's better than anything I've ever
built in Minecraft I also like to take
over Villages I didn't realize you could
do that with them cuz admittedly I just
tried to protect them uh butet I don't I
didn't I never I've never traded with
them oh well if you would trade with
them they end up like leveling up and
give you some cool stuff actually and if
they don't give you cool stuff then what
you normally do is you get rid of them
and then you get a new Traer yeah I
see so once again actually this place
needs cards M right cuz it never has
cards so let me put uh two in here and
then wait wait wait I'll put two
down and and oh actually I have one
more uh oh you put some in too okay M I
don't know how I got two but no okay I
have two left so with these two we can
go back mm uh
oh oh wait did they Loop this thing too
oh my God where did that go where did
that go
oh it's part of the hyper Loop now oh my
God okay then better to place it here I
guess and then press forward get in
there and then press forward uh when you
look in right direction no not that way
yeah that way that way or I guess button
pushon push there it goes
yay follow meiki while I stand by I will
try I don't know where to get off
um I think it stops you I'm back and her
beautiful
boobies make sure to look up
okay boob time
[Music]
2023 uh where are you right there
by on the right side you may see uh
something with a heart that's green and
pink it's a the it's the sauna of fauna
and SAA combine fauna and SAA and you
have a sauna so they built the
sauna oh yeah right iris's house is uh
down there
too wait oh I'll show you the the place
um The Flower Place flower place FL okay
follow me following once again we're
here on the gay
bridge and then we will no we'll walk
all around
cfp and
then ah yeah this this whole stream is a
little bit biased um I'm showing things
off more yeah that I made this is uh a
paper farm that I made with u my mother
um she helped me create this basically
it it's farming sugar canane but with
sugar cane you can make make paper and
why paper is so important is basically
once you get an elytra you want to make
fireworks and fireworks are made out of
paper and gunpowder so you will need a
lot of that yeah if you need it I don't
know of any other paper Farm there might
be but I don't know of any so just get
it from here okay I mean at least in the
Ian server I only know of this one
H so here is the place that created the
flower
meme they're like you know building
their first house here with all the beds
yeah and then they put a flower here and
then they said flower flower council's
first home oh very luxurious
mhm but you know
memories not M Kiara things it's empty
though I why do I have things here why
is there just a lava
pit it's a disposal pin p bin I get rid
of things oopsie oh no don't waste my
firewor I thought it was for me to jump
in no no no no no okay one more thing I
can show you cuz I know where it is is
the SAA here to the
[Music]
left this is the
SAA we
oh I love to go to sonas really mhm I
only recently started to get like to
have a liking for it um cuz I always
feel embarrassed about getting naked you
know that yeah
yeah you don't need to be with me Ki I
don't need to be naked with you f thank
God no no no you do need to be naked
with me you don't need to be nervous
about it
no okay one more thing I don't know this
this Iris even play I mean I could ask
this question about anyone really does
anybody really play Minecraft anymore
besides fauna and I'm I played recently
actually mhm this is iris's
house I never see her around here
though but that's what I could say about
everybody there's a lot of
dogs yeah she collects them
too this one looks different what's
wrong with this
one which one this guy is that a fox
well there's several foxes and several
dogs actually wolves I guess
officially what is this one that's an
arctic fox the front one is an arctic
fox the one on the very left is a z yeah
yeah that's a wolf actually a wolf
Jefferson cute wolves are not the Wolves
the the arctic foxes are so cute he's
got his tongue out ble he's blepping
like you see he's
blepping B BL is that like a carpet is
that a piece of he's holding a piece of
carpet in his mouth it looks like he's
bling oh my God wait is that on purpose
that's so cute probably I like
that so cute oh okay
leaving yes do you carry anything like
important with you food well I have one
important thing mm uh it's Subaru uh
takoyaki oh give it to me
okay why oh that's T that's supposed to
be takoyaki that's what it says I don't
know yeah it does it's actually potatoes
okay um ah oh this oh I guess we can go
this way why you steal my taco
Yaki um just
because for safety um I don't want to go
this way again no so much so
much around
around uh uh uh follow me uh although I
don't
[Music]
think I I don't I don't know
I no uh just uh just sleep
talking
talk
y i i i i i will show you
something Follow Me This
Way are where are you come here come
here come here run okay uh no so close
come here come here come here come here
come here what are you doing to me wait
should I give you should I give you my
important items follow follow me no
follow me run run come to mommy don't
look I'm not looking
anywhere no take free this first time
first time first time should I give you
my diamond sword I'm scared yeah give me
let me let me yeah let me give you my
armor too so you can give it back to me
cuz I think you're trying to kill me
okay it's it's the experience okay um um
try try to accidentally fall into this
thing where there's some light there's a
hole there try to fall into this history
about it okay H then go go back go back
oh no oh no oh no there Isa oh no you
fell to the hole nobody covered it up
huh where
that right it's it's safe I'm on I'm on
a jelly nice yeah I think I put that
there for safety cuz I didn't want to
close the hole okay how do I get out of
here that's the question yeah um I
didn't think about that did I you want
was down
by is there something that could kill
you I hear some
zombies get them to kill you maybe but I
have so many
watermelons and cookies and a cake from
s's Bakery
[Music]
waa you've abandoned
me uh drop okay wait uh I but the water
doesn't it just float well yeah okay we
can do that yeah I think I think I can
do that I will make you a water
elevator I just need to go get some
water really quickly just stay put
still but have you never heard of the
Minecraft hole the the my you I think I
have but I didn't know what it was so
now you've experienced it firsthand it's
a special hole you shouldn't be crying
you should be happy that you fell
through it I'm just I'm not crying I'm
just so pleased I'm so happy that I I
got to
experience you should be it's it's a
special very special f f the bat I'm
scared it's a privilege to experience
the whole of the server so basically
this hole sparked a lot of Minecraft
enthusiasts um who are watching our
streams to you know document look back
on everything even look at the the empty
server data of us before we moved in
everybody like had to investigate about
this hole because who was the first one
to follow me me who built it the hole
was nobody built it it was just
naturally there shitty hole and I just
fell into it I think several times and I
got I got so mad and then later other
people fell into it and everybody's just
just so mad at
it but it's so weird that it's like
there it just seems like somebody built
it but oh it's not natural are you sure
I don't know yeah right it it isn't and
then people were like who built it and
people were looking back and at all our
streams and were trying to figure out
who built it but it was just never
documented in the Stream so we don't
know who built it h but we we were like
pointing fingers at each other like you
must built it yeah people are saying
probably
gura no but nobody I asked everybody
from myth and nobody remembers building
this
so makes a question didn't Ena admit to
it did she really I don't think so Sude
died here Iris died here I died here uh
people died here well who knows so I
will pour down some water now okay you
should how how do I pour it the best
should I pour it
here oh yeah that's that might be good
water is coming soon you just stand in
it and
then uh space okay space I'm
ready
if you want to prank Advent make them
run randomly over this path and hope
that somebody Falls in I don't know
seeing how I didn't fall in I I'm kind
of I'm going to
drown but I I managed to fall in there
so many times
man oh you can make it I can even hear
you dying so you there you there you
there saved by my Senpai thank you Ki
for saving my life now give me back my
stuff that I stole
rightfully
please okay okay only if you promise me
to try to get somebody to fall in in the
future okay if I if I pass by it I'll
try good stuff okay here's the Takaki
what else um my
armor ah there you go and the diamond
sword you had some cake in your
butt U I think that's it probably yeah
yes
um yeah okay um there's you know
obviously there's still things but uh
this is the stuff that I mostly remember
and that's easy to access there's also
actually let me show you something um
just quickly there's some roboco sampai
stuff here as you can
see and and although I don't think she
uses it never fan that's not being used
as many on the server is P's house that
I built for her nice there was a time
where you know Ian server in Japan
server was connected for the first time
and then it was kind of a like a hype
thing for Japanese Ser uh Japanese
members to come over to the Ian server
and would get tours yeah and I gave her
a tour and presented this house to her a
yeah just for her to have a little
little place to put her things in the
Ian server so sweet I even give gied her
an elytra mhm where do you get these
elytra how what what the uh you have to
get them from the end oh I see we can
get one together sometime actually as a
collab help me I can teach you how to
Traverse the the
end yeah it's difficult you have to be
very concentrated though yes I've never
been there before so I'm
scared okay we can do Dad let's go um
and then oh yeah there's a Lamy house ah
you didn't see the Lamy house I can show
you that one quickly too yeah the lamyai
Lamy saai and Ena have a thing going on
you know oh yeah yeah so they uh live
together this was also during the time
when when the service got connected so
everybody was like you know loveby dubby
oopsie oh [\h__\h] ouch that was not not
comfortable we can go up
here M whammy the
whammy so it's actually I don't know how
we even missed
it but I guess cuz it's like in this
like uh hole more or less but it's close
to the one I built with
NY oh and there was a little shooting
why did she build a shooting range here
I don't even know practice yeah this wmy
house isn't it cute that is cute
it's a it's the the like the the mascot
thing of
wamy yeah it's cute it has actually nice
decorations here I was never inside but
yeah the Yuki mean y
mean oh my God how is it inside oh so
blue yeah cute wow I like it this is a
wool right what is
this um let me tell you
it's concrete blue concrete oh concrete
is so annoying to
make can you get up to the second floor
oh that's a nice house it's
empty yeah not being used either much I
think oh the bed looks nice wait that
looks like pill
what this all quartz stairs are made
into like another standing up pillow
that's genius I saw that before it
really looks like pillows mhm wow okay
cute H guys you have one last chance to
suggest something that I forgot to show
her that I should be showing
her one last chance cuz I feel like you
know I've done my job here my job ah
true true the never okay let me show you
something really important just roughly
roughly um also because we know this is
a biased stream and I
did the Cod jumped so
high uh um yeah I I used the nether M um
to build an ice path um that brings you
really quickly to some um biomes that
are really far okay basically you know
sometimes during our free years here uh
don't go in
yet you need you need some gold M uh
sometimes during the fre years Minecraft
would get updates um where new biomes
would be created is there anything gold
in here look for something
gold and the the problem is that for the
biom is you need to find uh a new
spawned region to load in for the first
time otherwise like here you couldn't
get like a new biomi in this area where
we're now you didn't find any gold
follow me wait okay where'd you go okay
here house
so what I do is like I go into The
Nether because if you go if you walk 5
meters in the never then you walk like
10 15 m in in the real uh Overworld
basically find some gold armor is there
any gold anymore um there's gold here
but it's not armor I have a gold ingot
can I take one of those yeah uh take a
take uh two four take
four okay or take the whole thing and
then put the rest in there I guess and
then go to this thing and then write
boots or or helmet whatever you want and
then make itot boots four for boots do
you have the
recipe for golden boots yeah okay I
don't know how but I got it okay nice I
got some boots you know why we need that
no oh wow you're such a
noob I didn't know you needed gold in
the nether
yeah in uh at least in survival yeah cuz
if you if you don't wear gold some some
enemies will um aggro you ooh
mm so yeah I'm also wearing them we're
we're matching the BS oh my God
buddies so okay I'll show you like some
um famous spots and then my my uh path I
guess we don't have
to don't touch him don't touch him ah oh
my God don't touch that either don't
touch
anything uh this here in here just uh in
case if you ever need um fancy blocks
that come from the Mesa you don't have
to go up now um uh this leads you to the
Mesa biomi that I discovered this also
leads you to a Cow Island if you need to
go to a Cow Island
forland mhm oh what the [\h__\h] why so egro
you little
[\h__\h] uh but yeah and then I extended it
recently right ow [\h__\h] you
um after the Messa bomi what did I find
after the mes of bomi
uh I like that you say biomi thank you I
like it
too uh can I kill this one like I don't
want to kill anything that somebody's
pet you know I don't know if it's
someone's pet if it's trying to kill us
if you're looking for Sakura biomi to
just Farm you know some some new Sakura
items that's past the Mesa biomi that I
uh discovered all all through here
basically there's an ice path you go
into a boat and then you go quickly
quickly
quickly um but yeah it might be a little
bit difficult uh at your first visit to
um Find Your Way properly come back
narissa can I kill this one
this scares
me okay I'm trying let's kill it good
job and there's more but wait there's
more but wait there's more and
more oh my God it's like killing a
spider and a thousand more spiders
coming out of it yeah that's
terrifying okay ooh One cart more cards
no cart
M so
let's walk let's walk so through here
although I don't like walking here it's
kind of
dangerous um this is like our
first path that we built in the in our
never M it leads basically what does it
even lead
to uh I haven't used this path in a long
time um what did we you're I'm scared
well yeah there's a kfp why there's so
many things I'm running I no one
scary Atlantis supposed Atlantis slime
farm yeah some things but not some
anything not really important I guess um
but you know it it's got history you
know yeah this is the place this is the
place
ooh there's a
um prisoner gotcha prisoner but didn't I
kill
him was it yeah well he's not in here
anymore there used to be a famous piglin
in
here uh where we were teasing him to
give us things it wasn't me but he's
dead okay good good good good I made a a
never kfp that's also a long time ago
nice no no no well good luck with that
chickens good luck never it was never
really a safe uh exiting system or
entering
system oh wow it's like making this
cooking sound oh he went back in nice
okay oh wow just yeah it goes even
further like there's another uh it's
really hard to see with my Shader but
there's another path over there that
leads
through some place I don't even remember
anymore but yeah this is another place
that has been seen in many Minecraft
streams of ours M for many hours ha um
how to get back
up wait not here not here not here don't
step on the
fire fire fire on [\h__\h] no not this
[\h__\h] pig again I [\h__\h] hate them
no I've lost
Senai a [\h__\h] hell I hate them so much
[\h__\h] them [\h__\h]
them well we must fight then uh the the
never the most in my opinion nice
annoying enemy in the nether is the
[\h__\h] pigs mhm there's no way to not
Agro them they're so aggressive Ki I
lost you it's okay I'm I'm coming back I
just had to save myself and then kill
this I climbed up high there's a pig no
don't go there no don't climb up come
back down that that place has many pigs
yeah oh oh and in the air there's a uh
oh no oh no don't oh why is it coming
down so low what the [\h__\h] go back up go
back up not you narissa I'm telling the
I'm going down don't worry good the gas
to go
away excuse me bless
you that that little [\h__\h] did you see
the thing that makes those sounds mhm I
think so that's a guest it's very shitty
oh what I'm back by the kfp building
you're
crazy I'm so
tempted you came too close to my
territory buddy I'm so
tempted
yo did I just one hit kill it
let's go look at you miss kiaha taka
Nashi
wow that went down easily okay let's go
back to the is there carts here actually
oh there are a few let's take them you
take one
too I got it
and uh is there a button oh yeah uh does
it work no what how's is work I'm on
fire oh
no are you trying to become a phoenix
yes I guess we just got to go on our own
let's
go press forward it's not working it is
it's slow at first until it gets on one
of the red glowing tiles it's not
working at all then just place it right
in front of a red glowing tile okay M
and then press W forward
forward Liar Liar pass on fire fire liar
on
fire okay now we can put them here so
people can actually use car wonderful
wonderful Wonder Bar Wonder Bar
o you like Sound of Music right I do
yeserday
I was on the hills of Sound of Music wa
really yeah like one of many Hills that
they filmed at least uh for like some
footage I think don't make me jealous
like that that's my dream man I didn't
even realize it cuz it was so normal
like such a normal environment for me I
didn't even realize
that hi I'm I'm Austrian and I just live
in a beautiful place by default yes I do
don't mind me
there's another couple of like important
paths like this leads to something that
I forgot but it was important at some
point that leads to something that I
forgot but it was also does it even say
oh it says copper Express this is the
copper Express M but but as you remember
here first station also leads to Amic
copper yes no actually I need to edit
this um
because um let me just put one down here
fourth station
new um Sakura
biomi uh feel free to loot and
farm yeah yeah okay okay okay um let's
go back to the normal World close behind
yes and stay put no
W yes
wonderful well thank you yeah my job
here is done let's go let's go let's go
to our home yes time to go back home
with my Senai I have a roommate who
gladly will live with me let's
go it's not the prettiest place but um
it looks like the places I would build
in
Minecraft so
simplistic ah oh yeah uh I will show you
the uh last but not least I will show
you the portals um to the new server
basically oh yes we'll go back it's it's
a little bit um to the side of where you
entered from so M I guess we should go
for the Rainbow Bridge again one second
yes m
M so how did you like it I like it it's
very pretty it's nice to see all my
senpai's Minecraft
efforts yeah yeah yeah we we tried our
best you know with our our little
efforts and our big soul and our big
hearts try to make something it's no you
know you know we made lots of pretty
things yeah let's walk let's walk
Walking is healthy
uh we saw hatam my Hogwarts from a
distance it's hard to get up there I
don't know any way of getting up there
without an
elytra and this lady can't fly yet even
though she claims to be a raven or
something I don't claim to I am well
show me show me okay make make a
[Laughter]
sound what wait stop you sound like I
don't know um what the [\h__\h] is
that that sounds so so
Cur you remind that that sound reminds
me of something I'm so sorry oh my God
please listen to takanasi K's M Crow
because they sound I that I love that H
Kermit yeah it has potential to be
Kermit or Stitch Stitch yeah you sound
like
Stitch oh my God how can you attempt to
sound like a bird and you end up
sounding like
Stitch I'm not that
difficult oh my God oh my God God well
look you speak you speak so you have
yeah I'm a I'm a I'm a girl failure so I
don't know what you were expecting from
me
no no no no no don't close your fro so
much no not
listen I can't roll my ARS how are you
doing that of course you can how are you
doing that I can't it's my tongue I'm
not even rolling it the Japanese way I'm
just rolling can't do it anyway I can't
do the German art
either say Kiara
K oh hey you kind of rolled a Japanese
japanesey thank you PR thank you when I
say Ki
Senai say Nissa
Nissa
cof oh yeah wait say it again
uh renc Ren coft oh yeah you can do
it you putting a little bit too much H
HH in there but very Switzer is at the
moment switcher Swit Swit swi switch
switch Swiss I guess
swi do you need a cough drop yes you're
ruining my throat Kiwa wa I'm sorry I'm
sorry I thought you had a like a talent
for this kind of
stuff I'm really bad at accents actually
well okay when I was born as a Raven my
um my tongue was fused to the bottom of
my mouth what yeah they had they had to
cut it like the you know the little line
at the Bott they had to cut it uh so
wait how how fused how would you
describe that uh it's just like that
little you know that little line that
like connect that was just like fused
you know fused as in like I mean it was
still moving right but like could you
perhaps barely they had to they had to
get scissors and cut it so I could use
my tongue
but but you were able to eat right no
that's why that's why I was a really
angry baby because I couldn't eat what
the [\h__\h] that's so interesting because
it's a little bit relatable to
me no
way it's not so bad for me but um I
could probably use some cutting there
really
why it it just it just doesn't it's
just I never talked about this before
but um I I I it just it just doesn't go
out very far M like I'm always
fascinated when when people put out
their tongue and they like and then I I
I I'm so embarrassed about this actually
don't be
embarrassed um like I have troubles even
eating ice cream like normal people do
that's why I just bite ice
cream I see
you've got a very I mean you can get it
cut it'll take time I've heard that
that's that's a possibility but I was
just too embarrassed to go to the
dentist and be like can you don't be
embarrassed see mine actually because my
tongue was just so weird uh I also had a
speech impediment growing up so I
actually had a permanent LIF so when i f
e I fed them like this and when I I
couldn't say ours either I I would say
a so that's why I can't I can't um I
can't learn I I it's really hard for me
to master RS in any other type of
language because I'm like I already I'm
already faking it till I'm making it you
know okay MH you know it's being a raven
was saying why dentist but I was told
that the dentist does it uh I'm pretty
sure anyone who deals with your mouth
will do it so I guess so do you want to
deal with my mouth sure I'll help you
out what's believe that this is another
thing where weate to each other what the
[\h__\h] that's such a random rare thing
yeah we've got a weird weird little
tongue except it seems like yours is
less connected cuz mine had to be cut
pretty soon after I was born or else I
would have
died oh my God we have to talk more
after the stream like about our tongues
we have to discuss our
tongues uh we could we could discuss our
tongues together I'm kidding I'm kidding
I'm kidding one a thing to bond over
yeah too compatible for our own gun for
real oh my God oh my God that's weird I
I
don't yeah let's compare tongues oh my
God I'm going to die
okay I'm so embarrassed like don't be
embarrassed there's nothing to be
embarrassed about no but for real like
it's so bad like um whenever there's a
like a like a for example like a doctor
situation like a dentist for example and
he's like go ah put put out your tongue
and go ah and I'm like I'm doing it and
and I'm like I can't go any furever but
he's like more more and I'm like what
the [\h__\h] I can't go any further and I
can't even say anything oh no yeah know
just bring it up next time just say hey
I cuz I mean some people some people do
it solely for the ability to stick their
tongue out further like you know those
people who can stick their tongue out
like really really grossly far like
aochi Maru from Nar that's that's I find
that kind of disgusting though me too
that's unary you you don't have to do it
that much but you could be like hey I
literally can't I'm my tongue is very
fused could you please help me could you
please just trim it a little bit keep in
mind though because it is in your mouth
it
will it will take some time to heal and
it will be really
uncomfortable I'm too scared to do it no
give it a try give it a
try give it a try so you can eat ice
cream
like you
know
well yeah trim my tongue no not trimming
the tongue trimming the thing underneath
you ever you ever think about getting
your tongue split have you seen people
who do that that's so disgusting you
think so I don't no that's so E I saw
like in the video I saw someone showing
that off like a snake right I'm like E I
don't think I could ever do that just
cuz like I like having one tongue I
can't imagine having two yeah that's
that's that's some kinky [\h__\h] man like
you you go do your kinky stuff but like
why why else would you do it if not for
some kinky stuff the athetic I know I
know someone who has a split tongue and
they just do it for fun it it just makes
them happy a it freaks me out like
seeing it like there's certain things
that I I when I look at them they will
make me feel sick to the stomach I'm so
sorry but that's one of the things um
that's okay it's okay poor it's okay my
not split so I will you can look at my
tongue and you'll be you'll see one big
beautiful pink pink tongue great it's
[Laughter]
great oh I I am wow I
didn't anyways we need we need to go
through we need to go through we wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait there's
two different ones um but I like
basically this leads to the new world
oh isn't this to the new connected one
that
you yeah I think that should be where
you want to go where is
this this is this is the combined server
as far as I know I'm pretty sure the
other one leads to the same to the same
one just like that the that leads to the
Japan World I think but it might just be
Wait no that's the old Japan World down
there is the old Japan world but you can
B basically wait wait if you go through
here M and then you look up here there's
the I world and then there's Japan World
and then there's ID world you think
you're already in Japan world but this
is I think the old Japan World m is it
yeah yeah oh yeah
wow this is another huge thing to look
at lots of History here
too yeah yeah yeah so these are the all
the old ones and we're now in the
combined one well I you want to find I
need to go back to the
here yeah oh the other one because the
the one through the through here because
that's where that's where the rest of
Advent will spawn I'm going to have to
lead them here oh okay cuz this brings
us back yeah
look see this is where we went
in wait then you were in the this is
where we spawned in when we opened up
the game this is the old one right this
is the old one oh you were hanging out
on the old one
were we okay well I now that I know next
time I can lead them I can lead them
yeah I mean there's a lot of history
here but I don't think anybody uses it
anymore do they uh so yeah now you know
how to get to the to all to everything
basically yay and
congratulations is it up here oh
wow the portal okay good okay nice yeah
well I will stay there because I am like
maybe maybe I am a contrarian I don't
know but I like to stay where I am no no
that's valid I'll stay here just so I
can lead Advent into the Ian and and
other
service yes you know I'm not the only
one who would be happy about it I think
fauna would be mildly happy about it you
know I'm excited to see fauna's world
tree I need to ask her to show it to me
yeah oh yeah wait what tree the one
she's bu
I know but isn't that that's in a new
server right I think
so yeah she needs she needs me to help
her cuz I asked if I could build a nest
there
too because I'm you know I'm a
bird you would be nesting in in both of
your oshi's homes then I well just so
you know you know just little extra
extra places that I can sleep as I'ma
traversing about you know I guess so I I
guess that's fine
perhaps do you not have multiple houses
kiaba
Senpai uh do do I I mean I have one in
the Japan the old Japan server because
it was gifted to me but I don't use it
and you know I am I am loyal to my roots
baby I
see you're so
cute I don't want everybody to leave
these memories behind I know what you
mean so try to be in both okay okay I
will try to make time in
both Yes sounds good what hope you
enjoyed the tour I did thank you for
giving me a tour Senai never forget
about Phoenix and also wait can you um
you didn't leave a sign but I can write
for you what you would say I'll I can do
it next
time no say tell me I'm I'm writing
right
now what was your impression I will
write it down pretty but uh pretty but
um needs work
unfinished
okay
wow ner cute ner like nauy NY n NY nauy
CH CU I ran I ran out of but let me
delete
this
um wait what [\h__\h] h i missed how can you
not go back ah uh pretty but un
unfinished needs
work and
then there
is that is such an underwhelming
feedback so sad it's so nice but there's
also there's just a lot of things that
you know you're like this isn't finished
well this one isn't finished but well
well that's mostly good that's mostly
good though she left a big impression on
you huh yeah I get she did there's a lot
of stuff wait there wasn't so much
unfinished stuff was
there this is we're going to build a
Haba house together kiata okay okay but
for now let's let's say goodbye and stop
stop our streams yeah yeah that's fine
I'll go cook I'll be cooking uh does one
notice I'm moving balers gate to
tomorrow instead because my my stuff
didn't arrive my camping stuff didn't
arrive so I can't film tomorrow guys so
I'll be streaming tomorrow good luck
yeah in baldi's Gate thank you bal's
galate let's go go go yeah and you are
streaming too to later or no right later
no tomorrow we're streaming all together
with Advent again we're going to be
doing a Japanese lesson mcft no um why
not Minecraft because of we had to
reschedule to next week because all of
us were already booked up a so it'll be
on F's
channel are they teaching you I thought
so they're going to be teaching ad most
proficient ones well I found out shot is
actually pretty good at Japanese too and
I'm really confused she never mentioned
it what yeah she just was sitting there
and she just like on stream randomly
just perfectly read something just
started talking Japanese and resp and I
was like what the [\h__\h] I was like she
what you don't mention this need to
investigate interesting oh sudden sudden
hidden Japanese she's hiding her full
power she's not unleashing it yet yeahum
she's scary I love her wow then maybe
she will have all the answers tomorrow I
know she's going to like meanwhile
everyone thinks I'm good at Japanese
when I suck and then like she is going
to come out and be like um actually I
love
wow okay I I want I'm interested in how
how you will do and how sh will do don't
don't look forward to it I'm bad I'm
bad speaking of I need to go do my
Japanese
lesson oh is it happening now it'ses FY
it's just I just need to do my Japanese
flash cards for the day so I can get
practice yes yes okay thank you guys for
watching our Minecraft cab yes thank you
for
coming and yeah little little trip down
memory line is that how you say it
Memory Lane yep Memory Lane yes Memory
Lane H yeah and so uh more Minecraft
maybe soon maybe maybe yep no we can get
the we can get the wings yes yes and
hopefully next time you and Advent can
check out uh everything yes success f it
should be good I think bi's internet is
already fixed so okay wonderful and
thank you guys for
watching and in Germany we say AV Z and
in Nissa we say
byebye
byee byebye byebye guys see you in
Ballers
guide stream
pineapp yes stream stream pineapple
stream POV stream Kyoto's music or else
please this is a threat this is a threat
indeed no just a please just just a just
a polite polite pushing you to listen to
good
music yeah thank
you it's in my description chat okay
okay byebye
[Music]
byebye