[Music]
so
is in us voice nice
hello my name is
the audio say something
hello i'm driving today
yes bring your license uh a bit too
small
inaudible okay okay okay how how about
now
wow wow wow wow
well today these professional drivers
and then and then we'll show everyone
the code okay okay okay
and everyone can join us chaotic driving
here this is a warm-up okay this one
doesn't count
it's a warm-up
oh we're going for the ice ice ice i
never i
never owned that road before i think
do you know that oh you're on a bike
i've done this a couple of times
okay here we go
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no i'm taking the first spot again
i've been practicing this isn't how it's
supposed to be
i have not been practicing by the way
i can't even see
oh i'm gonna show you the german driving
skills that i learned on the german
autobahn
i'll show you the power of paco
i don't know if octopus or taco is
allowed to drive but
don't worry about it they're so far away
oh no why is it so far away
it's my training i i went to the
training art kiara
yeah actually i just took a nap so i'm a
bit slow yet
okay this is my next slime that's the
sign i'm fine
[Music]
by the way we are we are driving against
each other and
against the people who are going to join
the room right
yes yes yes not just us we're gonna give
you the code
in a bit after this one this is a
warm-up
we gotta warm up
i don't believe you this is why you
gotta practice
kiara why can't i drift
i can't drift anymore
oh my god initial taco
yes yes yes
[Music]
you gotta learn to drift read read the
air oh it's trying oh i got a crown
okay okay let's show everyone the code
okay
okay three two
one wait i don't have any chance oh can
you see
one coat yeah yeah once i need to
okay this there you go friends
one one nine zero zero three one five
but inaudible
three let's work together again to
reveal against
the voice okay
yes yes yes
you know you and me together okay
because they're so strong okay we don't
have a chance against them if we also
fight each other we gotta work together
okay here they're coming oh
i like rainbow road oh my god no please
no don't choose you gotta choose
no no god no not rainbow
oh my god no that has the worst
that's the worst road ever no
don't do that to me i mean oh no
oh no rainbow road is the majority what
are we gonna do
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
i'm gonna fall off the cliff at least 50
times
okay i believe in you believe in me who
believes in you oh by the way
if everyone could be so fair to to leave
the room once they participated
one time please thank you so that as
many people as possible can join
you
now
oh
why did we choose this road
it's cause i went too fast i went too
fast
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's why i told you not to choose this
road
i mean we would have still
gotten you know
did you really think we have a chance on
this one
oh you never know hello
i don't know i gotta
i don't know
i need i need driving lessons oh my god
[Music]
no no no i
am literally driving off every single
curve
this one is hard
but it's colorful i like the colors dude
get out the way
what i believe in you oh really
oh wait i can't i can't tell which one
you are there's like there's like
multiple of the things
well
[Music]
um
okay not bad not bad not bad i feel like
i should
um
[Music]
my number 12. come on oh by the way
i want to give a shout out to an artist
called
ninomaya inanes who did the thumbnail
she is she's literally speech she did it
in what an hour or less 40 minutes or
something
right after my previous stream
she is sweet
oh hey the people actually left except
two people who are sleeping or something
but i respect everyone you lie
[Music]
next time please leave you youtube
people who fade in
oh god the gamer is here that's good see
gamer you little
oh it's just the same one oh yeah
someone looks like me
hello you look cute orange person
but it's only such why are we so few
maybe not everyone should have left
where is everyone
you guys can join in again later okay
everyone who just left you can join in
again
mario circuit yay
are those npcs yeah i think so
okay i can't win against npcs
npcs are no problem
i don't know i usually use that pieces a
lot of times
cry again
i'm dressing up
yes i should be using tilt control right
uh i'm not kill controls are better
are they tilt controls are superior
are they they are yeah
whoa i'm number seven nice
but you like them for free right now wow
[Music]
and then everyone you know
who left their winter wheels here in the
middle of the road
i thought you were bad at this game you
disappoint me i practiced this
i told you i had to forget i was doing
that
so i practiced damn that's something i
should be doing
no i'm fine what stupid npc
taking away
[Music]
winning against npcs is the real
challenge
[Music]
what wait don't that's not you that's
kfc
your employee my employees are i mean if
my employees win
i will take that as a win for me as well
even though they're grabbing against me
but i'll take it as a win for me
you aren't very good aha thank you
comments
what do you mean i'm not good what do
you mean
i'm number 10 okay no as long as you're
not lost
you're okay what the hell is behind me
two of my own people your workers
are behind me they actually i think i
saw them stopping on the road
you two
are you gonna lower their race i mean
you're they're pay
if they uh are no they're fired they're
fired
if they if they don't let me win they're
fired but v gamer and kfp
you can stay in the race
[Laughter]
you're doing a good job but i have a
feeling that now that i trust them
next next race they will they will um go
behind my back and win against me again
okay don't don't let her win guys
we gotta i mean i mean uh let's let her
win
we got a we got a um uh
yeah corporate car yes us two
yeah us two yes yes yes yes of course of
course
of course i'm using two controls
let's see that's it i'm the only one who
controls
chose the airport i just deserved
one luigi's mansion twisted mentioned
well that's basically
not sure if i remember this one tacoma
that one is called takomori
where are the taco nashes
i like that main combination
oh the shortcut oh hello thank you for
telling me
god damn it i got a coffee remember yes
very much
[Music]
well that star must be you yep it's not
anymore though
no two items again
why couldn't i go up there
race against npcs
[Music]
oh
it's so slow you know the big
the big plant thingy yeah it's useless
everyone's bumping into me eh
[Laughter]
oh there's a blue shell coming but not
for me because i'm not number one
i can't speak english every time i play
mario kart i lose all my english words
don't worry i do too
[Music]
we need to study english we should go to
calikaiba
we should go to english licensure
oh yes
in front of me or something i know you
should now wait
you should go number one
you should be number one what the hell
yes number one when
come on let's do a number one rta
okay who gets number one first
i got kicked out
oh wait i think it's the settings oh
[Music]
i'm pretty much back in again i think oh
okay
okay okay i think i think searching for
players
i got one right next to me
are you in the room uh i'm
going in now oh
oh i'm sorry oh i'm in i'm in i've been
but you're not there oh communication
error has occurred ah the width
good here we make the room maybe maybe
i have a room called speed do you want
to enter the room speed i made it before
it should be working
everyone let's let inna join first okay
please
it's 0 9 8 7.
wait i'm i can't get out of here okay
i'll communicate there okay okay
okay
uh i hope it works though
okay how about you write it down for me
and then i will
enter it okay i will like um
do not join yet it will be fine okay
okay okay um
they can they can follow some rules they
can obviously not follow the rule to let
me win
but they should be able to follow this
run rule
i'm joining uh it's currently closed
do you want to what
yeah whatever join speed yes
speech okay
yes this is fine
okay i'll change the code in my stream
okay
yes you drew in a swimsuit before could
you please draw me too in the swimsuit
okay if you win against me
i will draw you in okay okay
like in the next win against yeah but
there's like two or two
or three friends
[Music]
oh god you're in like a different room
no are you
are you no
you're in the same room but in a
different dimension yeah this just
happens because you know
i'm hooking people yeah
well i mean
okay okay we'll do it one more time i
will make a room
okay and then you can join before
before everyone else
okay yeah you can leave it i will make a
new room
sorry about that
[Music]
we know nothing about this game
we were like i literally picked it up
again because of the stream
before before today's spring like five
minutes before we were like wait
which mode should we use multiplayer
online yeah
it's all the same
maybe there's a different way to do it
how do i leave
this race oh you can put a skimmer on me
okay okay then
then i will show you my road rage
show me your german road rage this
is
[Music]
um
a driver's license like in real life you
know
uh i have a learner i learned
i couldn't drive i can drive but i need
someone with a natural license
so someone like me
i will let you know this code
[Music]
it's a horrible race between uh some
some nice people who are trying to stay
behind and me
they're so nice there's no way that
those people are
as bad as me so they're honestly very
kind
they respect this majestic phoenix
they're following the speed limit
let's just stay behind friends oh finish
okay i need to get out of here
someone here is called watson achillia
watson what is that
in i can't wink anymore for some reason
go on i don't know
i'm drawing i used to be able to link so
well
okay i gave you the code okay
uh let's see who's faster me or you know
when you're in
okay no i didn't i didn't update the
code yet on my stream but they're seeing
it as as i'm typing it they're saying it
okay
did you change some settings uh
i changed it because like last time it
like shuffled people after a few runs
oh but now it's uh yeah
okay i hope that hit that like button
voluntarily okay
okay okay and so they were forced to
leave
huh yeah after four runs yeah
but now people gotta leave by their own
will okay
well i mean please just don't stay
focused with you you see me
okay wonderful very good
here we go again here we go
now okay i will win this race and if i
win then
i i can't see you against you then i
don't
get to get me and you will drown me in
the sexiest swimsuit
[Music]
to find sexy
well i mean anything that i'm wearing i
will make sexy just because of my
existence
because i'm a sexy chicken suit
no please no please don't look
weren't we talking about like wearing
halloween costumes and then everyone
kept linking you like a chicken
please no i don't wanna be the chicken
costume
[Music]
please no someone i saw someone uh
do a a halloween costume fan art of me
and kelly though
and they drew me as a as a devil like a
red devil and it looked so cool
why does that keep on happening anyway
it looks so cool
i bought the game like ages ago but i
never started playing
yeah i'm uh i'm really bad with like
open world games because i'm directly
challenged i'm just like
wow you seem to find your way today um
oh there's only one way to go
no well sometimes there's other ways
like
i'm 12. i'm so proud of me
i cannot fight for that swimsuit fan art
guys help me don't you want to see me in
the swimsuits run by inna
oh no come on think about it okay
what do you think about it who doesn't
want to see it oh dear
damn it
i mean after that you can bully me again
let's go drift this
race we have to win okay kfc
[Laughter]
[Music]
no no applesauce what the hell don't you
want to see me in the swimsuit
yeah don't we all want to see me in this
book i actually also really want to see
inna in a sunset
there's not much to see
[Music]
please mercy who left their banana on
the road who was it
sorry of me i think
oh my god why are you second why wait
are you second no i'm fifth i'm
fifth okay okay it's someone else that
looks like me okay
a bullet
spin come on
don't worry so well i like this
no oh no
my dream of my swimsuit
[Music]
[Applause]
no i'm not doing this on purpose by the
way i'm not driving so bad on purpose
believe
where's your german drawings um
i love them in germany okay how about we
do this how about
you win any of the games today any of
the games
any of the games okay i'll get any of
easy you mean win them against you right
not again not against me
against me against me any of the games
you have a lot of chances you gotta make
it count okay
yo not everyone has to leave because it
feels like not everyone
not it's not filling up that well but
let's see okay okay okay everyone's
getting full control
um that's it what a shame
[Laughter]
health control health controls
here we go gotta fight for your swimsuit
okay
it's isn't it sad like uh at least um
in the land where i currently and which
by the way uh it's public now so don't
you don't worry japan oh thank you apple
sauces thank you for the super chat
and the summer ended so quick quickly
this year
oh and that made me really sad so i
would love to see myself in the swimsuit
well if anything you'll get yourself in
a spring suit
no i refuse oh please no
i want the cute you can't win you're
gonna be in a chicken suit okay
why does this go how do you speed in the
beginning again wasn't it
that starts speeding on number two
[Music]
it hasn't worked all day someone has
hacked my cart
someone has wrapped into the gate
oh i can't see
who did this with my with my with my
what it's not a card though it's a
what
[Music]
wow english skills always some point
when i play mario kart
how about we speak some german
[Music]
uh oh no i fell out yes
by the
[Music]
this might be the race this might be the
race where i oh no
is that
[Music]
[Applause]
here
[Music]
well you can do that too if you really
wanna oh that's true
can you make it like actually i noticed
that in today's funko art he gave me a
helmet
that kind of looks like a chicken head
anything you got to say about that
i mean you saw chicken right yeah
guys
oh how did the tables turn
how
you can do it like in a drawing stream
okay
i don't know about youtube couldn't be
nice what i trust
since you're not getting banned and
you're showing so much
non non-existent cleavage so okay maybe
maybe if i draw chickens to tiara
youtube won't burn me chicken soup
i can't believe this is this is not what
no seriously i won
swimsuit not not chicken sauce
what about chicken swimsuit huh
no no no no no
i want it to be sexy or cute
sexy chicken
i know you love me you're not the type
to bully me
um flamingo flamingo
oh good bird i like flamingos
but i mean it can be it can't it can be
a
a swimsuit with a flamingo pattern
okay what about
kitchen i really like pigeons
but i don't want to be in a pigeon suit
i want the swimsuit i wanted favorite
square okay i mean the kfc
employees might have helped they might
have helped but
not my engines oh i like the music on
this one
oh there's dirt everywhere my employees
well i did hire a lot of people much
more than i
actually needed to get the store going
now i have so many people working for me
that i just sit back and look
i turned on the the friend request
receiving uh just to add ina
and now i'm getting some requests from
kfc workers again yeah
stop friending me we are
our relationship is different it's uh
it's uh
your boss and it's employees okay yeah
would you add
would you add your boss on mario kart
would you add jagger on mario kart
actually yes i would
okay um different argument
we need to play against jago oh
i feel like y'all will be really good at
minecraft nah
i doubt it i doubt it he's only good at
tattoos
he's really good at tetris
did you see his hatred skills
oh when he was playing against tv yeah
yeah
he's like always like
amy what's going on you know what's
going on
are you lying laughs okay go get
me
for the kfb empire
channeling my inner cali with my gas
[Music]
[Applause]
why are we the only two ones if a
japanese flag even don't like i mean i'm
in japan
well well two swimsuits for me two
swimsuits
no okay one is fine what the hell is
that face on that
on that on that peculiar fan standing
next to me
so tiny why not it's beautiful it's
beautiful and deep
beautiful i think i saw that one before
and in pakoras
[Music]
wouldn't it be crazy if suddenly the
real peculiar would show up
we're the real peck you get distracted
oh i mean that would be fine for me i
already won my swimsuits
she's she's not in here right i think it
was up her name was i think
only um
[Music]
streaming at nine o'clock today so in 15
minutes so they have nothing to do right
now
okay
have fun but let me win
no that's not me to me
to us after all
we're a team right
[Music]
hello man
i'm just driving safely and i hope you
put your seat belt
huh did you put your seat belt on yes
i have my helmet my seatbelt
everything very good
i have speed
you better not throw those fireballs at
me
let my guard down
last round
[Music]
you're a bit far behind okay
so
[Music]
i'm getting better i'm getting better i
was just uh in the beginning i was bad
because i didn't practice before this
time
[Music]
it would be a different story oh you
want to do a one-on-one
you want to do one-on-one huh huh huh
let's take it outside ina you and me
outside that's right
okay our last game is gonna be a
one-on-one
you can do that let's see let's see what
you can do without your workers
[Laughter]
[Music]
no don't take my kfc workers away from
me they're all
okay amazing of course number one is
some is a peculiar event
upon
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes yes blame everyone
blame that health control paint control
did you choose yourself to paint
[Music]
the pain controls they're not working
let's see what we get tilt controls more
like tilted
[Music]
here we go petra kfp petra
petra from foreigners are really really
like
mario kart yeah i told them to change
the name so i can recognize them
oh i didn't finally for the first time
in today's stream i've managed to
speed up in the beginning first time
how was it that hard to do that
can't be showing me the driving skills
oh here it is this housing music
everyone's
[Music]
like
[Laughter]
i am
[Music]
uh left the map wasn't you kiara it's
okay
yeah it was me
just gotta do what a ghost gotta do you
know
it's just the job of the ghost
by the way did you see i'm having a off
collab with nana tomorrow
[Music]
you have the weirdest sleep schedule
ever
don't worry about it yes i see you
oh i have a blue sound truck feels so
slippery
don't leave me with that thingy you got
in your hand no
that's right you gotta go fast
oh i'm so slippery
[Music]
that's right
for stopping right at the at the
finishing line to let me become number
11.
not last oh here we are
baby pike here we go please stop rainbow
right now
it did not go well for you why did you
do this to yourself why did you choose
rainbow road
you fell out if i'm gonna suffer i'm not
going down alone
rainbow road everyone you guys wanna see
kira suffer
i already suffered enough yes you do
kfb workers it's it's your chance to get
back at her
for all the time she threatened to fire
you
the thing is though i fired them i fired
them already
so many times but they keep applying
again
yeah they keep coming back so i think
they enjoy it
no all according to plan god damn it
god damn it
[Laughter]
this is the sixth race
[Music]
gonna set a record
oh well it's going all right it's going
all right i'm not
falling off yet someone just went up
yeah i did meet her
i spoke to you soon oh why is it so
slippery today
and again number two
wow did you ena do you
do you produce eggs
uh no i'm human oh really
looking human out of all of us okay
chad is counting how many times i'm i'm
falling off i already lost him
why am i number twelve
[Music]
you cannot be friends with your boss
don't send me friend requests
[Music]
would have been a better answer for them
oh
at least i start when i get into the
finishing line thanks guys
thank you thanks for waiting
i was 100 gonna be number 12 but but
admiral and item has waited for me
come on you gotta make her suffer that's
close
it doesn't even matter because like
i'm already so bad
if i would be higher if i would be like
sixth or fifth or something that would
matter but but
if i'm this low it doesn't even matter
yes baby baby rude come on
there's so much favorite no but it
sounds easy rude
it sounds easy oh baby steps
baby checks
look here i think after this one is it
gonna be our 1v1
yes okay okay you ready
yes thanks for the super chat thank you
i don't know how i deserve them but
thank you well they're paying me my
salary
mine got chosen first yours now mine
so many so many kfp workers
this is unfair now they work against me
mostly so don't worry are you sure about
that
i'm not only like sure about that
there's only like two people who waited
for me at the end
[Music]
is
he slowed down to hit me with those
shells or maybe
maybe he was not trying to hurt me but
he didn't hurt me
and ghost
[Music]
no
oh
just like one lap where are you where
are you
i already already went no
look for those four that are behind me
they all waited for me
everyone's doing following the rules
today
wow oh god everyone's following the
rules okay are we going out okay
you ready okay yeah yeah bye guys we
gotta do it one-on-one thanks for the
games guys thanks thanks bank we gotta
one-on-one how do we do one-on-one
through friends and rivals is that what
we need to do yeah
um
i think yeah
yep oh no maybe not no no that's not in
one versus oh create a room create room
okay i'll make a room
and you can come in go to go to like
friends
and then you'll you'll see my name
and then you can click my name and you
should be able to join ah
nice okay
um chet do you have any recommendations
for a wheel
i think i need to change something like
how about monster wheels or
100 or 150 150
okay 150 normal items
no come all vehicles oh 48 races
four races i guess okay
yes
i'm explaining the rules what what's
happening
whatever i'm taking this
i'm ready random it's random again
no teams normal items no cpu all
vehicles four races
wow enough oh we're doing four races
okay
oh okay well we can just do one and then
call it
which one do you want to do i i just was
random
so it's fair and square oh yeah okay
okey dokey what will it be you
and me against each other phoenix versus
oh i like this supposedly a human
that is supported by the ancient ones i
am human
oh that then there's my super mario 64.
uh
clock thingy i love that one
how did you miss it hey i'm number two
wow that's not bad
content
is
[Music]
the one and only number one
yours truly potential piano
[Music]
i don't want i have to keep money
holding that
i don't want to have it on my ass
oh what
[Music]
yes
i
gotta be careful just gotta be careful
just gotta be careful because
[Music]
energy
uh
people are going to doubt if i really
speak german now
we're so close no are you trying to hit
me with that boomerang
that was close that was so cool it was
close
it was oh i slipped up there huh that
was close
i i think we are 50 50. we are
both bad drivers let's be real
yeah yeah i agree with that okay
well thank you for driving against me or
with me
in whichever way you want to see it
it was fun you know i don't know i felt
like kfp versus taco bell
taco bell oh my god never thought of
that i never thought of that
do you want to collab with me kfb and
taco bell
um depends we gotta figure out the
details in the
exact contract and so on how many
coupons are we talking
all the cute coupons lifetime coupons
yes
[Music]
thank you very much for today and
i'll see you soon yes um
do you have any awesome yes
number one swimsuit kiara coming soon
that is extra that's an excellent oh we
gotta we gotta
oh that's it okay communication error
between us two
never something like that would never
happen number two
uh in exactly uh 19
out hours no way
18 hours from now
at three o'clock uh three o'clock
japanese standard time
and i'm having the
i think everyone already knows but i'm
having a collaboration with nanda where
we're doing an
off collab karaoke concert and we are
the
everyone has a free entry ticket but you
know how
you know free entry kfp
people still pay me my salary thank you
just kidding anyway everyone is welcome
to
but you know you're gonna get a vip seat
yay yang did i get a backstage pass
yes yes yes yes of course yeah you can
you can also sit on the stage if you
want
to take a seat on the stage hold our
microphones
yay all right do you have anything to
say
um i'll just like to say uh
thanks for being with me today oh we
just
we just did uh 400k oh yeah
[Music]
i feel like every time i hit a milestone
i'm with someone
[Music]
oh i'm so happy for you 400 yes yes
yes yes mm-hmm maybe
maybe i can be there for four years too
oh yeah we can drive off
how about driving driving to 400k oh
yeah
yay okay
can i say my my german bye bye
yes do you do you have a well done
you'll have a bite um
no i want to see bye-bye okay
okay then
[Music]
bye
you