[Music]
foreign
good morning afternoon evening everyone
it is Taco Time hi
and it is also
my birthday
hi how's everyone doing today
laughs
for all the birthday
[Music]
birthday oh I'm so nervous
yo every time my birthday rolls around
I'm like ah it's just it's just another
day everything's gonna be the same but
literally like 10 minutes before I start
the stream I start like my heart starts
breathing real fast I'm just like oh my
goodness it's my birthday
thank you thank you everyone
oh my goodness and also sorry
um I have to apologize this dream not to
be uh delayed by two hours
yeah
um there were some scheduling things I
had to sort out and it was decided two
hours after the originally planned the
stream it's probably the best time so
yeah thank you thanks for joining me
today how are you guys still alive
you sacrificed your sleep all day you
ah
man
it's my birthday it's my birthday
I'm going older
so
um today's stream is a little different
as you can tell that uh my microphone
sounds a little more echoey and more
more I'm I'm out of breath it's because
I'm standing up the reason for that is
we're gonna bake a cake together that's
right
I was just gonna be lazy and order a
cake but I realized you know special
occasion it's our uh third birthday
together you know so we're gonna bake a
cake together and yeah I'm three years
old whoa
and I got a new mic set up so even if I
walk away from
being right in front of the camera you
can still hear me very clearly oh let me
just open this thing
yeah now I can move around professional
streamer Now isn't that great after
three years I finally figured it out
[Music]
finally after three years
yeah I got one of those like nice uh
clip odd microphones I've seen them
using the in the cover Studio you know I
took some notes for my own setup and uh
one of the uh reason so I'm actually
kind of nervous is because
the stream is gonna be my very first
time turning on the hand cam
and I might have to stop the hand cam in
the middle a little bit because it's
running on my camera is running on
battery
I didn't realize uh there wasn't a
different what should I say uh outlet
for the power versus plug it into my
computer so
um I ordered the the thing I can connect
it to the power source but it's it
didn't arrive on time before well let's
see if I can remember how to turn this
on this new technology you know
very difficult okay that's working
hold on maybe I should do this
okay and then there's that
and then I do this and then this
okay
uh
okay this should work this should work
they don't
the taco cab is back they use the ones
for Mario Kart but it's back
are you guys ready
hi
[Music]
hello I'm bringing like two layers of
gloves
it's my hand oh my goodness it's my hand
my is that my right hand or my left hand
it's my right hand I think the camera is
reversed
it's fine and see I even got a candle
for us I don't know if you can see it
but is it this way this way this way
it's gonna be our third
backwards the camera's backwards
hold on I can fix this
horizontal flip
where is it transform flip horizontal
there you go
this way oh yeah it's this way yeah
[Music]
it's gonna be our third birthday
together so I got a three it's a candle
yeah
Paco is e years old exactly
oh I should have probably like connected
the camera the other way so that
hello Ina how are you today oh I'm doing
great I heard it was your birthday today
oh yes it's my birthday oh happy
birthday thank you
but yes I can I can uh finally show you
guys progress of my cooking and by that
I mean I bought a I bought a cake mix
and we're gonna use the cake mix
so I'll probably be in voice chat as
well so some of the members will be
dropping in and out if they if they want
to visit but uh yeah hopefully we can
bake the cake of course any
baking stream first thing we gotta do is
preheat the oven
to uh
325 for dark or non-stick pan
foreign
where's my oven here's my oven
you can't see the oven but it's here
uh
I know how I know how to use this bake
okay maybe gloves not working with this
ah there you go uh three 25.
uh
start
is it working it says preheating
[Music]
I think it's working
oven light
come on
preheating good
oh difficult yeah let me just uh hop on
into voice chat for a bit
I'll just uh
yeah
starting out
and join whenever
okay hopefully I said everything
correctly
okay that's set that's set
I'll be here okay we're good
all right okay I have to open the box so
that's all for now
oh
wow
happy birthday
thank you
you keep on getting cut off for me
thanks to Discord
traffic
I can fix this
you can fix it
I don't know I'll just speak loudly hi
okay that helped I think though okay
okay good hi and yeah you're gonna bake
a cake I am are you what kind of cake
yeah what kind of cake are you making
uh just like uh what's it it's like a
french vanilla cake mix I'm gonna make
some whipped cream and then put some
strawberries and peaches and blueberries
on it
you know what's good yeah you know the
cake I got you in Japan I keep thinking
about it because it's so good
oh that was yum that was wonderful
to make a cake like that I think you
have to get a lot of practice in so from
today you will practice bake caking
caking bake what cake bake cake baking
cake yeah
so how are you on this wonderful day I'm
doing good I was very nervous because
it's my first hand cam but so far so
good
been there it's been like almost three
years and this is your first hand chem
stream I know I was so nervous to do it
but I bought everything to do it now
let's go
can you do something with in a hand can
you give us a heart a heart
around
yeah
what else can we do with uh oh do you
have like do you you don't happen to
have all all your takodatsu Plushies are
tiny aren't they a big I mean they're
all big and the and the one small one
that I have is like at my parents place
because
[Music]
but
okay I mean that's really only for you
viewers because I'm not I mean you know
I'm not a taco that's it
but I'm doing it for you guys are in my
chat you're talking yeah
[Laughter]
oh cute cute oh
oh wow it's The Strokes of a pro
okay it's backwards on stream I think it
looks so happy
[Music]
what's going on
you seem a bit uh needy recently in yeah
come visit me in Europe come on oh maybe
maybe I do want to go to Europe someday
yeah
well my doors are open okay Europe
stores are open it's easy to come to
Europe I'm gonna go eat all the food
there
food
I can cook for you too you know you know
I might cook a lot I've been seeing all
your food pictures you post and I'm just
like man
what's sealer
what's your favorite comfort food
besides like you know cup noodles
something that people can actually like
cook something proper
or Japanese Curry or different kind of
Curry
and it can occur honestly Japanese Curry
is pretty comfortable I think yeah
okay
yeah I've made Japanese Curry before
it's pretty easy so yeah no problem I
would like to make something even more
special for you but if you have people
for curry then I'll make a curry oh
but I'll have to make two different
curries because yours has to be egg
let's see
there's always like an option to get
spicy so I'll just get it spicy yeah
okay
but with like the jalapeno topping yeah
okay well I hope that maybe in some time
in the near future maybe we'll get to
see enough ready birthday live we may be
hopeful I mean it's being worked on it's
just we're not certain when exactly it's
gonna be yeah so we're still working on
it I'm still working I'll I'll be there
when it really happens
okay thank you until then time to bake a
cake and celebrate possibly at home
right yeah time to be
fun India thank you happy birthday to
you
good night good night bye bye
[Music]
hello hello
how are you
hello I'm Remy yeah I think this chord
is using the wrong mic or something it
sounds so different than how you stand
on stream oh mine is different because
it's the it's the lavalier mic I mean
it makes sense I can still understand
you though happy birthday
thank you
have you been
uh
pretty good Emma all right I missed I
miss you know hanging out I miss you too
I sometimes think back to the night we
had the okonomiyaki oh
yeah that was really nice I think about
that too pretty often
such a nice memory yeah so wait were you
gonna bake cake yeah see I have some
the cake mix actually not just the
flower
oh no those are the best
yeah honestly though
I I saw the um the gluten-free version
of I thought of you I was like I'm gonna
eat this cake you know they don't taste
that bad they're they're pretty good
yeah yeah gluten-free cake mix is really
good I got it before or made it before
yeah yeah oh and I I kind of baked you
kick two so I'm gonna send you something
okay okay
here you go
it's uh
might not really be able to eat it
but I don't know I think they'll be
happy if I eat it honestly
take a little slice out of its brain
oh double like oh yes thank you please
eat
thank you wise you know for eating us
this didn't work as intended but oh
but it's fine yeah
thank you is that a candle or
firecracker maybe it's gonna explode or
something
I like your glasses you know oh thank
you do you want one really
yeah I can make different colors too
probably that would be so cool no I mean
it's not my birthday so I shouldn't
receive it it might be just you know you
know if you go to birthday parties you
get like the oh goodies okay party favor
yeah yeah yeah
I'll get your glasses oh sweet
yes
okay
not right now obviously I'm looking
forward to uh your your announcements or
something who knows
yes maybe
oh yeah maybe maybe not guys I mean I
have merged that's one announcement so
oh oh my God she announced it right now
oh
sorry I can't see it until like an hour
or so now everybody knows so we always
have merge usually on these occasions
bye
[Music]
family Chihuahua
he's so cute I miss them much very very
much also where did the cake mix box go
I need the instructions they throw it
out
I did not
uh
oh there it is
what happens right when I'm talking or
like Emma I'm like on the phone I'm
doing something I leave something
somewhere and then I forget about it
so okay
um
I need
250 milliliters of water or milk I
bought milk for the occasion so I'll use
that
where's my measuring cup after this
150.
right okay 250.
[Music]
you like I haven't baked properly in so
long
I mean as long as the the pan like the
cake comes off the pan nicely I think
that's probably the best
okay the 250 milliliters of milk into
the cake mix
wow
okay
it's in
ah
oil I need
125 milliliters or half a cup why have
vegetable oil
uh
uh uh
ah
I guess this will work
okay 125.
125 or half a cup right half a cup half
a cup
okay half a cup
that's a lot of oil
but I guess like when you cook or I
guess bake you put a lot of butter and
stuff it's probably like half a cup of
butter to see okay vegetable oil in
and then three eggs
okay now this is gonna be a challenge
because I need to crack open these eggs
with my gloves on
I have to make sure the shelves if there
is shells that they don't get in the
thing with jig
so I'll do this
uh okay maybe this is not big enough
I'll use
uh I guess I can use uh I'll use this
okay I'll use a dish
I'll crack it in there
I used to know how to crack eggs with
one hand but I forgot the skill now kind
of unfortunate
okay
barely I won't mess this up in my gloves
well maybe I should take off my gloves
for this I don't know I don't want to
mess up I mean I can wash the gloves but
you know what let's do it
it's all over the gloves
it's fine it's fine
haha
yeah it's too late now we're just gonna
we're just gonna accept the fact
and own it oh
this is a disaster actually no no shell
has been in the
dish that I'm using Okay three eggs one
more
just add the gloves to the cake I don't
think that's how it works yeah
I don't want my cake to be
tasting like gloves
ah okay three eggs in
maybe I can wash these gloves are they
waterproof
they're not waterproof I have a hamster
right now
[Music]
oh the rules of cooking with gloves
Clean Hands Clean Hands All Good Clean
Hands
[Music]
okay I got three eggs should I whisk
them first I want there
maybe
I'll whisk them a little bit at least to
break down the yolk
I don't think you're supposed to but I'm
gonna do it anyways
you know I do have a stand mixer but I
think I'm just going to use that for the
whipped cream
okay
[Music]
whisk done
insert into mix
come right get in there
bad habits now now glove has more egg in
it
wash wash
goodness oh
happy birthday to you
[Music]
hello beautiful
baby
happy birthday to you
[Music]
whoa
thank you baby
happy birthday
thank you
you know for me I thought you were gonna
you're gonna do a payback to what I did
what the uh
it's too late Bae it's too late no good
guys
oh no
oh no because cake going
um I basically just started just
starting to mix the the milk and
everything else now hopefully it mixes
oh
I see Oshi whiskey I'm I'm mixing
shoes like not like clumped right it's
all fine as long as they make it smooth
have you baked yeah
uh I have but I'm not that good at
baking
[Music]
I always
no that's why well they do say baking is
science so understanding
it is it's a chemistry
it is
you just wake up
I'm still in bed yo
I like woke up from a dream uh open your
street
yo that rhymes
wow you're natural
I know I wanna wish you a happy birthday
and I know it's super early for you too
oh
that you remain
cool and
uh you wait what rhymes with birthdays I
hope you have a great
stay
in on your birthday
okay thank you of course I'll have a
great stay on my birthday
[Laughter]
oh not okay it's okay I totally
understand my brain when I woke up today
I was like
zombie
and then I set everything up and I was
like oh okay yeah
yeah you get you get it right you know
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh my god oh wait I'm fixing
I was I was looking I was like that
seems like a lot of liquid oh my god oh
I think it should feel like because I
got like three small pants I don't know
if you can see it's like three small
panels but it's gonna be like layered so
yeah oh hopefully it fails all three of
them are you gonna whip the whipped
cream by hand
mixer my arm's hurting already just from
mixing it
have you ever made whipped cream like
from hand
S I made something or I guess like
harder to make by hand just a meringue
do you know what meringues are
it was back in the day and I probably
will never do it by hand again
oh my God that was that was painful yeah
it sounds painful
the Army to break
yeah you should have a little oh that
looking smooth oh yeah
thank you oh
that looks beautiful actually what the
heck not as beautiful as you
oh yeah oh yeah
sorry what I missed that I was yawning
what did you say don't don't worry but
don't worry about it was nothing babe it
was nothing well what
was nothing
oh no
smooth
as smooth as this cake mix yes oh
damn I missed it
also okay so sorry no no go back to
sleep
and I will I'll see you later okay yeah
yeah we have Karthik phone later
I should yeah oh I hope you liked
oh yeah it would be send me a gift like
this morning last night
it's beautiful I was like she's grown so
much as my student
my art student
I should I just saw it look at the feet
I know I was like damn
thing wait what do you mean damn
look
damn feet
yeah look at it it's great wait yo
if my defense I had 10 minutes okay I
mean I couldn't have done this in 10
minutes got a beautiful capybara
this doesn't bode well for our collab no
no no I mean you
one thing and you learn 10 Things I
taught you how to draw chibis and you
drew capybara that's
oh my God
well I'm glad Sensei is happy with my
gross I hope you continue watching over
me on my journey for Mastery I'll be
watching later today
oh God don't disappoint me
send help
all right
after watching your cake making
happy birthday
thank you
I love you
[Music]
it is I the ancient ones here to wish
you the happiest birthday
uh where is that you
I'm sorry I'm a little bad at these
things like I'm just a little awkward
you're the worm right from from the uh
it's been a minute since we've talked to
each other yes
it's been a while since we spoke you
know my innerness I haven't seen you at
the shrine recently doing your Priestess
duties
uh sorry the signal is cutting
I miss you
sorry I don't really know what came over
me there hi oh yeah it happens sometimes
yeah I understand yeah yeah sometimes
you know these these demonic beings just
kind of take over my body
um anyway in a happy birthday
I see you're making a making a Tasty
Cake over there
yes not done yet but okay can you send
it to Japan
uh it might not be in top shape when it
arrives but I'll still eat it I'm crazy
I'll do it uh it might actually be able
to come back from the underworld
oh okay well that's a really good point
I don't know I feel like it'd be better
served being sent to the takodachis so
so it's all good
yeah yeah yeah that sounds much better
besides you know I'm doing keto so I
can't I kind of I can't eat this I can't
I can't eat the cake anyway so it's okay
don't worry about it as well
yeah okay enjoy enjoy unless it's like
you know a cauliflower cake maybe I can
make that work any cauliflower
I can cauliflower pizza is pretty oh
this is really not good yes of course
broccoli broccoli is great sorry I sound
like a chain smoker I just I've been
sick for the past five days no but so I
couldn't write you a wrap and I couldn't
I couldn't draw you anything because
gift you can give me is a healthy Cali
and happy calorie okay
that's why you're the that's why you're
the rizzler of of Ian you know what the
best gift actually is
is money well no hold on that's the
wrong way to say it no I sent you I sent
you some games
um on Steam
no no no it's not me it's not money what
I mean to say is when I can't use my
hands and I can't use my my voice I use
money so they check your Steam and I
sent you a couple games
thank you yeah well they're very
different from each other it's um I sent
you the new Dead Space I feel like you
should play it yeah I haven't played it
yet yeah so I got that for you and I got
a rubber duck simulator I haven't really
played it before but it looks kind of
funny
looks kind of fun for you to relax I
guess
yes
so enjoy the enjoy the games
yeah
I always I always remember you
um being so nice always so nice to me
and I always feel like I can talk very
casually with you because I don't know
we have a good vibe and I appreciate you
when you were behind me I guess during
the the 3D the 3D showcase I can feel
your tears as I was dancing and singing
and that's why I was able to do better I
want to do that for you someday so I'll
hurry up and have a 3D video I'll try
out hurry up
[Music]
we're playing ring fit today oh my
goodness you're not feeling you're
you're sick and you're playing ring fit
oh no no my body's fine now it's just my
throat oh but still you have to breathe
that is true well you have to breathe to
do anything so I'm very good at
breathing so worry not
well you eat a lot with
that is true however I can also breathe
a lot when I need to dot dot dot
question mark I bet it'll be fun
don't you worry you know ask yourself
okay well I I won't push it just because
you asked me to I'll remember that when
things are getting rough okay okay well
meet me in the ring someday in another
fighting game we gotta play Guilty Gear
again Batman is there there's new
yeah I'm disappointed it's not Johnny
but that's okay Batman is in there kind
of so I play I saw that he had some
stick like shoes
yeah sandals but they were they were
like sneakers oh yeah pretty cool well
Batman is dead man is kind of bed girl
now but the spirit of bed man leaves
lives on so yeah exciting I'm excited to
use bed man do not play the game and use
the same character and be better
kind of luck for fighting oh well yeah
that threshold I'm just like well bye
oh no I like playing fighting games with
you I feel like it's it's not it's not
just like a situation where I feel like
it's a game that I can play it's like no
it's genuinely very fun
fighting games too so a lot of fun
playing with you
I'm glad to hear that I don't know it's
it's calming when I lose against you I
don't want to throw my controller and
enjoy my my wall oh no punch a hole or
anything
yeah oh classic like I said there is
it's unbeatable
oh my well I'm gonna go rest my throat a
little bit before three but have a great
rest of the day enjoy your garlic phone
collab and enjoy that piece of cake for
me that I cannot eat okay thank you
happy birthday Inna
see you later happy birthday
is not available at the moment
yes bye
okay dear Kelly that's a hard worker you
know
like I don't know how she does it but
yeah I'm a biggest fan
okay so we mixed everything I think I
spent a little too long talking but
we're gonna fill in
the cake molds the oven is ready
Where can I
hold on
have a little
resting thing right here okay that's
good
okay
shall pour it into the molds
so I have to fill it up all the way
I don't think so as long as it's equal
between three right oh
um yeah I guess the layers can be a
little thin I wouldn't mind it
'll work
oh yeah I already uh well I was talking
to Kelly I greased the pans already
that's that's baking 101 you know
the cake is gonna rise I don't want to
fill it up all the way that means I'll
have to cut out a lot more oh I dropped
someone in the paper cloth
okay
a little more here
I'm doing well I'm doing well I think
this is gonna be okay hopefully
no
I'm getting there
I've been thinking about breath of the
Wild
even when I was about to go to sleep
I wish I could just play it all day next
time I mean now the birthday prep is
over I can
ah okay I think the Soapy
perfectly split between the three which
is good
maybe next week we'll be all breath of
the last week unless I have collapsed
we did if I have collabs next week maybe
I do maybe I don't oh
come on
make sure I use up all the all the cake
mix
this should be good enough right
I think it's pretty equal between three
okay that goes in the sink
some water in it so it's not a nightmare
for me to clean after
haha
okay
uh hmm I should probably clean the edges
a little bit I don't even remember if I
have
like oven mitts
happy birthday princess thank you
thank you guys for uh joining me today
you know I always think about how
there's
no so so many streamers and YouTubers in
the world how lucky I am to have people
you know join me for
special occasion I can't even speak
special occasion
it's almost three years since I've
rebuild
it really flies when you're having fun
but yeah you know I was always nervous
about
uh
in hand camp but
the right setup like today's it is not
too bad
I'm gonna have to wash this tablecloth
after and you just tap it to get the air
bubbles out
yeah
that's what settles very nicely
character development Maybe
it's gonna have your three layer cake
okay
oh
oven is ready okay how long does it say
s for like a two eight inch rounds it
should be like 28 to 33 minutes
maybe like 30 minutes
or all three
[Music]
less time for three
okay check at 25 for toothpicks I did
buy toothpicks just in case okay
I'll move these over to the oven
kind of scared
okay
set it for 35 check at 25. okay
actually yeah yeah that'll work
[Music]
number two
and number three
okay they're in the oven
oh
they're in the oven okay set timer
um
timer where's that set timer
I'll set it for 30.
okay I'll set it for 30 and I'll check
it at like 25.
I did preheat that's the first thing I
did when I turned on the Stream
okay the oven here is making my entire
kitchen very hot maybe I should go turn
off turn on the AC
ah
okay I lowered the temps for the AC
hopefully it turns on
how's my day so far pretty good
um
I'm actually quite surprised that oh
hello love
surprised that the um
the camera set up and everything went
very smoothly I was expecting some bumps
I guess minus the fact that the camera
is running on battery now is all good
okay and while the cake is baking we
have around 10 minutes until
announcement oh exciting so maybe I'll
wash some fruits and get them ready
prepare the whipped cream
yeah
like awesome uh strawberries
blueberries and peaches
peaches
[Music]
Okay so guess I can start by washing the
fruits
wash some of the blueberries I have some
milk left over too so I can probably
make like a milkshake if I have
uh
too much left over
peaches beaches peaches
okay
put that in do I wash all the I might as
well wash all of it I'll eat some of the
blueberries I have to
see
blueberries very nice
wash wash
always wash your fruits even if they say
ah I should have taken off my gloves
even if they say they're pre-washed
washed them once again
[Music]
very nice indeed
okay I should have a strainer somewhere
huh
what's that
the water out
myself
cooking with gloves on is more difficult
than I imagined you know
okay
blueberries ready
and then
okay don't forget to drink water I could
use some water
I'm getting thirsty moving around
okay
get my nice glass
of water
I think my fridge has a water thing
it can get very cold water
nice for delicious water
I want to sit down
and pie
why is water so delicious
foreign
ly hear me gulp it down huh
microphone's pretty close to my face
[Music]
as you guys eat
okay
enough water you guys want to see my cup
[Music]
got it while I was in Japan I'm pretty
sure I got it when I went to the uh
Capcom store with gura
it's really cute
okay time for strawberries
how many should I wash for strawberries
yeah the Capcom store had so many cute
things
I want to buy them all I had to stop
myself
I literally had so much luggage going
back home I had to leave some with Gemma
and then bring
the rest of the back on like my second
trip in April
it was a very interesting I should say
yeah
I think that's enough strawberries
okay time to wash the strawberries
I think this should be enough right
I think I'm gonna chop some
into the whipped cream between the
layers
and then have some as decoration on top
so I shouldn't need too too many I think
probably
okay let's straighten that out
gotta open the
beaches can the strawberries aren't
really in the greatest shape I'm kind of
sad oh well
okay
yeah like there were so many things I
want to buy
they're cute like kitchenware and
whatnot
I wanted to get but you know difficult
wait what happened to my timer
[Music]
oh
a tiger didn't set okay only the 20
minutes now
I have no idea
but I'm pretty sure I started timer at
the 15 minute mark
eight minutes has passed okay I'm gonna
use my phone then I can never go wrong
with phone okay so 30 minus eight twenty
22 minutes
okay
only two minutes okay okay we're good
bone always good to use
the one in the oven really you know
that's it
worked that well I should have used my
phone from the start
oh it's rising
the edges are rising faster than the
center though I hope that's okay and
natural
good thing I noticed soon I'm pretty
sure Chad what you guys would have told
me right like that would have been like
time for for the cake to be done because
you guys are good at tracking time
yeah
right
okay time to open
the sliced peaches
can
do I remember how to use a can opener I
do
for a second I thought I didn't have a
candle for her but then I did so I was
like thank goodness I didn't buy another
one
the strawberries can wait out to the
peaches first
okay
and uh
I need another dish for this
which is in the water
[Music]
uh
gooey syrupy water oh there's one left
in there come on get out
come on
it's stuck
I need a fork
okay
oh so the timer has been set for nine
hours and
56 minutes that's what it was
weird
I I have no idea why but I was set like
that
I have I don't use my oven that often
okay here's the canned peaches
okay
and now
I gotta use the fruit knife
to take care of
the
strawberries
[Music]
I don't know if I can show the knife on
the stream so I have to like
censor it
probably not oh yeah announcement never
mind we'll do the strawberry after the
announcement
okay
it is first
I almost missed it phew so uh to
celebrate
Ina's birthday 2023 we have some special
merch to commemorate the special day
I shall now
throw it on this this screen
are you guys ready
you guys ready
drum roll oh
get rid of the camera for a second
in a birthday celebration 2023.
wait I have some board apparently I can
use it
hold on I can use this
uh uh where is golf clap
there is no Golf Club
I'll just use drum roll
I can't hear drum roll that's a slide
okay we're good I know we got a
kuruboshi papa to draw the key visual
for this year thank you thank you very
much
such a beautiful beautiful illustration
and I'll show you uh some other things
if it's gonna work ah there we go this
is the complete set with the uh I
dreamed I went outside acrylic
smartphone stand we have the taco list
backpack and definitely not a book pouch
and you get a bonus postcard if you buy
all of them wow
and to have a uh
okay better picture
this is acrylic
marples down or you can put on your
phone here maybe your I don't know if it
fits tablets but you know beautiful art
there's the taco that cheese you can put
your phone here and you can even put the
wire like in that Gap there so you can
have it on your desk wow
next item being the taco this backpack
it's a pretty regular sized backpack
with some uh in their pockets with the
with the patterns of my tentacles
and uh there's a cute tag and a little
you know arm very good
and you have the little taco flaps
and the little uh what should I say the
strap to hang your bag on the wall is
the color of your onion rings
and a nice little pouch that's
definitely not a book but she'd like a
book like our Channel
uh what's it mass-produced auction but
it's not a book so it should be fine
right
and yeah it's it's pretty decent size so
you can fit a lot of stuff in it
and carry it around in your taco
backpack a full set
and there will be individual sales for
the items the smartphone stand the
backpack and the pouch and if you get
the whole set you can get the postcard
at my signature on it and there will be
some limited edition sets with
a handwritten message from me nine I
think
yes and written autograph for The
Limited
Etc yes
and that is it for the merch wow
what you guys think
did I take some useful items this year
too
now you can carry now you can carry
around tacos everywhere on your bag in
your bag on your desk everywhere
yeah
I really really like backpack I got to
see it in person uh last time I went to
Japan and it's it's a really good
quality backpack
those like uh canvas
material backpacks and the inside is
like nice smooth
you know pattern
yeah and the pouch I I haven't seen the
pouch myself yet but uh I'm not sure if
it can fit a pet it should be able to
fit a normal pencil right
when does it go live it actually goes
live very soon
uh by soon
I mean
uh
and in 20 wait
9 30 jst which is in 25 minutes
25 minutes
we'll start sales
yes
25 minutes
and I believe the link to it will be in
the description
of the of the live yes
soon pm
I know such beautiful art oh yeah I can
show you guys the Japanese
[Music]
I actually don't know I don't I don't
remember what it translated to in
Japanese so uh
I can't read the kanji
body
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
I dreamed of the outside
in the next one
[Music]
I can read this taco
I guess they call this oh
[Music]
I can read this one tonight
yeah so
yep that's it
of course the um the limited sets there
will of course will be limited amounts
available so if you would like me not to
right
on your postcard
that's what I've been told
[Music]
yes those are those are the merch stuff
please look forward to it in
minutes
okay maybe I can get this to
automatically
change
uh automatic I'll just cycle through as
I'm baking my cake
there you go
I'm trying I really am
okay
put it here you can't read it but you'll
know what it is
back to the Taco feed
yay
that is that is uh fortunately the only
uh
announcement I have for today I have a
couple more things coming up but they're
not finalized yet therefore
announcements will have to be a bit
later but uh I guess one thing to
mention is that there is one more merch
upcoming which is the new outfit
uh
celebration thing but that will be
announced and
uh
Stone
along with something else so please look
forward to it should be able to you
should be able to order it
with the same batch as
uh the birthday merch so
um yes thank you
[Laughter]
please look forward to it
yeah the link to the merch will be
in the description soon TM as in when it
goes live I think
it will be update I'll updated as soon
as it goes live I think or or now I
forget which
yes
but don't worry unless you want the
limited set
um it'll be on sale for
why are the birthday and the year
what you may call it a new outfit merch
so
yes
my mouse turned off wait
there you go
okay link has been updated I think it's
in the description
yeah yeah
[Music]
thank you thank you monitor
very very
okay that was that was it for the
announcements thank you very much
everyone honestly
um I do try it I guess think of items
that will be helpful or useful in your
everyday life
so I hope that we can accept more tacos
into your daily routine
but the new merch yeah thank you and
always you know as I said before thank
you always for you know watching over me
watching rather I'm watching over me
cheering me on supporting me not only me
but everyone else in whole life although
life production as well so thank you
always
baby let's cut it
oh yeah
okay so I was I was asked again to
mention the limited sets will be on sale
as soon as it opens and there will be
there will be a very limited amount
apparently so if you want it you have to
be fast
I wish I could I wish I could cite all
of them but
um
money time asked me to mention this
again so
my apologies
[Music]
got it prepared yes the link has been
updated so if you do want it please uh
yeah
please uh please hold until it opens
maybe I'll draw like a Taco on every
single signed one
you'll see we'll see we'll see oh
my apron
it's untied
oh no
okay
and now it seems we have
another guest in a tiny bit after
okay that's good all right
uh hello
[Music]
it must match hello
hey hello happy birthday oh thank you
oh
how you doing
I'm me I'm living
for real for real
we're so alike for real for real yeah
we're still alike I think we mentioned
this before yeah
oh man yeah have you been enjoying your
birthday so far yeah it's been great I'm
making cake
bacon cake I know not bacon cake baking
cake thank you
although bacon can be good oh bacon cake
yeah baking cake sounds pretty good it's
like the sweet and salty you know bacon
cake bacon cake big bacon cake yeah it's
like sweet it's kind of you know a
delicacy I guess
yeah real you know kind of series of
sweets no that you need no but what are
you really trying to make a cake a cake
what kind of cake
standard you know whipped cream fruits
cake oh yeah I can't do anything
unfortunately
it's okay I'm sure it's gonna turn out
good regardless yeah it's still cake
yeah yeah I wish I had cake man
really is that an invitation yeah of
course oh my goodness
well I don't mind oh of course anytime
oh off collab cake oh
honestly if we ever do off Club again I
just want everyone to like cook together
but Kate can you imagine the chaos
um I never really cooked before or
even better well I'll be a good
assistant for y'all I'll probably like
you know oh no no no we're gonna we're
gonna coach you
it's like it's like you know like the
master like only gets to like say what
you need to do you're gonna follow the
order so that knowing what to do
yeah but like crony put that thing over
there and you were like what what what
do I put in this thing and then you put
like okay I can actually hey I could do
something better I might not be
panicking you don't know that
uh yeah sure
yeah of course yeah I have some
experience with being a baking assistant
in the past so oh
yes so have you ever dealt with uh uh
Ina Ramsay
Ina Ramsey oh no
oh
it's wrong we're gonna say some unsay so
stuff to me I'm gonna bring two Subway
sandwiches put it put you between
and she doesn't feel like what are you
chroni
a failure
a Perfection that's what it is exactly
you can't you can't let me down
you lift me up more like huh
I wouldn't mind that
oh
yeah yeah
just wake up
I didn't oh good morning good morning
one day when did you wake up
um
depends on where I slept I I spent all
morning setting this up and then oh and
fell asleep a little bit and then I woke
up before the stream oh my goodness you
woke up in the morning
oh that sounds all too familiar man
for real for real
for real for real hey wow we are so
similar oh my goodness basically me
ah except I can't draw
we can change that there's a there's a
art course that B has been taking called
I don't know Art 101 was it
with Art 101 professor
oh really you could join us for the
classes that'll be fun what's the
tuition fear
a low price discount the price of 549.99
549 99 549.99
what a deal I mean yeah I guess it's not
sure
bad deal I I might consider
what a deal
yeah I think I think
it'll be better than you know me helping
you bake a cake
I feel like it might turn out better who
knows
oh it'd be fun to do like cooking
classes whoa
oh my goodness you're cooking don't
panic
don't Don't Panic it's good it turned
out great I want to see a picture of it
later
oopsied on stream too if there's a
there's a oh really oh there's a hand
cam yeah
oh my God
there's nothing
nothing
okay take them up where's the oven mitts
don't panic
I I want to see it okay hold on wait I
thought this is a still picture no it's
only because the the fruits are amazing
Focus right now is organizing the fruits
all the people oh my goodness it's Auto
focusing whoa it is real
I set up my really good camera for this
too okay I gotta take this out of the
oven oh
what is it what is that other one aside
from blueberries and strawberry what's
the other one peaches
the peaches yeah I love peaches
twice oh yeah
yeah this is the fun movie
really yeah
hold on I guess I can show
on
English
oh my goodness look how it's perfect it
is
I yeah a really nice tablecloth
look
where thick really nice oh
it's so cute it's so pretty there's
three of them so it's gonna be three
layers
though
put it over here
success
it is a success dude that's amazing
thank you you were worried over nothing
I was kind of worried it's been a while
since I baked the full cakes I mean you
can't really go wrong with cake mix
right laughs
oh if it's a cake mix yeah yeah it's a
cake mix yeah
angel cake or not just like vanilla
nice classic
okay I guess I can do this on camera I
think some strawberries put in the
whipped cream later
[Music]
it's a little difficult
I get that
that looks beautiful oh thank you not as
perfect as you thought cronie I know
that though I already I know you know I
I know I know but I know you know that I
know that you know yeah I know that you
know that I know that I know I know yeah
I know but you know yeah
it looks nice I might as well just put
it like on top
are you gonna cut the peaches too
a little bit Yeah a few of them nice
it really looks good
you see that I'll make you some cake if
we ever off collating again or visit or
you could like send a slice of cake to
me
honestly if I freeze it
Maybe
probably not we're probably not yeah
probably not
it'd be amazing though it'd be amazing
but yeah but if it maintains it yeah
it might be squished and you know yeah
but if it's frozen you know
you know if it's like maybe not
and it preserves its shape I I don't
think I'd be able to eat it
don't you think so I'll just I'll just
whatever
meat again
yum I know cleaning up is gonna be kind
of a mess though huh well it's not too
bad I'm sure they have like some some
airbnbs of dishwashers right
oh yeah true yeah you just gotta find
one with it
laughs
uh it'll be fine
it'll be fine
I'll I'll leave you be though okay get
some I guess you woke up but you can get
more rest might as well yeah
the weekend after all right maybe maybe
just a bit Yeah you can be lazy today
can I yeah
I allow you to be lazy today oh thanks
man bless I'll I'll do it for maybe
10 minutes then yeah sleep in 10 more
minutes mom
10 more minutes in a minute in a minute
okay okay
of course happy birthday thank you
bye-bye
[Music]
okay I think this is enough strawberries
for the
whipped cream
yeah crony oh she's so funny
I don't know why everything curly says
something I'm just like she's a natural
comedian
I do have some sliced strawberries after
all maybe I'll use this for decoration I
think these ones are nicely shaped I
don't know if you can see it oh
oh did I run out of battery
I think I ran out of battery
hold on I do have like one more
backup battery but I might have to
turn this off for a second
maybe I'll charge it while well we don't
have to see some things where's the
extra battery there it is
I don't think it torched to full though
so I'm kind of
kind of worried
I guess we'll see
um you put it in this way okay
yeah I have the one where you connected
to the wall plug coming soon but it
didn't arrive on time
unfortunately
[Music]
hey
back on
activate
uh
so next time if I do another another
camera stream I'll be ready
I mean I'm just surprised that the setup
is working
pretty well so
[Music]
let me test okay
all right
this should probably last me like
another 30 minutes or so
okay we're back
I think
yeah I want to do more cooking streams
because I like cooking
I'll probably make me eat healthier
we're back a little bit so
progress
on the strawberries you got this much
this is gonna go in the whipped cream
in between the layers and this one I
think is cheap pretty nice
I'm gonna put it on the very top
okay
strawberry ready I guess what we need to
do is make the whipped cream now huh
need much work I just gotta put the bowl
in the mixer and then turn it on
where's the Whisk
[Music]
where's the Whisk question over here
let's just I guess this is it
I thought there was like a whisk
like attachment to it
and out here I thought I had a whisk
attaching it
yes I don't have a whisk
unless it's somewhere else
oh
emergency
foreign
[Music]
but where could it be
where could it be
if it's not here where could it be
oh no no no no no
please
I don't want to whisk with my hands
I can't be
[Music]
it can't be
I was so sure I had a whisk attachment
well I'll see how far this will take me
I'll see how far this attachment will
take me and we'll go from there
that is so unfortunate
why why
how could this help
well
this is something I did not expect uh
okay how do I
let's just put this in and whip
that's it right
nothing else I gotta do just gotta gotta
whisk it till it whips
I should have just bought pre-made
whipped cream
I should have
I really should have
okay oh I don't know how much is enough
I'll make plenty
early
it'll be okay
I am afraid
actually I guess I can turn off the
camera for now to save the battery
and then probably
uh
turn it on again for
decorating
yeah okay turn it off for now
huh
okay
[Music]
oh yeah Mark should have should have
gone live like two minutes ago
you got the Limited
nice nice thank you thank you
it sold out already
you guys are too fast
go too fast
oh okay I gotta move this over
very speed
[Music]
it doesn't make it no
no lasted a minute
that is very Speedy I didn't expect it
thank you
okay
surely I won't make the same mistake as
I did with the recent
Ian 3D reenact okay well locked in
whisk thing logged in
that mixer plugged in
okay
okay turning it on
oh
to be honest this is not a whisk but I'm
sure
it'll do something at least
hopefully
it'll get me part of the way there
yeah it's the paddle
it'll do something right
as long as it adds air
okay I'll turn it on to level six okay
all right
the cream is mixing
it sounds like they're clapping
more power
disaster inbound nah I'll be fine
I'll just check back on it in a couple
of minutes
more power
the pan potato stands for power
I am potato therefore I am power
what should I do now
maybe should I cut some of the trick up
the cake I think
the cake cooled down quite a bit so I
can probably make it flat it's like it's
easier to stack right
while the whipped cream is
whisking whipping
yeah it's gonna be three layer cake it's
my first time making a three layer cake
I know it's like
what should I say it's a smaller cake
but still like I haven't done three
layers before not even in school
I mean
I don't know if there's any progress
with the lip but
yeah layers are difficult but I got the
exact same pan I'm hoping that it'll
make those things a lot easier oh the
cake came out perfect hold on I have to
turn on the camera to show you guys
it turned out like the most perfect
perfect cake I've ever
okay so this is the cake
came out very nicely
and I want to show you guys the back of
it hopefully I don't drop it
turned out very very beautiful
okay now I'll cut the name of the fruits
out of the way
here
okay
I have to cut the tops off
so that it stands flat
on the layers
just do it like
slowly
running across that
now we'll just put this back in the oven
it's so spongy
[Music]
and perfect beautiful
okay
I don't know if the Whisk is gonna work
me always
[Music]
get more air in there okay
so I'm gonna put this on this plate here
but it's the Kirby Cafe plate
it's the Kirby Cafe
it's a nice plate it got from the curvy
Cafe
you can like order food there and they
like have the option for you to buy the
buy the plate so I got it
it's the perfect size for this look
perfect size
okay I guess I can cut the other two as
well
I'm not sure if the whipped cream is
gonna work
ah this is turning out so great
the cake is coming out of this like so
cleanly
this is the best cake I've ever made
oh thanks to you guys
it's down look how spongy it is
[Music]
across
oh look at that
I need another plate oh no my dishes are
gonna be
they have a lot of dishes to do after
this
I guess that's fine I have a dishwasher
that's what dishwashers are full of
okay I'll make this
over to this temporary plate it's
looking so good
foreign
it's a little greasy you can see the
grease on The Cutting Board
you know what they say the unhealthier
it is
actually they don't really see that but
you know
[Music]
I was kind of scared that like one of
the cake layers would have like too
little of the batter it's gonna be very
thin
but they turned out perfectly identical
calculated
okay
is prepared
now we just gotta wait for the whipped
cream to be done
oh there has been some progress
there has been progress thank goodness
now let me take a
quick taste test
[Music]
that's good it's good very good
delicious
[Music]
so good
this cake is a success
delicious
Okay so
I have a brush
all I did
oh
I guess I don't have
the brush for
baking things
[Music]
yeah I'm still missing a couple things
in the kitchen including a brush
yeah I don't have one
oh well
yeah one trick that mommy has taught me
was that you know like the the syrup
from the peaches if you brush some onto
the cake the cake gets like really moist
and yummy
I was gonna do that
can't find the brush
I'll just use a small spoon
and sprinkle some over
that'll work right
it's a yummy yummy trick
the base layer mix on this
it's the mama Miss special
they used to make me cakes when I was
little for my birthday too
like one of the one of my favorite cakes
that she made was like this it's like a
really simple whipped cream fruit
I think
it's delicious okay I think that's good
enough
now we wait for the whipped cream I'll
turn off the camera for a bit
I could save the battery
save the battery oh wait I can't see
chat
I haven't been able to see chat for a
while oh no
I mean I have you guys open on my on my
phone
but on the screen you can't see yourself
there you go
oh
it's over over mixed
this is
not
what I expected
only the top has been really really
mixed
and the other top looks very fresh
I mean
is it over mixed
foreign
I must have over mixed it then
while I wasn't watching
I have more so I can give it another try
but
I'm trying to afford the layers at the
bottom but the bottom is like still
very
liquid
well if you guys
oh I guess no camera but
they do wrong
[Music]
I over whip the whipped cream I made
blood
foreign
I should probably watch over the mixer a
little bit
I like butter
I mean I guess I can
eat it with some toast later
uh probably I'll mix it a little bit
more to be completely buttered but
yeah let me wash this a little bit
you know what if
if we don't get
a a decent what should I say
decent whipped cream we're just gonna
have three layers of bread with some
fruit on top and that's fine I'll accept
it
I still have a little bit of whipped
cream left or at least a liquid form of
it we're not gonna give We're not gonna
give up yet
not yet
okay let me wash this real quick
the one minute that I didn't watch it
turned into butter
can't I can't believe it
[Music]
oh at least we know that uh cream or I
guess milk product is a versatile
yeah it's definitely butter it's oily in
here
oily in the bowl
I didn't mean to make one
well this is how people make like
homemade butter right they add like
flavoring to it maybe I'll add some
flavoring to that actually
got some herbs in there
pulled it in
add some salt I just unsalted butter is
good too
add some spices and herbs
so I showed mama needs like the setup I
made for the stream and I'll have to
wash the
cattle as well as soon as I showed it to
her she was like leave some for me she
didn't even ask what I was making she
just wanted some
toss it up
oh my goodness that's very oily that's
definitely butter
they call me the uh
the full kitchen Alchemist
try to get some whipped cream but I got
butter instead
[Music]
let me let me cook baking is basically
Alchemy right
basically
okay that's in there
I can just imagine mom and he's laughing
her belly buttons off already
[Music]
had a lifted and gotten perfect whipped
cream
no you have to make butter
go ahead and make butter instead
I'm gonna meet have you guys ever made
like cheese at home
butter
[Music]
like uh homemade cheese is pretty easy
to make but like you can make it with
yogurt
but like
was it yogurt I'm pretty sure it was
yogurt or something like that but
oh now I know now I know where's my
other glove
uh-oh
[Music]
love champ
where'd you go
this this is me again talking getting
distracted not remembering where you put
everything
I'm missing a club
you know I said I'm missing a glove
I looked down and I was wearing it
I can't I can't take this anymore Chad I
can't
I can't be kidding you
okay round two if I fail this it's over
I'll have just made
a liter of butter
this time I'm not gonna look away from
okay we're turning this on
we're not looking away
you better believe it
round two round two
ah
sorry if it's a little loud I'm like
leaning over to the
stand mixer but this is honestly the
only way I won't make butter again
I'm curious what it tastes like
also the water that came out of it is
buttermilk
oh
I gotta separate the the milk from it
science wow
I should have known better
who
time to make some pancakes Maybe
maybe there's like a
I could make butter
cream frosting
but I don't have frosting like icing
sugar
hello
you'll feel like grannies like grandmas
or no it's a grocery store buttercream
[Music]
I might as well go buy a cake at this
point
okay so it is
it is thickening up a little bit
but it's still liquid I'm watching
happy accidents homemade butter is good
I will try it
I won't give up I still have this
this a template
we might not have enough to like
layer as thickly as like the other cakes
I've eaten with the cream in it but
you know
still
you're not giving up
if this messes up then we're just having
some
some cake bread with fruits on top it'll
be like a crap it'll be like a very very
tall pancake
we'll put some syrup on
we'll put some syrup on it I call it
okay
it's still liquid
let me just poke it
poke it at it with something see how big
okay it's still liquid we're good we're
good safe keep whipping
there'll be three layers of giant thick
pancakes
I knew I knew everything was going too
smoothly when the cakes came out
perfectly and not stuffed to the pan
laughs
foreign
okay it's definitely less liquid than
before
I guess I'm like so used to making
meringues that I'm like looking for
those like stiff peaks that forms when
you're making memories
but it's not that it's whipped cream
it's definitely
yeah I definitely just left it in the
mixer for too long last time
at least I learned how to make butter
for later
yeah I used to really like making land
cookies
they're really simple to make if you get
it right
I have to say I'm high okay
all right I turned up the speed so it
mixes the bottom as well
okay I'm watching carefully it's still
liquid
so let me turn on the light here
hand it off
butter round two let's go no I'm
watching it closely I'm not taking my
eyes off it
I'm watching watching
okay
test time this is still liquid
still liquid
as soon as I see even slight big
of buttering
I will stop and he's ahead
I don't make butter again I won't I
won't
do butter or not to butter that is the
question but it is nowhere in the mind
to suffer the
the
righteousness of making butter again I
don't know
I really believe it in the in the Whisk
for this long the last one it didn't
feel like that long
I guess there's like a very small window
to put kids into your body
okay it's the liquid
come on hand mixer I believe in you
it was quite long okay maybe I got the
strap did yeah I mean I do get
distracted quite often too
much
okay so the liquid is hurting for
just turning a little less
it has been a little bit of
a little bit of uh improvements
we're not there yet
[Music]
baking is patience patience is not crazy
would it help if I put some sugar in it
I didn't put any sugar in it
I don't know
[Music]
yes
it does help oh
well well well
no wonder people see baking is science
I'll bring some sugar
you need it oh
maybe I missed
look at a recipe
[Music]
okay I added sugar
one tablespoon per cup I added some
oh I do see it thickening up yes
okay there is hope
we're almost there
laughs
Shirley Shirley
say no to butter say yes to whipped
cream
I should have just bought somewhere
between his bathtub
I didn't I didn't expect
this to be the difficult part
birthday thank you
you can make butter for whipped cream by
the way I was not aware
definitely don't have a play of
accidentally made butter beside me
definitely not
[Applause]
it's made meringue cream
and like coached it or something
that would have been better
because I know how to make meringues
better than whipped cream
surprisingly
it should be done by now it's the liquid
like very very liquid because it's not a
whisk it's like the paddle thing
it's the liquid here
maybe I'll mix it
need more air
I don't have the Whisk
should I use my hands now is this time
for manual whiskey
has it really come down to this
I have a hand whisk I just didn't want
to use it
can't be helped
things I do for you guys
all right I'm gonna need a chair for
this laughs
I'm bringing my dining room chair
you have to sit down
all right
it's gonna be loud
I hope you're ready
put this on my lap
time to whisk
I mean the the mixed stand mixer did
most of the work so surely
surely shouldn't be too
to the fickle right
arms
are Parts already
okay it'll be worth it it'll be worth it
I'm gonna Amazon the Whisk attachment
right after this
I'm pretty sure I had it but I guess not
I thought it like came with it
uh
it's like almost done it's almost done
that's why it's so hard to whisk now
I'll use my left hand
I feel like I left it somewhere it might
be it might be what mama needs Maybe
I bought it while I was still with them
so oh I think it's almost done though
oh is it dark
okay I'm pretty sure it's done now
thank goodness
stuff Peaks yes
that didn't take too long
oh the star mixer did most of the work
let me show you the butter
all right
turn on the camera
that hopefully the battery lasts till
the
end
alright so
you guys are curious
this is the uh
[Laughter]
it's definitely but
it's a beautiful butter I gotta say
I just have to separate it from the
buttermilk
it looks good it looks like good butter
it's just not whipped cream
okay so here is this
all right where's my spatula there it is
get my bowl
and there's the actual whipped cream
not much but I'll put
a thick layer of it
it worked
goodness
my goodness it worked
okay
is that
all right generous
serving of whipped cream
too bad I won't have like extra extra
whipped cream though
okay where's my strawberries
[Music]
oh I was gonna put some peaches there
too oh well
some
strawberries in the layers
[Music]
exciting
we're almost done
a little more
[Music]
nice very nice
lots of strawberries
okay
and then oh maybe all the very thin
layer of
glue
I don't know if I have enough to cover
the cake
we'll do our best
I'm sure I'll be fine
there you go
okay
second layer
oh maybe I should cut the bottom of the
second Nash before it's gonna be a tall
cake
push that down a little bit
and then
a little bit of peach juice
foreign
[Music]
very good
oh drop some into the whipped cream now
rescuing
bring it all over my
any gloves
oh no my gloves
should have gotten like more what's it
like the plastic gloves to put on top of
these clothes I'm gonna be like three
layers of gloves
unfortunately
okay I'll wash the clothes
okay I'll put them in the washer
and then the last layer the top
actually I'll put the peach juice like
on four and I'll flip it upside down so
it's perfectly flat
that's a tower
big big tower
of a birthday cake
all right
flip this upside down
whoa
you guys can see how tall it is but it's
quite tall compared to the plate
it's off the Whisk I gotta cover the
entire thing
generous amount
[Music]
oh it smells like milk
besides too
I wonder if I'll have enough
[Music]
at least cover the cup that's the very
important part
I gotta get this size just gotta make
sure I have enough
it should happen though
if only I didn't mess up the first time
[Music]
all right well we can do this we can do
this
at least get like a base coat on
[Music]
it's looking like a birthday cake
quite proud of it
[Music]
hey
I'll clean up or clean up the
sides and stuff for you
I have this entire site to cover okay
okay
we'll have enough kitty
foreign
[Music]
so exciting
foreign
looking slightly questionable but we're
gonna clean it up after this is just the
rough
foreign
okay
not too thin that you see the kittens
[Music]
oh Mr spot
that okay
there
oh
[Music]
a little more here
I know I get the feeling it's tilted
[Music]
it's fine if it's tilted has more
characteristics that way
thank you
okay
now I'm just cleaning up the sides
roughly
oh I should have brought like a
Piping Bag
a little more here because I see the
size because you can't really see the
sides here but
have enough cream on the side so we
don't see the layering inside
Festival
not perfect but it has
the memories of making butter
I think that's enough for me
a little more on the edges
show up the most
oh we have just enough
okay now we gotta clean this up a little
bit maybe I can use this
[Music]
make like a
oh
my jeans
maybe not but
[Music]
there's a hole
yeah I should have gone some piping
though so I didn't think I'd need it
[Music]
there's another hole no
I can fix it
laughs
[Music]
I mean it could be better but
yeah we just gotta flatten the top
we can get to the fruits
it drops around the day of a cloth no
no
the mess I'm making
unbelievable
okay I will just do the
spin spin
it's a lot better if I have the spinny
thing at the bottom but
I'm doing what I can with what I have
there's some crumbs on the side it's
fine
but uh
get this like this
okay
hands are shaky I can't help it
yeah we're gonna hide it with the
blueberries that's what the fruits are
for
okay not bad
oh no
definitely I could use like a Ziploc bag
I don't have enough cream for them
okay let's clean up the
bottom here
[Music]
what a mess
okay
good enough
hey this is the face is complete
now for
the decorations one
[Music]
two
three
I'm gonna put the candle here
wait
nice nice
and maybe I'll use these strawberries
um on the top maybe two of them
yeah yeah
hey time for the blueberries
fill in the little blanks
[Music]
oh maybe I should turn it
oh
we're gonna put blueberries at the
bottom too why not
foreign
cover up the the bottom part that's not
very cleaned up okay
it's turning out so good
[Music]
one by one
I don't even know if I'll have room for
peaches I'll try
that
oh
it's so cute
I'll put one more strawberry behind the
candle
yeah
and a big oh maybe not but like I commit
once it's Tinder I gotta commit
that
it's not centered three is not centered
it's gonna bother me but that's fine
[Music]
oh these ones have stems in it
no I ruined it
ah what are the peach slices hold on I
need some
me some
some Precision equipment for this one
I need some Precision equipment which is
chopsticks I don't even know if I can
use chopsticks with gloves I've never
tried
[Music]
Precision equipment
hey it works
[Music]
and it's really shaking it's from
whisking the the whipped cream
I'm playing the whipped cream
we're almost done though we're almost
done
okay
and
[Music]
Chopsticks listen to me please
the cake is definitely tilted but
the imperfections that make this cake
special
that
[Music]
like one more
probably like a decent sized one
that one will do
oh that's too big
look at that
yeah
I wonder if I should like chop some
Peaches I kind of feel bad for not using
it
no we're gonna do that we're gonna chop
some peaches and then put it on the top
there's a chopping board
[Music]
okay
grab a couple
juice
P just Peach piece of peaches
okay
this
where
[Laughter]
okay
you guys like canned peaches I don't
mind it too much I think
let's add a little more color to this
cake
looks good
oh that's too big chopsticks
so hard to use chopsticks with
gloves on maybe I should use a spoon
would have worked a little bit
go
a couple more
all right
maybe like two more in the back
[Music]
yeah
yay
finished
you guys can't really see it properly
but there's a number three on there for
our third birthday together
thank you
[Music]
thanks for hanging out with me today
wishing me happy birthday all your gifts
and all your happy birthday wishes I
really he really couldn't of me you're
here without you guys so thank you very
much I hope you guys enjoyed the cake
accidentally butter making stream
yeah
thank you
and uh yeah I hope you guys also have a
great rest of the morning afternoon
evening I gotta go prepare for the
garlic phone collab soon so
yeah thank you
I think paste some maybe maybe later
but yeah thank you very much everyone I
hope you guys yeah thank you I
I honestly don't know what to say but
thank you because
you know all the things that happen in
our lives led us here I'm glad I can
spend a special day ticket today with
you guys thank you
okay I'll see some of you guys later if
you go to sleep good night uh I still
see you guys next time have a wonderful
wonderful rest of the morning afternoon
evening
bye
[Music]
foreign