n
[Music]
oh
n
[Music]
hello we're all muted for now um was it
party or Allies I think
allies uh we're all muted for now
because we want to make it realistic cuz
we all spawn in different
places uh right so you know we want to
find wow wait I'm really that in the M
no where am I we were saying like we'll
we'll find out we'll see where the most
centered person is and then we'll all
run what the [\h__\h] is that what
the holy sh F was some kind of rat
where's she gone now
left we all go towards the person that's
most centered but for that we will you
know in order to see that we'll have to
add them
uh oh my God is she going to join here
again why did she
leave maybe she didn't want to like
immedi cuz I thought people were going
to make the character but I I already
kind of made it in the test what that we
did and I'm fine with it staying like
that so yeah now I don't know where to
go
um they they didn't add me yet why now I
don't know why to go oh but this is
exactly where I spawned in my test as
well let's check the rubbish so for the
people who don't know we're having a
whole life English collab uh that's
going to last like seven days funny um
do I want these I guess so is there like
a o nice
tab uh H multi backpack is that from
Hollow
packs uh we're all going to try to
survive this is basically
rust but with uh we're not joining a
party yet uh R but
with water cooler
bottle R but with zombie rushes ooh that
will be tasty
oh sh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm going
to die
immediately wait wait wait
okay ah [\h__\h] oh my God that's a
terrifying dog what happened with you
[\h__\h] no no no in my test oh God God in
my test it was so much [\h__\h] [\h__\h] what if
I died no me alone
no great great good
start it took me how long to die took me
like 2 minutes can we calculate that was
not seven days to die oh was
um uh
I'll stay muted until we find each other
in the middle of the map what's spawn
near my pack sure sure sure
sure go go go go go I kept on hearing
those
sounds uh did they see that I died does
it tell the people I don't think it does
does
it okay uh what where what that's not
near my
backpack I I got a completely this looks
way more
nice 7 Minutes to
Die yeah that's
beautiful and there's like Alps over
there this is wait where are all my
Foods no I'll have to find my backpack
[\h__\h] I have okay wait I have nothing
[\h__\h] where am I ah
do you think she saw my dead body I
wonder 7even minutes to
die
die who that person I thought was that a
zombie was that a zombie or wait is my
backpack running
no maybe maybe gigy is scaring my a
there it is there it is wait let me take
this this will be useful are you
going ah I found
it h
hello wait wait how did you do voice
chat again
uh was it not V uh uhuh I probably
didn't set it properly did she run away
don't run away it's nice to have a
friend yeah that's correct uh uh
where input
device R it was
r r where' she go oh well we'll probably
ah oh
H we'll probably end up using Discord
anyway oh is this my backpack no that's
the moldy
backpack uh go I'm so confused still I'm
nervous oh she's gone too it's all a
mirage oh God the [\h__\h] dog is it
still here I I I'm not going to I'm not
going to get too close this time that
yeah there's a dog house over there um
do we know who's in the middle
yet what what is the
middle I don't I don't know what is the
Middle where do we go I can't tell where
the middle is
stream Mirage me Mir you will the bones
be useful go to bio oh
okay
okay okay okay I'll try not to
die
um abandoned rubbish my the mushrooms
from my
garden lovely love it
uh wait where are
they what
where oh wait they didn't accept me yet
probably uh okay let me people will
probably see it and accept
it does this mean they sent me a party
request I think we're not doing a party
just yet B okay B added me so now I can
see where she is ah wow very far can I
set a a marker ah
yes okay oopsie and that will be over
there okay 1.8 kilm not too bad please
be careful with the are the in-game
mushrooms poisonous or are
you what are they talking the party Mama
Mia what
really except
D hello oh but they're not are
they I tried changing Pusher talk and it
didn't work for some reason that's okay
I think there's no like voice activation
I think it's just push to talk no no I
meant I tried changing my key I didn't
realize in voice chat
already actually yeah we're using uh the
party chat but yeah probably move to
Discord afterward okay okay byy it took
me seven minutes to die I see
someone did you die yeah I died like
seven minutes in
ironically no that's hilarious oh hello
everyone hello oh you're also big time
for
materials big strong a lady wow you have
makeup on how do you have
makeup wow you
hello dear sir boing Bo hello sir nice
beard nice beard oh where's this Eggo
coming from to you also very clean and
nicely shaven head I wonder how much
time that takes you every day I think
it's
Cecilia think there's a delay no I'm
just naturally bald I don't have hair on
my head could it be that the ingame has
a
long because of the pain a long delay
maybe maybe maybe we should hop into
Discord
hello God what the hell L that hurts I'm
sorry this is not a joke and now the
zombie will take you so
sorry I didn't know I could actually
punch you okay I think we're moving to
Discord voice check hello
hello oh I think we're good how I get
out of this
this is much better not having to press
the V button I will say why is my mic so
low that's weird let
me kind of quiet oh
God run run I think we're okay testing
volume tag tag
tag can you hear me byebye hear you okay
thank you yay we're figuring it out
together little together
why is it so quiet I'll turn up maybe
that'll help why is it so quiet okay
uhoh bow bow see I get to Stones who is
there weight in this game too like
materals like a a maximum of how much
you can carry in ter in terms of weight
nope sorry guys sorry sorry sorry oh so
you can just carry as much as you want
that's great I think so it's there's
inventory slots that are finite
wait there's a house over here can we
have it well the big goals for today are
to find a place to to chill out in
together um a base even if it's
temporary um well yeah can we take over
this house this looks nice this is
actually a really nice house we did get
lucky wow this like The Walking Dead
house what is happening crouching I
don't think so
enies here though am I
crouching what happens if we die yes
youcha you want to make a bed roll
really
quick
chair I thought we live in this house
there's a PC set up I can stream from
here
that's what streamer
house in the bottom streaming the
stream yeah this bad sounds huh watch
out there's zombies in the house though
there's there's baddies some reason I
didn't think of that
no
coming yay zombie noises don't B me I
thought you
was do you want to come with me to them
uh I'm already trying to make my way
towards uh b f apparently that's where
we're
meeting okay okay so I'm I'm slowly
making my way there we are we are in a a
big house that could be our home base it
could be our home is it upstairs bab do
you want to go upstairs with me we
should go this first people okay what
what are you scared are you scared is
that why it is a nice house I call the
bed but it has a giant hole here I don't
know I don't know about the Integrity of
this house I not sure we might just need
to fill the hole and then we'll be fine
but yeah you're right watch out out yeah
that's true there a oi don't hurt my new
friends I'm running out of Stam so
easy
close alive still alive but they're dead
yeah where' they
go he's got a bit of reach on him okay
it's just Dark Souls it's just Dark
Souls oh he fell I get the stones I may
need them there's a lot of room in
f m bunk beds down here nice I'll take
the
couch is there a way to improve the
stamina somehow you might need to level
up or something oh it's just stop being
jump scared by me thank you
sced on the C
there I'm going
to temporary
the crap guys I'm going to go on a
little trip to find clothes I will be
back to this house oh temporary base
okay you you can craft clothes by the
lake yeah I'm going to make some armor
actually we don't have to stay naked
forever and I'm going to start cleaning
the house cuz you know you guys know I'm
a clean freak I'm sorry it can't be
helped yeah this house is very already
you already reached the house your
bedroom yeah you guys can come check it
out it's we got really lucky actually
yeah come downstairs downstairs yeah
what do you mean like this is so
[Laughter]
broken it works it works now but it's so
broken we're going to have to repair it
so much you think we can find look at
this kie kie look at this giant hole in
the basement it's your
bedroom there is a pool table that is a
good point that is a good point fun us
playing pool together yeah that would be
really cool I think you know what You'
won me over you know a pool table pretty
good that's a pretty good it's a fixer
as they say just got to put some blocks
on crates and stuff yeah yeah a lot of
blocks a lot of crates a lot of block
there's snakes in this game snakes and
they're not zombie snakes they're just
normal snakes oh my God maybe I could
blow it up like in Shrek and make a
balloon out of
it okay put that there and then a big in
the W does any know how to get plant
fiber uh smack grass yeah just smack it
oh there's a water cooler bottle in here
that can we pick it up we could take it
to the water I think the one thing I
remember is that it's really important
for us to find water and not to like
save it like save it and not drink it
and figure out how to craft like water
reservoirs and water Gatherings merky
water yeah murky water will give you
tummy egg probably but yeah it has
denter in it
oh
oh you think this will work if we just
here to but there's nothing else up here
down here else oh
yeah miss the upper right yeah
yum does that mean it's not
working see look we can totally block
this hole it's dead challenge is done
basic surval we have no wood left you
see what where I'm getting right you
guys see what I'm getting at yeah I
think this is a oh I found $8 guys
anyone want to sell me something for
$8 I'll buy you dis infected
water uh can you give can you can I buy
wood I do I have 12 wood no I don't can
I have two okay for
$8 wait let me double check if it's two
yeah it's two yeah for $8 how do I how
do I drop
something the wooden block Cecilia and
Fu I'm still waiting for you to accept
my friend
request oh sorry you got mine right no
accepted everybody and got everybody
except Cil
and how do with fls how do I split pling
holes a thing like a stack I like this I
something you can craft more than one
how you split that stack or yeah so I
can give you
two oh I found it we're totally going to
survive how do you do it oh hold to drop
a swap attack okay here you go I dropped
itks look what I did I'm so smart I'm a
builder CeCe I'm a
builder oh wow you build already you
need a helmet this is not safe working
environment I do not I don't I don't
think she's already got drill
just plugging up the holes ladies
pluging up the
holes I'm going to mute myself a little
bit because I feel like you know when
they're already together in a group and
I'm not there I can't really
talk uh yeah what are gun parts this
early good and cotton cotton do I get
actual Cotton out of that or what I
think I
do B yeah but what window should I break
oh oh I thought the challenge was to
break a window or open a
window oh yeah I know these challenges I
know them I've redeemed some in my
tutorial before like when I pressed but
I was like I can't do that now I didn't
see what you're saying but like how am I
going to break a window like I'm not
near a
house sorry oopsy okay wait how are
we're looking here uh I can already make
them
easy oh wait did I did I use up
everything are we still yeah we're
waiting on making that can only make one
thing at a time I guess and cannot move
while
crafting what what I don't understand
what just
happened is it in my inventory I don't
see it where' it
go what didn't I didn't I just click CRA
to craft
that need more
woodo but I thought I clicked it and
then I was making
it all right more wood I can give you
more wood plenty of wood there is so
much wood I cannot see the
forest how about now let's start with
the outfit the full
outfit wait I forgot I have the axe now
it's so much faster faster with the axe
[Music]
yes I'm just going to get this whole
tree Knuckles of
Steel whoa oh wow
wa that was dramatic all right then
craft this craft that and craft that and
then where where the Mas looks so
silly gloves M wait oh seats that looks
like um that looks like grapes to
me okay more towards uh where was it
here that
way let's check the box though always
look at stuff because might be some good
stuff 1 Point what was it 1.4 kilome
kilometers is longer than I thought
a for wood pickaxe was yeah but for now
yeah for now all I have is this can I
already make a pickaxe or
[Music]
so wait uh be here Stone a stone shovel
what there's is there even a pickaxe I
think in this game you use the stone axe
for both oh no well there's an iron
pickaxe but it's going to take a while
could already get a bow
but I don't know if I'm ready to learn
that
that's like for
[Music]
later okay oh zappy
daap all
right so is this world abandoned because
of a zombie apocalypse or
what that certainly seems to be the case
can I CR can I cross this River
safely yeah you are wet I'm unbelievable
thank you Game I did not expect to get
wet by going into water that is a thirst
to
me stone X dance dance might want to
double check they moved to a different
house
what bruh where are they I mean I'm
still kind of going the right way no
where did I where's my marker shouldn't
be
there okay
okay well hopefully we're going to get
there
eventually another bird's nest what what
kind of
birds nest on the ground out in the open
like
this what weird Birds maybe chickens
because I guess
chickens but not out in the open they
would probably look for like a
like a bush or
so what do you do guys how do you do
it how do you do it out of stamina
m a resource a resource crate do I want
to go back for that I can't recognize
resource crates yet I don't know what
they
look hold who the [\h__\h] is that oh God is
that friends
uh hello oh okay what maybe you guys are
NPCs you hear me jump if you heard
me only only Shield didn't
jumped jump if you hear me fauna oh you
sent me a part of it
oh all right I'm already in a party but
okay
um how do I leave a party
how do I leave I need to figure out how
to leave this other party I'm in that
I'm currently not talking
to uh I'm not I'm not muted I'm not
muted I'm muted in Discord but they mean
in in the game oh Sho sh
it
oh wait I'm not sure I have to leave a
party that I'm in
how does one leave a
party oh but actually um even when I use
voice chat do they even hear me when I'm
in the party or does it
just is it just the people in the
party I don't know how to do
this oh okay it'll be in disc
okay yeah no no no no they're not in
Discord the Cali group is in Discord
right now unmuted but uh the other girls
are still muted partially and just using
in-game voice chat right
now but also I think there's a limit uh
for in-game party so yeah anyway we'll
just I'm I'm literally right there let's
unmute in
Discord
medication what a sworn I made too oh
here we go all right I'm finally where
you guys are I think I I I'm I'm
there welcome home
welcome I see you she's here
welcome Y is it a like yellow the papa
residence yes the papa that's our
streamer
house welcome fit all of us you can
check it out yourself to
okay
to I can make more bch oh oops I need
more more H did someone put that
building block down there and I
accidentally take took it maybe we pick
up yeah just to block the do okay oh how
this is even the corns are dead here oh
there go this place is awesome should we
put our uh bed rolls in here somewhere
did you girls do that already yes yes
you should Kiara oh the bed right
anywhere there's actual beds in here
there are yeah
bed oh wait did you build those beds or
were they just bunk beds by
default for us huh uh put your put you
you have to craft a bed roll and then
put the bed roll where you want to spawn
so I'm taking the master bedroom the
master
bedroom I'm going to make it
too how do we does anyone know how to
make like chests or something yeah I
just made them they're in the living
living room living room where oh there
nice thank you I wonder if I can put
right something on it I'll just put all
my garbage in here yeah sure just
materials and such oh maybe I should
have you'll get to sleep on this cfy bed
[Music]
nice lucky right oh there's
upstairs uh I think I got a building
Cube from the house I'm sorry that's
okay I'll Rec I'll reog it click right
click how do you place a bed down right
click right click okay but I don't I
don't know how to turn it so it will
just guess it can't be on the top no oh
oh I guess I can't place it on the bed
toilet a
water okay oh it's a pretty nice house
maybe we can fill up these holes fire to
clean it what I see work time out I got
kicked
out did we all get kicked out not me no
it said you disconnected okay I'm going
to sleep next to the PC then I sleep
next to the laundry so I can put them in
the washing
machine we have eggs no don't punch
the making
sure so I
guess bur Somey water some some peee
water
[Music]
I think so maybe I do want to burn some
peee water
huh PL block oh we might need
that there was a thing we could do
outside
oh here a visitor at our humble abode a
visitor yeah a good way
about they nice I don't know but they're
not
talking is it just a rando NPC is it
shieldy group
shieldy FAA group did you just attack me
I like this room I've claimed the
land oh
nice press you to use
um anyway we claimed this land with this
block uh what are you doing up my
beautiful G A
[Music]
see sorry we had ADHD
took us so
while it we have someone evil
I'm stop stop I have no control I don't
have no control of my
[Music]
limbs look you look beautiful look this
is my this is my PC setup do you like it
oh
nice oh I can sleep on top of it
actually maybe I
cannot can I sleep under I uh got this
place pretty Co where should I sleep I'm
going to find do you like it very I mean
yeah yeah it's co what happens if
we
yeah I like it I have some privacy too
sure I don't think we need it we getting
anything does anyone want to come I want
to go try going to a farm
okay let's go the let me set up home
here really quick let's go okay I
come well then let's wait for shy shy
did you say you want to you will come
with us or let me to my bed roll okay
okay got to set
that let's wait a
second is there a Traer near here or you
guys traiter
lless oh right a Traer near this
house we haven't found one yet we
haven't done
anything I like that even in the
apocalypse Trends uh thing and we're all
wearing the same style I accidentally
clicked on
something by the way if you guys open
the map you can set a marker for where
home is open the
map you can set a
marker
that this is
a I'm sorry every time I all tap back in
I punch
someone that's what happened I don't
mean it stay away from me okay truth
truth truth please don't touch me do
don't touch me
truth on guys be careful don't hit each
other
[Music]
each all right I'm going to stay back so
you guys don't hit me
God okay should probably yeah get him
get him get that
meat yeah oh legs LIF
disappeared okay this way I think was
the farm Yep this way wait wait who am I
following everyone looks the same a
little then just follow everybody the
one
with follow this the oh de corn okay but
I'm going to have ad on the way that's
okay you can have at any point you want
me yes oh there's corn corn oh my
God we the corn can we this can we cook
cuz I got some meat andato so there like
dead corn and green corn that was real
corn
[Music]
me there is some good corn too L I feel
like we should probably be oh they're
dead let's go yeah there is real corn M
here and there can we get can we get to
plant stole that from you I think so but
I I don't know how to do that kind of
stff got to be a good farmer I think
I'll be fine in hitting apocalypse with
corn that's all I need I'll survive most
of the Corn are dead though it seem no
there's
pl canow we just can't eat the the
people what this one is I me zomes on
people yeah
oh okay this this area has three three
skulls on it I don't know if we're ready
for that oh does that mean like danger
we're going to die yeah look at the
green one the lot's probably really good
but I just don't think we're ready like
skull images so I noticed that the green
corns actually contain seeds to probably
oh they do we can there's a ear corn
they have something different we could
set up a little farm by our home
let's do that can we feel like a
seed there's a house over here
here I see you got this is be careful
this is the three Skool area yeah it's a
pretty intense each other though there
zombies everywhere run run
run you got run what are you going to do
it's okay be fine what are they going to
do huh so much porn
all right I hope the corn re like
resupplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of things oh it's going to be
where the
farmers I so much corn I'm going back
home think so out of Stam yeah I don't
think it gives you anything can I eat
okay we can eat wait wait don't leave
me so we just need the big
ones or the green ones
who wants to focus on getting food maybe
we should split into like good idea food
gatherers this is just gaing people that
stay at home we've gone so far back in
time there's I found a land claim block
do we have to destroy this oh I think
someone put that down I just put that
there for the
quest not a quest I don't even know
where my land block is so if you put a
land claim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage on something okay
apparently
so so like you're safe in the zone I
guess or something like that or the
player who put it down is safe in the
zone it's like your land now that would
be good if we had it by the
house yeah we have one of those I put
one in the living room oh okay awesome
oh we're in the same uh Ally group too
so we should be good to go it won't be
harder for us to destroy each other's
things if we need to exactly are we the
party I have a question um um no party
Ser is
six how do you level up I'm not in the
part anymore kill I think I got to kill
oh killing zombies okay yeah if we find
a Traer he gives Quest and he gives a
lot of exp from the quest want to go
with me on an adventure to see if we can
find the traiter I know where he is he's
really far I know he is one on my map
too yeah okay is it the White River yeah
yeah he should just come to us can share
this way point if he wants to trade he
should come to us that's right he's not
going to do that I think but then he
won't have any business not going to be
our BAS by the way or he's going to stay
in hello oh hello
oh I found
peoplec welcome welcome wait you guys
are all wearing something why aren't you
wear where's your hat there's a hat yes
put your hat on what we should probably
like kill it
oh oh wait no I see a hat oh thank you
yes put it on Oh
yay
civilized need a Traer so where
Thea um he's far I don't know how to
share the way Mark with you guys what
what if you send like a screenshot
I can send a screenshot gloves I'm
missing
gloves oh that
works the craft anything just yet there
is a land claim box I hear sounds I can
make a me
gun meat meat meat is this our by the
way this is our base
yeah we should probably do multiple
campfires what is this land claim block
it's our our home base now this
basically zombies won't spawn around you
see it I put it in the channel of the
map what if we all put our land claim
blocks like around each other so they
won't spawn within a let's protect the
house can we get I don't have my land
block though
so where how to make land claim block
where's my oh this is oh I have a land
plane block um I don't know where to put
it though it won't let me put it
anywhere maybe because they claim this
land yeah is there a Max to can only one
person claim a land are you cooking
Cecilia would make sense I don't know
how are you cooking oh this is Mor me
that's oh here tree maybe right there
trying to figure out where to put this
oh yeah I can't put the land claim block
e oh yeah it's a pretty it's a pretty
large put I am dying of hunger put it oh
I found the place I want to
e all right wow I claimed this
land see if we can cook some more for
everybody much maybe here oh we need
cooking items oh oh I like the their
placement of this fire
right anywhere these days you put at the
fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying pan so
we can
actually
okay yeah oh I found a I found a cooking
a grill outside the house I don't
know put in the
house here near trees is there a town
nearby oh there a town very far
away oh at the
hill I'm going to eat scary food oh by
the way night time soon
everyone oh you guys have a nice campire
out here wonderful we can putes the idea
that I have is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions
oh that's a good
idea that would be great oh sorry
sorry
here cover the river she's here I don't
know what to
do I think I'm going to focus on finding
[Music]
foodion going into voice chat too if
anyone wants to go on an
next stroll I'm going to collect items
I'm going to gather stuff so I'll stick
around the house okay okay okay I will
debate on what to do I will like
deting how does one
acire do things is it here skill tree
I'm pretty sure what is the cornmeal oh
can I eat
this oh you need water to
cook yeah realistic it sucks huh finding
water I
can't for us I can't oh I can more
Stones how do we get Coral like purified
water
boil
eliminated um how
evil
why what a terrible person you have to I
think you need a pot how do I get a pot
bedroom we have to find it find
a now I can cra CRA cornmeal okay yeah
me too oh they're in the other SE I know
how hungry I am
bed hry violence between our allies is
concerning very concerning yeah let's
not how I know when I'm not hungry how
much do I have to eat I have harvested
what the heck okay I think I'm you hear
that my
stomach your stomach sounds like a
zombie
I'm sorry I don't mean it what I don't
know what to do no really sounds like a
zombie I don't need it I don't need it
are you trying to get in oh St saying
that about my stomach it really sounds
like a
zombie zombies I'm going to try to like
build walls or something yeah don't
remember oh we're not supposed to sleep
outside but it's so beautiful the stars
are beautiful coming in stop talking
about my stomach that way how' you
repair those doors I'm
SLA God we don't have closed doors no
windows can we sound proof our house oh
my God oh
my what oh my oh my God what sorry who
did this to
me what the fu anyway I think build a
building block I hope yeah this
terrifying how do I change a building
block to something
else how do you what the heck I can't
man building is
hard maybe if I just destroyed us at
this point how bad is 12% distant Terry
can I hand that W that's 12% bad
compared to zero doesn't seem that bad
double
need an item to building block maybe I
can snipe
too how I'm hoping to just put a block
here so we don't have Windows that
people can see us through good idea
people yeah these zombies can't watch us
yeah think about us and think weird
watch our sleepovers what kind of weird
thoughts you know weird thoughts can you
name why thoughts or weird
thoughts I swear okay that's a building
block okay can I open the door or
no help I need there's a weird
zombie M there's a weird zombie outside
M it's scaring
crony I have a candle what's this I know
where to put this no fear huh ladies I
know who to
Woo you're not afraid of anything
there you go do we need any more doors
anywhere I think we're good I think
they're they all look pretty
healed how' you board them up Kiara H I
just want to place a door
somewhere um there's very this is
Minecraft
yeah oh wow camping songs the acoustic
guitar how do I craft I have a kazoo
oh hey there's a deer here we can
eat unless it's a zombie deer come here
deer a don't need don't e the deer just
snap it ran away you cannot sleep like
Minecraft
sadly you cannot sleep oh no it's evil
Minecraft if
[Music]
only just need one more Stone nice I
just need more wood the trader
Quest do I heal if i s sleep at least no
no I don't think so what's the point of
having a bed my heart is beating so fast
fortify
things I'm low on stamina and I'm
thirsty how do you use this so much is
wrong with you this this you guys
experience thirst and hunger you got to
turn it on turn we God at the right you
see a bunch of wood make sure it has
fuel and then you just turn on like this
oh does this building block even do
anything we have curtains that should be
good destroy the broken blocking block
and a wood block how do you tell what
you need to cook something I have to
join a party a recipe I think how do I
join the party I'll just ignore you can
join ours a
party
definely allies wait no party just like
a yet invite
me Shori can invite everyone
right I received a party invite oh sick
oh can I get one too I'm currently not
in the party I I can't
aim you press just press
buttons
who party good
oh do I need a party I think I'm in a
part
yippe
yippe wow this is so domestic probably
stick around and harvest things around
here but if people want to go expl
thirsty my character is like satisfied
wait how do you experience
hunger what
oh okay bar too just very hard to see
it's a green bar beneath your
inventory so
privileged yeah I know my
invent oh now I'm hungry
okay Welcome to The
Gang This is good for harvesting bodies
if you use the bone knife you can
Harvest bodies like
rust is it safe to go outside yeah it's
safe yeah you can go out
okay y it's day one it's not too bad
right now yeah because it's day one
probably build tomorrow we die though
there's a with glowing eyes you think so
excited bad I think so are you sure it's
not
hoko that's
a shift a click or shift
click shift
click M you you can't build someone
else's area unless they allow it oh God
you have a
curtain place a torch oh can you not
build in the house area oh somebody in
my chat just wrote yeah we can't place
anything in a claimed area I don't know
they can allow it apparently I plac
stuff I yeah the bed I place like random
blocks oh hold R okay let's try about
this one no it just rotates animal fat
oh if you like do this
small hey that's my stuff wait I I
thought it turned into a wooden
block I'll just I'll just pick it up oh
I got to repair it how does one get
animal stuff okay it's okay I thought it
turns
into I'm just trying to cover up our
uh for our privacy yeah yeah if you want
animal fat Kara animal and then if you
right click with an axe I don't see any
animals H oh I probably need
yeah I'll go hunting wait really find
that bunny again I think so you just
need a stone a oh don't you need to like
upgrade with
stone really I have the axxe
yeah or maybe
any I
guess
oh oh you need more wood sorry guys I'm
I'll mute myself for a while I'm like
overwhelmed I don't I I realized I don't
really like it when I mean now it's
better because there's not as many as
before but I don't like it when
everybody's doing something different
kind of uh but they're like all talking
to themselves it's difficult
to like have any conversation it's
overwhelming to
me what's happening out of stamina oh my
God okay
chill yeah it's a lot and I want to talk
to my chat too right but I don't want to
like it's
awkward what is this dooming sound I
heard
yeah many of voice I can't even focus on
what the text says in the me in the in
the
quests anyway this will be useful not
what I came here for but yeah there's
barely any animals here I should have
killed that bunny should have committed
to it laa died bibu died what are they
doing I'm hungry and thirsty oh [\h__\h] I
didn't notice ah okay well first I can
do something about uh first
first oh God no no no
no oh [\h__\h] where did it go okay let's
let's try to use a bar how does this
work I don't know how it works I don't
know how it
works oh God these ones are terrifying
am I even hitting him yeah okay
oh ah I'll be fine I'll be fine he's
barely alive I mean he literally
Golem I don't have any rings on
me what ew what is that oh is that a
person over there he dropped
loot shotgun shell duct tape oh I heard
magazines are nice also oh [\h__\h] my
inventory is kind of full let's eat this
and a a stone shovel oh isn't this good
also do these give skill skills check
out our biks off-road
vehicles copters and more improves
vehicle crafting so I just use it both
of them
sick and a shovel what do I do with the
shovel where do I use the shovel just
like anywhere in random
places let's eat
this let me let me Flex I I got them
magazine for like making cars from a
zombie oh nice good job you can store
that in a crate maybe oh I already
learned it I'm hungry again oh my God
right you're the car person now I am the
car person now let's
go I like it is your job now your supply
of corn that's not a good
sign
scary I have too many things all right
I'm at the
Farm anyone also wants to play Harvest
Moon
Mo the corn monst there yeah it's really
scary probably oh it's breaking it down
oh that's a big
one I'm hiding in the
corn May the home that's a big it's a
big wait oh go what the [\h__\h] is
that what the [\h__\h] why is it glowing why
is the eyes
glowing is it hiding from
me I was going to ask you guys what
skill points
oh scary I want to go back home I'll
I'll hunt an animal in the morning
maybe I wanted to ask uh what do you
think okay here we are uh what should i
i this this is very overwhelming the
skill point thing menu is very
overwhelming like what the [\h__\h] like
wait that's not it where's the here is
that the is yeah that's that is wait I
don't feel safe oh let's help
them I have the corn response okay hope
I don't miss this waa what the waa you
have a gun I didn't want to use it you
have a
gun I got my arrow what the heck I stole
all the a big
booty think I'm hearing oh
sounds like a
clicker all right I'm heading back is it
a lot of zom zoms no we got rid of him
he's gone now there a bit what what are
these noises I'm
so oh yeah that's the dude that was
chasing
me oh crap I'm out of
[Music]
stamina oh no yeah I get the front I get
I'm
infected what you're infected we have to
kill you now I have I have I'm infected
with
ligma what's
ligma thank you g what's ligma I wonder
what it
is oh man here eat some corn maybe I'll
heal you you think you will I doubt it
but I love no but it tastes good we can
eat some popcorn some corn corn or some
popcorn corn yummy sounds really good
all of that I broke into a house you
guys but I want to wait till it's
daytime before okay here come Ona I
trust you even though you're infected oh
thank you I think in the end we'll all
be infected
eventually that's good to
know he's giving us her
Lima yay you don't want it oh I I feel
like you already have it I mean you
already have it
gigy no it's not yet I haven't been
corrupted
yet all right then it's about
time that must stay away from me I won't
get Lima
today I found coffee seeds oh that's
G you seem very knowledgeable can I
borrow you for one second in the voice
chat okay I am moving to three okay
hello hello hello I I I'm like super
overwhelmed with the skills oh God wait
I shouldn't have joined this battle uh
with the skills I don't know what to put
skill points into and what oh God what's
important and
what um um can you assist me you or
don't you know like much as as much as I
thought you thank you I I do not know as
much as you know but minor 69er and
motherload are very good ones to have
cuz they give you more resources yeah
strength skill tree and then they's
Scavenging things that you get more loot
are usually good ones to get so if you
like looting which we need a lot of
material and resources so maybe the
Scavenging perks and then you might want
some maybe some oh wait that's someone's
oh sorry Cecilia oh my God wait wait
wait wait I thought that was from the
okay one second one second
mon Cecilia Cecilia cilia oh really
CIA I'm watch me I thought that was from
the
zombie I was like oh my God committing
in daylight no no I thought it was for
the zombie I thought oh my God this guy
has a lot of loot wow
oh
was composing I read your I read your
magazines again huh you
read it's okay it's okay if I find now
you know if there's a backpack that's
surv well yeah if I if I find two more
magazines I'll give them to you I'll
donate them to you no worries no worries
I have a question yeah how do I get
daylight the sure to connect sorry gy I
had to apologize to cicilia it's
okay okay oh my God there's a a lot
going on um okay you said what perks the
motherload and and Miner 69er are good
ones if you're hitting rocks all the
time and you get exp from hitting rocks
and and then the Scavenging ones like um
69er it's under the strength one in the
perception you go Scavenging perk so
[Music]
maybe lucky looter treasure hunter
ah and then you should probably go into
the one that you
want your main weapon to be in it maybe
some recovery perks what I don't see any
minor 69er in the Scavenging perks oh oh
it's in strength so at the very top
under skills there's like the eyeball
and then there's the muscle and then the
plus sign uh uhhuh so you can swap
through
the yeah oh it's chasing me get away
from me increasing tool damage to bring
down rocks and trees faster
okay
uhuh and uh mother Lo is where it's
under perception so the eyeball
mhm and then you can get I think
generally the ones that are good to get
are tailored to your play style and if
you're scared of dying probably some
health perks but resources are always
very important in survival craft game so
I always think resource collections good
to get
okay okay well I I'll take a look at all
of this then yeah yeah oh there's a
brawler skill you should get that I'm
going to go fisting again I'm going to
fist these zombies you'll put so many
skill points into brawler so that you
can be Auto
fisting they come close to me I start
fisting right off the bat I don't even
ask who they are
I I just start oh I have yet to be
fisted
by oh wait I have to mind I have oh
thank God I didn't use them I can give
them back okay okay oh get hammered big
hitters okay uh if you want if you want
we can go back up or uh you know if you
want to go back to the chaos we can go
back to the chaos we can stay I'm going
to go explore over here too I I want to
join you but let me just ask
give give cilia one
one
Cecilia it turns out I haven't read your
magazines oh really okay you can have
them back here I put them in this crate
here oh thank you than
God did they disappear afterwards yeah
they I see thank you
wait you know what here [\h__\h] wait I
can't one sec whoops I didn't mean to
say
[Laughter]
that oh
shoot oh
darn go give it back golly this this
your uh golly your
reward nice exchange Mar together yay
big HS Mar together
is better Club crafting skills okay okay
I'll go with kie if anyone wants to go
with kie and I are going to the
farm going to Sur okay I'll go to the
farm too oh my
goodness can you guys bring like food
and water I'm
dying let's make the stone ax and things
will go faster oh food cornmeal you can
make cornmeal guys is it better to make
make a completely new club or should I
like aim for repairing this one I don't
even know how to repair it
but also craft a I got Club crafting
skill now so okay I guess I'll make a
new one right I mean does that apply to
this club that I had where did it go
here the wooden Club I guess I'll just
make a new
one okay new
okay I
learning looks important where is
it another what's up
here just let me know if you want to go
somewhere okay you see on the map I'm at
a gas I'm at a stiff tool station who
you're fast oh wow we should go to the
trader and do Quest two though the
trader gives a lot of stu oh you went
there before okay I haven't yeah I went
to the trader before and he me aun yeah
it was on the way huh on the way I
spawned quite South and then that was
the trader it sent me to all right then
I guess I'll go there you think it's
safe to go alone to the
trader uh at daytime it is H after I
explore this stiff tool area I'll come
to okay yeah I'll join
okay do we all have the Traer in the
same location though I think so they're
pretty static okay okay oh there's a
snowy
area I want my snowy area to
be there's a scary dog in there with
bright red alpha eyes no it's the Alpha
Dog alpha
eyes all right I'm uh making sure our
home is up to base or up to Coast or
whatever a cast there you have to have
enough wood
though do we have enough
doors oh nice we do you can never have
enough doors honestly no I don't know I
actually used doors to slow them
down
pretty there's a castle if you guys that
would in the snowy area oh my
God be
lat do we need for the yeah my
character's so
thirsty I am also very hungry right now
yeah I'm surviving on I'm sick of it I
just don't know how not to be we're
sorry crony we are commoners we're
peasants how does one become hungry oh
okay now I'm very hungry I
guess you have learned the ways of the
the common folk ah yes so this is how
hunger is yes
unfortunately oh oh no I'm
hungry I am searching toilets don't
worry I'll find food can you find water
in there oh I found some water in the
toilet let's go oh good oh no
think is helpful can I eat raw corn oh
you okay H yeah we're trying to get
resources yeah we're trying to help
you for the resources you can leave them
in a crate since we'll all be sharing
them okay if we get the cotton plants
then you can make them into are and
heal what in here does food oh this is
not
good how do you ever heal from an
infection
you oh yeah you die oh okay cool just
accept it do get infected I'll accept it
you're dead good to know maybe you just
have to have really good hygiene and it
goes away eventually I don't
know I have accepted this way of
life
oh oh
sure I why there's so many dead corn all
right time to get more wood I know what
they can be us for but I have a feeling
that they're all good or maybe I can
make more doors
what antibiotics and honey honey honey
are
expensive do we have to kill them kill
the bees yes kill at the zombies yeah do
we have to what are you a zombie
apologist I don't know I feel like you
know they might not be that bad trying
to kill you only answer is
kill is this
ore okay I'm going back home kill where
is home where is home uh home is on the
map press
them
home no problem get scared Common Sense
kind of
ow stuff oh yeah I'm just killing one it
looks like like the weather is turning
gloomy oh oh very
yeah is it 7g 7 a.m. or is it 7 half 700
p.m. in the game I think 7 7 a.m. okay I
think it 24hour clock okay good
oh e scary yeah I know many of you guys
are scared of
that yeah they killed my family can we
make Farm that's so
unfortunate I I can make I wonder if you
need a magazine for be a better
idea uh I think you need to make a farm
plot block you need Rotting Flesh for
that in this area rotting I was reading
books yeah I so I think we have to get
the zombie and may your favorite
magazine Vogue I really like wiring 101
hold find good
magazine yeah it was so good I read it
twice
two wiring 101 I just missed two point
blank arrow shots on this thing oh my
character's
tired if I find point blank arrow
shots oh thank you I need to learn how
to
aim o
exp stiff tool shop they have a lot of
stiff tools it looks like oh yeah is G
was like very dangerous you guys could
probably use a not dangerous both of us
we already killed two zombies did the
zombie
kumber
I'm what are you going
decoration yeah I thought people would
be so happy when one at a time they were
they're going to love your
PL my I can't tell if that's a town
cross the bridge I want to go oh yeah
I'm oh I found a a burnt
Forest
the you across the bridge okay good luck
on you good luck on
yours we can go scavaging for
it this way it's tough out
here I think there's a town over here I
can't tell this is a town before
destroying them we need clay soil
and dead bodies not zombes oh human oh
hit the head oh I got hone find dead to
find de
[Music]
carasses doesn't get better maybe should
make a double door in the is that this
must be our bag that's our bag from
before Oh it Mak block like
0.1% let's just grab it
great or is it slow ah it's going down
I'm healing myself with
honey nice honey works why is it so big
if you guys get Li mom just look for um
tree Stomps and
uh get rid of the tree stomp get the
honey and then drink the
honey okay that's
good what's that is that a I don't know
why is this door so weird it's like it's
float snow
honey no get it get it this this is a
useless door doors are usually not so
useless I find this to be a useless door
I don't know I don't know oh it's
probably cuz it's this thing I
see oh that's a
lot
a
really weird okay I'm just going to
focus
on oh that was fine
yeah I need water I just drank my last
sip of
water
theid it's a beautiful day
yay it's kind of weak I
guess I don't know I'm just putting Rand
CRA here car don't drink it Let's Travel
toward the trader and then to find a
deer on the way someone wants to come
with me to the trader oh oh I'm going
there right
now okay I'm at the
home home and we go together okay let's
put some stuff on except for the fact
that there are
doors I'm coming home I was a little far
away I found a
town should I just make a
maze yeah I don't know what to do
here no no no no no need to cook the
water oh I see be Bamboozled that'll be
like why is there so many I have find
some iron if someone needs by the way
there you
go
everyone what's up with the doors what
do we need it for again
for I don't think
so stress crafting crafting Under
Pressure oh God oh we can plant
trees first was for
planting okay
okay this is co going go without I'm so
close yeah I'm so close to home I'm
coming let's just Farm some resources
for now we done all right I see everyone
to split off oh this a building block
okay I'm over here okay go find that
house here go so what are all these
storage crates are they all just like
stuff that we can
call no it's from other people probably
yeah I think everybody has their own
little storage grave for now okay I just
put the I put food in one storage crate
since we'll all be like
hungry so hungry we are starving
it's I haven't water so long
seems like I can name it have a lot of
we
can if you guys go near the farm please
collect more
corn you find a pot okay a pot yeah oh
we can a pot everything how are you
cooking without a
pot we can label the
crates let us
know do you want to go to uh VC treat
okay let's do it okay let's do it
okay this and I don't even know put that
candle there I am so hungry and so
thirsty and there are so
many
people monsters GG I mean this in the
nicest way possible but everybody's
starving GG you're not the
only I am the only one Starving in here
and I need you to give me your food I'm
not feeling so well either
you stand by ta stand by
tax I am I am starving personally I'm
about to go forage for stuff cuz all I
have is corn and I'm sick of it
what how can you be sick of corn yeah
although if you go to the farm please
collect more I'm going to go to the town
the hate corn but please get me more
corn where do we get
water you have to find a river and then
I think you still might need pot or
water bottle to collect water from it
are you K snow can you turn snow into
water maybe you can drink from it when
you're oh it gets heavy
here all right I'm about to wander off
see you guys goodbye goodbye have a
great
one how I craft a tin land M no that's
not what I
want corn Pizza
[Music]
what are we having for dinner pizza corn
again
PL corn is a luxury you should be so
glad you even have
corn is it safe zombies ever come
[Music]
to is anything safe in this world
I found a
hospital a hospital a hospital who wants
to go to the hospital hospit to the
hospital we can cure your ligma
here
y take up the supplies oh okay
cool H oh wow you really far oh am I
damn yeah I found a town I was trying to
find a grocery store but there's not one
in here where's there's a grocery store
I love shopping I love sh we can shop at
the hospital it has five death
schools five oh wow wow I love that
let's
go don't go there five friendly zombies
I love
that I'm sure there's food in this
Hospital of five
friends I am going your way
yippe
[Music]
yippe so giggy did you already do the
like digging Quest from the trader yeah
I did the digging one you're so wait how
did you get to the trador I walked yeah
both you on the way to you guys I went
there how did you you're damn girl okay
maybe I will walk to the Traer he gives
you a gun for free so friendly yeah
that's shotgun from I see that's nice
maybe we should get guns before we go
into the five friend hospital or we
should just go in you're on your way
I'll
wait well well then let's get
[Music]
digging rather than the gun i' prefer
some water and food but okay maybe maybe
at the hospital they'll have water and
food I
see they
might
de you would expect the hospital to have
water people at the
hospital oh that would be a welcome sigh
more dead the zombies yeah compared to
the zombie oh no Undead people that
would be
terrible ooh
purse oh what oh wait oh that looked
like I don't know that looks like Chanel
maybe
Chanel what are you do Rob the zombies
of their PSE no they there was a there
was a purse lying around
oh got me some Louis Vuittons
maybe got them
Gucci here who died and left his Prada
bag here for me oh that's
crazy at this day and age the apocalypse
wow
apocalpse I'm very hungry your maximum
stamina is reduced how do I know
that oh I love the Chikorita
residence like the
bananas the bananas no that's the
Pokemon I learned about that one
today what why did I pick up anarita or
or Chita banana Chikorita Chikorita
Chikorita
bananas I'm eating a raw
egg what what's the goal in this
Quest so yummy G do I just deep dig
deeper and deeper until I find something
yeah you basically just dig down and
around in that Circle until something
pops up for you sometimes it's pretty
far
down damn I'm hungry and thirsty
life is rough man I mean this in the Nic
yeah I know I
know we're all suffering
here I'm not maybe we should just
convert to zombies sis now I decided to
stop suffering oh oh that's a spirit
like a approach yeah yeah yeah I'm out
of stamina this zombie is going to take
me out of my misery die maybe Life as a
zombie is
easier
maybe maybe they don't need like water
and stuff
so I'm not dying getting
closer somebody's
boat I can probably drink
glue probably did you do that when you
were a child
wa I'm taking myself a grave I
realize gosh they do have Louis
Vuittons in the apocalypse come
back how seven bucks is the trader evil
and they just like trap you into
building your own grave and once you're
deep too deep they will like cover it up
like you you covered up in never mind I
think there is treasure maybe they
weren't lying
they were not lying why would they lie
to you in the apocalypse I don't know
maybe you were in in with them and and
you were just trying to kill
everybody I would never you
could I'll oh my God there's a dead body
here that's awesome I'll drink that the
front door is 3,000 HP strong oh don't
worry I'll break it
open are you sure yeah by the time you
get here it'll be
open okay let me try right
now do I go back to the trade or
no thank
you f are you on your way to the
trader yes vaguely
ooh oh sorry that wasn't even on
purpose it's a reflex it's only natural
yeah
ouch sometimes you just
o it's
true ow sell your garbage okay wait a
the vulture is attacking me I don't even
know that can happen do I look like I'm
dead or
what sorry I'm I'm working on it it's
hard to tell I thought said it was done
I'm I'm don't turn
away she'll be done soon
I just just get so tired hitting this
door wrecked me me
too wrecked
I just it's just so hard oh oh it's open
he got to oh I think I'm dying to what
oh goodbye what you don't die to
her
o oh he gives you a choice call for a
gun what did you take G did you take a
pistol or a rifle I took a shotgun oh
he's got oh she lived from a
shotgun oh that's a lot um this is not
good everyone's standing up
ceiling whoa that's crazy I'm getting
out of
here five friends it's five
friends oh your friends are little
aggressive don't worry I have something
to put them out of their misery I missed
run it's okay I didn't have any
expectations you should have
expectations I could do better I can do
better I will do better I'm sure you can
okay just not
today why do they run faster in the rain
ow oh I had shotgun shells oh
oopsy wait how come I can't drink the
rain water I can give you the shot
shells right you have shot why am I so
picky how are you so picky in the
apocalypse I thought it was
zombies it's
just they made
it sell your wood you can easily get
more H oh wait I can drink drink
water what water just just look up at
the sky and it slowly replenishes um
what no way do it really yeah no really
try it no
no
no what person is busy okay I'll try
it no it doesn't
[Laughter]
work why would you lie to life
what is wrong with you you sick freak is
us being in the apocalypse not enough
for you you have to play with us too
what are we like respect for
your I'm just getting
wet I just cannot believe you would do
such a terrible thing to us you hear the
the Glee voice disgusting
freak already torturing enough
you think being thirsty is a
joke gy did you do any other quests like
the fet zombie okay I should though you
should wait wait you know what fauna's
on her way here so I'll wait for fauna
to
dig and
then maybe we can all we can do we can
yeah
questy yay if only it was a shortcut to
get to the Traer why is our house so far
maybe we should build our house next to
the trador we could move in right just
move in somewhere else we're not that
attached to the current house are we no
no oh oh my God what the
heck what if you're in the same party
you can share Quest mhm
[Music]
close it close it close close
it I'm hungry again what is this this
human bodily functions can I buy a bread
or something from you sir
please I have 39 Casino
tokens what nice what are you going to
do with that I want
food but it's expensive
[Music]
what you scared the [\h__\h] out of me like
what is
that crazy so scary
looking my
bad first you lie to us then you sneak
up on me you get off on caring people
lying to
people oh no oh a sham sandwich I hope
hope I don't get diarrhea with this m
you probably will oh search
Fancy what does sham mean I've been
eating those for a while now um it means
you will if you are not lucky you will
poop your
pants oh
oh I only know sham
marriages I only know sham wow sham wow
sham
marriages oh my God there's a person
you mean a dead person oh my God there's
a dead person I see dead
people canned
soups and this is so expensive like in
an apocalypse can you not have some
mercy it's so expensive why are they
burping oh ew they're like I don't know
yeah why was there no grocery store in
this town how did they get their food
H I guess I'll look for my own food if
this guy sells for so
expensive crazy gun hi guys hi oh how is
how do you say it again like I'm home
I'm
home eat
a
no okay we got some stuff you have food
yeah we found food 30 meat we Hunters
call the meat as as
the I I will say you are the the leader
of this group um wouldn't you say it
would be very much smarter to like move
to a house that is closer to the
trader yeah I think that's a good idea I
think for now this is an okay first B
bro you guys are blocking my
way you're
welcome oh no sorry yeah maybe we should
kind aggressive here because we have a
crate that's full of food for move
everything hard maybe you can make a
second
house and then and then slowly slowly
move everything
yeah yeah I'm going to keep these
shotgun shells
though yeah any goodies that you find
just dump them and I think everyone
should get um a bone knife at a certain
point cuz they're really useful M bone
knife and then I'm going to make a
magazine crate and please only take the
ones that that you think you want to
kind of minmax yourself on I personally
am doing like a fortitude strength thing
but for example there's like a medical
journal I have an electrical journal for
nerds okay you're a freaking nerd what
do you guys have you have you found any
other journals so far an academic
one I have she's a she's a what it call
she's a
scholar freaking po Dexter right she did
she's the winner she's the winner of the
spelling be so of course she's smart
that is true does anyone want to try
going to the trader so we can do some
Trader quests because I feel like that's
where the food and stuff will be easiest
to get and water I'm at the water would
be very nice I definitely need water but
first can we get a snack can you get a
little snack first I'm very hungry can
you guys who you're at the house when
you go to the trader can you bring some
food with you to share the only one that
can cook from us is Bib and I don't know
where she is right now so oh we need
more shed try and I'm so thirsty oh I'm
so thirsty I have one water I I'm so
thirsty feel so bad but I am about to
die take it thank you take it okay so we
let's wait wait let me ask what people's
doing one sec I'll be right back oh
thank God what is this I feel so
desolation have food
please you know I could probably cook
some eggs though yes EGS are easy to
cook
o how do you like your eggs need water
dang it uh Benedict no benedic cumber
batch
oh I love my eggs like that also ladies
I a farmer so if you find any Farm
relating things let me know cuz I'd like
to start a farming a little farming plot
okay okay but probably won't start plot
we're actually at the trader area you
mean far farming magazines or something
like that no uh farming yeah farming
magazines yes you're right that's
correct thank you I do have one
blueberry seed by the way yeah seeds
collect as many seeds as we can we're
going to need them okay I have a
potato you have a potato you have a
potato all this time we're talking about
hunger and you have a potato I have one
potato yeah we could share this
potato the potato
yeah it's dire times
Potato
Famine okay I have begged us on her way
and she will make us all food yeah and
then we can go on an adventure to the
trader and see if we can oh I found
coffee you have coffee we're starving
and you have coffee anding we're thiry
St why me how did you find like 30 on me
oh who was that was it you 30 meat yeah
I had 30 meat I put it
30 you have 30 meat like for real cooked
this reaction is
genuine wait the other ones they were
fake this one this one's genuine this
one's genuine H wait so how do you get
water from a river do you just like how
how do you drink it I'm punching it but
I don't get any
water you punch water to drink
oh to get
water when it's raining look up and then
you start drinking we've been through
this we've been through
this that's a
spirit yes ladies yes you w even there
when we've been through this and you
judged crony for it
what these other people in this call
don't know that yeah I don't know what
you're talking about what do you mean
I'm talking about yeah no
you're
just what what did I say actually
happened or are you guys messing up I
have diarrhea no like it did
happen you have a lot going on with yeah
didn't know you were going to Dr I was
just reading out what it said does
somebody have Golden Rod
[Laughter]
flowers space everyone should be
oh my God there's a diarrhea icon on the
screen well I don't want to see what
that looks like
jeez oh I want to see that yeah try
eating some more sham
sandwiches you'll get there there we
go come on mommy sorry about that wait
so wait but just the flower is not
enough right you have to O money you
have to boil it oh also I'm infected uh
I need to take any that's okay we'll
cool you when the time comes infection
I've just been uh eating honey from the
tree stumps it's really efficient good
idea I'll go oh I see the diarrhea
symbol now oh you got diarrhea let's go
diarrhea girlies yeah Yi I feel so
diarrhe
maxing yeah let's share a toilet
together that's I prefer not to go that
far oh all been like isolated as
survivalist for such a long time that
it's hard to gauge is that is that
romantic are they flirting I'm not sure
I think it's bonding for sure yeah it's
dire times get
it I don't think I
understand silly welome home
[Music]
IIM ever coming to the my cooking pot oh
I I dropped like 30 meat on you I can
make bacon and eggs and I can make
boiled meat so I'm going to thank God
blessed the heavens
yes T Monte let me cook we're so lucky
make bacon and eggs for us
y can you make tea too
bio um let's see with the golden flowers
you need jars for that
oh I found a golden rod flow oh I cured
my thank you for the tip oh you can make
you can purify water as well oh please
make yeah yeah we need that yeah basic
it if you have murky water I can purify
it I have that too we have some wow
that's cool okay I'm going to bacon and
egg we have two uh murky water I'll drop
it for you
here you go yay thank you look how cute
our all natural murky for the murkiest
reasons but we close to the Traer yeah
actually it's okay since we're near a
river with our empty bottles we could
theoretically go near it gather water
and just like boil that endlessly I hope
waa you guys have bottles I don't have
bottles infinite water trick you guys
get bottles mouth just open your mouth
look up you can't anymore why would they
do
that what about glass jar split a stack
I'm blind I think right I'm just going
to do a quest now then
okay oh I figured it out okay thanks F
Quest have you seen the trader yet K
anybody has any more cooking books uh
please give them to me yes I will give
them to you I do think I don't actually
know if it's like super important to be
honest I don't want to I don't want to
Railroad and be like oh we have to be
super careful when I have when I don't
know but this is just like my
inclination but maybe I'm wrong so
just I am at the tra do you I have
Golden Rod flowers can you boil them so
that I can drink him we have diarrhea we
can drink him yeah okay will sh I'll
just drop it okay and I'll also craft
armor so I'll read this oh I can buy for
medic if you want to give me the medic
thingy too expensive oh the medical
journals I put in the journal crate
which is over here the journal crate
it's right here so I need I need one
more level in cooking if anybody has
any cooking magazines cuz I can't make
tea just
yet okay the trader sells the tea that
you're making for 144
coins I have S I don't even know where
to get coins Earth to we get coins
that's crazy that's crazy my diarrhea is
going away on its own F you sir anyway
did I take the CL I'm happy for you cook
a bunch of meat right now I found some
acid if you think that could help your
stomach
problems it would help with the liquids
I
guess oh beep so you want to put the the
cooked food in this one the storage
crate which one
the right one and we should try to
figure out how to make a farm the one
that the one that you're looking at you
are where I need to go for my fetch
Quest when did you take this Quest oh I
think you're sharing cuz we're in the
same
party I'll complet it for you don't
worry how are you already
there oh I was just walking wait I don't
think I can do it for you doesn't let me
so you coincidentally there the moment I
what oh you can label the boxes
okay I'm on my way
time what you cook we can make we can
make glue I can eat glue no no no no no
that's not food idea I'm just gring meat
at the moment okay awesome it's like a
big sleepover Sur yeah I love it you
look like the lqu instead of watching
horror take only one item instead of all
the items guys I don't I know the horror
movie is right outside right click oh
control oh water yeah control I got to
drink some that's okay I've been
dehydrated
water should I contr
right am I finally like not as
dehydrated I'm so thirsty as
heck yeah why can my skin not absorb the
water from from the skin why not cuz
you're dehydrated the glass Stars just
disappear not how
stupid you eat them why why would the
Glass St disappear after using them am I
just going to crab out like hearts now
that you ate the glass you f glass
raining how too bad we can't drink it
open your mouth can I open my mouth just
write yeah opening your mouth yeah
yeah you just have to look up at the sky
you still there God already drank all
the water
you still are you still at the quest oh
yeah I think you are please I'm so
thirsty and so
unwet we do am I
drinking I can't tell if they were
kiding maybe no we're not you just you
have to wait it's very
incremental see I've already drank oh
spooky storm okay I'm going to start the
quest what should I do is there anything
we can do at night oh
probably oh cry I love crying me
too supplies in here hope the mushrooms
grow inside
there in here lost focus on my what
zombie okay all right
where doors the quest I think she's
doing a
quest me and G
are you
okay you're on your way I'm on my way
it's really scary it's it's dark I
missed all this it's very
scary oh maybe I can't Farm
here yippee I probably need a farm plot
a Rotting
Flesh yeah we need a farm plot if we
want to
farm might be man I can't make my hops
do any hope you enjoy my triple Quest if
not it's totally
fine I didn't want to I didn't run to
rush I just thought if you going to do
something can I not use it I got to go
there anyway um the food is going to
take a couple minutes to cook but I put
I put food might be one upstairs it
keeps saying chartred meat be meat no no
no no charred meat is the food it is the
food oh really Char wow
is at
yes that's the
option that's all I can make right now I
need one more book to make make better
stuff I want to take both it's okay it's
okay I'll put one back nice stabbing in
the back yummy you're going to eat my
Char and you're going to like spiled
eggs o it's so nice and dry okay I'll
cook some eggs I'm dying I'm dying have
water wait why you dying should I not be
here no no you should be here you should
be here what's happening don't worry
wait should we go into a VC the questers
yeah we can go yeah which one this one
but
uh one to
four I
I this isn't four but
F no one went wait wait what what are
you guys doing are you going to the
trader oh we're doing Quest right now
but I started the quest before F and Sh
were there and it said if you're not in
the raders you will automatically fail
the quest so does it say anything to you
I'm going to number four see you guys
love you oh okay I'm going to make food
while we're here campfire oh
o I have I have a lot of stuff if
anybody oh carry stuff what kind stuff I
don't even
know mechanical Parts iron pipe lead
duct
tape like
food I've got food and and I actually I
guess I'm somewhat fine with food but
water would be really nice but I guess
you don't have water I don't have water
but I have an old sham sandwich that
caused my diarrhea it's now slowly going
away so I'd rather not eat another one I
can I can relate to that I
understand wait so with the fire you can
cook yeah yeah how to you need a PO
though wait I do need a pot I don't have
a pot damn it wait I don't understand
how do I get this skill why is it locked
why can I um you might have to level up
your the main stat so if it's blocked
from getting you might have to level up
strength or
fortitude the big
attribute strength or
fortitude like Master Chef or so they're
not yeah
yeah this one
really uh okay I'm dying of dehydration
oh God no is there no water in this
house water outside
tell me Tell
Me I'm Scared were they where why is the
music so scary you're surely still uh
like healthy in terms of um
HP take him take him to take the
upstairs upstairs oh yeah now he's here
he came down I look for water water
please please why
is there's two zombies oh oh oh oh no I
don't know I've got no stamina cuz I'm
over encumbered how early do you die
after it told you that you will die
there's another one there's another one
oh
God in here we shouldn't be in here I
guess I'll die way
oh oh we left giggy alone in the house
I'm taking I died I have no stamina to
toke him eating me they're eating me not
you respawn respawn come back respawning
running
backwards spawn near my backpack let me
hear
oh how close am I somehow there's more
zombies than there I thought there would
be F where did you go guys I'm hungry
anymore I went into the garage oh I I
seem it seems like I'm going to die
because yeah not even my stamina fills
up when I'm
thirsty I guess dying is the better
option at this point maybe oh they're
fast now cuz it's night time is there
any downside in dying ones besides that
you have to run to your inventory it
changes the difficulty level of the game
oh to being easier yeah and then it like
changes the loot tables and stuff but
doesn't really matter we're just having
fun okay I wouldn't mind so F easier oh
my God there's like 20 zombies okay very
exaggerated the garage it's
okay should I just let her kill me then
my diarrhea will be gone too I'm running
to the garage I'm running to the
garage we're still just on day
two yeah just just just maybe just take
me
down
game the open the Gage I'm opening the
gudge
open I have
I'm going to die let's all just die
don't worry I have decided to die for
the
quest but but the
stuff we'll get it back we can do it if
we keep respawning we'll get it okay I
mean it'll be daytime eventually yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I spawn very close to
my I failed the quest do I have to
accept it again oh they're all around
my they're all jumping around my
backpack
uhoh ow oh they're all eating my body
while I'm is this maybe we should leave
because our Quest is over yeah no let me
just take my backpack how do I take my
whole backpack ah there there's a but in
the top right of the Box yeah it has up
arrows on it uh it says take all uh-huh
okay top left top top right of the box
top right of the okay so not of your
screen but of the Box what if you die
without picking up your things oh I
don't actually know top right of the top
I am also not sure okay I'm out of here
I'm out here we should find the house
next to the trader yeah I think that's a
good idea yeah I think I'm in trouble
cuz I have no speed is it because you're
firsty I think so it's cuz I'm it's cuz
I have too much stuff oh drop I'm also
there's so many zomes but I have so much
good stuff just it's okay you keep dying
you get get your stuff you go a little
farther than last time each time black
strap a super strong there's a lot of
zombies though keep
you ass what I found a a mining magazine
but if you learn it you learn how to
make
coffee ooh
how this is I don't know it says super
strong longlasting coffee that kept you
warmer than a well digger's ass canra
craft black strap a super strong coffee
should I keep this a good Miner needs to
know coffee yeah there's way too many
zombies near my backpack and I'm
freezing hey is your backpack still in
the in the quest
Place yeah oh no no no no no give me my
back I see you I see oh no don't die did
you die again oh no you got yourself
okay you shouldn't come over here
I'm right in front of me no you died
again
no I think I'm in trouble I just don't
want all my stuff to die cuz I had so
much good stuff I think the house you're
next to we can make home there that see
oh no I got a skill on
accident die die die
die this looks like it was a child he's
wearing like teenager clothes I feel bad
okay I killed a zombie I saw someone
wearing a t-shirt that said Riz
Riz he's got the zombie
RZ is it a zombie farmer oh my God he's
got a good Farm gosh a nice
house oh I I found a house we can make
it's really close
to okay the Traer okay I'm almost there
I'll start
putting stuff down I'm
leing no kill the it's not that house I
don't think so that's a zombie house um
which house is it wait distract the
zombies I'll find the right direction
um I can't distract
them okay okay I'm running towards the
house said we're apparently found it
okay okay okay okay I'm going to put a
chest down there are zombies in here but
we can turn this into our new house what
more zombies could you find an empty
house once I kill them it will be
empty won't they respawn there die no
they don't respawn okay ouch they just
spawn around you the Clement
residence oh I leveled up oh oh yeah
yeah I'm in here okay it looks
peaceful Where is the I might be leading
a million
zombies once I kill them they won't be
here
anymore it's very wishful thinking I
like
it wait did I lose
them
hopefully okay I'm just going to offload
everything in here in here I didn't lose
them I didn't lose them oh this don't
worry I have a gun with four bullets
let's barricade the door
away oh are you shooting them with the
shotgun I have shotgun shells I I have
no more arrows okay okay okay this
house oh yeah yeah I put that down
die behind you behind you sorry it takes
me really long time to reload okay okay
okay okay co co your living room die oh
all right a new bed
roll why can I not use the Band-Aid at
this time when I'm
hurt why um I think one of the Bandaids
is only if you're bleeding oh I
think all right well we have a house
so yes is this really where we want to
stay until we find a better place it's
good enough
Med maybe there's a pot in here it's
pretty close to the trader
too oh I still need to go see the
trader you can go pick up quests
together understand this I don't
understand this I don't oh there's half
a zombie on the
[Music]
stove what's for dinner half a
zombie how do you how do you make a
barricade
um you can make spikes and you usually
plant a bunch of spikes outside your
home how do you how do you like
barricade the window oh you want
tactical Warfare book what do you learn
from that oops um oh it's assault
rifles I don't need to learn how to make
an assault rifle I don't either I'm
going I'm going unarmed fist going to do
should we we make a bed roll and then
place it here or yeah I put one in here
okay just randomly in this
house all right and what happens to the
other bed roll that we placed elsewhere
I think as long as you use this one this
is your new spawn
point
okay when I place it it is is
automatically my spawn point or yeah it
say it's owned by you okay um
wait a second I need to heal myself
somehow if you die you'll be full
health that's been my strategy so
[Music]
far oh okay I also make a wooden crate
and place it somewhere we can place it
on the wall oh
nice okay
finally this
oh I
see I got my fists
out oh my God there's a zombie upstairs
upstairs let me punch him don't worry oh
okay I'll let you punch him propably
properly cleaned this place yet of it
dangerous I'm punching him he's killing
me he's killing me you guys need
help I'm clubbing him I'm clubbing him
I'm clubbing him Club him some more
don't fist
me
sorry don't die I forgot there was
friendly fire that is very important to
know fing
me door is locked who's in
here this smigle in here sounds like
smeagle that's my
stomach and this door is locked but
there's like look look do you want to
spend time together hitting this gun box
oh wait zombie I'm punching him I'm
punching him okay okay you guys might
need help
huh we're danging up on the zombie I'm
going to die oh he's hurting me he's
hurting me ow okay I did the finishing
blow with my sledgehammer nice ooh
cardboard box do you want to do you want
to hit this with me hit what oh hell
yeah Diamond chest scary oh that will
take a while maybe yeah but what if
there's something really cool in
here I believe
it has so much HP something must be
really cool in here I think there's a
zombie
downstairs is this house cursed will
there always be like zombies on
Gathering here no I unless they smell us
I'm scared oh I think they smelled
me I'm hiding in the bathroom we have
reached day three by the way oh yay day
three and but we're not playing today
until the seventh day r that would be
kind of long yeah we're only playing
until day four end of day four so one
more hour
four two two okay yeah two more
hour I'm still relatively awake even
though it's 500 a.m. oh I heard you were
adjusting your sleep schedule for days
yeah I I kind of like messed it up cuz
like my 3D live it was like at 2 a.m. my
time because I was trying to be more na
friendly for it and then after that was
my music video reveal so I was just so
excited so I I stayed up long and then I
was like well seven days to die is in
the middle of the night for me so might
as well not fix my sleep
schedule
yeah yeah we should put a land block
land clim block
[Music]
okay fun are you what are you doing
don't die by the way I'm hiding in the
bathroom what I hear the zombie
aggressively shall we save the maiden in
in the spare or how do you say it I
shall I'll shall almost wait I have 17 I
have 17 HP I can't go down there fauna
I'm
sorry I'm wanted to place my bedroom but
there's no room you not live in the
bathroom there's no room in the bathroom
okay don't worry this almost
open okay is it a safe or yeah once I
break this open I'll come kill that guy
or you'll kill me one or the other I
feel so safe around Gigi she's like
hardcore yeah right I have to open
this I have a machine now distress oh
yeah machine gun yeah yeah did he give
me ammo too I uh no he gave me a few
shotgun shells he might be in there with
you
somewhere what if there shotgun ammo in
this chest well I still got to give you
I still got to give you my shotgun ammo
okay you can also put it in the crate
okay okay I got 15 machine gun rounds so
I got to be very careful with
my I'll go
like one shot at a time which is not
what I usually would do with a machine
gun but okay okay all right it's open
open what was in it did we get anything
I didn't get anything did we get
anything I didn't get anything it was a
waste of time giggy okay um bad news FAA
let's say there's nothing in the chest
good news fre be careful it sounds
really scary down here we're on our way
to help
you I'll clean up the
attic you're hiding here and the zombies
not even outside
so
loud he is not inside the house
he's don't worry I will I'll kill him
don't go out there it's dangerous was
the zombie just a mirage perhaps no he's
here he's just he's just Outdoors
oh he's
chilly oh
sick I'm going to sneak up on him he'll
never imagine someone coming from behind
to hit him on the head if I can even
find a way out of here
what I have found a cooking magazine for
people and cornmeal and a chicken
rations he knew I was here I let him in
I opened the door like a vampire I
welcomed into our house he's going to
suck our blood the light in my eyes is
fading no I killed you
stop stop for of
me she keep fake of me I love staying
out of this I love feeling safe and
cozy oh don't worry I spawned on my bed
oh G where is he now I killed
him why why are you naked KY thank God
sorry I didn't mean to that was very
made me very uncomfortable
G where is I I'm just like a really buff
man he's over here should I let him
inside like the last
[Music]
one come in
help I'll use my
sledgehammer on your butt yeah
no by eating
you let let me hit let me hit okay okay
okay okay
7 HP you go geky okay okay okay she has
so
much hey I got her don't worry I got
her good very good good progress we need
to put down the the block the
block oh the land claim block I can try
crafting one L land
I don't want to do the bed cuz I'm
scared of oh wait this is somebody's
backpack is's
probably where's the house I I
purposefully spawned elsewhere now
because I was scared that if I uh choose
turn around wait did you guys already
choose spawn on your bed and you were
spawned in the house yes okay you're
going the wrong way right now I'm going
to run oh you're saying that's me oh
you're so sweet thank you
thank you you're taking you're having an
eye on where I'm going
sister randomly
screaming it's interesting when I have
no she dropped loot she dropped rifle
world do you want to learn how to she
dropped two rifle worlds I need that I
use rifles do you want
steroids uh do I want steroids okay take
it take the steroids off of her body
theb
pun better probably wait where are you
going this green thing oh
oh only 12
minutes steroids I never use items yes
don't you use machine oh I use a machine
gun oh I oh see I don't I don't know
cooking uh shooting is different
difficult I don't know anything
about guns even after all this
time uh oh we have the land clim block
nice I will keep this in here it's
daytime if 4:00 a.m. is daytime we
survived
ew I don't know what I expected to
happen I punched some guts until they
exploded Yik it was it was very
gross is that zombie or a person we
survived night we did it you where in
the distance yeah yeah I'm looking at a
car I'm opening this car are you looking
into buying a car in this economy I want
a car so bad we should get a helicopter
aim big or go home a little too big yeah
you can have helicopter in the end game
oh that dream is too large for me h
maybe too large for seven days I want a
bike I want a bike oh yeah there was a
bike part in the you found right yeah
handlebars for my new bike
a what's that let's go get a quest
oh Nest I'm crafting lots of arrows o
nice arrows are always good I should
probably craft some more too
really I haven't crafted in a while what
do you need again
arrows wood and
stone wooden Stone and Feathers
M pretty sure
yeah okay I've neglected the
feathers
e keeps punching ew they keep exploding
gross leg e
gross but I got 80 XP for
that we're going to be so we have to be
the richest people in the
apocalypse I have seven books seven
books dollar yeah oh seven books are
dollars what bucks dollars I wish I had
seven bucks wait can you spend money
here yeah at the trader but he's so
overpriced does he take cash no you have
to uh sell the cash you have into like
his kind of coins you your dollars are
worthless
oh there's actual bores and Bob and
coins there
is did I just eat one buried
suppli I'm scared to go in should I go
in hello oh that sound
hello
hello I got a quest to go dig stuff up
oh is it the ah it's the first Trader
Quest I guess yeah okay good yeah start
there and then we can try the the the
fetch Quest again at some point
okay together oh I have iron arrow heads
do you want that Gigi
okay can you use these
brass I found brass it looks like
gold ooh but it's brass brass yeah brass
we can make a a trump bone with the
brass yeah from bone
champ I have a quest 500 million miles
away oh can probably make bullets what
quest is that um I don't know you see it
on your map but it's called tier one
clear no I don't think I see yours maybe
she needs to do that okay I'm going to
run over and kill them oh maybe hey wait
no don't go with me too later
okay I I'll help fa with digging yeah we
got to do the other one
mhm dick dick D another sandwich
no don't eat that
fun dis Terry sandwich I'm getting used
to it really can we build tolerance
towards it I think there's a perk you
can buy oh but I didn't buy it do I
have uh one
point H chat tell me what to where to
put my point if I want to be able to
make healing items
items o we need Aloe
Vera right but can you cannot make that
by
default I think there's a book for
[Music]
it cuz this is just boosting your
natural
healing am I just supposed to
dig magazine only oh really okay did you
start the quest
yes oh no should I have
waited no you can start
it
okay I let my device
die uhoh not your
device not myice digging my own
grave you are I will be burying you
here where's my shovel this my shovel oh
how found found it food here I will dig
your way out there's a zombie I will
kill this zombie instead while you dig
your way out I'm
stuck I'm stuck don't be stuck I'm
killing him he has a very cool shirt
very not a mustache where are
you what oh you're in the you're in the
you did
did
w how how can he
jump how do you get to places so fast
gig it's almost like you're
cheating I run really
quickly I'm getting him I'm getting him
oh no I don't want to be in this hole
ah
him oh sweet sweet
exp okay we can go turn in we're going
to the trader again so we can turn in
the quest okay now once you accept the
new Quest I'll go towards wherever that
starts and then we can start it
together
back I have an aloe vera
seed that'll be great for making an aloe
vera Farm maybe yeah need those for
heing right medicine y
yeah
yeah ah okay I put the shotgun shells
into my wood crate you can take it
whenever you want thank
you wait am I going the wrong way wait
it's this way
right yeah it's that
way okay I'm out of stamina and will
this automatically be in the same place
where we were before or is it like
randomized I wonder they're random Quest
you can pick which one you want to take
and then I took one that's really far
west why would you do that can we get
the same no that's in head I know you
can share them yeah cuz that's what was
happening when I started the quest and
you were there then we were sharing it
actively but the people who weren't
close to it were not sharing it I see so
we should start it when everybody's
there at the objective
so I'll go towards the Traer for now cuz
you girls are there
[Music]
ugie check what you need to craft better
gear like wouldn't I need a new magazine
for
that you
might and this menu is just so much I
feel like rest was easier uh heavy armor
like that one maybe
he has books he has books but don't so
expensive we can find our own I know
what to scam
yeah yeah I need an armor
magazine oh I'll return back to the
house real quick cuz I have 5 million
items again oh the arrows me too
actually oh you are coming
okay I see you I'm here I see you yipp
salvation no no myness myness you took
it from the bird I am the bird mother of
all birds me running away with feathers
in my
mouth you have eaten my children
feathers oh my God you are the most
terrifying of them all you're so happy
about
[Music]
it FAA I'm so sorry I can't believe you
did that do we have to just pretend like
everything's fine because otherwise she
will go against us she keeps defending
us from zombies so I think we have to
okay this world it is kill or be killed
it's like we're befriending
Sauron is it that bad it's not that bad
okay I gu that's a bit dramatic we're
just the befriending
ad oopsie sorry fun you like Lord of the
Rings right yes you did you try
watching rings of power no I have I have
not is there a reason for it should I
well I people [\h__\h] on it so much but the
second season that just aired it was
pretty good I'm so scared to say it I
think I could like it cuz I really like
I really like fantasy and I really like
lord of the ring setting so yeah yeah
yeah yeah people will probably like
every time I bring up rings of power my
chat goes like shut up I don't want to
hear what you're saying but but the
second season was pretty pretty good
so if you just want something more like
you know like fantasy just see it as a
separate fantasy show you
know ah it doesn't need to be good for
you to like it yeah what does that mean
wait say that again slowly it doesn't
mean to be good to be good yeah yeah
interesting te wolf is my favorite show
ever you think that's a good show gy
wait don't run out come back oh did you
see the ammo in in my crate up
here top left why is it up here yes oh
thank you not in the
way
okay well then shall we uh did you guys
already accept the quest from the trader
or did you just I have one Quest I have
not accepted okay well we can go to the
really far one we'll get it once we're
there for
gigy okay
okay we can see there's anything fun on
the way too okay any books to
read uh I'm laggy literate oh yeah that
was
laggy let me make sure that I
have I isn't it why is it on my compass
oh I see it it's 1.6 km West O all right
but let's not get into too much trouble
until then because otherwise we might
just arrive there dead
no no it's
fine fauna you know what somebody says
what fauna likes Twilight cuz it's bad
it's not true I like it I like it cuz
it's
[Laughter]
good you haters in the chat you
haters I mean I've never watched
Twilight so you never watched Twilight
yeah I purposely stayed away from it and
perhaps it was the right choice
but I I don't know but you know I don't
know vampires are like a little bit too
tacky for me what about werewolves
Werewolves too you might hate it
then but if you love anything
vampire you will probably like
it even in Sims I didn't like the
vampires s a little strange vampires
yeah those aren't real
vampires yeah no they seem pretty
realistic to
me have you seen a real vampire the FL
they act like The
Sims I I assume that Sims is a life
simulation so everything that is in
there must exist in real life yeah I see
they teleport into your house and then
they play on your computer until you ask
them to
leave have I been deceived is it wrong
have I been
bamboozled real vampires smell you from
a mile away and then they smell your fa
Mon oh no it's like they got a good good
nose they do and then you can smell so
yummy to them but gig are you also a
Twilight fan then no I'm a werewolf fan
but I like vampires too but werewolves
are in Twilight no
but if you're a werewolf fan Twilight is
not going to be a good time it's a
mushroom Mining Company mushroom M on
there's an RV in here do you think
there's
stuff Wait f
wait are are you should we go in there
without gigy I'm not sure but it looks
interesting I left
you I'm be liing for the quest okay okay
okay oh yeah wait where where is she e
oh that way that way I'm at this cool
thing got you oh the RV
e yep like Breaking Bad yeah I am
Breaking
Bad ooh I think Breaking Bad ruined RVs
for me cuz it's all I think of now I
didn't watch Breaking Bad either wait
you should watch Breaking Bad I should
yeah I watched it recently it's good and
better call Sal too is good there's a
pile of books there's a a harvesting
tool crafting skill book and a
workstation crafting skill book W that's
a
lot I'll just take the books for now but
I won't use them so we can share a
picture of one of the game developers
dogs every time I see like a regular
photo of an animal in a video game I
just assume that it's one of the
Developers mean that this picture Tre
animal is this does this mean that the
picture of this bird here is also from
the developer of the game no this is
like a pho did you see this one or that
is the developer this bird looks so
humanlike oh yeah this is a dog on on
someone's line and then this Eagle why
would why would the developer not have
an
eagle he could own one I can imagine him
owning an eagle if he wanted yeah
is that
legal probably not but who are we it's a
legal
eagle have you guys SE illegal the name
of the developers of this game no idea
like when you copy pasted the like I
forgot to do that what their name is on
that on that copy paste
thing their name is on there yeah yeah
you should look it up huh I forgot to
put it in my description cuz this was
very last minute the you fire
poost wait she's running oh wait what oh
Ki just like runs away and loses
us got to be fast in the
witer licks the ground she went this
way she's on a mission I use my vampire
senses can you smell me mhm
oh my God I found Oh I thought this was
a church but it's
not that is not a cross that is I don't
even know what that is wow those are
lights oh it does look like like a the
vultures
yeah I thought you were a
zombie F the vultures please oh we got
it I was so mad cuz I thought it was
like a regular vulture
what is it not a regular vulture it's a
zombie vulture and you can't eat it I
feel like vultures are just always
zombies yeah kind of they're very zombie
like all
right get down get
down oh I can't collect my we're doing
so
good did I get it we're doing good
indeed I thought you were a zombie
it's
there here in this world it's killer be
killed I want doggy dog I want to get in
and punch him punch him he sled him
let's
go
ow what's
inside this guy's kind of strong he's
slapping me uhoh he has stronger fist
than
you I'm beinged by the zombie oh that's
the ammo I need nice oh it's a
lumberjack um he's strong he's very
tanky ah he can
jump there's something the magazine wow
lady can I have your Dr I'll avenge you
I'll avenge you oh
no he's eating eting I'll stop him don't
you dare eat my friend's corse oh he's
he's dead he's
dead
a I want the dress give me the dress
lady there's a dress she's wearing a
nice Dr really nice dress oh
H wait did I lose my experience do you
actually I thought you didn't lose
experience when you die I don't think
you do wait what's purple the purple bar
oh yeah it is is that food the food is
it lower it is I think unless I leveled
up can I level
up think I leveled up actually you're no
longer infected so we won't have to put
you down you would do that you would put
me down I might have to Old Yeller you I
don't want to do it think of the rabbits
Lenny the rabbits are so beautiful going
to have a nice rabbit farm just look at
the water and don't worry I zoned out
for a minute what are you talking about
I don't think that's old
[Laughter]
yell well do you want to be a dog or a
human we're talking about um putting F
down don't she has gone through too much
already yeah you have to go through a
little more why no what are you trials
you're putting her through should we go
across the water or should we go around
the
water is it smart to travel through the
water are there sharks in the big Waters
no well then but you will get
wet is is this guy did he used to be in
a b biker gang yeah right he looks like
the biker in
GTA except for the helmet they weren't
hi
him damn he's buff he is really buff
die fauna has to go for a cannon event
bunny hold on guys I want to kill this
rabbit no I want I want the animal fast
no don't hurt the rabbit I'm sorry but I
need the fat this is about Survival how
will we eat no why is the bunny it
became a fish why it's like oh we killed
it it became a fish did it Fly Away it
no it dived
away in the water yeah it just went like
onto the ground in the water like really
far really didn't want to be eaten by
you has some crazy survival skills
bunnies on the water I guess we can go
around cuz there's so many houses nearby
do you want to look into all them yeah
who am I to turn down a cool house a
boat we have that that would be nice
it's kind of a weird boat though looks
like get on my private
yacht yeah me when I'm inviting women
over yeah I have a yacht this gives the
impression that this is a
shop because there's a neon sign
open but I don't believe it oh hi
zombie hello
zombies ow oh my gosh they have sealing
zombies in here what ceiling zombies
just a follow of that it's
terrifying ceiling like a ceiling maybe
it's hanging from a ceiling fan maybe
the ceiling fan was the curse the the
cause of
death ceiling fans nowadays guys be
careful some of these zombies are so
tanky yeah I know
now they don't get that fast it's
dead sorry I might have punched you no
no yeah but if we go to so many places I
I feel like we might be very hurt by the
time we get to the destination we just
we'll just respawn you know about that
right I just got a [\h__\h] ton of money
from
from the cash register we can share our
findings if you want Oh two
magazines a wood splitter mod we're rich
electrical crafting skill and
workstation crafting
skill do any of you use 9
MMO I use 7.62 very specific and I have
found a pipe
rifle a fully built pipe rifle I have
ired do you want one fa because do you
have a gun yet no I don't use
guns hey weren't guns the the uh reward
for the digging Quest I got a I got a a
pipe weapon oh okay a pipe weapon and a
book a that's a great reward no book is
the only one that came with a book it's
the only one that improves your skills h
I'm the best
one uses the same SE oh nice then I'll
continue using cuz I have that
ammo okay
well this was so I'm running out of
space yeah I'm full up on garbage again
yeah that's also why we shouldn't have
you know gone so far so much fun stuff
we can
consolidate GG do you want my feathers
okay learn did you run away
no
[Laughter]
no I'm here I'm here will we ever run
into mountain lions I have a magazine
that teach that that gives us 10% more
damage against mountain lions mountain
lions you not that much riding flat okay
do you want gas what gas okay what about
you're just giving her your trash we're
consolidating yeah it's called clay
soil uh no not really do you want a
splint maybe that do you want um cloth
fragments and plant fibers and [\h__\h] and
maybe cotton
[Laughter]
oh how about a sewing kit shotgun shells
I'll take those oh yeah she'll take
those nitrate powder I have nitrate
powder
pow how do I take one of these I'll take
that do you want a
mushroom just a singular mushroom yeah
do you want singular
cornmeal okay I'll take the corn meal oh
my God girls do you know how I separate
one item from another um right click
potentially yeah you're right alt right
click okay does somebody want this
magazine it's a good one
four oh I read a few of these are you
read if you get fun on then or you could
get even
stronger for you oh I read a few of
these too oh you too you did too you can
both get
stronger you want a seed maybe I'll take
it back cuz I only read one do you want
another
seed
okay oh the seeds H I'm leaving what oh
gosh we're following we're
following I guess we can go across the
water I suppose okay Quest I'm on my way
Yi oh there's a car in
here who who
drowned guys I can't breath car ground
what kind of question is that it's
telling me that no way you can't breathe
here why not I don't know why can't I
breathe start reading everything
game's
broken can
I my stamina okay this is why maybe you
shouldn't swim across big Waters because
my stamina is uh am I going to die I'm a
little SC I'm driving I'm driving I'm
driving I'm ding I can't guys guys just
make it across just my stamina loaded
back up okay while I was
drowning how am I thirsty when I was
literally in the
water this question will never leave us
I suppose yeah wait this water looks
clean maybe we should it it's very green
I mean
[Laughter]
blue oh nice
shot die oh
wa I think there's another one I would
really like to find a cooking pot I know
right they seem rare for like how much
you need them yeah where's our cooking
pots he's dead don't worry we're only
400 m away from my
quest it feels like a much longer path
than
that we got so many goodies on the way
it's
true oh this is true I have terrible
news everyone m is there more water no
but I I can't breathe all of a sudden
that is a
problem just make sure you're full on
stamina before you start yes oh but it
loads back up worry even when you're
drowning it loads back up we'll
survive oh maybe not yeah we'll be okay
and this the stamina goes down very fast
yeah it kind of does don't
worrying drowning okay I'm back just
keep I'm drowning keep your head up I'm
drowning and I'm back it's a fish on the
over here drowning oh God Dodge him
Dodge him and I'm back and I'm drowning
and and now and now we're
back no I'm drowning too don't worry you
when you left no no oh oh I shouldn't be
sprinting huh I didn't know I was
sprinting in the water I didn't know you
could it's very fine when you're not
sprinting
I'm drowning stop sprinting it's fine
when you're not sprinting There's a
Zombie over here don't look at him don't
make eye contact I've already made eye
contact she's walking in the water maybe
she will turn into a drowned in the
water how could she do that let's see
does she change no maybe she'll have a
trident when she turns into a drowned
that'd be
sick I realize now you're talking about
Minecraft I thought you were talking
about The Witcher for someon no oh did
you watch the
witer no I
didn't but I did beat I right I right
you were playing it you beat it you beat
it well just the just the base game I
still have the DLCs to play I'm going to
play it at some point too but you should
it's really
fun it's good right now I'm playing
Zelda and then also now I will start
playing Diablo again because the DLC
came out Diablo
yeah gy you did you play the you did you
did you play the main story or are you
going to start from the beginning I'll
start from the beginning okay okay and
we can get together for the DLC yeah do
you like AR RPGs
FAA what is
a did we talk about this what does the A
stand
for reality
it's like the top down style of game
RPG yeah kind
of like Diablo yeah yeah Diablo
4 what about I played torch light too
what is that a long time ago I think
it's that's just like Diablo GGY GGY
stop pH it's really far behind just wait
I'm I'm coming don't worry Okay
Okay g gy gy so fast I'm sprinting yeah
but once I get here it'll be over I'm I
think I'm half actually halfway through
the main story so like I'm pretty close
apparently to the main story ending and
then I'll wait for you ay yeah I need to
maybe that would be better than playing
uh World of Warcraft together I don't
know we can do both we can do you guys
to play wow yeah you want to play WoW
too I'll play WoW with you let's go I
knew you were a wow kind of
girl oh wait now you're both so far from
me play WoW once and my experience is it
took a million years to level H and then
I got tired of it so I used like the
level boost that you get when you buy it
but then I switched my class and then I
had no idea what my class did because I
was suddenly like level different class
H well the thing is I already told gigy
we're not taking any kind of level
boosts no level boost yeah cuz I feel
like it's for the Nostalgia you got to
grind through the quest and everything
go for all the beginning like areas that
you that you experienced in the
past think when I played it was like
when was it it was like in
2020 or
something no maybe it was earlier
2018 and I think they like paired down
the leveling a little bit since then M
cuz it was very long at that point maybe
there's exp like experience
Bo I just don't I mean like the the
something that boosts the rate of how
you get
exp I don't want to boost the level is
this the quest spot
or yeah it's the quest spot hey did you
start it yeah I started it I think I was
no am I I did do I have it I think I
have it okay okay oh I think I I have it
too okay
yay dropped loot
loot a he's got shotgun shells take them
yay more
shotgun oh jeez they're here I thought
they were dead I don't fit through the
door how did you make it through the
door I haven't been
eating lost some weight okay I got rid
of the door
get him get him get him get him oh
there's so many of them oh this is such
a cute like American
Diner how lovely not sure about the
customers
though maybe we should call the manager
like this is not how you should do a
business here oh I missed my shot I am
not throwing away my shot you haven't
missed your shot with me
yet really pointing my fingers can we
get married on wow is that a thing what
yes I'm we have to have a wedding on Wow
we can invite everyone to our wow
wedding oh God we got to go to the to
the to the
Inn yeah what is it the
server spicy time and spicy time in the
in take off your armor oh we to
consumate our you just sit down on a on
a bed in World of Warcraft you can
literally not do anything we stream it
everyone has to see our marriage and
everything after too yeah otherwise it
won't be believed that you know that we
got married back in the day in medieval
times is there zombies on the roof I
think there might be zombies up there
kill them we haven't times for royalty
you know there was always people there
watching to make sure that the the air
has been placed in the lady you know I
don't want to die I don't want to die
this Ison up here yeah this I'm also oh
my God don't worry don't worry I'm
taking the shot I'm taking a shot
okay I'm sorry I'm just really into
medieval
stuff like wow is wow wait I'm dying
infed too I with an
arrow who hit you with the
I don't know that the zombies can do
that it's
crazy I didn't know the zombies knew how
to do
that that's what I
get uh anyone still alive we did it we
did it we did it we cleared the quest
did
it shotgun shipping crate is it always
shotgun gels Grave Digger
mod 25% more damage shot we hurt the
hurt the dirt hurt the dirt do you not
want the shotgun shells oh where are
they in the crate oh and there's 9 mm
ammo which I don't think I use do I does
somebody need need the 9 mm
ammo I have some in my inventory I'll
just hoard them do you need
7.62
ammo uh I need yes I need indeed oh I
drop here even though I have yet to use
my gun I'm scared to use it there's
another photo of a dog and I'm telling
you it's one of the developers
dogs oh look at this dog we have do you
go cute you
go this is wearing an outfit on a couch
so cute this is totally one of the dev's
pets that is someone's dog for sure
they should have name plates too yeah I
don't like this dog you don't like this
dog that's the kind of dog I don't like
I'm sorry where's the cats yeah where
are the
cats actually one of them is lying next
to me on on the bed I can't believe
she's still here normally she normally
she goes away when I'm talking CU she
knows I stream yeah I don't like you
talking no no no no she likes me talking
but she knows when I stream cuz whenever
I talk to the computer she gets it and
then when I'm done talking she
immediately re-enters the room yes
you're giving you your privacy our cats
are so smart I thought it was only I
thought it was only my cat when I scream
and leaves a but when she's like really
really needy then she will stay in the
room like now she really wants to be
next to
cute yeah it's because like I
interrupted our nap that we were having
and now she's like what the hell where's
my nap I was supposed to have a nap with
you so now she's here cute smovie it's
her bedtime it's kind of late for her
it's always her
bedtime how much HP do you girls have
83 83 but at least fin Arrow we can try
to go straight back to the trader
without yeah let's go to the trader yeah
wait I want to drop off all our item she
de she dead oh damn it okay next time
we're in danger I'll test my
gun this looks like don't worry guys
we're only 1.2 km away from
home that doesn't
sound oh oh I just realized that by the
time we get there he might be close wait
he closes he closes at night he hates us
oh well we can sleep over it should we
go to jimbos wait that store looks
really cool I want to go to
jimbos one 00 worms for
you yeah also here is
a zombie there's a lot of zombies at
jimbos wait where did you go yeah let's
let's save my ammo for the Jimbo uh
zombies the jimbos jimbos we are on our
way uh is this a good
idea yes it's always a good what's wrong
with dying and coming back to life
workbench it's a destroyed workbench
all mail
boxes steal their mail yeah mail boxes
are fun free of
them I can learn how to make a
coffin oh that will be
useful wait what do you do a
coffin I don't know sleeping
them like a vampire a
vampire oh ranches for one wrench oh
those are useful I think you can use
them on the car on the car do items have
levels they do or do I have three
wrenches maybe both or it might be a I
think it's a level three wrench okay we
get inside here uh the door is locked I
want to be inside
jimbos
ow I lost an HP on the fence
oh can we break this oh I'm dismantling
it all right oh you're C you're
crazy oh there we
go uh it's very loud in there you zie
behind you okay how do we use this oh oh
is that
you tast m she's shooting a oh okay
smoothie left my cat has decided this
this is enough
screaming oh the vult the
vultures Jimbo watch out I have a
shotgun with your name on it okay okay
oh he has
mood well it seems uh gun was very
efficient you want some 6 7.62 mm ammo
oh
yeah I hope Jimbo has a
pot I know how come none diarrhea tea I
can eat sandwiches
again is that what it is
yeah I have found so much
water ity water a lot of water like
water we can't drink because we don't
have a cooking pot I might drink it
anyway you want to drink for you kiaha
what water ammo oh okay that's nice
thank you I found some water I found
some pure mineral
water can I please have you can drink it
off of me after I kill this your belly
button yeah you can sip it right out oh
my goodness that's the best way to drink
water it gives it a little bit of a
taste you know a nice
taste get him get him I don't want to
waste my ammo too much okay you can have
my pure mineral water let's
go what's in here oh they're stealing
Zombies watch out ceiling zombies cute
the ceiling
zombies Yum Yum Yum I'm punching his
head
ah oh
no okay head shot come
on oh yeah oh yeah yeah oh wow that
looks like fireworks oh my
God you
good oh
no I'll be okay where are you down here
I jumped down from that room oh wow oh
where did she come from there is quite a
bit don't kill me
out I have one HP one HP all right I
missed my shot she sorry sorry sorry I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry for screaming
don't worry I won Miss this shot after I
drank water man now the water was for
nothing don't worry I won't miss the
next
shot
ah so I will spawn near my backpack
now oh oh
no wait where okay they're gone we are
safe
scary I'm coming to get my backpack
oh there's somebody here still oh okay
die whoa you w oh God I thought you with
zombie my
bad Jima where the cooking pie I like
how unlike with was was it like that
with Minecraft when you pick up all of
your stuff it goes back into the exactly
same slots where you originally I love
it yeah
right why are you in a
soup I'm checking his
boats boats boats boats nice
boat he's got these homemade boats
too everyone in this world could only
make
boat can we get it
started I will
is but there's helicopters in the game I
wonder if there's also like any way we
can have our own
boat swim anymore it probably wouldn't
even be worth it right cuz are there any
like real big like oceans on this map
probably
not that must be good loot oh it's not
really well oh should we be swimming
back to the trader oh is it going to get
dark soon yes yeah we should try to make
a way
back wait do we have a fire can we make
a fire I can make a fire or should we go
back we could go back okay I'm going
back okay am I cucumber no I'm
cucumber I'm so
cucumber damn that's why we should go
back
ladies I want to grill some corn M me
too but I don't know if I can actually I
have the recipe but I don't know if you
need a pot or grill everything in this
game needs a podt we don't have it I
know it's like the apocalypse can't you
like improvise a little bit guess I'm
Hammer just throw the corn right on the
fire it'll be
finees let's make it lotes you would
think there' be more abandoned pops out
here too yeah right
maybe the trader has all of them all
right Trader we're coming
back when does he
close too early he's probably already
closed now yeah cuz it's like 10 p.m.
now almost he opens really early in the
morning but like
six okay we'll get there we'll still
need some time to get home
anyway wait where's I'm following fauna
fauna are you following gigy no I'm
swimming s oh she's still in there ah my
leg is broken and I'm over wait do you
need to SP oh yes I need one of those
flints I
you no don't worry I'm almost there are
we going to have to take you out back
and shoot you no I'm not ready I'm not I
so much to live
for the splint thank you what is the
splint does it fix legs yeah it's going
to fix my leg also it's actually broken
okay it's not it's not my leg's fault I
just have a fracture so it's not going
to help me I'm going to eat this egg
instead oh I can hold the Flint though
since you're over
encumbered okay is a raw egg good no no
does not taste good at all do you want a
lamb
ration I'm disappointed in you girls
that you're not ready to eat a raw egg
especially you gy thought you were hard
want ear of
corn I'm eating the eggs you can have
this corn me or fauna I don't need it
you want corn oh can I'll take it but I
have like I have chicken rations and
peans just one each okay I well we
should get running if we stay in one
spot for too long they'll smell
us just like a vampire will imagine the
smell of us
combined what does it smell oh what do
we smell she's so fast I missed she's
too fast she smelled us she's killing
me she's a
Zoomer but I hit her no oh you got her
oh she's still alive
damn okay I think she's dead good job I
mean we could just run away from her
but we get exp right yeah we get exp
okay all right you ready to swim across
the ocean ah my leg is
broken no good thing we have another
splint
wait the zombies are coming wait can I
swim with a broken
leg yes if you want to survive you will
wow oh hey it heals in two hours oh wait
that's pretty good H
speed can heal your leg like that oh
zombies Sprint at night that's why
they're so fast makes sense not so fast
scary
like I am I'm definitely swimming
slowly what are your thoughts on zombie
vampires I mean vampires are kind of
zombies right they're Undead so do you
think zombies are hot no there's only
one hot zombie and her name is Ollie hot
zombie yeah there's
one like the ones in this game not
really the ones in the dress still have
kind of banging bodies though yeah
no the one of the red
dress I they model them like
that she was a she was a model in her
past
life um when I get out of this water can
I have a splint or whatever it is yes of
course thank
[Music]
you I'm almost out of the water too the
one person without a broken leg
so
fast what fauna also broken leg no wait
I thought I thought your leg got healed
immediately by no I think mine's a
fracture I have to look at my debuff oh
it's a sprained
leg jumping or sprinting will delay
healing or even hurt you but the zombies
will catch me this finally made my dream
come true I always wanted to break a
leg you really yeah I never had an
experience like breaking something and
getting a cast I haven't either but I
don't really want I don't really want
did you never dream of having a cast and
having your friends in school kind of
yeah kind of oh
yeah and then like I don't know your
friends always carry your backpack for
you I guess they would maybe they would
would
they if you break your leg necessary to
have
friends okay here right here thank you
all right uh how does one use this where
did it oh oh it's it's like
a I see
use does it go away right away it does
go away but I have like 39 M of a leg I
don't understand what that means 39 M of
kind light long
way oh hey I think it's something like a
cap in how much I could run or no I
don't know is it minutes a minutes oh
well okay that's confusing because could
also stand for meters
so I
see I can't run or my leg hurts more
damn this Affliction my stupid buck of
life okay
okay are we there yet are we there
soon 690 M don't worry we're really
close oh okay well then this place looks
familiar oh we're in America wait this
is the place this is the place that
where we were chilling and hanging out
when is it when we were um testing it
out like a couple days
ago at least at least the group that I
was with with when we were testing the
game I think we were just in a field
yeah and then fauna stabbed me while we
were talking staff was talking to us I
just got stabbed it's because you
punched me you didn't even notice you
punched me you should take this to
court hey I you have no proof of this
you have no proof doesn't heal faster if
I use another
splint I don't know you should try
kind of want to
try see if it
Stacks oh you cannot use that at this
time okay but I think if I Sprint uh the
time increases for how long it takes to
heal does it like a sprinting I hear a
zombie no sprinting with the
Sprint don't be scared her eyes are
glowing red we're so strong
together we have two guns take a two
fist we have six
fists we can't use them like fauna does
though she she kind of she's kind of the
Fist more than you how disappointing I
know all I have was a shotgun and a bow
and arrow maybe you should give your
fist like is it like a a weapon fist
weapon you should give it toana like I
mean the not in game I mean your actual
fist weapon watch out there's a there's
a dangerous
oh God oh God I can't run okay I'm going
to try wait stand still nope I'm out of
shots ouch ouch it hurts me I'm going to
die stand still let her touch you I
can't going to kill
me okay she's dead that hit oh oh no
she's still alive still still alive
still alive oh oh oh reload
faster I'm out of Amo kill out of am I'm
out of am
oh she's dead she's dead she's dead
she's dead it's cool it's cool it's cool
we're chill oh level up level
four oh we're at the Shady Slaughter
RV nice that's the RV with the
dog it's just a picture don't
worry that's a real dog I started
sprinting on
accident my
ankles if you die do you lose the
quest I don't think so oh only if you're
in the process of doing
it aren't we in the process of doing it
now it's done return to Trader there's
no way
that we can fail it now knocking on
wood I hope it open soon how do how how
do I repair my M weapons and
tools um you press tab there should if
you click over it it should say repair
underneath it really found the icon you
just need the map it's spray out cuz I
don't have the materials but it doesn't
show me what materials I need otherwise
I'm blind I don't know I'm not sure wa
where did you go oh there what it
[Music]
needs maybe there's a popup that tells
you when you try it or you might need
the book for it maybe if it's high level
why do we need books for everything in
this economy I was able to rep repair my
sledgehammer though I guess the
materials are just whatever you would
originally need to build the gun for
example but I didn't build it
so there are repair kits also I found
one
on we're so
close I can smell her just like how the
zombies can smell all of us
combined is your leg well enough to be
running no i f for God I
forgot this is so
sad uhoh zombie but this one's eyes
aren't glowing so it's okay they're not
don't worry I'll try not to hit you with
my bow and arrow
ow
oh he's
dead he's indeed dead you're you're H
you have feathers in your mouth once
again M you're so
good I just love
feathers I don't know how long I can
tolerate
this no no no not
[Music]
again you know it's crazy how many birds
there are cuz they're laying eggs still
and and yet I haven't seen a single bird
I only seen
vultures you think they're the one
laying the EG yeah that's what I was
going to say what does this tell us
about if egg or bird came first when
there's only eggs
around maybe I think the egg came first
yeah but then why is the egg not making
the
birds if if there's only eggs eating
them all I guess so maybe we should stop
otherwise we're we're destroying the the
bird lines watch me put this egg in my
mouth
no give it to me I'll sit on it and I'll
hatch it I'll
no no ow she's stabbing me well you
killing our future well don't worry I
ate all the eggs in my inventory also I
didn't stab you I sledg hammered you she
sledg hammered
me I'm 14 seconds away from being cured
from my my bad leg are you ined 14 oh I
guess you no had a fractured leg damn
just my poor sprained leg can you two
girls get a kiss on my leg maybe that
will make it go away
um oh your toes are I'm out of here
thank you wow I feel like that gave me a
big healing
[Music]
buff I'm healing the world is healing
really honestly the world is healing
yeah I think you've already forgotten
about Gigi eating all of the
egg why would you remind her I hate her
n Orange lady why h no I would never eat
the eggs on the ground that I
found
never you are lucky that I am reliant on
you are we there yet we're we're so
close to our house I know right oh are
we going home yeah the tr's not open
right now oh yeah we are so there's a
zombie she's going to bite me I think
our
session is basically end is it ending at
the at like when are we ending no Day
end of day four or
what I think at the end of day four cuz
I feel like wasn't there like there was
kind of a plan so that we can time when
the when the invasions
are
yes Trader opens Trader opens at 4:00
a.m. 10 minutes w wow why is so Random
that's so early
uhoh he's on all
fours barel just like a werewolf dad the
sound that that thing makes sounds what
apparently I make sometimes what I've
been told I have an example no wa what's
that called again Chad I might die I'm
going to die sound like
have the jumps you can
jump he can jump he can jump Revenge
avenge oh he he died he died Raptor oh
yeah people said I sound like a raptor
sometimes I think when I laugh or no was
it when I laugh or when I I don't know
but sometimes apparently I sound like a
raptor and that sounds like a raptor to
me does sound like a rapor right veloc
hear an example yeah I need to hear you
do that I honestly don't know so when do
I do that Chad when when I laugh really
that's so
rud I don't laugh like that I laugh like
a
lady I'm going to kill this deer so I
can feed my dependent wives you found a
deer if I can kill this then my wives
will depend on me more and they can't
leave me cuz I have Stockholm syndrome
them in the apocalypse f are we the
wives I missed every single one of these
arrows she's a little bit
don't worry I killed it we have meat for
dinner I do appreciate that let's let's
learn how to cook it
though I'm going to learn how to cook it
wait I want to I want to punch it too I
want to get animal fed give me give me I
I I think did I no my arrow we're home
I'm going to get any animal fed but I
got some steaks
okay so uh I wonder if if it would be
worth it to not just rely on BI boo
cooking for everybody especially when
our teams are often separate maybe we
should also learn how to cook we can
learn how to cook I think it's good that
multiple people know how to
cook does meat go bad like raw meat does
it go bad no I need a grill I don't have
a cooking grill it's over it's over how
do we make a workbench oh we need work
station level
10 a damn this is so difficult I know so
much oh I have a like a fire buff wow
wholesome is there an auto
deposit um no move items to fill up oh
there it is there oh yeah on the
bar on your
inventory hm
[Music]
what is this ergonomic G ah will it be
easier to use the
gun I feel like we're going to die of
carbon monoxide
poisoning no we have an alarm
it'll feeling with smoke right
now it's really no it's fine it's fine
oh my God it is very hard to see we have
open walls you see the window out front
we're missing the
window
yeah it'll be okay we'll be fine in
here um
question although you oh wait
recipes chat is this also from a
magazine
is this
[Music]
also skill
a stone tools should I put a
what need what 46 magazine oopsies
not mean to stab things
[Music]
just do we have any more magazines lying
around that nobody has read yet that
could be useful I put I don't think so
no these two cooking in here if you want
to learn how to cook J we have to cook
oh yeah the cooking magazin
M who of us should be the cook who who
should be the chef I think I might have
one point in it already oh then go for
it wait do
I where's
cooking there's a lot of cool stuff in
here the
potato why you keeping the rotting flash
will that ever be
useful we just never maybe it will be
H could be okay I need one more duct
tape and 20 scrap polymers and I can
make a de
collector a oh I do have one level okay
I'll read
some I could make cornbread but but but
I we don't have any cooking
items cooking items as in like a
stove yeah or is in like a pot or
grill literally have
nothing do you think the trader will be
open now did they sell like a
pod I think he has some I don't know we
have enough money for it I can make
grilled
meat wait can I no I
can't I can make something
though cornbread chat what should I
[Music]
learn what should I learn you can maybe
buy a pot or Gilla at the trader yeah we
could put our money together I think
after this trip we have quite a
bit I am so drunk right now I'm
fast infurious are you drinking I drank
some beer and now I'm seeing double
where where are you just started
sprinting more stuff get so much done
while I'm
drunk I don't understand
this so can I not put a skill into this
chat is this magazine only I still don't
understand this whole
menu I know it's a lot
right what weapons do you like so far I
don't really care I mean I think it's
good to have one like weapon like a
hammer or so besides the
gun just in case I run out of ammo so
for now I'm doing
Sledgehammer the Traer open everyone
these are the books they're try to open
okay oh wa you girl already so
far
ladies we don't have to turn it in at
the same time right but it will feel it
will feel more wholesome oh I turned it
in I so
fad what a Zoomer you think he'll be mad
if I dismantle his truck yeah he makes a
noise and everything
he's yeah try it I can't
run why didn't you go carry me with my
broken leg come here he has a cooking
pop for 600 and a cooking grill for 600
600 I don't wait how do how much money
is that I have 400 on me oh we can put
together the casino token in your
inventory I have I have almost 200
Casino tokens oh oh wait that's what it
wait there's some in the um there's some
in the chest too oh we can give a pot is
is there no way to find a pot out in the
open world I guess it R just have to
find
it it's probably very
rare can you sell
stuff oh it's only worth nine the
cash yeah the cash you should sell and
you get the coins that he had has is it
worth
it uh I would yeah yeah yeah I don't
think you can use the real money for
anything else the the the the cash the
US dollars or whatever that is I don't
think it's I got a quest to go to the
mushroom Mining Company oh we've passed
there but that was the Minecraft thing
that you ran away from and me and FAA
looked into it for a moment oh now we
can kill it for
real wait
he how do I give back the
Quest how did you give back the
quest I just spoke to him and then he's
like here's what I have for you cuz you
completed my
questend it all oh oh I'm so dumb this
menu is so overwhelming chat I'm sorry
tactical
Warfare proofs assault rifle crafting
skill crafting skill a bundle of free r
I'm crafting oh I think I'll go for the
what did you girls
choose I took the club I took the book
what okay you got a club from the this
very oh the club book oh okay oh oh he
gives you 400 Casino tokens too that's
crazy oh he's so mean though
wow can treat us like this just cuz he's
richer than us in the apocalypse
he'll be hearing from my the worst part
once we get our cell phones working
again we can tear down his small
business and leave bad reviews on Yell
yeah yeah are you already going to the
next Quest oh no I'm going home first
okay
okay you got to wait for us wives should
we yeah wait for your wives my wives
that I'm making dependent on me and buy
yeah cooking pot or I have 700 coins now
that's you take from the
house yeah
yeah yeah we can we should we should you
know invest in this together if we get
the pot we can boil our water so it's no
longer dirty and disgusting wait I have
a water purifier but I don't know how to
use it oh
interesting where is it I don't even see
the
pot oh I took the ones
inside the chest we have 500 or I pulled
it together I have 521 oh so maybe we
can get both the grill and the pot yeah
we can make clean water oh okay wait
this water purifier goes in your hat
that doesn't make any sense I'll buy the
oh maybe you can drink dirty water and
it's like a straw it's
attached to your face I purchased the
pot so you buy the grill they're
trolling me it
doesn't you buy Grill oh why would they
lie to you and ra
ra how much Italian did you learn with
her
um I I feel like I already had a good
amount of knowledge because I learned it
in school a little
bit so it was like kind of just
remembering what I learned there like
what she was teaching me was like stuff
I already learned in school but I had to
remember some of it she reminded you
about
Italians I am pretty decent in Itali why
you take your hat off it does your hat
bright Joker green hair is just so
shocking
was there no better green than
that
no the green but actually thinkk if you
if
you if you shower once or twice that
green should fade into a more nicer FAL
green it's
natural I'm sorry girl that doesn't look
natural to
me even though you're
nature not very natural
do you have 100 coins I can have yes
yeah take some money
from hold on what's wrong with you well
she likes to be barefoot don't judge her
she's Barefoot by default
sorry no Senai respect this girl I got a
cooking grill I'm going to go back home
okay I I she's so what happened she's so
intimidated okay let's go I got the pot
you got the grill and we got the girl
also fauna come on and the
girl try to put back on yes
yes we don't want to step were you
modding your shoes too yeah I was
modding yes modded shoes well you modded
your shoes H got a cool flame on it now
what no
way it's like when you put charms on
your Crocs you are Barefoot still
I haven't put them back
on
yet I should just AFK for 24 minutes cuz
my my feet are so
broken I'll eat some
pears O I Love Pears but M I feel like
they're often a Miss like they're either
hit or miss that's very true PS really
depends on the type of pear yeah you can
make us grilled meat now FAA I can I
think I'll put the meat in here so you
can cook
it does it really get more if I run
let's
see wait should I cook our stuff does it
go bad no it doesn't go bad it's fine it
doesn't go bad so I can just cook it all
yep let's go I'm making grilled corn it
went
up it did go up a
minute damn it grilled corn he
lotes
wow I I'll drop free steaks can you take
the raw oh
God you're cooking them too I didn't I
didn't want to drop in over there thank
God they're not catching
fire oh wait I can't make good meat yet
that's okay I can only make charred
meat
wait guess I guess we can wait a bit oh
I should open this she's getting better
at cooking don't bully her magazine
gotcha I got Rob robotics crafting skill
two of them and armor crafting skill two
of them and spare crafting skill two of
them oh
wow I'll definitely learn the armor
crafting
skill I'll learn this
too I don't know what kind of Robotics
you can make in this game but sounds fun
can you put the pot in oh yeah uh
how I can make cornbread I think yeah
you put it in the thingy oh ah
okay C
fancy that's so cute I have to learn how
to do you girls sometimes watch like
those videos on YouTube where like
pretty ladies will like Vlog themselves
going camping and like really
professionally like they are like
absolute prows at camping and sometimes
they bring their dog orell or there's
like at these camping ons sometimes they
have cats apparently and then the cats
will go to their camp and hang out with
them for the night which is so cozy I
want to
I want to learn the all those camping
skills man should we go camping IRL or
like yes yeah IRL I would love to but
does any of you have experience camping
no should we go
glamping
glamp maybe like honestly I feel like
glamping is a little bit too much maybe
like an in between between camping and
glamping yeah we don't have any running
water but but we have an
RV what IRL or in game I'm not sure what
you're talking about
IRL really have an R we have to get the
IRL RV you have an RV or are we no no we
can investing in one okay we're
investing in an RV I will say that I
have camped in the very very wilder
wilderness be like last year and made a
video about it and have uh provided
myself with eggs from wild chickens
and I remember that video you watched it
I'm so sorry wasn't okay for what did
did you like the scene where I I like
cut from like a baby chicken
to it's cinematic I will definitely say
Ju Just so I mean I I think you
understood what happened there but no
chickens were harmed in the making of
that video
[Music]
yeah that was the real
Wilderness you can be our camping Pro
you can teach us how to Camp okay I
don't really know how it works but I
have a
tent and a a nice sleeping
bag can we all is your tent big enough
for all of us I think we could fit cozy
no we would
snuggle I'm down oh sorry I took all of
your water out
it
was what's wrong with my 30 minute water
it wasn't it wasn't outputting one at a
time it was just going to wait 30
minutes to cook all the whole
stack I want to make
cornbread I've never had cornbread
before IR we need more cooking magazine
you never had corn we should get
cornbread IRL right yeah I do I do need
more cooking magazines oh I don't think
I have one no we can run towards doing
the mushroom Quest while our stuff is
cooking and then maybe go to houses on
the way and I have a magazine that
teaches you how to make super strong
coffee I
think give me coffee I thought it was a
mining magazine but it seems like it
teaches you coffee I don't
know well if you're in the need for that
it's in my
crate you can learn become powerful with
coffee there's a lot of H life members
that you could bait with the coffee
that's true you can woo with coffee yeah
rule the world coffee rules the world if
you like corn cornbread is excellent but
cornbread is something like cake right
and for me cake shouldn't tastes like
corn it's not really cake I mean it's
sweet but you eat it with SA Foods
usually okay I feel like the texture is
unlike a cake
too
yeah huh all right it's kind of uncommon
here in Austria I
think yeah what's it called anyway mice
C mice Po in German what is it mice mice
mice
mice I look it up mice mice po cuz corn
is mice and bread is
BR chat why are you not telling me
normally you tell me everything I guess
the German speakers are sleeping right
now it's half 6 a.m. I guess they are am
I SCH really H well well well oh wait oh
no never
mind I thought we didn't go to the Traer
yet but we did did wait KY where are you
why are you 200 M
away running no I'm I'm hitting rocks
and trees mushroom place we can go to
mushroom Place yeah we should go to
mushroom Place let's go as long as one
of us has the quest we're good right
yeah yeah yeah so okay wait I'll drop
two more things off how's your leg my
leg is it still needs 17 minutes and if
I rush it will be longer oh no
timber timber are you yelling timber I
was going down I'm yelling
timber
yippe
yippe yippe
huzzah
huzzah well everyone should come to my
house iel and then I'll drive you to
both Costco and to get
cornbread and you give me my passenger
princess
you can sit on each other's laps and we
can get pulled over what no I'm fine
sitting all right I'm going
to I can't just have only one of you be
my passenger princess it's are you not
the passenger princess if you're in the
back no you'd be it's like then's an
Uber it's like hello your Uber is here
to pick you
up right what was the I don't want to
run all the way to the Traer if the
quest thing is in the other direction do
we know we're going oh no it's this way
yeah okay okay okay I'll walk slow it's
where we need a
car I know we need a car so bad do you
see where all of them are inside that's
where our Quest is the rest of them
where all of them are inside oh they're
there
ah okay oh there's a bunch of people
there ah the last H cuz some people
already ended their Stream So the
remaining girls uh came together it
seems see
M where the last one stand for today huh
yeah yeah well do they have a cooking
grill and a pot we should ask them we
should flex but they'll probably say
yeah cuz wasn't biu already
cooking was she with her bare hands oh
potentially I see that is not quite the
[Music]
same can you make a splint no I I can't
use another splint cuz I already have
one on but 50 15
minutes 15 minutes unless I run too much
then it's more again this sucks I regret
this already I why did I wish for having
a broken leg
Place how did you break it in the first
place cuz I fell from a high like
Mountain this game is too real yeah so
scary diarrhea then the broken legs then
the vampire zombies and the really sexy
zombies too so realistic that's so
realistic and then me objectifying the
really sexy zombies it's like can I not
catch a
break do you I play video games or
escapism do you guys watch horror movies
no scary sometimes sometimes I'm sure
there's sexy zombies in in there too
right probably should we find one I hate
hate horror movies oh yeah they're too
scary it is spooky month yeah October
I'll watch a scary movie if it has a
sexy zombie in it we should just watch
scary
movie the first one ideally watch scary
movie do you know do you know scary
movie
yeah we can watch scary movies scary
movie is it dumb which is that the one
with Jason no that's Friday the 13 I
think the first one is the one with the
exorcism on the lady where she wait a
supply drop I'm running for it yeah see
those suckers not if I hit those first
wait I can't run so
fast we'll get it for you oh they are
really far where okay I don't even see
oh you see them it is so far are they
good I'm not going there they might be
good if we get them before they do even
though we're working together yeah we're
working together don't forget
that we're not enemies we're not Rivals
like in rust or so maybe we should be we
might die though cuz it's noon right
now what it's okay what's a little death
in the grand scheme of things wait why
would we die oh you're already going for
it she's zooming
see I need drink I'm out of here how
much long do you do you girls personally
want to play
today I think we're St at the 4our Mark
right okay so is that in you mean in 10
in 20 minutes minutes okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah so is it worth running
there for you
two yeah it's only 400 me away well then
don't get distracted like a Zoomer all
the time and run into other places while
you're going there oh don't worry I
already did fa stop her I can't I really
want to see what's in this
I you'll never make it in these 20
minutes I'll make it we're so close it's
actually not that far it's actually not
that far we ran further for the quest
but does that mean we're not going to
the mushroom mining place we can still
go we'll make it I don't think we'll
make it
running we're so fast there might be a
mountain in the way Ain No Mountain High
Enough girl a no mountain low
enough to get me to that supply drop
right now there there's a mountain okay
but what how do we get around this
mountain there has to be a way around it
get yourself a
horse and then oh no just go straight
up I need a goat he I haven't seen
horses in this game yet I guess there
are no horses if there was a horse I'd
eat it already what
well o the hores you need to feed it so
much you are such a
[Music]
werling what is this
scarecrow I have arriv this Farm is
using a naked man as a scarecrow I have
arrived at the mushroom Mining Company I
will just wait here until you girls come
because my leg is healing slowly we're
trying to find out how to scale this
mountain oh I just went right up
oh you can go right up yeah okay I need
food just like enough room oh wait I
have all the food oh egg egg egg egg
please please please egg please egg yes
egg pleasee uhoh there's a Hopping
zombie over here fun are you carrying
food with you yeah okay when you come
here here I need like at least a piece
of something okay thank
you there's some good stuff in
here knew was worth
it girls look at the
time plenty of time plenty of time I'm
almost at the other supply
drop
okay let me look where you
are oh oh you already collected one of
those supply drops what was inside
um a blueberry pie oh armor plate Rod
Golden Rod
tea crafting skill magazine bundle a
blueberry pie and a claw hammer well you
said blueberry pie twice we or to inside
wait did I oh there just
one I really like are you hungry for
like IR actually am
hungry the talk about cornbread made me
really want cornbread gigy what's in the
second one six books and a plaster cast
for your broken foot oh oh a shame that
you're healing in 10 minutes
yeah too
late well for next time yeah for next
time I also got two fisting books for
fa I want the fisting book
nice okay we're heading to the mines
okay
[Music]
the come over
here yes
yes the mind of
Moria I want to watch The Hobbit
again which one the new ones the new
ones there's a new one well they're not
really that new yeah there's like an old
animated movie no not that
[Music]
one no no no
no now I just want to watch the CL so to
say I guess you can't call them classic
but the ones that you know that I mean
the free Hobbit movies Martin Freeman
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I do like
him as bbo yeah bbo
Bings you know for my last
for
my up until now all like my birthdays
and anniversaries I have collected
several greetings from Lord Of The Wings
actors have you yeah I did get uh Sam I
think right oh and I do have uh an
autograph of Sam I think oh yeah and I
got Bill ball and I got fro too right I
have uh like video messages of three of
all those three that's awesome there so
many of them yeah and I fle
my what almost done with what you're
collecting all of them right you get one
from every single actor well I I don't
know I would like gimly I would like to
get one from gimly if he does that stuff
but I I'm guessing he doesn't cuz
otherwise I probably would have already
gotten a video
message you have collected them all I
know I got Pippen I got Pippen Sam fro
and Pippen that was it right right I
didn't get
billbo pipin was so
[Music]
funny Pippin was like so funny literally
oh do you girl know watch did you ever
watch gimma
girls no I you talk about it though why
does nobody relate to me with gilo girls
I have yet to find somebody who likes
the show as much as
me I like the meme the meme what's the
meme go piss girl what is that from
Gilmore Girls is
it think
so why would that be from that's Gossip
Girl there's just so many girls oh
God or is it from Golden Girls because
no they're golden I don't know I don't
think the Golden Girls are telling each
other go
oh my god when I when I mentioned
Gilling girls to cie she thought I was
talking about Golden Girls and that was
a pretty funny
misunderstanding cuz I was just yapping
about gim girls this whole time in her
head I'm talking about old
ladies hello I made it back you made
it blueberry P oh please thank
you blueberry oh my God take the
fistings yes thank you I'm going to eat
started Quest the blueberry pie I think
gave me a running
buff I got more fisting
magazines so many oh a bow magazine two
bow magazines and two explosive
magazines
wow nice what do the explosive magazines
do let me
check in explosive crafting wow okay
doesn't anybody already have anything on
that cuz I don't I don't think I don't
think I
do do you want spear
hunting is that CRA for crafting
Spears yeah oh bleeding damage Spears
have a 25% chance to cause bleeding
damage well that's kind of
cool uh interesting I don't use Spears
right
now someone should take wait is she's
stealing our stuff no no I took it I
took it I got paranoid too I guess we're
friends I guess we're all friends yeah
we're all friends we need to remember
we're in survival
mode
holy oh I have another cooking book for
you maybe you can make us meet I can I
can make you meet now there's a person
inside the quest so I can't start it yet
oh I oh I don't know why but aren't they
just leaving right now cuz two already
came out of here yeah bi bi also left so
I I think they're done with that Quest
now let me in Us in the to take the
banded armor mod maybe I have to dig and
put it on your
shirt can you just do that oh
Yi so remove your armor and then there's
like a modify slot and you put it in
there oh wait wait don't run so fast let
me try that remove move the armor modify
slot is giggy already running in there
don't worry I'll clear it out I'll clear
it out for you so you don't have to
worry about a single thing oh that's so
cool ah maybe that works the same way
with the shovel then yeah yeah
ah Faun how did you figure this out I
think my chat told me
wow wait how do I wear it now I'm stupid
uh
uh uh uh okay okay I got it oh it
doesn't really reflect in the visuals
but okay I'm sure you're stronger now
I'm sure I am M
mushrooms oh can we eat them yeah I
think we can at least pick them up for
now and then cook them for
XP for for food uhoh
oh well I have no am at all it seems so
we have to go
melee
melee ow ow ow ow oh jeez this bone
knife is not so
efficient I don't think it is cie was
like better weapon cie was saying oh you
got to get the bone knife it's so good
maybe it's just because she likes
bones it's for the hunting animals so
you can take their skin and wear it
really no it's just for you get more um
items when you kill an animal if you use
the knife oh F let's go deeper gigy is
like probably really deep in
it yeah yeah I
am what did you go I guess we only have
we have like N9 minutes 10 minutes oh
yeah yeah we got to rush
speedrun
oh ouch
oh
no yeah get
him
ow okay okay okay okay
okay
this swinging at him he dead he's dead
he's dead he's dead take my arrows from
him do we go up here yep okay I can see
inside of you oh
don't so so empty empty Holo there's
nothing in
there I am full of joy and happiness as
long as I with you
girls oh I saw that what you're seeing I
think it's just a mirage stream Mirage
stream Mirage stream Mirage you sold me
on Mir shake your head yeah you like
obessed with the the sequins the like
sparkles on the shorts thank you thank
you so good I'm glad you like it takas
new song hey wait I'm too scared to make
that jump with my broken
leg you could always wait over there
there's knuckle wraps in here knuckle
should take those level two oh and ammo
and a muffled connectors mod I don't
know what that's for oh that's my ammo
come on let's go muffled connectors mod
ah to make it more
silent like a why do I need to make
stealth kill these zombies yeah I don't
know cuz if they can't hear you then
maybe you can't alert other nearby
zombies or so I don't know think is
there anything up there no it's just a
shortcut you can go back around or you
can make the shortcut to the entrance oh
I'm scared to yeah me too me too I'm
going to break my leg
again wait what I'm scared to oh we
already cleared
it yeah what was baby Zone what was
there to
clear so easy I think Gigi just did
everything this is just like parkour
civilization right now you guys are
jumping for the chicken we should be no
it's
Minecraft you should watch it I watched
the entire thing at two times speed
yesterday which is like 4 hours of
Minecraft yeah Minecraft Parkour
civilization I'm lost perhaps possibly
no never mind I'm fine also I can't
believe I will give you credit because
we still have 10 minutes or 9 minutes
yeah yeah and you've done both the TR
and this
okay I think we're winning not that it's
a competition but if it was yeah I don't
know maybe the the others aren't doing
so bad either as TR will show up and
they have like a helicopter yeah no no I
think we're winning we shouldn't get too
cocky also I'm thirsty do we have water
at home maybe we have so much water
cooking right now
okay I'm going to drink out of a pond
cuz I have the mod that lets me drink
out of a pond you wear it wear it
my helmet lets me drink out of the pond
I think that's amazing you just dip your
head
in um I think wait how do I
drink uh open your mouth and then
go gulp gulp gulp I want to try oh you
need your
hands wait I'm I'm 130 M away from you I
want to try
to wait don't you shouldn't drink it
unless you wear the helmet I can give
you the helmet yeah yeah yeah I'm almost
there I'm just trying to not run too
fast cuz I have 1 minute left on my foot
the walking brida filter
[Music]
mhm 55 54 53
52 oh I found you girls
hello
hello blue is fauna fauna oh okay let me
experiment and fill my tummy with put on
oo
wow primitive Hood where is
it ah there it
is wow and so how do I drink the water
in here uh have an empty hand uhhuh and
then you can push e at the end
what but I'm just punching it again girl
to the edge come to the edge what come
on over here huh I thought you were just
messing with me again no ah eat to drink
trti from
Cony can't believe this
works
oh is there any indicator to see like
how thirsty supposed drink too much
right or you'll get sick
oh press E Yeah but I would like to see
like cuz we have a bar for like stamina
and a bar for health do we not have
anything like that for
drinking there's on the on the bottom
right side you see it underneath your
the blue
one oh and green
is hunger is it purple is exp maybe yeah
purple's exp and then left side is
hunger and then right side is waterit I
shouldn't be drinking this without the
helmet oh
just slurping it up here it is here it
is it's okay in the water oh did you get
it it didn't seem too bad it seemed fine
okay A little bit of fine little bit of
f what are you doing with the gun oh
that's
bio why is she threatening us I don't
know we better go turn our quest in yeah
we should go and then end it maybe she's
telling us like girl you have to end the
stream today get off of the server now
yeah get off the
server soon soon just giving back the
[Music]
quest people scares me I know why is she
just walking menacing around cuz we got
the supply crates is that why well
they're ours she
mad she mad well she got to stay
mad oh I think our last name is the
Clement our last a yeah our resence
house yeah that's a house name do yeah
what do you want everybody wants to talk
to this guy why can't he talk to more
than one
person incredible you can talk to him
you have to angle yourself a little
differently from them oh I guess so yeah
what do we have this
time crafting the medical journal yeah
I'm getting the magazines again too what
do you mean you're getting the does he
only offer one to you I get like a
bundle he only offered one I get bundles
all the time me
what maybe maybe this one medical uh
Journal is better than all these bottles
that I'm getting
maybe oh let's open gotcha time I have
receiv received gcha explosives crafting
time two Sledgehammer crafting uh two of
them
okay and spare crafting ah lame no wait
that's the old one armor craft is that
is that from before I got I think armor
crafting is new okay I learned
these can you
upgrade your weapons to the next
level me I don't know anybody is it
possible I don't even know how how I
would go about doing that oh you can't
you have to recraft it I think yeah I
got to get the skills
Going
H wait did they
leave one of them
left oh oh they're leaving left it's
time yeah it's time it seems to
be oh they also left the voice
chat oh are they have they
ended I want want to say I had a blast
with you girls I'm glad we got together
to Adventure yeah may I mean I I feel
like it's probably like lame if we
always stay in the same groups but if we
end up I don't know somehow end up
together tomorrow again I wouldn't mind
I wouldn't mind playing again
together
okay this is our Clement house are you
back at the house
already i' been running okay can run now
my my leg is
healed it was fun it was fun yeah we did
so much we were effent lot done yeah
yippe hooray we can end once kiawa gets
back home I'm running I'm
running I'll go hit some
trees let out your
aggressions why are you hitting them why
don't you get an axe yeah you Ed the
stone axe so you are using it right oh
yeah I am okay but if you really want to
let out aggressions you should use your
fists that's fa's job to fist the trees
she's a master Fister here wow you lost
your job KY I lost my job in seven days
to die she became the Fister I saw the
tree fall
Timber okay I'm
home welcome it doy M no no
no but I mean a food would probably be
also nice to be greeted by when I come
home no I'm not that hungry I'm not that
hungry it's fine I have some pears no
it's fine I'm not actually hungry okay
okay is our water done yeah a lot of our
water is done we should get out of
cornbread is the water in in the in the
yeah it's inside it how inside
corn meal I okay now it's EMP I can put
it in the top
chest I can't find anything wow where's
the
cornmeal I've got some cornmeal too I
think in my chest yeah I got two
cornmeal we had
more I did not take it maybe we have
been no I'm might wait it's literally in
my inventory
I'll put the cornmeal into this
seemingly food focused chest I'm making
a bunch of cornbread okay okay shall we
shall we l time log out it's time to go
let's get out of
here goodbye goodbye beautiful
princesses
fwell farewell thank you guys foring
thank you thank you I guess tomorrow is
same
time not an hour oh thank God an hour
early good then I have a collab but if I
can make it I will see you guys oh like
you're going to join Midway through or
so I might join Midway through if I can
oh okay okay well goodbye keep the house
warm for you I'm going to come back
you're going to be so much more well
fisted no going to have cook
I I don't know what other words Master
Fister uh
puncher knuckle knuckle girl
Knuckles
Sonic
yeah all right all right then good night
I guess yeah goodbye bye bye take care
see you later bye
I'm so happy like the beginning with
everybody was overwhelming but once I
got into this little group it was a lot
of fun I feel like we had a good
time
W yeah smaller groups doing smaller
things good stuff good morning
Wawa there was going to be I don't know
if it's today but after staying up so
late I don't think I could even join the
like evening jst time slot that's at
like 300 p.m. my time cuz now it's 700
a.m. uh I ate like so to say dinner like
6 hours ago so I should probably eat
something small now before going to
sleep like the real dinner in the
a.m. and so that probably means I'll
probably sleep around 900 a.m. or
so [\h__\h] me how am I going to fix this
I don't know how I'm going to fix
this but yeah uh tomorrow an hour
earlier so it should also end an hour
earlier hope you guys had fun watching I
think it was good after all that I put
up a stream just so you could see my
POV and can you join another time um
well it's totally free and up to the
person uh uh one one doesn't have to
stay until the end of any session and
one doesn't have to be there from the
beginning of any session either um what
I might do is
like uh join at the beginning but don't
stay until the end of the session but I
think tomorrow we will have a zombie
invasion cuz now today we played four
days in game and the 7th Day so a little
bit earlier than the end of the like 4
hours slot or so somewhere like in the
middle should be the Zombie
Invasion exciting see you later Queen K
Queen
K thank God it's an hour earlier the
stream was great when I'm dying here are
you from Europe are you suffering
through this with me you don't have to
hope you're
[Music]
okay you were on day five oh are we
already on day five okay wow then it's
going to be like 2 hours or so on this
on the
second hour of the stream it should be
Invasion could you leave at the start of
day eight yeah I'm probably just going
to leave right when the zombies are done
attacking maybe make it a little bit
shorter I don't I don't know it depends
how motivated or Ganky how how energetic
I
am yeah uh guys if you have missed it I
I I said in my previous stream today
that there's some Mirage milestones for
certain Milestones even like 50k
Milestones um I will say if we reach the
where are we
now if we reach
the we're now at ooh if we reach the
400k views Milestone on Mirage you guys
get a dance short of me with crony
dancing Mirage you want that I know you
want that
so make it happen and then 500k will be
the full dance choreography
video which is really nice too to look
at
that and then after that maybe every 50k
I'll put out more dance shorts like with
the the one with crony that you haven't
seen yet but you'll you'll understand
what it's
like yeah cuz I was inspired you know
I've not you know that like when
recently there's a brand that when whole
life members like Marin or so put out
songs um they'll give out the like the
MMD motion or so for people to make
their own dance shorts with it um but
they're usually just dancing alone and I
thought looking at you know cuz I'm a
K-pop fan oh smovie I'm almost done when
I look at uh you know the trends there
um usually they do dance challenges like
as collaborations with other K-pop
artists whenever they meet them in like
other music shows or whatever and so
it's like always like a collaboration uh
like they get a different artist to
dance their song of them and then on uh
for the other artists they dance their
song also that they're promoting right
now so yeah they always together with
someone so I'm kind of doing that with
other Holo life
girls it's
cute yeah
okay 700 a.m. I'm going to eat something
and then and then I
will go to
bed in the middle of the
day I'm going
smoothie yeah now I'm messing up her
eating schedule I feel bad sorry I
choked in German we say in bye-bye thank
you for watching W PE
I I I'll put up a POV again
tomorrow bye-bye thank you for watching
go watch me rash and if you haven't uh
considered getting my merchandise yet
link is in the description for my
Anniversary
merchandise bye-bye
n
[Music]
fre