[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
welcome everyone welcome
welcome how you doing
uh sorry uh
this is a
a little bit I need a little bit of a
time because
my game has just closed itself excuse me
click clack click clap
uh of course it happens when I start the
stream yes yes
oh nostalgic outfit but hey this is not
that nostalgic it's not that old
but guys we're playing blue archive have
you heard of blue archives
it's a cute
[Music]
oh did you hear that did you hear that
yes blue archive it's a cute girl game
with cute girls and I want to play it
because I already put a lot of money
into my account
please let me in please let me in
[Music]
please let me in game
maybe it's Cortana
oh my God
she's taking over
[Music]
uh was working just fine before the
Stream
let's see what happens
it's oh I mean it's loading right now
it's open here as you hear the music you
hear the music right
but don't worry I'm planning to make
this longer anyway longer than it's
supposed to be
so we get our extra time don't worry
about that if it works
hahaha
I did watch crony's stream on this game
a little bit and I think I also watched
a bit of bales
it is it's a little bit we're almost
we're almost there I feel it let me in
come on
I love the music though
such a buff
[Music]
cute
can't listen to it forever
EDM song Let's Make A Idol song out of
it oh yeah normally it doesn't load this
long
oh yeah
blue archive
I want to play you
come on
updates no already updated
please open
[Music]
again please please
let me present this guy to my audience
I think it's kind of stuck
yeah I'm leaving the screen off I guess
until
it's uh
until it's I'm really in
[Music]
um
maybe I should read maybe it's stuck for
real
maybe I should restart
it's been stuck
uh I see the beautiful city though
you guys don't see it
come on
come on I will read I think I'll restart
before it started just fine tap a few
more times no that's not working
let me close
oh shh
oh sure
oh
shitokusan
the gray-haired girl right
the one that I put on my thumbnail I
heard I heard legends about her
thank you for the membership welcome
okay opening up the game again
crossing my thumbs
yeah that's sweet alcohol cute she's
cute I like gray-haired characters gray
gray-haired characters mwah always the
best
oh you hear that again it's opening up
again she it'll go
she don't go data initializing
resetting game data
8384 percent hundred percent loaded
[Music]
again now loading
no not exploding I think the downloading
sign is gone I think I'm getting in I'm
in
foreign
I don't need you to wake me up I I'm
awake I'm fully awake let me show you
guys the window
[Music]
where's the window
OBS capture game please
[Music]
sorry about the trouble normally it's
not like this
normally it's not like this I swear to
God
I swayed I swear to the god of Cortana
on it
[Music]
definitely now will show me
Kiana
yes that's me I'm a teacher today
hold it
[Music]
I'm gonna open a new one
game capture oh there it is
okay please please be be sweet be kind
to me look at my oh wait you don't see
it I think you just say it a moment ago
am I going crazy
it's open for me did I what happened
YouTube Studio
and on YouTube will be a studio
let me open a new one after all
game capture
capture specific window there we go
All In
[Music]
what
um
why
ah
how long
so long
so I don't I I have this beautiful girl
here on my screen
let's hope it goes well now here look at
my look at my gotcha money I got a lot
of money for this opportunity
um I have gone for a little bit of the
tutorial
is this too loud
maybe a little bit
um but I I
had to uh because of time issues I
couldn't quite focus too much on it yet
he showed who this car
[Music]
because I needed to put in the money
but we'll take a look at it today I want
to do some gacha and I want to do some
gaming as well I want to see how the
game works what yes 36k why are you
surprised when I got to I do it
seriously I do it with all my heart and
I think I want to start right away
me also I mean I guess I should mention
this stream is is sponsored uh by Nexon
Korea thank you
now I can practice my Korean huh
now what's the best pickup is usually
good right should we do a recruit tent
of course I just did the like the the
forced uh recruiting that they forced
you to do in the beginning
um
let's see
oh she's so cute I love her design oh my
god oh yeah uh how was my sign again uh
my signature there's a working one girl
oh my oh my God I love you wait ah hi hi
I love the design it's all like so
Japanese
she's a maid I think that's like a Maids
outfit like a traditional Japanese style
made out of it
also cute a little bit down here
[Music]
that that's isn't that how you write I
am a senpai's name
Striker oh yeah so there's like
different roles and there's different
clubs I don't quite 100
understand it yet but we're gonna get
there
like can I put it on can I put my Kotori
on here you see it oh no wait ah damn it
wait it doesn't work with my cat ears
but I do want my cat ears today to fit
in a little bit
that's a cool art style too
I really really am a sucker foreign
[Music]
in her school bag she has whipped the
sweets popping out she has her rifle
popping out a relationship yes
um okay uh school lunch Club Everyone
likes food here it's
sunny
cleaning and clearing okay maybe you
could teach Aqua Senpai something about
cleaning
okay she might not have gray hair but
something about that beige hair with
that like kind of shy look but still
look at that oh you can see through her
blouse here
and then the Meg on it I'm normally not
the one that goes crazy for glasses but
look at her oh she's a joke though
she was her birthday is April 1st why
would you make her a joke oh no what's
so funny about her I think she's just
cute okay
[Laughter]
I'm rude use thousand five I'm on my way
I'm on my way give me some time okay so
we got uh some like golden ones but I
guess the special ones have different
colors they're really special ones of
course girls you're all special don't
get me wrong
did I click recruit again oh oh that's
how they get you I didn't even know what
I was doing uh okay since I can't do my
signature in one girl you get a hat
done
I like that you have to sign these
that's a cute thing too Implement like
touch screen
I think like I'm already happy but I
guess so when you get more of the same
character uh I guess you can like kind
of yeah here upgrade them with these
things I've seen this before
um okay prefect team
not perfect team okay
I like how her that like serious uniform
is combined with a cute apron and Dad
um suspicious looking frying pan school
lunch Club again special
we've seen it before but she looks like
a like kind of like like a bird because
of the this this stuff around her hair
looks like they're trying to make her
look like a bird a little bit I might be
completely off there
um but oh my God she's cute too I like
white school uniforms
um
okay nice to meet you again
I guess don't only estimate me because
I'm small I have big potential you know
yeah yeah that's what the small girls
all say
she's the son and I love the twin Tails
cute again after school sweets Club okay
she likes sweets let's remember
[Music]
there's like I see that they used
um not a different artist for every
single character but there's like some
repetitive artists and I really like
seeing each each artist's uh art style
gorgeous
wait look at her hair hers also looks
like British don't you think that that
pigtail
what was I saying oh ah each group as an
artist ah I see it this style looks kind
of like a old school anime if you know
what about me
[Music]
I want to lay on your on I want to put
my head on your thighs if that's okay
can I rest my head on your thighs
what a difficult mission to use 1 500
pie Rook zone or whatever
that was not very difficult
I've gotta do more don't you worry game
don't you worry I recruit ten more hmm
yeah am I doing this right am I supposed
to use a different Banner or something
should I use a different banners
do regular oh oh yeah yeah
okay we'll switch to the regular
afterwards doesn't matter
I saw something magical
pinkish
I got a rainbow for anyone nice too
oh she's cute I love that rifle is that
a wrestle wait look at that uh the the
Watson concoction at the front the the
the the injection thingy what do you
call a needle thingy
oh my God who I
what who is this good choice thank you
oh oh
wow scary
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll make food out of you that's what
I'm gonna do
oh my God she's cute wait I need to
drink water I'm getting thirsty
um
okay I'm so sorry
from the same group as the other uh the
the the the the rainbow one that we got
because she looks like a similar Archer
I might be wrong
she's from the same group
yes yes she is oh okay okay cool cool
cool
she's kind of her design oh my oh my God
don't you
don't you feel a new contact I've been
I've been uh
um how do you call it when you don't
when you're like off of alcohol or
something like that for long I've been
sober I've been sober for such a long
time please stop wait stop stop stop
confirm don't why why does my finger
automatically go to recruit again it
feels so familiar okay so you guys say
this one is um better
really but every 10 recruitments one two
star or higher student is guaranteed
students who have already been recruited
will be converted into eligma and Ella
Ah that's basically the same ah but this
app from this one is increased chance
for me Tony and momoi and for this one
it's just more General
not better pickup is better
regular has no the rate of this a lot
oh okay I guess this one has a wider
pull no
look
pick up okay they say pick up so I guess
I'll do pick up
uh oh my God I still have so much okay
let's let's do more
can I have her though why is she not
available huh
I wonder
okay no rainbow that's okay let's see if
we get something here
oh
you're new foreign
[Music]
oh no
hello
[Music]
she's on my phone too this is what you
gotta do you gotta put the girls that
you want on the thumbnail
and and then you will get them yes yes
it's a little trick that I have found
out seems to be working I will secretly
uh share this trick with you guys but
don't share it with anyone else bye
yes yes give it to me cute girl what was
her name again uh here dollar sign
okay I need those rainbow girls please
she not so cute
she's not so cute I know I could skip
this but we're still getting new ones
as long as we're getting new ones
foreign
design and oh my God I love the twin
tails and the horns and her uniform
and look she has like these like Devil
uh wings or something like that vampire
is she a vampire or devil what is she
she's cute
good
okay
okay record again
Euro
many many Heroes oh
the golden ones
[Music]
sorry my brain my brain I didn't want to
skip that side I wanted to learn more
about her
[Music]
look at this
time
I am in love
sorry my oh
took my breath away
she took my breath away
let me know if you're hungry I'll whip
something up oh please do I need them I
can I hire you as a maid
so cute look how her hair is like
wrapped around her horns
cute I love the the cute face
she looks so say so
oh yeah
Florida
[Music]
she said Your Design is so beautiful
I mean the the tired types of characters
you know the ones that are like sounding
really sleepy and talk really slow maybe
I'm not my
um I I'm not my biggest preference but
but the design oh man
oh man what can I look at that bazooka
whatever you have down there
what yeah she's she uh
she seems to be like a like an Oni oh
light blue color design very pretty
confirm I need more
what
what more
[Music]
[Laughter]
give me good stuff
[Music]
look at me
okay okay you left me a lot
um
cat I think actually that's so cute in
your hair I love your hair gray hair
gray hair with like green yellow eyes oh
I love the ponytail and that waviness
um it's the perfect amount of wave um
[Music]
very dust Millennium Science Squad
there's like different schools right
oh my oh good
oh my God
oh my God what
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh from now on
um
okay show me something
no I am sensex can I call you girls
senpai
oh no yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
foreign
[Applause]
I love that school uniform or whatever
uniform it is that's so cute with the
Ruffles and the pattern down there it
gets like low-key tiny tiny Gothic
Lolita Vibes but only down there and
maybe with the color with the blue
blouse here but that flower I just
noticed that flower oh my god oh flower
ribbon and that's huge ass rifle look at
it how can you even carry that are you
good do you need some help carrying it
oh my God I love that uniform
[Music]
I'll take you again this time for sure
[Laughter]
I don't know
what could it be
who couldn't be here
maybe yen is currently high on the
market although I don't know which one
matters
shall we explore the world of fine
dining
oh you guys are excited again yeah
being good she looks good she looks good
you're jealous thanks nice nice she's
strong nice nice nice okay oh wait bat
wings oh oh oh so that was a bad tail do
bats have a tail like that what since
when
so cute I like the the way the like a
ribbon is wrapped around her hair here
gray hair of course winning uniform cute
Gourmet research Society
wait is why are they all so hungry
someone give them some food why are they
so kushim I'll teach you guys a good
word in Japanese someone who really
really likes food you call them in
Japanese
[Music]
um
yes so you are a Christian but holy
foreign
are you sure you're protecting the right
parts of your body you're protecting
like I see only armor right here
you're a little bit unprotected
everywhere else
the only part that's protected is here
[Laughter]
attack in the game really
she's a tank
another hotel how do I how do I see that
by the way it's a striker a tank Striker
doesn't really sound like a man
are you saying that for real or are you
just saying it because of the
Bubba hmm
but she's a striker too
okay
[Music]
you are so cute your birthday is
on July 6th
my birthday one day after mine let's
celebrate together let's sleep over and
then on midnight we can celebrate both
yours and my birthday
yeah
smart isn't it
thank you don't get fooled by her what
do you mean
a different enzyme sign
come on I paid you when give me
something for it okay
skip skip skip skip skip skip
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's cute though I like her God you
know you gotta you gotta respect the
lower
um Rarity girl hi no lower Rarity girls
as well and if they're drawn in such a
cute way I am fine with it I don't
respect
foreign
[Applause]
midnight
you don't look scary you look
interesting you look like you're in a
face
not a face okay not a face then cute
though she stands out a lot with her
hairstyle
oh she says it's not a face don't don't
bully her okay
don't bully her
she listens to My Chemical Romance
[Music]
[Applause]
were you able to see what I was drawing
cute mommy wanna hear a fun story let me
tell you tell me tell me tell me tell me
I'm listening are those headphones
please please sell them to me
oh that's a wonderful design that looks
so cute I love that art style need to
follow the artist on Twitter please tell
me who's the artist
cute
I like the rifle design a lot too
if you combine certain people you get a
bonus or what
she is
I believe
only those two
says because they are twins
wow so only for those two you get a
bonus wow is it worth
is that weapons
[Music]
she looks like her so I got two now
haha
but maybe I already got her though there
was someone in the same art style
you said twins isn't this what you meant
but it's actually triplets
triplets now okay I need more I need
more I need to spend all my money please
we still have a lot
um
and
[Music]
was was this a currency sign I think
one
but I'm not winning why am I not winning
the first gen sign worked well let's try
it again
the
this one
this one worked well
I got a rainbow on that one
I got him
and how did you know that
the envelope oh wow
it's dangerous that's dangerous I guess
she likes to work out damn can you teach
me can you be my trainer can you be my
prep it's working you oh my God oh my
God Japanese Yen winning
oh athletic Training Club
yo she's so cool
[Music]
she's strong too you guys are not saying
you're jealous
[Music]
I want to eat food indeed
should I eat tonight
okay okay I don't
think again but we can
[Music]
um is top here at Fleet wiper swimming
is okay on cheese parade uh-huh
the experienced blue archive players are
in the chat right now
foreign
[Music]
my luck right now
I got mail you got mail
oh what
we
[Music]
oh I see
oh that's the twin is this a twin no no
it's not it just has the same artist
God damn it
ah
what what about this wait where do I see
it where this is a normal one isn't it
change into a rainbow one even
afterwards
will be picking oh but that's a lot of
golden ones
yes you can sometimes okay okay okay
don't give up oh
okay okay
[Music]
I'm not giving up okay
I present to you my Japanese Yen
[Music]
the speed is it's getting faster
um
uh patience
come on come on I'm we're halfway
through my gacha money
don't make me feel like I need to buy
more
Somewhere Over the Rainbow
there's my food
girls are here
my two favorite ones
what I can do Midori pickup what
what does that mean
here
but that's where I am though
um
great info
what do one more Temple oh my God look
at that look at that it can't be a lie
because it's all written here in exact
data
I believe
but what do you mean select students
what does that mean
during the pickup we're going to every
time you obtain a new year
I don't understand
pity pity
one more chemical
pity system
I
outfit Petty system oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah
oh yeah
[Music]
want the pity
now I am there okay
okay do I have to go here select oh
acquire
don't I already have her I don't know
I guess I'm taking the PD Exchange
oh I'm very proud of how this
illustration turned out oh you're an
artist
game development department oh I'm the
best player and I'll help you out okay
thank you she's cute
she's back here in the background too
oh oh well what should I do should I go
to regular or should I continue with
this one is it the same rate
that's the twin yeah
no more
regular regular okay because I got the
the ones that are here anyway okay okay
okay
what should I write this time
[Music]
where's my luck guys
come on
bird power unites
two more I'm running out of touch on my
knee
I'm running out of it
[Music]
the brain is gonna fall out no
um
foreign
[Music]
if I look at it with these eyes
one more opinion I gotta say no no what
for what for my future that's not
existing
I'm not gonna say for non-existent
future
um
foreign
[Music]
who is she
the best oh oh
where's the rainbow where is it
um
[Music]
oh
wow hi guys
[Music]
a scribble scribble
word
can I talk to your manager
well you know she'll get stronger right
if we get dopes we can make her stronger
uh and upgrade her right
um
uh yeah
[Music]
I'm in the regular one and you can use
me going to the regular one
no no no this is pickup I'm a regular no
no no no no no no no oh baby
everybody
oh I don't think we're getting any more
rainbows
if I wanted to see my wife
but like in the wrong way like I got
those dupes from midoni okay this must
be not a dupe though
okay
I was about to become really loud
negative and feel like no we're not
getting anything else out of this
oh
God
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
anything from my Lord
foreign
I've got a blue team what does that mean
what does that mean
you're jealous
today's her birthday today
do they do anything special for their
birthday do they get more experience
can we sing Happy Birthday
happy birthday to you you happy birthday
to you happy birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
that was her name right
say to you
oops wonderful
yeah wow what do you want for your
birthday you wanted to find a new Sensei
your wish has been heard
oh
why okay I'm I'm satisfied I'm not happy
now
but I'm Gonna Roll again this is the
last one supposedly unless we get some
more free Stones uh
I'm telling you the moment she was
taking out this envelope I was like
focusing my inner Mantra or whatever I
was I was I don't know if you saw it but
maybe you felt a special energy for me
because I was definitely like focusing
and like like you know communicating
with the game I I I I didn't sometimes
it comes when you don't expect it when
when you don't ask for it
go thank you
[Music]
thank you
here comes with Shadow no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
girls how many Rainbow girls are there
in this game
[Music]
no don't don't drink what does it
means you're gonna be jealous
foreign
[Music]
are you ready
but it is a tube
okay but um I mean
dupes are good too right you have used
for dupes
[Music]
oh my God that bunny is so cute those oh
man
cute cute
love the purple twin tails with all the
Band-Aids copium shush
good good I I I want to cut some more
um
[Music]
okay
that's a wonderful dream
sometimes
sometimes you're gonna be surprised
okay okay
um
can I like is something in my with my
inbox
still had something I still
[Music]
oh but
um
convenience store okay wait we're
getting we have no
no damn it it crashed I'm sorry I got
you too much
no power
overwhelmed the game
they wouldn't want me to spend my life
let me spell money
God damn it okay
ah gotcha
gotcha gotcha I got the gods please
oh
okay let's play the game a little bit
normally shall we hmm
let's play the game
um yes yes yes
well so far I'm happy with like the
characters that we got they're all
pretty they're also adorable
everyone looks so cute they have old
genius designs there's literally not a
single design that I'm like no that's
that's all that's not attractive
every every girl so far that I've seen
looks adorable
wait I already seen the screen why do
you guys not see the screen there it is
there it is
[Music]
let me in let me in let me in let me in
okay
I don't read notices
I still see it wait it might come back
to you guys
and come back to you guys in a moment
foreign
[Music]
how much is that uh
300 how much do I need seven I have like
um if I buy this one
oh you saw it
but it disappeared
I'm still in the game though don't worry
I'm I'm just buying some I'm just
babbling some stuff
[Music]
so I think for
a temple
all right uh
when it keeps on disappearing come back
to me
[Music]
receive my gacha currency
wow reward acquired I need 200 more
maybe if we play the game a little bit
do you think the game
um reward us with something
maybe the game sometimes the game
rewards you
and gives you stuff
there it is okay please
okay how how to put uh let's first I
guess uh look at this look at our
beautiful students
the music is so nice too I love the
music
oh these are our beautiful pools okay so
there's there's a
Strikers and specials okay
how do I campaign
yes yes
look what can I what about this what
about this
why don't you claim all of it then yeah
[Music]
um
let's go see how nice the game is gives
you free stuff
look at how nice the game is to me
ow
[Music]
um
uh oh that was supposed to be a faking
emoji okay
I see it means that I should stop
okay okay
[Music]
let's look at our formation
uh I was told it would be useful to do a
combination of the five of beetle
students
or four problem solver
characters
let's see I don't uh
who are the abido students
that team is really not good okay uh
should problem solvers were uh
was this a problem silver
you have shun I guess I have when yeah
this one is shown yeah yeah I think that
was my purple my the one that you get
forced to do
change Force what change sword change
sword
oh oh Academy name
is it Academy
[Music]
Millennium no that was not it it was the
twins the twins the twins the twins okay
so that's her and her
okay and then who should we combine with
that it's not important okay maybe uh
um
not sure what to sort for rules
oh wait ah ah here's his tank and stuff
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay and I know I don't I
don't I don't I trust you guys I mean
we're in the beginning of the game so it
can't be that difficult at it okay now
we need like something here in the back
uh who do we want in the blue slots
for the lore
setting up for support Serena Serena go
to special ah
whoa Serena
and Hannah yeah you guys said Hannah is
a really good healer I don't know but
what about shizuko what about shizuko
okay
don't take two healers ah okay
um
not two healers but you said Hannah is
the best healer
okay this is gonna be my team look at
them posing like twins cute
okay uh so this is my team we formated
foreign
and I guess for now using the the
relationship of the twins
okay earn various rewards and promote
student growth by fighting battles
taking place all over kibautos
enjoy a wide range of stories taking
place around people does here to start
the show of girls night and this is my
channel My Stream
Bounty commission complete commissions
and obtain various items ah if you need
to grind for items for upgrades
and told myself combat powerful enemies
and earn even greater rewards and
tactical challenge participate in
tactical challenges interesting
let's do a mission area one
oh
so did I already do I guess I already
did the elbow one look at the hashtag
way home from school hashtag downtown we
on Instagram ah wait that's a sub Quest
can I did I do did I do album
we did it as a tutorial okay I thought
so
[Music]
okay and then this unit mobilize
submission is next okay okay okay let's
fight and go
strong team hey Overkill team
by the way I'm not playing on on the
maximum quality you could play this game
on higher quality right now
[Music]
what does she do increase his death by
28.1 percent for 30 seconds okay I guess
so
tired
they're so bouncy they walk so cutely
okay attack
that's what is this is healing right
continuously recovers uh-huh what is
oops oh deals 274 attack the damage oh
okay wait maybe keep that no
okay I guess I didn't want to use it on
a random enemy but oh there's no there
are only random enemies okay
[Music]
oh and I got 20 pyroxones or what what
it's called
oh some students say covering combat
finding shelter in the surrounding
terrain yes yes yes there is like I I I
did read that
the the terrain
the terrain yes yes
depending on the terrain there's there's
apparently depending on the character
they have terrain preferences
oh so now uh on it I have to uh do this
one isn't that what I just did
no I guess not
okay
never stop Quest
they look so cute
yeah when I first saw blue archive I was
first of all I was really hooked not by
the not only by the characters but the
girls but more like actually the whole
like really clean and bright designs
I talked about this on my stream before
Aesthetics
of the layout and all that you know what
I mean
the blue and the white it just works so
well oh
it's like so refreshing and it looks
really easy
sorry it's so loud
it looks really clean and modern hmm
okay we move on moving on run run run
you could do a story after yes I want to
oh
that's cute
use kotama to bug you no no yes yes and
we have humans
we have uh damage dealers we have a
buffers and all that we have all kinds
of different characters
go to Lobby
okay
uh story we're gonna do a story again
where the girls are like having
conversations with you wait what is
why is she speaking German shinatsu
of him I'll flus what does that mean
what Sensei why is there a toy receipt
included in the Charlotte invoice buying
towards has nothing to do with work
it's it's not a toy I needed to do my
job
no sense it's your job to set a good
example for the students this invoice is
a mess I'm gonna redo it all I'm really
bad at writing invoices indeed you
didn't mess it up on purpose so get out
of doing it did you sense it
Yuka Yuka We're Not Gonna become friends
like that you gotta let this one slide
okay uh there's e what is the total
assault event I wonder I also want to
check out the the club and the cafe and
all that but I still can't do that
where should I go oh what is this what
did I click
what what's happening
oh the music changed and I I just have a
different screen here that's so cute and
what is that
[Music]
finish chapter one you mean the campaign
oh wait story here it is
ah characters unlock those lines to do
when you do their Momo talk ah I say so
by improving the relationship you get
these special ways of interacting with
them I think
okay
yes yes for example if you were too busy
to actually listen to the story you
could go back here and replay the
memories
foreign
foreclosure task force okay a Beatles
orbitals is in danger of getting shut
down help the foreclose your task force
to save the Academy I
wow
[Music]
enter
oh we have some Story Time guys
I don't know
good morning sensor should I read this a
lot of people are starting to talk about
Charlotte and we've received letters
from other students asking for help
that's a great sign and it means there's
a lot of work for us to do
um but there's this one letter we got I
think you should take a look
what
who's trying to quit their job today oh
this is emotional to the advice of the
federal University hello my name is
I'm writing this letter because I want
to ask for your help our Academy has
been harassed one of the local gangs has
been tormenting us oh no
oh no oof it's a long story but we think
this gang is after the school building
itself the students are doing their best
to stop them it's only a matter of time
before we run out of ammunition and
supplies though at this rate School of
Falls to them for sure nah we can't
get weapon that's why I'm writing to ask
you for help can you please help us
Sensei yes that was I was what I was
born for
the backgrounds are so pretty
actually I got like in order to make the
thumbnail I got like data to make like
the thumbnail and uh I was sent like all
these beautiful backgrounds in high
resolution and oh my God they look so
well drawn so beautiful
I should just use them as my desktop
background
and binos high school huh it used to
have a large driving District but it
fell on hard times due to climate change
the district was so big that people
would even get lost in the middle of
town
that must sound ridiculous how does
someone get lost in the middle of modern
civilization I'm sure that was just an
urban legend
anyway I can't believe the academy is
being bullied by some new life gang it
sounds pretty dangerous series I wonder
what brought this on
I need to go to the builders to save the
cute girls
you want to have the hair right away you
really don't back down do you
all right then good luck
[Music]
um YouTuber Debbie when
I eventually wrapped in albedos albutos
albinos but got lost in the middle of
the district it took days to find the
school
I'm in a school anime let's go this is
my dream this is the dream of every
anime fan
oh oh
I I'm good at touching more
wait this is this is this looks like the
same but it's not right enter and no way
this is uh
oh I'm done with chapter one
oh oh
I can't do these okay
how do I get more chapters
you need to do more missions uh-huh what
about sub story oh
looks like I can do this one no
I can
that is making the game part one we've
got this year's game of the year in the
back oh let's see if you're gonna get an
award
let's go okay some sub stories to show
you as well
oh
[Music]
and the 8-Bit music is cute too
what are you up to Sis
this is a critical moment
one more hit just one more hit and I'll
be victorious
ah students find the two you've been
playing this game a lot lately huh
They just added online matchmaking in
the last update online
was I thinking of dating dating
matchmaking
now I can play in real time with people
at the arcade
I was starting to get bored because I
was only finding easy opponents but
after the while I finally ran into the
worthy challenge
[Music]
oh oh what a messy room though you need
to hire one of those mates
but I got them cornered now I just have
to use a command grab to cancel their
guard
what the heck they did a guard invention
into an uppercut
[Music]
what assistant Peach spider has been
defeated
[Music]
hopefully I made one tiny mistake at the
end and I got the tables turned on me oh
how to turn tables
so close it was by whisker
nothing you can do about it though A
match is a match
I I should send them a thank you message
for that good game Gingy yeah yeah Gingy
spider good game free one two three days
let's have a rematch sometime
[Music]
really wow
what this is a completely uncalled for
rules
send him a virus in a zip file
come on what's with that attitude you're
acting like a child well you are so
trouble
yeah yeah you're a child here not me
actually seeing how you slow your moves
here maybe I should be calling you
Granny instead
he's calling you Boomer
good granny
I almost beat you remember
is someone crying sorry I don't speak
loser
oh
toxic
where did you
oh oh sh oh oh it's
going down
oh
he had that
he oh
he blocked her
unbelievable
how dare you
oh boy that's rough what the heck
what the heck
what the hell right I know
unbelievable
now crying my shoulders
well since they did that we're going on
their real life
you're not gonna try to hunt him down
are you
what us too
you want us to come with you
of course intimidating the opponent is
everything
I'm 100 sure that we're dealing with a
video game nerd so if we show up with
big group they'll get scared and
apologize
aren't we just as nerdy as they are
though
you really have to get so worked up sis
it's only a game you lost and they trash
talk too that's all
just a game this is a matter of the game
development Department's dignity
that person not only trampled over my
gesture of sportsmanship but also called
me a granny
a granny
oh God
forgivable
you're angry about being called a granny
then losing the match
silly toxic players are bad influence on
the fighting game scene
and the unpleasant experience becomes
the norm every time someone plays a
fighting game who will ever play them
for the sake of a clean gaming
environment we must teach this toxic
player a lesson
I agree when I was playing an mmrpt a
few days ago my character got killed by
a Max Level player it was so painful
that I just wanted to put the game
completely
then I caught up to their level and have
already had my revenge oh
wow these girls are amazing
yep already reached max level seriously
your obsessiveness scares me sometimes
but don't you taunt the opponent
sometimes when you win says
as soon as you finish the game a game of
fruit jellies with me you taunted me you
said I could beat you using my feet
it's okay to trash that people you know
it's much more rude to say things like
that who's told strangers
Oliver anyway when I searched this
person's match history I found out that
they logged in 10 minutes ago from a
nearby arcade
there's something wrong with the game
that you're playing if it tells other
people random people that you even
blocked
where they were playing from
I think this is
problematic
uh data leak no not even a data leak
it's on purpose what is this game
or is she a hacker no that was the game
literally gave it to her
oh my God which means that we can find
them if we head over there right away
let's track them down and get them to
pull oh my God is this like the Mean
Girl Club
I happen to have some business at the
arcade myself I guess it wouldn't I
wouldn't mind joining you
it's like a quest to defeat the general
of an evil Lord a four-player Reigns I
don't have any business at the arcade
and I don't want to get in a fight
either can I set this one out
in a quick boss battle each and every
member has a critical role
Zone control works best when there are
four players each blocking aside
but still
oh yeah the new console that you've been
waiting for should be on display there
aren't you curious about what kind of
new functions it has
a new console
you never go out on your own anyway
let's take this opportunity to go see it
together what do you say
all right fine
but I won't get involved I'll just watch
from behind
that's good enough
[Music]
a full player party has been formed holy
what is that weapon though oh my
God
let's kill him
[Laughter]
oh my God oh my God
I I actually I mean this is really
surprising I didn't expect this kind of
story here but I like it it's funny
really are you for real oh my God
take him down
oh we got part two as well you guys want
to listen to part two let's can we like
listen in what happens to the dude
I am I am curious
and you get a voice over from me yeah
it's getting real let's listen in
okay okay
going in Potter oh wait that's the
chicken on the left side
it's much bigger than the last time we
were here but they ran over at the
building or something
seriously whoa they brought in the new
space cat machine
years old there's a new console display
finally the 15th generation of consoles
is here let's see I added a new cooling
mechanism on the side that will
definitely improve the problem that the
previous gen hen
not only that the response rate is much
faster now thanks to this high-end
gaming memory whoa
news will always get so excited about
gaming stuff
let's go play Space cat says
the music is so fun
I want to use it as my stream bgm if I
could
okay but I won't go easy on you so
Bracey I wait this isn't what we came
here for did everyone forget why we're
here we have to find that toxic player
right now
actually I came to buy a new controller
we have a lot of monsters to slay momoi
which game should we play first
months forever to stay here and look at
the new console and find someone no even
at this very moment the player might be
trash talking others
if they keep doing so more and more
people do the same there might be not
there might not be a single fighting
fighting player left
I'm jumping a little too pessimistic
here
this is a sacred battle to save the
world yes yes you get it Iris
hey Wells it's high time that we head to
the evil Lords then
[Laughter]
all right let's head to the section
where the students fight the two
Machinists
let's track him down
there aren't as many people out here as
I expected maybe the guy already left
no there's no way check the IDS on the
screens
it's not this plan
not this planet Eva oh
damn
she's a cutie too oh no oh no
when I'm on the winning streak
you mean that clunky combo was your
secret move are you serious ly my
grandma is better than you
hi you're who can't even game
right
and dog
it I can't believe that there's a player
out there who trash talk in real life
like that
I found it the same idea
[Music]
oh my God
you guys you guys want to challenge
[Music]
fun free one two right you're the one
who called me a granny online
oh
[Music]
you are Peach bye time
look at you you're just as wimpy as I
expected
what did you
think you're so rude I can't believe
you're still saying that stuff face to
face I mean she's pretty brave I must
say
at least she's like like most people
they're only able I mean it's not
probably not a good thing to be able to
say it in real life too but most people
only able to say it on screen they're
big big big people on the interwebs but
when they're out of the interwebs out of
their homes they can't do
oh
but yeah she got balls
that has cleansed this evil door she
says
we're the sword of light yes I will help
too I guess evildoers must go we must
stand on the ground
apologize for your abusive language I
Will Show You Hell of a test right now
[Music]
nope not gonna do it
don't apologize the people weaker than
me and what hurt my pride to bow to an
inferior player
why are you little
should I shoot
I mean I think that's a little bit no
why is it going I still have the game in
front of me
they probably don't want to show this uh
uh extreme scene here
hey capture the game please
oh there it is what happened
oh
the game I'm so sorry uh I'm sure the
game works better if you actually play
it on a device like uh like a phone or
so
should we try to get it again let me try
let me try let me try I oh I'm dead
uh come on wait what happens to the
storage like um
I wonder if it's if it takes we can
re-watch it though even if it's already
like uh considered to be done
oh my God
all right that took over my whole screen
one moment
might have to fast tap a little bit
what do you mean
I was tapping I was dumping
[Music]
okay getting into the game again
one moment please
uh-uh you mean okay if we have to go for
the story again we'll just tap tap tap
tap tap tap
blue
that sounded cool
who wants that do you guys recognize the
voice which character was that
it wouldn't have crashed if you weren't
such a granny oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
the oven they're here three two one is
in in my chat right now oh no they're
salty I'm in the game
I am in the game there we are cute okay
uh how do we get back where was that
where where was that uh was it a
campaign
[Music]
story strawberry milk
some story
here
okay
going in again
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
OBS obs
obvious
[Music]
this scares me makes me feel like the
game is about to crash but it's still
here uh she's trash talking me right now
I'm
so bad oh there it is
no
no no no
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
in the trash talk it's the trash Talk's
fault
oh no
I mean hmm
we're already over now or that's for
sure I couldn't Fury but I don't want to
see the end of that story it's such a
cliffhanger
hmm
hi I'm Cortana
I love that though that was legendary
like what the hell was going on there
okay I'm trying to I'm trying to go in
there one more time
if however you guys should get uh the
game oh by the way there's a link in my
description now you can get the game
live uh you should get it on your phone
or on your tablet or something I think
it won't work much better I am really
really really sorry that this is uh so
unstable here
um
excuse me I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry
do we get gacha funds and now that you
get my catch a lot maybe it will rub off
on you yes
it will rub off on you you just have to
watch the stream and you're watching her
right now so I will give you some of my
Godzilla
um
it should come back soon but yeah
uh I think even even if it doesn't work
we've already seen the gacha we've seen
the story or seen the fights and
unfortunately no no Cafe I wonder how
how the cafe looks like but there is a
like a cafe
and that you can unlock later I wonder
how long it takes
sorry Dad I couldn't show you guys that
I'm just taking
some time to lower here
thanks for your goddamn blessings you're
welcome I really haven't played a Gato
game in a long long long long long time
so it was definitely a lot of fun I like
these kind of games but
um I I didn't have the opportunity to
start like
um another one that I really liked for a
long time but this one has such a cute
graphics and ah the music is so good too
the interface looks so nice the 3D
models are so so like wobbly and cute as
well and bouncy
um
got a bit mentioned two one to unlock it
oh okay well I'll do it on my own time
then
I mean that all of that gacha must be
used for something right it seems like
I'm having troubles getting back in here
let me close this again
sorry everybody sorry
uh
I'm trying one more time
oh wait let me let me try something else
one second
um
Maybe
yeah okay
okay
um
come on come on come on come on
oh next on
next song
[Music]
it's my birthday in an hour
happy early birthday
so many birthdays it's quite the
surprise that one of the rainbow
characters that we got had her birthday
today though
foreign
I don't know what I should consider it
to be
oh I did that welder Wilder I did that I
can't get in anymore I don't know why
um
no me
middle is very strong you're very close
to getting her to force that oh wow
wow that's pretty cool
uh
oh here I'm gonna try this
did you hear that
window sounds
no no don't give up yet
don't give up yet hello Windows yes
a little archive
come on come on come on
maybe I used all my luck on the Katya
gods
next song I see the logos oh oh game is
open
ing
I'm scared
I'm scared no
foreign
[Music]
I just need you guys to see it
come on
um
hello
[Music]
where is it
open up
let me try something else let me try
something else let me try something
again
[Music]
wait well ah yeah okay that works better
probably
uh
okay one second
wow
okay different capture method
[Music]
we show
okay
now please please please let me just
look at the end of the story
song was bopping indeed
I really like the
how do I say this in English I like in
Japanese I would say I like to say
kaikan the world
feeling that sounds weird in English in
Japanese it sounds better is that a
better word for that
[Music]
let's show you the end of that story
maybe it's not good if I skip too much
ah the setting the World building yes
yes that's what I mean
looks like
so
so beautiful with all the
um
the the blue and the white it looks so
refreshing
oh
he's gonna tell his mom
it's gonna tell Amy
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
until what
part here
yep somewhere here I think
it's gonna do it
[Music]
apologize to people weaker than me it
would hurt my pride oh I already read
that what
well
should I yes yes here here we are
hero I'm ready to draw my sword just say
the word oh that's a sword
you think that's unfair unfit and why
don't we
don't wave now to settle the score if
you can get one round of me I'll pull it
poets for what I said she probably isn't
okay fine but I won't go easy on you
this time get ready to get on your knees
and franchise
well then
who's gonna win
so oh no oh no
you lost again after talking such a big
game what a toe scrub
you can't you can't just sit in the
bottom left corner and away that's cheap
cheating oh I see it
housing pokes
what are you talking about
the game so they're completely Fair if
you don't want to get hit by them then
come up with a way to counter them I'm
about some made up rules
does this sound like everyday life to
you guys like are you trash talking or
are you guys getting trash talked in
games as well
I I don't really play those type of
games where people could trash talk you
I guess so I don't really have that
experience
sometimes
I mute everyone
that's odd Lane poking moves aside none
of the special moves that since you seem
to work yes yes sometimes oh man so you
guys are having a Deja Vu or something
is this hashtag relatable to you guys
is there something we're missing here
the opponent is probably exploiting
above
a bug
yes there's a bargain student finder
tool that freezes the machine very
briefly when the second input is done
that's why I'm became Frozen crashed
I think the opponent is using that bug
to dodge momoy's attacks
then there's no way for us to win
you might have a chance if she was much
better than the opponent but at this
rate
oh
oh I'm out of here
see Elena loses
oh oh
hey would this be okay if I played
instead of full movie
what a new Challenger
sure bring it on but you will be yet
another victim to my Superior techniques
I guess I'll have to get serious then
ready fights he's gonna win she's gonna
win
yeah oh wait that sounds like she just
hit her in the face for real
well as Queen you that Queen flowers
wake
me
no no way Ella I lost a kid like you you
too I can't even get a hit in a new
finishing with a full combo
now apologize she's so cute I need her I
need her
missed
fine I hate to stand for the promise is
a promise oh rolling room
oh I didn't think she would really
apologize
sorry I said some harsh stuff before
wow
thank you though you smashed that
arrogant gamer in like a second
a parasite Victory you're awesome
that was a victory wave of the name Ice
Queen
plane stop making bunch of funds
everyone it's embarrassing
wait so you're us Queen the legendary
gamer who's remained number one in the
online leaderboards critically acclaimed
and has never shown their face to anyone
I'm now legendary gamer but here I am a
scream
[Music]
got curlers earthquake
there's an earthqueen that fabled gamer
who not only ranks number one in
fighting games but also won awards
I can't believe that I get to see us
going to The Flash
oh my God she's Fame oh my God the
internet's Fame the dog kind of line I'm
getting your autograph first
now that gives me Aqua Vibes like being
ink yeah help me
[Music]
um
the people recognize their username
since we're at an arcade
look at all the fans Uso has it makes me
so proud oh
hello if you are here hello
and why did I read that in Japanese
okay well if you wish to become a great
ruler you must bear the full weight of
the crown
she's so wise
all I would at least
to be okay
love no more oh
user is now able to leave the arcade
after being forced to greet her flock of
fans
funny that was cute oh
that was great
it was really fun oh that was that was a
nice story
relatable for a lot of people in my chat
too
it happened so often doesn't it I know I
know
hmm I feel bad about the game crashing
so often I wonder if there's one more
thing I could do
[Music]
maybe we can do one more like battle
a Terrain adoption okay let's do this
okay
oh what ah is the first team that I have
to use this it looks like it wow she
looks so like uh like like like uh like
Yankee
has a different meaning in the Japanese
I think than in English I mean the
Japanese meaning
foreign
[Music]
yes I heard of that foreign
I know what that is
what cover is not such a scary company
you don't have to hide and protect them
yourself when you see color
s
and that is true
yeah yeah she's she's not scared of
cover
oh
wow okay I love her she's fun
[Music]
look all right
that's fun
what about you what do you do oh fan
shaped area oh okay you won't hit many
but oh well show you those skills
oh my God
oh my God she's so aggressive
I love it no no we're done already
I wanted to show more scales
you need
she's very interesting
she needs to chill
we got more pirate scenes yeah
okay
what is this it's cute
we did the terrain adaption okay that
really didn't take much time let's do
this one too
what do we have here
oh and we go with our favorite team with
the twin uh Advantage
yes begin Mission let's go
huh all right how does this work again I
gotta walk over here no and face enemy
face
I gotta walk over to the bus but first I
gotta go here
oh girl girl girl
oh which mask should I wear today
cute
little comics in the waiting time for
you to read
okay wait I didn't look why are you
happy about the terrain
what is this
playing switch
whoa
wait so that's a that's a a
skill for like both of them they
activate it together
what is this
oh my God
what should I use I don't know who to
use they're so weak are we already done
nice shot oh how about you
in action deploy tactical Shield because
does someone need heal probably not but
look this is how the healing works
she's cute
what a cute team defeat hundred enemies
wearing helmets I did that easy Club oh
Sarang well that was easy all students
survived I would never let those cute
girls die first I would I would take the
position because I'm a phoenix so it
doesn't really matter okay then to the
we have to end the face and then we move
over to the boss and then we go kill the
bus
eating yummy yummy food
battle commencing battle power up oh
what's this doing again increases attack
oh yes yes
[Music]
nice
foreign
guys like not only out of this team but
who's your favorite character
oh oh I'm too late
is that it where's the bus where's the
bus warning uh oh
of course I do
oh
hanaya
that's a good idea
[Music]
oh so strong
down
[Music]
oh shun popular
then I guess I was lucky to get her in
the beginning
[Music]
oh
no
reward acquired some nice fashion
credit points pirate scenes waterproof
sports bag Etc so these are like the
items you grind in order to upgrade I
think weapons and stuff
or or skills or well you definitely need
to upgrade something
okay uh no we're not going there now I
think this is where we should end it
already uh went uh overtime yeah but
this is a really really cute game thank
you next time for sponsoring the stream
I hope you guys all enjoyed it even
though there were some uh tiny problems
here and that I'm sorry about that but
it is a great game I think you all saw
that the gacha is fun there's a lot of
really cute characters no matter which
one you get you will get a heart attack
just like me yeah
so be careful prepare yourself for a lot
a lot amount of sugar the link uh for uh
there's a tracking Link in my
description that you can use to download
the game I would be glad if you would do
that and yeah besides that yeah I just
really hope you guys enjoyed it
[Music]
up yeah
okay
so cute she says that to me but you were
the one chilling and hanging out and
dreaming in the background
head Pat can I have pet you too
how was that like someone said that I
could do ah
huh did she just react ah okay if I tap
longer
it went to be done like half that's me
neither understandable have a nice day
now downloading good job go downloading
[Music]
out now it has been out for a little
while
oh I like this ah like this oh that's
how you head pet someone yeah she
doesn't seem so excited about it
I think there might be other characters
who enjoyed a little bit more
thank you though guys for watching and
thank you next one once again I will
leave it at this and I'll see you guys
sometime soon for the next stream thank
everybody for
money playing and enjoyment we say
[Music]
that's the chance to play Blue archive I
was really already interested on it when
I saw the council girls playing
um thank you for letting me try it out I
had a good time the characters are so
cute and I love I love their
personalities
and I'm gonna say that I really mean
them personalities okay you guys always
doubt me but I really mean the
personalities okay
I mean they look cute too and I'm I'm
gonna be the first one to admit that
but they have each one has a has their
has an individual funny
characteristic and all that you know
no you guys doubt me too much
[Laughter]
guys have a nice evening a nice morning
Wherever You Are
take care everybody
bye bye bye bye bye what's up
[Music]
foreign
again
[Music]
see it's really short but it's so cute
you guys are on the ground with me
[Music]
one more
okay gotta go sleep now