foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you foreign
laughs
hello welcome Happy Easter welcome to
the hollow Ian Easter spectacle yay are
you guys singing yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
it smells like hard-boiled eggs here
eggs
[Music]
for the big delay but we are here now
and we are ready to celebrate this
joyous egg day
thanks
[Music]
excuse me
[Laughter]
um
the word egg with the s in the front I
said eggs eggs I said it twice so yeah
probably came for that would we like to
hear some introductions from these
lovely participants that start to my
left side with Iris
okay Iris it's Iris
it's Irish and I am so ready to find and
collect everyone's eggs yay
thank you for participating I always
even though it's really early over there
I'm good
it's okay over here we have a dead phone
uh
are you okay you're lying in the foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah happy Easter hope you'll find a lot
of eggs today oh next up behind we have
the crony copter not quite just today is
small cloney
I mean
hello it's it's an excellent day for
some Easter egg hunt
what I was gonna do crony
damn it my
bags guys please wait what I didn't get
it
it's gonna be very exciting
oh yeah thank you
and really exciting uh jumping up here
is who
[Music]
oh that sorry yeah crony uh poached my
egg puns
hey everybody Maury Calliope here today
is the day of eggs
and and I love hard-boiled eggs they're
super yummy and you definitely should
eat the whole thing and not just the
outside the yolk is good too hashtag
yolk
um it was nice talking to you in the
chat well I mean I guess I guess if
you're training for like Macho Man
attorneys or whatever blend it with your
nails your nails smoothie anyway I'm
ready to win this find some eggs win
yeah
hopefully you can find all the eggs
kind of tall am I oh damn just a little
bit I can look oh there you go
[Music]
hi it's fauna I know exactly what to say
on this extraordinary day
and that was it I'm gonna find the eggs
maybe
not into that
that was amazing
gladly
don't do that
[Music]
hair is gonna be a little bit delayed
but please introduce yourself
and I'm excited to find some eggs and
stuff
[Music]
yeah wow
Foods
one is so small look at how tiny she is
Crusher in my palm oh yeah I'm gonna put
you in a jar no don't eat that oh please
don't
she's so cute I love that okay so uh
basically let me explain a little bit
what we're gonna do today we have kind
of um two games prepared I want to
prepare for you didn't make it in time
hope two is okay guys
um so we will play a quiz here later uh
actually not right now we just wanted to
say hello over here but we'll move over
to the council race world and then to
the myth world and both worlds currently
have a lot of eggs hidden everywhere
there's random eggs that give you one
point and there is special eggs that I
remember Drew I remember basically Drew
one personal egg and if you find that
egg it will give you uh more points 15
points actually wow incredible so
everybody must aim to find their
personal egg hopefully you could even if
you happen to find somebody else's
personal ink you could
what's going on
finally keep it to yourself
[Music]
easily okay don't easily tell someone
hey your eggs over there
don't do that okay okay production games
so when you find a random egg you click
on it and it just collects it
automatically and it'll add it to the
school board over here and then the
other worlds also have the scoreboard
and then if you get your personal egg
you must bring it to the egg cups each
person has an egg cup that already hears
spoilers design a little bit well aren't
they looking gorgeous
it's just
it's basically oh I'm in with some cool
glasses Iris egg is that reminds me of
like
pop team epic or so I don't know I was
inspired yeah
oh cute and Cali Zack is her kitty cat
it's just two too
he's a crazy owl I mean not so crazy but
she looks what's crazy about that it's a
bar now it's really scary it looks like
nightmare fuel like my sleep paralysis
demon are you really scary or really
cute just like no in-betweens
[\h__\h]
and uh for me I made a little chicken
that hatched out of the egg you know and
then crony what was that was what's the
inspiration behind this one that is
boros I have a sparkling like the star
that he is
cute
he had out of yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
more yes
[Music]
egg
yeah they do snakes lay eggs too
[Music]
I'm pretty sure yeah they're they're
eggs they're not they're not mammals
yeah they're eggs they're eggs yeah I'm
surprised the egg can predict its future
of how it's gonna look like
yeah
that is by Fall now this is this is a
sapling is it a little sapling
[Music]
some of the random egg designs are by me
and actually I see the the design on
this cup is also by me yeah oh this I'm
really proud of the design from this cup
that tutu is on because this is a burger
it's supposed to be a burger egg
[Music]
a tomato
that is a tomato there's onion there's
salad there's cheese and there's two
patties it's ruined I'm just kidding
well I was wondering what the purple was
it was onion yes
[Music]
I'm hungry
all right so well without further Ado I
think we will move on over to the first
world you know follow me follow me okay
cameras will follow us as well let's go
to the myth hub first
said please
hey why does crony move faster than me
that's not fair she has an advantage
well okay let me tell you this in order
to move as fast as you possibly can if
you're on desktop mode you have to press
shift while running oh thank you yeah
all of a sudden
what do you mean she's always cute okay
we're done
you're not the only one fauna has
disadvantage too okay
[Music]
yeah break it down
below
I can't do any movements
[Music]
okay
so this a whole miphop every room should
have eggs again just press left click
and when you find your personal egg
bring it here also there will be a kind
of a time limit I think it's seven or
eight minutes and the um there will be a
voice cue to tell you that time is
running so
um how about starting position will be
uh at everybody's cups okay okay I'm
ready okay I'm here well I have to be at
the button but it's pretty much the same
okay wanna crony stop kissing
and then you come I need to
over here over here
come on guys leave room for Jesus
Jesus are you ready to find all those
eggs
the least
time one go
mine no shift no shift I'm not shifting
I'm in vrs okay no
is fast
[Music]
I'm a desktop
okay
yay what the hell
with no eggs in here really nothing here
[Music]
grab the eggs in the trees
what what on Earth how do you have 26
what 26. we have 26. maybe
[Music]
17.
it took all of them already broken are
they worth well remember they're all
worth different points
a personal one what if they do
what are you doing the personal one back
where no Malia I found Cali I don't
think we can take each other's eggs I
found calories I don't think so I took
all those eggs
[Music]
how does Kelly have so many wait
I'm a winner
they weren't like I feel like there was
so many more eggs when I like first saw
this area oh my God how can you all get
so many eggs so fast
you guys thank you
um
a long time yeah me neither I swear
where where is it father have you really
collected 41 days I don't think I
collected
[Music]
you guys are not allowed in my room
they're my ex now
[Music]
get out there
it's a button you gotta press the button
I found my egg at least I found two two
eggs
please
get to a spaceship what
why are there eggs in space can you ship
eggs in space
[Music]
I found iris's eggs in my room
and I found mume's egg
yeah
[Music]
what how do we get back inside are they
in the same plate are we yeah
yeah right yeah
it's a spaceship but if you guys come
over here to where the main lobby is yes
look over here
over there that door
we're doing this to give them hints with
her eggs are no they just haven't seen
the spaceship before
wait when did crony get 16.
how do you get back inside I'm outside
right now and I can't you gotta press
the big red button
damn it there's a big red button that's
floating it's not letting me collect it
right here is that Iris turn around
bring it you have to grab it it was just
going up into space
come back
[Music]
and Iris was the Imposter
yeah but how do I grab this while also
pressing the button uh left click and
then keep click holding it okay I would
say I'll take it in for you but I don't
think I can press the button oh no the
leg where's my egg I haven't seen my egg
I don't think anyone can wait
[Music]
you have to think logically there's a
lot of eggs
but what is it with bonus score
got a bunch of eggs I don't know I did
find several eggs they must not be worth
one point though right okay maybe
different colors are worth different
points
should have been one point each I think
we found every hair guys
[Music]
they're all gone
yeah
my egg is stuck in space
it's not over yet
is it is it though I mean I think we're
gonna go to council
wait wait wait don't wait but Iris my
egg is stuck it's okay it's okay you
have to leave the egg behind Iris yeah
Iris no you need those points
[Music]
[Laughter]
because you did found find it so it says
you can push the egg through the glass
don't be mad at me now we're allowed to
run Iris you can push the egg through
the glass Maybe
you can it's okay
what can I we just gotta find a hole in
the spaceship sneak it in
I because I couldn't get it I do not
understand
right here
I can't I can't grab it anymore I don't
know how many you grab I was I can't
grab it it shows up like I could grab it
but it doesn't look okay but I think it
makes sense
because I only grabbed like I think
there's a letter before I try to grab it
from the other side
what do they mean I did not I wish I was
try coming back inside and try grabbing
it from the inside what an egg Thief
it will
really they like highlights for me if I
stand right here it's stuck in between
the outside and the inside it doesn't it
doesn't highlight for me wait
wait
it's on a different plane of existence I
was standing right here by the corner of
the pillar and then it highlights it's
stuck no Iris egg
[Music]
it's okay
she'll she'll live looks so sad
your final score plus 15 points that
will be your score okay yeah
[Music]
that's the best number so technically
I'm the winner let's go
there you go
I think that the eggs were not worth one
point each
possibly we got a confirmation okay no
our top three is Anna
yeah I like how it's taped
there's also a date
oh it expired expired
yay yeah
okay guys let's go back to the studio
ones please no okay okay okay
all right and from here we go to the
council Temple same elevator
on the same elevator okay home
[Music]
in the area where the scoreboard is
I love these statues
[Music]
she's so funny especially
yeah Bales no not a rat anymore but but
a bunny all of you are bunnies now
pickle pickle
[Music]
congratulations you're so funny looking
no
no yeah here and there there's some
Easter decorations like there's a big
egg up in the in the mountains in the
trees on both sides can we collect that
one no
important
too yeah but yes um activate it
supposedly they could be everywhere
yes
[Music]
are we beyond sit on where the ankles
please go on your egg cup okay on top of
it okay okay prepare yourself for around
ready three two one go yeah
foreign
give me that
these are not one point in front of us
what the [\h__\h] oh we gotta go to our
score from before
[Music]
I'm grabbing
I can tell
they're such a 71 how does she do it
that's a lot of eggs
well
no Kiara
I'm fighting for my favorite wife here
okay
I'm the I'm the collect collector oh my
God we're collecting The Collector huh
[Music]
okay
Emoji egg I found one too yes
[Music]
it was a nice map yes
why are you in my room get out wait I
wonder if Cody's room
get out of my room oh here are the rooms
where's crannies room
I found it sampling right where they
belongs
[Music]
you can rent into the right room
rescuing the little chicken
bringing it to it all the rooms are
already cleaned out
little Jimmy
um
[Music]
well I'll just look for my egg then
random eggs in the rooms huh only the
personal life
I found I found I have found crony's
doggy makra no no
that's mine I get to look at tutu's cute
face I just washed it I just washed it
recently oh it smells like crony
it's mine
I don't know
eggs
such a gamer I feel like you I guess for
us the crony's room is small is it just
from yours is small
packed with a lot of Personality yeah
true and love and it's just packed with
culture
stop stop get out I'm gonna open your
panty drawer okay
why do you have so many shoes
it's because A girl's gotta dress up and
stuck it out of my room
here stop
[Music]
it
stop stop I think we found all the eggs
again could it be
stop it
[Laughter]
[Music]
top
you know oh wait oh wait I thought we
were off camera
turns out you do the eggs that I drew
that I designed are five points
huh and then there's this like randomly
randomly designed just one point hey yo
cure why can't I get these eggs up in
the tree no that's not fair
that's not fair I I call a recount I'm
sorry I call a recount
hey don't don't play at it
[Music]
still possibly some hidden ones
he's fighting is this oh my gosh here
movies like this
okay
[Music]
check every
Bush's hand
no I got all the hand I need
do you need a hand with that watch this
hey you're watching granny
don't do that
oh my Lord You're a psychopath you're a
psychopath you jump down there
for real
[Music]
day of love a small I want to catch the
bee I'll follow the piece who eats the
bee where is everyone
where is everyone looking for eggs
still frantically looking
I don't know you weren't frantically
I'm not giving up I can multitask
I think they're gone now I think they're
all gone
seems like they've all been taken yeah
they've been cleaned out
we were once again too efficient with
egg cleaning and collecting so like
turning to make sure of course
fauna sweeping the eggs
figured out the eggs so the ones that
Kiara made
along oh okay they're Five Points I
already said that nobody was in there is
that moment yeah there are like where
the eggs that you girls designed those
are 15 points and there's eggs that I
designed just randomly like not my
personal leg those are five points and
then there's really really random eggs
those are one point so like for example
the burger egg is Five Points what if
you take your special egg out and put it
back in over and over and over again I
don't know please don't test it there
might be about there
I don't think you can thank God that was
um
I think Solutions designs of my eggs
that I submitted
oh oh the timer
oh yeah unfortunately yes
oh the timer went off yeah yeah yeah
okay well oh and I'll stop the count
stuff because we already found
everything I think
oh my God look at that school board whoa
sweep yeah
but Mom I also worked her way up and
yeah from the podestal now it's
Kelly looking pretty strong here but we
have to consider the fact that I
actually now has 80 points wait
[Music]
no no it doesn't show the scoreboard
that is the unthinkable currently
cronies uh the last socrony do you have
so yeah
that's because the first round was
ranked and I was keeping my word about
walking so
I was done dirty
um
oh well
unfortunately this is how it is now so
we will have to deal with it
no no but you can maybe get more points
if we go back down to the quiz points
[Music]
I'm going to
faint on stage but let's go
I get scared of quizzes oh well don't
worry about it don't tell me what to do
this change
don't tell me what to do please
don't tell me what to do oh my God you
lost hold on I didn't see where everyone
went because my contact fell out hold on
a sec
[Music]
either request a penalty
I request a penalty to be added to me
for my damages my pain and suffering 50
points
[Music]
for insurance before yeah no yes
hold on okay the elevator where's the
elevator
I went to the rooms the girls rooms it's
not there you have to go back on the
opposite oh okay I got it I found it I
found it
I found that I found it I'm coming back
I'm coming but I was joking I knew where
it was all right I'm here
foreign
[Music]
I don't think I've been waving all the
time
but look at hummus oh my God she's such
a thing
[Music]
you gotta put her whole weight down
yeah she's so adorable so everybody
um here uh until now you may have used
your bodies to get points but now you
will use your brains we have a quiz and
I don't know how many points for each
question you look at actually but
hopefully we can change the scoreboard
up a little bit there are two
tuitions which are more or less related
to
um Easter or bunnies or whatever and I
hope we can get Kiowa
[Applause]
what
all right
there's so much wrong with you
I I thought I was dead like I I did the
dying animation
[Music]
well now it's dead
okay what was it before
[Music]
oh okay
you're on the way you're on the way
you're fine no you're fine you're fine
okay
okay is everybody ready for a quiz yes
[Music]
please let's hope this works I'm ready
and didn't work so well maybe the
question interesting face but now let's
pray
first question from which country does
the egg giving Easter Bunny tradition
originate please look at that by the way
if you don't know where the question is
[Music]
Poland OH B England or D Germany
do you know the answer guys I must say I
must say
don't say what you said don't say what
you say I mean she could be wrong maybe
she can say what she says oh okay go say
what you want to say
I already pressed the button was that
okay okay yeah it's just everybody
locking your answers
[Music]
Easter Bunny appeared first in the 1600s
Germany
hi Google search years ago wondering why
the Easter Bunny lays eggs
Google search you cheaters
no she said years ago oh years ago years
ago years ago when I was when I was
wondering why the bunny used or the
bunny laid eggs I looked it up ah yeah
that kind of makes no sense but I guess
it's kind of misleading and confusing
the Easter Bunny in German by the way is
hazard
wonderful perfect pronunciations here
all right thanks so sorry for the sudden
Interruption but I'm gonna stand in the
corner for a second because I'm not
feeling so well all of a sudden
I'll be I'll be back is it the oyster
Hazard the oyster Hazard oh no no no
it's not I'll be back
go take care of yourself there you go
take quizzes you're not it's nice
very nice
and just noticed wow also I must have
got no point for that how many
is that a water gun
yes
does it have water in it
currently not I have also
this
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
a menace
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna oh yeah
here point point action
where's she
[Music]
no it's okay
come on
this would make a great game like a mini
game
she keep really fast
[Music]
oh my gosh she's in the trees
how did you get up there we stack on top
of each other
I will burn it I'll set it on fire oh
hey home
it will kill you and all the fees all
the bees come down here these are
important what come on
yeah they are I guess
I wish I had VR right now and not
desktop mode I will SWAT the [\h__\h] out of
you
and you'd be enjoying it
this is your tongue
what
oh no are you a frog or a cat I can't
tell
I died
[Music]
you should die from too much saliva
unless you drowned she drowned no she
threw a poisonous frog
oh he's so funny he will be dead by
poison
oh she looks sad
[Music]
magic kiss or whatever
I have to get ready get ready get ready
for the smooch kiss all right
[Music]
I feel better I also ate a leg oh it
should be it should be better
it's not one of her wings I guess
she says five legs you don't look like
you're better with that face of yours
oh there we go
[Music]
she likes jazz
criminals
[Music]
too much magic oh she's stalking she's
stalking
[Music]
overseas guy's face
stay attraction I'm so glad your imma be
today just like in the thumbnail it
really matches the environment yeah
right at home oh by the way I think the
lines are on the ground we're supposed
to be for an egg
um balancing game
[Music]
maybe maybe next Easter
can we do them oh what's the word
a Congo line is that what it's called
yeah
everyone do your best to reach me your
goal
right there you gotta reach home what if
I just cut them away
[Music]
yeah here we can be a two-person Congo
line it's okay I I'll jump instead
yeah
um
[Music]
flip
oh God
oh yeah
I have nothing to do with the prize what
what was the point of
[Music]
Point yeah I want 100 points for
participating in the conga line please
it was just a participation you know uh
it was just an example of how to do the
lion game exactly more or less it would
have been exactly like that of course I
feel pretty betrayed I don't know should
we I don't know when crony will come
back if she will come back we will do
the rest of the questions I mean it's
not so serious sure she sues anyway I'm
just kidding it's okay true true yeah
she's at the bottom of the scoreboard
how many extra points do we get from
each right answer
uh I didn't notice that someone in the
audience noticed how much more we got
Sarah said 69 now I don't know what what
number I was on before yeah before I was
who knows we'll know what the next
question
I got five oh it may have been Five
Points
and there's 12 questions
some possibility of 60 points oh wait
why are we only on the first question
[Music]
and then we resurrected her and um
some of you are still dancing
[Music]
that's Easter
are you feeling better
I just brought a heated blanket oh okay
yeah oh all right then let's move on to
the next question
[Music]
here we go how many many orange carrots
are present in pekora's default outfit
one two three
sure I know this one
[Music]
that's what I'm thinking
about the hair oh I'm putting one more
than I think there is me too yeah man I
was just thinking about the hair now I'm
just in case
I already answered my answer I don't
know if I can change whatever it's okay
I feel like being gaslighted into
thinking it's it's four it's actually
three
we will see I guess free
one answer is
yes
[Music]
because of her hair but then yeah
did anybody get points yeah I did what I
lost that
points
because Kiara was like oh I was going to
keeping track about the hair I was like
oh it's too wait everybody has cutting
points
everybody got points I didn't get points
oh yeah maybe who answers
[Music]
it may be bugged but um
everyone additionally personally what
their answer is okay so let's move on to
the next question just so we know just
so we know what their answer will be
okay the next question is oh in France
many villages cook giant omelets with
over 15 000 eggs on Easter what
how's that even possible what is the
supposed Legend behind this a Marie
Antoinette B Napoleon see a saint D the
villagers just like
in The Villages delicious I like how A
and B are actual names and then C is
just a saint oh yeah that seems weird
kind of vague yeah
[Music]
so in all of France 15 000 eggs are
being used or everybody in France uses
15 000 eggs for their morning
or like the whole village The Village
that's insane I was gonna say they just
like eggs
I don't
[Music]
hmm well I was actually Marie Antoinette
in a previous life and I can tell you it
wasn't her
[Music]
so okay
everyone what's your answering I was
wondering are you entering I'm answering
D okay I will also answer Dean what
about you
okay
okay I don't know you don't know Kelly
what about you d d I think they just
like eggs yeah
um crony I said c e okay
I said B oh and then the B next to you
says uh I pick B for b b
[Music]
all right let's go let's see what it was
and if you got points
oh I got points even though
I was wrong okay
everybody's getting points
a story says that Napoleon tasted an
omelette in a local Inn and liked it so
much he told The Innkeeper to make one
for his soldiers as well okay they're
fifteen thousands
how nice of Napoleon to think about the
poems but what if one of them were
allergic to eggs yeah they will before
they die allergies didn't exist back
then they will die either yeah
[Music]
that absolutely doesn't matter anymore
let's go on to the next question just
for funsies
the term Easter egg is used for a secret
for viewers to find in what medium was
this term first used
to be in comics see in video games or D
in paintings
ah but I guess the term to look here is
first first
okay I know I first heard about it
what about you Iris
uh do I say
yeah okay
don't worry I won't copy your answer
already put in D okay see before I was
Mommy where were you
I'm gonna go through how I first learned
it which was a okay uh Cali
I'm gonna say d not for different
different
not like the others
uh crony knee I'm gonna go with see ya
all right
[Music]
Sandy
yeah paintings and the bee says a for a
b
B no
hey oh okay nice that's how it works
okay
[Music]
wait never mind I can talk about it
was an animated movie it was another
animated movie in the you said
for the record I first said c then I was
gaslit of course
[Music]
wrote his own name in a hidden part of
the game and the concept of hiding
Easter eggs for players was born 1980 oh
like 40 years ago
well
[Music]
long time ago long time ago which is
also egg chemical
get it long time ago
haha
always laugh for people right yeah yeah
not good
if their egg cysts an Easter tradition
of kids dressing up as witches and going
door to door trick-or-treating
which oh no wait it's for Eastern what
which country below does not follow this
tradition
all of them
that sounds crazy
what I've never heard of this before and
I am kind of close to all of these
countries so
that's weird
um we don't do that in Austria I think
go we just didn't know it I think this
is
a trick question I hate trick questions
I'll I don't think I mean why would you
dress up as a witch on Easter
I think I think
don't you what
okay
um because
that thing is a trick question what
about you Iris
[Music]
okay I said
what
okay wait give me a second is it C for
crying it's um it's
[Music]
as deep for this okay
guys thank you for making it so clear
please wake up again
[Music]
I bet it's one of them but I don't know
which one and I'm just gonna put D okay
and Cali I say c for cute and C for
cause I'm Different oh
I go against the Green
[Music]
that's green I go for Dia cause I think
it's a trick question oh my God I said
the same thing
[Music]
I think it's real but I don't know which
country I said c okay I imagine Sweden
and Finland are buddies so they
celebrate together
why am I doing D if I think it's one of
them too but I don't know I could have a
higher chance of getting the point if I
selected one of them but however what if
it isn't any of them and I'm just
telling myself that it is because I've
been convinced that it's a trick
question and exactly I think it's a
quick trick question Emma what are you
going for yeah
[Music]
foreign
the custom has origins in old witch
Legends instead of threatening to
perform a trick the children give a
decorated Willow Branch in exchange for
treats what
Denmark is playing for Halloween on
Easter he's not playing right
oh they're not playing uh-huh Sweden and
Finland are though ah but really only
those two countries do it then it could
be more and they just wanted the
questions oops I need to know more about
this it's interesting because like I
feel like more your if any more
countries do it then probably like close
by countries rip willow trees
[Music]
square and it's interesting I've never
heard about this before next question
please it's oh rabbits are an invasive
species in Australia what animal have
they used as a substitute for Chop what
is bae
hey I wonder if they would know this she
probably would wouldn't she I don't know
what a Bilby is I think I heard of a
cool World Cup before but I don't know
what it is either quokkas are very cute
they're camera they like cameras with a
Bilby then I have no idea
mice but not mice yeah
marsupial it's true yeah probably it's
Australia
oh well no Australia experts except me
Austria all right are here today but I
will I think I don't remember either
exactly what it looks like but I think a
wallaby was kind of cute and maybe
bunny-like so I'm gonna go for a wallaby
it could be very wrong
Iris what are you going for I also said
a because I was debating between a and C
but I think chocolate kangaroos are kind
of hard to make shape wise so I'm gonna
say a okay
I'm going with B because I know it's not
it wouldn't be a kangaroo or a quokka
and I have a stuffed animal of a wallaby
and I don't see it being an Easter Bunny
damn what does this look like a
wallabye well my stuffed animal is brown
well it's not minus my animals it's
brown and has little ears and it kind of
looks like a beaver but without the
beaver tail oh I dream about a beaver
last night yeah that's kind of what I
thought oh well okay Cali
maybe a
okay A lot of people are saying B so I
wouldn't say
[Music]
you know what I said I just want to do
the contrarian wait
I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry don't worry
it wasn't still contrarian because I
chose it as well
okay what about you I don't know anymore
um I think I'm gonna go for a beat
because
uh I don't think I don't think clocus
are I guess famous like you know they
they are popular they are popular like
as an animal by itself but it doesn't
really represent Australia but wallabies
and kangaroos they are representing
Australia most of the time but they're a
little too big for chocolate bunnies so
I think I'll go for baby it was a very
reasonable answer thank you
[Music]
yeah I don't know what are you fauna
with me okay yeah because kangaroo is a
little too on the nose you know I guess
so stereotypical that's true yeah what
about bee the imma be uh
uh B but I think kangaroo is a
reasonable one because they have pouches
so they can carry eggs you know
[Music]
yeah
I think they put eggs in there wait are
kangaroo
jelly beans
[Music]
wait is our marsupials different from
mammals wait what marsupials
okay okay
their wombs are outside
foreign
[Music]
I should have chose
Billy
Billy's out is a lifetime marsupials
with long ears they are also endangered
and the prophets of Easter babies often
went to their conservation
I have to look up what it looks like I
know I want I gotta Google this too
I don't I don't know anything else oh
they look like ant eaters ish
[Music]
[Laughter]
a and not you they're cute
okay next question guys let's go in
Switzerland the Easter Bunny does not
hide the eggs for children to find who
does it instead
the parents they used to know seed
Easter Fox
is a good thing that like it's a bird
right that comes out of the cuckoo clock
but like it also exists on its own
cute bird
I have no idea Switzerland is like my
neighbor but I don't know
it's interesting how it's Easter it's
like about oh my gosh it's so funny
bunnies don't lay eggs
[Music]
two years ago
I don't know
wait banana says the bunny it's the
Easter Bunny it's just it doesn't hide
eggs for children it hides them for
something else it's what does it hide it
so they stop the Easter Bunny
huh but they're hiding it from someone
oh wait is the question that the Easter
Bunny hides it from for example the
Easter Fox yeah yeah yeah little Tides
the eggs yeah
[Music]
wait what is the actual question
because you know the Easter Bunny hides
the eggs for the kids to find
[Music]
I don't know anything
foreign
[Music]
I think that's I'm gonna go with the
with the cuckoo bird okay I'll go with
the fox Iris you
okay I have to retire
no
Mommy
I have to I have to retire
I am in shame
well yeah he's supposed to be knowledge
or something okay
[Music]
I'll guess
I'm gonna guess chicken okay okay
I'm gonna say C because that's I think
that's marketable and the birds are too
obvious
foreign
people's yards
okay fauna I said B because I believe in
the Eastern gnome
oh God
that will be very painful for everybody
who has a gnome phobia which I feel like
could be totally a thing because they're
just as creepy as you know clowns and
Americans too I feel like it fall into
the same category
be what a b now I call you just B Ahmed
what about you uh
[Music]
no okay I love that you always give the
zoom some time to come to you
sir
[Music]
high five wrists what yeah
well Easter Bunny is becoming more
preval prevalent prevalent prevalent
traditionally
personally the one responsible for the
eggs was the cuckoo in Switzerland and
the fox in Germany
the right answer then right get cocoon
[Music]
for Switzerland this is just side info
but maybe that's why I thought it could
be Fox yeah marketable animals
[Laughter]
not for children
nobody likes gnomes I like gnomes
it's the Easter for me I think gnome's a
bit scary because I think in Sims one or
another Sims game gnomes are like
spawning on your lawn
yeah right right yes
and you want to get rid of them but they
keep on coming back no yeah that's why
they have a movie
yep which one
Gnomeo and juice
[Music]
[Laughter]
really really
impressed really they look so mad
that was not funny
it's a real movie
[Music]
it's in crony's head don't listen
Gnomeo and Juliet what I think they're
even make a sequel
never ever do that aren't they dead
[Music]
[Laughter]
would you die
when they died
in the kids movie yeah
I should film I wonder
The Lion King too where they don't die
because that's based on Romeo and Juliet
was like Sherlock gnomes
[Music]
all right guys let's move on to the next
question I don't know how many more
there are but the next one is in Asian
folklore there's a rabbit with a mortar
and a pestle what is the rabbit doing
what is the difference
[Music]
why is the right answer there twice
with me mixing her herbs well okay is
that the right answer it sounds right
but which one is it B or C
this is cool this is cruel
what is the pounding watch it twice it's
just that important that they had to do
I'm gonna choose C for contrarian I
don't choose B for bounding mochi
okay
bouncy Mochi yeah bounding but bounding
multi Iris will about you it's very
important B for bouncy Mochi okay uh
woman did you choose now
I'll do I like
[Music]
um
I like the the way to see the font it
pisses me off so I'm gonna press I don't
like it typo I keep being a sheep
somebody's handwriting I'm sorry no no
no I don't think so Kelly you chose C
right I did okay chronini because it's
cool I chose C way too many times so
this time I'm gonna change it up to B
okay
I think B because that's what crony
picked okay
because I'm a b
[Music]
okay perfect the answer is
oh correct just for the record I was
still right I was still right I was
still right though
yes no it's the right answer no it's
right it's the right answer actually
because actually conversely it's
opposite day it's opposite day so I win
yesterday
because like the other like he went from
dad then he went from alive that's like
the opposite
[Music]
so uh the rabbit is supposed to be
making elixir of life in China and
Vietnam but in Japan and Korea it makes
rice cakes
Asia loves rabbits yeah
[Music]
yeah
I think that's that's truly where she
streams from most of the time
okay next question
is what animal lays all the biggest eggs
whale shark emu a b kiwi
see a whale shark working an ostrich oh
pale shark
[Music]
how big is a whale shark and does it
really lay eggs maybe that's the joke
what if they're tiny
or what if they don't even lay eggs you
know I've ridden on an ostrich before
and I've seen their eggs before
ostrich eggs are supposed to be really
really really big yeah did you guys see
the size of those kiwi eggs though man
because animals and ostriches are both
big burps ah oh Emma's also perfect huh
you know those are big they're like the
Australian ostrich
ostrich eggs
easier to get and I'm gonna say are you
are big and they could lay eggs are you
sure that's believing everyone on
purpose
deeper into my shame I would not
okay so mommy are you going you're going
for dinner you can see
Kelly
[Music]
I said d d for Deaf huh Thief for death
okay huh
yeah I said dear oh no
Deez Nuts I see ama is the only one
going for Steve why no my controller
died
it's the silence
[Music]
oh
yeah
well we'll see maybe you are actually
right let's see
[Music]
hey guys
herself
so the kiwis have the biggest egg
compared to their body size and whale
shark eggs hatch inside the mother's
body so they don't actually lay them
but it seems like if we wouldn't you
know think about the laying thing then
maybe the shark eggs would be the
biggest ones
interesting maybe yeah
we learned something new again do we
have another question oh we do how old
is the oldest found decorated egg
612 BC
3520 BC
20 000 BC or 60 000 BC what
[Music]
I mean it's not necessarily an Easter
egg right it can be any decorating
decorated egg like an Ancient Ancient
decorated egg from the Egypt
like a caveman egg
I bet there's a caveman Fred Flintstone
egg I choose d
my shoes
C
well what about over here I was if
humans even existed that long
um
I wouldn't yeah
I've been killing them since then so
yeah yeah
nice okay
you can still change your answer
actually yeah you can you can still
change your mind until you maybe I will
no okay
[Music]
and what you want B yes ah that looks so
bright okay young B crony is on hey what
you know
I haven't chosen eight in the water oh
my God I can feel better about itself
don't you yeah it seemed a little lonely
that's so sweet oh I see fun on B
interesting also kind of early an egg
would be preserved for so long
don't Nick become a stone maybe how
would they know it's decorated caveman
egg Limestone eggs like some scribbles
or so on it maybe
[Music]
turned Stone
oh it's all possible oh it was always
Stone to begin with who knows and you
know like a fossil you know that's what
I'm laughing uh
she's an a
[Music]
and maybe you could make them even
stronger
water flasks that's pretty cool
that's using your noodle
like pretty thick right
yeah the shells are pretty thick so I
can see that being used as water flasks
or as a weapons to knock you out perhaps
Maury was actually right why the [\h__\h] do
you sound surprised Chad
I'm sorry
you want to come a little closer and say
genuinely shocked
I existed back then ostriches both
[Music]
this is before Christ right what about
because there's still years from after
Christ and then oh yeah well it's time
to go back to history class with mume
Iris go go so
time for anthropology
we'll have a little class later for
everybody uh who didn't get uh these
answers right we will gather at mummy's
place all right after school classes
[Music]
extra lessons all right maybe we have
another question
[Music]
[Laughter]
everyone gets a point yeah
it's rigged it's always been rigged
never ever changing our
[Music]
okay I will go for
um
I'll go for it in England I guess they
seem like they would make that although
yeah
a for England okay okay
[Music]
difference
on the recorder it's the only song you
learn on the recorder yeah England
other things
everybody did indeed get it right Hot
Cross Buns originated from the 1300s
England and have spread around the world
and sometimes eaten all year round
I'm gonna go eat one later maybe it
sounds really yum actually I want to eat
that in a hard-boiled egg yeah what what
the hell what are baby rabbits called is
the next question maybe last one
a baby rabbits one is
be kittens see pups or D baby rabbits he
pops I think I've read this one before
I've heard of this one
maybe it's like once like unfittingly
pups or kittens like even though it
makes no sense
I really like kittens so I'm gonna
choose B
I have two kittens there's a war going
to remember ghost cat
bunnies all right
yeah I would I thought I thought bunny
was just a cute way to say around it
yeah I think at least in German there
are two different things or anything
they're hairs oh yeah different ties
there's hair and rabbit those are
different
oh
actually indifferent
in English no funny is just cute way to
say rabbit oh okay
which is different okay
Neil is currently keeping us from
streaming maybe cats baby cats okay
we're back now baby cats welcome back
[Music]
okay have you heard it before or just
guessing
I'm I'm
uh
uh I'm just just guessing
yes guessing
I'm doing B because I feel like I've
heard them called kids before but I'm
also questioning if I really heard pops
okay interesting Cali's going for b as
well Pony too
is going for bunnies
or am I thinking of foxes we foxes are
also called kids why are you going for
bunnies on there are you just
automatically choosing a now controller
is dead yeah also that but also like
bunnies people say it's like a cute name
for like a rabbit usually at least here
so maybe it's like people say baby you
know like baby became like a nickname
it's like funny
you know
[Music]
that makes sense yeah
I like that close-up
um okay then the answer shall be
one we are kids
I thought I heard that they were called
pups before that's why but I didn't
watch you guys the answer so I I'll take
that side what yeah but baby rabbits are
called kits or kittens a female rabbit
is a doe and a male rabbit is a buck oh
I know about the bus but yeah that would
make sense
a dough like a deer yeah yeah it is a
female
okay
I guess
that was it oh there is no next
challenge but that was the end of the
queen
[Music]
I think like you know the scoreboard now
is obviously meaningless but maybe you
guys uh wrote down the I mean the chats
maybe wrote down the answers of us on
the road and figured out who is the real
winner of the quiz uh but we might as
well never know maybe we're all winners
I want chocolate like the accurate how
are you getting me CPR
I am gonna give you
a smooch
to wake you up oh but then never mind
crony is is
jumping on her so never mind I'm good
we're lying together it's like we're
gazing at the top of the studio
there's no stars no stars just like the
lights lights are kind of like stars
it looks so warm I want to go towards it
go towards the light movie it looks so
oh okay guys with us
[Music]
three crony four it's like counting
sheep
[Laughter]
I don't see so many cronies
[Music]
basket because it's an egg I'm stuck
here
why I can't move oh my God
unbelievable
[Music]
let me take you out you're the are you
queen bee I mean are you a queen maybe
one day or you're saying workers well
not Stingers where's your stinger stuck
in an egg
do you die if you sting someone yeah
yeah her butt comes off if she stinks
someone right
yeah and you guys want to know one
tradition that we do in Austria I don't
know if you girls do this yeah you know
that in Austria we do
um uh
Aya bacon it means a egg like I don't
know you like punch there's two people
each person has an egg in their hand uh
like a boiled one and then you you know
punch each other with the eggs like you
plant the eggs the other person's egg
would be your own egg and then you see
which one got destroyed basically so
then if your egg is less destroyed then
you're the winner
yeah with the shell oh does anyone do
that
you guys and then you have to like walk
with it blindfolded or something I think
I don't remember does anybody remember
[Music]
oh is that for Easter
oh it isn't a game though
Loki what I wanted to do today how does
everybody say the word egg
egg egg egg egg
[Music]
what do you say egg egg
how do you say leg
leg leg leg leg egg
what are you trying to do
there's slight differences and people
make fun of each other for them
oh egg egg leg
[Music]
big big
I never thought about that before
big thing
yeah be careful how you say it those
words depending where you are because
you'll get bullied
who would both
take them back
legs
[Music]
oh I I don't have um I don't have a
tradition to say but I just want to say
that the only correct way to eat the um
the Easter Bunny chocolates is starting
at the ears if you start anywhere else
you something's wrong with you write the
face off
speaking of the Easter eggs
do you know that you know the leftover
ones at least in my country are being
melted back and then made into the
Christmas like Santa chocolate figures
yeah Santa chocolate like figures yeah
in Austria we have like it's not sand
some are Santa Claus and some are more
like Nicolas which is a similar like
more thin version of Santa there's a
cinema
yeah there's a fan version of Santa who
comes a bit earlier and he brings like
Gremlins that will like punch you and
you know hurt you that's hardcore
yeah Nicolas it's our fun
Traditions
yeah whips they bring with I have to
look this up because now I'm just
thinking of like a buff Santa but I
don't think that's right how do you
spell his name what the one I told you
about yeah Nicolas
[Music]
m-i-k-a-o-l-o-u-s okay and he comes with
like Krampus yeah
[Music]
feel free to come over
we can meet Krampus
yeah
it's so scary because like it's when I
was still in school when that date would
come they would raid schools and like
the streets and everything they would
literally invade the school like with
like tens 20 or so of them and then they
would really whip the kids but they're
like excited for it
and you're like please take me take me
and then they throw them around and it's
crazy people really want to be treated
like that but I always they're training
them to be massacres starting a little
okay in Austria
it's really scary I don't want to live
here anymore just kidding yeah
yeah but anyway I don't wanna you know
keep you girls anymore longer because
some have plans after this and it's also
really late for me and I'm so sorry for
the delay that happened but I hope you
girls enjoyed it and I hope to chat
enjoyed it too I wish everybody a happy
eggster huh
thank you
[Music]
thanks to all the modelers and
programmers as well that helped make all
this is really cool yeah
[Applause]
drawing something on the eggs or else
amazing the egg cup
[Music]
eating some eggs please think of kfp
they are providing them to you eggs are
sponsored by kfp all over the world
did they like the eggs
what wait do chickens have to be
chickens have to be pregnant to lay eggs
you kind of want the opposite although
there is a delicacy that involves having
now basically you have to have a rooster
just running around the like Cottage
where the uh The Coop where the chickens
are and then just buy the rooster
running around there they get excited
and they lay the eggs actually they'll
there's a baby you're eating baby
so chickens chickens don't have
intercourse together no
that's what you do yeah
yeah okay so enough of the baby talk
so where do babies come from us
[Music]
thanks for watching guys thank you
thanks everybody have a great day
[Music]
sir
oh sorry I'm the one
[Music]
what
thank you foreign
[Music]
further