[Music]
do
that loop is [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's 40 seconds not 20.
so
okay okay
[Music]
why why why are you gonna
why why do you need to work again also
let me let me fix something real quick
oh okay what did
you want what body
[Music]
well dead i didn't let's just let's just
uh act as if i didn't uh come out yet
but where was it again
[Music]
ah here
where was it again
[Music]
um
oh
oh i don't know how to do this oh
okay
i'm trying to
i'm trying to do something oh okay oh
[Music]
why
okay whatever
hello oh my god big
hello
[Music]
i'll be looking up a lot i think i tried
to reset it i don't know
had to reposition my camera and all that
you know
uh
because i brought
[Music]
[Applause]
hello everybody
it's nice to see your faces
somebody doesn't give a [\h__\h] she just
wants to be here hello
have you gained weights movie
no it just looks like this right now
right this is the angle angles are
important i love you
your mommy has to stream a little bit
okay okay mommy just
gonna stream a little bit
[Music]
why am i not able to look down i don't
know why it's so weird i can't
when it'll really really fly down i can
look down but otherwise uh it will just
be like this i i am
looking up hi danae
[Music]
you know
i would probably be really depressed
right now if it wasn't for my cats
you know leaving the maldives was hard
wasn't it ah it was so hard ah
oh it was so hard
you go to bed
oh and yes she can sleep when she wants
don't tell her what to do
she's an adult
that's our emotional support so
true so true
but yeah it was really nice seeing my
cats again we'll talk about some things
today uh catch up a little bit on things
that have happened recently
and yeah post vacation depression really
dull like i don't think i was ever
[Music]
i don't think i was ever this sad before
uh like okay i've been sad before
leaving a vacation
but never this sad
i remember i cried on my way back from
when i once uh left japan for the first
time like um after after living there
the first time not the first visit but
after living there the first time and
moving back to austria i remember crying
in the
airplane on my way back uh that
i don't think i really
did i cry the last time i
if i cried i probably told you guys when
i when i left
uh japan the most recent time last year
i can't remember maybe i did
but that's different because i lived
there but this time it was vacation and
and and yeah i never cried before i
think on my way back from
vacation
um it was
ah
it's
it's kind of i don't know it's it feels
almost stupid but i wasn't the only one
crying in the airplane not saying that
reyna was crying i don't think reyna was
crying even though she was surely sad
but i saw like we were on the on the
seaplane
and you know there's not much space in
the seaplane but but it was packed and
then i saw
like two seats in front of me a lady a
pretty lady she was also crying
i don't i'm i was definitely not the
only one and oh what's happening why am
i not moving
chihuahua
jet lagged
is this a jet lag
no i was looking out the window because
i was crying later
[\h__\h] why am i not moving
eh hello
i'm moving on my phone what's happening
let me check my technical
difficulties actually surprised it it
worked so easily in the beginning to
begin with
um
without me doing anything what no hello
hello
iphone what's the matter
um uh camera i mean
don't break don't break immersion
marshall okay i restarted
the camera
well oh and i'm so back
i'm so back yo
my
emotion
i don't even know where to start i saw
um i feel like i'm i may tell you some
things that don't only mostly apply to
me
and not really things that apply to me
and reina so like maybe i'll tell you
like about my um trip home
and
and and and some other things
uh but the things that mostly apply to
me and today them will tell you about on
the on tuesday which also leads me to i
should show you the schedule and we
should talk about it and talk about
everything that happened and stuff that
i uploaded and oh my god yes so many
things
[Music]
so today will be a chatting stream
chatting stream
which we don't have often
whatever happens in the model stays from
the moments no no no no we will share
everything pretty much pretty much
everything
yes
i also um besides the song that you hear
right now i prepared a tropical house
playlist
from audio stock oh the loading screen
btm
didn't that sound like animal crossing
for you
but what a surprise because i typed in
animal crossing into the search bar and
audio stock they have everything like
that is not from audio uh from animal
crossing but it's a you know they do
stuff that sounds like something
something if i type in zelda they
probably give me zelda ish music
yeah
i love animal crossing music and it
actually fits so much for the vacation i
think at least uh for if it's like from
the last animal crossing because island
you know and oh my god as we've
mentioned several times this is so
uh
this is so nerdy but
and i felt it especially when on the
last day
when we were walking with our butler
towards the the seaplane to leave the
island
um you know you know i really like our
butler she was really sweet and nice and
and um
she seemed like maybe maybe around our
age i'm not sure
um but she
i don't know she was cute so i i
i was like i was uh taking a picture of
the seaplane alone and in order to
explain myself why i'm taking a photo of
the seaplane alone and not with me or
something just with the seaplane um i
wanted to explain to her you know why am
i when i'm so excited about the seaplane
and so i told her that i was like do you
do
you do this game called animal crossing
and she's
like what
and i'm like oh oh oh it's a
it's a game and um it's like you know
this this seaplane looks exactly like
out of the game
but then i realized
maybe maybe island people
don't play
switch games i don't know man
i mean
i don't know i don't want to
say if imagine no i don't think so i
don't think that applies like she could
have totally known but i guess she's
just not that kind of like gaming
type of person
she was so cute the butler was so cute
yeah like um you guys are really
surprised about you know me mentioning
that we had a butler but i asked and it
seems like every
every
apartment villa whatever came with a
butler and the butlers have like several
guests to take care of and um i don't
think every resort
comes with a butler but our resort came
with one and was really really really
cool because we definitely made use of
her
many times in the first couple days
especially
when
when it was uh raining yes there called
that she introduced herself as our
24 hour butler she even said that we can
call her in the middle of the night and
like no no no i'm not gonna do that but
she was like
if you need something if you need
something even at 3 am
you can call me i'm on call
yeah baby fancy never had that before
did you tip her now we were wondering
about that you know if we need to tip or
something in general on the motives and
the internet said it's not obligatory
but um
let's say like on on on food and drinks
we mostly like try to not
not
um tip too much because we were also
like you know when we saw that we paid
six dollars for every water bottle and
at dinner
um even though dinner is included
okay drink drinks were not included but
we had a free course dinner every day
um
i understand that drinks may not be
included but hey at least water what the
[\h__\h] but okay so the water i think is
kind of like
kind of like a service
a part of the service fee i would
imagine
yeah so considering that
we were like
and considering that everything was
[\h__\h] expensive we wanted to try to
save as much more money as we could
um i don't know if you remember but we
mentioned in the previous streams that
for example
did we mention lena
buying like a plastic cover thingy
um
that you can put your phone in to take
photos on the water and all that
we mentioned that didn't we and it
costed 50 50
you know
[Music]
[\h__\h] insane so we wanted to save a
bit of money but at the end um at least
for the butler we tipped a bit more
because we didn't want to oh i i felt
like i felt like
you know she deserves it even though
it's included but she looked so happy
and when they gave her like the money
she was like oh you didn't have to she
was so sweet
and i think she deserved because we
annoyed her so much in the first two
three days when it was raining so much
which i mean yeah it might be her job
i yeah she said that
but i'm like
yeah but you did your job well and
that's what tips are for and she was
like uh like really really
um
kind kind and and
positive
and all that
yeah
tips around
generously on the first day
[Music]
i know i know
i don't know it's my first time in such
a fancy resort
uh
the thing is like you know
i felt kind of like
this is not only this resort
i'm 100 sure that the other resorts on
in the maldives on those islands do that
too
but
they definitely take advantage of the
fact that you're on an island
and if you would want to go to the main
island to do some cheap shopping it
would cost you like depending on which
island you are on
300 to 800 bucks to get back to the main
island and then again it's not worth it
so they take in insane advantage of that
um and charge so much for literally
anything as i said for those for the
stupid
plastic
cover or like the floaties
[\h__\h] floaty uh am i saying everything
in the right way because you guys made
fun of us when we say floaties but you
know we mean the swimming
ring the big one that you can float
around in in the water
they paid like 90 for that i don't
remember how much mine was probably the
same amount
they cost like what 10 bucks normally
depending on where you buy it amazon or
or outside in a normal shop
10 to what maybe 20 maximum 90. yeah
they took so much advantage and then oh
on the first day you know we checked out
also we checked the shop for the
floaties and then i saw they also had
like swimsuits and dresses like really
really typical simple like
beach wear kind of dresses vacation wear
kind of dresses you know what i mean
like you know like white
dress like a short white dress that has
like
i don't know like a really simple cute
one
nothing special no designer dress
something that you could buy
for
15 bucks
somewhere else
i
was shocked
it said like i think it was like
500 bucks on the price tag i'm like
what
are you [\h__\h] who's gonna buy that
[\h__\h] are you [\h__\h] kidding me even
rich people like i don't know why would
you buy that
that is not worth 500 bucks
[Music]
yes insane five five hundred that was
just one of the dresses and one of the
simpler ones i don't know what the other
ones constant
yeah crazy
all right i hope if someone forgot to
pack the clothes um well
oh
i i don't know why you would go shopping
in that resort obviously everyone brings
some clothes a certain amount of clothes
and a certain amount of
swimsuits that's that's something i
think you wouldn't forget if you go to a
resort on an island you wouldn't forget
that would you
i think but
yeah
but at least they have stuff in case you
forgot something important
and we used to have something but yeah
big big big taking advantage which
which i feel like is so
what's the word in german it's fresh
savage
no that's not that's not exactly the
right word but close enough
rude now
[Music]
i mean cheeky sounds too cute in english
that sounds cute why does it sound so
cute
[Music]
bold
yeah it is
bold anyway so yeah now you made me
understand why we were trying to save on
things and also like like even um you
know we had breakfast and dinner
included
uh it's called half board
um
breakfast was
really everything included like water
yes water oh my god
and and uh
food and like you know they had a big
buffet that you could pick from and then
you could order some extra things like
fresh like an omelette or pancakes or
waffles
um
yeah so we did that we made big use of
that every day and then uh
for dinner it was like a free course
a
meal that was included but not
everything on the menu like we could
choose from it was basically uh
basically a la carte for free like a
starter a main
and uh a dinner
um
started i made the dessert uh but like
some some things were not included for
example like there was like choices for
like wagyu
now that that would not be
available unless we paid extra and then
all the drinks were extra even the water
but that's all that's okay it's okay but
like if you would order something
outside of what's included then it was
like really really expensive so we we
usually try to just
order at least for the food order what's
on the menu um
yeah i like you
i don't know i didn't try it i think
dana had some
like she and one day she ordered like a
surf and turf i don't want to talk too
much about these things because we talk
about it on on the first day and
wednesday first i think but yeah they
never had like some kind of
uh
mix
uh no no no no no that was not vague
no i don't think so i mean i think it
was just a chimpkin
[Music]
but i think it was on the menu i think i
was eyeing it but it was uh it was on
the menu but it was extra charge
surf and turf is uh what was isn't that
like a mix of things
i don't think i ever had surf and turf
before so i wanted to try
oh yes with lobster oh yeah but i i also
don't i also don't like uh
i mean i don't know
i've never had lobster before
and in german we say what's the balance
christine usually steak and seafood
a nice mix huh
for people who like
both
all right anyway um
yo yo we need to get some order into
what we're going to talk about let's
talk about
the first about the schedule for this
week
[Music]
i know
i didn't i didn't
put this up on the community board yet
remind me please
so we have right now we have the m back
stream
tomorrow i didn't want to take tomorrow
off immediately but it didn't fit
anywhere else need one day off it didn't
fit so well anywhere else so
i'm taking tomorrow off i guess
but
i
i need to
i probably should be um
practicing my dance moves tomorrow
because
um birthday is getting closer and closer
and closer and i told you guys i want to
be honest about this um i'm
pre-recording it for
you know technical reasons
um so i need to know the choreos
or all of them earlier before my
birthday way before
and
yeah
i'm i'm starting to stress out now about
time pressure because um the choreos
that i got done for songs that you also
haven't seen yet like besides
are very um
they're all very intricate
i don't really have a simple choreo oh
no no no there's some like there's uh
like uh for example there's
let's just say at least one cover song
and um
um
might be might be not so intricate those
ones oh well i hope i can learn them all
in time
um
oh suyu okay well
you know i'm very open with you guys so
um let me uh tell you something
[Music]
so
we caught at this point we contacted
probably
[Music]
every single [\h__\h] studio mocap studio
in europe
and
uh
it's like like half of them
we can't use for technical reasons
and and then the rest of them is more
like
let's just assume they had
um
[Music]
open schedule
let's just assume that which
a lot of them had actually like some
that we found eventually
um but then
[Music]
you know
a while ago
my team was like oh yeah yeah this
studio
you might not
you you probably can't go with this one
because they're like
out of budget and i didn't ask any
further because we still had some other
choices but then uh yesterday i kind of
like got more replies and i was told
like all of these are out of your budget
and i'm like what do you mean out of my
budget like how much is out of my budget
and i just want you to understand this
so we can
gasp about it together and but we're
we're
we're talking six figures
for like one day
of using
and i have to cover that and well i
don't i don't even have i mean i don't
have things being used in my bank
account
and even if i if i had let's say let's
say i have exactly one million in my
bank account
using all of that up for one stream um
yeah i
i didn't expect that
and
it's looking pretty bad now so
in my mind um
[Music]
kind of kind of uh moving away from
the thought of
using a studio
seems pretty
impossible at this point
unfortunately that's very sad
um
no no we're talking six figures but i
don't know if it's one hundred thousand
or five hundred thousand but even if it
was one hundred thousand the very most
low lowest six figures then let's be
honest
uh that's still too much like
it's still too much it's still too much
i'm not gonna get that back even even
from a special birthday stream
i would go
at least double in in the minus
um
if not more
so we're not doing it no no don't even
don't even try funding it because it's
insane um
um
so but okay let's look at it at the
bright side let's look at it at the
positive side because
we want to be mrs brightside
um
but it's just so price i pay destiny is
calling me open up my eager
eyes cause i'm mrs brightside
um
i hate that i'm looking up the whole
time
um
so yeah the thing is
my suit
might not arrive until
end of june which is too giddy giddy we
need some time for like
after edit
um
i can't rely on that
so it really seems like i have to make
use of someone else's suit
and oh yeah so here comes the here comes
the positive side
this means that
my 3d um birthday it will be pretty i
will not give that up no matter [\h__\h]
what i'm not giving up on that
but
um
it will well ah maybe you guys have seen
like you know i'm
trying out 3d recently
it looks
fine except for like a lot of
clipping of the arms into the body and
all that
but but see that's another thing that we
might be able to fix in the technical
after editing um but still it it
obviously won't be like as good as
the 3d streams you see from whole live
japan members but
that means you know i i always had this
feeling that
i want things to happen in the right
traditional order right so 3dw
should be before everything else
happening with 3d so at least
if we do it this way with the suit which
is lower quality than studio quality
then it means that we can at least still
have like a a proper studio
debut stream sometime and it will make
some sense because you will not have
seen
my 3d in that quality just yet i mean
unless you saw the concert um but since
then
yeah so
so i still want that 3d birthday to be
as high quality as possible
um
[Music]
in in
in
the means of what i can do
um
yeah
positive thinking i want to see you
participate in gym japanese 3d streams
too i want to do that too yes um well i
think i think you know at least like
we've been seeing japan
starting to open up
and um i'm very very um positive about
um
the fact that we will be able to do
like studio streams in japan
um maybe by the end of this year
at the very latest um um
i am
thinking it could it will work um at
this point and i've been i've been very
negative about it for a while like this
is never gonna happen they keep on
delaying it it's never gonna happen but
at this point i see i see
i see possibilities
so
it will happen
yeah visiting um is house funds thank
you i already looked up flights
yesterday
i told ame yo i mean it's like six
figures i'm coming over
i'm coming over
um so i might also
maybe maybe
if i have some time
i might combine it to see some others
maybe
if if it's somehow
if it's possible to arrange it
i don't know it will be stressful for me
anyway this whole coming month will be
stressful for like planning
um the whole 3d concert in the last
stages and
oh [\h__\h] i actually this
there's like i just realized holy [\h__\h]
there's really not much time left and i
still we still have some problems behind
the scenes when um
in terms of merchandise since
we we are experiencing a lot of delay
currently in in many ways not only like
is is really gonna happen or not but
also merchandise
um
but uh yeah i'm trying my best to juggle
many things at once right now also
document preparation and
um the
the song that is coming out that as you
see on the schedule on friday
um
i have
haven't seen the draft of the music
video yet but it's pretty much done
apparently
i only saw like in like an image
board mood board image image board when
it's called again it looks [\h__\h]
amazing um
it's gonna be fine this should be fine
it will make it in time until friday
that is for sure um but then i'm also at
the same time i start normally like up
until now
um
[Music]
kind of because of what that's how the
music department wanted
it to happen i wasn't really able to
um
plan
a new song when the old song or the
current song didn't come out yet you
know so that's why like
i couldn't like blast them out so fast
yeah i always needed to kind of like
wait until one has been released and
then you you can start
like working on the next one and like
okay i want to work with this producer
um
yeah let's go
um but this time i was like
this new upcoming song has been taking
its sweet time uh and i i need to i want
to put out a song from like um shortly
after my birthday so
oh wait i have just realized i don't see
you guys when it's on the screen there
you go sorry sorry for covering you guys
were you guys like seeing black i'm
sorry
um
so
uh yeah i was like yo i need to get like
going on this yo also because i need to
also have it ready
um earlier than
my
you know my birthday and all that i need
to have it ready earlier way earlier
because i need to get a choreography so
that i can perform it before release
maybe
which means it needs to be done earlier
than
if i wouldn't need to get a choreography
because when someone needs to make the
choreography
well
with a song that is at the point where
it won't get changed drastically anymore
so there's like yeah that's why i
already
listened to my new new song
during my vacation on yeah i think it
was monday on the on the first night me
and lena were chilling on the balcony
and i i suddenly received the first
draft
that was already very very advanced uh
from my new new song the the summer song
um and listen i listened to it and it's
a
[\h__\h] banger like
you guys
don't understand it's so good
it is so good
it is so good and i like it yes she was
vibing to it
um it's really [\h__\h] good i have an
earworm
i love it so much
i'm so excited for it because i had a
certain
certain inspiration for it
um
and
the producer absolutely nailed it let me
drink some water
[Music]
absolutely nailed it holy [\h__\h] it's
gonna be so good and i want this one
to have a
pretty music video i
i didn't prepare one for uh i didn't
want to do like i didn't want to use my
3d model for the upcoming song yet
because i thought that
it wouldn't fit
um i thought that my default outfit
wouldn't fit the the song now my default
outfit doesn't really fit the next song
either but i want to dance to the
upcoming to the upcoming one
so
i will
when i get the
the suit
i want to record the dance
and then
uh yeah well i'll be recording it from
home
um
not in a fancy studio but oh well
we'll make it work and we'll make it
into a 3d
music video a proper one with like
choreography danced by me yeah
yeah
which is why i um already have someone
working on the choreography
of
my both of my upcoming songs yay
yay let's go very busy very busy we're
busy also recently finally got a choreo
for sparks as well
haven't
i don't even i don't even know how to
dance hard challenger yet
still need to learn how to challenge her
and then learn sparks and then learn the
upcoming song and then learn the
upcoming song and then learn a couple
more songs because
you know i have i'm i want my 3d
birthday to be like kind of a concert
because like i'm i don't have this
opportunity very often so yeah
yeah it won't be the first time and i
wanted to be special
thank you yes very busy there's also
things i can't tell you
um some some other
things that are
occupying no
making me busy very busy i can't tell
you about it um but just know
you only know things that are on the
surface mostly and i try to i try to
keep you
under the water
i try to drown you as much as i can in
my problems
but there is a lot of
problems
and things that you don't even know
about
classified data
it was that example another good example
you prefer to stay on on the surface you
don't want to be drowned
there you go yeah it's probably better
that way
um just just look at the
look at the look at whatever you see
from the surface
it's just the tip of the iceberg
iceberg
berg is
iceberg burgers german you guys know
that why is it why is it called iceberg
in that ice mountain
you guys stole a word from us
why don't you guys
why did you guys take
the word berg
where did you take it
why did you take it away from me
okay it's okay we steal words from you
guys too
but why don't you call it ice mountain
it's not like you don't have a word for
it
why'd you do it explain yourself
sounds better
it does
it does sound better
i missed talking to you guys okay see i
didn't get very far um i tensioned it
off of tuesday
that said that the day of sleeping and
maybe learning how to dance
now wednesday we'll have a vacation
recap with photos and videos maybe and
playing it on my channel
um
and then
another one on the first day on the
latest channel but with comics because
like i landed just kind of wanted to do
a recap on her channel as well
so we're doing it two days in a row but
we'll try to somehow maybe
like par separate some stories so that
you don't hear everything twice okay
um
on friday we have a new original song
released by me finally the the song that
i've been telling you about for like
months now i never worked so long in the
song it's not not because like
this summit this time it's not really
because
it didn't take so long because it's like
such an intricate song or so it's just
that when i started working on it i
didn't really like have a time pressure
like i didn't put temp pressure on
myself i was like oh let's just let's
just work on it comfortably not give
myself such a strict deadline
and yeah that was a mistake because
[Music]
now it's like
so much time has passed
um
like previously like i wanted heart
zealand jen to come out on valentine's
day when it starts to come out on my
birthday i wanted tina tony to come out
on thanksgiving so it all had like a
fixed deadline and then for this
upcoming one i was like
well i guess i don't really i don't
really need it to come out on a special
date so whatever let's just let's just
work on it normally
and yeah that just
didn't pressure us
enough
[Music]
okay
foreign
procrastination
i guess so
well i hope you like the one the song
it's um
has a very specific genre and um
it's english
and what else can i tell you yeah oh
yeah there will be a teaser
cause i wanted to tease it um
this time and
um i didn't want it to just be like
a part of the song like the chorus or
whatever no
uh you know you know those those k-pop
teasers
i mean i'm sure other people do it too
but i always see it in k-pop when they
upload like
like
you you you only really get the
atmosphere you don't really
get like spoilers too much
by
the teaser in like k-pop songs
so i want i wanted that
yeah like a 10 to 20 seconds teaser i'll
be uploading that probably like 24 hours
or 20 hours or so before
you won't really you won't hear me
singing
in the teaser
um but you will definitely with the
teaser
understand what genre it is
yes
[Music]
it's not kpop though the song is not
kpop
it's not kpop but we just i just uh gave
it as an example because of the teasers
[Music]
yeah
oh it might be kiara pulp yes
um
and then
i i do want to do a stream on friday too
like either before or after
and
i originally was thinking after
because then we have more to talk about
it about
um
so maybe like
one or two hours
stream to chit chat about the song and
celebrate it afterwards we gotta
celebrate you i can't just put it out
there and then go to sleep hello
no we're celebrating
we're celebrating
[Music]
almost a
year i guess it's getting closer like 10
months
yes
yes yes it's been a long time it's weird
like
it's been a long time but now i'm i'm
like i'm full speed again because next
song is coming soon after
uh in july um
so keep up with me kfp
keep up keep up and never be afraid
it's been a long it's really been that
long yet it's uh
it's it feels too long
i want more music out there but i guess
you know in those 10 months i put out a
lot of song covers
so it's not like i wasn't doing
anything
um
okay drink one
[Music]
i haven't been using my playlist let me
lose my playlist here tropical house
let's go
okay so
[Music]
yeah
and then on the weekend we finally have
the wind waker we can come back yeah it
was a two weeks break i'm so sorry wind
waker weekend has
had a rap rap time starting out but um
next
week next week should
[\h__\h] wait no what
next week
is next week document
oh wind a weekend keeps on getting
interrupted
ah
it keeps on getting interrupted
he's dead before it was even born so sad
so sad
maybe we'll finish it on sunday
you guys think i could finish it
what do you guys think
how far am i how many streams do i need
how much gameplay is left
yes no it's possible
no oh no
no way okay
oh okay well we'll just have to skip
another winner and go again you know i
refuse i could i could do wind waker on
a different weekday next week
but i refuse because i called it wind
waker weekend so we're always going to
play it on the weekend
we'll just have to wait another weekend
no no one's like a wednesday [\h__\h] that
no i want it on the weekend i guess that
could still be www though
ah wednesday
i'll i'll i'll take a look and see
um
if i can't think of anything to stream
next week then i guess we can do it but
um i i
think
i think next week there will be an iris
co-op
and there might be
maybe i'll do a vr chat
stream
maybe i'm not i'm not sure yet i ever
want to do a
vr chat stream or just record something
because i want to
show you
guys
like in my head i have an idea where
i show you guys how to
cheer
for my songs in preparation for doklami
yeah
not quite like really legit super
ultra
ortage
but like more like gentle
like the
sharing guide that anyone can make use
of also in the future
also in the future for maybe my 3d
birthday so you can cheer from home
for my original songs
although for dokomi yeah um i can only
do it for
four songs i guess because i will only
have four original songs at that point
um
anyway
um anyway anyway that's the schedule so
i shall
put that right here
[Music]
there might be
one more big surprise next week before
dokomi
i'm hoping
i'm hoping my plan is to surprise you
guys before you'll call me but
[Music]
yes
let me try like this what about not oh
now it's way better no no maybe no
no what about what about now
okay maybe maybe oh this is better okay
finally look down
could finally look down hallelujah
full of surprises yeah
some things that i've been working on
like the song and another thing
i'm finally gonna
yeah get out finally
finally
so let's talk about some things
that happened
during the vacation
number one
and
uh
valkyrie i'm just gonna put this up as
an image valkyrie connector
uh the collaboration was launched
[Music]
it was launched
and you guys have been playing it like
crazy thank you
actually
the original
hurdles
have already been overcome all the
milestones have been reached
so we're getting the presents
can i tell you like cause like it said a
rope robot for cat
uh as my big big dream gift that i asked
for
um
but robot robot for cat is not quite
correct
uh
explanation let me show you
so i don't know which which version i'm
getting but
i asked for
a little robot specifically from that
company
because i think they make the best
the best ones let me show you i'll show
you
i think they make the best ones but they
don't ship to austria
connect
it's not a condom
what the [\h__\h] it's not a gun
oh no it's not a rice cooker
no it like turns around
automatically it like senses
not sure if it senses it or if it's like
time a time thing
um but yeah you never have to scoop the
litter anymore and it just turns around
and and puts it like at the bottom i
think and then you just like throw it
out uh
yeah it's really really really good
it's really good i hope my cats will use
it though because like chances are that
they don't like it but they will have to
like it
they don't really have a choice
they have to i'm sick of scoping
[Music]
yes
oh my god is it that talkation a famous
character from the valkyrie connect
whole life collab available now oh my
god it sounds like the emma quote
yes it's me oh my god oh my god
so exciting
yeah i'm kind of worried about chunkers
because she is still
still after
all these
years by now
still like runs away when i turn on the
the
vacuum cleaner she still runs away and
hides in the
in the most furthest away
secretist hole that she can find which
is usually in my closet
she's a scaredy cat yeah
she's gonna run from the litter box i
wonder like if she's gonna step inside
and then
it doesn't turn when you step in though
it only starts turning after the cat
leaves it so
maybe she's gonna be fine hopefully
hopefully
yeah and if you guys uh weren't
following it so basically the valkyrie
connect collab valkyrie connect is a
it's a phone game
like an rpg like kind of like a gadget
game and there's like four whole life
members two from english whole oem two
from whole japan we're participating so
it's me ina
and uh la purasu and piccola senpai
and uh we were like implemented into the
game with like special outfits so you
can see there and the thumbnail
and uh yeah we also have like small 3d
chibi models
with those you can find
oh and there's even like another special
outfit that you guys only like um saw
after we were implemented and after you
guys played for a while you know like
kind of like an idolish outfit
did you guys see that one or did did
anyone miss it because it looks really
pretty
it's kind of like an idol outfit
that one here is apparently extra you
have to pay for it
advertising on the loan screens ah
25 dollars for skin it
i
i thought that's like a
how much did i used to pay in a certain
katja game for outfits i feel like it
wasn't like about the same i don't know
i feel like
in a game that's like you know hey you
got everything else for free you don't
have to get it but i feel like
i feel like uh
well huh
i haven't played like gotcha games for a
long time i don't know what's normal
anymore
i don't know what's normal
how much did i pay for those
i don't
remember yeah skins aren't skins
generally usually around that price
anyway
[Music]
but anyway you don't have to get it
because we already look cute in the
in the like default outfits when i say
default it's not our default but the
valkyrie connect the evolve
yeah they upgraded my
my sword in my shield it looks really
cool and yeah yeah um seeing us in
action in the game ah
i was really excited it happened
ah coincidentally and i didn't quite
realize you know because of time zones
and everything and being busy bleeba
blue didn't quite realize it was like
going online when we were streaming in
the motives
that uh during that first stream right
it was happening
i didn't realize and you guys didn't
mention it in the chat at least i didn't
see
and then it went online and huh
yeah
yeah yeah so if you guys didn't download
it yet the game is free
feel free to
download implemented not just like a
image or not just like doing a sponsored
stream on it it was like we're like in
the game
and there's voices too
some messages
that they made us record yeah
and now yeah they added another
milestone because we already smashed
all the other milestones
[Music]
exciting
please continue playing the game and
penguin you guys thought that i would
put out in penguin
but no no no
it was m dolphin
this is what i usually make i
put like i create an image like this and
then put it up above my head and i'm
like
a little bit of dolphin
um
i was am dolphin
just because
hey you thought it would be in penguin
damn penguin was their idea
um so i had to look up i was like hey
they want me to do penguin noises what
the [\h__\h] so i went on youtube i typed in
penguin noises and i studied it very
very seriously
did i sound like a penguin
it was their suggestion yeah
this stupid milk line too
it was also terror their idea the whole
script they wrote it i mean at least
they did their research but that's so
embarrassing
the milk line what the [\h__\h]
it wasn't me they wrote they wrote all
that
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
the japanese legs were so good yeah they
asked me for some zeppelin japanese
lines too i don't even know when they
show up
uh i saw some of you guys recordings on
twitter
like one of them one of them only
happens when the milestone is reached i
think
um
uh on the main screen
ah the japanese oh yeah i thought so it
sounded like something that they would
play on the main screen um
like rotating with the other ones
oh yeah right there is like a storyline
too
um i'm going to be honest it launched
during
me being in on vacation so i have not
like checked it out
oh shame on me but hey it launched when
on the first day of my vacation
yo
i have to have to catch up you will try
yeah i was vacationing
anyway what did i want to talk about oh
yeah yeah yeah uh i guess i can tell you
about
my it's already already been one hour
i'm gonna give you a story from my
vacation
um
i wrote down so much and elena was like
whoa
well you're writing down everything so
detailed that's so it i oh my god can
you share your notes with me and i'm
like yeah
yeah we're done everything properly and
[Music]
here oh my god it's it's on my phone
and i have like 14 pages
on my phone
of memo
oh it's okay so
let me tell you i don't have much
batteries on my phone but we will be
fine so did you see on on twitter that i
wrote
i was
on a plane and transit for 25 [\h__\h]
hours
did you see that
[\h__\h] nightmare but i mean
it's not like it was like like things
like accident like it's not like
something happened no incidents and
actually everything went pretty smoothly
but i lost my [\h__\h] patience
i've i lost it
a little bit longer and i would have
gotten insane
so
but
i prepared well things went mostly well
so i
i had a really really late flight
uh
the thing is like you know seaplanes
don't operate in the evening
and there was only one seaplane
leaving our island on that day it was a
saturday
saturday i think
so we left around like i think 4 p.m or
something
and then
uh
our islands did a weird thing
even though the maldives is one time
zone our island uh
had their own time zones because they're
special
so we
um
after
[Music]
after we had one more after we arrived
at uh back in the main island we had one
more extra hour to stall
so we were on the main island for i
think like eight hours or so
and we knew that beforehand that we
would have a lot of time
so
we
uh beforehand
asked
like
um
about like going to the city if that's
possible and then they offered us
a tour and we were like that's gonna be
[\h__\h] expensive isn't it
actually i don't really want to tell you
about the tour i want to tell you about
afterwards never mind well i'm not going
to tell you i'm going to tell you about
that like on wednesday maybe let me skip
that skippity doodle i didn't want to go
that back that far skipper
so anyway after the tour blue blah blue
we went back to blue blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah and then
airplane blue blue so here's that's my
journey here starts my journey without
elena
here ends my journey with lena and here
starts my journey back home okay so this
is what i'm gonna tell you
so
i
flew
through
dubai uh on my way to the mothers and
also on my way back
and it was like um
one flag was emirates
and the other one was fly dubai which i
think is kind of like their
uh cheap airline
uh which i definitely noticed on my way
to the maldives because like the
emirates flight had uh
i don't know the whole plane was bigger
and
more modern and
yeah i don't know flight to vice seemed
like more of a budget airline drinks
were extra um to pay
and yeah uh
so i had um on my way my way back even
the flights were longer by one hour so i
had like
i think
five hours
from the molips to dubai
and then i had
a whopping
13 hours
transit
[\h__\h] kill me
and then i had six uh hours back uh to
europe so
i just didn't really have a different
choice like there was
on that day
um if i would have like chosen a shorter
flight i would have had to leave the
island way way way way earlier and we
were thinking when we were choosing the
flights we were just we didn't know yet
um about how
to get to the island and how to leave
the island we thought that maybe we
could stay like all day
possibly on the beach just chill until
the flight so we should make the most
out of that day and just leave as late
as possible
um but the latest like there was even
like a i think if i remember correctly i
think there was like a really early um
plane
too early
so we would have lost the whole day
or a really late one
but that one has insane transit and i
was like
isn't that worth staying a few more
hours like
10 more hours or so in the maldives
yeah sounds like whatever i'm just i'm
gonna regret it later maybe but let's
just do it let's just do it
[Music]
so
um the first flight was already really
late like 11 p.m or something
and i was really tired because we got up
early on that day to call in into ina
stream
and
i only had like five five hours of sleep
we woke up really early and and then we
didn't go we didn't go back to sleep we
lied to you guys we didn't go back to
sleep we stayed up all day and then well
at the end of the day we were so tired
so thankfully i was able to sleep on
that shitty budget flight and yo yo yo
yo on the budget flight i had two hi
smooferella hi
i had two flights and two seats empty
next to me the whole world was empty uh
even though the rest of the plane was
pretty full
um and so i lied down and i slept for
the whole flight pretty much i just was
looking up for some food and i was like
oh yes
eating with my eyes half closed
i'm really lucky out of my four flights
so um two flights on the way there and
two flights way back
uh
three out of my four flights
i had the whole row for myself which was
[\h__\h] lucky yo my quota
my quota
of getting
the whole row to myself yo because i
booked economy
when me and then we're looking at the
flights we're like should we take retain
like something better than economy but
then we looked at the prices and we were
like nah you know what we should spend
that money for a better hotel
so
yeah i have still not made the
experience to fly with business or
anything else only economy
and and you know what i just don't think
it's worth it because those were in
theory the the flights itself are short
like what five six hours i don't think
it's worth
like paying
a thousand two thousand bucks more
i don't i just don't think it's worth it
because you're getting out of the plane
soon after
i just don't see the value
in it
for like a seat where you can recline
then you just have to be lucky like me
and have the whole room to yourself and
you can lie down
yeah
um i've i've been to japan a million
times on economy
uh and that's those are 12 hour flights
if i could
i would
want to
not go with economy
because that that at least makes a
difference 12 hours or so in economy
can be very painful especially with
chronic pain
that i have
um
and and other issues like not being able
to fall asleep easily
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
spending so much time
there on economy is [\h__\h] but if it's
just four or five hours i just don't
feel like it's worth it so
yeah we didn't we didn't uh make use of
that where was i again okay yep so i i i
had
once again the luck of having the whole
road to myself so i fell asleep
immediately i was so lucky
and i woke up and i arrived in in dubai
it felt much faster than i
thought
but
it was at like
three
am four am or something i don't quite
remember
and
uh the dubai airport it operates i guess
24 hours um some shops are closed at
that time some are open
but it was like like a ghost airport it
was really really empty
because i think at that point of time
the only passengers that are in the
airport are transit passengers
no passengers that start flying from
dubai because
yeah
i don't think if you fly if you live in
dubai and you want to go somewhere you
don't choose a flight that's that
leaves at 3am yeah i think pretty much
everyone was just a transit passenger it
was really really empty it's so
different seeing dubai airport so empty
actually
um
someone
like
when me and dana were in
um in the sauna in the on the resort at
some point there was like uh by the way
we were all wearing swimsuits in the
sauna
um but there was a there was a dude a
british dude he was talking british it's
not the one i tweeted about
but um
um like we went we went in it was kind
of awkward so like i just i just um
i just was like oh my sunburn
it's it's burning because of the heat in
the sauna even more
so the dude he's like he's like oh
it's gonna be okay look at me and i look
at him and yeah he has like his whole
face is really red
and he's he has also a tendency for
sunburns and then we kind of got in like
into a conversation
yeah
uh because i am i am just good at having
conversations in awkward places
and uh
oh yeah we talked about ooh this is your
first time in the maldives
where are you from
and then i tell him that i have a super
long layover in dubai and he says that
uh oh no i said that because he said
that he lives in dubai
and i'm like yo after super long layover
in dubai and then he recommends me to go
um to this super big the biggest
shopping mall in the whole world which
is in dubai apparently he said i'll have
i'll have everything i need there
uh it's the best place for women to go
and
i'm like oh thank you so much and for
the idea
he says that like the the taxi from the
airport can take me there for like five
dollars is really cheap and all that
but at that point i already booked
uh kind of like a
a hotel in the airport
kind of like a like a
a mix of like
i
i feel like they took inspiration from
japan from their uh internet cafes and
capsule hotels because it was a mix like
that
i was like 12 [\h__\h] hours i'm gonna
sleep i'm i can't take this i don't you
know when i travel alone
um i don't like
falling asleep on the airport randomly
because i'm scared that someone will
just take my back and run off and i just
don't know this because i'm sleeping
if i was like with someone else i think
i would be fine
but
yeah i wanted a private place
and i thought well dubai apple it must
have everything so i found like a nice
capsule hotel style hotel
and i booked that
in advance so i didn't go outside i know
12 13 hours would have been enough to go
outside and reina was like i want to go
to dubai i want to go to dubai i want to
go to dubai the whole time like every
time i mentioned dubai she was like oh i
want to go
and i was like look let's let's switch
please i don't want the 13-hour layover
into fly you're welcome to go instead
but yeah
so i arrived at like three a.m but i
couldn't um
like my my because i reserved it my
check-in time it was like i had like six
hours
but it was three a.m and my check-in
would have been at like 7 a.m dubai time
so i had to stall some time i slowly
walked through the airport i first made
my way to
like the terminal where the hotel would
be
um
because i didn't even know my own
terminal yet and my own gate
and then i looked for a cafe to eat some
breakfast slowly
everything slowly i just did everything
super slowly and then i went to buy some
aloe vera
for my skin
and then i creamed my my my arms and
everything i put aloe vera on it
and then wait and i went and then slowly
slowly one hour early went to the hotel
thingy
and i was like yeah no i'm early but i
just want to know do you have my
reservation
and then they actually let me in one
hour early
and and uh i didn't have to leave one
hour early no they added they gave me a
free extra hour because they were so
nice they were like oh
yeah we already have a room just need to
clean it fast and then i cleaned it like
in five minutes and it was ready and i
was like thank you thank you so much oh
my god i have a private
oh a private place for myself yeah
so
they had like um
like do you know those
for example kind of for example the
internet internet cafe seats in japan or
also the
or the manga cafes or or just kind of
like a business class reclining
type of
pod sleeping pond yeah and then they had
actual rooms so i booked like a room
with an actual door
and walls which was super thin like i
could hear everything
but people were mostly
mostly quiet
um
oh wait i still have that
i still have this one here oh
i saw this one here let me get rid of
that
it was mostly quiet it was uh pretty
comfy it was pain yeah
pretty spacious i mean
um
spacious i guess i don't know
it's a bed and then maybe like
one and a half square meters next to the
bed
it's really just a bed but it's it's a
like
almost a double bed
size
yeah
so
it was definitely enough space um it
didn't feel like super tiny it was
pretty spacious for what it is exactly
yeah yeah
um
and and i turned off the lights i got
cozy i still like chatted a little bit
with manager's son with genma because
there were some things uh to discuss
and then and then i was like okay
chiang mai i booked six hours in this in
this thingy i need to make use of it so
good night
and then i slept like a baby until until
someone
uh
like really aggressively
really aggressively knocked on my door
and and tried to openly like rattle the
door and look knocked out not not really
loud like what the [\h__\h] and i hear
voices outside it was like like a family
i think like five people were outside
and trying to get in my room like what
the [\h__\h] is your problem
yeah i but i didn't get up because i was
really tired i was in the middle of
sleeping yeah i think they were they
thought that it was their room or
something
but yeah every now and then i would hear
people who just like came into this room
thingy um like just checked in
and some of them came in groups so they
thought it was okay to have
conversations maybe they didn't realize
because they were the only ones talking
how much of the sound
would reach the other people it's a
[\h__\h] sleeping place can you stop
talking
um yeah but if you're the only one
talking then you obviously don't realize
how much of the noise that you make is
heard by others
but yeah i heard everything um but
mostly it was really just like some
phases where it was a bit louder and
then mostly was really quiet and chill
and i was able to sleep get some good
sleep i even woke up a little bit early
naturally or not really naturally
someone made a noise again and i woke up
oh yeah so oh my god this made me so
[\h__\h] mad
this movie is here but she's still
behind me hi baby
i look at her and she turns around and
asks for belly pets no no not now
smoothies please wait please hold the
line
um where was i oh yeah i woke up i
remember now because i heard of an alarm
a phone alarm ringing
and
i was gonna
continue sleeping but it just did not
stop
it just didn't [\h__\h] stop it went on
for i swear
at least like seven or eight minutes
oh yeah i locked my door so yeah if i
didn't lock my door they would have
entered well thankfully i locked the
door yeah
at some point i realized that it was not
their room
but yeah anyway that was a different
thing yeah yeah someone just i think it
was ever
someone um slept through their stupid
alarm for eight minutes
or
someone forgot their phone like in their
sleeping pod or whatever
but that reminded me of how much this is
a this is a pet peeve pet peeve
of mine a thing that really annoys me
is when people turn like have alarms to
wake up and then even not turn it off
even though they're like partially awake
and they know that their alarm is
raining and just ignore it and continue
sleeping and dozing off again
having it run and run and run or the
people who have an alarm then wake up
snooze
sleep for five minutes it turns on again
they snooze and they continue that for
like at least 10 [\h__\h] times and if
you're like staying with that person in
the hotel room for example like my my
old roommate was one of those people
it [\h__\h] annoys me because i'm the
type of person i put on an alarm i hear
it i i wake up immediately i turn it off
immediately and then i'm awake i get up
i i i just feel like i don't want to
waste time by having the alarm start
like 20 minutes before the actual time i
need to get up because how about i just
sleep through that time and then wake up
properly
so many of you guys say that's what you
do you [\h__\h] annoy me you're my pet
peeve
i hate that because you can maybe sleep
through that but i cannot and you can
maybe fall asleep again but i cannot
when you have your lunger off
you better wake the [\h__\h] up you better
turn it the [\h__\h] off
and then wake up
this is this is what's really difficult
when you stay with other people
somewhere or they thankfully did not
have this problem we actually most of
the time never used alarms anyway
because we naturally woke up or i
naturally woke up really early and i
would wake her up
um so we didn't have this problem in
this case but anyway so i really [\h__\h]
hate it when this happens because like
i s let's let's say in the night before
uh you wake up you say oh yeah tomorrow
we want to go there and there so our
breakfast is at 10 until 10 30 so let's
wake up at 9 00 a.m okay
and then
um you think you think that that means
you get up at 9am but now then the other
person that you whip for example my old
roommate turns their alarm to
8 30 and then has it going on at 8 35 8
40 8 45 8 50 8 55 and me i cannot
[\h__\h] sleep through that
you woke me up 30 minutes early for what
to get up 30 minutes later
what is it with you guys what is it with
you guys do it when you're alone maybe
but don't do it one way over here
because i can't [\h__\h] sleep
okay
okay this movie left i think because it
was too loud and she doesn't want to
hear me rant
no okay rmt i'm team
this is this is not completely against
rnt it's also against all of my other
friends who do this [\h__\h]
makes me so mad
[Music]
one time oh my god one time
one time
um
one time one time i i had this a similar
experience where um the person
my friend that i was in a room with a
hotel room
had
um
connected their phone to like some kind
of speakers in the hotel room
and
then would blast
like some kind of song as their alarm
at
some time in the morning and i'm telling
you so [\h__\h] loud
not normal
so [\h__\h] loud
that i am honestly confused as to why
why she would not wake up because i the
moment that went off obviously i wake up
because it's like louder than the
[\h__\h] club music
but but she's
not not waking up even after five
minutes of the song blasting through the
speakers
not waking up
and then the only thing
that would wake her up
is a call from her mom
yeah this person legit has their mom
even besides the speakers has their mom
wake them up
every morning
because they won't maybe it's some kind
of sickness maybe
i don't know is it it's not sleep
paralysis though i know i know she
doesn't have sleep
paralysis paralysis paralysis
um
but yeah
doesn't live with their mom but still
has them call them every morning
isn't that crazy
yeah surprised that that wakes them up
but not the music hi hi monkey hi
baby
yeah can people just please please wake
up the first time they set their alarm
then you then you don't lose so much
sleep
like
aren't you don't you feel
better after sleeping
eight hours instead of
seven and a half hours and then the rest
of it is just losing you could have more
sleep you could have half an hour or
depending on how long you do this [\h__\h]
one hour more slain
you do you
as long as you don't do it with me
[Music]
those are the kind of like things that
and
you have to like adjust if you're like
traveling with someone but as i said
thankfully elena didn't have that issue
with
[Music]
yeah yeah they probably think it's
normal if for them it's normal
but like that's so inconsiderate you
should play
kooky umi
please play this game cookie yummy yo
this is a a a good idea for
the next kooky yummy game maybe put this
situation into your game i wonder if in
myth anyone does it i hope not
can we what was it with kelly
did she do something like that i think i
think yeah i think kelly is
um she doesn't sleep much
but i think she does the snoozing thing
i think she does some at least one
snoozy
oh no i'm not talking about habits in
while sleeping but like when waking up
you know you just tell oh yeah right oh
[\h__\h]
if i ever stay somewhere with ina in the
same room
i will i will tell her i would offer her
a very special
once in a lifetime or limited time offer
of me being her alarm so i'll tell her
you you are not setting an alarm tonight
i will be your alarm trust me
i will shake you until you awake
i set the alarm on my phone it will be
one alarm i will immediately turn it off
after one second then i will keep my
eyes closed for another
one or two minutes and then i will get
up
and i will wake the [\h__\h] you up
that order of the sentence was wrong i
will wake you the [\h__\h] up
what a deal what a deal what's the deal
a house scream kick it again yeah that's
what the kick in the key is for to wake
people up yeah
yeah
kanta has a pillow that vibrates to wake
you up really bad that's a funny thing
to exist maybe we should give that to
ina and other people who have the same
problem is that really a thing
okay back to back to dubai
so
um
i was in that room for like seven
seven out of like 13 hours
oh and then before that obviously i
already stalled quite a few hours like
three hours so i woke up and i was like
okay okay let's leave this place
so
uh i make my way to find
lunch dinner breakfast i don't know what
to do what it is at this point like
really i don't know
um but
uh
like close by there was not that much
choice so i went to a shake shack they
had a shake shack and i never we don't
have sex in austria at least not of my
knowledge so it was the first time i
tried shake shack
shake sound they had the same sex looks
exciting sex sack
shack i heard so much of shake shack but
i didn't have a shake
didn't get a shake
i didn't feel like shake
shake it's a it's a fast food chain
shake sex
[Music]
i don't know if they have different
choices
uh in other places but they had a lot of
they had a lot of avocado burgers
i'm not really interested in avocado
burgers
no so a lot of the choices on the menu
fell through
pretty much all of it they have felt
like they had avocado and 90 of their
burgers so i just went with a really
really normal
uh
i think what's called shack burger or
shake burger or shake shack burger i
think it was jack burger
like their signature burger i guess like
the most the most basic burger
um it had a beef patty
salad
inside because you know salad is a must
in a burger i repeat salad is a must in
a burger and a tomato which i love
having a big tomato in my burgers and
some some kind of like
mayonnaise-based sauce i think
and with fries the fries are really good
they have like kind of like wavy wobbly
uh really crispy
fries the fries are really good
on the fast food restaurant
it was pretty good although i must say i
don't know if this is normal if they do
that in every shake shack but um
the
so
we are in the kfp here right so we must
we must uh talk seriously when it comes
to the competitors burgers
uh now let me let you guys let me know
if you guys have been in a shake shack
before how was how are the buns because
the buns were like
almost soggy like it didn't feel they
didn't feel wet but they had like they
were so soft that it was like
weird like
the buns were
weird they they are like that
they were like way too soft like brown
brie softer than brioche
it was like so
mushy i don't know
what's weird like i don't know
hey yeah they don't toast them they
should
they should i like a brioche bun but
it was it was too
weirdly soft
the rest was fine
they had they gave a big portion of
fries man and yo they have like this i
appreciate because i don't know maybe
it's just this shake shack but um
in other fast food restaurants the big
ones you have to order like sauces for
the fries separately right and you just
get like a [\h__\h] tiny ass package like
i i ordered mayonnaise for my fries
usually i think it's like one package
but that's enough for like maybe five
fries five out of what how many is it
usually 30 fries
how many packets packages do i need to
order for all of my fries
but in the shank shack
you can have endless mayonnaise they
have like a counter where there's mayo
and ketchup and everything and you put
it in like a little cup and you can take
as much as you want
now that's fascinating i love that so i
took a [\h__\h] ton of mayonnaise
mayo
yeah yeah
i like me i like fries with like
um
mayo the most currently i used to like
um i used to like it more with ketchup
and then i had a time where i wanted to
eat it with um like nothing for a long
time just the fries
but recently i've been into mayo don't
judge me
a few
i can eat my fries the way i want to
love mayonnaise mayonnaise
don't you dare judge me don't you dare
judge me so is it normal and shake shack
that you have a counter with free sauces
because i'm starting to
forget
have you noticed my throat has been kind
of rough today
i think it's partially because before
the stream i had this thing again where
uh i i choked on on a drink
uh i was drinking iced tea and it went
into my my breathing
tube
and i [\h__\h] died and then after that
my throat hasn't recovered yet
it stays like that for a while
you're supposed to normal at any
american really
freak
free condiments what does that mean at
the american producers
oh hey you guys get sauces for free most
of the time
oh that's nice we have to pay extra
in europe usually
sauces are not free no no
no it's nice
you never prefer sausages instead what
even though even if you want many
or do you only get one
nice
that's brutal
the smart thing to do is that you take
your fast food with you home and you
keep like a tube of whatever sauce you
like at home in the fridge and then just
use that
huh
uh what
my my my my youtube thingy broke and i
only see your chat on obs and now it's
going too fast
oh god
you can't read that
i can't read your answers i need to i
wasn't it's my fault because i wasn't
using
uh
a hyper chat it's my fault
okay
youtube broke for me
let me go fetch youtube real quick
it's not
loading it's not loading youtube is not
loading this youtube load for you guys
if you refresh it
and i use hyper chat often but sometimes
i'm too lazy to
open it
[Music]
um
well i'll read on obs for a while
i can't be helped let's go back to ah it
loaded
[Music]
and then
chateau
oh my god i just saw the super chats
thank you guys
holy [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
that's me
it's me okay okay hyper chat have a chat
i'm so sorry for not using you here i go
hyper chat
welcome back hyper chat i'm back from my
vacation hello hyper chat
don't you dare don't you yeah
don't sit there pull out the cables
there okay oh she she's
she was like on on the
on the cat's tree that i have next to my
table and now she's walking over my
table in front of my monitor and i think
she wants to lie down
on my stuff
you wanna yes she's lying down
she's like i sit if i fit i sit okay
okay
yeah okay
yep she wants the she wants the belly
pets
and the chonky wonky i love you too i
already gave you a million cuddles today
this space is now cleaned by cat yeah
i froze yeah cause i was looking at
chunky wonky
i recently like calling her chunky one
because she got a new new nickname from
me she missed me she did i was gone for
a week so long
honestly like um during the vacation
like whenever i'm gone i surprisingly
can
stop thinking of my about my cats
pretty easily but then rayna kept on
talking about her cats and kept on
showing me pictures of her cats which i
don't mind but it reminds me of my cats
so
this was the thing like she
she was actually the one who kept on
showing me her cats and talking about
uh her cat
her kitty cat
wasn't me usually it's always me
[Laughter]
usually it will be me but then on the
last day on the last day i showed her
everything
everything and she was really excited by
it and she was really really really like
um
i have to say
she was fangirling over my kitty cats
make me very happy
it's always always nice to hear
someone appreciating my kitty cats
what
everything
what what did i say
sorry my brain was partially
offline
what did i say
wait everything what do you mean
everything
what what did i say
you guys are so stupid
i didn't say anything wrong
i didn't say anything wrong you guys are
so stupid
um
you guys are so such sassy buckles
okay back to my store so i was in dubai
i was done sleeping i got to shake shack
um
and i had a little bit of a sad moment
because i got like a sad message so i
was crying in the shake shack
was trying
trying to hold it back but i started
crying in the shake shack yeah
emotional kiwawa
i tried to hold it back but it kind of
ruined my moods
[Music]
that wasn't so nice but then
uh
yeah then i don't know i didn't do much
more after that i just made my way to my
gate and i boarded my second flight
and
holy [\h__\h] i was once again lucky
because the plane was pretty full but
still i once again had a whole row to
myself and actually booked the same seat
as i did on my way there
so i think i now know
which
which um
like one of the seats that will give you
a high chance of being alone
if i i will recommend this one to you
because it worked twice
people around me were full in rows just
me
[Music]
i was alone on a window seat with two
seats next to me empty
it is um
somewhere
like if it's a big plane somewhere in
the middle
around somewhere around the middle but
more like in the back of the middle
um you know how it has like a plane let
me show you
uh what's a big what's a big plane uh
which one did i use i don't know
what's it what's a big plane i want to
show you the seat
uh
airbus 777
is it nervous boring
uh
ah okay booing
oh that's
that looks kind of small
i don't know but maybe it works
[Music]
i feel like mine was bigger than that
does that even have two
two floors because mine had two floors
my plane had two floors uh the higher
floor was uh
like business and first class
uh seven for seven is two floors okay
seats
seating chart
here i'm gonna show you life hacks
travel hacks
you you should be so so grateful
uh
is this one which one is it which is
there's so many when i look it up is it
this british airways oh yeah okay let's
go with british airways
but this one looks different from the
one i was into oh well
uh no no no actually not
i don't want this one maybe this one
this one should
this one also looks different how about
emmy rates
emmy rates ceiling chart maybe i'll just
get one i don't know which plane it was
but maybe this one
oh
yeah
[Music]
that could be
maybe
it not quite
but it will do
ah just the same as a jpeg
why
um
i had a big boy
uh even though it was such a short
flight they had a really big one i
usually only have these big plans if i
when i um fly to japan
seating
okay oh yeah oh yeah
i think i think this could be oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] don't come oh did i put it on twice
oh there it is okay so
look at this main deck is economy upper
deck oh it's the place that none of us
will ever go to
um
so i have something where i live with
that i can point on on something
looking for something that's kind of
pointy oh well i'll use my hands
[Music]
where's my face hello hello i'm not why
am i not moving
[Music]
hello
if you wanna exit broken
coming back soon
i'm restarted the app again
look happy
but you know what i don't need to be
moving for this okay so um
economy we're talking about economy
which seat do you guys think
you will have uh the seats to yourself
well let me tell you first of all i was
on the left side uh twice
and then you want a window seat right
because window seat is best so you
choose one of the window seats on the
left side do it do it do it and then
um which could it be what could it be if
you choose somewhere in the middle of
like one of these sections i'm telling
you
you will not be alone you have to choose
this one
or no wait no not not this one that one
behind the toilet no no could probably
end up with you being uh alone as well
but you were choosing this one which is
79.
[Music]
i guess it could work on the other side
too 79 this is the one 79
i'm telling you this is a travel life
hack 79 will give you all the free seats
to yourself unless it is a fully booked
flight mine was fairly booked not fully
but still it's a miracle it's a miracle
79 yes
you know 79.
now everyone will book this no no no no
don't worry don't worry
i don't know what it is i think it's a
mix of um
you know
i can't apparently people don't like
being against
this wall there is a wall there but you
can recline normally i don't know why
people don't like it though
why is my
why am i not moving though
restarting again
the usual seat it's a lucky seat
oh there we go okay
i think probably like the seats in front
of the toilet are also unpopular because
of the sounds you will continuously hear
the toilet sounds like flushing it's
pretty loud
um
yeah and
you should go for this one in the back
this one
i also often uh made the experience that
on the very last row as well here very
last one yeah
also high chance of being alone
engine sounds oh you think here you'll
hear you'll hear them everywhere it
doesn't matter
i think also a lot of people prefer to
be in the front of the plane because
you've some people think that far
that you can
probably leave the plane earlier than
others but why are you such an impatient
piece of [\h__\h]
why
impatient children
it will not take it will not save you
that much time because you'll end up
waiting at the baggage claims section
anyway understand
understand
you think you got off the plane
three minutes earlier than the ones in
the back okay but you're gonna be
waiting at the baggage claim anyway
sucker
unless you unless you didn't check in
the bag but if your chances are that if
you fly in such a big airplane
is that you're flying long distance and
that you have a checked in baggage
so anyway that's that i want to go to
the upper deck one day but [\h__\h] those
prices
it's just like i i
i will pay
the price that is necessary for things
where i feel like it's worth it but i
feel like
business first class etc is just
insanely overpriced
and i will not tolerate that
um
i will not spend stupid amounts of money
on things that are not not exactly worth
it if if if it's like a thing that i can
have permanently like
maybe cloves okay but not even cloves
i'm not gonna dress myself all on gucci
uh speaking of gucci i watched uh i
finished watching the house of gucci um
on my flat back because i started
watching it when i was uh on my way to
the maldives
but it's a pretty long movie
it's a pretty long movie so i couldn't
watch the whole thing and i finished
watching it and holy [\h__\h]
it's it's pretty interesting i'm not
gonna lie i didn't like the acting from
lady gaga um there were some parts where
she did well and then there were some
parts
um where she did worse like maybe you
guys saw the movie but
she plays like the the wife of mauricio
gucci so she's not a gucci person she's
just
like an italian girl
and with an italian accent her italian
accent is fine
um but
like they're like in the beginning her
character is supposed to be
like more natural innocent sweet and
then later on her character will get
more and more
controlling
and salt not salty but like what's the
right word
[Music]
what's the right word not mean but like
bitter yeah more
perhaps bitter
sassy resentful arrogant yeah stuck up
yes all of those words yes yes all of
them
so i feel like
uh the character goes through like quite
the um
personality development
and she did not
do a good job at all of them in my
opinion
no i feel like they only chose her to
boost the sales of the movie
yeah
but
huh i i did i did really enjoy hearing
about the whole story because it's
insane i never knew about this did you
guys know about the history of gucci
it's insane
can i tell you
it's like a history tangent but not
medieval this time can i tell you i'm
sure a lot of you guys don't know
so okay like in i think it was 1917
[Applause]
in in the 70s or 80s
um gucci
uh because she's a family
brand okay
if you don't want to listen to this and
i guess don't listen
but this is this is i'm not spoiling the
movie i'm just telling you about real
reality
i'm not going to tell you about every
detail anyway
yeah so
uh
70s 80s italy um and it's it's a family
and it's kind of being led by
the men of the family because there are
at this point no
kind of no women in the family
um
yeah and and it's like there's like um
two main people
uh who lead the company 50 50 uh their
brothers i think yeah and one of the
brothers no they both have a son um and
yeah anyway so it's all gucci guys okay
and at that time they're already pretty
popular
here and there as a fashion high fashion
brand but not so much like all over the
world like they are now but they were
already pretty big
so
anyway this this uh one of one of the
sons uh marries a random girl that the
father doesn't approve of so the father
disowns his son his only son
at the point of time where he's already
like pretty old and
and yeah probably gonna
die sooner or later at some point though
he kind of forgives
and and forgets and then accepts the
wife and um
yeah
she she's a gold digger basically uh
and the father knew it from the
beginning
and she
kind of she made her way into the family
and she wants to have the gucci name she
wants the money and all that and then
she tries to
um really do her part in gucci
and and manipulate and all that [\h__\h]
and
at some point the father dies
so
uh mauricio the guy the son he has to
take over partially
and they
they they kiss the ass of the other
brother the brother of the father
so he ends up really liking
the non-gucci girl the wife
and
yeah very fond of her so that that other
brother he gives her a lot of support
and yeah they work together for a while
then they [\h__\h] over
um that other son from the brother
guy okay
and eventually you know they sound like
they all [\h__\h] each other over
um so eventually
the maurizio the the sun
[\h__\h] over the other sun
uh
no no first first with the help of the
other son the two sons [\h__\h] over
the
the one brother
by
um reporting him to the police that he
had like 6 million u.s dollars evaded in
taxes
in america because they were living in
america by the way not not even in italy
six million dollars invaded tax paying
money yeah so they got him into prison
his own family got him into prison first
of all so then
um all of uh all of the
shares of the gucci company
went to
the sons the two sons i guess
and um
but then they so then the couple was
like okay let's [\h__\h] over our brother
they
did something really really really
[\h__\h] mean i'm not gonna tell you too
many details but they [\h__\h] him over too
so
uh
then he's just out of the picture as
well and um kind of gets poor he
eventually dies
from poverty yeah
they let him die from poverty
one of the gucci brothers
so but that happens way later and and
and and and okay so now now we have all
of the shares belong to this
the
son and
not really his wife but she thinks she
thinks she's a gucci so she thinks it
belongs to her too
and she tries to control the company
eventually
uh maurizio gets sick of her and
disappears
and leaves her for someone else they
have two daughters by the way in the
movie they only have one daughter
um to reduce child labor
and then
yeah she gets really mad she by the way
uh frequents a
future teller psychic kind of girl
and um
she gets really mad she gets like
absolutely [\h__\h] crazy that's crazy
and
and goes through her psyche and she's
like my
my my husband left me what the [\h__\h] do i
do i want to kill him
how do i kill him and this is this
really happened yo so she's
her psychic tells her now i can help you
her psychic goal goes off to
find her um like killers
to assassinate
the last okay at this point it's not the
last why did i stop moving again
oh the connection is really bad today
whatever let me finish the story
[Music]
[Applause]
at this point so we have um
one of the gucci sons somewhere about to
die in poverty the other one the the
father of that son in prison
will later be released and then die as
well of age
and then only the maurizio gucci who has
the full shares okay
so
the wife
finds killers
pays them a [\h__\h] out of money
and then writes so stupid writes in a
[\h__\h] diary on the day her husband
dies
paradise the word paradise yeah
so she's happy later on two years later
she uh gets found out also partially
because of the the the diary
um
she's just insane at this point she
uh i guess like how many years was it
30 years or something in prison she's
out by now because of good behavior you
can find an interview where she says she
was real really happy when she heard
that it worked and he died
um
yeah now at this point there is no
living gucci anymore
gucci is being
organized
managed by non-gucci's
can you [\h__\h] believe
this story
the gucci dude
married a gold digger who ended up
assassinating him uh by the way the
psychic also got like about 30 years and
the the two people who were involved in
the killing were also uh
um
arrested for like put into prison for
like 30 years the the one who did the
actual killing didn't got a few more
years
than the others but yeah
and now she's kind of being like also
because of this movie i guess we have
another situation like uh
the the what was that movie that i
watched the anna and uh delby was it
story
uh
where i was like yo this kind of
makes them
popular though doesn't it it kind of
glorifies them
and
puts them in a good light and promotes
them even more
i reinvented anna yeah so i don't like
that i don't like that but it's
interesting to hear about uh the whole
story because i didn't know that it's
[\h__\h] up it's really [\h__\h] up and you
imagine
[Music]
a brand with
such a
really dark history
is still
one of the most popular high fashion
brands out there one of the most
well-known people i don't know they just
continued buying that stuff because okay
i guess i guess
an
assassination shouldn't stop you
i guess it doesn't have anything to do
with the fashion but i think it's wild
story of versace as well i'll have to
look that up
but
yeah people didn't care
that's it's a spicy it's very spicy
story
why did it stop moving man let me
refresh again
it doesn't matter to them which i guess
i understand like of course the the
clothes don't have anything to do with
the
family problems but i'm just surprised
that this kind of
it's not you can't can you even call
this a scandal anymore it's like way
past being a scandal how did that not
affect
actually yeah the scandal didn't affect
uh gucci anything but uh the guy the
maurizio gucci the guy who got
assassinated he was kind of doing a
pretty bad job at running gucci almost
ran it into the ground
[Music]
so he wasn't really doing well
it was it took off more after he was
dead and and the company
was taken over by random people um
yeah interesting though eh ysl story oh
is that eve slow oh oh my god
do they all have such a
yummy duck history
yummy
eh hugo boss what the [\h__\h]
okay
okay i will i will look them all up
miss you in a nonsense babbling excuse
me nonsense
no
none
nonsense
excuse me
what
anyway
uh oh yeah so i got three seats to
myself
and
and then i finished watching gucci
and then i tried sleeping some more
uh
in the end you know i actually got quite
a lot of a lot as much as you can get in
like five and six hour flights oh
yeah i got i was able to sleep pretty
well thank for thanks to getting the
whole road to myself
but i was still as you know
cause i immediately fell asleep after
the 25 hours of travel i finally arrived
i made my way home i greeted my cats i
chilled on the bed a little bit
with my cats
and then pretty soon before midnight
again
i fell asleep
i fell into a deep deep deep deep
slumber because i would have thought
even after 25 hours of traveling where i
did get some
okayish sleep but just you know
in in such
sections it's just not
i need to sleep like continuously like
like eight hours without a break but i i
guess it maybe i don't know the
exhaustion of traveling i don't know
what exhausted me that much but
i guess traveling exhausts you because i
was really really tired after that
and yeah
woke up at like 5 00 a.m
and realized oh yummy
well worth it because
it was comfy sleeping in my bed again
travels can do that traveling do be
exhausting
traveling is stupid tiring
oh my god
some one more thing
no never mind forget it forget about it
in detail that's not necessary how are
your summits um
oh my sunburns are still there
um my feet's dull my feet are not so
bloated any bloated
no that was not the word
what's the word
what did i say on twitter
swollen oh yeah they're not so swollen
anymore
um like still a little bit but then it
mostly went back i think
during the last night
um
are you peeling already are you peeling
already no i'm not i'm not peeling yet
it will take a while
uh but i'm trying to
put like you know
hydrating creams and aloe vera on it
and yeah don't go outside into the sun
anymore for the next
two months just kidding
and i'm leaving my my
my place at the latest for dokomi
already but yeah
i'll take care of my skin it's just it's
just um
yeah
during the vacation i did put on
sunscreen but i kind of forgot to i
didn't take it so seriously to reapply
after
going into the water because on that day
where i got that insane sunburn um
first of all we weren't even outside for
that long but second of all
it was very cloudy
um
we were not really
under the direct
shining bright ass sun
it was
always kind of cloudy um
so i thought that it shouldn't be that
bad but
it did yeah i guess so
[Music]
they still go for clouds yeah
it really got me on
some of my body parts more than others
and then my feet the fingers of my feet
you forget about them don't you because
i forget i forgot about them i think
people often tend to forget about their
feet
like the top part of my of my feet not
the legs just the feet
those i completely forgot to put
sunscreen on
so
they turned out the worst
really painful
then they ended up being swollen because
because of the sunburn
yeah
it was really bad really really bad
so
like on the on the following days when
we went snorkeling
the flippers for the feet were really
really hard to put on and off because
everything that touched
my feet already hurt but then the the
rubber material of the flippers
would hurt even more because it kind of
like it's pretty tight and then and then
my feet were swollen so it was even
tighter
especially after getting out of the
water trying to take them off without
rubbing it too much so my skin really
really really really hurts ah
especially on the last day i feel like
that my feet were swollen to the maximum
shockers is here the whole time by the
way and then i'm rubbing her belly the
whole time
it was really faithful yeah
by the way me and elena are like super
super super super like um excited about
going more snorkeling we're like really
into it no it was our first time
but both of us
and we're really really really
like motivated to go
to different places
doing more snorkeling and buying our own
snorkeling equipment and all that um
snorkeling in bali i don't know is there
snorkeling spots in bali
one thing we noticed is that
you know the place where we were
it had like
one good really good big snorkeling spot
but
that's it like at least close by they
only told us about one snorkeling spot
and we went there like four times
so
or three times i don't know but at least
the last day
i kind of left the water pretty early
because of
one reason was i started
um swallowing too much sea water again
and i started feeling sick again and
then the other reason was i just didn't
really see many fish on that day and the
ones that i saw were just the same ones
that i saw on the previous day
um
so yeah i want to go to different places
and see different fish and all that
after going there several times
it's just always the same kind of i
don't know did we do something wrong i
don't know we can't go deeper with the
snorkeling stuff we would have needed
some diving equipment
anyway yes that was why i think why i
threw up on that one day
um i didn't even
i didn't even honestly on that day i
didn't even swallow that much seawater
but i think it just hit my tummy
in the wrong way in that moment
we were like we were um
we were snorkeling
uh
from the reef back to our over water
villa i had this idea that how about we
swim all the way back instead of walking
back it's not that far away
and and it's fun
let's do it so we struggle with smoking
smoke but it was really exhausting
and then when we were like really close
we stopped like one
one villa in front of ours we stopped
for a moment and and i was like
i noticed i was feeling really sick
and and elena was just like standing
next to me and i don't know moving her
goggles or whatever and i'm like okay
reyna you should
you should i think i'm gonna throw up
you should you should quickly quickly
swim away
and she immediately takes it she takes
took it seriously thank god she
immediately swims away
and then when
thankfully she was already out of the
danger zone
[Music]
and i like really throw up
i throw up my whole breakfast
and i kept on like swooshing it away
like so that goes away um
i wasn't like covered in it don't worry
thankfully the water like spreaded
pretty quickly pretty nicely
yeah
and thankfully no one else was in the
water anywhere nearby no one saw it
besides maybe um partially uh dana but i
think she was busy with swimming away so
she didn't even see the act of me
throwing up
yeah
it was not not a nice experience
throwing up my breakfast i haven't
thrown up in a long long long long long
long time
yummy treat for the fish i was i was
wondering while i was throwing up if i'm
doing them a favor or not
apparently i did
apparently i did do them a favor
so um
[Music]
it wasn't for me i was not i was not
very happy about it but maybe the fish
were happy about it
yeah
what did you eat i just had a normal
breakfast it wasn't because of the
breakfast i was thinking too why did
that happen i think it was the sea water
it wasn't too much to see whatever like
sometimes
it would enter my mouth through the
snorkel thingy the tube
and then
like in some moments i would i would
just kind of panic
and and swallow it by accident
yeah and then maybe maybe in combination
with
the sunburn and the exhaustion from
swimming so far
uh i think it was maybe a combination i
don't know
[Music]
but yeah i've read that um the sea water
can be pretty bad for the stomach and it
makes you throw up if you
yeah
drink too much of it it wasn't that much
but i just think it hit me wrong
thank you guys it's okay i recovered
pretty fast i swam back to the villa
um i took off those [\h__\h]
flippers
and i drank some water i brushed my
teeth again
and
then after a while we had a lunch
where i had because we had normally on
all of the days we didn't have lunch
except for this day
um and i told you lunch wasn't included
but uh we needed to have lunch because i
threw up my whole breakfast
so
we went to have lunch and i paid 35
dollars for a lasagna
everything on the menu was that much
like then there was pasta that we went
to like an italian place it was like
pasta that was also 35
there that was that yeah it was between
30 and 40 dollars all the normal dishes
um
even the starters were like
25 to 30 dollars
was it good it was okay i have to say my
lasagna is better
i totally need my lasagna but also i
gave her a bite because she never had
lasagna before
i'm a girl what you have to try
[Music]
only the pasta only the pasta though
just just okay
yeah yeah
yeah
it was okay
missing out yes
olive garden i've never been to an olive
garden
[Music]
before um pouring all the ingredients
made that some expensive no it's not
because of importing it's because they
know that you have no other place to go
yeah so you have to you have to
eat what's there and buy what's there
[Music]
olive garden is cool other garden is
gross you guys
have different opinions huh
olive garden will be disappointing to
you yeah i can imagine uh
it's probably not very
very accurate italian food
hmm
[Music]
give her a bite of the
noodles
and the tomato
yeah
that was okay also one thing elena never
eats her salad
like the dishes that we would order
would always come with like some salad
and
[Music]
yeah she wouldn't she wouldn't eat it
sometimes i would eat her salad like
even if it's just a small one but she's
just she doesn't seem to like salad
apparently
but i love salad
mmm
yum yum yum salad is she a picky she's
not a picky eater at all um but
she's the type of person who orders
big dishes and then doesn't finish them
maybe even worse than me like i can at
least like kind of judge
um like how much am i gonna be able to
eat
i will give her
um
the
what was what's the word uh i will i
will give her that that the the food
they they served big portions at least
for us
so we both
left over some food um
quite often
yeah
you mean appetizer what
no what
no we i've gotta say that we
we both unfortunately
uh
yeah this is because you know there's
like three courses and they all were
except for the desert they're all pretty
big already the starter was usually
pretty big and then
yeah the main was also pretty big
yeah
but the portions are pretty big maybe
not for
i don't know american standards but for
our standards it was pretty big we both
have small tummies and what what can you
do can't help it
they just um
yeah if it was a buffet then i would
just take what i eat
please tell me you didn't waste weight
i'm sorry but like we don't have control
over how much they serve us
oh at least i mean on the last day for
example i
i skipped the the starter because i was
like i know i know i'm not gonna be able
to finish it so you know what even
though it's already paid for i'm just
eating
maine and dessert
put leftovers in a doggy bag ah yeah on
one day and one day i took the leftovers
back to the room
what the [\h__\h] is a dog why are you guys
calling it the doggy bag like you're
picking up the poop from your dog when
you're walking in them in the park
huh
you guys call it a doggy bag when you
bring food
back home
ew
it's an american thing
that's such a weird way to call it
you bring food home for your dog
even if you don't have a dog
yeah this is just your take out whatever
it's called can i can i take this home
in a
you know i don't know plastic dish
whatever
we don't call it that well some of you
apparently do call it that
what a weird thing to say don't be back
anyway guys i'm already tired
you guys you guys know me so well so you
must have been surprised too but i was
the one always going to bed early and
then waking up early and dragging dana
with me
i don't know but during the vacation i
was always able to fall asleep like five
minutes after we turned on some netflix
episode
and then i would wake up on my own
pretty early always
no i'm also tired but surprisingly i
don't know you guys said jet like jet
lag but the maldives are
not that many hours ahead of my time
zone oh how many hours was it like as i
said they added one more hour
um
what was it um
right now it's ah
so it's three hours
three hours but then they added one more
hour so four hours
it's not that bad
it's kind of like uh
yeah
i understand jet lag if you go to a
country that's like almost like
night and day difference
but
why add one more hour they were like on
the first day they were like okay so
here
we have a one hour difference from the
main island because we like to have you
start your day early and make the most
out of the daylight which i think makes
sense because especially on the first
couple of days it got dark
so early because of the bad weather the
storm and the the clouds
the last couple days
it didn't get dark that early but in the
first ones it made really sense and
uh yeah i think it was a good idea i
guess hmm
it's really pronounced molded yes it is
i'm pretty sure
it's not small dive so i can tell you
that
here
maldives
well that's an american he just doesn't
know how to say it
maldives
male dives
see they say it differently she says
completely wrong mal died this is just
random people saying no this is wrong
it's not maldives who the [\h__\h] are you
they don't know how to say it
moldives so everything's different
maldives
maldives i don't know how to say it
maldives well okay i will give you i
will give this one
maldives maybe the point maldives
maldives maldives yeah yeah maybe
maldives but not my male dives or
moldova snoke
how does the local call them um
i didn't hear them saying the name of
their island that often but
it was not maldives
um
anyway since i just said i'm tired
i'm tired i need to read super chats
though
ah [\h__\h]
because the next few streams are collabs
i need to read super chess gamble
[Music]
but um
i think you know cause it
it was my vacation
i'm not gonna read the vacation super
chats out loud okay
i'm just gonna read the ones from today
that's the one from today
the other ones i'll take a look at um
after my stream
chottomata
[Music]
yes okay
well i'm really sad to not be in the
maldives ball dives anymore but
it's also nice to be with you guys again
on chit chat things are back to normal
that's nice
[Music]
yeah it was it was like [\h__\h] paradise
not the paradise of that uh
uh
patriciani
um
found
when she killed let her husband be
assassinated that's a different paradise
um
[Music]
i but yeah it was definitely [\h__\h]
paradise it's like
um
i don't it's hard to after this location
it's hard to ever go
to a vacation
beach vacation anymore that's not
like an island
because i know the difference now
not like um unfortunately okay islands
they will be more expensive but
the good thing about them is that it's
like more intimate more private there's
not a million people there there's no
randos
and and um
it's more like like a family
and and it's like smaller so they treat
you more special
and the beaches first and foremost the
beaches and the water
are just a million times more beautiful
because it's so much cleaner
because there's like no traffic and no
no like um what's the what's what's the
word
um civilized
civilization or so
yeah
so i don't know i've seen a lot of
beaches elsewhere some decently pretty
ones
but the bigger the island
the more cars the more pollution and the
more all of that
the
less pretty the beach will be
i mean actually that we saw some trash
floating in from outside the ocean to
the island but i also think that uh
because it wasn't that much i think like
ev every i'm pretty sure every day
there's like staff going around the
beach side and picking up the trash
because by the next morning
is it was usually gone
and then yeah we saw like some stuff
floating in that like for example like a
soap dispenser which was covered in
some weird living ocean
stuff that i we didn't know what the
[\h__\h] that was it was there was a crab on
it and then a lot of weird
sticky thingies i don't know
i don't know what it was but they were
breathing and blah
blah blah disgusting
but it looked like it was on the ocean
for i don't know how long man a year two
years three years five years i don't
know how long it takes to look like that
um
barnacles oh god do i want to look that
up
or in
barnacles
yes
[Music]
that's what it was
it looked
and did they all look like that
uh it looked um
oh it looked like that
but like we saw it floating in and then
we saw it on the beach and when it was
on the beach the crab left and and the
the barnacles were like coming out of
their weird shells
and trying to breathe and look [\h__\h]
disgusting
barnacles are kind of cute those did not
look cute excuse me
you
you're looking at pictures some of them
look okay but others look disgusting and
that's how it looks like
ew
you didn't throw no no no no no hell no
i'm not we're not touching that but no
of course we wouldn't throw it back
um
ocean acne
ew
what is that that's your
feet oh they're so disgusting
barnacles a type of arthropod
constituting the subclass cyripedia in
the sub
fulham christosia and this has related
to crabs and lobsters oh wow really
barnacles are exclusively marrying and
tend to live in shallow entire waters
typically erosive says do they are they
able to like move around because they
were like sticking to the bottle but
they like how if they're related to
crabs
and lobsters are they able to move
around
it didn't look like they would like be
able to move around
very slowly they're stuck
they can move a bit
they attach stuff permanently yeah
that's what it looks like ew
why don't they attach to plastic though
can humans get barnacles eel what kind
of question is that commonly called
skin barnacles yeah this is one of the
most common
non-cancerous skin growths in older
adults
you should start to appear as slightly
you you you you you you you you
you you you
you you you okay stop
i don't want to rain anymore
no
hey google no
my throat really hurts man from that one
time of
choking
[Music]
make it stop okay maybe i need to
smoothen out my throat with some
chocolate i have some yummy chocolate
here
let me
eat it um
[Music]
she heard the noises
of me opening something she's like mommy
what's that
i mean what's dad
no this one is white chocolate
haven't had white chocolate in a while
oh it's so soft what the [\h__\h] you
okay
i'll bite in it like a sandwich out
i'm so soft it's lint chocolate
[Music]
oh my god
she's still
your cheeky junkie one game
she's still like um
little piece of
um fruit candy wrapper
that was empty
when you suddenly see like a paw
only the paw reaching in to steal
something
nice movie hi chunky
um
oh it's so good okay i'm um i feel
motivated now
super chat
time
and violet in the garden danger what is
your profile picture
that's not me what the [\h__\h]
take it for yourself thank
i didn't miss you at all
i was only pretending
i mean you know what i'll actually i
know this is you trying to add sunday
but you guys didn't even have a reason
to miss me i uploaded every [\h__\h] day
and we streamed three times so
in reality i was watching the tides of
my real actual oshie riser which i just
started to play unai zoo i wasn't
waiting in front of the kfb building or
thinking about you crying oh
but no you guys are so spoiled
but it's also because
i vacationed with someone who
streams as much as i do and is fine with
streaming on a vacation too if i have
occasions with someone who wanted like
i don't know more chill time
more off time
then i would have adjusted to it i guess
and and streamed less but
me and reina is like we're we're
similar in
a couple of ways like how we feel about
streaming
yeah
and
and don't worry guys it's not like i
feel
not rested or anything
i do actually even though
we were like oh god we were on the phone
way too much i'll tell you that like
checking social media and all that we
couldn't really
turn
our like work brains off maybe
but we were in [\h__\h] paradise okay
uh so that was good enough like even
like oh
it was doing its magic even though we
were still in work brain don't worry
about it
we had fun
i mean
it's even even when
we used our phones a lot and all that
it's still
fun because
we could connect like there was someone
that i could talk to
about the things that were going on
behind the scenes
and like talk about streaming things
uh
yeah it's like we were connecting for
work as well
and also talking about things that
annoyed us for example which is kind of
a stress relief too
and yeah
and and and we enjoyed it like also the
little streaming we told ourselves you
know not every day
because we want to enjoy the
we want to force ourselves to just you
know give ourselves some free time of
course and and also
we only did one hour when we were
streaming um to not waste too much time
but still even when we were streaming it
was fun because that's what we are we're
streamers
yeah
and it's just we were constantly
surrounded by ocean sounds and
the the color of the ocean and all that
so
it was it was very healing even though
we were actively working against it
yeah
and and i i just feel like when i'm on
vacation with a holo member or not even
a vacation when i'm just whip with a
whole member i mean it hasn't happened
that often for now but like an
opportunity like this
meeting a whole member for a short time
who i know i won't be able to meet again
anytime soon
um
i want to
make memories
and i want them to also be recorded like
i like
i like off collabs
and i know you guys like it too i know
it's very special for all of us
so i want to use the opportunity
to stream
um
yeah
so i'm glad that elena was totally in
the same boat
stream is
like not as much as possible but at
least uh
yeah i don't know if it wasn't a
vacation if it was just a meet-up then i
think we would have streamed every day
um love the shorts thank you oh my shirt
you mean my my small videos because like
the short that i uploaded ended up not
even being short
i was like yeah this is my first short
at first you know we we uploaded it and
then kept it private for a while and uh
i was like oh yeah it is my first short
because it was a short at that point of
time but then i uh added a premiere
and it didn't say that it would happen
but it made on it i made it a short
it wasn't too short anymore after that
apparently like reyna was like oh you
can have a premiere to a short i didn't
know
well here's the thing you can't add it
but then it's not a short anymore
yeah [\h__\h] then it means it means we'll
get another chance at having our first
short at some point
um
i wanted to make use and try out this
famous shorts algorithm that everybody
talks about
now i didn't even get to make use of it
what the hell
we'll get another chance sometime we'll
better make use of it better make it the
good one
anyway the game mccree dungeon decided
by duncan
thanks for the pinky welcome home i'm so
happy you took time off to relax and fun
for vayne speaking of locations i leave
for my europe trip on the 25th
you mean the welcoming trip
i can confirm that the best internet
i'll have is 2g
so i'll try to keep you up to date see
all the documents
cool gene
i don't know how slow that is but in the
hotel maybe you have a bit better
internet at least maybe
but wait do you also going to other
places in in europe that's nice please
enjoy it make the most of it
i'm looking forward to hearing your
stories too afterwards
chunky wonky so soft
and you're cute
you also like a barnacle because you
stick to me chunky wonky yeah you're
like a barnacle you're a barnacle
hmm
uh pinky
thank you thank you
first letter of each sentence
it's a wrinkle [\h__\h] you
turn around thanks for the two pinkies
wait didn't you say you have to save
money just a super chat ago
yeah wait first it says wanted to send a
red but gotta save for dokomi soon and
then a few super chats later you sent me
two pinkies which is one
red you think you you hacked the system
or something
been working overtime for a few weeks
now and i earned enough to send the
super chat to my favorite coastal
phoenix
what happened did you
forget about it
[Music]
what happened i thought you wanted to
save the money and here you go and send
it
two pinkies is still one red
if you add it together
ah
i'm sure that among the sea breeze soft
set and friendly company you were able
to find some serenity cata i i think i
did yeah glad you're back safe and sound
also i saw in the one-on-one video
threatened to fire someone over
forgetting letters
just now i've made sure to include lots
of pages in my recipes i know these days
and i'm still working for the head chef
hat boss please have mercy on trying
it's okay no i know i know i'm not even
uh to today when i mentioned it i mean i
might have been thinking about you
partially but it's not it's not about
you i'm just saying i like i like me
some lettuce
um
yeah thank you
thank you very much i think i think i
didn't see it but i think you were uh
doing another
cooking video while my vacation
i think
is that true
maybe i need to check it out
this is a burger again is it with
lettuce this time
what did you make this time
nuggets and a wrap
nuggets
that guys are so easy
a wrap okay
if you wouldn't have put lettuce in the
wrap then i don't know man i would have
completely lost hope for you
the wrap needs the lettuce yeah
maybe i'll make a wrap okay
maybe i'll try to copy your recipe
you get a red one
a kiss because in theory that's a red
one you can't escape from it
there's no video i know i know it's okay
too
yes you have finally understood
wait are you just doing this for me or
have you have you realized by tasting it
yourself that the crunchiness and the
freshness of the lettuce really improves
the burger
have you reflected
and understood have you seen the light
you get it now
you get it cause i get it
yes okay
[Music]
he gets it now
listen to her reflect on luke
nice
lettuce mmm tomato as well please mmm
doesn't go with everything though the
tomato is optional if it fits the the
burger
sands verb fake oh santa
stamp oh my god okay i'm getting too
excited thanks for the pinky cat it's me
your child will be here forever remember
the lord you're never gonna believe this
but i'm going to the mothers too it's my
honeymoon spot after my
wedding what the [\h__\h] i'm marrying
snoot from the skyway so it's speaking
okay well will you be purple father at
my wedding
i think i'm frogging out of you my
flower frog
you're so cute
[Music]
which chicken wrote this super chat huh
it was a sandburg profile picture
i i have a good feeling who it could be
they're so cute
for [\h__\h] sake
sad bird
going on the honeymoon to the maldives
so cute
[Music]
i will be your
maiden of honor
yes i almost said honor of maiden a
broken man tangesian
thank you
tomato and pomegranate oh my best friend
actually uh showed me a picture of her
own arm covered in
yogurt and telling me yo yogurt
really helps for sunburn as well
apparently yogurt and another like milky
product that i don't know what to call
it i think
yeah yeah no it's true
no it does
you're good
and what was the other thing
europeans are an interesting branch
you're a little piece of [\h__\h] that has
nothing to do with it and and europeans
are surely not the only people who try
to put yogurt on their arms when they
have a sunburn okay
respect the europeans you better respect
the europeans
you think thanks for the pinky welcome
back here mama i'm not able to meet you
on live so i send the budget first oh
hello hello archive gang thank you for
sharing many great moments during your
vacation we can feel how happy you are
and how sweet you interact with rainer
please take care sunburn it really hurts
thank you
no you know it's not it's not only
because we couldn't turn off our work
brains that we were sharing so much it's
also you know um we weren't really or at
least i i couldn't speak for myself i
don't know about reyna but i i was
tweeting so much as well because i was
excited to share and
excited about you know you know meeting
dana for the first time and all that
it's just like i need to put these
thoughts in these memories somewhere i
need to write this down i need to write
the feelings down you know
and you guys enjoyed it so i felt
motivated
well you know i like to share a lot of
what's going on so this was like how
could i not share the bathtub thing for
example
how could i not
now the bathtub thing by the way wasn't
was not organized by the butler it was
uh by one of the
uh one of the housekeeping people and on
the last day
um i saw
i saw that uh person so i gave them a
tip
i was like
the bathtub
the bathtub person is here we should tip
him
um
yeah yeah so this this is something
where i feel like this is worth tipping
this was sweet
that was sweet you know
okay neem diesel dancing kfb
what did you say kfb
jim tracy you think thanks for the pinky
oh another pinky
by the way i heard spikes in our radio
station last friday was requested by a
listener
was it you look
uh
was it someone else if yes and that was
wow
the coincidence that you are listening
to the radio at that moment you guys
should request my songs too
at the radio do it
good
i'm very happy that sparks was streamed
on the radio and everyone can listen to
this amazing song at the same time so
excited for your new original song let's
go
i requested it before did it work
this work
you can do that yes
of course you can
thank you that's so sweet also chunkers
stop stepping on my champion
meow
chunky wonky you're so cute
they're so needy these cats
you think you get a kiss for that for
the two pinkies
are we talking online radio like radio
radio i don't know but you can do it
with both
yeah it's an officially registered song
yeah yeah yeah
it's on on the on the music services so
it should be no problem in theory but
it's just you know
someone has to request it because it's
not mainstream
[Music]
my friend isn't watching me anymore so i
can eat about how
he joined valkyrie because i started and
then we went so hard he messages at
midnight to run connect pals oh cool
glad you're enjoying it together with
your friend
nice huh
typhon duncan for the pinky welcome back
we've missed you but it sounds like you
had a great time i can't wait to hear
some stories when i get back from my
meeting hopefully the sun burns healing
well
uh and that 25 hour transit hasn't left
you too tired to cuddle the cats i'm
never too tired to cuddle the cats
yeah they welcomed me back nicely they
seemed a bit more needy than usual
yeah yeah yeah everything was fine after
i came back
and um
yeah i haven't unpacked yet though
because i fell asleep immediately i
didn't even i didn't even take the
medicine that i usually take
i just i just fell asleep i didn't even
eat dinner right yeah yeah yeah
i was like i came home at like how late
was it
oh i don't know it was like late evening
uh
yeah late evening and i was like i still
gotta eat dinner dossier i should order
dinner because i don't
really have anything in the fridge
uh so i was like okay i'm gonna do that
later first i need to chill with my cats
and then i fell asleep and i woke up
like in three hours later and i was like
[\h__\h] it i'm sleeping through the night
yeah so i slept until like 5 a.m
and then my yeah my first my first one
was uh
breakfast
[Music]
melatonin after my dad like stuff for 11
hours oh yeah melatonin is really good
i recommend it yeah yeah i'm glad i
tried it too i didn't bring it to
the maldives though because yeah as you
saw i didn't need it
anyway where was i chased back
we're trying so much
thank you i saw them all
yeah yeah yeah
really really you were really inspired i
suppose thank you for all the art thank
you soon
nathan content thanks for the pinky
welcome back to engine we missed you
hope you had plenty of fun with the
turkey she's not a turkey
here's just starting the next vacation
fun thank you
oh yeah
i want to go again
i said that if the weather is [\h__\h] for
the whole vacation i'm gonna book
another one
uh it was actually pretty fine for
um
half of the vacation
yeah um but i still i don't know i wanna
i want more i want more it doesn't have
to be the maldives no um uh i remember
there was another famous
vacation place that the the germans and
austrians like to go to
it's it's also an island
um
but i think it's not like like as many
islands as the maldives has
let me look it up
ah yeah it's way less islands but it's
called uh the seychelles
like seashells say shells it's in the
indian ocean of east africa
it's kind of similar to the maldives
it also has a beautiful
or has beautiful white uh sand beaches
beautiful clear water and it's like
islands yeah yeah
you guys know it
yeah could go there too i already showed
uh
there's i think there's like we've read
when we look it up we saw that there is
apparently some kind of pink beach
somewhere in the seychelles
somewhere
but this could be a great place to go to
next time because i as great as the
motives were
i don't want to repeat the same place
for vacation over and over because you
know you gotta make use of the world and
visit as many places as you can
i might still go back to the maldives
sometime but not to the same resort even
though it was great
i always want to go to a different place
as great as they were and as great as
the butler was
i was gonna go to a different place
chocolate
chocolate chocolate
wow
[Music]
um
indonesian snack no like i told like she
told before in the first stream that we
did
where we did the
the souvenir
um
the
gift exchange
she said that she bought something but
then she lost it in the airplane i think
or in the airport
yeah it's okay though it's okay it's
okay it's okay i can eat it someday when
i visit indonesia sometime
ah
canada england can cannery islands
canary canary
canary islands
[Music]
santa cruz the tenerife
i heard of it
and where is that
and morocco is close morocco is close
i've been to morocco before
not a good memory though
ah it's part of spain right
oh yeah gran canaria
fuerteventura la palma
tenerife i know these places
the beaches look more brown not white
sand but they still look beautiful they
have like oh it looks like a desert oh
in some places
oh is that a volcano
the islands look nice different from
where we went but
it looks more like spanish i guess
nice
the french overseas territories yes yes
yes oh my god i might ask you guys for
recommendations uh again sometime
and we choose my next travel destination
i don't know dana reyna did say like she
wants to travel
uh again somewhere
um and uh maybe maybe i don't know maybe
we'll go again or maybe we invite
someone else to join us we should invite
subway to senpai apparently super du
senpai took my advice
from long ago
really seriously
uh
i i saw that like she she was talking
about it
um because i
i told her several times
i tell everyone in in japan
to take a break and uh you know
if you if you have this job
at least you have in theory the freedom
to create your own schedules and and
decide when to work like other
other
jobs in japan don't allow that and they
work you
to the bones i don't know um
but hey if you're in hollow you have the
freedom to do anything
you can't even work from vacation if you
feel so bad about it and if you want to
but there's no need to force yourself to
stream
with no break for three years or
whatever
yeah you should take a break
so she apparently took it seriously and
i don't know i guess she's she's she's
gonna stream less i think she's sad and
um not stressed herself out too much
uh maybe me and wayne i should start
planning a vacation with her
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
we should
if she wants to join
i wonder if she wants to join
of course she wants to join
kidnap the duck
duck nap the duck
hold your vacation yes
a full hotel your vacation is very
unrealistic that's never gonna happen
get that out of your brain
that's not gonna happen
you know how hard it was to get people
together for one collab what do you
think how can we get it together for one
vacation impossible
nathan cotton dashing for the pinky wait
i already read that did i i don't know
no maybe not
welcome back sanji we missed you you
hope you had no i did read it here's the
starting and then yeah i did read it
thank you thank you
next vacation fund is already
uh being
uh
started opened up yes i wanna i wanna
travel i wanna travel i'm i don't i i i
would feel bad going too often but
i i wanna there's so many places i wanna
go to guys and i wanna enjoy life um
yeah i was gonna i'm i'm gonna i'm going
to go to korea too
uh meet nabi sensei nabi mama
maybe i don't know august october i
don't know
uh
september
and then vacation vacation october
november i don't know
i need to go i need to go
enjoy
[Music]
don't worry guys i'll take you guys with
me
everyone go
navi mama birthday today tomorrow the
24th
what
for me it's still the 23rd
not me mama birthday
oh my god
[Music]
wow birthday wow
mommy's
i hope she celebrates and eats cake and
has fun and gets a lot of love and many
presents
[Music]
and with your own all the happiness
hope we can
uh collab soon and like become friends
so that we can prepare for
a meeting in real life
carpal tunnel's
thank
you you for waiting for me it was a bit
worried you guys forgot about me
how can you forget about me i was active
the whole time
but here i am and we're back in in full
speed full power again
yeah
i hope you guys can keep up
next weekend i'm gonna be yeah actually
the next week
i don't know the weekend i i probably
won't be streaming because very very
busy because convention
so yeah i might take like
[Music]
friday saturday sunday off
first day i should still be streaming
yeah i'm gonna try to prepare
something
[Music]
some
cow carrot
we can make another one of those videos
within one week he's already preparing
the next one anyway i think
he was living pretty fast with the last
one like basically
or maybe oh
basically if you want to know like first
of all like i decided
uh we together we kind of brainstormed
like
which videos we should do first what
what what we could make videos about
because it's going to be a series and
which ones should be like the first ones
and then um
and then kyle carrot started collecting
all kinds of material
and
and and created like a like a timeline
for the video and like like a
[Music]
how to say like a plan he planned out
the video yeah yeah and then he showed
me
like a draft with the like the parts
where i would speak were like you know
empty
um
and then
he he gave me like a rough
cut carrot don't spoiler it
he gave me a rough idea of what he
wanted me to say roughly
and then i i just kind of
improvised
and and wrote down what i felt like
would fit here and then what i wanted to
say
and i recorded it and then he put it
like um in between
and edited and finished it up and
subtitled it and there and there it was
it was so good right if you haven't seen
it yet
especially if you're one of the newer
peeps but also if you're one of the
older peeps you should watch the the new
video that i put out today
this morning my time
the kfb 101 had to become one with the
bucket video
yeah yeah yeah it's not just a clip
compilation it's like
a history
lesson on
kiwawa
streaming lore
and
yeah i think it was
made pretty well
i love the whole montage of wings
yeah
oh
yes there will be more
we're probably gonna do one on the usual
room
on casper
on
oh
what can we do maybe the whole stream
but i don't think that would be
much because
i think the stream something something
meme thingy will be pretty short i guess
i don't know what else
room of truth ah that's maybe too short
that should be included in the usual
room lore maybe that the koreans call it
room of truth
um
oh yeah hashtag
that was one that we wanted to make
maybe that one would be shorter than the
casper one i don't know
hi john can i see you
i see you below my screen
i see you
hmm peeking through the screen on the
bottom all right i'm giving her some
neck scratches
i read debut yes of course of course ray
debut
needs a video
um
jimmy
baby bottom left no i guess we kind of
decided to not do bottom left because
[Music]
bring it up anymore i guess you guys
said so too don't don't bring it up
anymore
i feel like it would have been
okay to at least like
explain where it came from because i
feel like i feel
a little bit a little bit proud that
um i mean it got used in the wrong way a
lot but
i feel a little bit proud that i kind of
coined a word that then went on to be
used so much
in other people's streams like
throughout the whole life fandom too you
know what i mean like i basically
created
a word a meme
it was not only used for me it was also
used for other people
and on reddit people will be like haha
that's bottom left or another people
chats will be in the car one left
oh yeah i even used outside of holo
apparently
oh my slime pinot
it went it went to places and
yeah and i think because of that a lot
of people don't even know
why where it originally came from
and that i think would be worth
explaining
yeah
you know just like australia that one we
explained but we're not gonna
really
use this anymore are we
just because we explain bottom left
doesn't mean that we're gonna use it
again
i just feel like you know that that was
a
that was one of our first or it was a
second collab that we had and
because of that that's so old like
people don't this is what the series is
about to explain things that people
don't know where it came from
i don't know some of you guys seem to
seem to understand me now um
[Music]
i i don't think it will necessarily
revive it just by making that video
certain things just cannot be revived
it will you know people who still use it
for example
are the kind of people who don't watch
my streams anyway and and it doesn't
matter for them whether i make the video
or not it doesn't matter for them you
know
you guys already understand if we know
if we make that video you're not gonna
use it anyway
you know what i mean i can't i can't
influence the people who don't care
about me anyway
they're gonna a lot of them are probably
still using it
not knowing that i don't like it being
used
i mean in the wrong context i mean if
there's a real bottom left moment and
it's okay to use perhaps
yeah but you know you know yeah
um
i don't know for now we probably have
other ideas if we if we
can't think of something else and maybe
maybe we'll make a little video out of
it
i have a point right right i do have a
point
anyway okay
i need to read some chats
i still want to cook after this by the
way i didn't get my new hellofresh
order yet but i have something else
because i got i got something for free
sometimes they sent like
uh really only sometimes that was the
first time i think they sent like some
free stuff like because they're working
with companies i guess sometimes they
want to send samples for free for new
products so i got something for free i'm
kind of like it's called schpetzlet in
german
it's kind of like a kind of noodle
and it came with a recipe so i was like
okay i guess i'm making that today
yeah i'm making a
spatula with prosciutto and mascarpone
uh yeah i think that's it
did we make that before we made spatzles
before yes but you can use spreadslit
just like noodles with all kinds of
sauces and
yeah
oh and cherry tomatoes i'm using a
prosciutto mascarpone and cherry
tomatoes
it's a different one yeah very different
okay continuing a scratch cut me off
thank you soon
i forgot how to read korean i need to
practice again
oh no i forgot
i need to practice my no
final thumbs up little pinky you always
send the super chat and i um i forgot
i'm so sorry i i knew i knew your the
signs looked familiar ah jonkers don't
certainly jump on my table
i love you
i can't be mad at you i love you
i love you i love you
okay what does it say uh in korean but i
translate it to english welcome back all
the carefree employees worked hard
waiting for the manager it's great
just
it's great to see you become yakitori
with the hot sun of the maldives ah
yes
um i have i have lights uh studio
quality lights in front of my face so i
brightened up
my skin so it doesn't look like i'm
sunburned
yeah there's lights that you don't see
there's some soft boxes and [\h__\h] in
front of me so you don't see it but i'm
actually really really red actually no
in my face no so you wouldn't see it in
my face anyway i wasn't able to protect
my face
don't even have a sunburn on my nose
my face i really put a lot of
uh sunscreen on properly
um
yeah i would like to have an applause
for that because a lot of people get
sunburned on their ears and noses
because they they don't they kind of
don't take it seriously and forget it
forget about it i had the experience
before
but not anymore not doing it again thank
you thank you thank you thank you
yeah yeah i was like putting sunscreen
on my ears and told elena that i once
got a really bad sunburn on my ears like
who would expect [\h__\h]
hell to get a sunburn on your ear
that's one of the easiest spots to
forget and one more is like the
um like your your your hairline on your
scalp
the one line that doesn't have hair on
it
it's easy to get a sunburn there too
actually really easy really really easy
but it's also kind of difficult to put
like sunscreen there
i got a little bit of a sunburn
uh and on the first day but it's already
gone i think yeah that one was weak
[Music]
yeah don't forget to put sunscreen on
your head
the less hair you have on your head the
more
sunscreen you need
oh i guess yeah some of you guys maybe
don't need
i i forget like for me it's like putting
on sunscreen is normal but i forget that
some people don't need sunscreen
cause they don't get sunburns
man what the [\h__\h]
this is not fair
never had sunburned no
[Music]
some people built different
yeah
nice good for you
more resistance yeah
you could not we saw
making sleeping noises
some people can others burn
not even that i mean some people don't
even really tan
because they're already like
pretty dark
so i feel like it don't like makes no
difference for them
but yeah definitely no sunburn there
[Music]
and me
look at me but my face is fine my face
is fine
[Music]
i don't tend i don't burn
nice
okay continuing a certain scientific
[\h__\h] thank you for the pinky [\h__\h]
what why oh oh cause i'm back again
thank you for waiting for me
i like your name
reminds me of one of my favorite animes
i know it's a reference
tanaka thank you
our ronin thank you salute
[Music]
i'm happy to
you should go i really recommend the
maldives to everybody we're gonna talk
about it i think in the recap but the
motives is not only the islands which
are expensive you can also stay
on the main island
uh they have nice nice beach too
and or you can stay on the main island
and then like take a little boat to a
close by island
and chill there for example
there's there's um some options that
should be
relatively cheap and the flight from
austria to the maldives for example
uh
was really not that expensive and it's
not that far
my family always goes to the mall is
without me what the [\h__\h] why what what
what what go with them go with them
what
going that requires going outside home
you will not regret it yo
it was like a different [\h__\h] world
when we were there like i was like holy
[\h__\h]
we like every day
every day like even like you know we
would be on the beach for like three
hours and and like even after three
hours i would still be like
again and again and again and be like oh
my god the water is so blue five minutes
later oh my god the water is so
see-through oh my god so beautiful
i would
like continuously repeat myself
and yeah
it was amazing the water was so
beautiful so see-through
so clean
everything was so beautiful
i mean the corals were a bit
manduk-style we both cut our
feet
several times
it it hurt
step of that it was like
not everywhere but like
yeah and some some spots had like a lot
of corals
yeah
even though even though most of the
beach was like
completely
clean sand but when you go into the
water you will first be met by like one
layer of corals
i don't think uh
it's the same everywhere but
[Music]
of course enjoyed being stepped on at
least
good for them i guess
coastal rocks yeah yeah yeah well
the ocean always comes with one kind of
obstacle either it's rocks big rocks or
small rocks or it's corals or whatever
you know what i told dana about
something and she was really really like
surprised about it
i told her that for example i went to
croatia
for vacation when i was younger and they
had also really clean water but they
didn't have a sand beach but a stone
pebble kind of beach and she didn't she
didn't know
that that was a thing
i told her that it makes the water
really clean kind of cleaner than the
sand
but
uh
i don't know it's kind of it hurts often
so you need shoes for those kind of
beaches
um
your rock beaches they're usually pretty
clean
um
yeah yeah yeah
yeah gravely
those are usually clean
can't beat the sand
i've been to a lot of dirty sand beaches
so
as i said like if you go to an island
like that like we went to it will be
clean beautiful but if you go to a beach
on a big meow
if you go to a beach on a big big big
land
then yeah
chances are it's gonna be a bit dirty so
now i never can go back meow yeah
what this movie i think cause jonkers is
sleeping on my table
thank you father
goodies goodies dancing uh oh god go
dies
no but i told her that we can watch it
together on discord if she wants
originally
she was she was really excited and
fascinated by all the shows that i
showed her because we originally started
with scrubs because i downloaded them to
watch on my flight
um
and then i didn't really watch them so
on the first night we watched scrubs i
introduced her to scrubs and she loved
it
and she wanted to watch it on the next
day too but then
i don't know why it wasn't like this on
the first day but on the second day
maybe
because maybe because i didn't um
connect to the wi-fi until then
um but then my ipad
realized that i'm in the maldives and
they don't have netflix
no disney plus they don't have disney
plus there so
even though i downloaded them already
it wouldn't let me watch it
yeah
so i was like i'm so sorry we have to
watch something else i have netflix
though and she was so
sad about it she was like no why don't
you watch scratch
watch the hospital so i wanna watch more
scrubs she was so upset about it
so i tried finding something similar for
her so we went through my netflix and i
showed her like um and this is friends
have you watched it no oh this is game
of girls have you watched it no she
hasn't watched any of these shows oh my
god but she likes anything i show her
and then then i um showed her this show
that i i just started watching i was
just
past the first episode so i was like we
could watch it together because i'm not
fine with that anyway
uh which is maybe you guys have seen it
i don't think it's well known it's
called
hard cell
it's like kind of like a mockumentary
in a women's prison
in the uk
they have a very heavy
accent that's even a bit hard like quite
hard for me to understand
it's funny
it's funny though
yeah and then enjoyed that one very much
as well
and then on another day we watched like
this netflix animal
documentary show that we got
mostly sheet i liked it too but she got
so invested in it
i downloaded i felt like i was her mom
or something but i downloaded a few
episodes and on the airport uh we were
waiting for our planes together which
was really nice because
we didn't uh
separate for really kitty kitty
at the end but um so we were waiting and
maldives airport is literally just six
gates so it's all in one like hall small
hall
so we were able to stay together and and
i was like okay
i have the ipad she's like i don't know
what's animal documentaries i'm like
okay
okay mommy's gonna put out the ipad now
but you can't watch for longer than half
an hour because then you can't sleep
anymore
and then i turned on the the animal
challenge
we for the last time we watched it
together
before
separating we are watching the story of
a seal and the lion
cub and all of those
and i was like
but like her mommy because i'm bringing
the ipad and the entertainment
actually um
on the last day i was getting kind of
sentimental and sad so
i
don't make fun of me but i am
several times
once on the seaplane
um
once in the
once in the cab
and on the tour
and uh
in the airport lobby i was holding her
hand oh i reached out for her hand
and um
just
held it
hand-holding it's not ludo it's just you
just hit it
yeah
no spicy no loot just
now i realized [\h__\h]
it's the last day and then we actually
really
bonded and spent so much time together
and it's kind of like yo we're not gonna
see each other for a while probably
ah now we gotta go so sad don't wanna
leave the maldives don't wanna leave
right now
um
yeah we were holding hands
[Music]
yes
she was even
already looking up flights on how to get
to austria
she's pretty serious about it i think
um
[Music]
i recommended her i told her that all
seasons are nice but usually people
come the most for like winter time for
skiing now dana told me she can't ski
and she can't snowboard but i told her
she should come anyway and try it out
and learn it because it's fun
yeah i mean it's also terrifying but
it's also fun
has saint ever seen snow oh
yeah i don't know but i mean
she's traveled before so
maybe not in masses like
i i don't know
i didn't ask maybe not you know as much
as you see like on the mountain maybe
just like snow falling
gently
call mr yodel
i wonder if there's a yoda looking
teacher skiing i don't think he can
speak uh
english he's like a you know a really
really old
old old old austrian boomer i don't
think he can speak english
i've seen snow on the ground before but
i've never seen it falling
isn't it usually the other way around
like it falls and it doesn't
um
like
stay on the ground because it melts
anyway i need to read i'm exhausted
um
dual instantiation silly fellow
thunderstorm of laundry thank you for
pinky thank you for the insane amount of
streams clips tweets and pics during the
vacation and made your break really
enjoyable for the fans as well yeah i
know i thought so
it's really one of a kind welcome back
missed your lots
[Music]
i can't really do that duty on this time
because we have wind waker weekend
and i wanna
i wanna celebrate the new song
i don't think that what you're saying
really
makes such a big difference to be honest
well they um
i'm too excited i can't wait 24 hours to
stream after my original song release
no
i refuse even if it affects the song
a little bit i refuse even if it does
who knows if it does but
you you guys just have to make up for
that
just
watch this watch it a bit more often you
will want to watch it anyway because the
video is gonna be amazing
yeah i can't wait stream before it no i
can't because then you didn't see it yet
and didn't hear it yet so what are we
gonna be excited about and talk about
huh it has to be afterwards
stream upcoming original song oh you
know what i'll give you the i'll give
you the initials
i'll give you the initials you can try
you can try to figure out the title
it's a two word title
and it's f
and n
f
friends
neglecting no
foolish
nuisance why am i coming up with these
weird names
funky nuggets
fortnite no
fire nation
fried noodles oh my god see you guys
come up with the crazy ideas that's the
important
stream
free nutella
finally nuggets oh i love that finally
nuggets
fried nuggets
that's some good ones
well we will see
you guys have to come up with some ideas
i would be i would be
impressed if someone gets it right
like the full title
and
spanking time thanks for the red super
chat
welcome back because i'm being as
lovable as mine i was at anime central
ah where gouda and bay were
here's 10 floaters that you can take
with you the next time you go to the
maldives no
it's totally fine but that is one floaty
one red super chat is like one floaty in
the maldives
oh what do you mean yeah i should buy it
beforehand and then bring it with me
yeah yeah yeah yeah next time i will
probably do that
by oh way
on the on the last day when we were
packing
i'm gonna say this now because i feel
like we're not gonna mention it in the
other recap stream and we were packing i
am
you know we at some point realized oh
[\h__\h] we have to let the air out of our
floaties we had
one big of mine one big of hers and one
ball like a like a beach ball that we
never used
um
so
i uh we go to our floaties and she's
like how do you how do you do this how
do you open it so i i
i don't think she ever
like did that before so i show her where
the thingy is and she tries to open it
i'm like no no no no you have to pull it
out
outside yeah yeah so then she does it
and then she's like why does the air not
come out and i'm like you have to
squeeze it
then she tries to squeeze and try to
make the air come out but she's like she
was doing a pretty bad job at it and she
got exhausted really fast and gave up
and she's like i'm gonna translate it
so meanwhile i i i
get rid of all the air of my floaty it
takes a while but i did it a few times
before so
i eventually i'm done and then i'm like
oh well whatever i'm done packing so i
guess i guess i'll help her
so
i did all of them i did my floating i
did her big ass floatie and i did the
the beach ball
everything i was like
like letting out the air of those for an
hour or so
sitting on them laying on them squeezing
them
changing position all the time because
it is pretty exhausting
and you have to change positions to get
like you know the best kind of
position to let out the air
natural mommy exactly like this is again
such an ipad moment
sometimes sometimes there were these
these mommy kiwawa moments yeah
she must have knew you would a
new one just made you do it no no no no
no i don't think so but she was very
happy
she was like whoa how do you do this why
are you so good at this i'm like i don't
know i just did it a few times
she was very happy when i was done
yeah
yeah yeah yeah what's an ipad moment you
know when i said that
i i brought the entertainment and we
were watching
uh some stuff on my ipad it was like
like you know
mommy ipad please i wanna i wanna watch
something on the ipad and then mommy is
like no
you already had your ipad time today one
hour you get no more
anyway i felt i felt very skilled and
cool you know and when there was that
marshmallow question
uh
was it a marshmallow question or did i
just ask it if if there were any cool
senpai moments from kiwawa and she
couldn't really think of any wasn't that
a cool moment
me letting out the air of the floaties
knowing how to do it but that happened
on the last day so she couldn't have
known yet
if i had a nickel for every time you
became an indonesian woman's mommy i
would have two nickels
yeah
you're rich now two nickels let's go
that was my question ah
thanks for asking that
like i first let reina go for the
questions and like the ones that she
liked and then i went for afterwards and
i saw your question i was like oh
oh
i want to know
i wouldn't want hearing her answer
yeah
maybe i'm not cool
she didn't know
a cool thing about there's okay but
that's okay i'm more cute
and
cute
maybe
spicy
if you would have asked that way that
like cute cute senpai moments you
probably would have
known a bunch of them
[Music]
hi um melee sprite thank you soon is
that is that
is that my no again i think it's my no
yes mai no
come san nita thank you
not funding it fund
what the the the six figures stat studio
cause that's insane
don't even don't even try it's not worth
it we're never gonna get there it's okay
though it's crazy um
let's just let's just go
where where am is suit
i hope it fits
[Music]
out from the wind
thumb
people let's go
well all the people who started funding
it your money will go towards a flight
to amma place you know i was even
thinking maybe maybe just this once
maybe just this once i can take business
class i don't know
i'll think about it i'll see i'll see
how much it costs
i always feel like it's such a waste but
maybe just this once because that's
gonna be long distance um
long distance slide though
i have business class why is it so
expensive
it goes up from like 1 000
economy to like 4 000
business it's insane
write it up as a business expense yeah
this one i could probably the maldives
i'm not even gonna try
because my tax person she's really like
she's really proper and there's like
a lot of things that you could maybe
write off in america or in japan
but you can't in austria
[Music]
they're they're i guess a bit more
strict
yeah it's expensive because it's a
luxury
luxury huh it shouldn't be luxury
it shouldn't be
when economy is just torture then
business should be just normal and then
first class could be luxury
it's just the way that the society
makes it look like it shouldn't be like
that
business should be normal
normalized business class
we live in a society
a torture class
thank you thank you pump jack mcgee
duncan every another called thanks for
the red zipper chat mom getting
attentions back to count to six figures
at least five
uh
you guys are
very sweet but
yeah um
it's just it's just not no it's [\h__\h]
up man why did i charge so
much i don't get it
i wanna i wish i could just fly to japan
and use the japan studio but even that
was kind of hard to use
because of scheduling
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
therefore not studio one one thank you
it will be used for the flight instead
[Music]
thank you
jim transcendent
glad to have you back but between your
vacation tweets pics short upload
streams and hearing your voicemails and
valkyrie chronicles hey chronicles
connect
it was like you never left also this is
totally not studio our blight fun hope
you get to visit disneyland oh
american disneyland i don't know i don't
know if
there's time for that or like you know
but um i'm not i didn't really plan much
yet i'm still like waiting
maybe one more week before i decide
maybe
maybe one studio
graciously
gives us a realistic quote
um maybe
i'm still hoping but
yeah it's looking pretty bad i didn't
expect it to be this bad
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah just mixing it up in
in your brain i understand
similar names yeah
[Music]
your boy stephen adams thank you maple
leaf 2501 thank you for the red super
chat welcome back
glad to see all the fun you had on your
vacation glad to see you back to
continue your awesomeness thank you
yes there's already a lot of awesomeness
coming up guys this week new song next
week dokomi and
some secret thing
it's even next week although or
immediately after doko mean
we will see
thank you thank you
thank you very much look forward to
having kiwawa back thank you maple leaf
mwah
your boy stephen adams thank you and
brandon thanks for the pinky oh my god
this is just the takanas you can't have
the hell yeah already
yeah you can say that about me now
yay
brandon
oh it's okay i actually ended up telling
dana too because like you made me worry
a little bit but then i was like
snorkeling in the water and i was like
imagining what if one of one of reyna's
steps on something so i i
i went up until the until the air and i
was like
just just so you know never step never
step on the stones because there could
be a crazy fish that kills you on it
okay don't don't you ever step on the on
the stones there okay
i was more worried about uh elena
because i would feel i would feel guilty
if something happened to her you
like a true mother yeah
so i
i use your knowledge to protect reina
all is good
ah mosquitoes oh i did get mosquito
bites which worried me at first but
seems everything was fine
they had like
um
they even had mosquito repellent in the
hotel room
in the in the room in the bathroom for
both of us like a bottle for each of us
which was nice i even brought it home
um
and i used it i got like maybe three
mosquito bites anyway
um but i'm fine yeah i'm still alive
yeah
thankfully
uh okonomiyaki fluffy hoots tank soon
thank you
black friday and crispy dancing optimus
love hearing your stories hope you had a
blast with lena
yes it was a great bonding experience
thank you
free is pretty good considering it of
tropical island yeah we didn't really
see them at all like we never saw a
mosquito flying around i just suddenly
woke up with like
a new mosquito bite but yeah it's okay
the sunburn was a bigger problem
just turned in what did i miss you
missed so much i'm almost done though i
think with the super chats
and then if you want you can watch the
archive
miyako thank you
maybe the rain kept them away yeah
probably at least on the first two days
first two three days
miss pistachio
gotta refresh now
by the way we haven't had the membership
thingy
happening yet right
it hasn't been rolled out to my channel
i think are you guys able to gift
memberships i don't think so otherwise
people would have tried it out right
um yeah the gift it's not happening yet
um
no i didn't do anything
it just like gets rolled out in
[Music]
like
channels not at the same time
i don't know like i know before
you know some guys have some guys made a
good point
uh
about we shouldn't use it
i don't know maybe at least try it i
don't know
it's not here yet so i don't even know
[Music]
a redirect option uh
i don't know where it would be
yeah that's a that's a rating thing
right yeah that's also been implemented
but i don't know where it is so it's
probably not available for me either
i don't think i'll i also said this to
the other em members like they were like
yo are you guys okay and just to know
who who's okay with being rated who's
not and i was like yo i'm okay with it
in theory but i don't think any one of
you guys is ever gonna raid me because
when i start my streams no one is
streaming
except sometimes maybe cali
but
i don't see anyone ever rating me from
en
so i don't think we'll have that
happening maybe i can rate ina for
example
um but i don't know i don't really care
about the whole whole rating thing
it's just awkward
like um
do you guys know the japanese streaming
website nico nico dolga
they have
like something similar
it's kind of
interesting i guess there's like a
there's like a 24-hour stream
um
i don't know if they still do it but
they at least had it back in the day and
it's called nikon
nama
cruise
like it's a cruise like a cruise ship
and it it shows you
random streamers
uh
for like i don't know two minutes or so
and they see that you've been watched by
the nico nico cruz and it has a lot of
viewers usually
and
uh then you can comment and the comments
show up on the the
invaded you stream up and then you can
decide if you want to leave the cruise
or not and then you go to their stream
usually when people get like the cruise
it's like oh wow hello and they try to
appeal to them and they're like oh look
at me
i'm so funny
and then you know then you can get off
or you stay
uh
um oh yeah that was even like
an
ah
a pole the the crews would always do
like a pole
if the cruise wants to continue watching
this streamer for like one more minute
or not
and if not then
it just leaves and goes to the next
person if it does then it gets like
extended and the cruisers can watch it
longer
yeah
yeah anyway it's it's a it's a nice way
i guess of finding new unknown streamers
um
yeah that's their their way of reading
yeah it's a concept that is a bit
different from a typical
raid
[Music]
um
you should tell you know that you can
turn off membership gifting for your
channel
i should tell you that you can turn it
off i think she already knows we
discussed it on
on our discord
um
[Music]
i think she knows
i i'm feeling really
exhausted uh my head
head hurt
oh cool i refreshed i don't know where i
am
i hear maybe
when you want to stomp
there's not so many left
one
maybe
maybe another time
sometimes
is way past my sleeping time
oh if this is where the mold is i was i
would i would be asleep by now
um
[Music]
i need to cook
i need to make food oh [\h__\h]
i think once i end the stream and move i
think i'll be awake again
yeah
okay if you guys are okay with it i
don't know when but uh hmm
hmm i could i might read some super
chats after the original song release
i might
oh my god i'm tired
i wanna i wanna jump into bed
all right away
oh man i can make pizza
i bought frozen pizza
[Music]
oh
my heart oh head horn
suddenly the exhaustion hits
okay maybe i'll cook the other thing
tomorrow
um
don't have to cook let's go
[Music]
this is nice i keep hearing
oh my gosh movies is a snail
she's like curled up on the floor why
are they they're so clingy right now
and what you know when i stream usually
they're in a different room but right
now they just
trying to stay as close as possible is
so cute
this
[Music]
did you hear that
didn't you hear that
[Music]
she's like mommy stop streaming
hey hi baby
she's looking at me
ma'am
wow
wow i'm talking to her
she doesn't want to say anything anymore
she's just waiting down there they're
both waiting
okay i'll be with you cats thank you
thank you so sweet
thank you
did you hear that she didn't pull she
did a book
wow
yeah
[Music]
oh donkey wonky
cute
he's so cute okay okay baby i'm gonna
i'm gonna join you guys now
yeah
she's looking at you guys she's like
mommy give us some chimken they look so
delicious
but i need you guys
she jumped up to a tree while saying
pork
he's so cute
he did you did
i won't no i need you to be alive for my
song release you
okay i'm gonna go now thank you guys so
much for welcoming me back and i will i
will uh
we'll recap even more on the vacation
and share my notes with you guys in the
photos on wednesday
yeah tomorrow
i'll try to recover a bit more from the
jet lag and unpack my [\h__\h]
and then
and then i will
uh
[Music]
hopefully
do my dance practice yeah
so thank you very much it was nice to be
with you guys again it's nice to have a
place to come back to
yeah
it feels like it's been a long time
since we had
like you know this intimate time
together and i appreciate it thank you
so much
yeah
thank you for all your love and support
thank you thank you thank you for being
here
and also for making you know dream
vacations like that possible for me in
the first place
yeah i i will admit it was quite a
luxury
a little bit expensive so
i couldn't do this if i had like a
normal job if i wasn't hollow then i
would not be able to
afford this but you guys
made it possible but don't worry i'm not
throwing your money out of the window
i'm i still try to
spend it wisely
um
exactly
nuggets for example yeah
she's like
she's she see she she saw something on
the wall apparently but there's nothing
um
[Music]
vacation isn't throwing it out the
window
no i agree i agree um it says it was a
very special vacation and also
uh it was partially
even content creation as well so
yeah oh yeah okay we're adding the
stream she wants me to end the stream
[Music]
allowed me out yeah that one was picked
up nicely good job chunky wonky
good job oh
they're so cute they're so [\h__\h] cute
okay and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
i love you
wow
thank you
oh oh and something really funny if you
didn't see it check out kanaulu twitter
and i think also it's on youtube too
probably kano
twitter and youtube because
uh
he made a really funny video on my
request that i can't upload myself
because of copyright dmca um but it's
really funny somebody's watching
the bird dancing every time i see it
it's so funny
i'm so glad i asked to have that made
the mating dancer
it's all funny
bye bye
[Music]
do
you