a
[Music]
o
oh
[Music]
n
K Cy
K hello hello hello hello oh good
morning
everybody I am awake at 6:00 a.m. let's
go and I didn't stay up
to 6:00 a.m. I awakened at
5:30 yo I did it I freaking did
it good
morning have some tea that hopefully
wakes me up green
tea but I'm pretty awake I'm okay thank
you for your concern today's stream is
sponsored by tribe
nine yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you
very much I'm excited when I got this
offer I was immediately like yes yes yes
yes looks good I want to I want to give
it a try looks very
interesting yeah so I will talk a little
bit about what it is in the beginning
and then we will dive into the game this
is not the typical 1 hour sponsorship
it's going to it's going to be a little
bit longer
uh probably like 2 or 3 hours because we
want to reach the boss the first boss
apparently yeah 2.0 W
yeah K hello hello welcome welcome
welcome now you you will stay you will I
will make you stay so let me talk a
little bit about it uh listen up listen
up
kfp so today sponsor stream for the
deadly demo of tribe 9 uh in my
description there's a download link that
is kind of a referral link so if you
click it they will know you clicked it
because of me H it was released a couple
days ago I'm a little bit late uh with
my stream I suppose but it's still going
to be fresh
yeah so it's free the demo is free so
please check it out and click the link
in the description or in my tweet and
tripe 9 is a 3D Souls like action RPG
they say for PC and smartphone and it
will be released by akatuki
[Music]
games and it's a completely new game
based on the original idea from the
dangan lum creators as you may be able
to tell by the art
style which is very unique and very cool
I really like
it so what kind of game is
it let's tell you a little bit more
about the setting
yeah uh in this game this is set in a
near future Tokyo controlled by a deadly
game so future but not too far in the
future colorful characters confront the
looming and unjust presence of
death cie why would you talk about Cali
like that poor C she even did a
sponsorship on this on this game as well
can't believe they talk about her like
that man poor cie she always gets like
you
know harsh treatment well the game is
packed with unexpected twists and turns
offering players a roller coaster of
emotions from surprise to Joy anger and
sorrow are we going to cry a I hope not
um let's talk about the
story I have a little bit of a text for
you to read out
loud uh so it is the year
20xx in neotokyo to resolve their
conflicts teens replaced violence with a
dueling method similar to baseball
called Extreme baseball or XB the loser
of an XB match must obey the winner
baseball I'm not very good at base I
never played baseball
before however times have changed XB
extreme baseball has been abolished no
and the world is now ruled by
XG what is XG a deadly game with lethal
consequences no bring back the baseball
that sounds way more
peaceful in the 23 cities that have
taken a turn for the worst what awaits Y
kuraka and Amnesia teen and his friends
H well then let's also have some fun
today is a quote from a character it
[Laughter]
seems I but I saw it I don't think
baseball is completely gone because I
saw like baseball in the
game hopefully we'll get to play some
baseball yeah so so so so so so so so
that's what we're going to play today so
let's get started with the demo
bu oh this is a cute starting screen
little bit of retro oh I think we get a
lot of retro
actually actually can I change this no
never mind whatever my screen size is
just really
tiny that's
okay oh oh I should stop my music
oh tell me if it's like too loud or
something like
that okay oh oh I'm not controlling this
kuraka he's got a safe file with 9,273
hours how many days is
this well then oh is that literally what
I just quoted a moment
ago yes it
is will be very fun right not
disturbing rookie
numbers oh
cute uh oh hero AA you are back I have
always been watching over you come start
your adventure
today
cute
retro what is the matter have you
forgotten what you have been
doing uh yeah seems like it understood
then listen closely I will explain again
you were commissioned by me to go to the
items Merchant in the village to buy
some
herbs herb just head straight down this
path and you will reach the village did
you get that go to the items Merchant
and remember to bring your wallet 10
gos oh yeah oh oh what will I hear that
every time I receive an
item that is
um quite the
jingle you're all set now the part heroa
I'm a
hero Adventure Basics here the basics of
this game in this game players can
control their characters to reach
destinations to continue the story using
the radar can point out the direction of
the destination as well as give an
overview of the surrounding area main
objectives will be displayed on the
radar if you're unsure of where to go
next be sure to check it
out
cute let's go purchase some why is it an
exclamation marks herbs that's a bit
concerning cute talk to me I really feel
like I'm playing this on some really old
machine how we going to talk
[Music]
click
uh wait let me look up the button I have
my PowerPoint
presentation next to
me wait
wait
[Music]
controls e
H thank
you konaka have you finished your
training for the day you've got to work
hard and become a reliable hero and
defeat the Demon Lord the Demon
Lord I see so you're not going to sell
me those
herbs when I first found you having lost
all your
memories the typical protagonist thing
on that rainy day I was really surprised
who would thought you were a
hero you have to become stronger to
defeat a demon lorddd okay I'll try my
best wait are we still going downwards I
guess
so no memories allowed
heyo wait is
this cat can I talk to the
cat
meow
yeah I think I gave the right
answer hello ah you're the merchant oops
you found me yes I'm the item Merchant
oh you're here for some herbs correct
lady goddess has already given me a head
up it's 12 gold for one herb do you wish
to purchase I don't have enough money
but I'll try anyway oh my you poor heck
well you only have 10 gold how Reckless
of Lady goddess thank you for four years
fine you can have it for Jingle oh
[Music]
[Applause]
really what was that I was going to say
I feel so accomplished thanks to the
Jingle what what what what what's
happening
thanks thank you for your patronage I
look forward to seeing you
again it glitched I didn't just imagine
that did I I'm keeping watch over you
just gave some mon to try to get in the
village it's still too dangerous for you
to leave the village you have to train
more in the lady goddess do I have a
sword wait the map is telling me to go
up goodbye slime I'm not going to bother
with you cuz I don't know if I have a
sword let's report back to Lady goddess
yeah over 9,000 that sure sounds
like we're like m imprisoned in some
kind of endless
loop that I would like to get out
[Music]
of great you are back maybe I'll give it
some Reverb great you're back hero
kuraka hero hero kuraka here's next
order listen
carefully you don't need the
herbs did you say
[Music]
something yeah you don't need the herbs
I've already brought it back
he's the only one he's the only one
who's voiced so I don't know if I should
read it out loud oh well you can only
answer yes or
no wait what was the
question what was the
question oh yes just let's always say
[Music]
yes oh oopsy sorry dude good now I will
give you the next order go investigate
the clay pot at the other side of the
bridge let me first crumble the big rock
blocking blocking your
way thank you oh my the big rock is
crashed you're all set now depart hero
[Music]
kuraka this is
weird this is certainly weird can I run
or shift doesn't
work
clayt investigates The Clay Pot but he
doesn't find any
yeah I
know yeah I just wanted to
check okay no going off the main path oh
this Clay Pot wants to be investigated
though mhm doesn't find
anything this feels this feels like a
fever dream doesn't
it yeah this is strange like she keeps
on making you do things
that where there's no point to it at
[Music]
all yeah let's go to this
gaslighting gatekeeping girl bossing
lady
[Music]
why
yeah yeah you're not going to get really
far with this kind of training very
pointless maybe it's like a training of
your mind trying to make you go insane
because the fight will also make you go
insane I mean yeah that kind of mental
training might be useful but I think
you're just harming him
[Music]
he doesn't remember anything he's been
here for
[Music]
years I I hope so for you I hope that
there's a
[Music]
point it will all be
okay maybe it won't be okay
don't
[Music]
jump
huh why she just walking is that BL stop
fake
it's it's not the air you can literally
just walk on
it she's
cute what
[Music]
is he supposed to look familiar to me
from a
certain wait yeah 16 bit I guess that's
a bit more bits than
ours oh they're Superior to me
[Music]
oh maybe try to step into it you were
GID all this time that's just like a
green screen but in blue it's just some
fabric probably just step on
it for sure aren't we all
tired there's a 1080 bit girl in the
corner to that's me
[Music]
W I am I'm 1080 bit oh is that
am I 1080 B because I'm streaming
1080 does that automatically make me
1080 is is that is that how it
works
[Music]
no yeah I know those are pixels I don't
know don't judge me somebody said so so
I give them my
belief my whole belief system is
yours H I am 32 bits am I but that's not
very much more than what they
were I'm 24
bits which one is it that doesn't sound
like very
much I should be way
more great you are back hero kuraka
what is the
matter you're
crazy I see you have done well here's
the next order I will just completely
ignore what you just said listen
[Music]
[Laughter]
carefully hero Kaka you need not
worry they are all Pawns of my gift game
I see them all very
clearly yo
kuraka no matter what happens you will
always be
my see what I did there was that
spooky
oh I think that was
good oh
god oh
sorry oh is she still talking to
me you need not worry
Pawns of my
[Music]
game I'm so good at this yeah it's so
imersive isn't
that slay
mate no matter what happens you will
always be my slave
always I'm so
good
spooky oh there's
[Music]
more system failure uh-oh let's get out
of here kuraka
let's get out of here this is our
time this is our time to release
ourselves from this gaslighting world oh
they're gone they're gone where are they
should I go to the
pots there's no
music
uhoh corrupted
data what if I okay I I'm still like
kind of bound by these limitations
oh maybe we can find the 16 bit
people nothing can stop us let's
go a little bit faster would be nice
but no
no no response yeah cuz the data is
corrupted they've been logged
off they're not dead they're not dead
don't don't worry about
it they're just logging off
AFK not girl out of all
people oh there's some 16 bit
people
Warrior wait now he doesn't have voice
lines okay thank God you're okay
H who are these guys I've never seen
them
before they're the demon Lord's henchmen
enemies of the villagers what they're
the ones
who there we
[Music]
go they got good
voices what are you talking about who
the heck are are m
wait wait wait do you know how they've
been talking about the Demon Lord or
soul but the way he just said calm down
in Japanese was like ma like like well
you know and
theni I don't I wonder if that's a pun
because it's together string strong
together he was
saying yeah which is Demon Lord wait was
that FAL purpose
no I don't I actually don't think so
can't be intentional wait am I the Demon
Lord is he saying cuz he's like cuz I
interpret it
as but in reality he's is calling me by
my name Ma am I the Demon Lord no
way got the voice
now oh I think it said something in the
beginning uh uh like oh this is still a
demo there might be some uh sounds that
are not working so maybe the voice lines
sometimes
disappear we not to the same page is is
the page that I am the Demon
Lord
yeah
man Oh I thought it was a lady goddess
[Music]
don't be fooled hero Kaka they are they
are the demon Lord's henchman so they
are my
henchmen yeah that's
right you don't know your first name
y
yo yo yo yo indeed I agree she should
[Music]
be he
did y
Mom let's not bring a y mama joke into
this sponsorship
of course they they Ras my memories
every time I log in
man what are you waiting for help me and
we will avenge
everyone shut
it
Pow Wow
strong let me ask another question yo
kuraka do the names
sua and yako ring any
bells in part yeah some some of like the
part Parts like eloha and
S yeah ring the bell
partially wo
wao I think I'm turning 16
bit
wa wao wo wo let's
go character development
literally that's why I couldn't enter it
there was nothing to
[Laughter]
enter mind break
time have you ever tried to enter it
before Kaka maybe you should have tried
to enter one of these houses before or
look behind
them oh oh that looks like some kind of
rapper name he's triangle raka
yo triangle
raka oh oh oh
oh oh now things look way more flat but
also not so
flat
[Music]
ooh
interesting he yo look behind
also look he's what what how many bits
is this guys we we need to make
clarifications here we're in fredd now
he looks hella fine in
[Music]
fredd is he shi's
brother all the bits infin
bit well he's 3D I'm currently not in 3D
so he's he's got one above me he's one
up
me but look look at this
guy what's what's going on the
[Music]
warrior
Min is he back to normal is he friendly
now oh look at his fancy hair well your
hero seems to have come to his senses
what are you doing going to do
now I have an emergency requesting
backup requesting the
backup what are those
bicycles look like actually okay from
the side they look look like um those
like one one or like upwards bicycles
what are you doing you probably still
have no idea what's going on but rest
assured I'll put you to sleep in no time
go back to your
dreams no I want to stay
awake okay battle feature
unlocked
uh noal attack left click evade right
click I'm looking at myol memo raging
Destroyer minion and wise double speed
he's got two baseball
bats in neot Tokyo there will be
sometime there sometimes will be enemies
blocking your way a battle will engage
in case of an enemy encounter can now
use left click to deal damage to
opponents for continuous tapping you can
deliver a series of consecutive attacks
yeah you can play this with controller
too by the way
uh press and hold right click for
character characters to dash right click
to
Dash or L shift right yeah when dashing
the character can move quickly while
maintaining distance from the
enemy when there's sufficient amount of
evasion gge hit right click or L shift
for characters to execute an evasion
evading right before an enemy LS can
enemy attack LS can turn this into
perfect evasion no find attack uhoh
he's going to hit me or what he's got a
lot of HP okay maybe oh there you go now
I did it yeah the first time I invited
into the wrong ah the wrong direction no
no
no not perfect but I mean good
enough this
F
no please don't kill me in the tutorial
please don't kill me in the
tutorial thanks for warning
me who okay I'm fine I'm fine I've
called
up no yeah
y y ow no I hear a ringing in my
ear That's So
Close well I me for the first ever fight
that's a bit rough q
q action skill but it didn't they didn't
teach me yet but maybe I could have done
it oh you're not going to ride those
what a waste it would look
funny you okay bro oh wow he's got some
deep deep I uh bags or more honestly it
looks more like he got punched real
hard funky hair I like him they all got
funky nice hair H not bad I didn't
expect a trapped princess to be able to
fight
Princessa excuse me I am a
hero what's with this guy
who are you H looks like you're finally
ready to talk first we're here because
you're cute twin
tail sorry my cat she's so
cute sorry sorry chunky wonky is meowing
a lot
uhoh I'm I'm
scared I'm so
popular oh why made no
friendly who are
you
cute childhood friends
he we're we're but don't worry seems
like you haven't remembered everything
yet well I suppose that's to be
expected what's going
on my childhood friends you two are not
from the village
though
a how long have I been gone to
them oh they must think I'm crazy now
standing in front of these
like uh paper houses I'm like uh you're
you're not from the village I I'm from
this Village this is a real Village I'm
not crazy you
are he was crazy
once crazy I was crazy
once hi chalky
wony come to think of it there never was
a village in this in the first place oh
you you realize already everything I've
seen was just props then what did being
a hero even mean it was your true Neo
imagination they locked me in a shoe
box a shoe box in September a shoe box
in 21st of September and 21st of
September made me go crazy crazy I was
crazy
[Music]
once they L me in a shoe box a shoe box
in September a shoebook in the 21st of
September and 21st of September makes me
crazy crazy that was crazy
once I don't know what's real
anymore what are you blabbering about
you seem a bit off bro it's not his
fault though after all he's been locked
up in this so-called Village all this
time and he's been looking at it from a
somewhat Bird's point of view so of
course he didn't see that those were
flat
things for 2 years to be
[Music]
exact
for I like this feeling of Despair feels
familiar
[Music]
[Laughter]
desare they are all Pawns of my game I
see them all
[Music]
very y Naka no matter what happens you
will always be my best best
[Music]
Playmate we must find out
he good pretty
good he's still very Cho he's still like
narrating his
feelings needs to take his meds
man whoa is that the
god that's been manipulating me oh is
that the Demon Lord I thought I was the
Demon Lord they called me
ma all well I hope we're not getting
into a fight I don't think I can do that
looking at my tutorial fight
[Music]
well how long was I sleeping this time
I like how he's also very CH he only has
one glove and he holds it gently ever so
gently yeah let's go
I like this
background I like the mix of
like
everything I wish I had a beep I don't
know if I have a beep on the
soundboard a a f a monkey
who what who called who a
monkey Q that's his name
Q you got you don't have a better name
than
that
than huh eight other allies are the
resistance huh
City oh that doesn't really look like
Tokyo to me how far in the future is
this I thought it was near future
that's that's very far in the
future I
mean
uh-huh well at least in this case it
also looks like we're floating in the
sky so maybe that wasn't so fake after
all people walking around in the sky
might may have really been in my
imagination
oh oh what this whole thing is like
controlled and taken over by the en by
enemies are we in there
we're in it right now right can we go to
the Earth
he seems so knowledgeable now didn't he
a moment ago like wasn't he kind of
confused about their
presence oh
well accept it accept
true
H do you hear her
hi no she's a baby chunky
wonky what is
it she ran away with
a cute
[Music]
Invasion on the
surface oh she came back already
I'm trying to
focus you're already streaming again
yeah good
morning sponsorship
baby yeah I told you so
oh last one did you guys run away you
[Music]
cowards see you also have memory
problems
[Music]
stop fighting teenage
boys I kind of remember I kind of I just
had a fight
let's ask about the
boss I saw him in a
vision that's pretty epic that
one-on-one Showdown there that must be
pretty epic maybe we get to do that at
the end of the game again
yeah yeah I I could
guess everything I was experiencing in
those eight bit or whatever was a mirage
too there
he
for her saying you like that makes me
like kind
of think of I am
[Music]
Miss but it's just his
name PE
yay
peace
okay can we walk in the sky
now Escape pods
okay
ah I see
it's a
[Music]
r exciting
oh no I know for a fact I'll be the one
protecting you guys the
end I'm the protagonist I'll go in front
of you
guys okay maybe just for now I'll I'll
leave it to you guys a little bit
[Music]
sorry my character has been reset
because I lost my
memories oh okay so I'll be on my own
anyway thought was going to say
they're running so fast with the B bro
hey hey hey
hey
bro I forgot to use my legs it
seems ohing ding ding interesting we
have like some
Venus wao oh
cool
uhuh locaa is that my
outfit I want more is there different
outfits I can change it
to exting where's the cash shop where is
it nothing to see here but there's
challenge item compatible monsters first
aid kit training materials what's
this oh messages on my phone oh nothing
there for
now okay here we go I can run
now uh oh dear but I can't go down huh
oh who are they fighting y yeah there's
the there's the cute
white white haired girl that I saw
oh what is this I pick it up why about
this someone seems to be defeated seem
to be defeated by 24 tribe
speed ah
oh is this
cie it really it leaves these
behind H okay let's fight
bro wa bro
nobody healed
me call also died a lot okay thank God
nobody healed me game
over bro where do I get to
restart I didn't have healing items okay
restart the same battle from the
beginning okay okay thank
God ow hey I was right clicking
though I was bro
hey I hey doesn't react fast
enough there we go there we go there we
go there we go I have I just attack
right did I do
it oh is my stamina bar empty is it
because I'm dashing around
okay I want it I want this
one trash can can I open
it multi-purpose fabric can I cover my
wounds with that uhoh I'm I'm certainly
going to
die did I walk by
a y he's got a big
Shield okay action skill two can now hit
e to execute another action skill you
those action skill two can deflect most
enemy attacks when executed at the same
instance mm it's like a
block cuz it's deflecting this action
functions as another key method to avoid
enemy attacks aside from evasion observe
enemy movement and practice executing
deflect in this
battle
okay that just seems like a normal
attack pretty good one
though ow oh it didn't work my stamina
was probably too
low where's my which one's my stamina uh
I guess the well load up okay okay
okay
okay well well well well let's
retry no wonder there's so many dead
bodies around
there
[Music]
orbs wo wo wo wait zero zero zero is it
always zero no hit me
W let's go let's go let's
go W that's what they wanted to
[Music]
see ah it's too late bring up do it
again do it again buddy
oh wow I was quite early on that one
damn they really wanted
[Applause]
early
uhoh huh good
enough ah no I was waiting
for
Dam
D I almost want hit
away
no okay okay I'm getting I'm getting
there
[Music]
hey I'm pressed
it damn it damn it need to be
faster not the perfect timing
but wait where is this cool down I don't
know where I can see the cool down
he's I got to be so careful okay I hate
these Shield shielded enemies
already they're
bullies okay just just go around
him oh my HP is pretty low again though
we're good we're good we're good we're
fine yeah just got to go around
him okay ooh what is this control P does
it open up one of the locks wait I can't
oh there we go hit to stop spinning
circuit but connected circuit to fix
the
oh there we go
clear aha
aha but yeah okay there's a chest here
interesting open
up weird my e button just sometimes
doesn't work I
guess but hey there's another chest over
there
ooh bicycle but what about this thing I
want to look at that all right let's
fight the bicycles
[Applause]
he's scared of me he's running away from
me what why my HP so
low ah so much doy doie in this game but
not the not the nice doy doie
come on you can do it you can do it yeah
oh he switched over to the other one so
I guess the other one dead
now okay okay okay good
fight good fight B Dodgers a lot are you
going to say dodge less I dare
you I dare you to say
it okay here we
go what's going going on over here who
is that cute
girl tell me more about her is she the
one in my
thumbnail my God we have so many cute
allies H who's who's pink
hair yeah they were walking in the air
no
no you didn't really mistake
that oh you're finally here I was stared
to worry that you've gotten lost
honestly if you were going to be late
you could have at least contacted us
first
voice I want to hear that
voice
cute I'm going to die we shut it down
and blew up the master controls it
should be rendered useless for
now oh he's got a voice
okay man look at his bling
bling this is
AI what a name
he call he calls me a legendary hero I
must be
special a legendary
hero what it was
Jor keep on calling me that I'll fake it
till I make
it so many friends
already oh my God she
cute I like her design her hair is so
fluffy and
long and I love the
ribbons oh I like
her help guys help help help help give
me a good pickup
line I like her she looks unstable yeah
for a little bit like
huh eat
me I got some herbs do I really have
them I thought they were just in my
head she likes it easy to
please oh my God I'm so in love
he looks hardcore scary look at his
beard look at this little beard fig
tail I
mean I don't know that part is so cute
the rest of you look so
hardcore oh my God
timing timing is of the
essence yeah his hair looks fresh looks
like he just went to the
hairdresser group fight yeah fighty
battle cool cool cool cool cool
then I won't be suffering so much maybe
how big is this
battle are they all in my group are we
doing like separate
groups no
way oh okay
free starting from this battle you'll be
able to fight alongside your allies
thank God Su is able to recover the HP
of allies as well as diverting the
attention of the enemies if you are in a
pinch don't hesitate to fall back and
create space between yourself and the
enemy and leave the fighting to sui Su
is the girl or him don't remember your
allies skills may help change the
situation of the battle so it's all
right to reposition yourself and avoid
the battle temporarily oh God oh God
yeah B to the heal that's a big
heal did you see that
perfect
avoid
evade ow
oh more enemies okay we got a big
one oh this is fun with more people
especially having a a full party is
three people the full party I
wonder so having a Healer is definitely
good
yeah he e just needs to be a lot earlier
it
seems car like a lot
earlier ow heal please where's my heal
healer ah
healer
healer I was on cool down well where can
I see that out four 3 two one I see
now for the
power sick pretty cool pretty
cool
yeah were we did we really do that
a there's so many
people so pinched or
strange I'm clearing it faster than them
really no way
don't make me feel so
good oh cuz you were being G kept
gaset thank God
baseball excuse me extreme
baseball no don't worry I
know how could I
forget of course I
was of course I
was no I was
is is batting the part where you bat
like you don't catch it you're the one
yeah
right I'm the best baseball
player great great thank you you're
you're really good at explaining game
mechanics girl
M that's a big relief thank you I feel
so so
secure
[Music]
for has she even said the full word out
loud
yet I I don't even realize probably that
it's baseball do
I what do I think it
[Music]
is caring a I have really
can
[Music]
we her voice sounds very familiar I
wonder who else she
[Music]
was
oh huh
[Music]
wait that sounds as if but there's a
danger to it and it might go wrong us
returning to the
[Music]
surface is it going to be
problematic that flag he
is this automatic by the
[Music]
way I wouldn't do it with the fists
normally but okay
[Music]
um
sure
spicy what about you two why just
me we should make it more clear
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you although
that might be even worse now as
[Music]
a look at him
for
okay don't die don't die don't
die oh look at those broken
bicycles all right here we go AG
toi overflowing trash industrial alcohol
multi-purpose fabric my babies my girl
my cutie PTI we're all done here no
let's get out of here no need to go all
the way down to the low levels how about
we just blow a hole in the ground I like
her
spirit why
not they men something about you being a
legendary hero seriously that sounds
kind of cool but hey my big brother is
still cooler than you don't get carried
away just because you're a hero oh
they're all buying it now I'm officially
a hero now
y could KN five number one number
six hey what's up you want something if
not let's keep moving that's not the way
to talk to others sorry yo Q isn't the
most friendly person but he's not as
scary as he looks please try to get
along with him no I am as scary as I
look how dare
you oh what was that H did I do baseball
just now
he's blocking it
out get
[Music]
down M need some help over there no
problem need some help over there too
I'm pretty
overpowered hey oh more B your bicycles
arrived too late if they came earlier
you could have still
escaped no more Escape for
you oh
yeah I'm I'm ironically really good
really I'm getting better you really
saying that
[Music]
you're so nice
chat yeah it gets much easier with a
Healer
uhoh well probably just straight for now
oops no I was going
straight oh it's fast oh it gets even
faster oh it got slower again there you
go
clear cute ah we can go down now should
we go down well let's get the chest
first and
everything
because here we go another fight for me
to
win I'm coming
enemy arrival
no yeah I'm not I'm not a big fan of the
song either I saw the performance uh
some
like some recent American award
or music show or so I was
like not
do I already get rid of some of their HP
when I do not know is there any point in
hitting them first with
uh to go into battle cuz in other games
sometimes there is a point
with did I dodge successfully or what
ow yeah I'm out of
stamina well thanks for the
heal do it do
it what I thought that was I thought
that skill helped me
like
deflect I did it at the same time as he
ATT but okay I see how it is you lied to
me you lied to
me too soon N I feel like it was like
perfect it's just unable attack
yeah another control
panel okay here we
go that one's so fast
oh
[Music]
God that's pretty
difficult
pretty not easy I will tell you I'll
have you know
okay here we go here we
go hey what's wrong with you
bicycle my bicycle is
malfunctioning are they even if I'm not
fighting that enemy are they warning me
for the big enemies big attacks huh
aha you stop that laser
now I shall not tolerate
it you haven't come really far there
have
you without my help can't do anything
pretty good I would say when I have
stamina I can dodge well enough now I
have no
stamina there's like uh skill points or
so that you can put into stamina with
some kind of some kind of improvement to
to make you have more
stamina go these are strong W I need
some healing now for real thank
you wow they ganging up on that bro he's
my healer leave him alone
come on
die there we go yeah the battle system
is really
fun I'm liking
it and the fights are not too easy
there's definitely a challenge
there
mhm very fun
is it a floppy
disc close
[Music]
enough emotions such as despair
okay we need a card reader time to hit
thank
you pretty nice of you even though you
look only for
me another membership thank you
you just want to see his butt don't
youall he wants me to bend down and pick
everything up from the ground I wonder
why there's only one good reason for
that you want to see my
butt I knew I can tell I know your
strategy I've used it myself
before it's a good trick just throw
things on the ground to have people pick
them up for you see the
butt tension represents the moral of
either side and can be confirmed through
the gges on the top of the screen the
higher the moral the higher the chances
of winning and vice versa it is an
important element that will greatly
affect the results of the battle okay I
don't understand it yet tension face
extreme tension can be increased or
decreased for factors such as attacking
enemy units when tension reaches a
certain value the tension phas will
increase when the tension phe reaches a
certain level attention card is like a
like a special attack when it fills up I
can activate it probably make full use
of this card and seek Victory against
might def foes seems to be something
like you know a special attack do I need
to equip the card or is it already
automatically equipped uhhuh
tippity
tappity are these equip tension
cards but even close attack is attention
card
now is it it is maybe it is said that
tension cards are formed by memories of
people you can equip up to five tension
cards in
battle aside from those that can provide
direct enhancement to certain abilities
there's also cards that are capable of
greatly affecting the battle conditions
you can treat tension cards as items
that can change the rules of a battle
there are many types of tension cards
check out their effects and obtaining
new
cards wait so if I was not carrying
this close attack when a character is a
certain distance Clos to the Target
increase their damage bonus
ah yeah sure surely there's also some
card that like increases my stamina and
stuff as we just talked about what is
this when party consists of free members
when none are knocked out increase
attack Point by 133% increase defense
Point defense Point by
11.25 the equipped ones are grade out I
guess yeah select attention
card recover 2.25% of own maximum RP
every 3 seconds for 15
[Music]
seconds I I'll do
oh The Shield The Shield resistance is
equivalent to
6.75% of the operating characters
maximum HP and decrease damage by I
don't know that sounds good I'll take
that so now I have the maximum of cards
I think in my set I'll just keep the
others the same for
now oh is it ahuh are we done I think I
think we're
done yeah Shield sounds really useful
okay all
right o
chest let's go my favorite
girl blow up all the enemies take them
out before they take you out hey do you
know if you attack the enemy first the
battle will go smooth I so I was
wondering about that especially if you
attack them without them noticing fast
feeling ever okay I she telling me to
sneak on this guy hey he hey it will go
smoother huh is that so I wish you could
start from back wa what the happen what
did I just
do what did I do that was
safe I'm not sure what I
did bring on some more enemies come
on CH out at all was it my Parry the
perfect
Parry oh bicycle
ble
extreme an extremely dangerous
status please be extra careful when the
enemy reaches maximum tension their
attack p has may change and become even
more
ferocious enemies in this status can
deliver deadly attacks that can decimate
the whole party in an instant T face
stream will deplete over time focus on
inviting enemy attacks for the time
being and you will eventually find the
opportunity to strike back okay oh we're
starting off like that that's not
really evading evading
evading is it
over how is it the ex I have to wait for
all those free
bars to the
plete why did I run into
it I think my allies are not really
evading much
oh chain
skill only the first one okay certain
attacks May Grant impairment on enemies
when the other operating characters
grants impairment to enemies allies will
have a chance to execute their chain
skills combo attacks with allies can be
performed through granting impairments
suuki is a character that attacks from a
long range and specializes in granting
impairments she is the key member of
this party to initiate chain well wait
so what I can't have a chain skill
unless an impairment has been
granted can I grant one through granting
impairments to enemies continuously you
you may activate chain skill combos with
your
allies how what's is there a button for
it chain skills can increase a great
amount of tension so remember to
activate as many chain as possible is
there a button for it though woo okay
let's go
[Music]
well I'm just going to fight as per
usual bottom left says one on my left oh
well wasn't necessary in this case maybe
in this
fight this should go
smoothly otherwise I'm fin
complain
oh what what's that
bar
wow what's
happening should I have pressed
[Music]
something what was that that was a
perfect Parry
again just chain chain chain chain
chain during extreme phase we oh look at
look at
that w w w w I don't care about you
extreme
[Music]
face good heal oh wow I what how am I
continuously activating this one Chrome
is it my beautiful Parry or should I not
get too cocky is pretty
extreme oh I should have I should have
pressed I thought they would do it on
their own
okay okay okay no
problem next
time s she's so cute you want to know
how to increase your tension during
battle right it's written on your face
so allow me to give you the answer the
key lies in chain skills chain skills
are combo attacks in other words it's
the proof of the pudding what the trust
and friendship between you and your
allies if the free of you Mr y Muki and
Mr Su are fighting together then the
chain will start from Muki granting the
enemy status
ailments n hold thanks for repeating
everything I already learned ah sorry I
was trying to talk to the trash why are
you feeling like I'm talking to you that
don't be so mean to
[Music]
yourself oh I feel like there's a big
fight coming up could it
be just a normal fight
[Music]
woo oh okay I was looking at that at the
bottom I was seeing a a countdown there
wait free she didn't get to attack I was
looking if there was a prompt but I
didn't see a
promp that's pretty cool
though a lot of flashy stuff going on
but like feels good to
activate attention face extrem I don't
care do I look like I
care woohoo
[Music]
I'm coming for
you I'm Coming For You enemy
Ring Hey Oh My My Chain attack is about
to
start oh no never mind what was that
countdown
now there's a different
countdown oh there we
go it didn't work this time cuz he was
already
dying ah was it the cool down the the
numbers that I was looking at
maybe kotan this one has an actual
name oh [\h__\h] should have oh no oh no oh
no enemy Dan face
what you want me to dodge when they're
extreme oh not me I'm a
hero I won't let
you play with me like
that one
[Applause]
[Music]
yes extrem
again fck
no they got me they got me justce once
I'll let you have it just this once in
this world enemies are usually very
strong and can easily deal heavy damage
thus it is always important to watch
your step to avoid yeah yeah yeah don't
tell me about evading I know how to
evade no no
no
shade rud
[Music]
okay okay I don't like this bicycle guy
no I want to like the bicycle guy wait
how do I switch [\h__\h] I
wonder and number three
[Applause]
extrem thank God they healed me right
before that
[Music]
sorry I was going to run away but I was
a bit too
slow oh so close to the end power
yeah oh no I'm embarrassing myself
failing too
much let's get the guy
first I don't like his balls wa that was
a powerful
[Music]
bow enemy tension phase has been
decreased than God oh all right good
time a better time can never RVE this is
the one time for your tension face link
attack
[Music]
whatever okay be
careful heal me he he he thank
you oh what the
hell he he
please okay then I'll I'll just um punch
you on your butt if you if I'm not
getting a hit thank
[Music]
you extreme again how often do get to be
extreme there's certainly playing
extreme baseball
here but we also get another link attack
and the battle's over first uh first
times the
charm damn that was
something that was quite something does
it go down
here it does is it a dead end cuz I you
know I always want to make sure that I
check out every corner
my friends want to talk to her
again it's suffocating to be in a place
filled with hostility I wish I could get
out of here as soon as possible to get
some fresh air that's said it's pretty
much the same wherever you go in this
world whether it's in the present or the
past she's your favorite really well you
know who's my favorite so far the twin
tail
girl but
hey I wonder if these are all the
characters or if we're getting
introduced to even more thank
you oh
dear for baby
yeah thanks for the membership gift woo
I locked in guys I was locked in in case
you haven't noticed here we
[Music]
go I wonder if the boss that I'm
supposed to fight today in this uh
stream is like at the end of all of this
or even further you guys probably know
if you watched Callie's stream or
so I miss the chest
no I'll go back if I
can Trash tribe it's a pleasure meeting
you master you there is something I
would like to inform you about there's a
very strong enemy head oh you might fall
again oh my we sincerely look forward to
meeting Master you on the surface when
it comes well it sounds like it might be
the boss that I have to
fight I was told if I have some time
left over after the boss I should try
out the
baseball how did I miss it it's like
literally in front of
me I got some cucumbers on my eyes or
something or
tomatoes
Tom
television yeah I know the baseball part
is after I know I
know I don't mind trying it
out but are you saying the bosses now do
I not get a heal or something before the
boss
oh look at all these
[Music]
deaths took you nine tries to beat it
it's hard
wow to well now we have feel in the
party
that' be so
cool gets
to I love
that back is silently lurking thank
you wame let me fight let me fight
I was hoping she would talk
again need to hear more of
her she's so cute
[Music]
brutal that's the future guys satellites
shooting
us honestly I can see
it space War
true each hit takes five
years damn
same a little
bit give me a
break it's 745
here oh
[Music]
what how do we go to the
Howes it
work yeah both me and you just woke
[Music]
up ground P
incoming oo ooh
wow
she she's still alive
guys wait she gives me n
Vibes or shall I say rock on
baby rock and
roll hey let's go let's go let's go
she's like that yeah yeah she's got that
childlike energy the
yay o we get some time to like rearrange
our cards or whatever but let's just go
for
it what do you mean still streaming I'm
streaming again I stopped quite early
yesterday and I slept quite early
final judgment Andrew here
we
go what is dead what's that dead
[Music]
bar good that I stayed
away did I miss
he's like rollis
skating I W roller skate in M
skate
oh it's already almost like 50%
down what is
that can't touch this
ooh I I anticipated that huh what the
what's a dead bar what wait what is it I
never know what but I wish they wouldn't
do this on Z because my keyboard is like
always something else is it Y is it Z
it's always different and so I forget
which one is German keyboard which one
is English
keyboard ultimate skills are now
available you can execute them my
hitting de should try both buttons y or
Z get lucky ultimate skills can be
charged by attacking enemies
repetitively use ultimate skill is able
to deal a huge amount of damage to the
opponent and allow his allies to execute
their train skills ooh launch a
full-fledged assault to deal great
damage to the
opponent uh hit
lctl and2 or LC and3 to execute allies
oh God why such combinations okay the
ultimate chain skills basically so this
and then one and two and three uh wait
only two only two or three ah I see I
see I see two for the upper bro and
three for the right
girl
uh now
when when when was I to U maybe they
need to load it up first maybe the
countdown is for
that and now I'm distracted
is there a second space or something cuz
I almost got him
oh kill baseball time or not
[Music]
tce a purple outline
okay oh ah there we go I see now he's
got three health bars okay we got one
down
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's let's Go's let
go
yeah set set wherever it is pressing
both buttons
again thankfully the other one is not
corresponding to anything
no no bro that's a lot of HP you're
taking from me no it's doing so
well yo he took like 70% of my HP with
that attack was good that I was always
dodging that so
[Music]
far I'm so far
good first try though
Dam all right here we go
again
ow oh this time it didn't do as much
maybe he gets stronger throughout the
his his
phases oh
extrem that attack may be really strong
but oh it gets him stuck in the floor
for a while so I don't know buddy your
defenses are low on
that yo that link attack just brought me
really close to
him it got me in danger I was keeping
distance here we go second death
[Music]
no problem no problem yeah is there
enemy attack pattern does he always do
that after the pew pew
pew was it always is it always after the
PE PE
PE okay then I
shall okay ch
[Music]
here we go is he about to do the
PE
uh-oh not sure what he's doing
hey let's
go I couldn't get out of it with my
stamina heal heal thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank
you my first try was better oh here we
go here we go as long as I'm far away
from him doing that oh he's not doing it
this time though there you go okay so he
does he and then he does like a couple
of wings here
there all
right distance
distance first Pace almost
over ow what the
hell
oh yeah yeah why
not and he should be
done come
on with the first face come on good okay
okay okay here we go second
space uh-oh distance yeah oh now he
doesn't do the the swinging around uh L
free lots to do lots of buttons to push
this might be easier with a controller
for
sure oh no extreme maybe I should stay
further away from him
green what is this bubble am I being
protected oh [\h__\h] I should have stayed
away I should have stayed away I almost
died it's ah it's still one from my
attention card oh sick yeah Heal Me Heal
Me Heal Me Heal Me heal me or else I'll
die heal me uhoh I don't know if that's
a good idea getting so close to him now
I'll die when this is over this cut
scene
a get out oh I got
healed get out of
there uh way too risky who's my low
stamina all hey Dodge
bro I wish I had like a distance attack
but she's she's she's going for it she's
she's having a good time why is she
always got the special attacks the other
bro has never done one so
far oh my
[Music]
God okay almost face
over this face is almost
over F oh extreme no no no no no
no he he he he he he he he heal heal
heal heal
he last phase last phase oh chain attack
let's go let's go he's stuck in the
ground let's give it
[Music]
everything okay get out of here too
scary I don't want to fail now
bro bro bro I swear I'm trying to dodge
but I'm just too late my input is too
late
uh-oh there we
go well she's ready again she's always
ready this girl was born ready look be
aw Le if she
died almost done him oh God oh
God don't die oh okay okay chance
chance let's not let it go to
[Music]
waste I'm pushing all your buttons
baby yo stay away yep yep y yep yep and
gires gr boss time has arrived once
again kill
[Applause]
him careful careful careful careful
careful she can do it she can do it I'm
full HP
now that was so risky so risky that I
went for it I fought wait there's one
more
face wait what oh I want
the I'm trying to dodge I swear but I
have noise is stamina
no that's so
close all right baby all right we're on
yeah I no I know I could have just ran
but then I accidentally pressed attack
and then it it dragged you it's P you
in oh
okay ow
ow don't count this
one don't count this one
please no no no no no no no no no no
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
we straight for me
there all right here we
go do that somehow
[Music]
picking up that Mexican dance cat meme
right
now I wish I had more stamina
[Music]
set it three times cuz it's important
woohoo go for it go for it go for it
he's stuck in the
ground
[Music]
okay ah too stupid to dodge that look
here we go new phase apparently there's
four phases wa I thought he only had
threee but yeah
easy to Parry the Spin Attack maybe I
should go try it out
huh oh he's stuck in the ground perfect
timing to get close to
him okay thanks for distancing your stth
from
[Music]
let's
go no please let me leave let me
leave heal
please uhoh no please don't die please
don't die I literally could not get out
of that no no no no
no this time you'll definitely win you
were wrong but
it's fun it's
fun yeah I didn't have stamina and I was
trying to
run can't I I literally can't Parry the
missiles is that so bro please don't
count it again that's not fair such a
bully don't count
it I can do better I can to better why
was my first try to bed I'm trying too
hard okay here we
[Music]
go go
did she
miss I think I really can't Parry
them uh-oh
uh-oh just dodge no no I guess no I mean
I'm I'm not trying to Parry I'm trying
to
dodge but even that
somehow oh I see what's up if I have
that attack ready while he's spinning
totally worth
it oh he's doing it
again a a to the Y A to the Y A to the Y
he's he keeps on repeating it he really
wants to do his move to its fullest
potential but when keep on interrupting
it does he always want to go back to
it
uh wait but I should still get out of
here even if it's that's not not a good
idea go away
yeah okay good let's
leave calm
down okay see okay I can do it it turns
out I can do it okay
now my turn
baby give me my time to
shine time to leave time to lead abort
Mission okay what's
next ah damn
it ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
thanks beans I wish I
[Music]
had quite busy like this no
no
[Music]
yeah but I'm learning more about out
this fight I was doing really good but
yeah now I lost track of what's coming
next Dodge forward
okay forward forward can I
okay I'm going to lock in now I
[Music]
try
for
for ah when I do it from behind I guess
he doesn't care for it
foree let's go let's go let's goe
[Music]
next
base o uh but he's going to do it let's
go away let's go away I'm
scared oh he's dling
[Music]
it she's so
cute I wonder what the other people's
attacks look
like do the spin do the
spin that's
fine how come he's not doing a thing
maybe because I'm not giving him a good
opening window
good am
I he to the
y' follow up nice
follow for real oh s we're comboing him
real
hard W we're on Extreme what's that mean
for
us you almost had me cuz I was going to
get really cocky now
I'm out of here
oh get
stuck Get Wrecked I
mean he doing it
again we're on a roll we're so on a
roll let's let's get
away ah
no I'm so sorry I don't know why I ran
back into it I fumbled I fumbled so
hard a but this is
fun they had so many
combos let get to away into the attack
our time
dead did time that one though
drop my digital spaghetti oh how I love
to drop my digital spaghetti you know
me
wa
carrying quite fun in this
game f face
too oh [\h__\h] spaming mashing buttons just
now I'm a lucky little
be what are you going to
do this is so action I love
it very difficult but I love the action
was I too
[Music]
late a little bit too late oh get away
get away oh oh we wanted to chain okay
sure where was my part in this oh I'm
lost no no no no let me no no no no no
let me I want to go away oh okay it was
after somehow
can we somehow cancel out that
big ground pound attack of
his oh standing around
ow
[Music]
again face almost done
sure why not get behind him while we at
[Music]
it yeah the missile one I'm very close
to him uhoh wait it's it's after right
it won't hit me right it won't hit me
right it's fre
baby y
very scary very
scary I'm
scared thank for
heal this must be so sticky
online play like if some a real person
could control the other characters that
would be so
sick please Implement online
play stream
that's really mean to bring me
back right in front of his speed attack
just really got to hope that I can catch
him with
a a Dodge Parry
something oh [\h__\h] I'm scared don't tell
me that I was not I was not even looking
I was just chilling walking in now you
put fresh on
me got to s
not getting me this time
buddy but I am pretty low on HP you got
to be careful
[Music]
and I'm dodging away I don't know what's
going to happen next oh
actually stop and oh I got this one
going for
me okay let's be careful don't want to
fail
now now it's the time now's the [\h__\h]
time baby
can't believe it can't believe
it no
way no
[Music]
no I didn't even get greedy I was
dodging away
[Music]
fore
but I'm feeling more and more like an
well oiled
machine this
is feels
good I'm surprised it's not frustrating
honestly just my voice when I scream
kind of hurts
but I'm definitely more than most other
games able to
read patterns normally I really suck at
[Music]
that no but for real like what I would
legitimately play
this or like in the Stream like a nor
stream
[Music]
like it's it's normally stuff like this
really
um frustrate me SE other games where you
die a
lot but here I'm thriving just like the
Phoenix I
am uh yeah
okay feel like I'm definitely getting
him down
faster definitely got a feeling for
it power
a I'm not letting you go
yet we have an
appointment one more come
on you and
me let's battle it
out oh you want another one let's see
can I maybe too
late but here I come again and I doded
away I DOD away cuz I'm too scared of
that
attack that is my Nemesis but I know
when you do it I
know I know when you do it
[Music]
buddy oh you didn't do it this time
interesting but now yeah there we go
there we go that's what I like to see I
like to see a pattern
and number one and number two and number
three
baby oh baby a
triple ouch get out of
there no no yo they healed me in in the
middle of that didn't day
heal please another heal how are they
always full HP like how are they doing
it are they ever like in danger of
dying please heal me please please bro
new phase but please heal me
otherwise you little [\h__\h] why would you
not heal
me I want to fight to okay there you go
but I'm so
[Music]
scared with one HP it would be really
stupid to get in
there get out of
there oh he did it
again he loves that
attack what did he just do it
twice What in close
succession that's so mean is that what I
have to expect in the last
[Applause]
base throw it all at
him and then run away
let I had that
ready use it okay
distance oh okay again again
bam going to do it though go away I'll
I'll I'll I'll go away so you going to
do it twice
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't believe I just very
dead and that was his
death
I that I was so scared I could have
messed up so
bad
oh
crazy he almost got me got if I would
have
missed I was just like hey I got my
Parry ready might as well throw it in
there see what
happens
[Music]
wow this might be one of the most fun
sponsorships I've ever
had
damn damn I'm saying that genuinely holy
[\h__\h] if the whole game is like that wow
wow
bro
crazy crazy let's talk to the girls that
was a great battle I was inrig by skills
thank you I mean I know I died a few
times but I it's still very very very
fun it's good to see that these kids are
strong G you could have taken it down
instead of just standing there yeah why
did you guys not help H this immersion
of having a bigger party but only only
the small party helps me wow you
defended the big guy
awesome you've got potential with
special training you can become good
mercenaries thank
you you were able to defeat the robot
thanks to the tens cards I gave you oh
my God you should show your grud
properly I hate him I'll never put him
in my party how arrogant can you just
give a straight compliment shut up I
deserve to be properly acknowledged for
my contributions I can't believe my
cutie patootie is hanging out with this
guy
bro that's expected of the legendary
hero and his allies you've defeated the
oh wait it's a blue hair guy talking oh
well whatever you've defeated the demon
Lord's minion
brilliantly hey Kazuki sorry I went a
bit too far congratulations that was a
great battle what I can't tell who's
talking when even though it's written
there sorry there's no girls in this
group I don't want to I don't want to
talk to you but okay impressive I can't
believe you defeated that robot you guys
are really strong Mr
kurona I could have taken down an enemy
like that all by myself don't get too
carried away you
guys wait that was both talking him I
don't even know I don't even
know that was
crazy that was
crazycap pods how convenient
[Music]
oh why you speak
oh yeah I thought I was the
demon I need to reach max level
first can't have final boss in early
game what are you
doing the plot fiens it goes fast
yeah snap
something
baseball these mind
games my nose is
running cuz we're his play it not
playmat Playmates
creepy
hands yo those could give him a massage
24/7 actually I want those
hands if only I was the Demon Lord and
I'd have those
[Music]
hands
got h
[Music]
oh not so
easy you weren't done
huh want us to listen some
more hey no
hey oh
oh no oh
no oh
no we got a psychopath in front of us
[Music]
that's
destru oh of course you
can of course
it yeah
actually that girl is a mix of Ren and
R got some fetishes excuse him excuse
the daro
guy how would you put
yeah yeah
yeah everything's a game to
you but let me break your
guys I am playing a game right now this
is a
game I'm very aware of
it oh
[Music]
no no
no no not
quite I like games but I don't risk my
life with them
fore
[Music]
it be like that sometimes
the surf is
wor sorry everybody was waiting for me
huh kept you waiting huh sorry
little boy you need to eat more
broccoli oh
is my is that why we have so many allies
because they're going to get less and
less and less over time for this
game normally you get more and more and
more party members
for an
RPG is it the other way around in this
game honey what is this why is it
locked get uh fight L and everyone
create an opening get on the Escape pods
that haven't been destroyed there's
there are some find
another let me use this is this like is
this when you clear the game once and
you get an extra option or
so yeah I mean it makes sense yeah with
this kind of
game can
we got their
wearen how foolish would it be of him to
leave some behind
yeah no we will
die certainly we will
die
why okay
oh now we get the Lo
option we
don't okay
[Music]
uhoh don't tell me they'll be the first
victim
oh
[Music]
no oh
no yo
oh no that's so evil
[Music]
wait
but
huh oh they're going to die they're
going to
[Music]
die
uhoh both leads to the same probably
yeah
no don't look at me like that right
before you
die that's so funny when everything's so
serious they're like you don't even know
what extreme basball
is we like to play baseball here I like
to kill people and have fun with you
guys like that but I love baseball too
priorities
guys no no no no no no
[Applause]
no what a crazy kind of head
shot
[Music]
no
foree fore
oh oh oh oh oh no no no I really like
her push her and take the hit yourself
you idiot oh no no what you have to do
is GTI GTI cuz he doesn't want to kill
me right we just have to
hug hug her for freaking oh my God then
he will stop this
shot
no just become one
he will not shoot because for some
reason he wants him to stay
alive
Noe holy
[\h__\h] okay
okay they bleed purple interesting maybe
they're aliens maybe it's good that
they're
gone I guess we all bleed purple in this
game reminds me of the good good old
times watching the anime
yeah sure I'll play with you what choice
do I
have my be to
[Applause]
[Music]
die my God
I don't know
man this is
extreme extreme
[Music]
baseball we're retrieving our memories
now that they're
[Music]
dead what is this from
they really pushed me to play
[Music]
baseball Japanese people really love
baseball
baseball the baseball part kind of makes
it hard for me to St serious baseball
saves Liv
[Music]
okay I'll do it for
them I'll do it for
[Music]
[Laughter]
them okay I get it I get it I get
it no more more
okay I'll I'll play baseball okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay thank
you I'll do it I'm going to ball for
them
yet
oh took you a while they had to die for
you to
understand that you need to play
baseball took you that long maybe if you
would have
[Music]
realized if you would have realized
earlier we could have avoided all of
this they were talking to you about
extreme baseball for a while now and you
just ignored everything you should have
just like asked them for a tutorial
earli
on the ball game
um like I figured we would play baseball
but I didn't think that the first time
we play baseball is against the final
boss I don't know about that
one fore
[Music]
just like brat a ball run into his face
while he's
talking and then break his mask and then
it reveals it's me I am the Demon Lord
after all it's
a
for
stream for
there is never any chance for no other
Cho oh now you'll take us down to the
ball end to the
surface okay okay
[Music]
well if only you wouldn't have freaking
broken
them
bicycles
drones more like drones huh
is this slowing down or
fall I hope
so it all comes down to baseball
guys solution to everything is baseball
baby
oh let's go let's go let's go teach me
how to play
basball want too free oh there's
the the like the in like a baseball
court is that like you know like those
I mean I heard of it many times now
you bring them back come
out it's crazy
man yeah we got to sing the opening an
that's not a baseball
bat that's a I mean it's not even a
sword
honestly versus Zer can now settle the
score of zero for XP nah it can't be
that easy we'll surely
fail it's all
[Music]
scripted it's an extreme baseball bat yo
and his friends triy to escape 24 City
but zero had predicted their every move
their means of Escape were destroyed and
Suki and S killed by Zero's lasers even
when all seemed lost there was still one
thing y had faith in with the words of
his two childhood friends that he didn't
didn't even know until 2 hours ago that
they were his childhood friends engraved
in his heart he cried out let's have a
showdown with XP one
inning okay I I really don't know how
this is going to
[Music]
work okay we have the full team
I'm number
six what does that
mean home team visiting team
[Music]
talking I'm so ready for this just
explain me the
game even the conversations are extreme
faceless get ite
of my
sister my
sister you know what I mean you know
what I
mean you guys don't get it
correct correct
I don't know if I can shoot it that far
bro they're really
stretching before playing
baseball the full long
[Music]
time I just want to play baseball
what okay then please explain to me the
rules
interesting question I don't know about
that extreme baseball is a debate where
players fight for their own beliefs what
we're
debating it is a competition as well as
a
showdown the key to this game is to re
re rebut the opponent's perspective
observe oh I'm not actually like playing
baseball like trying to like play it
properly thank you for the the gifts
observe how the responses is is it
mental
baseball how the responses can affect
the game do you see a familiar gge in XP
tension will also come into play and
affect the game conditions different
from battles the tension in xp games
will change the game progresses during
XP characters abilities can be gradually
bought out as tension changes allowing
them to dis play Stronger
skills okay what you will face multiple
multiple Mighty foes and have tons of XP
showdowns from now on this is where we
say game start good luck and have fun
[Music]
oh wait can I choose a different one
it's like not
moving I guess it's the recommended
one did he C catch it is that like bad
for me I don't understand
no I think that was good for me when the
when the when the guy catches it that's
good for me
right title drop he didn't even try to C
like playing
baseball while dising the
opponent I like it
oh you remember
something starting to
it's supposed to be tribe n bro
I suppose so but this is like a flag
again I'm going to lose
it
[Music]
what doesn't look like baseball
extreme
base the quoy mode looks like one of
those baseball gloves
he doesn't even know the power of
friendship yet which surely count in
this game
now one thing that is certain is extreme
baseball oh here we go am I dissing him
again you cannot fill up the Gap uh oh
is is it recommending me one again can I
not pressy I don't want I don't want to
try I'll show you if my emotions are
Petty or
not I Gra and lose you that doesn't even
sound like a good disc but
okay
oh W they're moving is this a home
run let's go face girly oh but she
failed no no run run run run I don't
understand how baseball works but yeah
keep on running yeah you got to get it
before he arrives I guess or so
oh
s what he got oh he got it he got the
[Music]
point is it randomized if he like in the
future
can influence whether or not he can run
through all of
it maybe by
putting people in their positions more
mindfully
wow okay he's really good at dising me I
need to come up with better
lines your team is kind of small how how
am I losing
okay yeah I mean I agree with that
sentiment
[Music]
but you're telling me to give up
okay we're not giving up of course
not defense offense wa where what am I
what what
I'm good with jpgs but I'm not good with
baseball
[Music]
chain who's the batter
isn't that the one with the stick was I
not the
B Basics I'm not playing extreme
baseball I'm playing basic baseball I
need the basics down
first I was a
pitcher what's the
B so the pitch has the
best no the pitch sure
Frozen he's got the bats the enemy in
this
case and then no wait no no no wait no
he's he's the he was the p
i pict fro ban hits okay what do we call
the guy with the
glove now I'm the pict
think you can beat
me uh aim new XP feature unlocked uhoh
aim
do can now use WD to search for the
flaws in the opponent's words adjusting
the aim should affect the game's
development what Ops will vary according
to your aim don't miss out the changes
on the screen make the most efficient
resp
[Music]
oh just because I have the brains
doesn't mean I'll neglect my emotion hey
you and your monkey business I'll prove
it to you that sounds
good yes I believe I can yes I believe I
can this this one's kind of different
because it's the only one like I don't
know if that means
anything should I try this
for let's see what the outcome will be
if it this a good choice he's
running
oh why are we running
now that was
good I want a home run
please base
baby second base I'm getting to second
base with you
[Music]
no wait okay here we go
aim just shut up my job the pros bring
Victory to the employees don't act like
you know me oh this one again has just
like several more options than the other
one but it's still like forcing me to
choose maybe they're all the right ones
because they're all purple but oh
well this one stands out to
me none of your
business next base next Bas next
Bas damn he can run
[Applause]
[Music]
save it's not force I can
choose excuse me I'm sure she has a
[Music]
name they really
I believe in her she's going to roast
him real
[Music]
good front of absolute power what can
your emotions
do would be a great answer I think but
let's see if we have
it my mother charge through a life with
ups and downs
I don't see ruthlessness as
strength a straight should and I'll
knock get out of the
[Music]
park I don't
know I'll go with this
one say here
P please work please work oh
oo looks good I don't
know
[Music]
TI
yeah can you even lose this
match good job girl
is that
bad
[Music]
oh music stop
I don't understand what you're even
saying Richard I don't I don't speak Bas
language therefore you cannot
emotionally
hurt I understand
[Music]
let's see it
then you want to hurt me with
boredom I
guess being
is bad
but kind of
lame I'll never feel bored with me on
who is me I prefer celebrating over C W
aren't you the crazy
one all right so I don't I I still don't
really understand the difference between
these
icons this is like
strong and there's the aiming
ones the brown head girl
the map yeah but the I don't know is
there does it matter in which direction
I
shoot uh okay yeah but I don't know does
it matter where I should I see the
explanation
but later
[Music]
I don't know
baseball I don't know if I'm if it's
necessary to understand
baseball I see that I see this part but
I don't understand what what will be the
best
choice I know
oh yeah it's probably scrip
ah was that boun to
happen was
that has no one in the not
normal
[Music]
for GR your
eyes
damn it's like next level
deprived looks more like your blood
vessels are all broken
I'm sure C likes that Co
I don't know where to
go or does it even does it even matter
what these phrases are
saying what should I prioritize the
direction or what these phrases are
saying like I would say this sounds the
best to me scripted so no okay
oh that looks
good and now what now oh oh
oh oh what what what that's not how you
play
baseball they're
wrestling oh I'm back to the base
[Music]
yeah that was
uh to be
expected you were
waiting like you want to play games and
stuff cuz you're bored but doesn't it
make it more boring cuz you are
controlling everything and you know the
outcome and everything and you can you
can make us lose or win however you want
isn't that what would make it more
boring cuz you have too much power over
it found a hole in your logic my friend
that's kind of nice of
him he wants me to suffer but he wants
me to have fun while I
die so considerate so
mindful that's your phrase let's see how
do we get back who who who who what my
HP oh
oh yeah I think we got to hit him with
this emotional
[Music]
strike give him back to me my
friends
no his
[Music]
hands it didn't work
one come on you're the best extreme
baseball player in the
world I don't like how you kiss
my why I want to
know he's so
KY e
[Music]
I'm interested
in finding out
how this game
balances game play we had up until the
XP the
XP how much xp do you play in this game
how much of the other
system is that his Halloween
costume wearing a freaking
blanket oh those are nine people
yeah two more no one more
so I have to like fight all of them and
win against all these eight
people of course I will
I have no choice
buddy definitely got Hunger Games Vibes
yep surpr they mentioned that is that an
actual
word movies
XG wait what what is it XG now wait what
yeah what
[Music]
uh does it
matter
gasb
G extreme gambling gambling with my life
maybe it doesn't matter it doesn't
matter
right doesn't does
it for
no no no I think I understand the very
least I think he knows more about XB
than
me don't hype me up like
[Music]
that yeah yeah
yeah yeah
but H okay wasn't what I was going to
say but sure yeah makes sense very much
sense you have no friends
buddy oh he sounds excited
actually see he doesn't want me to die
that's why I should have just hugged um
my friend when the target was on
her just completely covered
her death
ball
[Music]
oh that is certainly extreme baseball
what
[Music]
what no I can't run
away is does it say tag
this
oh
oh uh oh
oh I now remember our
dream that's my
[Applause]
[Music]
name Staying Alive
in your
face I don't think you did
it
yeah oh we get to
see some of his
face you your life where am I
dead I think I'm dead
[Music]
I'm almost dead they're going to push me
back
world
[Music]
e
fore
for
Fore foree
[Music]
then you'll be back
Le you better
be
yeah X XP
why you such an
[Music]
ass no you
are no I certainly haven't that was very
dramatic
[Music]
no don't show me that
again thanks for reminding us
[Music]
I was revived in a really nice
mansion on the 98
[Music]
floor I wouldn't say it was all just
dream okay will this game give me a
point to end somewhere can I save
anyway's no manual save oh
there's
a my
no it's pretty nice
you princess
it looks kind of similar to that one
picture we
saw may I may I
know it's all scripted I can't control
myself okay there
we go I mean I don't know if gacha is
playable
now I assume not
so in that
case doesn't look like there's a safe
function even there just a return to
title so I guess it saves on its own
walk through the door
okay okay
[Music]
you're messing with
me it's
all it's
all mess
up say it's a dream maybe this is the
dream
was before was the reality but this is
the dream maybe I don't
know I'll feel better once I play gcha
for sure
excuse me are you really rest in
peace why would you say that directly to
an obviously alive person right in front
of
you that's so rude saying that it's also
rude damn can't say anything
right
okay it
a it was a
j
are for saying it so
what she's kind of aware of
[Music]
it not all okay no no no no no it's not
that
simple don't just don't just push it
aside
[Music]
this was all but a
scratch
off no Perma death after
everybody gets revived when they
die but that's so weird what's going
on I thought it would be quite funny if
we lose all our party members throughout
the play
through instead of
gaining if Tu is alive then Su is alive
come
on she's alive and Si is alive logical
thinking kuraka
yeah they're putting up a flag only he's
going to be
[Music]
dead
okay show me the
9999 trash I've added the two of you to
trash tribe group trash tribe I've never
heard of this name which city does it
belong
to Tri doesn't belong to any City it's
basically a rebel alliance against zero
like to I like you guys to join forces
I'm in I'm
in can we make the decision for S of
course Su definitely won't say no that
picture is
cug welcome M
mm why does she only have the she should
change her profile
picture he yeah yeah yeah
meow wait Kaki has
cat I like him more now
I want to
Playa I'll tell you the details later
you'll understand better that way okay
better to decide what we'll be doing
next I
don't this game won't let me
stop I'm trying to find a good ending
point but it's hard to find
one should not have stepped outside guys
I should have stayed with that
Cliffhanger thinking that my friends are
dead who is you we are neon a group
opposing zero we are concerned that
Master Yu is involved in a very serious
manner we agree that serious oppression
cannot be left uncheck therefore we have
decided to offer our technology to help
you special machine is it a kacha
machine
did you hear something
strange that looks like a crane
game could have be the Special Machine
NE mentioned earlier is it the
G it's
cute crap
G well that makes sense but it stopped
moving after taking out a book seems
suspicious but we don't know the
identity of the person who sent the
message yet don't worry about it just
play
gotcha let's check out the book first it
should be about the robot
M I
see huh is this even possible it'd be
amazing if it could do that what does it
say one shouldn't be afraid to try new
things come stand next to this machine
okay let's fire it
up what kind of things can I got
you wait I already have this character
don't I
oh it's free what a
deal I
[Music]
don't
o oh wow wow wow it's in a freaking
torpedo or does this mean that this
character becomes available for my group
now to put them into my
group
understand what happened gotcha happened
baby
oh why isn't he responding and I think
his body is a bit
transparent what you see before you now
is not the real Ki kinata it is a
projection using our technology please
think of it has a mirage even if for
some reason a person is not with you
this illusion can be a substitute
however since the person is not actually
there you will not be able to
communicate with them please make up it
there a stop Gap until you meet the with
the actual person
uhhuh
okay is there an imposter of
me sounds like something new to learn
about all messages Okay cool so you get
more characters to use in your
team is it otherwise just like Su and
and so
on that's
cool I wonder if there's any more than
the ones that we already saw in the in
the
tutorial oh
got
yay we did
it this is the real game you can obtain
tension cards as well okay cool Co cool
for the characters whom you haven't
encountered yet neon has provided a
simulator to create virtual images of
them to accompany you as you progress
for the story that you will be able to
meet the characters in
person so but if I don't have get them
fuga and then I meet them in person
before getting them through gacha do I
just get them into my team anyway or do
I have to obtain them through
gacha I
wonder oh
switch character new feature
unlocked they're always in your
no does it make them playable only if I
use the
gacha do they take real money or is it
just in-game
[Music]
money now that you're a member of trash
you can operate characters other than
you each character has their own set of
actions and battle Styles and are fitted
for different roles you can check out
each character's traits via their core
passive skill in the character screen to
see which character fits your style best
characters who Accel at fting enemies at
close range are usually able to execute
skills that can deflect honestly I was
quite happy with the with uh your I
don't know how common it would be to
change your character oh it would be
nice to change to a female
character not to her though I like to uh
like in a in a game like that I would
prefer to be close combat if I'm
fighting together with NPCs if it was of
real people then I would consider um
ranged combat but cute what is that what
do you have
there that's cute it's like a squirrel
raccoon cat
thing interesting pet there are got in
got a few characters you didn't meet oh
really that' be amazing
hey I want to do more gacha
please wait that looks so funny it looks
like y has twin Tails because she's
standing right behind
me can I play G again no well then you
you losing me
[Laughter]
here okay okay okay okay I went uh a
little bit past uh the where I have to
play but what you saying I I don't I
don't have the money for it
probably I have zero but so this looks
like I might be able to use real money
for it can
I check mail
[Music]
that's a
lot you're kidding
me do you use that currency for anything
besides
gacha they are off for in the best girl
to me here oh you know I got to go for
it my besty my cutest the
L come home and mushroom
girl first try first try first try
that's the stand B well it has her face
on it so I want
it it's a
weapon wa tension cards okay tension you
don't
starter find
[Music]
macarons guard a
cactus I get myself does that make me
stronger when I get more of the same
person
probably can probably Max myself out hey
yo who are you
[Music]
she was not in
the um first couple of characters that
we
met that is at least something nice to
see convert what do you mean convert
what does that
mean I don't know what that
means I don't want to look at that right
now just want to play
morea I got another guy different new
one are the chances low to get
inoi who are you I don't think we met
him
either I got so much
money oh my God
HEI am what attention card
character who are you I wait it's The
Snake jacket
guy yeah yeah yeah it's him it's him we
know
him blonde
guy go go go
go give me my
w danion card oh
no character just a special attention
card it's demo you think after the demo
like when it really launches we won't
get so much money from the get go huh oh
cute full course
love is that the best thing I got no
give me
an give me should I is it better to go
for that but I don't want Kazuki ayama I
want
enoi but well we have so much money
let's keep on keep on going standard
okay guaranteed with 80 PS
oh that's
me please
but that's a lot of fancy attention
cards but not what I
want do I just get her on my atth pool
for real for
[Music]
real I swear she's like a combination of
ladin
Anda yay
[Applause]
[Music]
W I love
her she's my fa she's so
cute didn't even have to use all of my G
she just really wanted to come to me
[Music]
understandable
okay very nice I think I've reached my
personal end goal end game
thank you guys so much for watching the
sponsorship uh I I I already said this
yesterday in my stream but today's
second stream is going to be cancelled
SL delayed but I'm going to upload the
uh next YouTube short dance short today
maybe a little bit later today I already
have it ready but I don't know should I
do it right now I don't know I'll wait a
little bit H it's looking really fun so
look forward to it keep your eyes open
on your subscription box and in any case
I hope you guys had fun with this
honestly it was really a lot of fun I
mean the the baseball was a little bit
overwhelming to me right now cuz I don't
even understand
baseball but uh the battles were a lot
of fun I especially had a lot of fun
with the boss fight that was quite
challenging but very exciting and I
didn't really get frustrated it was just
more and more fun the more I tried
it so give it a try guys for yourself
test it out for yourself see if you find
it challenging or not if you can get it
in less deps than me the link is in the
description to the deadly demo uh it's
it's a referral link so if you want to
try the demo don't go straight to steam
or so no go to the link of uh mine that
is in the description I would appreciate
that so yeah
to recap we played chapter zero this
time and I think we went a little bit
past that for sure uh you can play until
the end of chapter 1 apparently in the
demo so even in the current deadly demo
there's around 20 hours of content to
enjoy we've just played 4 hours of it
surely you could get through it faster
if you wanted to um but yeah tribe 9 is
breaking away from the Pay to Win
principle it says the game emphasizes
player grow through experimentation
enjoyment rather than simply paying to
get
stronger that sounds promising the
deadly demo is available since October
15th uh so go try it out and you can
download it right now check the link in
the description or my Twitter post and
oh a Twitch streaming campaign is also
being held to Hype up the stream next
Fest together with all the streamers so
check it out twitch huh okay we're not
on Twitch but sounds fun
H
yeah please try it out give it a try and
give the g a try
too yeah as I said had a lot of fun
honestly would love to play more I hope
I hope you guys enjoyed
it thank you for the sponsorship I am
very honored
thank you so much for your support I
will see you again sometime later
tomorrow maybe it's already the end of
the week so I guess I got to make
another
schedule have a nice day in German we
say Al in byebye
and I'll miss you an noi I will miss you
I wish we could have spent more time
together ever
[Music]
byebye
yeah I keep an eye out for the short
bye-bye
oh
[Music]