​​​ ​Lala lalala ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoo! Whoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look over here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Someone's addicted to​ ​​
​​ ​human pop culture...​ ​​
​​​ ​I am Nerissa Ravencroft,​ ​​
​​ ​the Demon of Sound,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I've escaped from prison​ ​​
​​ ​in search of idol songs!​ ​​
​​​ ​Idol-loving Demon of Sound​ ​​
​​​ ​B-Broke out?!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's a fugitive!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's a good kid at heart...​ ​​
​​​ ​Though her voice can​ ​​
​​ ​drive people crazy if her guard's down...​ ​​
​​​ ​La la la la laaa ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ack!​ ​​
​​​ ​The human mind​ ​​
​​ ​probably can't take this...​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice, I'm feelin' good! 😄​ ​​
​​​ ​Gyah!​ ​​
​​​ ​The world is doomed...​ ​​
​​​ ​Not on my watch...​ ​​
​​​ ​Marine-senpai, what's wrong?​ ​​
​​​ ​Something's leaking from your ears! 💦​ ​​
​​​ ​It's your fault!​ ​​
​​​ ​Operation Feed Her to Defeat Her!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sh-She's right.​ ​​
​​​ ​If Nerissa has her mouth​ ​​
​​ ​stuffed with food, ​ ​​
​​​ ​she can't sing even if she wanted to!​ ​​
​​​ ​Senchou-senpai's home-made food...​ ​​
​​​ ​Try this for size!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nom nom...​ ​​
​​​ ​Nom!​ ​​
​​​ ​Marine-senpai's food is... sooo good!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're singing again!​ ​​
​​​ ​Next!​ ​​
​​​ ​Operation Idol Otaku!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sh-She's right.​ ​​
​​​ ​We can draw Nerissa​ ​​
​​ ​away from singing​ ​​
​​​ ​with our idol performance!​ ​​
​​​ ​Play with fire ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Take me higher ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Kyah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Play with fire ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Take me higher ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, you're joining in?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Next!​ ​​
​​​ ​Operation Make Her Fawn!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sh-She's right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nerissa's got a pretty dirty mind​ ​​
​​​ ​so she'll be distracted for sure...!​ ​​
​​​ ​What did you say?​ ​​
​​​ ​You better shut your mouth...​ ​​
​​​ ​How 'bout we shut you up...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hyah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hyaaaah!​ ​​
​​​ ​My ears!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Even this phoenix is​ ​​
​​ ​being mentally tested...​ ​​
​​​ ​Senchou's heart is​ ​​
​​ ​barely human now too..​ ​​
​​​ ​What's wrong with me?​ ​​
​​ ​All I'm doing is burdening my senpais...​ ​​
​​​ ​It would be better for everyone...​ ​​
​​​ ​if I'd just stayed in prison... 😢​ ​​
​​​ ​Even after everything,​ ​​
​​ ​you're still worried about me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Even if her critical human self is lost...​ ​​
​​​ ​Seems she hasn't​ ​​
​​ ​forgotten her hololive heart.​ ​​
​​​ ​Even though I'm like this? 😢​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's raise this poor creature together...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeeeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Glad I could hear her sing before I go...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh man, everything got destroyed.​ ​​
​​​ ​My idol songs...! 😭​ ​​
​​​ ​Rounding it up. FUWAMOCO!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you enjoyed this,​ ​​
​​ ​please subscribe for more!​ ​​