[Music]
duh
you guys hear the popping yeah i'm
making the popcorn right now
hold on hold on a second we're going to
the shrek room i want to go to the trick
we're here in the shrek room now i
entertain the people while i go check on
the
[Music]
i got a present i got a present for her
i'll give it to her before that movie
[Music]
share this popcorn and also uh a headset
in between the two of us
oh we're sharing this one
[Music]
what is the popcorn not ready yeah i
don't think you only popped it in like
two minutes
god
[Music]
popcorn
by the way guys i i arrived at
kelly's place a bit late but sorry about
that but i just came here
and i saw the valentine's chocolate but
the only part that's left is the crystal
part so she's calling me [\h__\h] with her
chocolates
she says we all know she ate the eye and
now she out the whole
porter part as well she couldn't hold
herself back
don't listen to her melted when i left
my home i left it out everyone
don't put it in the refrigerator cali if
you put it in the refrigerator it's
going to taste bad
guess what bottom part built because the
air conditioner melts and i was watching
[Music]
it's way too loud oh okay i'll cook it i
figured wait how do i get there
[Music]
there you go i'm gonna burn it otherwise
whoa
popcorn the popcorn is it really done
yes it's
yeah mostly it's gonna start burning
otherwise
yeah i'm glad to have something salty
yes it's really hot it's really hot
don't burn yourself don't burn don't
burn yourself
don't burn yourself
[Music]
oh bgm yeah i figured bgm will be loud
hold on yeah i don't want to turn it
down
here oh yeah it's about it's about to go
away
so yummy yeah well kelly
mm-hmm um so today
i brought you the youtube play button
right mm-hmm
and i brought you this chocolate which i
did not eat
um where and it did not melt
my valentine's chocolate for you thank
you for the valentine's day in the red
box that
i don't know if you saw anything of this
dream where i was making it
yes i did i did i did tune in i was very
nervous the whole time but i liked your
gloves
[Laughter]
yeah that was very um riveting riveting
rivet
riveting what you're a frog um
yeah so yeah before we get started with
uh shrek do you wanna
give one of them a taste yes genma was
very excited about the chocolate
oh and she said it was yummy and she
said she even ate more than one
so i didn't force her but i don't know
it's been like
i don't know five days in the fridge now
okay well
let's give it a try i'm gonna eat it huh
oh yeah the whole thing good
it's very tasty i made it with uh lint
chocolate you know european
quint lint lint l i n d t oh yeah
good stuff and i put in
almonds and walnuts and corn flakes
wow and blueberries as well
blueberries dried blueberries oh she ate
the second one
should i try here it tastes bad
compared to this it tastes bad really
did you use um like
japanese cooking chocolate or like other
what chocolate did you use
here's what i did i went to the
supermarket and i looked for the place
um where they say you can make homemade
chocolate with this and i bought one of
those
wow yeah those probably taste
kind of yeah i don't i don't think it'll
taste
bad but it's not gonna taste good i'll
try okay i'm eating
the u the u now the u of the remaining
kusa
do it
[Music]
oh white chocolate i love the white
chocolate i mean it tastes like
chocolate so
there you go huh what else did you put
in
um there's some little crispy balls
yeah i taste that mm-hmm yummy
and i put some um condensed milk
also i heard that well wonderful effort
but i've got um
one more thing for you oh yeah that i
wanted to give to you like angel's
god oh what is it i went in your live
reaction that's why i
kept waiting oh what is it look look to
the front oh yeah
keep on looking to the front okay
keep on looking okay
what's what's oh my gosh did you draw
this
yes oh okay because this is not my
stream i didn't prepare the picture for
everyone on the
in the stream oh but i gave her the
drawing i've been drawing that
my members oh and you remember zombies
this is so cute i love the jacket with
the skulls i want to own this yeah
i will upload it on twitter later guys
but yeah
this is and you got it framed and
everything yeah it's framed
wow it's me i look so cute with my
earmuffs
and those yeah those
yeah i was gonna say that look those
look like our matching gloves you're
wearing
ranching clothes oh yeah the ones that
we bought at don quixote yeah
wow this is so cute you're so good at
drawing
no not i want to be good at drawing
you're still forgotten
no no this is so good you're super good
i love your art the last time you drew
me you drew me like
when i didn't draw you looking like a
chicken with legs
ah yeah i need to repay you now we need
to
make some archery no no no no no no no
no no no i want to draw you
this was supposed to be in my christmas
present for you
oh but then i didn't finish it before
christmas and time so i wanted to give
it to you during our trip and i brought
it in my suitcase
and i was like you remember that stream
yeah you do it a stream
yeah yeah yeah yeah no i can't yeah i
had it next to our table
um under that pillow i had it hidden i
had it ready and we tried to stream but
it
didn't work out so i had to hide it back
into my suitcase later that's when i
told you
could you please like uh leave the room
for a moment oh
this is so adorable i'm gonna put it on
my desk
if i have any room i'll make room for it
this is so cute
thank you so much you're welcome
i'll put it on twitter later so everyone
can see yay
thank you you're welcome
i love it i will treasure it forever
thank you now i feel bad because i
didn't do anything
dope for you no yeah yeah
yeah it's okay i'll finish we still got
some time here
i'm gonna eat this last chocolate later
i will save it for when i'm starving and
i can't go to the grocery store
callie got us bubble tea i did
i chose two flavors i didn't know which
one cause it's totally weird one i chose
strawberry and cookies and cream it's
kind of like the idea of both
but did you know that like bubble tea
itself i
i i'm not like one of those bubble tea
addicts
i don't dislike it but but the bubbles
in the bubble tea
i would prefer without bombs oh the
tapioca yes same actually
i wasn't sure how you felt about that
but now that i know i'm like oh
kind of wish that i didn't kind of wish
i did
it's fine yes i know for next time i
know for next time
usually i just avoid them if they're
like now we can't talk oh my god i can't
believe you
you're doing the same as me yeah
yeah yeah are we ready for the movie
we should watch shrek um hey for those
of you shrek lovers in the chat who
don't know where to get shrek i put in
the description the different sites
where you can get it
yeah um so you should search for shrek
if you can't find shrek on any of those
sites i'm not going to say anything else
but
just do your best to watch shrek with us
and that's all i'm going to say that's
all i'm going to say
now hopefully the place that i have
chosen for us to watch shrek will allow
us to watch
uh shrek um did you not test it
i did i did however uh
you never know about things like
buffering and what i have very strong
internet
it's very strong mm-hmm um how you know
you know i just i'm just not sure
so i guess we'll find out won't we
everyone
all right well let's go ahead and get
this this shrek party started it's been
such a long time since i watched trek
one mm-hmm me too me too one of the best
movies ever
yeah i was really surprised to learn
that you like shrek it's it's hard to
find
i mean what there are some people who
don't like shrek believe it or not
no they do exist in this universe
i think those people you call heretics
all right heretics yes yes
i think i think it's heretics yeah
um indeed indeed they're non-believers
yep indeed so for those of you don't
know how this works i have a timer here
yes ataima which is not the devil's
cabbage um
no that is one way you can say it in
japanese
listen or you can also listen
listen i have a timer a timer
and when i when i press start do we do
three two
one start um it's three
two one start and on start you click
you click play but i don't wear that
depending on
where they and then the that beats and
the chickens watch it
yeah um they might have a different
starting point
i did check on that and all i know is
that the place where we're watching it
is uh it aligns with amazon prime okay
i checked the movie is exactly one hour
30 minutes
across most sites um yeah well i'm
lagging by the way
sometimes that's fine it should be okay
do you guys start off with the
dreamworks logo
hopefully you start off with the
dreamworks logo start at the dreamworks
logo yes
we can just tell them for a little while
what we're seeing
okay yeah you got it yes yes yes most
okay everyone's saying they started the
dreamworks logo okay
largely yes okay good so i'm gonna play
about five seconds let me mute the
desktop audio so we don't get copyright
stricken um
so what i do is i start the i start the
um
the video i play it to five seconds and
then i start the stopwatch
so basically yeah is the dreamworks logo
with the fishing and whatever we're
fishing right now yeah
are you stopping yeah it's it's seven
okay so it's at seven right so
basically um yeah just make sure that
your timer matches up with my with my
time
the timer on your movie matches with the
timer on the screen okay kelly is just
the first time you're doing a movie
what's wrong
no no i've done it many times but there
are some people who are new here and i
just want to
give them a helping hand you know all
right so here we go
i'm gonna start the timer and then we're
gonna start the movie
ready everyone are you ready
okay remember it's three two one and on
start you click play
okay here we go three
two one start
okay
all right here we go shrek time baby
time for shrek we love shrek
uh let's hunt for the people so they
know where we are
[Music]
dream of pictures presents yeah that's
the one
though also our our our voices are like
maybe half a second behind as well just
because of microphone lag so
but it's fine we'll be basically around
the same area perfect think really guys
we see a book now we've seen a book
it reminds me of my debut oh that's
right yeah fairy tale
we started with a book too yeah
remember that was a lovely princess
next page give him a play by play
[Music]
the timer stopped ah because oh yeah
yeah it's still going it's still going
it's still going
i just had to pull it back up it's still
going don't worry you guys are fine you
guys are fine
yeah it's bad right yeah listen i did
the best that i could
all i'm gonna say is do you know how
hard it is to find the original english
spoken shrek in japan
no i mean it's because we're watching uh
we're listening with the
with one earphone oh yeah it's not
happening headphones
here we go it's the iconic toilet
somebody wants to oh
god yes somebody
[Music]
listen all right some people got the
wrong idea they think that like i want
to date shrek
shrek is a friend a long time homie okay
though shrek kind of cute though
i found that shrek's cannon height and
then you know it kind of
kind of changed shrek is pretty tall
[Music]
hey now check it out now you're it all
good
[Music]
your rockstar gets you to show on get
paid
oh that
[Music]
what a cutie have you ever watched this
movie on a 4k
tv like ultra high definition
no this is a 2001 movie so you might you
might uh
see some fun secrets
it's that this movie doesn't look very
good kelly you need to be vibing why are
you not vibing
because uh because
you're doing plenty of vibing for the
both of us
[Music]
damn shrek is kind of ripped i mean if
you say so chat
here i'll vibe a little bit whoa hey
thank you so cute really
so cute i'm getting dizzy
vibing yeah you know sorry get to
get get your game on go play you know
all that glitters
should we sing that in our yeah why not
let's do it it's on the list okay cool
let's sing it together
on saturday yeah saturday morning
concert
look at these hate and ass fools count
your window is so bright
i know i can't do anything about it i
need to get a curtain for it
yeah it's just very high up
mm-hmm yeah that's why i always wake up
super early
hmm
oh that's right mike myers is a shrek
is there any way you can turn up the
earphones this matters
sure oh look at this tool bag
oh nice oh yes windows noises
thank you
[Music]
so what a charmer get you a man who
looks like shrek
and can scream in the faces of your
enemies is that really what you want
a man who looks like shrek i mean why
not yeah he's got a good soul
okay good green dead i think me becoming
a frog was close enough
yeah sure enough but like i said it's
about the soul i'm a reaper so
you know i want the good soul them good
tasty souls you know
oh it's all coming back to me now i'm
remembering the entire plot of this
movie slowly
so i would say that you are shrek uh-huh
in this movie sure and i'm the donkey
i think so that's me that's me
definitely eddie murphy and i'm 100
mike myers yeah
hmm wait that's the first time i watch
it in english
wait really where how did you watch it
german
really you watched the german dub always
oh my god
this is special what what a special
occasion i mean nowadays i like to watch
movies in their original language but
back then i mean i was still small oh
that's so cute so watching it in german
was a
pretty i thought he might yeah yeah yeah
definitely
german shrek german i want to hear
german shred i recommend
it i feel like
oh no no donkey
[Music]
rejected even though
english is the like original like voice
for this movie i feel like it would
sound more natural in german
why yeah
oh not for long not for long
oh
[Music]
ouch
now callie help me ah you can't not yet
not yet oh dunk it right in due time
oh nice ass you got there hey
back off back off that's that's my dude
oh real scared now
f f
we're scared of you callie um
[Music]
oh oh it's love at first sight
oh people think she's dangerous gotta
stay with her again
what a cutie
oh my god he's so cute i do love donkey
donkey's probably
actually my favorite what yeah
not trigger heck no i mean shrek is
great but
i like their dynamic that's a good
dynamic
they're both pretty cute
oh
hell yeah shrek is such a soon today
oh my god
you're not impressing me
the popcorn is killing me oh i forgot we
had popcorn yeah
thank you
oh his butt is so cute
that was pretty cute the little butt
wiggle whoa
here you go donkey it's got so close to
being a musical
oh that's a rude thing to say
a cutie
really tall oh no
that's so sweet though he doesn't see
him as a monster
yeah i just think he's cool i don't see
you as steph i see you as a beautiful
beautiful
nice woman well that's very kind of you
to say
because it's already
yeah yeah that's why i like shrek
because this is literally us
yeah yeah get out of my swamp
yo if i if i visit you again like for
for halloween do you want to go extract
can i go as donkey
sure that could be fun i'm happy to be
shrek
yay yeah
i yeah me too shrek
i know this is like it's supposed to be
supposed to be a children's movie
but it is genuinely funny there's some
good jokes in this movie
i forgot
me when i come back to japan asking you
if i can stay over
please let me stay at your place
yeah yeah
outside make you sleep outside
no no what the hell sorry our swamp
i love this part so i'm remembering yeah
shrek that's the way in it settle down
with just a chill martini
a tasty home-cooked meal even though
you're alone forget it you know
you love you love to be alone just like
me would be such good friends
that's disgusting no i do not actually
it's pretty nasty
i'm like i'm like shrek minus the nasty
things
um and i'm not green
and i'm also not confident so maybe i'm
not shrek
can you pass me the wine bottle yes
thanks i think i'll have a i'll i'll
pour one out with shrek
a nice chilled drink of shrek
[Music]
oh
wait what is that is that casper my
mouse
sorry i brought the aspirin with me i
didn't realize
what a lovely bed i love i love the mice
i forgot that there was my stare
and then being blind makes sense because
i tried to get casper out of my house
with uh
like mouse poison that makes the the
mice blind
oh wow i mean i didn't personally do it
but the the mice um
extinguishers yeah yeah yeah
it's casper and jasper casper jasper
that's that's
our cat our cat is the wolf
i love that oh what a cutie
uh-oh the whole crew is here the whole
squad it's time for a party
a lot of caspers
oh my god i should have brought my
sunglasses it's so smable
oh yeah i wish i could do something
about it now you see why i wake up so
early
oh
[Music]
i have to makes sense i have to
is that the thing ah we missed the thing
no i didn't miss it i was i was so
invested why
why would i say what are you doing in my
swamp when i'm trying to relish the
moment
no yeah
oh lord farquaad the german accent
i think in german language those pigs
speak like a german
special dialect oh really yeah yeah to
make it even more german
nice
let's check this chord
does he am i imagining does he sound a
bit british
i mean mike myers is doing his best you
know but yeah maybe
you'll use everyone's hero now
all right it's freaking girl let's go
everyone's like yeah our hero we want to
go home
i mean they just want to go home they
don't want to disturb him on a swamp you
know
they decent they decent shrek is
scottish
the person behind you like is scottish
here we go here we go this is the homie
now some of you say things like oh lord
lord farquaad sure is your type callie
because short and confident
yeah true um but lord farquaad is also a
big old jerk and
jawline a little too strong oh yeah
no but i still chill i still drink like
a glass of wine with him and like hang
out you know
i think he wants to drink milk though oh
yeah that's true that's right
what is he gonna do with him oh
you're a monster
you know looking a little closer
maybe laura farquaad could be like kind
of cute you know
if you like talk to him and get to know
him you know
if we just had like a glass of wine
together but his soul's pretty not tasty
it's like a remix that's good
look i'm just saying his soul is kind of
nasty all right well yeah
he's pretty cute though he's pretty cute
but his soul's just a little if his soul
was a little more tasty maybe we could
have a drink and get to know each other
eat eat ah yes the quote unquote proper
usage of the word ute
besides
here they are i love this part me too
it's cute
sushi and hot tub
oh yeah that [\h__\h]
she's cute she's kind of cute too
they're all cute
it has too many guys oh my god she's a
hiram
can't be say so can't be
she's a real [\h__\h] though she's still
she's also cute
i still give her a kiss oh but this is
the real deal
fiona
nice joyce
[Music]
i didn't get that reference
oh yeah i guess not huh i just thought
it was a cool
cool chill song yeah
number three oh
oh man it's time for the tournament ark
hey don't be rude shrek don't be rude
the doctor doesn't get it he's like what
okay
[Laughter]
i'm glad i'm watching this again because
there's so much stuff i forgot
it's pretty funny they got jokes
ah do we get the thing the music thingy
yeah
and then what would that defeat me for
you drooping yeah they did like a little
number
like a little musical number one yeah
and there's like a little like a little
lyrical fake out where you think they're
gonna say a curse word
oh yeah oh yeah yeah sorry i'm spoiling
movies
excuse me if you haven't seen shrek by
now
like just get on my face kidding kidding
you're still welcome
it's so cute that's pretty cool
wipe your face ah
it's not even like a bad bad word they
could have gone harder with
it aren't so cute
i love that so much that's pretty cute
yeah didn't they do that again in
another shrek movie
i'm not sure i'm not sure actually maybe
oh
you would smack his bottom shred hold on
it's time now that someone said it in a
chat i
i didn't notice it up until now but it
does look like the facebook logo
yeah yeah it sure does huh i wonder if
they got like
mad like hella smacked by um guy that
owns facebook guys
lord facebook
i love this song though yeah mark mark
said yeah the zuck
mad smacked by the zuck
i love the song that plays
i'm blasted in my car his accent though
yes it's pretty strong
i agree callie just fights with alcohol
yeah i mean that's the way you got to do
it that's another common point me and
strength
[Music]
is
i mean they'd all be dead if that
happened but this is a kid's movie
[Music]
yeah you slam jamming them all
yeah all right all right
can you do that to me give him that no
hey
you're going the right way for a smack
bottom
oh hey hold up that ain't fair
that's a little zooey
yes sick of shrek
yeah it's his swamp
you do got kind of a nice voice that's a
small dude yeah
it's kind of low like for how like tiny
he is but
i feel like um it's kind of it's kind of
growly like you know in a way
it's like there's a gamma way you know i
kind of like that
oh famous german line in the movie oh
but i mean it's obviously english yeah
onions have layers
people
[Music]
this is my favorite line of the movie
stephens
people don't like onions oh
i like that idea too
why not why not i love cakes
parfaits have layers too true very true
see you later it's literally you when
you get angry at me
no one's not i'm not that mean
was it such a long way i mean i mean
yeah i guess it seemed decently far
[Music]
i'm eating all the popcorn
why this is so weird why does she have a
sconce accent and
irritates me
i always thought my he would speak
normal like american english
oh yeah
are all ogre scottish
that's a great question you should ask
one
do you have contact with shrek by any
chance
i don't not me does anyone in chat
i mean can you blame him love is not
that bad though
all right look look you get used to it
baby steps
i'm scared i wanna fall in lava you good
minecraft flashbacks oh yeah minecraft
love is pretty scary
that can actually hurt me unlike real
lava
no ducky
oh here we go no no
no
no that's so terrifying no it's not lava
that'll do that'll do kiara
that'll do now i want a piece of cake
no big deal
oh everyone's super dead
sorry it's like almost no popcorn left
that's okay i'm not very hungry i'm good
just breakfast for me you're good
you must nourish yourself
one thing shrek
okay
don't say anything spoily this movie did
come out in 2001 but
dragon also kind of cute everyone kind
of cute oh
yeah she is indeed really cute
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] she's fire literally fire
this movie's just full of husbands and
wives really
yeah you're right chad maybe she know
kaicho
that's i guess that's the shortcut oh
nice yeah
oh
hold up hold up hold up hold up
yeah yes smooth smooth talker
and there's one thing zombie can do then
it's doing a flirt yeah he's a good
talker
oh would you like that
oh well she likes
oh you're toast now eddie murphy
you're getting a princess i'm getting a
dress oh it's cameron diaz
what up cameron so pretty
yeah she's so cute
how romantic
she's also so cute i prefer her german
boy still oh yeah
you don't like cameron diaz's voice i
mean i like cameron diaz but
yeah i feel like german might actually
suit her really well
right at that point she doesn't realize
that that he's uh he's an ogre right
right yeah she can't really he got the
mask on and the gloves
yeah she thinks he's just a really
handsome seven foot tall dude
she was so prepared
how handsome
oh
he meant it literally
that's also true shrek is very special
that's another reason why i like shrek
oh look it's their love story this is
sweet
oh
romantic
oh shrek don't ruin it for them come on
homie they're so sweet of you two
rescue me dough yeah of course looking
out for you
i love this little shrek role play with
in before there's going to be
fanfictions of us
an alternate universe huh
oh where did you learn those moves
to him yeah
did you do stuff like that before no
i mean maybe first time timer huh yeah
i love the dramatic music me too so
sorry i'm just a little traumatized from
from the past scene
it's pretty explicit i gotta say
this ost actually bops i can't even
disagree with you it's good
sure what do you mean
go oh man we matrix now
ah
[Music]
that's a cool scene it's pretty dope i
feel bad for drugs
it's crazy donkey you know no now our
love is being taken away
from her
don't worry donkey will find happiness
yeah love always finds a way
hmm
yup it nice a little bae oh
she's so sad still feel sad for the
dragon kill
oh
she's all alone there too you know it's
okay love finds a way
oh
yeah very noble indeed she called me
nope
mr steeds
oh
on strike you know you want to
oh she really is quite sheltered huh
it's cute though
good
do it mike myers do it
oh
he's cute tell him he's cute
oh that's so hey hold on wrong with
being an ogre
he's cute
because he's a big old coward and his
soul tastes like [\h__\h] because he's small
hey hey small hey listen i
i didn't say i always says he's small
hey
small can be strong it's the get moai i
like
uh but farquaad isn't strong he's coming
so yeah a small brave
person is good perfect
that was cocky wow that was really cool
what a stud
i love how donkey is also getting really
cocky yeah
he thinks he's cool now that he kind of
yeah he thinks he's steed
and that he's with uh with ogre he feels
much stronger
short and very handsome strong job
i mean from her eyes maybe better than
an older though
hey hold on hold on not from my eyes but
she seems to have a problem with vogers
i mean yeah and that's shitty but what i
have a problem with is what shrek just
said
he's making fun of lord farquaad's uh
height and that's very rich
yeah that's right get him stand up for
him
hey hey hold on a minute
i have a problem with that shrek
we're gonna have to have a talk later
small just means easier to snuggle now
chat gets it
jack gets it oh my god
don't worry my short king's in the chat
i'll defend your honor
i think i need some homie touches too
it's just homie touches not honey
no you said as long as that is so good
hold me thank you cal you guys are
welcome
see i'm more interested in the romance
between shrek and donkey
they're true like like bro homies
bromies yeah
they're homies and they i don't think
they would mind
touching each other yeah having a little
kiss or no
maybe no kiss but like they're hugging
they're just they're great homies
that's some deep [\h__\h] bro yup like you
shrek with your beautiful
on the outside shrek is an ogre which i
don't have a problem with plenty of ogre
looking
people in the underworld um but
but shrek's soul is very tasty he's just
insecure
wait no
wait a minute table that cali
i wonder if there's any like shrek x
donkey fan fiction on the internet
i bet there is definitely
[Music]
shrek feels like he needs to build a
wall around his heart because he's just
insecure
you know
[Music]
he's really a little lonely he just
needs a friend
oh he's different
not me i can't i get his reasons
i get it that's so rude i hate them
why is my hand like this no you're not
no i love you shrek please
i'll be your friend
i didn't judge you you beautiful the way
you were
oh look at them they're true friends
haley that's the one
oh but that's a donkey
yeah by the way shrek just want to say
look at all the shrek lovers right there
in my chat
that love you i know shrek is a
fictional character but
i'm just saying man so many shrek lovers
here
oh that's music i love it
[Music]
that's kind of a sick it's a little
tacky but
that reminds me of uh that dude from the
big bang theory
um the the one who lives with his mom
oh yeah i've seen that show
i'm sure chad knows what you're talking
about for sure
today today yeah
howard yeah howard yes it is yeah there
are some people that know
oh i love this scene where they stop
blowing up things
oh my god don't spoil it kiara
it's fine all of you have seen this
movie if you haven't sorry
[Music]
oh
a lady can cook sometimes you're gonna
take some of those eggs
and make some fried egg out of it i love
a good cookie
i can't cook anything so
donkey
hey
shouldn't that stone be freaking hot
yeah pretty hot i think that her fingers
are just well trained she must have been
a waitress back in the day
wait is that where that face came from
yeah
that's the original
is it made the face the face the chest
got wild
yeah that's the face oh she listened
in on your conversation the other night
you can't tell them
what oh no oh yo it's robbing the [\h__\h]
off robin hood
the french i love you french debate
oh here we go oh merryman
whoa it away
he's got bars
yeah i got this whole break dancing crew
yeah i get them
i don't got that either i guess the
german is different though
i'm so glad to watch this again
wow wow
get him
oh no yeah get him hell yeah
oh my god whoa
god she's also such a cutie look at her
kicking ass
oh damn she's slaying
do you think i can marry every character
in this movie no
is that against the law maybe you can
imagine it
okay she could have slain
slayed the dragon on her own oh he's
he's falling in love he likes her he
likes strong woman he likes strong
ladies
dramatic he's being a little dramatic
huh
bamboozle
blue flower red foreign
get you a woman who can yank an arrow
out of your butt
that's what you need i prefer to go to
the doctor
it's all around you
and maybe she knew that he was
colorblind oh yeah
that's a good point
oh get yourself a room
oh they're in love they're in love
i can't take shrek i can't take fiona
they're perfect for each other
yay
can't take it oh oh the music oh yes
this music is somehow nostalgic i don't
know what
oh they're falling in love how sweet
wow he likes her he likes to be stepped
on
no way just like me
that's okay actually not true
kind of disgusting but okay like to have
your nose sucked
why don't you bring that up and frog
and frog wow
you need to do that next do that one
next okay i don't
do i just go and snack yeah
okay okay that's it i can't do that yeah
did you see i did crowd the other day
i did i saw that and i was like wow
kiara's going all out these days
you're a shame shifter yeah oh my god
those poor animals
that really sucks i'm sure they're fine
now you don't know that just saying more
so good so good
[Music]
you are eating my smell or rats plus b
ew rats yeah
weed rat ew yum
devil's cabbage
that explains that casper didn't show up
in my house anymore
there you go back in 2001
casper time traveled
oh
what you're inviting a woman over
[Music]
shrek is in love for the first time
that's so sweet
look at him he's so dokie dokie
oh
but there goes his confidence issues
again
oh shrek you you look great you're so
cute and the princess likes you you guys
have personalities that match
yes that's it
i'm seeing so much i don't remember as a
kid yeah yeah chat me too
it makes me like it more actually
donkey's too smart
oh
no he just doesn't have a lot of
confidence
he acts you know all all rough and like
like he doesn't care and
he's angry all the time but it's just
because he's insecure
you know people treated him like
[\h__\h] for such a long time
oh no donkey don't go there
no
donkey now
what
no way
the hotter fiona says
i mean she's still cute princess
no
you haven't
definitely my type now says
i mean yeah maybe i still think that
she's very cute
hmm
no it's not true
not that ugly donkey
but your true love might be someone else
doesn't have to be a disgusting king
yeah with a
with a soul that tastes like [\h__\h]
look at look at my boy shrek
oh i love sometimes
i don't really like it but
doing a flirt i'm in trouble
you'll be great shrek oh oh no
no no no no no don't get it wrong
or as callie would say no don't get
twisted
listen
no out of context
no she's talking about herself shrek no
no
[Music]
look a clipper
no context
those are the kind of misunderstandings
that happen if you clip ass
out of cartoons that's right this kind
of thing happens
and like how he turns around when he
does that
sweet and cute like a doggle oh look at
him
i bet donkey's a sleep talker too just
like
you oh
you must tell him but shrek i love you
what's wreck
shrok shrug where you went
there we go she's doing a sailor moon
transformation sure is
um magical girl haitian i would have
liked to see more of the transformation
part
yeah but you know animation costs money
his feelings are hurt
double misunderstanding
oh [\h__\h] oh my gosh no
no this is so out of context
that hurt so much when i first saw it
no
wow impressive perfect
just kidding die
i mean if he was like wow thanks a lot
shrek you did a great job
and was like kind to him i'd be like all
right what a cutie
[Music]
um
oh so many feelings hurt
pain
oh
donkey you gotta tell him yes dunk it
no no don't you gotta tell him
shrek no shrek
he doesn't mean that he's just sad
he's just sad he doesn't mean it he
doesn't mean a donkey
yeah you got it all wrong you got it
twisted callie as per usual
no it's not me it's shrek this dragon
got into myself
it was just sacred coin oh my god do you
remember the words
but you don't really care for music
i know of the hallelujah part it's like
this
the fourth the fifth the minor oh dmca
the baffled king composing
hallelujah
[Music]
don't cry kiara
hey
i love this song i sing this in in
karaoke in japan
often um
victory march that's cute
looking good boss
oh literal short king
[Music]
come on fiona that kid you know the
movie
kind of contradicts itself a little bit
being like oh it's not about appearances
then they [\h__\h] on farquhar
being short and whatever you know i know
that his soul is nasty but listen man
i think she's just expressing her you
know sadness and anger
frustration i guess
[Music]
the chat agrees with me
i'm just saying shrek you guys could
have done a little better
but farquaad is evil so i mean i guess
it makes sense yeah
i don't know i feel like it would have
been better if he was tall though and
like
super handsome you know
but like an [\h__\h] on the inside that's
fine still good movie
it's still like a movie shrek two faces
oh you right you write chat we'll watch
shrek 2 next
yeah yeah
donkey stand up for yourself
yeah get him donkey a donkey's had a
doggy has had enough come on shrek you
love me too don't you
yeah you tell them donkey hell yeah
onion boy your boy
no no no no
no you dummy
a boot
oh i'll always forgive you
oh look at them friends
they're friends
hey yes sorry you're okay i cracked my
neck on you you're okay
oh this is why oh yeah yay
oh look at how excited he is
[Music]
no elastic he says he's cute
it's cute movie
roller coaster baby
so cute everyone in this movie is cute
[Music]
no doubt i especially love all the
fairies you know the cookies
yeah i like yeah i like the gingerbread
man too
genji
ah
revered silence
oh no but if he can't love you for who
you are
yeah that's the thing it's not gonna
work out laura farquhar kind of has a
double standard to be honest
he wants a he he if he if he sees her
the way that she is
at night then she's gonna be like ooh
ugly he won't like it
yeah it's like hold on
whoa hold on a minute
so cute
oh there he is
he wants fiona
oh no you didn't he has a nasty taste
and soul
she knows what he wants to say
shut up you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] laugh no
you jerk because she makes me so mad
i will make fun of far corn because he
is a jerk not because he is short
you big jerk i hate you
what an evil soul you have
no no your soul is gross
murder time
[Music]
oh she's gonna she's gonna show him
oh magical girl henshin
what a cutie fanny cause she's so
beautiful
what a jerk kill him kill him shrek
kill him make him even shorter
you suck you suck yeah that guy that guy
sucks you guys haven't kissed yet so
it's not real
yeah kill them straight kill all of them
oh
you passed it no you won't
you'll have nothing
yay bye-bye
[Music]
yay
really really
yay kiss
oh
[Laughter]
yay no ogre forever
but yeah
she thought she would say human right
mm-hmm she's gonna be sad about that
yeah but it's okay because shrek loves
her just the way that she is
that's what matters most
i love shrek so much
[Music]
now i'm a believer yeah
not a trace down
my mind i'm in love
i'm a believer
yeah get down eddie murphy i'm a
believer
oh they're all so cute
hey hey all right i'm in love
oh
if i try hey
uh
[Music]
hey
shades
today's today's kids movies like
ensemble cast
singing numbers at the end of the movie
just don't hit the same as shreks do
tonight
it's just not the same anymore is it
nice that it doesn't end here it doesn't
edit it we're gonna watch the second one
oh yeah that's right yep we do have to
yep we sure do we got just dragged the
second
to watch we're not watching the third
one watching the second
shrek two it's next but i feel like we
might need to take a a little palm spray
wash your hands break because my hands
sure are sweating holding this wine
bottle and
getting drunk washing shrek you could
have put it down you know
yeah but i dropped the cap and i figured
it just wasn't worth it to put it back
on because they just keep sipping on it
so you know
there's only two shrek movies watch the
fourth i actually haven't seen the
fourth i saw the third in theaters i
remember
um but i don't remember anything about
it so it must not have been that good
well i don't remember watching the
fourth what was that about i haven't
seen the fourth
i heard there's a fifth is that true
chat is there a fifth shrek movie i mean
there's also a lot of like smaller
movies
yeah yeah yeah no interest i'm happy
with just the two and having that be
like my shrek universe in my mind i
don't remember the third one being that
[\h__\h]
yeah some people are saying shrek four
is not very good
four is okay three is not good four hold
on hold on
fifth is in the there's a fifth one is
in coming out
i see i see fifth is it's spin-off it's
spin-off
isn't there is isn't there a post-credit
scene chat am i wrong
is there the fourth fourth is not good
luck
right i can't do i've
see what
i had the same thing i guess you have
the same syndrome as me
but i'm not gonna say because i don't
know if you want me to say it
but let me just say i had the same thing
and my my my viewers
knew about it and teased me about it
many times until i
fixed it i didn't know you had to say
huh i'm so curious
oh my it my hand being up no no no wait
oh
hold on hang on is it this
i don't know what i'm supposed to do
you're just you're supposed to
activate the freaking call oh
it took me a while because where do you
get the code where'd you get the code
they said uh it's it's on the pc
actually on the on the right side there
oh i see maybe i'll do it later
because we both got a pc from the same
maker i see i see
yeah she also doesn't have videos
actually
oh i guess i'll have to activate it
later
it took me like a month or so until i
finally the reason why i did it was like
people saw it like when i took
screenshots of my screen like thumbnails
and [\h__\h]
i see and they kept on teasing me like
you need to activate windows still
didn't do it and it got so embarrassing
after a while that i just had something
okay
all right
hey i missed the post-credits scene
question isn't there a post-credits
scene where they all dance and someone's
like i like
is that blessed and i cannot lie yeah i
think so
maybe not hey
kinda did huh rate the movie what would
you rate this movie there
is there is not there's some people are
saying no
some people are saying oh it's on two
okay it's on two notah
okay well then it's for shrek 2 all
right time to stop then time to stop
stop the timer
okay then we're done we're done with
strike one how would you rate shrek one
kiara a million out of ten
yeah i would say it's pretty solid i
like it it's quite short though i just
realized it's pretty
short it is pretty short yeah but i
gotta say i i did think about this
before
i really like the plot um just because
like
i don't know you don't see i don't i
thought it was very original i always
thought it was really original you know
shrek when was shrek 2 made oh no idea
no idea maybe the japanese 9 out of 10
early 3d is weird yeah especially if you
watch it on the 4k tower
swamp out of swamp swamp out of swamp
2004 thank you
swamp out of swamp
why is this bond does not have a fourth
i guess not no i guess we're changing it
what all right that's very strange uh oh
this one does not before either what is
it with four
oh there you go anyway um i need to put
this on a different line because it's
blocking my face that's weird
let's see yeah
it's time now for shrek 2 i love shrek 2
because i love
um puss in boots antonio banderas
this is the one we're putting boats oh
my god are you get ready for puss
oh my god the cute eyes the googly eyes
oh no
i love i love posting boots i had a
little puss in boots doll back in the
day that i got
from an early birthday yup and um
[Music]
yeah oh yeah doug doug jackie chief is
yeah the the male cat nail caddy boots
oh that's so
sweet i love that that's so adorable
i'm very excited wait is uh
the the english name puss in boots uh
isn't it isn't
you know that weird only for female cats
uh i wouldn't say maybe i mean
there's no why so it's just puss in
boots so like um a pussycat could be
like uh
i don't know i feel like it could be a
dude like put some boots like a
character like an
actual fairytale character what did you
what did you think of uh pussycat dolls
when they were active
day right they were i i mean i didn't
listen i didn't bang their tunes all the
time but
it's not gendered uh
[Music]
don't you wish your girlfriend was a
freak like me
maybe don't you do you need to wash your
hands because i need to wash my hands
okay well don't say anything strange to
my chat or make them feel uncomfortable
like uh do you want to suck my nose yeah
i'll get mad if you do that i'll go
watch the archive and if you do anything
like that then we're gonna have a
problem
so please do not i'll be right back sure
okay
the problem is i cannot say not anything
right so i guess i'll just have to go
quiet completely
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
and it didn't say anything i didn't say
anything weird
don't tell her don't tell me
you guys ready for the second movie note
and i wonder like depending on the time
zone if some people have to go
because it might be too late for some
people how long is the second movie
though is it longer than the first one
hope you guys can make it until the end
i'm quite surprised so many of you
are here watching a movie with us
together but i guess shrek was a
something that was uh expected for a
long time and hyped up for a long time
about the same by the way guys
on saturday my time but uh friday
for many of the american time zones um
we're having a tagamori concert
on my channel i don't know if it's on
cami's schedule that she posted did you
even post one
but it's on my schedule and it's on my
channel we're having like a 30 minutes
unarchived potion and the 30 minute
arcade potion
so it's going to be like we're going to
be able to sing a lot of songs that
we're normally not able to sing
and we're also going to be singing some
songs that will be archived because i
thought it would be
i want to sing like i don't want to be
restricted by by the art
archive you know and by the copyright
but
i do also want a part of it being
archived so so that
there is something we can look back on
so yeah
look forward to it
i want one oh yeah maybe we could make a
do a live rendition of
wawa world hello yeah
so help you guys when i'll be there it's
on it's on my channel it's basically
you know because karaoke is something
together kind of okay something that
is pretty hard to do when you're not in
the same place
so she'll be coming over and it will be
the
uh the second to last time that we will
meet
before i leave there will be one more
time after that
but that's yeah that's that's the last
second to last time
we will meet before i leave this country
and i won't be able to see kelly for a
long time probably
yeah so
ah there will be a lot of feelings
there's just one song i really want to
sing for her
i'm probably gonna cry oh my god i'm
thinking of
writing a letter too maybe
it's gonna be so so hard hitting in the
fields
oh man oh it's gonna be painful
get your tissues ready guys
even for the people who who don't really
you know ship
this beautiful ship i think even then
you know
it's something you gotta see hmm
also i ate all the popcorn goddammit
and i eat i the chocolate that kelly
made actually wasn't
even that bad i like the the the the
white i've eat i've been eating the
white chocolate ones
and the poppy things that she put in
there it reminds me of a certain german
white chocolate that we sell in in
the land of australia you know
oh she's singing pussycat dolls
[Music]
welcome back okay hey don't you wish
your girlfriend was hot i don't wish it
because
i know she already is hot
i have agreed to nothing we are hot
girlfriends i have agreed to nothing
nothing nothing shark two baby
shrek two times you sure you don't wanna
wash your hands or anything
i'm not i'm fine good no palm spaghetti
your palms aren't sweaty no no no no no
well that was the only thing is that you
know uh
i wish i could not be blinded by the
lights
oh yeah sorry about that oh yeah the
sun's really kind of sitting over you
now you know how i feel when i have to
deal with this uh
terrible light issue okay gotta put
something there
yeah i need to find some kind of curtain
it's an interesting uh
interesting window position yeah yeah i
mean it's
it's nice and like very beautiful in
some ways for the most part
it's kind of annoying i have to wake up
at like eight everyone
all right now are you all ready for
shrek 2's do you have your shirt
what did you talk to my chat about i'm
basically um
in the beginning i didn't talk anything
uh-huh but then i told him about the
concert
and um and you know
well i've stole my body well how would i
do that
no no no no sorry i'm gonna watch the
i'm gonna watch the vod
once you leave and i might have to send
you a message
guys she said weird things dad hey
my my children are i mean my deadbeats
are
really cross with you one thing i can
definitely one thing i can definitely
say is that i did not say anything weird
okay
fine i believe you she was inside you
all right you know what chad no i'm
gonna go do some investigation after
this but for now it's time for us to
spend some time
with shrek and fiona who are
accidentally in love with each other
yeah so get your shrek 2 loaded um
loaded up
onto your uh computer device so we can
watch shrek 2. because i want to watch
shrek 2.
is everyone ready okay i'm excited for
this second
one yeah me too is there someone wearing
only
all the fairies go like a party
yeah i think so there is something with
like fairies like partying and [\h__\h] i
forget this movie completely
uh i forget the plot too so this is
going to be exciting all right dead
beats are you ready remember it's
three two one and on start you click
start okay
strike two time all right here we go
ready okay three
two one start okay we see
we see clouds yeah there are clouds the
dreamworks logo
video is one minute thirty two oh okay
play we see balloons balloons go up up
up yeah
and there's a boys yeah yes it's called
the dreamworks look
down on the moon and the balloons they
fly they're flying do you guys are
on time are you stinked and dreambox
there we go there you go there it is
with the rainbox animation yeah i mean
i'm using
amazon prime so if you're watching on
amazon prime should be the same
[Music]
all right it's time for the continuation
of the beautiful love story here we go
perfect do you think
nice yeah nice okay
here we go it's the same are you sure
this isn't just shrek one it's the same
actually i guess it just starts the same
way
i guess so oh now the voice is different
yeah
oh
okay yeah this is shrek 2 yeah
it's about the in-laws yeah
fiona's paris
ah yeah yeah this is the origin story
why fiona turned to ogre oh that fairy
beach
yeah yeah she's not great
oh yeah yeah i remember prince charming
okay
yeah they they fixed their issue their
issues their double standards they fixed
it
isn't it kind of late yeah yeah you'll
see chiari you'll see
i i i haven't seen this one in a long
time yeah it's been me too me too
very much pretty boy all that hair oh
it's fun
he must be washing it with gravy just
like me
it's not exactly my time yeah i was
going to say too i know that
prince charming is supposed to be like
the stereotypical like hot guy and
it's like a heartthrob which is good i
applaud them for that not personally my
type but
pork illustrative oh no
wait a body oh it's that kind of
magazine
yeah with shrek who's very attractive on
the inside
oh yeah so you said what's the problem
baby what's the problem i don't know
well maybe i'm in love think about it
every time i think about it can't stop
thinking about it how much longer will
it take to
cure this just to cure it because i
can't
ignore it oh my god you know the lyrics
makes you want to turn around and face
me but i don't know
nothing about love come on come on
turn a little closer faster come on come
on
the world will follow after come on come
everybody's after love i'm trying not to
get dmca stricken but i know this song
i had it on my ipod back in the day
because of this movie
oh so i said i'm a snowball oh no
yeah i get her bye
oh the sharks that's what's good
[Laughter]
it's good stuff can amelia be prince
charming they both have
like luscious blonde hair and blue eyes
[Music]
i feel like it's a fit is that from the
reading from lord of the rings
yeah i mean kind of looks like oh
never alone never alone no no
i mean definitely with those valentine's
day cards you're definitely
pretty charming yeah definitely uh oh oh
it's fine those are my other headphones
you're good you're good
it's cool don't worry about it we're not
using them
so who's you know it was is there's like
a taco monster in this movie or
sexy
that's kind of rude you can't teach
children that this is okay
listen every time i go to the public
pool and there are children doing that
they're like oh hi it's funny because
shrek did it no
stop that movie stop children's movies
yeah well no i mean you just know that
they did you just know that they saw it
in like a kid's movie
and it was haha funny this is rude
gosh the songs first wreck are so
important though mm-hmm
sure are mm-hmm
[Music]
good thing we're not watching strike
three
oh oh donkey's been lonely
good job donkey
oh no well you look at the time
what if we kissed on shrek's couch
no chad now
just with each other
without without you
nice thank you
oh donkey
going out with the homies
they just want to spend some time
together
oh they love each other i'm so happy
donkey stop
oh other guys
hmm
wait the king he didn't he didn't get
married yet though didn't he
oh the king the king
oh it's it's transparency yeah
wait whatever happened to lord parker uh
he's in the dragon's stomach
oh oh really apparently still alive yeah
right you're right scottish accent
great
[Music]
i'm gonna watch uh shrek more times so
that i can practice that accent
yeah yeah i think you could really get
it down perfectly because i wanted to
speak some
english british and scottish and all
that australian canadian accents
want to learn those you should do your
best accent stream
of course shrek gives in he can't resist
fiona
no no they won't party time boys
freak out
moving on row hi
wait is this where donkey's gonna be
like are we are we daring
are we here no way but now
where we're now where we're now kelly
are we there
no kelly what about now no
how about now
what about now no are we there now
no yes yes no who am i now kelly
kelly kelly are we no kelly
tell me are we there oh are we there we
did it funny
plain intend to switch or something
don't tempt him shrek do not tempt him
oh oh
what's he gonna do oh
no no no
no
five minutes
chill
yata oh man i wanted to see more of that
no it's party time
hey welcome to far far away oh
yes here we go oh not yet hold on
it's california it looks like california
it looks yeah it does it does looks very
similar
it's funky town time for a guy that's
right for me
[Music]
talk about it
taco bell
hey all right
funky town
wow
oh it's mom and dad his head's a lot
bigger than hers
huh yeah i just kind of noticed you'll
see you'll see
i mean yeah it's pretty good yeah this
is pretty big not as big as lord folk
i mean yeah definitely not but still i
think it's kind of sweet i don't know
there's something cute about it
time to step out of the onion come on
[Music]
gasps
i think they're a very cute couple
bye
very happy
no
i love this part it's very well written
oh
oh harold i think i remember a bit about
him now
was me also quite the colored
so nice to meet you beating the in-laws
and i'm not sure if they take that as a
compliment yeah that's you got to read
the room shrek
my man you're doing your best but you
got to read the room dog
the big bird above him about to catch
him
it's you big bird
oh he's very angry what is that
caviar come on shrek you've eaten
we've eaten growth or things
i guess so
oh excuse me so she's still polite
they're perfect for each other that's
perfect
[Music]
i prefer shipping donkey and shrek yeah
same they got a real sweet romance
bromance sorry
oh no he's a friend
mhm
[Music]
respect the donkey that's right
no no oh
yeah i wouldn't have known yeah i said
look at how polite donkey is so elegant
so elegant
he's a noble noble state steve yes deed
seed steve mr seeds noble steve yeah
noble steve
the children
oh that's rude
oh i love this scene
i'm tasty lobster
once again or is that a turkey
guess it's a turkey 50 cute ogres
oh my god
oh you spread those legs yeah spread the
oh hey look at those tricky legs
oh
they're just enjoying dinner
i think they're going to be great
friends oh yeah pig yummy
catch the pig doggy
poor pig
oh fiona is upset
she didn't like that
hmm it's very stressful
if the timer stops moving don't worry my
head's a little big i think
sorry you can't see the movie no problem
there we go that's not so big
well you want to fix your hand maybe
yeah i fixed it i fixed it
it you didn't yeah i did it's smaller
now look at it your hand
oh my hand are you right
poor hand
what
i know what every princess needs
do you remember the shrek 2 movie better
than shrek 1
yep why um i think i had lived a couple
more millennia
uh when i saw this movie i watched it
more recently
[Music]
i also really loved the video game girl
also loved the video game video game
never i never played a shrek video game
nope it was all i played back in the day
for the ps2
[Music]
your troubles will soon be gone with a
flick of the wrist and a
just a flash a ton of cash oh no game
about track two
yeah mm-hmm
[Music]
the video game was great it was a good
game
prince would date write your name on the
bathroom wall
give fiona a call oh my god i can't
believe i remember so much of this
the show for kyle oh my god
[Music]
hmm
stop that makes you go crazy
oh no come back man
hey
oh
that puppy is so cute but i prefer big
big big dogs you like big dogs yeah
little ones they're really big ones like
samoa samoyeds
the big boys i like greyhounds and um
the ones with the really long nose oh
the
boards something i love those ones
boris zoie's something i forget
dreadnoughs
corgis though yeah yeah yeah boys kills
away of course
all size dogs are good i wanna pet
the corgis but they're pretty cute
yeah oh you're an ogre too
oh [\h__\h] stupid dog
sacrificed some things didn't she never
let me down before
indeed indeed it's true because she
loves him that's why she's okay with
sacrifice and losing us
exactly that's the whole point mm-hmm no
no no that's what's married what
marriage is about
about you know giving up some things for
them for the person you love
yeah you gotta make sure that me what
you want apparently yeah yeah
that's the word on the street huh
donkey is a good wingman
[Music]
mm-hmm
oh
good morning yeah she's a good mama
gosh i don't like him
yeah he's a little superficial but i
think he'll learn his lesson
he's at least redeemable unlike lord
farquaad
[Music]
y'all be hit y'all [\h__\h] oh harold
oh harold
oh
it's this nice bloody room in the toast
bloody tower
yeah that's a good point
kfb
welcome to kfp i like it number nine
uh number one is with a side of
surprise what's that line i don't know
that by heart seeing contrary to
everyone in the
in the chat
where is that boy
[Music]
says fat boy on it
for the kingdom i can't believe how many
lines from this movie i remember
unbelievable i can't believe it i
watched this movie so many times back in
the day
does she want him to keep it water
yeah probably something like that what
something like that
he doesn't look like a guy who could
kill someone honestly why would you give
him that job
no way he could do that yeah i guess
it's time who's there it's time
dude you're missing an eye yeah i think
that you look super handsome
like my town oh
with a little drop of boys
i owned the soundtrack back in the day
just play it throughout the house oh
that makes sense
oh no that's a sexton woman
i mean i still think she's pretty cute
who's the guy
her eyebrows need some workout she could
get him waxed a little bit just a little
clean she already got that wax she's
just painting them on
oh i see i see
also that lip liner needs some work too
could also be a little better
into my room
i love antonio banderas cat
what is that is that oh it's my
valuable services
it's our boy elgato
boot booth
i'm glad all that music oh
it says oh that happens
[Music]
everyone says is that justin
oh that song so cathartic
tried county sheep no wait it's i'm in
too deep
then later it's a tri-county sheet but
the wheels keep spinning around
no don't feel too bad
shrek
you can't snoop shrek you can't
you can't be a snoopy
why would you send it away
no oh no
she was quite obsessed with that huh no
no
she wrote that a long time ago shrek
she's changed
she's changed she loves you for who you
are
calm dad
yeah go fishing together
that's super ishii
hello sauce
hey
you can hear the furry he's happy
he's happy to see them
come here
no no gotta be careful of those orange
cats what a sweet kitty
oh
wow wow
[Music]
no i hate it when cats do that makes me
so worried about it i get really scared
for them
yeah oh that feels better huh
oh good baby
i didn't like that
oh
[Music]
baby
no it's not true
not helping buddy
hmm
that looks like that business card that
we got in um
in uh papers please yeah pink vice
yeah like a strip club
oh yeah you're right
yeah yeah i gotta go find some mizu hang
on
[Music]
i need to go wash my hands real quick
keep watching the movie entertain the
thing i'm watching
i'll lead 2010 to people the movie's
entertaining are you right you're right
oh it is a tear oh
gosh my ear hurts from the earphones
now i won't do it again everything's
just gonna be bad guys
also my foot fell asleep so
i feel i feel uh very ticklish i can't
move right now
um
oh
[Music]
so cute [\h__\h] that puppy cats are
superior
stupid puppy you can't do anything
without you owner
cats cats are independent cats poop when
they want to poop
you gotta have your person bring you
outside to poop and to pee
i mean dogs are okay i love dogs too but
cats are superior
now you're crossing the light
i don't like dogs i've lived with dogs
before
they're very cute what are we loving
okay
welcome back i'm ready for more shrek
thank you
yeah what the [\h__\h] dad
you don't know that though
shut up man you know you're talking she
already found happiness yo i mean it's
lost chocolate
yeah that kind of sucks
oh my god the cat is manipulating shrek
mm-hmm
[Music]
i um cats but they are kind of evil
sometimes
[Music]
well i like that that savage part about
them
they're such good friends now donkey's
jealous
i would be too
that looks just like her
that's a lie she got that face tune
going on now film this
no way
they're so smart
oh no no
the burbs and the tigers no
big ol factory is this what it's like in
kfp kiara
um
way nicer replacement yeah yeah i
believe
i'll believe you i hope you give them
dental insurance
damn they have to pay for it themselves
but yeah okay they can get any insurance
they want as long as they pay for it
wow that's great
you know this is a pg movie like a
hashtag
kelly lost no no no this is a pg movie
oh she harsh though why are you trying
to say [\h__\h] huh yeah she's pretty harsh
uh well maybe hell yeah they do
yeah those dirty green sausages that
knee
he does have sausage fingers yep that's
true
hmm
it totally blends in wow looks like he
belongs there for sure
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hold on
he's so excited to be friends to shrek i
mean who wouldn't be
um
hmm
ah oh no panic time
oh it's a little small
yeah i probably just need to break the
whole thing
uh oh
oh i remember this song
[Music]
hey
fall in love with someone never fall in
love in love with someone never fallen
in love with someone you shouldn't fall
in love with
bringing it down
[Music]
copyright hold on
yeah fall in love with someone you fall
in love with
makes sense true true true true
that level was really fun in the video
game
deep fried and smothered in chocolate i
kind of like those things separate but
you know
someone you know my chocolate contest
yeah someone sent in fried chicken
covered in chocolate
i'm so mad some people may enjoy that
maybe it tastes too good they're just
trying to tease me
yeah the running part yeah you know what
i'm
oh
i remember the plot now
i remember the plot these first two
movies
had such good plots he's well thought
out
eel no no
yeah they're absolutely solid i think so
too
oh no i'm jealous boy
no don't drink all of it ah
beautiful
maybe it doesn't work on doggies
i remember back in the day i couldn't
believe that puss in boots said the a
word
but he loves fiona moore
i knew it ah
[Music]
[Applause]
that's unfortunate
no no it's not true shrek it's not true
what's in concussion is that a side
effect it was a concussion
are you saying that the fairy godmother
is connected with
emilia watson amelia
[Music]
oh
just gotta you just gotta give it a
minute guys gotta give it a minute
sometimes it takes a minute to work
hmm
tomorrow oh sleepy
oh
[Music]
oh i love fiona and she loves shrek and
shrek loves fiona
they're so cute true love
oh oh oh the potion affects her too
yeah yeah
no but i remember what uh
donkey transformed into but i don't
remember what happened to shrapnel clc
oh [\h__\h]
he he becomes i'd i guess beautiful
[Music]
i mean it's still shrek on the inside so
you know will kill us
oh my god ladies no please please
a new kick haha
look at him kitty
it worked oh
my god
i don't remember that at all yeah you
turned into that yeah
oh he's got the girls
[Music]
look at these chads trotting
this is having fun
oh you should have read the small
letters
enough oh no
haha
[Laughter]
no
the poor horse
huh perfect don't need that wig though
oh my god
i don't really need the wig
ah there you go perfect
that's a bit better yeah
i love this song
[Music]
time may change me but i
can't change time
oh look at how confident he is now
that's kind of nice
what i was looking for i i can't i can't
dead straights
got
[Music]
me no stop turn around but then the
movie would end so
no oh no
oh oh
how sexy
it's me yet for you baby
no
you want to dance pretty much
just strangle her shrek just kill her
throw her out the window you could do it
you're powerful enough
those big strong man hands eat her oh
oh no no not all
no that's not shrek
your accent too huh where's the scottish
accent
yeah we're just scottish accents
was he supposed to be shrek forever like
come on man
she knows something's wrong she's like
this ain't my shrek
no
what a jerk a slapper
you're gonna spit around and slap her
throw out the window
what a jerk [\h__\h]
no
says the fairy what the hell okay but
yeah she's also an ogre dog
no
no you know what you're talking about
lady
it's a misunderstanding
[Music]
prince charming doesn't have direct's
personality she's gonna be miserable
forever
she can't be yourself with prince
charming
people just ain't no good i remember
this song
[Music]
top 10 saddest anime moments
no she thinks that he is you it's
another misunderstanding
did we not learn our lesson from the
first movie
it's i
unhappy hour i like that
she
oh she
told you
no
oh no
oh
no
so yeah god the drank that too
he drank it and then kissed his wife
yeah yeah yeah you'll see you'll see
you'll see what his deal is
uh oh i don't understand why prince
charming can't just go find
uh a princess that he's more compatible
with yeah you know
i'm sure that there's a lot of uh
shallow princesses yeah yeah yeah i
would like him just for his looks and
like lack of personality that would be
like and then they'd have a great life
together yeah exactly and they'd have a
great life together both
they would be both be happy
oh [\h__\h]
this lady reminds me of someone in real
life
the announcer yeah i think probably
knowing knowing that this movie
it may be probably based off of someone
real
a chat says yes
joe in reverse who's dab i'm not sure
probably a special tv person
seems very familiar
i remember this part from the game more
than the movie
the freaking mice they're so cute
the bad fish
nice
no
that's just you know cat cat wheat yeah
cat grass cat cat cabbage cat cafe
catnip
they're like oh we gotta do something
yummy
no no you can't
i give catnip to my cats before they act
really cute
yeah they do they nuzzle their their
heads all up to it so
yeah you love it
dad no don't do it
damn right she knows
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank god
dead donkey
this part in the game was so fun you
break them out of prison
and you can play as the different
characters yeah
[Music]
that's freaking commission impossible
i thought this part with pinocchio was
so funny back in the day you'll see
[Music]
amateurs
there you go there you go
oh god
oh he likes wearing those funks huh
nice and comfy to each their own i mean
don't tell the don't do not tell chat if
you're a thunk
i'll not tell them my reference
same i do have my preference
[Music]
let's talk about it after stream yeah
yeah once we once we turn off the stream
oh it didn't didn't who gave that to who
didn't someone give that
to in christmas it wasn't that one of
the presents i don't know
put it in the bad libya
so that's what gouda wears huh probably
i don't know though i'm not speaking
from experience can't guarantee you
cannot guarantee cannot confirm
yeah there was nothing like that in the
pictures we saw
[Music]
thirsty oh
nothing in there
jumbo cute
he's wearing lipstick
he's a bad actor yeah not very good you
got to be more like shrek
oh i remember this
all of you wanted me to sing this at
karaoke
other good men gone
where are all the gods
where's the streetwise hercules to fight
the rising odds
isn't there a white knight
on the fire steed
she does have a pretty singer stem
yeah what oh
yeah get him oh
hit it
hero this is such a good
sequence
the good voice yes i agree yeah
i like the beach me too oh
oh no the flaming gum drops no
someone stopped this madness stop it
wait is is is the mother man supposed to
be like godzilla right now
yeah pretty much pretty much get him big
boy
no no no no is that hot milk
nice hair dude working
oh working you know she gotta be out of
breath from doing that
dancing and singing is tough bro you can
probably confirm
yes oh yes oh yes yeah
no another one no
ah no
jinjin
go
nice one yeah nice save nice save
no be good
oh no
yeah he's got it he's got a super secret
technique you'll see
being cute isn't just being
[Music]
oh thank god it's not a shrek that's
shrek
yes
[Music]
happy end for him again yeah
yeah roar away nice
oh donkey to the rescue
no no
that didn't last long this is a good
movie
i got it i got it yay
yeah bros they became friends character
development noise
no no oh
nasty
yucky
no kick him in the nuts come on do it
yeah
that's not that nice because my dad is a
chad that's why
oh
oh you're right you didn't drink it oh
yeah oh i forgot no
no
harold no
bye yay dead
dead no
oh rip it ribbit damn frog
i'm fried frog
i mean being a frog is not that bad
yeah you would know
was he originally a frog yeah mm-hmm
but then then his wife kissed him and
then you became a human
being yeah oh
i forgot
he's a cute frog good frog dad
no well then i'm surprised he's not more
understanding of the
he was not more understanding of the
whole shrek thing yeah
cause he had lost his way a bit i guess
but it's okay
it's all good now love prevails
oh
hmm
so cute
it's a good movie it's a good movie
it's okay you're cute you're so cute
you're so cute as a donkey it's fine
oh
[Applause]
black cats and voodoo dolls i feel
a preposition that girl's gonna make me
fall
here we go
new kicks in the candle light
for every day and night she makes you
take your clothes off and go
dancing in the rain
but take away your brain like a bullet
to
your brain they actually eddie murphy
and antonio and padera sound really good
singing together
[Music]
no
bring it down
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
the jumping pose high school musical
jumping pose
they say yeah isn't this the one with
this with the scene afterwards
they turned into a little musical then
let's watch the credits
too
you know that the the producer that was
just written there jeffrey katzen yeah
yeah you know what
katzenberg means a mountain of cats
really
german oh that's dope that's such a
weird last name
people in germany don't usually have
that name oh yeah
is it a german name yeah cat mountain
yeah cat mountain
i want to go to cat mountain i don't i
don't know that i don't think that
exists
well i want to go to a mountain of cats
that would be nice
i'd love a mountain of cats cats that
love me and want to
come up to me you didn't isn't my cats
they're very loving
hit him with the remix need a hero
uh-huh break it down ay ay ay
here we go
oh by myself
oh good catch up
compadre
oh the wife is here
could have come earlier would have made
things look a lot easier
would have been helpful
i guess they kind of had to nerf the
team it would have been too strong
yeah oh yeah
oh my god you're dead flying donkeys
oh look at the children that's so
adorable
oh
i don't know how they i gotta get a job
oh my god
beautiful nice
[Music]
guys yeah we watched one in two we did
it it was a shrek marathon super special
shredding
marathon was this movie shorter than the
last one oh no it's about the same
about the scene the other one also ended
around 120
yeah i mean you really seem to like the
second one a lot because you watched it
many times you played the game but i
personally have to say i prefer it in
the first are you like the first one
i still think the first one's good yeah
you know this
is still a sequel i just remember it the
most but i still think one is probably
the best
yeah i'm not a big fan of sequels in
general i like contained stories that
happen in one go and don't continue
afterwards but this is this is an
exception
but wait have you seen shrek3 or have it
just not yeah i saw it in theaters i saw
it once and i never saw it again i
didn't think i didn't hate it but i
don't think it was very great
you know i watched and i was like yeah i
guess that's the third trek movie
i mean now that we watch one and two i
think eventually even if it's not that
good we still have to watch
three and four one day do we have two we
have to
just to end the the shrek stock and then
and then one day we can
you know watch five when five comes out
yeah a lot of people are saying four is
better than three
but we gotta get there yeah
okay maybe maybe we'll watch it i'm not
sure what one is i mean i
love the fourth up maybe i've never seen
that a lot of people are saying that the
three is not very good four is is okay
uh
drag four don't force yourself
oh you guys are so you guys are true
lovers
look at these true shrek lovers in chat
they just love shrek so much
but like it's like when people say that
the hobbit wasn't good i love the hobbit
i mean people just have
extremely high standards i don't know
yeah i guess that's true
also my internet is just too so i cannot
look up shrek for it
oh that's cool i'm sure that we'll we'll
figure it out later ah
with that guy with the crazy hair huh
crazy hair
oh no that that is not is that it oh
it was not the third one i think i
remember that being the third one but oh
is that the third one uh maybe i'm the
one that might be wrong
because they did they named the fourth
one 40 and the third one 3d
i'm not sure that's a good question
huh nothing's going to the funky town
maybe i can look it up
no no no no no one with the crazy hair
is the fourth one oh really though oh
that that one is also originally german
isn't it uh because of the grimm's
fairy tales all those uh fairy tales are
originally german
yeah it says the final chapter that
wasn't very
yeah isn't there a fifth one coming out
well that one's
i i i don't remember that one being bad
what about the shrek forever after the
final chapter so i did watch that one
but i wouldn't mind watching it again
here let me see then how about shrek
shrek the third i remember
this is the one that i watched i
remember this
the wait is over see the fact that i
don't remember the plot
probably means it was really not that
good
i don't know what happened in that movie
i have no idea i don't think they have
children yet
i'm not sure but i see his baby
i think that they find out that they're
going to have children i don't know i
can't i can't
quite remember so i guess i don't know
if you guys want to if you guys want to
i mean we've watched we've watched bad
movies together in the past
so i mean if it's a bad movie then it's
a bad movie but we still will enjoy
watching it together
i guess that's the end huh
that was fun i gotta stretch after this
and then i gotta play video game later
so yeah
shrek shrek thank you shrek lovers for
joining
two other shrek lovers and watching the
shrek movies it has been done
mission accomplished yeah we did it hey
hey break it down now
can i um ask you one thing alex yeah
um you did you did
watch my new music video right
no i haven't seen it yet no
at all i mean i i took a i took a little
listen i listened to the song but i
haven't seen the music video yet
i play i played it in the background i
thought it was very cute
but i haven't looked at it yet you
realize that
i made a song for you huh
what you're even in the video that's why
that's what i kept telling you did you
watch it yeah did you watch it yeah i
listened to it
yeah you have to watch it oh and the
lyrics are also all about you but i
guess yeah
the video just makes it easier to
understand that's why you should be
watching the video oh
i'm i i was keeping it um i told you
before that i'm making a new song and i
told you it's like really some
valentine's day but i kept the secret
that it's actually for you so i've been
waiting that you watch it ah not a
holiday i've been really excited that
to get your reaction okay well i'll i'll
watch it i'll watch it later
i'll watch it later i didn't know it was
about it it was about me
i mean it what you you give it's about
giving chocolate right
that's that's why i also made that
chocolate making stream and made the
chocolate for you
oh because it's all related it's all
connected to my song for you
i see i see no not now i want to watch
it later by myself
okay but yeah there's a scene where you
show up actually
oh i do yeah i didn't know that
you know i don't remember doing that
[Applause]
it's austin school in school yeah in a
school setting
and um me like uh realizing oh it's
valentine's day soon so i start like
figuring out how to make chocolate i
look at recipe books
and then i start making chocolate and
then i then i write a letter that
for you and i'm like oh my god i just
have too many feelings to convey
i don't know how to write it all in one
letter and then
and then i've tried to figure out what
to wear and what to do with my hair
and it's like a whole process you know
and then finally finally after the
guitar solo
i i am ready and i i confess my love to
you
and i give you the letter and the
chocolate and you yeah well you see
we will see what happens yeah that's so
that was my original earlier release
song on valentine's day
okay wow i guess i'll have to go watch
it there is an english translation so
in the subtitles so you might you might
want to join those on oh yeah
hey i can understand some japanese hey
listen
what you said you listened to the song
and you didn't realize it's about you
i mean hey lyrics are still hard for me
to understand you say the same about my
lyrics their english oh they're just too
fast they're too freaking fast
yeah well you know sometimes it'd be
like that but i think if you
read along you'll understand if you're
watching
okay anyway that shrek movie was fun
yeah let's let's uh let's um
sing some of those shrek movies in there
yeah yeah those special shrek songs i'm
ready anytime any day of the week
baby yeah i guess that's all
for now yes yeah good donkey
good cat yeah good shrek the most
the most handsome out of everyone we
love shrek here we're all big shrek fans
so i guess i'm your mori i hope you'll
remember me
okay as always yeah and and and say
goodbye to the people
and in german we say peter james
exactly
[Music]
bye guys keep loving shrek peace peace
freedom freedom that's in germany
for freedom really aggressively freedom
freedom uh freedom
freedom was that okay
yeah baby
[Music]
do