[Music]
so
uh
[Music]
so
oh
um
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
no
amelia
watson
no
no what
no no
hello
okay
um i am
i'm here to watch the concert with you
guys today i have the wrong pen lights i
don't i i was i think i only have these
moving ones from
the first gen
concert
pen night oh my god
please forgive me it is
8 30 in the morning
uh
damn
did you see that
onion
onion my korean friends as well
um so there is on the official live
channel there's a
um
a free free section
probably what 30 minutes or something
probably
as per usual
um
did you guys watch the panel
i linked it in the pinned comment it was
a few hours ago
did you guys watch the
myth panel i just i just woke up i like
i went on discord i saw a few pictures
of things
i also saw
miko
miku daniel
and
ahmed onion
small almond meeting
mikko dunya
and people meeting no
small ahmed what yeah um
good i don't know what's going on
i don't know what's going on yet i also
didn't watch the the video yet that khan
would have made with ahmed on ami's
channel i want to watch that how long is
that
maybe we can watch it now
um
oh [\h__\h] that close to the website i'll
keep it open
12 minutes oh we can watch it now
yeah
oh let's watch it to wake up um
but i will download it if that's okay
and then show it to you guys that way
i i did some voice lines but honestly i
i i just did them one by one and then i
don't i don't i don't know
i don't know
anything
i mean i know something that we're like
on on the moon or is something youtube
download
but i don't really i don't really know
anything
about anything about
i'm i don't know anything uh
um
i don't know
and
i don't
[Music]
it's gonna be maybe loud for a second
oh [\h__\h]
oh he said
oh whoa what is that format
what is that
what is that fancy format
tonight
okay i think it was this way and then
like this
okay go
here it is
[Music]
watson
get your grubby hands on my trident
hey gooda i wasn't gonna take it i mean
i only wanted to borrow it for a second
yeah well last time you borrowed it was
gone for three years
three shark years that was like nine
minutes in ahmed time
[Music]
hey hey why is it every time i see you
two you're bickering like children is
this how a group of idols should be
acting yes uh idols shouldn't be
stealing i wasn't stealing it you guys
know it's much and the christmas
decorations are still up
uh-huh borrowing the trident for
i'll take off the christmas decorations
i can't believe it's been three months
already since the christmas party you've
got to believe it since we've cleaned
just think of it as three extra months
of christmas that makes sense since all
the time spent with you guys is a gift
what's happening whoa whoa
[Music]
it's so cheesy
oh it was so cheesy
brown rice wait for me
whoa
is that the spaceship i gave to almond
noise
let's get here why is she not using my
spaceship it's been interplanetary idols
traveling on a spaceship that's right my
dude huh
oh okay
uh i think we hit something big
hey guys
why are you so small
that is
abnormal holy [\h__\h]
she must have lost her swirly limiter
again
can you guys hear me
what do we do has anyone seen her size
limiter does it look like i just carry
her limiter
maybe holy [\h__\h] the lights look so good
what did i say oh
well ladies looks like it's time to suit
up is that not just a lollipop
[Music]
for a moment i thought they were gonna
reveal how pretty what do you mean this
is sour pretty this is so pretty
this is some dope fashion she's gonna be
like teletubbies
[Applause]
okay girls
[Laughter]
we need a better way to do this
oh yeah all right everyone let's go
you know take the lead
ah that's why i'm gonna get that sounds
wow
[Music]
you should be quiet guys i don't think
she knows we're here but i thought sound
doesn't travel in space oh that's right
kiara we could yodel and yell and she
wouldn't hear us
[Music]
i can talk in space because i am space
where is that song all right let's do
this
well that was easy i was like oh [\h__\h]
we're going to fall but no we're in
space
i'm beat let's go back inside
come here little fella
i'm small
because you are who will work we should
probably take her back to council yeah
we can't just keep her
but come on girl i bet sana wants to go
home too yeah plus we visit council all
the time
you'll always be mine in my heart
i'm a space learner
[Music]
all right to council
this one
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] up
who goes there oh no this is correct
who goes there hey cronster crow no no
our alarms almost went off and sawed and
lizard you guys into tiny chunks and
pieces buffana said we should disable
them uh thanks fauna
all folks
you guys found sana she kind of like
almost capsized our ship sana was gone
but luckily your local interplanetary
idols came to the rescue yeah i guess
santa forgot her limiter at her place oh
thank you guys for bringing her back
son of a beach roommate's cheating again
oh hey guys
what's with all the construction
oh wait here there are places we're
going to add a bathtub that fits five
people not ready our bodies are still
under construction too
uh after all this elevator messes up the
christmas party
there you go little one now don't get
lost again you're here
sana is eternal
sana
is an all-present constant being that
can never truly
thank you for reuniting me with my
friends chill santa i think can be
lonely
i don't understand any of what you just
said but you're so cute
[Music]
almost like something near the ship is
setting off the radar is it treasure i
could go for some sweet chains
we should probably go check that out oh
treasure
i want some
this looks important we should go we'll
see you guys later bye
bye bye
thanks again
see ya suckers what anomaly
no batman i wonder what it could be
it looks tasty um we are running low on
run time my dudes all right guys strap
in nina set the coordinates yara prepare
the jump sheriff and i call dibs on the
guns
this place could be dangerous hey i'm it
i mean which button is it again this one
[Music]
that wasn't so bad
we're here
oh
i'm cool
like you were all like oh
come here you little suit up ladies
radars are beeping and we're going in
[Music]
here we made it it's kind of hot here
could make a good vacation spot
oh we could put a kiddie pool over there
and then oh and then over there we could
put a cooler and have like a bunch of
like drinks and stuff oh a couple of
beers with wine
we set up here oh
keeps on talking this place is kind of
spooky guys don't worry i'll watch your
backsides it reminds me of the
underworld a bit oh kelly i wanna go
kiara we've talked about this the
underworld's no place for someone who
won't die well why not i could sneak
into your house and surprise you
like old times what are you talking
about
did you hear that
it's probably just the wind oh
that must be it
it kind of looks like some sort of
portal
it's like a [\h__\h] movie man
so cool
oh i see something shiny inside
yeah
huh just give me a sec it's a movie
let's investigate now when you're
sitting right now any weird switches or
buttons okay guys
what's that big glowy rock in the middle
maybe it's some sort of bomb
i want to touch it
why you
oh wow it actually feels pretty nice in
here
um i don't know if we should go in there
guys oh there's a little thingy here it
says
4d
i wonder what that could mean
it kind of feels nice in here you know
like a like a warm spot in the pool
you know
if the radar is beeping that stone could
contain some valuable materials let's
try to take it back to the ship and scan
it
i will take it no me this rocks hmm
don't break it guys i'll keep watch out
here
oh
[\h__\h] iris
you guys fell for my trap what who said
that show yourself
it is i iris
here to deliver help to the people what
does that even mean why
wait my hand stuck
mine too
why are you doing this iris i'm just
giving the people what they want now
tata
[Music]
in the morning are you guys there even i
can't see anything it's really dark wait
do you guys hear that
no i don't think we're alone
[Applause]
[Music]
my tail feels so real wow i can't wait
to dance
[Applause]
[Music]
that was amazing
that was
amazing
man
i'm
delivering us the good stuff as always
i know please watch it again on youtube
and give it a like
and leave a comment
that was great let me give it a thumbs
up
good thumbs up holy [\h__\h]
oh
animation by kana 3d assets by seafoam
voice script and sound design by ahmed
yeah she told me
on the vr chat day i think
that she was like she still had to do
the sound and all and i was like hey
you're doing that yourself what girl
[\h__\h]
yeah
sasuka
and so going
my girl my girl
please give her love and support
she deserves it
thank you
for making this video
it's so cool it's like a movie
so cool
hmm
that was great
you got done it you got me tied
and oh those poses at the end got me the
moment i saw them sheesh
okay hmm
six minutes i think until the concert
rain
[Music]
sorry
[Laughter]
six minutes
yeah
uh
what
what do you mean fauna voice i am kiwawa
kiwawa
iris
oh
oh i'm not
oh wait what
[\h__\h] what
i don't care
oh live indonesia
oh they did an announcement thing
[Music]
i wonder if i should preemptively uh
open it in a different browser because
last time
yeah last time
i had a problem
because it didn't load yeah it started
buffering maybe i should what did i what
browser did i do it on um what's that a
cortana was it cortana what the [\h__\h] is
cortana
no no no shut up cortana no no no not
you you're the wrong person i'm not
looking for cortana
edge edge oh yeah give me that straight
edge
oh wait i just realized this is the
browser for me this is the browser i'm
meant to be in
straight edge browser
yeah yeah don't forget about low latency
mode everybody um and if you feel like
syncing up with me even more then
um
stop the
feet on your side for like one or two
seconds maybe no yeah two or three
seconds maybe and try to sync up with me
that will give you a better experience
because then it won't be so awkwardly
delayed every time i'm cheering
um
yeah we gave every myth member a browser
before yeah yeah
okay quick login click uh
[\h__\h] uh
uh
oh i'm already logged in hallelujah
just a bit super house on it
my tickets
uh what do you mean there are no tick
uh
oh ah [\h__\h] i think i
put it into a different account yes i
did
oh wait shuttle wait
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
log
where is the log out
here
uh where is the login
this sounds like
macros frontier
music i know it's not but
not frontier delta
gives me markers macros delta vibes the
instrumental
oh my god right
oh my god
[Music]
[\h__\h] i should do this now i need to do
this now otherwise
otherwise i will be [\h__\h] later
[Music]
what song was that again
oh
you guys know
oh i think i'm logged in
ah stardust ah
[Music]
all right all right
right
what do you mean what do you mean what
what do you mean buy a ticket i already
i want to put my code in
oh don't [\h__\h] with me
i'm on the right account now my tickets
this is there we go
okay
okay okay okay
i'm ready
bridal time
do
right on time
okay um
whenever the girls come out i think i
might i might just i don't know if i
should i i want to watch it quietly and
i want you guys to enjoy it without my
screaming but i also want to cheer for
them oh that will be tough man that will
be tough
holding back but at the same time not
holding back
it's happening
first 30 minutes free on the official
whole live channel guys
is that la
pudato that sounds like la production
was that coriolis
let's go
oh my gosh oh my god oh my god i hear
people
probably gonna start with
um nipple rubble
turn up that volume
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm so tired but also so hyped up what a
moon
we got that bye
[Music]
wrong name they wrote the wrong name
there
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go
audience louder please i want to feel
them coronary
turn up the audience no i don't know
make him louder
[Music]
oh yeah they're introducing the day one
members only right now
[Music]
my girl
my baby
poor cow
is she gonna sing
if she does that i will kneel
oh my god
oh
the girls are here
the girls
oh my god
it's really happening
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
look at the people
[Music]
oh
idol outfit
have we seen that before sorry but
my brain
ah
hi
hey
[Music]
we haven't right
she stands out so much
hi hi
i see you guys
[Music]
mmm
oh
[Music]
food
i
[Music]
a
you
hmm
[Music]
oh
didn't just hear a cat or was the stream
oh my god
[Music]
why am i crying
i didn't bring tissues
oh
lookie mine
oh cool
oh my god
yay
hey
hey is that twerking
hey hey
ah cute
i'm gonna die
ah
oh
it looks so good
and sounds so good
hey
look how even
the beautiful colors
hey
callie's been real quiet
hi
whoa
thank you
huh
okay
[Music]
what's in it
perfect
these are my two first hotel guests so i
know those two girls
had them in my studio
oh
ah they're doing they're doing it
um
yay
cute
a
[Music]
that was so good that was so good
everybody's now changing their pen
lights like who's next who's next what
color should i do yeah be a bit tell me
early holy [\h__\h] it takes so long just to
change the color when there's so many
[\h__\h] colors dude
oh they're still here
she's telling them to turn off the pen
lights because she's just imitating
oh
she's like why are you doing that pose
oh just because
what
oh
she's saying they have a special
connection because they have been doing
radio a radio show for so long and they
announced the song in the radio show
yo it looks so real like they're really
like there
i mean they still look like anime girls
but still
talking about
having practice so hard
that they're focused on themselves
and weren't sure about the dance moves
saying weren't we killed yes you were
is anime real yes it is
apparently
4th gen 5th gen
en id
oh yes uh her ears
everyone is gonna be on stage
yes
oh they're solo songs
oh what kind of units will there be
it's over for us so
sad about having two part ways
[Music]
such a big stage let's run around
go go run my refund my money come on
oh
people
oh are they still keeping one seat empty
in between it looked like it
i
i spaced out i zoned out
[Laughter]
i'm tired man
i'm so tired
i think they're hinting
at songs
yeah
next song is a song with lots of people
on stage or like with everyone
she said sentai
i'm so tired i need to save energy when
they're not performing when they're just
chilling
oh oh cute
now they're like okay what color what
[\h__\h] color should i do
[Applause]
so light blue
red
ah okay free people okay changing colors
faster faster faster guys faster guys
faster are you ready with your colors
you got what you need
oh wait her alone first
[Music]
hi
oh
it looks so pretty
[Music]
huh
hey
is this still in the free portion or uh
is that over now
still free oh nice
nine more minutes oh okay
[Music]
oh nice close-up
oh
guitar let's go you air guitar
wow she can play avatar
i didn't see that coming
my eyes
[Laughter]
[Music]
look at the back there's a band yo
damn
sick man
yay
oh
cute
[Music]
she um
gave the audience a lot of energy i
think
ah
secret second circus
yo
okay it's not pop pop
hi
victomus
i'm ready
hey
[Music]
wake me up
wake me up inside
call my name and save me from myself
can't wait
she's so great i love photographs so
much
why is why is the fifth generation so
so based huh
why are they so dope lit and super based
no bass dope and super lit or something
like that
hey
oh
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
i'm doing otage don't mind me
yay
cold water yeah that would help
oh
i'm blind can't see you
two more minutes
broken two more minutes
perfect perfect
next is
[Music]
color
change your colors to yellow yes yes
faster
[Music]
hey
oh
cocky
rock and roll baby
hey
her cute voice fits the rock and rolls
so good what the [\h__\h]
damn
whoa whoa
hmm
let's go
hey
what
she did a flip
she's just flexing at this point
she's just leg sitting
man
the broke gang didn't even see the
cartwheel
she cut they cut up just before that
didn't they
or is it still going
so going okay i'll go
and i'm so tired
[Music]
this stream is for the tired gang
who still wanna vibe
[Laughter]
you'll be healthy what she said
something about uh uh keeping our our
ububs safe and treasured
why do you have my ububs give them back
to me
she's [\h__\h] built different
are they gonna do an mc
no music next three people i suppose
you need to drink water hydrate
everybody
my god oh my god oh my god very orange
looking here this is very orange
oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god all together
[Music]
i love this song so much
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
a
[Music]
i love this song so much
mm-hmm
[Music]
yes let's dance
one day one day i wanna do a unit with
energy
maybe in fourth four festivals
foreign
[Music]
moonlight merry-go-round
i always try to sing this song alone in
my karaoke
supposed to be sung with more people
[Applause]
[Music]
i met all of these three all of these
girls on the stage right now i met them
in in uh in japan
this is my
awful awful cordable
avocado unit
[Laughter]
i love that song
bye bye girls bye-bye
or are we getting emc
what's happening emcee i think it's time
for emcee
quiet total quiet
yes
time for mc
now let's candy go around
broken still here
very generous indeed
okay self introduction
30 minutes season 2 they forgot to turn
it off manage your son you forgot to
turn off the free section
is it still going it's been 40 minutes
but i don't know someone said that in
the comments
don't tell
it's like when you're in school and
you're the only one who did the homework
and you're telling the teacher that
they're forgetting about collecting the
homework and then everybody else in the
class hates you
[Laughter]
why did you have to say that kiana why
okay okay
let's see what will happen maybe it's
one hour holy [\h__\h]
then you gotta say thank you to yago
gotta say thank
you she's like holy [\h__\h] this is insane
oh
she wants to make them wave
separately
middle people
okay there's some people on the right
side joining as well
wait wait wait wait wait
live together
live together live together
oh
hmm
ah sorry we're talking about dance
lesson they started out with that move
oh i think that you said mata did it
really well
she said she likes that time when she
goes in the middle and she feels the
pressure from the side
said if you stand in the middle you
can't make a mistake
no it's okay
i'll translate what i can
oh yeah they can't cheer
ah
they can only clap
god i'm so tired
um
[Music]
really good
well they're talking about the previous
performances
i don't drink coffee
ah it's ending it's ending the broken
goodbye they're saying it's over sorry
as
so what super sample i said no more
[Laughter]
goodbye
you can still stay and get a rough idea
of what's happening
next song
[Music]
wake me up
wake me up inside
call my name oh
e-d-m-a
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh again okay
with
azuki
and then it oh okay
okay okay some rip repeaters
oh solos maybe this could be solos
though
yes it's solos
[Music]
are you ready
hey
[Music]
oh
i love corn
wow
[Music]
say
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
[Laughter]
[Applause]
love love
okay tired time for two seconds
this is a
husky
wake up wake up babe it's azuki
oh
her voice
hmm
beautiful
hey hey
[Music]
oh it's okay
okay
i i i i i
me
[Music]
yes wipe your hands
oh
it looks nice
[Music]
oh
those audience shots so nice
[Music]
next is an energy with a solo song
which one
no no no no no
[Music]
no no no
m
[Music]
seals in the background
wow she's really high energy today
it's
song
foreign
[Music]
yes
toilet town
everyone go to the toilet now there's no
other time to go you gotta go now toilet
time doing time
give it all you got let it out look at
that let it go
you're back
no no no no no no i'm gonna fall asleep
no no no no no wake me up
welcome back she's back from the toilet
break
let's go
[Music]
ah
she's so
cute i'm going to melt away
[Music]
who is next oh one two three four five
six
hachama
oh just uh those two okay oh
together
yeah red power hmm
i think they fit well together yeah
they have like a similar style of
singing
and they're both crazy yeah both crazy
wow
i don't know the song name
nice
high key
does someone know the song name
they're not writing it on the screen as
they usually do
oh they're putting it on twitter as
they're performed hold on
official twitter
i love that hike here
i need to rewatch this in hd
it's kind of
low mosaic for me a little bit
there's no i don't even see an option to
make the quality higher
um
it's the bitrate
i wonder if it's better in the archive
if it's fixed afterwards
ah not on low latency mode ah
okay
no no quality option for low latency
oh wow it's okay
wow that was great high energy rock and
roll
good duo very good duo
what's next mc looks like emcee feels
like emcee
yes
oh [\h__\h] oh it's dead
calm down angela calm down someone
someone
put some belts on her
hi duma
amazing how portugal who's really
energetic doesn't even seem that
energetic next to hanzo
well she says that from the previous
idol songs now suddenly you get some
rock
in her in the song that they did
and they're talking about
each song
that's the song name something like that
she said oh i already did my song
oh she's like oh hi tomorrow you didn't
sing
a solo song yet she's like are you
looking forward to it
now my
she moved so much
she's still in it
she's like look at my hideout friend
it's the first time on this stage and
then hotel was like really first time on
the stage and then puerto ka was like
well it's the first time for you on this
stage too
red combo
different red different red
[Laughter]
those two need to collab more
oh
um scolding here
[Laughter]
nice to call me
nice tsukumi and bokeh damn comedy duo
oh it's like did you forget to say
anything
oh my god
she's like i don't know what song i'll
sing but please look forward to it i
almost said it
she said everyone's used to you already
someone go get her manage your son
manage your son
she said it's life so there are no ngs
no cuts
oh my god
it's so enchanting
i love it
let's dive next song let's go
harvard that was the best emcee
[Music]
they brought some energy into the house
let's kiss hachima
[Music]
oh
pink and red colors
one sec
[Music]
oh
wow
[Music]
oh yeah miku senpai also big baby energy
lots of babies
cute
[Music]
hey
hmm
cute
[Music]
bubble
i'm gonna have some troubles translating
her
i love how official translations always
translate her in baby speak i guess i
need to do that too
oh
[Music]
how much work
it's going to turn whole talk into whole
world to work
[Music]
bumble
i'm losing my energy guys
when are the girls coming
[Music]
i need to keep my energy for them
we still haven't seen noira
and mikko and toa
yeah yeah yeah still haven't seen some
girls
nah man
oh man
fight oh
fight oh yes i'll hang in there
i'll keep my pacifier
for now
elite miko
oh yeah
what do you call this genre
it's like what is this
sheesh
trans oh yeah trans
sounds like trans so far
oh
it's nice to have different genres mixed
even if you don't really like trance but
oh it's really cool though
it's magical
oh
japanese is getting better get out of
here get out of here
woo
oh the cherry blossom is so nice
would be even better if they had like
cherry blossom petals falling down from
the ceiling man
that would be so dope holy [\h__\h]
oh
she is poor janitor
yeah the cleaning would be
um would really take a long time
yeah plus three thousand
for cleaning huh 3 000 won't even won't
even be enough probably
you gotta tell the audience to pick them
all up when they're leaving i'm sure
they will want to bring something home
as a souvenir
[Music]
those lasers
is so cool
ruin a reef yeah
elite elite elite
wow
that was really cool that set a
different mood this different vibe and
atmosphere
next is mine
i'll take off my
pacifier
oh
not ahoy
oh sheesh
wait what is she singing
monster hunter
it's not unison it's not
ahoy
no one knows
what does the official twitter say
yeah i think a new song would be kind of
weird to perform yeah angry
hey
cute
it's it gives me musical vibes
loki
new song
has she been talking about a new song
oh
it's like
adventure style song
i like it
oh flute
you're hurting here first guys
probably
hey
oh no the [\h__\h]
save the ship
don't don't leave the ship
essential must stay on the ship until
the bitter end
ship goes soon
ah her voice is so lovely
um
i love her voice
she's such a good singer
i feel like as a singer she's so
underrated because when people talk
about good whole life singers
they forget about her sometimes
she's so good
yo
[Music]
uh
too bad they can't sing along in the
audience
but she got that backup track
hey
oh
mc time
probably
no no i'm saying
oh yeah i guess they're doing free free
emcee free free emcee
[Music]
what are they going to sing
did someone just scream in the audience
yeah
a princess and knight ah
yeah that's cute that's a cute theme
baby and mommy
yeah princess and knight
so many fitting themes
kelly is crying in the corner
[Music]
oh
so unexpected but interesting combo came
over oh no
oh no
well no i don't know it's a game over
it's not a real game over you just gotta
go again and again and again and again
elden ring style hey hey
i
haha
oh
yes audience noise is necessary
i'm craving breakfast now
damn
i have pizza from last night but i want
to warm it up
don't worry i'll wait until the
[Music]
end sorry guys that i'm not
high energy anymore
[Music]
are you guys holding up how are you guys
doing
the best part is still coming yo
madame
mother mother
i i knew they would save us for the for
like later
it would have been dope if uh
ian and id would be in the free portion
for
obvious reasons
would have been cool
but that would reveal it too early i
guess
yeah we're too powerful
we can't be contained in the free
portion
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry gummy
yes they're now pointing out why they're
uh
a great powerful fitting unit
oh oh [\h__\h] luna just said did you ever
do something like a night though
you're not very nightish
she's like do you remember she played
games but she was really really really
effed up
roasted
talking about the song that she
performed
her solo song
she says that she's really happy to be
able to perform her original song in
front of so many people
she said she was really nervous
talking about mikko senpai
they're like was that really mikko
simply
was that really her
she looked really cool
no pawn moment
i sound barely conscious oh oh yeah i'm
trying to hold on
i'm trying
she was like what's what was wrong with
sancho she was so cool too
they sang shindeshimao
what is the song name
the lyrics there was also
a princess and a knight did you know
this
didn't have her solo yet
oh
she's roasting her so much she's like
have you ever seen dungeon doing
something cool
mitch is
okay they want to change colors you need
to give them a moment to switch your
curls down your pen lines they got to
push the button push push push push that
was fast
yo
these people are on another level
ah
no i just said ah now we we're getting
better along right
we got closer
she's satisfied okay we got nowhere to
stand by satisfied
it's time
for the next song
oh
wait what
is it
it's happening is i think
i think it's happening
she said that the people that everybody
was waiting for are coming
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] how do you want to know
i'm not ready [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm not
ready
this is happening
are my girls coming
so much
what's up
[Music]
calm down
oh my god oh my god
who's first and by that order it should
be you know
if they they always go by that order so
in yeah
oh my god
reflectors
so cool
[Music]
oh
let's go gurah
[Music]
screenshot guys
screenshots are okay
yes
this is the first time people are
singing go good alfredy
some of the see all this going to see
what you mean what do you know either
much i know
it shows
this part is so cool
oh
sparkles
how
there's real bubbles there you real
bubbles
[Music]
tell him gouda
what'd your vacation
shark is all you ever been
she
oh
[Music]
what do you think guys what do you think
wow
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
yes
typical army song
so cute
ah
she looks so good and pretty
[Music]
tiny
hmm
[Music]
i always feel like she's mistranslating
that but i don't miss pronunciation
every time she sings that
that word
but i don't know the real lyrics but i
think it's
mispronounced which makes it even cuter
[Music]
uh what do you call that the the thingy
on around her neck must be so annoying
wait when you look at that audience
point of view
it's really
mysterious
me tiny
[Music]
love her love yes
i'm fully awake now man i'm fully awake
[Music]
yeah my neurons are activated
clap guys clap audience so i'll [\h__\h]
arrest you
clap for my girl
you know
you know you know
please say no please
oh then i will go from purple to purple
i guess
ah so pretty
oh yes
so pretty
[Music]
oh
you know how are you so cute how how you
do it
ah she's so angelic
don't know how she dances in those heels
though holy [\h__\h]
her legs look so nice yo
[Music]
legs
looking respectfully
[Music]
oh man
such a pretty song
[Music]
tentacles doko
yeah the swaying hair is so pretty
[Music]
oh
ah [\h__\h] that's not it
i was so immersed
i know this song
[Music]
um
such an angel
how was it
i was the first three girls of ian
doing 3d for the first time ever
it's boone
oh her stance really cool already
isn't that her
new song yeah yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
i really like the song
yo she got that attitude
clap clap clap clap clap clap
like gravity
hmm
yeah
um
nice
[Applause]
good job
yo
i was ian id
it's not over yet though it's not over
hey
what's next what's next
i want to see people's reactions on
twitter and so on man
[Music]
yeah tomorrow it will be me and callie
and ill fiandisou
yes yes yes yes
still going strong tomorrow oh
oh i thought they were gonna perform
no suicide should be today she's on the
banner but she still hasn't performed in
thomas senpai as well right
i've been waiting for them too they're
the only ones
the only ones who haven't uh
performed yet
hmm
oh they're bound from the banner
me
they're saying it's the first time
seeing so many people on such a big
stage
oh they wanted to do something together
he wants to see those pen lights
oh
[Music]
not enough what do you mean not enough
everybody's already waving they can't
raise their voices
yeah too bad they can't raise their
voices man
saying that was fun
oh couldn't elsa want to do something
oh
train train time
[Music]
slow wave that is way slower than the
hatchimal wave
the train has stopped for a short break
some technical problems
going on going on moving on
we're soon arriving in uh tokyo station
and going back to
osaka going back to osaka
nagoya first nagoya first
okay i'm just happy
oh she wants to talk about how she feels
about today
oh
you're saying ian and id were really
cool and cute
finally everyone together
thanks to you
thanks for your support
she likes good on his ironman
performance
[Music]
do another cartwheel
oh she wanted to show off a cool side
because people always say she's not
elite not elite
oh
why is
mikurona here
because
huh
they're gonna sing together
afterwards
nice
oh
it might be a song that you don't expect
from them
oh first time performing that song
okay a new song
we'll be right back they'll be right
back
[Music]
it's like they're hiding something
special
well they are special
oh
huh
i know this song though
i know this
song what
fire
there's fire on the stage
ty okay disco
the fire is me
fire is me spitting fire there live
right now
bumper
i'm falling asleep again
i was like really hyped during the enid
part
gave all my last energy
but this is really good too
me corona is so cute
mikko senpai works so well with so many
people
water in the fire
can't wait for your performance tomorrow
thank you
yeah i will set the whole stage on fire
don't worry about that
[Music]
oh
i won't tell you what i'll sing
no no no no
otherwise my manager will kill me
whoa
it's getting hot in that first row
i really wonder how that feels i don't
think i've ever been um so close to
fire at a concert uh
in real life
i mean i've been in the first rows
before but never had that fire in front
of me
[Applause]
to lust
to hust
towards we say
come on you've been keeping us waiting
for the singing queens
okay okay
uh solo noir didn't get a solo yet
that's right
and hot tama too yeah yeah yeah
they're getting solos first
ah
if you watched whole talk
then you know the song
[Music]
sun
papa
[Music]
oh
i'm so tired
ok ok
[Music]
oh she's singing i'm tired i'm tired
she's even singing it now
foreign
[Music]
first review of enid and they make the
overseas fans
stay awake all [\h__\h] night man
it's tough to be a kai guy nicki isn't
it man
[Laughter]
well i mean you could watch the archive
i guess but who can [\h__\h] wait for
that huh
well her hair was like
that's not a red heart
that's not red hard
infinity
ah
oh yeah yeah yeah
more edm let's go
am i cute
until now it gave me carly rae jepsen
vibes for some reason
i don't know why
or else city i don't know what i'm
thinking of
i don't know
hey
wow the background
visuals okay
we're traveling i guess
we're traveling through infinity
she took a chill pill
compared to the
last time we saw her
she's really calm now
is that really hot tama no that's
akaihato probably
[Laughter]
um
okay never mind that carly comment i
think i'm thinking of owl city
my beloved
oh
sorry i need to stretch it
[Music]
thank you a tone
of gives you emotional
vibes that song
can do
hmm
don't say that
you gave me
you gave me some shivers
someone in the comments said thinking
this is her goodbye song to cuckoo make
me cry don't say that what the [\h__\h]
don't make me cry
was your bus late or what's going on
[\h__\h] traffic jam man
[\h__\h] cars
let's rock
oh camera is getting into it
[Music]
destroy my monitors over supply
oh it's back to normal
somewhat
whoa
she's like [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] and smashes my
monitor again
you're not getting to watch me in hd no
yeah
ah
[\h__\h] i see nothing
she's giving me everything and i see
nothing
[Music]
hey hey
hey hey hey
and hey
for life
yeah
she's too strong man
she's too strong
even the camera has woken up again
let's go camera man
let's go crane
show me the ceiling
slightly
i see those monitors i see those
monitors
yeah
[Music]
bad ass
sweet say
toko
she must have taken a
german train
oh come on
what is happening
[\h__\h] teasing us
eternally
okay azuki senpai and ppt
kanatan
it's the last boss yeah
oh
whoa
[Music]
really old vocaloid song
um
[Music]
i don't know
to japan
[Music]
hmm
hey
[Music]
yes
okay
[Music]
what
kanazu
they have a unit name
light light
and red oh i thought it was pink
ah
kanazu
which is basically just a combination of
their names
she's saying that they don't have much
time so she's gotta
spell
yeah
not talk too much
me corona ty okay disco
oh
saying that the otakus are getting going
crazy about mikuroni
oh
it was really cute
how many know me from noida was after
that
keep on praising keep on praising no i
just don't buy it
are they trying to twerk
nah they're imitating noise dance
they're saying they felt the emotion in
it
get more indeed
have fun at work see you tomorrow
born to be
born to be real
uh
from tulase empire
it was really cool i was saying it's
just just the usual they're commenting
on all the songs that were performed
was that kalora
it was great
it was really good
they had fun practicing
oh
saying they got closer by collabing
monkey monkey monkey monkey yeah they're
running out of time
oh yeah cause
kind of doesn't bite in a solo song too
you got
she just god
is dead i need to save energy
i'll be reviving soon
revival coming soon
it was a great song
with nice phrases because there was some
talking in the song
time is running out on you
revival in 3d hell yeah
last split
oh
yellow
they want them to change the color to
why
someone with the image color
yellow
oh super didn't get a solo yeah true
it's like a senpai overslept or
something
she's probably i'm stuck in bed
ah somebody
very yellow and orange and
finally first they woke up
okay okay
wake up darling
welcome darling
yes so by the senpai first
mods
five
senpai
nuero is fainting in the background
yes somebody was if
what an idol is like
damn
ah
idol oh my god
oh my god
i feel like she could be a character an
idol master
she would be perfect
like she's so perfect she could be a
character in a game you know what i mean
this is perfect she's like like dickie i
got that like
just perfection
she's what we all need man
[Music]
i
tropical vibes yeah
hey
oh man
i'm speechless
i need to dm her right now
i need to dmr
oh
i'm shaking my head in disbelief
it's just a girl
oh my god
why should i time
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go
cute
[Music]
bye
kim
yeah she's created dancing too
oh
i feel like out of
everyone in whole life
matsuri has the biggest
what you call it glow up
[Music]
me
oh thank you
i'm glad
you're enjoying the watch long
thank you
yay
and last but not least
so he says
oh the audience can't hold back the
cheers
yes
damn
oh
i'm just gonna
quietly enjoy this
wow
let's say quietly did i say quietly
ah
yes
queen
oh
[\h__\h] man she's killing me
oh [\h__\h]
gonna change my oshi just kidding
damn
oh
wow
oh my god
whoa she's just like i'm gonna go on
this stage last and [\h__\h] destroy
everything because who cares about day
two
i'm just gonna destroy the stage
i mean okay this isn't by worth it i
guess
worth it
holy macaroni
damn
did not see that coming
no i very much did see that coming
oh
ghost
i'm dead
don't mind me i'm dead
on so many levels
damn
ah
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
damn
sun
yeah
then
it was really really cool
really beautiful
so it was like yo when it's my turn
the whole time
same girl
sam
recent ghost how did you like it
very much
last do it
saying thank you for taking the last
spot
yeah
she's so energetic
very much like subaru senpai
so i was like i i really i really
respect super saiyan black for being so
energetic
but said it kind of awkwardly
saying that's not like you say say
it doesn't fit to you
after that
we're stellar
saying it's tough to follow up that
those genki songs those energetic songs
um
so he said somebody suggested singing it
and then told him i was like yeah yes i
like ghosts
she was feeling really really torn on
what to sing for her solo between stella
stella and ghost but then she ended up
choosing stella stella but still wanted
to choose using ghost as well so that's
why she suggested it as a
as a collab song so she could do both
so she got both nice the best of both
worlds
[Music]
new song born to be real
yo you late
[\h__\h] your alarm
throw it out of the window throw it on
the ground
you need a kiwawa alarm
next song apparently is the last one
use the hashtag it's
alive
um
oh
will there be an encoder
will there be an uncle to do
i was really sad at a third gen concert
that they didn't give an encore
it ended so abruptly
i hope they gave us one
hey
[Music]
yeah
last song with everyone but ian and id
unfortunately
yeah i would have loved to be part of
that too
oh
[Music]
they gave them
t-shirts i love that because like at
idle concerts
for the for the uncle they always
put on their merchandise t-shirts
i love that
huh
[Music]
the black ones look better
ah cute
be careful up there on the second floor
be careful
[\h__\h] it's so pixelated
i i
i i i i i i
oh
what's the empire really lower stuff
the uh
voices
she stands out so much
honestly i i i cannot believe
that tomorrow i'll be on that stage
nah
i still feel like i'm just gonna do
another watch along tomorrow and just be
on the outside again
hi i i i i i i i i i i i i i
it's so surreal
are you guys are excited
i'm coming for you
[Music]
i think uh short jeans shorts would have
looked good with that
but okay
i wanna design their stage outfits man
i've seen so many idol outfits
by going to so many idol concerts in
japan
i really just want to put some outfits
on them
thank you
yay
yay was that really the last song
no
i don't believe it
i'm going to now they can't even cheer
for uncle to candy
if the credits are rolling i guess that
means that's it
it's so sudden
no show me the audience clapping at
least a bit more
why you gotta roll the credits so fast
and destroy my hopes and dreams
[Music]
the god language
oh setlist there you go
[Music]
there you have your set list
airmen
candy go around
safe and vary
and so on
so tired yes very tired um i'm thinking
of just doing a super chat reading on
monday if that's okay
yeah i don't i don't think i can take
this
i need to eat breakfast and [\h__\h]
and sleep i'll go back to sleep i need
energy for tomorrow
yes reflect
put it put it in violet
great songs
is just
damn such a fun song
that must be so much fun to perform
hmm
and i think inna's song
is just so calm and and magical i'm sure
that the audience really loved having a
little bit more of a calm song there
and it showed off
her character and her
um beauty and all that
when i say character i mean like her
personality
because like she's she's the calm type
yeah
and for ame i mean i wish i wish she
could uh perform like some kind of
original
but punifully is something i connect
with her didn't she sing that in her
debut or definitely sometime in the very
very beginning
so
it's very nostalgic
so in that way it's kind of
emotional and fitting as well to put
uh in in that in that spot on the stage
yeah hopefully one day we can see her
performing original
but i'm proud of of the girls i'm proud
that we can finally
be on stage like that i mean
i think
at least for me it will be a while until
um i can really
like you know
do more like this i'm talking as if i've
already been on stage
not yet but
it will take a while
um but hopefully that will make it even
more special
um maybe maybe one day
[Music]
maybe one day we can have a ian
whole life english concert yeah
oh
now they're writing the
the um
the fan names there
tentacle chambers teammate teammates
tomorrow it will be can't be written
there
i hope they're not going to write a
kiana fan club
because that's
our old name
link your wish
link your wish whoever fruitfest
[Music]
hmm
i'm so hungry
damn
really talks like one of those uh tv
voices
it's a terribly boy course today
so hungry
oh they're splitting uh
uh
the announcement voices
iris
how did she pronounce vice verse
fun
i didn't even know they were doing that
i didn't i didn't know
oh only
oh
one day you'll be on stage too and
you'll [\h__\h] blow everyone away
cute cute kid
yeah i hope they can be on stage maybe
next year or so
hopefully
um
yeah
well
okay
this was day one everybody of whole live
food fest link your wish
uh
was pretty damn good i think they
improved like a lot from the last big
concert uh in terms of you know stage
and and you know
you know the way that uh we are on there
no one i don't wanna you know
break any immersion or whatever but i
thought it was really really well done
like it was really impressive oh
really really really good visuals
and uh the live band was awesome
big amazing venue thank god they're
they're doing in two days
yeah i've barely seen anything from the
expo because i literally just woke up
when
you know right before the concert
when uh expo was already
going on or like basically ending for
the day i guess
so uh i think after a nap if i can hold
back i'll take a look at
what's going on
at expo
look at those hats
camouflage
hats with our bodies
um gonna be honest i don't like
camouflage pattern
but i thought that one's funny
yeah oh look buttons buttons buttons
buttons yeah they're still showing the
merchandise
default post hats let's go
it looks so stiff man that default post
silhouette
oh now these are cute the stands of the
official artwork
here ina has the tentacles
false advertisement she didn't have the
tentacles in the in her performance yo
where were those tentacles
uh oh what else we have clear file set
um
oh
paul kerr the joker
and a pamphlet
oh yeah oh yeah
i wanna look at the pamphlet because uh
wearing that too
oh
all that whole live uh sweater it looks
like from some kind of university
coach jacket
interesting i didn't look at those
clothes yet before
beams me oh it's a collaboration with
beams
oh it's a fashion brand
okay they don't look very um
they don't look very
how to say anime-ish
gosh i'm so hungry
oh i'm so hungry
wait it doesn't even say here that
they're not allowed to talk but i guess
they told them separately i'm not
allowed to like scream it just says bore
your mask and [\h__\h]
don't record
premium booster pack
white swatch sponsored by
supported not sponsored supported by
restaurants play white spots everybody
they said that the stream started
man
that's that's the saddest thing
um
at least we can
as always raise our voices here at home
yeah the life was really good everyone
got like spotlight time everyone got a
solo song right everyone yeah everyone
got to sell the song everyone except ian
id got a unit song
uh and then the
united tete
final song and the first one as well
it was what three hours about three
hours
so they packed a lot into those three
hours i i gotta say it didn't feel like
three hours at all
it felt like i don't know
one and a half
that's so weird
something
[Music]
yeah it sounds really short it felt like
40 minutes probably because you watched
uh the free preview only
[Laughter]
no maybe you didn't but
just a funny tsukumi from my side
um
[Music]
i mean um
i think it's really cool that
ian got to sing solo songs um because
then you can really see
them for a longer time than if they just
performed one group song and then say
bye bye
and show off our original songs because
almost everyone from myth has an
original song
anyway so
yeah i gotta show him off right
um
[Music]
today i was still doing the waterline
but finally finally finally tomorrow
finally i will not be one i mean i'll
still do a watch along afterwards for
members only by the way if you didn't
know uh if you wanna like
watch it together uh like a couple hours
later
uh on my own
on my own with you guys i'll be doing
the watch along and members only so that
we can talk about it
and
yeah
go through it
step by step one by one
thank you guys for the super chats and
uh and the memberships
will be there oh
at the at the venue
looking at me and vadami senpai closely
so
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
ah oh man i want to look at the i want
to look at the reactions i want to also
watch the other watch lungs
to see their reactions to en and id
because like what hollow whole x didn't
watch long right i wonder what they how
they reacted to
my girls
what's going on on twitter let me go on
twitter what's happening on twitter are
there screenshots uh overloading from en
and id
scroll scroll
this
damn
damn oh oh
[Laughter]
perfect capture it's as if they saw it
coming as if they knew she was gonna do
a cartwheel damn how are you so ready
oh
oh screenshot screenshots oh
i see the screenshots
hey john writes muna is the hottest
performer i know
[Music]
oh cute screenshots on twitter
oh
good eye looks cute did i look so small
sorry i'm just going for twitter at this
point
damn
all right yeah are you excited for kelly
and me tomorrow and of course the others
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah
a backflip with my back
i think i will i will
die at the spot
by breaking my [\h__\h] back
[Laughter]
just because i'm a phoenix doesn't mean
we can risk something like that
yeah we'll have to
immediately break off the song and then
he called a called a wee while we were
emergency emergency
barrel roll if it's a forward roll i
guess i can do it although without a mat
on the on the bare ground that's pretty
tough
anyway
a wambulance
an ambulance called the ambulance
[Laughter]
at school
revival process
initiating one
two three failed error error what are
you gonna do if it even ever happens huh
gonna be so [\h__\h]
[Music]
up
you know
i'm like really excited and this concert
is so cool and all that but then i
still i'm so sorry i still have this
this huge feeling of like regret and and
sadness and
low-key loneliness for not being able to
like walk around the halls there and
[Music]
just walks around there in her small
farm form she can fit me in there no
can
she fit me and that's in that
it's not a suit small almond it's a real
small amount
nobody's inside there except
real small almonds
yeah right yeah well i guess you can't
fit me in
after all then [\h__\h]
there's nothing no no space to fit
anyone in there
no
[Laughter]
if only they would have like one day for
like uh only staff
yeah
although i mean i mean i it kind of
already exists because like with a big
ass venue like that
you
gotta you know build
[\h__\h]
you know so it's obviously like in
theory
you could go there
probably at least in the evening before
realistically speaking
yeah
i mean i'm sure there's some people who
check out the venue
the day before because otherwise it
would be chaotic and everything would go
wrong
yeah
hopefully hopefully
uh
assuming that we have a concert like
this every year hopefully
by the time it happens again
that the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] sea thing
will be
gone i i was so close i was so close to
pushing that button at the right time
but oh no there's a delay i was not able
to
censor myself correctly
the [\h__\h] sea thing
perfect timing
and oh imagine if that's gone then you
guys can come too
yeah
ah
then we gotta add a few days though i
had a few maybe at least one more day
to make space for more visitors
[Music]
live world tour next year
one can only dream
about these things now
yeah
a bigger venue i mean
uh these venues are pretty huge within
japan those are makuhani
is like um the the stage that you saw
is um
kind of like next to the uh halls where
expo is happening and i don't think they
even are using all of the halls
that makuhari has to offer so they could
still like rent the same venue and then
uh rent out more halls if they wanted to
but they're yeah they're definitely not
using all of the halls i've i've been
there a couple times um
well it's already pretty big damn
saitama arena but they wouldn't really
have halls for
an expo i think
they're just a live venue without the
extra holster that's the good thing
about makuhani because it's like a
it's like normal halls and then there's
a live concert hall
um
so it works well together if you want to
combine the aspect of an expo and a live
concert
have i been inside the master party no
[Music]
i've been in a lot of the big venues
watching my hello project concert but i
don't recall
there was another huge one but i think
maybe that maybe that was yokohama
yokohama arena
um
please release the ball oh is it not
available yet i guess it takes a little
while to
to uh
go through to process yeah i want to
watch it in hd again
has to process yeah yeah
give it some time give it some time
i'm sure it's late for the most of you
uh or early
want to take a nap and then visit
back visit it again revisit it
foreign
[Music]
um
how much of your tears will fall when
you debut on 3d tomorrow
i don't know
i don't know i can't cry when i'm on
stage
but i don't know
no i
it's so surreal i don't know it's hard
to imagine
i think once once i see the audience
holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] but there won't even be really
time to take in
what's happening i think
until afterwards yeah
yeah
i don't want to think about it i don't
want to think about it
just because i just did the watch along
it feels like it's not happening
i i i won't i won't be performing
tomorrow no no no no i'm i'm just the
the person who watches the concerts i'm
not the performer
kanka kudaiman
don't escape reality
that's a funny thing to say about
virtual youtubers yo
don't escape reality you tell me aren't
we all escaping reality
not only me but you too
by watching btubers
okay well as i said sorry guys i think i
need to recharge energy so i think i'll
just do a chill super chat reading and
chit chat on monday
also looking back on the concert on
monday
and talking about it and all that and
maybe telling you
catching up on those tangents
yes
yes yes so next time you'll see me is on
tomorrow on stage and then members only
uh after voice watch archive watch along
and also if you missed it uh
is there archive available now the
youtube archive of the panel
um we were the second panel after the
opening ceremony so pretty much in the
beginning of that expo stream it's in
the pinned comment actually let me take
a look let me take a look
oh yeah
it's available i think
yeah yeah yeah yeah
um for some reason it opened up in my
chat window
[\h__\h]
it's up yeah
uh
no exponential
and there we are oh yeah i i actually i
don't know if you guys have time to
watch it yet but i was the one
um
in charge of i was put in charge of
leading the panel and
um
yeah being the emcee
yeah yeah
management
said kiwawa you do it
and i was like
okay
yeah
there were some troubles uh
in creating the panel
yeah i need to watch it i need to watch
it see how they put it together um
i felt some pressure being the
being the lead
uh i had to uh
uh you know keep keep a strict schedule
uh and a good timing strict timing
because it was a what a one hour panel
an exact oh no actually
a little bit
a little bit less than a one hour panel
so yeah
very difficult to keep these ladies
within a certain time limit
okay
yes
keep the limits uh keep keep the girls
within the limits
hi
hi hi chi chi chi chi mi wait
huh
anyway anyway anyway oh
where was that screen
yeah
oh
no
they say you already watched the battle
it's just a start yeah it's sick
when was that
i'm trying to find it
i can't find it
ah no no no
where can i watch today's archive which
one there's a free portion on youtube
for about 40 minutes that you can watch
now of the beginning of the concert and
then there is an archive of the expo
panels and then there's an archive of
spawn
not yet they're still processing
uh on spawn but for that one you have to
pay
anyway
uh okay i'll leave you guys uh
at that uh holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
it's day one is over tomorrow is
um it into your memories and into your
eyes okay
look very closely and break a leg hey no
i will not break a leg i'm not part of
your system
but i will need your luck indeed please
wish me luck please wish me luck
i did i did practice my choreo for the
past uh let's say uh many many months
it's been
i've had it for a long long time so i
have more than enough time to prepare
so i hope um i'll be able to show it off
smoothly for you guys
and that you guys can
see
what a true idol looks like
you know
from way before when before knowing the
concert oh
it's happening
yes yes so
yeah it's time to release those limiters
oh also don't forget you know there's a
lot of things happening today but don't
forget to watch that video that uh ahmed
uploaded on her channel because that one
was really great too
coming tomorrow
thank you everybody and in germany
[Music]
live tweet it out tweet it out
tweet it out loud
link your wish
[Music]
no
that's not
it
i'll see you tomorrow in a different
point of view in a different
different
way
yes
let's get excited hi pie pie bye bye get
your pen lights ready to charge for
tomorrow don't forget don't forget your
pin lights yeah
bye bye bye bye
bye
thank you
[Music]
ba
wait what the [\h__\h]
i just saw the super chat you're gonna
you're gonna stay make me stay very long
on monday aren't you
oh by the way i'm thinking of putting up
like a like a chatting uh stream for you
guys to hang out during the concert
probably
uh
yes yes
[Music]
okay
see you there
holy [\h__\h] thanks for the support guys i
do not deserve that yet yet
i may deserve it tomorrow
but i guess those are preemptive thank
you very much thank you
[Music]
okay okay
see you on the other side yes yes
i'll be wait what no i'll be still
inside the screen i guess
bye bye
good night good
night a good day
that said
see you in japan
yeah
honda oh i see my show
[Music]
why are you guys still here
what are you doing
go home
[Music]
why are you still here it's my channel
it's my channel okay
i can be here
yeah oh okay bye-bye smoothie's here