oh
[Music]
is
you if it's
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
i'm
is
[Music]
so we'll take a solid look in the mirror
stand against time put your hand in mine
here and now you're part of me every
to get that gold never get old remember
[Music]
is
shall we
[Music]
inside
hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello
are you guys ready for a party guys i
want to show you something just wait a
minute hold on just hold on a [\h__\h]
second please be patient just hold just
hold
hold the [\h__\h] on just wait just wait a
minute just just wait one [\h__\h] second
just hold the [\h__\h] on
i have something to show you
[Music]
hi
hello
i'm here everyone howdy howdy a very
rare occasion hold on hold on hold on i
got my [\h__\h] i got my [\h__\h] i got my [\h__\h]
together i've got my [\h__\h] together okay
listen no no that's not the [\h__\h] i
wanted hold on no i'm learning how to
use this look this is new to me okay
this is very new this is very new hold
it wait go down go okay the reason i
decided to do this is because tomorrow i
wanted to hype up tomorrow's dancing 3d
yay 3d yata i'm going to be using this
um
well i want to save it for special
occasions i don't want to use it all the
time but this if there was any special
occasion i would say that this will be
it um
you know just just saying
that
why the [\h__\h] is this hashtag thing in
front of my [\h__\h]
go down go down you [\h__\h] you're ruining
my my look
you're ruining my freaking look
there we go
there we go in front of the thumbnail
anyway um
rawr xd hello everybody i'm here
um
and doing call-ins of friends
um there's still not a lot that i can do
with uh with this because i don't have
like special tracking quite yet
it's crazy because um even though i'm in
japan i think some of the other girls
can actually like technically do more
than me um
in terms of like how do i say
in terms of like tracking like hand
tracking body tracking and stuff like
that because they have those kinds of
suits and they're really hard to get
your hands on but the girls have already
worked at getting them
so they can actually probably do more
like movements than i can which i think
is is just kind of funny but
nah nah nah i'm gonna get one soo so
don't worry but uh yeah for now i've got
the default moves that i can do like of
course the famous jojo pose this is my
favorite one why is the phone
i really need to check um
like the order of things
my layers i thought i had checked for
everything but guys we are celebrating
can you believe it can you believe it
hold on
confetti
my birthday
yeah
yeah yeah
i hope you guys are all very excited
thank you for coming
lots of layers like an onion like my go
french shrek but you know what um i'm
planning on hopefully getting a chance
to do more like 3d stuff in the future
um especially after like um
tomorrow's birthday for now i want to
keep this kind of to a minimum until
everyone can pretty much do the same
thing
um
but yeah
i won't be doing it all the time
but this is one of those special moments
where you know it's like
i feel like it should be okay you know
i feel like it should be just just fine
moving myself over here because you know
it's a special occasion
yeah
and also to hype you guys up for
tomorrow's 3d because oh man that's the
thing that's happening
i'm gonna start doing my collins okay
and you guys aren't gonna know who they
are until you hear them
okay we decided to do them rather early
but
yeah
happy birth thank you very much we're
almost there not quite there yet all
right now let me go and talk
to my first my first person i hope their
volumes everyone's volume's a little
different so
here i am
[Music]
i hope that my settings are okay
i should have set them correctly hold on
just a moment there's default analog
three
baby face pro army
ah
[Music]
mosca
well that went well
yay
i thought i was so prepared you guys oh
that's
[Music]
oh no
she can't hear me you guys can't hurt
can't hear her i can't all right hold on
hold on
[Music]
hello hello
you're right actually yes my birthday
eve
nice nice that's right yeah birthday eve
is good
thank you so much dewicham for calling
me i'm so happy
me too
you're so cute that's awesome right yes
you're the first person to call me today
so happy oh my gosh how are how are you
i'm good how about you i'm excited but
uh i oh but i'm i'm nervous
nervous you're 3d
yeah so beautiful yeah oh
thank you very much yeah
my first time
yeah beautiful and cool
you're so nice
good is she
i'm glad i like it i'm happy
about i could be friend you
i didn't think
we could get along so well
but we will uh
friend right yeah very good friend i
think so
i
consider
you my best friend
best friend really yeah
and me i love you
i love you
again with you
oh yeah nice idea
nice id yes because uh i want you to
uh clear the game okay
yeah okay you're gonna play the game
no no problem you're wonderful
sugoi
yeah i was so impressed you're amazing
so keep working hard and
i want to see
i want to see dewey chan's 3d someday
soon okay
yes for sure
karaoke live stream
yeah yeah yeah and maybe play games uh
in 3d someday like um like darts do you
know darts
dads yeah yeah yeah they they have darts
at the 3d studio
yeah
okay
i was surprised so let's play together
yes
thank you for inviting me
of course of your countdown party yeah
of course no problem if uh if you have a
totsumachi
please uh please invite me
okay
i'm looking forward
uh
birthday concert your birthday concert
i'll do my best
and thank you
thank you for inviting me of course
love you too choo choo choo
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
hard on my singing training
so i can have that confidence to sing
with you
so next time
[Music]
yes great job well thank you so much i'm
happy i'm happy because
you like my music
thank you very much i'm so so happy and
please
do your best come back okay
[Music]
i will do my best
please okay don't give
[Music]
[Laughter]
bye mama
why is she so cute
man my my cohai are so cute why did i
choose them first
because now my heart's exploding and i'm
like i'm gonna throw up but like in a
good way
why'd i do this to myself guys i'm kind
of a dummy
whatever
anyway
next up i wonder who it could be i
wonder who it could be i'm glad i get to
talk to a lot of folks that i don't
really get to collab with often like
coyote we still haven't collaborated
together yet yeah
but we got a chance to chat with each
other on stream and that was nice we've
talked off stream but never on stream so
hello hello
oh my gosh kron is here
[Music]
oh yes celebrate beforehand yes yes yes
okay of course
yeah happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you
[Music]
is
um
[Laughter]
oh
yes please everyone please drink water
when are we going to collapse
[Laughter]
foreign
senpai
likes little kids
no no no no no no no no no i like no i
i like teaching
children english
ah
i like
short
um adult man
and adult woman
tough man
small body
man small body
i see it huh okay
okay
[Laughter]
you're so cute thank you for your nice
question kiss kiss i love
[Music]
yes please let's collaborate okay
yeah thank you all right bye bye
bye bye see you
soon
bye
[Music]
those are you saying fbi open up and
open up in chat i'm gonna i'm gonna
[\h__\h] kill you i'm gonna find out
where you live and i'm gonna destroy you
i'm gonna strangle you you don't know
what you're talking about
i will destroy you i will end you
okay
how do you even answer a question like
that these days
like hell yeah i do but like i like
teaching jeez
[Music]
how are you supposed to say that that
you find
that you find people endearing and like
to teach without sounding like a weirdo
anyway like i said i've mentioned this
before
it's the gap that i like
it's the gap
ah it's okay kroy chan is sweet and i
love her so it's fine she gets a pass
stop digging i'm not digging i'm
defending myself you have to defend
yourself in this freaky internet climate
all right listen i'm just i'm letting
you know that's how it is all right
don't get mad at me for defending myself
against the freaky internet all right
whatever man short kings i love you
short queens i love you you guys are
killing it in life also tall queens i
love you too
[Music]
it's all kings
you're also cool at the end of the day
it comes down to personality but i can't
i can't help a little a little blush
when like an adult short man walks
around in front of me i'm like oh wow
that's a that's a short adult man
whatever
i just think i just think short kings
deserve like respect you know
they don't get a lot of it and i think
they deserve it it i don't know it's
kind of weird well i'm waiting for the
next person to come because i guess she
she may have forgotten about it lol um
oh coyo chan so sweet
reminding her um yeah while i'm here
while i'm here i guess
cry is an average size average size is
beautiful too but when i see
i see crazy [\h__\h] on twitter like
some ladies saying hey short dudes will
never love you
who are you don't you speak for me
don't you speak for me who the [\h__\h] are
you anyway just wanted to let you guys
know that's how i feel it's getting hot
in here where is the air control i am
getting so hot i'm gonna turn the hair
down
i'm not sweating
i'm perfectly confident in what i'm
saying
anyway
i'm tall now and i feel sad
well i mean you're still great all i'm
saying is that it pisses me off when i
see folks on the
madames on the net saying things like
hey short dudes no one loves you makes
me sad i'll see that happen a lot for
tall dudes but to be honest i jumped to
your defense as well in that case
no matter what height you are what
matters is what's inside it's corny as
[\h__\h] but it's corny as [\h__\h] because it's
overused and it's overused for a reason
and the reason is because it's the truth
[Music]
that's it
well
my dearest missed her her turn but
that's okay because she may have another
chance to come back
now we've got another dear friend
waiting in the wings to come in
[Music]
we'll just we'll just let her in when
she's ready
might be shy
i don't know why is my mouth moved
hello
howdy
[Music]
huh
says renee
my discord
in one word
so it sounds like a discord
that's okay we wait for her
no worries reina you take your time okay
we're just hanging out you're good
you're good you're good
oh good all all according to plan
it's cause because we're waiting for
friends
no no no no no it's fine
push his glasses up man it would be
great to have megan air right now
but what can we do you guys this is the
best we can do
oh see internet moment
i wonder maybe she's not the only one i
don't know
bro the hands i just wish they could be
oh ollie's here though
ollie
what are you saying
oh my gosh
hey
happy birthday
you you sound like you're trapped in the
closet
i'm trying not to scream because on your
last birthday i nearly broke your ears
that's right i remember that you
screamed so loud that i thought i was
perishing i thought i was dying
do you even know how it feels to die
um i mean i have to be familiar with the
feeling as i am a reaper but i mean i
don't really know the consequences of it
you know
ah
ollie thank you so much for coming bye i
wonder why you sent me
this picture of you with your eyes
covered
yes you never know if it's really me
what is it what do you think you never
know is this your is this your mom on
the on the discord talking music
no but oh actually speaking of my mom my
mom actually sent you like an early
happy birthday eh
yeah
she's a very big fan of you wait what
is that
is that true or is that is that another
is that another april fool's joke
you can actually look for a clip of it
my mom is a very big fan
wow i saw that you did a stream with
your with your mom so i actually i think
i might need to check that out a little
bit later
nice i'm very honored that's sweet
yeah she listens to your songs like 24
7.
ollie mom
oh yeah thank you so much
that makes me happy
yeah
wow sadly though i i didn't bring you
any presents this year oh that's okay
you're my president
okay
no i'm okay i'm thinking
though i mean i think the deadbeats you
know they
i don't know they may wanna they might
wanna say callie do it do it for us do
it for us but
i don't know i don't wanna get banned on
youtube so i think i'm gonna go ahead
and pass on that one sorry about that
but
that that's okay you are my present
though just so you know
thank you but anyway since it's your
birthday do you have like any particular
wish you want to come true oh my wishes
let's see i feel like everybody kind of
already knows but i want to meet
everyone that i've met since i or
everyone that i've met online since i've
joined whole life so like i want to meet
you and all the indonesia girls and i
want to meet all the hololive english
girls um and i want to meet uh all the
others in jp that like i have
established a good relationship there
with other a lot of members in nola jp
that like i think are really cool but we
haven't talked very much so just
randomly meet up and be like hey yo
what's up it's kind of weird but i feel
like with the the indonesian branch at
least with the first two generations
haven't talked to the the new the new
folks very much but i hope to
um with everyone that i've met in uh en
and id i feel like we already have such
a good relationship with each other that
i could just hang out with you guys and
and go get some some drinks or if no
drinking we could just go party and i
could invite you guys to my house or
something like that kind of thing
so
that's my wishlist that's my wish
it'll come true for sure i hope so i
hope so we're all working hard for it so
yeah
let's keep doing our best
let's keep doing our best anyways again
happy birthday cali senpai i'm wishing
you all the best thank you so much ollie
you're so sweet and i love your passion
for everything you do keep up the hard
work okay
i will i'll make you prouder oh geez i'm
already too proud ollie if you make me
more proud i'll explode
awesome i'll wait
you're so silly i'll talk to you later
okay
talk to you later bye goodbye
peace there she go
there she go now kiss
no
don't kiss your friends too much
unless you read unless you guys have an
understanding
you gotta have a mutual understanding
you feel me
oh
please come
[Music]
let's see
okay got it we had a break in the middle
for a reason just in case anyone
couldn't come in the first part
and now who could it be
who could it be
next up on the chopping block i mean
next up in the the totsu
[Music]
she's still in machi though
we're waiting for rain
we're waiting for my fishing buddy there
she is
there she is
hello
everybody hello or is your internet okay
are you good
internet well you know the typical like
if you plug in a new device and then
your mic you know
like that i had some scuff in the
beginning too it happened
it always happens to me when you know
when it's you know somebody's birthday
during important stone like why please
but yeah
birthday eve
birthday eve yeah that's right it's
birthday eve oh thanks a lot reyna i
appreciate it
so excited to see you in 3d right now
too
i don't know no listen like
when when i first saw you in 3d like you
know the small cali 3d like and seeing
you like super expressive and 3d it
always you know see
basically seeing you move around is
always is always
in
interesting i know what's the right word
for it interesting but in a in a good
way i swear
i don't know what it is but if people
can see me move a lot i just suddenly
feel the need to move a lot to be honest
something about the myth girls just
makes me want to jump around and act
like a fool like i did in like high
school around my best friends
you know in front of other people i was
always super shy and didn't move around
a lot but whenever i got into a group
with my really good high school friends
i'd always be the joker doing like
stupid dances and like making a fool of
myself and being a public nuisance
chad said the word is captivating okay
it's captivating that's the
is really difficult english is difficult
all right yeah
he's a little bit you know
yeah still completely like native
sounding so i mean it's funny yes
actually yeah
i wouldn't say it if it wasn't true
omori wouldn't say it if it wasn't true
oh
i love you know i love to one day you
know play with you collab with you i
don't know in 3d when you know if if in
the future if it would be possible you
know seeing you you know because i also
like to move around yeah yeah yeah you
can just be dummies together yeah i
don't think a lot of people know but i
do really yeah move around a lot too so
i think it would be really really
interesting if like someday we could do
something together yeah let's do a ring
fit adventure together so
let's go
yeah and then let's i don't know just
meet and go eat yeah stuff together i
don't know izakaya
and you know what i bet by the time that
you and uh and the other gen 2 id girls
get your 3d thing it'll be
way way way easier to travel so i'm
going to set up the welcome wagon for
you yes oh definitely no
great everyone at ib
gen 2 when you guys get a chance to come
here to debut 3d i'm going to take you
all out for for drinks and they're all
on me okay oh yes ah thank you thank you
thank you let's have a lot of fun i'm
also super super hyped for the 3d
birthday concert yes the more more of
moving mori
yeah they actually told me to stop
moving so much because they're worried i
wasn't going to be able to sing well and
i'm like i'm like no it's fine and like
i could sing okay but they're like you
can sing better if you stop dancing so
much and i'm like okay
it's what makes you feel like you're you
right we need that movement
yeah i mean i guess it's true it just
means i need to build up my stamina but
you know what i'm three days away from
being able to go back to the gym so i'm
extremely excited
very nice i'm so so excited for tomorrow
too yeah good luck with that stamina
stamina building i'll do my best so
yes also also i have something to tell
you oh i remember that uh the little
thing we had the the the collab we had
the collab we had the three people
collab yeah it should be able to it
should be coming soonish
it's in the works should be coming soon
so much i've been thinking about it i
want everyone i need everyone to see it
it's so cool i need it i want to yeah
i'll let you know i'll let you know how
it goes okay
dead beaks get super excited because me
and me and renee and somebody else
bang history a mystery
yeah made a banger so get ready okay
get ready
yeah
i hope you have a lot of fun today and
tomorrow too i'm so so so excited for
you oh my best thanks a lot rainey thank
you for cheering for me
man all right will you take care of
yourself mwah here's a kiss for you
mama
god she's so damn cute
goodness gracious
why why are all my friends just the
cutest beings on this planet earth if
you don't think so fight me i'll [\h__\h]
kill you man outside the family mar i'll
be the [\h__\h] out of you
fight me
i will fight for that
anyway
that's all i wanted to say about that i
love my friends a lot
if you couldn't tell
they ain't speaking of friends speaking
of friends
[Music]
[Laughter]
stop it stop it i can't oh my god
[Music]
oh my god
thank you so much
iris thank you for joining in when are
you gonna finish jojo's so we can do a
jojo karaoke together i finished i
finished every everything yes everything
oh my gosh that means it's time you guys
iris and i we're gonna be we have to do
another karaoke collab at the studio and
we can sing some jojo songs yeah wait
are we allowed to sing songs at the
studio oh my god you know no we're gonna
make it happen yeah oh no worries i
actually um i got some arranges made of
songs actually i wanted to i wanted to
cover some jojo's songs um if you want
to like join in with me sometime
if you would like
people wouldn't be ready for it i would
kill to be a part of that yeah yeah i'll
let you know more about that later but
i'm glad that i have a jojo
i'm just like if i'm gonna call i need
to do that in the beginning yeah that's
right that was so perfect iris thank you
so much for coming on my my little
birthday countdown yeah i'm excited it's
almost only 15 minutes left 15 minutes
we're so close
yeah
thank you i'm trying not to not to use
it too much it's just this is a bit of a
special occasion so i'm like you know
what we might as well cause i'm gonna be
in 3d tomorrow anyway yeah i can't wait
for that tomorrow that's going to be big
yeah can we do that jojo pose again
sure thing i love that it's called chuni
syndrome pose i'm like why don't you
just call it oh i guess they can't for
for certain reasons but of course
but you know
this works well enough the fact that
they programmed this into the thing just
makes me so
incredibly happy
it had to have been honestly i what i
want to do is get someone else in this
in this room thing and then place them
back to back with me and then have them
do this pose
man i i want to do that pose one day man
that would be the thumbnail for for our
karaoke
yeah
oh man where is where's my 3d iris so we
can do a concert song together because
all i could think about was how badly i
wanted to sing on stage with you like at
some point
yeah one day one day yeah
one day i believe it because you know
you've been you've been popping off with
the singing lately so i'm sure that
you'll get to
get to shine in 3d too and do like some
some concerts of your own and stuff like
that so hopefully yeah
[Music]
i hope so
man
but
ah
i can't believe i can't believe that
your 3d is going to happen tomorrow i
know right even i'm like dang it
something we've been like all waiting
for for like you know e and e and 3d
right i really i'm i'm excited for the
others to also get the chance to because
it's kind of it's something that
everyone can do now um
so so that's that's exciting like i said
i wouldn't have i wouldn't have like
been okay to do this if the others
weren't allowed to do like 3d birthday
parties and stuff like that so
so um
i'm just excited i'm trying to not let
like the negative thoughts get to me and
just like look forward to to singing and
dancing for you guys because i practiced
really hard i practiced super hard the
other day my legs are still sore i saw i
thought you were dancing in swedish's
senpai's concert
you were busting moves i was kicking and
even sleeping was like wow she's moving
yeah
yeah it was pretty nutso to be honest
but i could imagine myself breathing
really heavily if i tried to move like
that
yeah i mean i kind of was but i was
controlling it really well so that's the
good news that i can do it but
performing live is tough man i tell you
what like i can imagine yeah i didn't
know it was going to be like that hard
but
yeah man you know it is what it is i
think iris are you are you um
showing up for the thing tomorrow yes i
am and i'm excited to see what's what's
what's in store for tomorrow
yeah
i hope you have fun with it oh yes i
will definitely i'm gonna i'm going to
have the time of my life yeah excellent
i can't wait for also uh jojo
the continuation of jojo's season uh you
know part six but oh dude yeah i thought
it was gonna happen in march and then
they just kind of announced it doesn't
happen in fall i'm like oh yeah it's a
long time to wait you know but it is
what it is at least we're getting fed
someday it's gonna it's gonna be worth
it that's what i know for sure for sure
for sure and you know what we can watch
it together yeah
if you want i got a i got a nice the
only like extra expensive thing i own in
my house is it is a large tv
you can come to my house so we can watch
it on the large tv that's about as it's
not bigger than the wall but it takes up
about like 70 percent of it so
that's pretty big
it's just because i wanted to play elden
ring like i bought that tv like a year
ago thinking about elden ring
um and what in high definition
yeah exactly
so um but then i ended up playing most
of elden ring on the monitor sitting
next to me for streams so whoopsies
yeah i can't i i really want to try it i
want to visit your your your humble
abode one day it's very small but you
know what i welcome you and there's a
place for you to sleep my couch is like
it's like a it works as a bed because
like i've got like three foot stools in
front of it so like honestly you could
just like lay out a blanket and sleep on
it so you're welcome anytime have a
little drinking party let's do it pop
some champagne let's do it let's do it i
miss i miss hanging out with friends but
me too yeah let me do that one day all
righty i think i should probably
uh
get out for the next person oh yeah
that's right yup the next person is not
a whole live member so i have to go call
them okay all right
all right love you dude talk to you
later
talk to you later bye bye bye
thank you iris goodbye
[Music]
there she go
now who could it be that i'm going to
call next
do you know
can you guess
let's start a little voice call
[Music]
hello
wow
see
thank you for showing over my birthday i
am great now that you're here and all my
friends
ah thank you for showing up i'm so happy
you showed up thank you well thank you
for calling me your voice is blessing my
ears really i'm glad to hear that i'm
sorry it must be an ungodly hour for you
no no no it's fine it's only 10 am it's
okay okay ah thank goodness how how are
you doing mousey i'm good i'm good i'm
just happy that i could talk to you on
your special day of course yeah i mean i
i wanted to invite you because you know
we've not only have we done so many
collabs but like i just feel like
you know you're such a cool like friend
to me and like an inspiration to what i
do like i've i've been seeing you like
get more and more recognition and i'm
like hey
hey check that out
mousey has like inspired me for so long
you're like the og i've said this a
gazillion times before what you deserve
this is the truth
it's the truth the og come on now you've
been at this for so long and i don't
know i mean i still
[Laughter]
let me tell you a little bit about the
v-tubing days
oh my god i like this voice keep going
oh sure i like to use the grandma voice
every once in a while oh grandma i want
to bake you cookies really you want to
bake me cookies or do you want to eat
cookies i bake for you
the golden girls sounds good to me
listen i just want to let you know that
you also inspire me and i'm just really
happy at all your success i'm so proud
of you and
your album is amazing and you're amazing
and everything you do is amazing and i
just want you to understand that i love
you everyone loves you everyone for you
and we're all happy for you but i'm and
i'm just happy that i get to spend
another birthday with you mom
you're gonna make me cry damn it don't
cry we can cry if you want to just
they're adding tears to our models at
some point soon but for now you can just
imagine that i'm tearing up a little bit
dang it
i don't know i'm only speaking the truth
dude
i'm just really honored to be honest
because like i don't know like i said i
really respect that you like brought
yourself up from
from nothing pretty much and like you're
so creative and amazing at what you do
and i'm just really glad we're friends
so thank you for for liking me and being
my friend no no thank you for liking me
and being my friend
god why are you the nicest person on the
planet
every time i talk to you it's like a ray
of sunshine is dropped straight onto the
stream
let me blind you now i can't say
let me blind you but you know what you
blind me because you are radiant and
you're amazing
oh god it's just gonna this is gonna
turn into a sugar fast again i can't
joke
i'm just telling the truth here listen
um um
i wouldn't lie to you okay if you if you
were just uh uh
i would be like oh yeah that's great
kelly yeah
yeah you're great kelly you're great no
you're amazing
accept it now
okay
thank you thank you
mousey i freaking adore you dude let's
hang again real soon
i saw that bae was on your bae was on
your uh talk show and i was so proud of
her i was like i would love i would love
to one day go on if you'll accept here's
me inviting myself over like a freaking
rude person
i'm dying to have you come on my
freaking show now oh yeah oh not now now
but now yeah a little busy at the moment
with the stream
yeah please i would be really happy to
um any time
i do i invite myself over to parties but
that's okay
listen i just haven't asked because i
know you've been super busy and i don't
want to be like
[Music]
you're very considerate you're a very
considerate person mousey thank you for
that and i do appreciate it hey windows
thank you
no thank you for being such a wonderful
person you're just
amazing let's have a play date soon
again okay yeah
thank you
you're doing your thing okay mousey you
do
all righty i'll talk to you later okay
happy birthday i can't wait to see your
concert thank you i'll do my best
knowing you're watching
do your best i love you
i love you too kiss for you
bye
there she go
there she go again
maybe the nicest person i've met my
entire life i don't know
wait hold on there are two actually
there are two people i know that every
time i talk to them it's just positivity
and sweetness and joy and love and
laughter this is the last person i'm
calling before the countdown
moshimoshi
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry for the uh epic entrance i thought
i had to do something you know i wish i
had i didn't have your volume down so
loud so we could have blasted out the
eardrums of everybody listening but it
was close enough they still hurt i'm so
sorry i'm so sorry i hope i didn't break
their eardrums oh no i hope it's fine oh
i hope that you send everyone to the
hospital with your beautiful
boy oh no no no no oh
i'm so happy that you invited me on
thank you so much
you're one of my bffs dude what the f of
course
thanks girl
oh i'm so happy ah
yeah so you're not regretting me asking
you to come under this this little
program on my veneer no i'm so happy
actually kelly thank you so much for
inviting me on the show regretting it i
really appreciate it actually appreciate
it oh yeah
now i'm getting out british but
i mean no milk is from iceland but she
she doesn't
uh conversations though i agree on the
short kings am i allowed to name drop
some short kings
wario
oh you get out of my stream with that
[\h__\h] just kidding you're allowed to stay
but holy god damn
i saw that clip that you posted on your
twitter and i was like oh lord who is
over there playing garlic phone with you
dude
oh don't you just love him though i
don't know when you say short king
that's who i think of think warrior
yeah well
yeah i know then king of something
you've only got like three minutes right
if i have something to say should i
should i say it now should i say no sure
right i don't even say anything i
prepare i prepare a little thing all
right here we go
cali hope you're excited for your
birthday and to showcase everything that
you've practiced hard for it's been
amazing to watch you grow and make an
impact on so many people's lives with
your music and personality
i'm so honored to have someone this
talented funny and inspiring as a friend
you keep going and doing you and going
towards your dreams and i'm so proud of
you can't wait to see what your next
year will bring we all love you cali
you wrote a whole ass speech for me
i mean i gotta write a speech you know i
can't just come out and sing jojo and
talk about wario
all time
god writes something i mean
you make a good point
i mean i mean every word of it you know
i wanted you know the deadbeats and
everyone we all we all are so proud i
love you so much callie and we're so
excited for your 3d concert and
everything you've achieved so good luck
honestly amazing that means the world to
me considering that like i know i've
mentioned this before in a lot of other
places but like you kind of convinced me
that like
idols aren't all like
ingenuine and like fake and stuff like
that and you can genuinely have like a
sweet personality and like
you showed me the idol truth which is to
make folks smile it like persists
through every single idol that i've ever
seen even the fake ones the real ones
the the ones that pander to different
people the the idol truth is to make
people smile and you like yeah i don't
know you showed me that and you made me
want to try and cry out for for holo so
thank you
i love you dude i love you me too kelly
you're your friend dude i can't wait
till we hang out again next time i'm
definitely i want to i want to stay over
at your place you can stay over at my
place that was just yeah definitely
especially if you can watch more mean
videos yeah watch more meme videos and
eat more moss burgers
let's do it let's do it okay that was
that was darn good those rice burgers
are so tasty
all right milky i'll talk to you soon
okay happy
thank birthday
so much for having me goodbye callie
goodbye bye
bye vilkey
peace
there she go
oh man
right as the last minute of me being
no plus one years old approaches
let me see the oh the seconds tick down
well it's not quite accurate but let's
go with it ten
nine eight seven
six
five
four
three
two
one yay hey
i'm no plus two years old
da
do a little dance
do a little dance huh
do a little dance yeah
do a little dance
yeah
do a little dance y'all
yeah yeah yay
something real quick
i love [\h__\h] up on things before i
hold on a sec
[Applause]
all right we're about to jump back into
a call anyway
anyway uh thank you everyone for the
very kind messages and the sweet super
chats look at these fireworks go
look at these fireworks go
i suppose i should do something how
about a roar pose
rawr xd
la my waffle copter cringe cringe cringe
cringe cringe cringe cringe cringe
cringe
while being self-aware does not make it
better
it does make me feel free
that's what counts doesn't it
doesn't it
it was kind of nutty is actually guys i
never really told you about this but um
why is this so in my face that's not
what i meant um
i never really told you guys actually i
probably did i think i actually
mentioned this before i definitely 100
mention this during a stream but i was
so afraid before a whole live of like
showing up and being cringe um and
people calling me cringe and like that
was something that terrified me for
whatever reason and then i thought to
myself how can i avoid that
and i thought well since you can't avoid
it make it your brand
just go ham with it and be the biggest
freaking idiot ever in your entire life
um
and you know what
it's worked out perfectly because it is
my brand what's up where are my cringe
lords at aka deadbeats how are you guys
doing that's right queen of cringe here
feeling proud where's my crown it's
already on my head see the crown on my
head that's the cringe crown anyway um
thank you so much for the big birthday
wishes
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you happy birthday it's
super effective
excelente
that's what we're looking for
this is maybe my favorite pose
i like this one because it's easy for me
to look smug
you know
like these
yeah yeah check it out check it out joe
anyway
i guess i better not keep the the
forgotten guest waiting
we gotta talk to her i won't i won't
leave her waiting there
so she can go get her much-needed sleep
she needs she needs her idol rest too
right
all idols need their rest
okay
i'm gonna jump in
[Music]
oh i i jumped into the waiting one uh ah
hello
senpai kawaii kawaii
kawaii so cute
thank you for
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
you are so cute thank you wow
oh my gosh i want a birthday present
birthday present
happy birthday to you
[Music]
thank you wow nice present now can i
please throw you
yeah
[Music]
thank you yes please please enjoy okay
yeah please come cheer for me thank you
oh
[Music]
she fled so quick
[Laughter]
she fled so fast
i love her
i shall come to accept me
she'll come to accept me
ah maybe i pushed a little too hard with
the throwing i gotta sneak it in there
you know
denied very typical
very typical
she's so cute though
hey do you guys want to see a birthday
present i got for myself would you be
interested in seeing it i am totally of
sound body in mind by the way
but i realized that there was a box in
my room that i hadn't opened yet
and i finally was i was cleaning my
house today and i was like you know what
i might as well open this and then i
opened it and lads let me tell you what
let me get la plus off the screen
because she's
she's uh not really wanting to submit to
being thrown by me let me go ahead and
put her away for now they're taking a
little break
i am of sound body in mind
this is normal
this is a normal thing
check it out pop-up parade
gurren lagann everything
went on amazon bought everything garand
lagon related that i wanted
there it is
check it and there's me too hanging out
with my friends because i'm friends with
them
you know
they're like they're like my brothers
so
yeah this is my little birthday gift to
myself you guys like it
yeah i opened it up before the stream
and i set up everything and i was like
i'm gonna i'm gonna flex on my device a
little bit
of course the yoko figurine is the the
bigger more detailed one but like it was
kind of funny because like like the bra
part right it's clearly a separate part
of the model
but if it is meant to be like or
supposed to be able to be taken off um
it's extremely hard to do so you can
tell it's a different piece right but
like uh boots are trying to like pull
off the bra like if you touch him and
like try and move him around he moves
around a little bit and it seems as
though you can break him off though so
it's almost like the model makers are
like oh you want to try and pull off
yoko's top like pull pull pull but [\h__\h]
around and find out destroy this
expensive figurine you bought [\h__\h]
around and find out you idiot
so whatever i like her like this she
looks nice
she looks she looks very nice i was just
curious i was just curious
what
why did you try no i didn't try i just
noticed that it was a separate item i
was like oh okay i don't care though i
don't actually care about that
it just made me laugh because i imagined
all the i imagined all the fans trying
to like take it off and stuff like that
you
new dirty yucky perverts you hentai
you hentai i can imagine you trying to
take it off and then you're like well
maybe if i just remove the stupid
pigmole and take the
and then you and then you look and then
it's like there's nothing special there
and you broke your [\h__\h] figurines
that's what you get you silly willy's
anyway just curiosity don't you ever get
curious i mean i don't really own a lot
of figures so
um
kind of my first time seeing that kind
of thing but
anyway i love my boys so much i put the
glasses on come you know because such an
iconic look and i'm dragging my friends
to my house for a movie marathon because
i got both the movies and i got friends
who haven't seen the series who have no
interest in watching the full series so
i'm like all right [\h__\h] i'm gonna sit
you down on the couch and you're gonna
watch the two [\h__\h] movies with me and
i'll cook for you okay does that sound
good and they're like okay curly
i think they kind of want to watch it
they just don't want the slog of sitting
through like 24 episodes it's not a slug
though it's perfectly timed in my
opinion but
whatever
i'm so glad they didn't make a sequel
it's just perfect the way that it is to
be honest a perfectly contained
masterpiece in my opinion anyway that's
me fangirling over gurren lagann i felt
like such a nerd like arranging all of
this i'm like
got some figures here
oh [\h__\h] i feel like a huge nerd but
that's fine it's not necessarily a bad
thing
anyway
a sequel would be too much yeah it ended
perfectly it's a perfectly contained
story
um and that it's because of that that i
actually like strive to write perfectly
contained stories that don't go on
forever or at least i did back in the
day when i was doing comics so
anyway we have another friend calling in
who could it be
hello
she's still in machi hold on oh there
she is there she go
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
i gotta raise your volume a little bit
because it's a little oh there we go
hello
hello who is the hello new phone who is
this
that is
just hanging glad to have invited you
welcome welcome welcome we're all just
just chatting but i was waiting for you
bae i was waiting for you because you
sent me a gift
you sent me a little gift didn't you
you sent me a little presento
i said you'll present so
and i
yeah it's a very uh
well i opened it i opened it so i could
have a picture of it yeah
yup it's not this gurren logan merch
hold on a second let me switch
however there may or may not be gurren
lag and merch included in the photo but
that was uh not bob bye
this is a beautiful flower
a beautiful flower sent to me
by my dear kohai
look at that
it smells wonderful it smells like like
fresh spring garden
yeah so this is they preserve flowers so
they'll last a lot longer really and
yeah they're preserved so you can yeah
they last only like one to three years
apparently
[Music]
but if you put them inside like a glass
case or something apparently they last
longer but
anyway maybe i'll get a little glass
case for them
yeah i just want i thought it was a
perfect because you know sakura it's
spring there and and also i've told you
before that your office your uh head
song is it was very special to me oh
you're so cute what the heck
it matches my hair too look at it yeah i
thought it was puff is that it's pretty
and sophisticated like you oh
i'm i'm not really i'm not really
sophisticated but thank you i appreciate
it i'm glad you i'm glad you were under
the illusion that i am thanks bae
thank you kindly i'm gonna put this
right next to the picture that uh kiara
drew of me so it'll match perfectly
yeah
i'm so excited for your concept
please come wave your glow sticks okay
yeah i'm gonna be vibing i'm gonna be
it's gonna i'm gonna be waving the
license so hard i'm gonna peg them at
someone you're gonna what
never mind yay yeah please please
um please come to the concert and cheer
for me i have i'm announcing really big
stuff too so it's a super important day
um so yeah i hope you'll have fun and
enjoy it you sound kind of tired i'm
sorry if i woke you up from a nap
oh no you didn't i'm just i i just i
just i had a nap earlier but i was just
i was studying like oh
study rad good job i wasn't proud
i'm proud of you
keep it up
you got to keep it up okay
keep up those those korean studies too i
saw your your korean society stream
that was cool yeah
multilingual rat you're so ako
rather
you
no
yes
yes i'll fight you i'll sit here in the
call for the rest of the totsumachi and
and and do a a yes no back and forth
with you bae i'll do it before you
[\h__\h] test me
don't you test me bae
[Applause]
i i
no i refuse to thank you but anyway
i look up to you a lot and have a
birthday and i love you okay bye okay
bye bye see y'all sleep well bye bye
another freaking
cutie very adorable
we love bae in this house
we love this rat
typically like i said you know we don't
really trust a rat
but this rap
this rat we trust this is a special rat
why has the phone been like between my
boobs the whole time
it's kind of weird
weird mouse sensitivity today
anyway oh
oh
oh oh oh
a friend is here
oh
of course you can you're too big for the
hat i set up for you there you go
sana too big
happy birthday beautiful
sauna you're so sweet thank you so much
dude how awesome
you're beautiful i am
healed
thanks a lot i i will pull it out every
once in a while for special occasions
such as this one so
yeah thanks for calling me while i'm in
the gym
yeah
pose is so gorgeous oh yeah let me do it
again for you
know
[Music]
thank you
of course yeah anything for you it's
like a present to me oh really anything
mostly anything
can you look up
can i can i look at you
[Laughter]
oh yeah shall we shall we just take a
little peek shall we oh oh oh
what's this
oh wow
i'm getting gazing into the universe
what a lovely under chin i have
oh thank you
wallpaper my best angle obviously
my best my best angle
sonia you're you're a freaking you're a
freaking troll i'm telling you now but i
i love that about you you're so sweet
and wholesome and then you you pull out
these
these knee slappers i tell you what
you're funny i love you dude you're
great
[\h__\h] you
i love eating yeah i feel very proud
that you are in my life cali
we do have we did have the longest
collab stream in en together didn't we
all we did yeah a lot of bonding was
done
you totally blasted through all my
social links
that's right yeah i blasted through all
the levels just easily right away it was
like no no contest
let me ask that i haven't seen personal
all day
can i say something right sure
that i don't think i can do any other
day
just because it's an embarrassing yeah
yeah i really
yes
um
i really
think that you bring the best out of
everyone you really do
yes you always just see the best out of
everyone around you
and you're just a treasure
oh
that's very nice i mean i try to there's
a there's a lot of shitty [\h__\h] garbage
going on everywhere around so i'm honest
i try to be as possible
you're a treasure in this world and i
speak from like i don't know being space
or space or bigger wow so it's a true
big
and you're always ready to try anything
and yeah
that's right that's why everybody loves
you and everybody is so attracted to
hang around you
because
yeah when we're with you
we want to do our best as well
you've been so cute i'm like
dang i don't even know what to say
i'm glad i'm getting i don't know what
i'm saying should i should i try that
again no i
no no no no
please
a treasure
in this universe
universe well space is space herself is
is saying that then i mean
i i guess i gotta i gotta stop being so
self-depreciative
self-de deprecate doubt self-dep
depre
something like that self-depreciating
about myself ladies and gentlemen yeah
it's a hard word
what is it what is it even what even is
the right way anyway don't answer chat
we'll get a gazillion different answers
um thank you sana that's very sweet of
you let's keep doing our best we can
just keep doing you because we all love
you callie
we can be the biggest idiot together in
our life i really i really like that
advice yeah in space that would be best
in all of space we can all be just the
biggest dumb dummy dorks together
you know yes please yeah i guess i want
to come over and eat something together
and sure i just yeah when i'm with you i
just want to
do everything
i'll be preparing for your arrival okay
whenever it is whenever we do get a
chance to hang i will be ready the
welcome wagon will be waiting for you
thank you thank you
you take care okay
leave the next person waiting too long
yes okay yeah excited for tomorrow
you're you're confident yay i'm so i'm
so excited i hope yeah i hope you'll
enjoy it i'm gonna give it my best give
it my all okay and and um excited for
the the other thing that we're gonna be
doing as well you're coming to that
aren't you
oh oh oh yes yeah you're actually gonna
be a little part of the stream so that's
exciting
please look forward to seeing that you
guys okay
i will look at your nervous i mean i
will look forward
oh yeah please feel free
everyone's looking at it feel free
all right sana i'll talk to you later
okay okay bye bye bye sana have a good
sleep
peace
here she goes she's right about the nose
though
thank you
where's the uh
jack daniels drinking
emoticon
senpai
yeah
cute sheep senpai yahoo
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you
senpai
thank
[Music]
okay
let's see your present um
[Laughter]
beautiful happy birthday glasses
my happy birthday
[Music]
wow let me try okay
let's try let's try glasses happy
birthday
glasses
hey what's
yeah yeah hello everyone peace sign
peace happy birthday
thank you senpai senpai i miss you
i miss you too
[Music]
yes i want to show you everyone me and
watame senpai made
something amazing amazing thing
secret secrets still secrets okay so
[Music]
is
okay
thank you so much for watching
let's jump in soon okay
okay duncan soon
okay okay bye bye
[Music]
i wanted to change poses but i didn't
these glasses are so special i'm like
oh man let me put them on mr skeleman
over here real quick because you know he
he looks like he could use
a little party favor
there you go oh the happy birthday's
backwards but that's fine the scuff is
you know it's kind of there's something
cute about it you know
something kind of cute about it for
sheep best sheep yeah between milky iron
mouse and um
and watame senpai i'm like oh i can t
pose too by the way um i'm like um
sweetest human beings in the earth are
my friends interesting
thank you
this is my dinner meat stick yes wow
thank
[Music]
um
wow anytime anytime okay
please you're so cute
i love you
see you soon okay let's play yes
she's so cute
[Music]
is
okay
no problem no problem i'm an english
teacher
yeah english teacher beautiful teacher
yes yes uh you did
so
good
last time
today
[Laughter]
who came up with this [\h__\h] lap
okay
amazing
i can become sexy
pirate captain
okay
it's a hat hat i need my pirate
um
[Music]
is
please yes i want to sing with you okay
[Music]
i love it
um
yes but uh but a little
a little kyoto
little space
little little space
okay
i love you bye
bye bye bye bye
i think i made her sad oh no
but i tried my best there to not break
my relationship with my senpai that's
very important you gotta remember your
relationships with your senpai
come
first they're very important
very important
you know
i tried my best i was getting pretty
desperate there though for a minute
i was pretty desperate oh by the way i
also received a little video you guys
um from somebody who couldn't make it
today would you like to see by perchance
would you like to take a gander
my sweet senpai could not come today but
that's okay because she gave me
many gifts
she gave me some sick gifts gifts
where is this video it's here somewhere
where is the birth there it is here we
go give it up for
my good dog senpai
hello
[Music]
do you remember me
carly do you remember me
okay okay uh number one question
well
wait
oh what day is it today
uh my birthday
it's my birthday
did i did i get it
happy birthday yes i can
wow many many dates
[Applause]
she gave me a kiss
[Music]
i what wait she gave
oh my gosh look
look what coronet senpai gave me you all
you all look check this out
okay
now i want you to look real hard okay
first i get this so i get to be me while
being me
isn't that crazy
i i swear my senpai just has like the
biggest brain on the planet sometimes
here let me just
she's such a smart dog
there is no smarter dog than corona
sempai
look now i'm me
and now i'm going to get the more uh the
most vital the most vital item
in this present package
from corona senpai is of course
you guessed it date tickets with corone
senpai
okay so i have 14 14 dates what happens
at date 14.
do we get the whole hands
oh man i feel like i'm leveling up my
social links today
like like i'm a like i'm a persona
character
oh my gosh
oh man
i'm so freaking happy right now
rawr
senpai
thank you so much
i'm so happy codenae senpai made a
little video for me even though she
couldn't be here today
i was so considerate of her to do
i'm not t posing anymore stop
i'm normal everything is fine
extra social link special events
on 14 you run from okay
okay gotcha so i'll be going to the gym
to prepare for that then good good good
well 14 dates unless we go on like three
dates per day then i think i have some
leeway i'll be fine
surely it'll be no problem
right
this seems like a lot for me to
a lot for me to process
you guys have to help me okay
you help me or i'll beat you
[Music]
one second
[Applause]
[Music]
one second
oh no someone got confused or maybe i i
gave the wrong time oh i'm such a big
pawn
let's see
[Music]
[Applause]
i hate time
zones hate time's up
anyway all good all good
no problem
we're all on we're all on time
now we're just waiting for another
friend to show up
so i'm a chill
marine senpai isn't here anymore sadly
much to my
incredible
[Music]
i sadness you
oh no
was it no it was not it was not the
crown
it was it was not the chrome street was
somebody not
not in the the shared discord i have one
more non-hollow friend to call tonight
so
yeah
ali sancho i can still feel her her
presence
in the moonlight
calling out to me kari tang
share the same bed and me screeching now
giving her a hug and running away
here let me at this person
[Music]
[Applause]
we talked to mousy we talked to mousey
before the date rolled over
and now it's the fourth
and now it's the fourth i was thinking
to myself what if i took um a sip of
this giant daniels every time i called
someone but then i was like uh no let's
not do that
let's never do that
but i will be casually sipping on a nice
regular whiskey
calvin no calvin's never coming back
well he might he might come back
actually he wants to play with ako but i
told him
don't you come around these parts
anymore you're
you're you're acting kind of
kind of silly you're you're being a big
dummy dum-dum
[Music]
i know a lot of you guys liked his uh
like this mixtape and i'm i'm happy for
that but he's he's uh
why
i just think that he's got the wrong
idea in what he's doing
definitely adam sandler
yeah we got adam to come join the join
the call-in
[Music]
for whatever reason my mouth has
sometimes been moving when like the
others are talking
it might be because
their voices are hearable through my
headphones which means dang there's some
good voice tracking here
but i went i don't want it to track my
voice i wanted to trap my mouth
what am i talking about this is just my
camera
well i don't i don't know if this per
this person is kind of notoriously
always asleep so um well she might she
might come and say hello another time
possibly because i don't plan to
immediately go to sleep i wanted to at
least try to um to uh crawl through some
of the past super chats right um i
wanted to get through the big
announcement super chat um
that i did a while ago just so we can
get in the jump king one too just so we
can make some progress before
uh tomorrow
because tomorrow uh might get a little i
mean hell today is wild
i'm i'm gonna group
today's supers and tomorrow's supers
together
um
in fact let me turn these [\h__\h] off
right now thank you so much for the
incredibly kind super chats you guys are
the freaking best and so sweet i'm very
excited to read these on stream
um on the fifth because on the fifth
we're having a big party to talk about
all the things that i'm announcing
tomorrow which are really freaking big
things
um
i know i've teased like the hell out of
some of this stuff but
it's um
it's kind of history in the making like
not just for me so i hope
i hope you guys will be happy with it um
so
fingers crossed it's it's a good thing
and something i'm happy about but you
don't you don't want to miss it i saw
the announcement video the other day and
like i almost started crying
i almost started crying so 4d stream
[\h__\h] they figured it out
j chad call the whole thing off
call it off
but
i think you guys are gonna be uh
excited
well i don't think i don't think that i
think that she may have overslept which
is fine because i've been there before i
mean i've done that with the
withdrawal deeral ahmed though i did
come in clutch and and woke up and then
wrote like a 30-second rap in 30 seconds
and then and then um she danced as a
muscle-bound um
ahmed for me
anyway that's okay if she drops by we'll
say hello but who do we have here
who do we have here dropping in oh
what a sweet
look that you have on your face right
there
the face of innocence
[Music]
let me raise your volume up a bit
oh oh me
yeah the face of innocence hello
hello yes
hi moomster how are you how are you
doing
wait can you hear me hold on i can hear
you perfectly
okay hi i'm good how are you happy
birthday oh thank you thank you for the
happy birthday wishes i'm looking at
this picture of you that you sent to me
now and i'm just like this fits so
perfectly because like you come in here
like oh hello cal you're like so sweet
and like adorable and then i tune into
your streams and you're drawing like
nightmare fuel
um
which is really like
yeah oh dad you have a present for me i
have a present yeah i bring it on i get
my own nightmare fuel doodle oh
you might be a bit disappointed
let me see
it's actually cute
this is so sweet i love this i'm
throwing it up on the jumbotron
is so cute
curveballs every once in a while
that's cute honestly i was i was
expecting like like a bloodborne
creature version of myself or something
like that
well honestly i was going to make like a
more uh sophisticated jojo
drawing of you but i got really mad and
i went to sleep and then i woke up and i
drew that
you can try it again if you want you
need those good vibes no it's okay this
is perfect this is the perfect um
perfect image look at this guys look at
how big uh my
my face is
yeah and my eyes
yeah
dang it they're uneven aren't they wait
i'm just now no no it's perfect the
problems oh no no no no wait
i've been there too look i see i think
it's perfect no no no no no this is
perfection you can't gosh you don't do
that it
yes i mean well
to real
to real life i mean
let me check hold on um
it's kind of hard to tell i feel like it
changes depending on the day
oh yeah it's like gravity or something
right yeah gravity like you're just your
body side you sleep on yeah yeah yeah it
happens to a lot of folks actually the
the
some of you guys may not know this but
the size changes often wasn't it i
didn't know this oh maybe that's because
you you don't have too much going on
there
but that that's not an insult that's
just me you know saying it listen listen
i'd give you half if i could my back is
[\h__\h] killing me i'd give it but yeah
no i think i think that if you get to a
certain size you notice that they like
change size every day
i know that yeah some of you guys in
chat know that yeah some of you some of
you folks out there who also carry the
burden oh
yeah of having a big head yeah
yeah your head oh yeah that's just
having a big old head
is it true that wait what part of your
body never stops going never mind this
is not the time for this um
it's always the time for this moment you
and i get into like the most bizarre but
awesome conversations in the world like
we were talking about like kabuto
creatures like down in the sea and like
making meals with them
and like looking up that [\h__\h] while
playing jump kick
and they were so cute right it's like
how can you put them they're cute it's
so watery too no i'm thinking of
something else that's like a sea
creature and when you cook it you have
to like get rid of all this water
oh at that uh
i kind of want to see i love weird sea
creatures
we should watch weird sea creature
cooking videos yeah weird sea creature
cooking
uh
we can do that off stream to be honest
i'm down
i am also down please cool
heck yeah
thanks for showing up moomster for the
sweet little drawing i love this song no
worries i hope you have a good birthday
i was so excited for your concert oh i
hope you love it thank you so much super
excited
i hope you have a good time that makes
me happy
i know i will i'm so excited
uh
i'll see you i see
happy birthday thank you for having me
here of course i'll see you later
moomster
i'll see you bye bye see ya
bye here she goes
why is it that i always add like stir to
the end of the kohai for ian like
cronester moonster i don't do it for bae
or fauna or sauna i guess it's just
those two
for them it's easy
i don't know
is there a friend here
there's a friend here waiting
all right guys get ready to have your
ears tickled
hello hello
is that a hello that i heard from you
is that a hello hey
i'm gonna hear you farfa no look at the
you look at your disc look at your
disclaimer
it's okay i started hearing my own voice
and that's an immediately get out of
that's all right you take your you take
your time
oh i remember why i can't hear you okay
all good in the neighborhood you take
your time fafa you take all the time you
need i'm putting the hat on your head
correctly
here we go hello hi can you hear me
testing testing i don't know why i can't
hear oh
hold on discord audio
out i can hear you option oh yeah
i was messing with my asmr last night
and i had my other headphones on or
they're the same headphones but they
were like plugged into the different
interface and i found everybody i see
that's all right
it happens to the best of us fun don't
even worry about it i know what that's
like too it's hard having a bunch of
microphones and stuff like that yes pain
in the butt million wires happy birthday
cat thank you thank you so much fun i
appreciate you calling in to say hello
and and wish me well
yes i'm
so excited for your concert and for your
announcements thank you i hope that i
hope that you're excited for it because
uh it's something i'm hype about but um
i don't know if everybody in ian knows i
know a couple people do do you know what
it is fauna
i don't think i know okay that's that's
even better don't try and look for it on
the desk
don't try and look for it even better
you'll be like whoa
i won't go snooping sometimes it's fun
to learn
with the hype with everybody else you
know right i've noticed that you get it
earlier surprises but it's also fun to
see the announcement the way it's meant
to be viewed you know
yeah yeah exactly with everybody else
super hype now i totally feel that to be
honest i i definitely i see where you're
coming from it's like not one and
wanting to be spoiled for like a pokemon
game so like you don't go on twitter for
like a gazillion years you blacklist any
words about pokemon
exactly yeah i feel ya
i do have a little something well you
said that you were expecting something
cursed from mummy yeah but you got
something cute
well if you're still seeing a curse oh
something cursed
here we go now this but this is art this
is like
an avant-garde
piece that i think everyone can really
appreciate um
wow is this like uh
i've turned you into one of my people oh
no not a triple kieran
oh oh
is this what all kierans look like
well you know kieran means a giraffe
right so oh
but you don't look like a giraffe
giraffe like well i'm not the giraffe
kieran i'm the mythical
elegant and beautiful kieran of the
forest oh okay
okay i'll turn you into a giraffe that's
cool where are my giraffe ears
oh under the veil
oh okay cool i see i see so i'm a
giraffe here let me see i can help you
hold on hold on okay
all right we can we can do this i was
doing this the other day in the studio i
was like trying to disconnect my head
from my neck so much and turn my neck
into a snake and i think the studio
people were getting really upset because
they were like gosh yeah i could do it
and like um one of my one of my senpai
who was there who's gonna be uh singing
with me was laughing super hard
and was trying to do it too
i want to see if
i can only do it in the studio yeah i'll
do i was doing like a little head thing
where i was like
but like it moves properly with my body
with this setup but when i'm in the
studio it's like i can disconnect my
head from my body and then i can truly
become the giraffe that will make you
proud
oh please
i can't wait yeah i turned my neck into
a noodle for you
just the finale of the concert right
yeah exactly i feel like it's because
it's important announcement of your
career i am becoming a giraffe everybody
precisely i will see you in the fields
see you all in the fields i'm a kieran
now
i mean i feel like um i feel like it's
become something like something of a
game for me to find ways to distort my
body and my model in like whatever way
that i can
um like you know with the whole looking
up thing i just burst out laughing so
hard and so when i got to the studio i
was like what can i do to contort myself
so ridiculously
yes
so
yeah
anyway
all right i think i see your next guest
is already waiting
oh my gosh i believe so
happy birthday kelly happy birthday
happy birthday
thanks so much
see you later goodbye fauna thanks for
dropping by
bye-bye
and we got a cute little fan art
cute little fan art from fall fall
now who is who is waiting for me right
now who could it be
who could it be
we have a friend in here
[Music]
we have a friend
a little friend
[Music]
oh reverb hi oh reverb hi
hey
ina
thank you eno i appreciate that i think
why does it feel like we haven't talked
in ages yet we literally collabed like
yesterday yeah i know right time
why am i tearing up already
no don't cry no no no it's not time for
crying you got to wait for tomorrow
you gotta wait for tomorrow
oh my gosh
dude i feel like it's been so long since
we've done like a one-on-one collab but
like i feel like every time that we
collab together it's just like for
whatever reason you know when i collab
with people i feel a lot more calm about
streaming but whenever i collab with you
it's like my most maximum like
comfortable time like i have like no
nerves at all and like no anxiety about
anything for whatever reason no matter
what we're doing even if we're playing
freaking guilty gear and there are a
bunch of fighting game enthusiasts in
the chat for whatever reason if if i'm
with you it's like i feel no anxiety
yeah it's just calm the zen yeah
something about you
enough i don't even know
what the heck
hey hey hold on a minute though i gotta
ask you how is your elden ring quest
going i see you're addicted that's good
i mean oh no
it's like oh my god oh no it's so
unfortunate
oh man
[Music]
i really wish that we were on the same
platform so we can play together but
yeah
that means that we can't there's another
game that you know since before debut we
talked about playing since before debut
guys since before i really bought at the
yeah not too long ago so
and play with you sometimes please oh
man if you feel like you need to finish
your elven ring quest first i totally
understand because
that is that is completely natural you
got to go kill maul become that elden
lord you know yeah
exactly get get get all the maidens in
the land but after that
you can join me and i'll go help you any
time that you want because by that time
me and snoop uh dupe snog are gonna be
uh really over leveled um but we can i
thought this would be kind of fun play
the dlc together
if you'd like
oh my gosh
which one
yeah that's the one and i'm trying to
convince iris to play bloodborne too so
i'm trying to get like a crew of the
three of us
yeah yeah it's a play so i think that
would be super fun we can do that too
and then anytime that you're playing um
and i'm not doing anything i might just
pop into your stream and be like hey ina
can i invade you to either help you or
you know
and maybe not kick your ass if we if we
wanted to do like a tournament because
though that's implying that i would kick
your ass you're really good at souls
games so i don't know but lauren has it
but i've been uh i've been practicing a
lot of perry so you know
if your timing
if your timing is see in bloodborne you
parry with a gun
oh
so like as someone as an enemy is like
about to attack you um you fire your gun
and that's how you stagger them
um so as long as your timing is good i
think you'll beat the [\h__\h] out of me ina
is getting scary good oh boy all right
well some pvp actually ina i wanted to
mention this i saw that some other folks
were doing like um
like some kind of little elden ring like
um competition where even though we're
playing on different platforms we all do
um like a race to see who can like
beat the tree sentinel with just a club
as like the waste of skin class oh yeah
okay so like you start a new file yeah
just go
i see i see it yeah whoever can be
yeah or margaret or whoever i just think
that would be super funny and like brute
force it and see who can do it first
that would be so
funny yeah
anyways
all my time is over i see it i see the
next guest i can talk to you forever
damn it
we could we can continue another time
yeah we are running on time here um i am
so so so proud of you you're like the
shining inspiration
like
to me and
i don't know
you're amazing i'm so proud of you i
can't wait for tomorrow it's gonna be
big
and uh
yeah
oh you know i love you so much dude
please let's hang out again soon okay
one day i'll go visit you i don't have a
lot of fun i'm i'm preparing my house
for you you're not gonna sleep on the
floor you're gonna sleep on my big couch
okay
i like i like floors but that's good
[Laughter]
all right
thank you
bye-bye
bye
see ya
speaking of friends i can talk forever
with
you i mean i could talk forever with her
now who's next
who could it be
hello
whoa
i'm sorry i'm sorry i keep going on with
them
there's a new meme queen in town baby
it's me
my fellow kids
see i know that i mean that's a meme too
actually some meme within a meme
that is a meme [\h__\h] kill me girl
hey every how how do you kill a reaper
uh kill me like you killed that npc in
elden ring
[Music]
ouch
no it was
listen listen in fairness it was super
funny and made me laugh really hard so
i didn't know
i didn't know that nbc's came after you
it's okay girl it's your first souls
game so it's like everybody does that
their first time i did that my first
time with a souls game i was like oh can
i just beat the [\h__\h] out of this guy and
then they never forgive you
yeah apparently it's like carried on
throughout the throughout the game like
it like it messes with you forever yeah
forever within the game like after i did
it people are like oh hey yo guru just
start the save over it like start over
it's not worth it
side over guru oh no
i saw there was
there is one npc further in the game
that if you hit them a bunch of times
and then you and then you kneel to them
they'll forgive you apparently it undoes
it
i don't know who it is but i think i saw
it sometimes freaking hilarious oh my
gosh yes i hope that i hope you get to
play some other uh from soft games like
off stream that you like because they're
super fun games i think like once you
get the hang of them but they're not for
everyone so don't force yourself either
you know no hell yeah i've been having
fun with uh
you know interestingly enough that's the
only one that i actually have like a
hard hard time with to the point of
where like i can't really play it
because i suck really bad at it so
nice kudos to you dude i get it
everybody's got their soft game they
[\h__\h] suck at and then ones they're
super good at so i'm glad to hear that
you're having fun with seguro hell yeah
dude
yeah i mean or you could just play kirby
kirby yeah there's is it they'll make
you swear just as much it'll make you
curse just as much as a from games
that sounds like a freaking nightmare to
be honest well it's a pink nightmare but
you can do mouthful mode you can't do
that and from something no mouthful mode
what does
have you ever wanted a traffic cone to
hit the back of your throat well you can
do that in kirby
wow wow
did i say happy birthday by the way
that's something i've never thought of
before nah i'm sorry i completely
launched into a conversation with you
now that's kind of just it happens this
is kind of what happens
what happens when we hop into a call
it's okay dude
yeah yeah i'm so excited for your yours
your concert i'm so excited i'm watching
you in 3d you're so bouncy and 3d it
looks like it's having a hard time
keeping up with you sometimes yeah i
know right they could they could never
put the camera like super close on my
face because i was moving around too
much let's make this like can you move
last so i'm like no i want to jump
you're like
wild free
that's how i get for whatever reason
when i'm like in the studio like for
whatever reason when i see myself like
on on the tv it's like i become like a
different being or something and i start
doing all these like weird like
weird dances that like i wouldn't do if
i was like actually looking at myself in
the mirror it's like [\h__\h] bizarre
adrenaline yeah stage mode activate
stage mode speed mode pretty wild but
yeah yeah either that or in vr when i
can't like actually like again not see
myself but like see
you know me in small form or something
like that you know it's weird you seem
to have two modes in in vr from what
i've seen it's either
a non-stop movement or dead on the floor
there's no in-between and they come and
go in spurts of energy i feel like
does that make sense yeah yeah
it happens it happens anyway um
i hope i hope now that i have two
million subscribers i can get an android
so i can put mine next to yours so
i keep thinking about it let's
isn't that second overall uh second over
all in a whole alive i think and maybe
again two million yeah
third third overall possibly maybe maybe
fourth um yeah something like that yeah
thanks for freaking insane making
history thank you man
i appreciate you
i wanna hold on let me get my let me get
my my mushy gushy in here before i have
to boogie woogie okay i just want to do
bed
honestly seriously you are one of the
most hardworking people i've ever met in
my entire life and your
absolute
go-go power is
i wish i had some of that i you are such
a go-getter and you are going and you
are getting and i think that's
absolutely remarkable and i am so
thankful that you are a part of a myth
because
you just you're just the best you're
such an inspiration for so many people
not only me but the deadbeats
and the rest of halloween
i'm serious it's really remarkable you
are incredible politely
don't stop
sleep but don't slap don't stop sleep
sleep but don't stop i need to sleep but
uh
dude i wanna meet you man i want like
hanging with you
what have we got to do we gotta go to
disney we're gonna go to work
we met some roller coasters or something
please are you a roller coaster person
girl
you have to force me but once i'm on
there
let's do it
please just make sure i breathe
otherwise i'm going to pass out and
you'll have to carry me off the ride but
anyway leave it to me
i got your bag i love you dude
i love you too dude go get him thank you
i'll do my best knowing that you're
watching i'm gonna give it my all okay
just watch me
watch me i'm a boy give it a hundred
percent boy
i mean happy birthday
happy birthday my favorite is the happy
birthday oh you too
oh thanks oh youtube
thanks man i appreciate it take
care hey by the way guess what what
that [\h__\h]
why did she do this to me
why does she do this
[Music]
i love gura
i love girl
i love her why did you just
god damn it
oh man
[Music]
what a legend what a freaking legend
only reason i wanted nendoroid is so i
can put myself next to her
well also for you guys as well of course
all right i'm gonna call my
semi last guess we have a surprise guest
that was able to make it so let me go
ahead and call my
my little surprise
guest no one's going to be able to
predict
none of you will predict it
i guarantee
here we go
i call her now
i call i do it i'm doing i'm doing it
hello
let's turn your volume up
hello hello
am i quiet hello hello oh no you should
be okay oh my god your voice just like
hit the back of my head and like tingles
went up my spine dude
well happy birthday thank you for having
me
thank you so much
i'm sorry monarch whoa i don't know what
came over me that was really weird i
literally almost said happy birthday
mama reaper mama
i think the dead beats would correct you
and say father
close enough hey dude thank you so much
for calling in today i'm glad we get to
talk again
yeah i know it's been a minute yeah i
feel like the last the last time that i
called you it was 5 a.m i couldn't sleep
and i think that i had like maybe like
drank a little too much jack daniels so
i was like
i can't i can't sleep let's call a
friend i wasn't exactly drunk but i just
i do remember that like i was kind of
like feeling friendly and i was like
what's great
yeah i'm off with the weirdest hours so
feel free to always call me it was it
was really fun yes
yes of course that was a fun chat give
me a heads up so i can drink oh yeah you
better be on the same level absolutely
oh my gosh no dude i feel like i've been
waiting so long for us to be like able
to collab but like still with your album
you know you can't rush perfection and
like
it's it's gonna it's gonna be out guys
don't worry about it um it's just taking
they're like like things going on that
just don't worry about it it's coming
out and when it does you guys minds are
gonna be blown and then we're gonna do
like a collaboration stream to celebrate
it but to be honest i feel like since
you can't rush perfection we ought to
just do like a collab anyway
you know yeah let's do it just like
before the album drops
no can't rush perfection it's true it'll
be worth the wait for sure
exactly me too you guys you guys aren't
even ready it's a banger track
oh man and the video looks sweet like i
can't wait to see it video two was like
some like a shot of the video in
progress i was like ah this editing is
so dope who edits your videos this is so
sick
i have a small army yeah yeah i guess i
guess you do you've got a lot of a lot
of awesome folks like helping you out to
make your incredible like covers and
also your original works as well are
just so
freaking great and um i'm really honored
that like we get a chance to like
like get to hang and like
become friends and stuff like that
because i've said this before but like
i've been a fan of your work for like
really long
so
i'm always so happy when you say that
because you are one of the huge
inspirations for me making a youtuber so
whenever that collided i was like but no
you i love you
[Laughter]
that's so crazy because i remember like
back in uh back in like reaper high
school days i had a friend who messaged
me and was like have you heard of amelie
check out all of her english covers she
writes like non-cringe lyrics and
they're so fitting for like all the
songs and she's literally incredible and
she's like on spotify and then i became
a big fan and like now
now we're like we're like friends it's
just nutty i don't know no i know
man crazy timeline is wild i'm here for
it yeah
you know original album your original
album is amazing like the new one that
wasn't dropped it's crazy thank you like
number four like of all
right that was pretty crazy especially
being my favorite number four is the
best number so so shiny got me a number
but thank you so much
lucky lucky shinigami number but it is
an honor to hear you say that
um
if you ever get a chance to come to
japan um i would love to hang out
because i know we like talked a little
bit about like about like girl fangs and
like going out to tea and stuff like
that so um
yeah let's do it i love all the best tea
places in tokyo so
oh okay i gotta go back there is this
amazing onsen that i want to go back to
it was like there was this onsen that we
just stumbled upon and it was like
it was like stepping into final fantasy
yeah
world sounds so freaking magical
love onsen big onsen fan here so
i'll make same yeah give me some hot
water
i found found my pupil heck yeah we got
to go to the onsen then for sure
wine and onsen i'm here for it
oh yeah dude you're a wine fan too as
well huh i see you holding the wine
glass oh yeah i do oh yeah
that's the one you chose yes yes
fresh red a fresh red of course my
brother
my brother who love red wine you gotta
represent you know
gotta represent incredible
wow thank you so much for dropping by to
come talk with me some dead by daylight
someday soon
let's do it i am i
i am so obsessed with my daylight i will
play any hour four am double daylight
drunk
we uh take a shot every time we die
[Laughter]
either on stream but then but then like
we get to a point where we go off stream
yeah
we reach a certain way we're like all
right guys leaving you and then we
then we stop and just continue until
someone's only
oh man you're reminding me of when when
i watched scarface with my deadbeats and
i said let's take a shot every time a
crime is committed and that was maybe
the drunkest i ever got on stream
oh no it was bad i still have memories
of that
it was wild
anyway
yeah heck yeah yeah hit me up please i
would love to absolutely
thank you for calling in today dude
we will definitely let's hang out soon
okay
let's do it yeah hit me up all right
bye-bye
bye
[Music]
she's so cool
ah
drinking bodies well like i said a lot
of a lot of folks in myth um
aren't like super into drinking which is
like fine all good
um but like it is nice to have a friend
that does enjoy a sip
every once in a while
[Applause]
i don't have a do you have a png
any chance we have an unexpected
uh guest as the last guest
on
you guys gonna guess
while i'm waiting for this png or i can
just search myself oh no she's got one
always
heck yeah always prepared
there we go
well we do not have amelie here but you
know who we do have
[Music]
you know who we do have
a special hard-working bird
was able to make it no cubase don't open
please no no okay no license or thank
god holy [\h__\h] that was gonna destroy my
computer anyway
hello
oh no boss i'm so sorry
i kind of impersonated him as if
japanese wasn't even his first language
oh i mean
i mean i figured that you talked like
that because you've actually like spoken
to him before for hollow talk so i was
like is this an actual live impression
i've ever spoken to him before i have
yeah
yeah i feel super awkward even more than
even more more often than me at this we
have had a few meetings actually yeah
oh how fitting the picture in the
background it's you and me my mommy mama
you're louise shred it's too perfect oh
my god when are we watching remember
yeah was it was it september when we
watched shrek i don't think so
oh um
you know i have no freaking clue
everything feels so long ago it's been
over a year since i left japan and left
the land of being close to
hawaii
well actually i i wanted to wait to tell
you this news but um
actually i'm coming to visit you
huh austria
because i'm in europe so i'm like why
not just go say hi to kiara when
june
in june
yeah
in europe in june yeah so i'm just what
what you doing what you up to uh you're
not gonna be able to stay i can't say it
on stream but i'll i'll text you i'll
i'll send you a message later on
june that's interesting timing i think
there is um
there might be someone else here in june
as well yeah that'll be so depending on
the timing
yeah well we'll talk about it later but
yeah definitely all right definitely i i
want to come see you because i'm like if
i'm in europe no no shot i'm gonna miss
going to see kiara so
yes oh that's nice yes i've been i've
been kind of lonely here in uh europe so
it's nice to hear that you planning that
of course i've been kind of lonely too i
mean i i have i have iris and j chad but
it's just not the same you know
it's not oh when you're having for
example you you work with soy say
sandbox
milky queen and you have lots of people
around you yeah well i hope you're not
being loved by everybody too too lonely
or anything you still get a chance to go
hang out with friends and stuff like
that right
i hope
well non-b tube of friendship yeah yeah
yeah i get you i'll catch you on that
one yeah for sure yeah no um
kelly just just the the other date
yesterday the day before yesterday i i
was wearing your clothes
um
[Music]
wait no you mean just kidding
not you need in vr
yeah yet
close but i gotta say
yeah buddy you look you look best in
them i don't know i feel i feel like it
worked really well on you though
it did it looked like it really
edgy yeah i just feel like the only
issue is like orange and black are like
halloween colors so like if one of those
colors was changed then it would be like
really like
super fitting like if you have your same
hairstyle but you decided to dye your
hair pink then i think that like it
would be perfect for perfect match for
you hair yeah
pink hair is quite
is something i always aspired to have
yes yes yeah but i think orange is
perfect for you to be honest oh thank
you oh thank you thank you you rock it
sorry if if i left you the
your outfit kind of uh i don't know
dirty or sweaty yeah i tried to keep it
as clean as possible no it smells
perfect i had no issue i would i would
be growing at you if there was a gravy
smell maybe a little bit but i like
gravy though so you know
you're all good
oh and uh
congratulations on not only your
birthday but the 2 million thank you
thank you chiara i appreciate it i
worked i worked hard
4 million 2 [\h__\h] millions a lot of
people right
i like don't believe it sometimes i'm
like really there's two million of you
[\h__\h] here damn all right yeah
wow wow wow
it was uh it was deserved though you've
been like on a [\h__\h] ride this whole
time
we've been working so hard so the two
million they come
as a given as a gift thank you
it's very sweet of you kiara we both
have been grinding super hard you've
been doing some great stuff as well too
i'm excited for for you to
show off your your room and stuff like
that and some of your like 3d stuff you
can do when you get a chance when you're
ready to do it in about a million years
whenever you're ready to do it i think
everyone's going to be really excited
because i feel like um
if i if i may say so your 3d model is
maybe my favorite because it's just so
freaking good it's so crisp oh thank you
it's so perfect
yeah thank you thank you thank you i
love your snow thank god it's so elegant
and it's just perfect to me i really
love the the contrast but i mean it's
basically like people i heard that a lot
of people said that about me but i also
think that yours is just like
exactly like the life to do just in 3d
like for me it looks perfect yeah the
flowy veil works even better now right
we just gotta you know they're just i
just gotta get a little plastic surgery
here and there but you know what that's
fine that's fine
those are just little things to be
honest i mean overall
everybody has bad angles right i mean
also i was looking at suicide senpai's
model the other day and i was like
wow her model is
perfect and then i realized oh suicide
senpai has been at this for four years
so it just comes with time and she also
had a bunch of makeovers so yeah that's
that yeah exactly exactly so you know it
comes with time but to be honest i think
this is a great start for all of us i
think we all look freaking banging to be
honest yeah at least it's finally out
there finally finally and we get to do
like more stuff and it's it's exciting
you know it maybe it wasn't the big like
bang three 3d
debut for myth all at the same time
everyone meets in japan thing that we
had envisioned but we're still to get to
do that you know full holo myth concert
meeting for the first time and whatnot
it's not going to be any less special
and we're still going to get to debut so
that's good
if you say so kawaii be more identi
let's be true
i know about that try to stay positive
also
also congrats
on the secret thing that you're
announcing tomorrow yeah yeah yeah kiara
knows kiara knows guys i i told kiara no
no no no no no i know nothing no no no
no
yeah she won't say though because she's
a great secret keeper but thank you i'm
glad yes i know i know when to keep my
secrets when it's necessary
yeah i'll try to make i'll try to make
everyone proud and i'll try to make you
proud too
but it's great that there are so many
great things happening to you like i'm
so happy
when i look at you when i look at you it
feels like
um that that when you work hard it
actually pays off like you seem to be
the proof of that oh man
yeah like if there's anyone who ever
doubts that i could be like look at
caliber murray that be tuber from whole
life
look at her you can't tell me that
youtube dad working hard is not worth it
look at her and you see it you just
really really really really really gotta
hustle
thank you that's a really positive way
of thinking about it i appreciate that
thank you chiari you've always been so
so damn supportive of me i appreciate
that
at this point i worry that you may have
no more dreams uh left over
i mean now i'm trying to think of
impossible ones so that i'll always have
a dream forever until until i cease to
exist anymore
and possible ones maybe instead of a
whole live expo how about a miracle ip
expo oh yeah yeah yeah that's definitely
never gonna happen
so we can we can have so i can have a
dream forever to strive toward
i mean i mean it is some form it might
be it might be possible
i'm telling you you're making impossible
things possible
so
you can do it i'm sure that you've done
things so far that you have until that
point thought they wouldn't it would
have been impossible oh look
yourself wrong
a lot of them that's for sure well
that's a good way of putting it you
always know what you always know what to
say tencho
thank you do i do i usually
i struggle with that sometimes 90 of the
time well at least to me i think when i
mean when we talk
i don't know i feel like you always got
something like positive and helpful to
say so
what was it helpful the the the the
i see i see you figured out your problem
was that helpful what i wrote yesterday
oh yeah
yes it was finally i can help with
technical issues i'm usually never the
one i'm never the one usually always
i was struggling for sure so thank you
for that
i did something
dude thank you so much
appreciate it if there's anything i can
do to help ever um i i don't have so
many um
unique
skills but if there's anything i can do
then please go ahead ask me whenever you
need some
an extra hand because you seem to always
be needing extra hands you try to juggle
everything alone but
but juggling 10 balls at the same time
maybe you should just throw some balls
to the other people around you yeah yeah
show them something in the head yeah hit
them in the head with the balls that's a
good idea
don't juggle them all on your own okay
right because i'm gonna drop one at some
point
exactly yeah and then it's like dropping
spaghetti we don't want that no no drop
spaghetti
not the spaghetti waste of the spaghetti
no my mom's spaghetti
your italian accent is pretty good i
gotta say
oh oh thank you i studied
dang those were some bars
i'm joking that was great italian nice
oh i mean i wouldn't i wouldn't know
i wouldn't know because i didn't
actually speak italian but it sounded
good sounded like you knew what you were
saying
or maybe when you come to europe we can
go to italiano oh man yeah let's see
italia i've been to rome
oh i've been there also like many times
not rome but like a lot of other cities
this is a neighboring country so we can
go there like yeah immediately
immediately let's go just one step away
vacation i'm down yes
okay then i'll see you in italy okay
i'll see you in italy kiara oh and i'll
see you tomorrow as well
uh yes i'll see you tomorrow for the
thing
yeah good luck
thanks so much
bye-bye thanks for dropping bye
peace
yay yeah kiara wasn't sure if she could
come but i'm glad that she was able to
come in the end
because you know time zones oh and
another friend
[Music]
thank you so much you're so cute
yeah i'm very happy
happy birthday hello
thank you number one samurai samurai yes
yes i'm samurai not ninja
okay deadbeats deadbeats do you
understand
a ninja okay ban ban everyone j chad
okay
okay no problem no problem
so cute wink
[Music]
my
[Laughter]
yes only samurai okay
okay
record goal
thank you you are jumping
yes i'm jumping you too you're a jump
king oh thank you but uh but no
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
yes yes come come to fight me come beat
my
my record okay
uh my record is seven minutes
56 seconds
wow yeah 7 56
um
oh
[Music]
yeah my schedule is so crazy
thank you
[Music]
thank you for happy birthday goodbye
everyone i know
is just cute
[Music]
why
see that was my mouth moving and nobody
else was talking but it just felt like
moving i don't really get it but okay
whatever anyway that's all for
totsumachi
we did it
lots of talking with friends almost
three hours worth that is pretty crazy
because you're cute too
you're just saying that i'm not fishing
for compliments though i think my hair
has a nice sheen to it and i think
the the picture of the void in my eyes
is kind of nice i have good scents and
jewelry
um
and i can paint my nails well
learning to compliment myself day by day
day by day day by day day by day
anyway
that's what's up
i'm overslept no amelia told me that she
wouldn't be able to make it um
to to this one but she will be a part of
something happening tomorrow
if you guys noticed i mentioned that um
some of the uh some of the others would
be
um
coming to join me
right
tomorrow for some shenanigans before the
little concert we're gonna do because it
wouldn't be
it wouldn't be a fun 3d stream without
some some dumb shenanigans with me and
my friends
so we're going gonna do some silly stuff
hope you guys look forward to it
it's very silly stuff
like ridiculously silly stuff
but i hope you laugh
so tomorrow four four
and please use the hashtag cali3dbd
i would love for it to for it to trend
somewhere that would make me very happy
but if it doesn't that's cool too i'll
keep singing my heart out anyway and we
have huge news if you didn't see it says
huge news that i've been hyping over and
over and over again not literally not
shutting the [\h__\h] up about it um but
it's because i'm really excited about it
so i hope you guys will be excited too
um
yeah
[Music]
it already trending
no
i don't think so
you're trending in the usa why
why
i'm not even performing
i'm not performing yet
come on you guys
thank you though
i really do appreciate it
since the totsumachi is done we can go
to my other room that i wanted to go to
i'm not really planning on singing
anything but this is where i wanted to
read super chats just a little forest
forest i made up for myself tomorrow at
20 jst
uh we've got the birthday concert it
should be scheduled pretty soon
i don't know there's a weird line over
that's kind of that's kind of suspect
that makes me feel strange
i don't really get it but okay here let
me see if i can pull it
pull it up
um
yay happy birthday thank you very much
thank you
you guys are sweethearts
thank you for always cheering for me
you guys think you want to do this [\h__\h]
you know oh wow i feel like i can do
whatever as long as you guys are
supporting me
i can try to be um
[Music]
i don't know my best my best me
i'll pull out
my best moves for tomorrow
i'll i'll try my best to impress and i'm
i'm not gonna dance too much
just a lit just a little bit just enough
to to be for you guys to be like wow
callie sure isn't she can dance all
right um but not enough to affect my
singing because there is a fine balance
[Music]
damn it i really am going to have to
wake up bright and early tomorrow i was
thinking to myself how about i read the
super chats from this stream right i
thought that um at first
but then i was like ah hold on a minute
i have to wake up kind of early tomorrow
um so
let's read supers from other streams
so that's what we're gonna do well i'm
scrolling scroll and scroll and scroll
and what we can just chat
um but yeah there are actually a lot of
announcements tomorrow like like a lot
like
a lot of
[Music]
there's more than one there's even more
than two
i think you guys will be happy though
um
yeah
and collabs
singing collabs
yup but i think that was kind of a given
you know now that i'm here
in japan i think you guys kind of
figured out that that was gonna happen
yeah
like just kind of obvious
but let me switch the internet down to
here
but um
there'll be some fun stuff
and an interesting little event in the
beginning that some of my friends get to
join in i wanted to have something extra
in case people couldn't make it to the
toad sumachi but almost everyone made it
so that was cool
[Music]
is it four
i don't know is it four it depends on
what you count as as announcements
yeah and in that case i don't know maybe
maybe it's four
i don't know does goods count
uh
if goods count then yeah maybe four not
that i'm releasing birthday merch or
anything but you know it's possibility
you know anything's possible in this
wacky world we live in right
in this wacky
[Music]
yes wacky crazy
insane oh world
i'm surprised no crohn's it's okay don't
don't get
don't get upset at her she
i have bad sleeping issues too i've i've
slept
i've slept in as well
despite the fact that you know i said so
confidently to kiara i was like i will
never sleep in i've done it before so
it happens it happens i'm sure that
cronie and i will get a chance to talk
again when we play more of that orcs
game so time zones do be like that right
i mean a second ago amelie was like did
i get the time wrong and i was like
maybe i got it wrong and
it was just it was kind of crazy but
it's nobody's fault it happened so
please you know don't don't go give
crony [\h__\h] because it's happened to all
of us like at least most of us at least
once so
we'll have a chat some other time
[Music]
we will have a little talk and i'm sure
that she'll you know if if she would
like to
wish me a happy b day on her on her own
terms because that is something that
happens believe it or not friends
believe it or not
something that actually [\h__\h] happens
is that some of us choose to wish each
other a happy birthday um
not on twitter not before the public eye
it's more common than you'd think
so
she'll hit me up if she wants to
people make mistakes yeah and alarm
clocks make mistakes too and phones also
choose to run out of power
yeah
you talk offstream yeah why not
oh i think you said that sarcastically
i'm pretty sure you said that with an
air of sarcasm
no way
of course not everyone though as i've
mentioned before i've also made the
point that i'm not bffs with every
single person in holo which is also
completely normal and healthy
got you need to remember that
i i see too many friends getting [\h__\h]
about why don't you talk to this person
who's my second favorite
doesn't work like friendship doesn't
work like that man
you want to see a fun fake friendship on
stream no
everybody i invited today or folks that
like
i legitimately chat with off stream or
have chatted with on stream
have had some interactions with and
stuff like that mal was really cool we
actually got to meet at like an event
thing we went to the same event and it
just turned out that we like happened to
cross paths
and we were like what
it's you
we didn't get to like chit chat too much
but we did get to hang out um and get to
see like the
the show together and stuff like that
and it was fun
she is way cute
she is just as cute as i knew
she would be
like even even more cute
than i could have imagined
i was like wow
chef's kiss
[Music]
you know
anyway now mel is a sweetheart honestly
she's very adorable
and i'm looking forward to potentially
seeing her again sometime soon
i hope
because she's she's a cutie i think
everyone's a cutie that i've met in
hollow irl
so you say is a cutie too
when we were rehearsing for her um
for her show
every time i would do something like
stupid and ridiculous like do like a
weird dance move or like
something idiotic like an idiotic dance
or like a weird movement
she would like start doing the exact
same thing
which is how i knew that we could be
good friends
we'd be like looking at ourselves on
this on the tv and like sitting in like
chairs and like i'd start spinning
around and then she would start spinning
around
and we just start cracking up
and then i'd start like doing like a
weird dance or like weird kicks or like
gangster poses and then she would
she would join in too and we just die
laughing
she's very norinori
she goes with the flow it's like your
sisters or something
it seems that way doesn't it
nah she's so much fun
she is so much fun
i did get to see
a bit of uh
a bit of a psychopathic
which was funny to witness
because like she's still cute like she
is
she is exactly the amount of cute that i
thought she would be
cute and talented
and like
it was it was funny because like
watching her perform
um
like i i was watching the stream but
like because i had to stay in the same
area the whole time i couldn't take my
eyes off of like
her
you know
instead of watching the the stream on
the screen i like couldn't stop looking
at her the whole time
because
god she was just
she has like so much incredible dancing
ability and you know she dances and
sings at the same time and i'm like how
do you do it
and she just looks so
so beautiful damn she is a beauty god
damn i was like stunned like she is she
was born for this damn
um
but
yeah
there were some
there were some moments where like i
could envision her holding an axe in her
head
that's love my dog
true idol
yup and she puts like everything into
what she does so
very excited to see that her her song
reached number one on the charts
[Music]
it's super good if you guys haven't seen
it there's like an animation music video
for it so go check it out on her on her
channel
yeah
yeah but she did put a lot of work into
into what she does and that's why in our
song wicked i wrote the lyrics thinking
about things that connect like the both
of us
and the fact that we worked really hard
you know
burns to be wicked and we aim to
and we aim to fly whether anderson
devils it is do or die
no cap kick it while the sound is hot
broke backs getting what we got
because like getting to talk with susie
i heard all about her past with like
jobs and stuff like that that she had to
do and i was like wow
me too
i've had to do things like that as well
while trying to do music stuff
and so i wanted to write lyrics that
kind of like
both of us connected through
you know
wish you could understand
his part uh speak japanese well i'm
crossing my fingers for some kind of
translation to come out somewhere i
think it might happen
lots of fans are like um into
translating songs here and there so
i think that would be cool
yeah it's a it's a really great song so
please enjoy wicked as well
yep
anyway i'm gonna read these big
announcement super chats and then i'm
gonna turn in because i got a show to
put on tomorrow
i'm sorry hold on a second i got a show
to put on tomorrow
[Music]
hold on
oh you're approaching me
right
[Music]
i'm not saying anything
so yeah anyway that's what's up
and i don't wanna
don't wanna [\h__\h] die because i'm
gonna be
busy all day morning tonight practicing
to make sure that everything is perfect
for you guys
okay so
i love that i can but i can do this with
with this application get real close to
you right
you guys want to see something fun
let me get this get this [\h__\h] dumbass
mic out of here hold on
sorry mike i didn't mean to call you
that
and if your name is mike i apologize you
guys want to see something fun
[Music]
oh wow that was not what i wanted to say
what the [\h__\h] was
no
no wait a minute
[Music]
stop
that was not what i wanted to do i
promised that was not what we were
it says kabedan pose
mail
now
you guys know that that's not going to
stop me from doing a kabe dawn all right
it's not going to stop me
but
i guess you're going to see me with no
what on
earth rawr
and tipos
let me just try it one more time
just one more i want to believe
[Music]
oh okay no we're fine we're fine i'm not
bald it's just that my arm
makes me look like i am so like if i do
it
the sh the shade right here it oh nope
i'm bald i'm bald yep i'm bald
nope i'm five million percent bald
like not even a joke like that is that
is me without hair like that is five
million percent
me with not a shred of hair on my head
check it out
you guys want to peek behind the curtain
there you go
special sneak peek for all of you who
stayed here
my eyes
it's not cute
it's very kind of you
let's see sit with crying
oh
sit with cry can i
i'm sitting and i'm crying
[Music]
wow that's my body
this is fun
i'm a fan of this
[Music]
i do need to turn a little bit if you
don't mind i'm gonna
if i could just turn
where's the where's the turn my body
button
throw a kiss
wow i think i [\h__\h] the whole thing up
but you notice what it is stand
stand proud
[Music]
work in the hips that's so raven pose
yeah
yep that's me that was my favorite show
to watch back in the day at sir raven
i watched it with my babysitter my
babysitter loved that so raven she was a
big fan
my babysitter and her and her daughter
were big that's so raven fans
anyway shall we read some of these super
chats from the big announcement oh this
is so exciting because i can post for
you guys too per super chat that'd be
great
we've got a big ups too
z conator thank you so much z canadore
for the red super chat what is this yeah
no message
what a chad
absolute freaking legendary chad thank
you so much zeke nader you're always so
damn sweet to me i appreciate it thank
you thank you thank you thank you
oh man this is going to be fun
i feel like it's not the same without
your twitching eyes well let me see hold
on i wonder if i could ask them to do
that to purposefully make them super
glitchy glitchy and twitchy hold on
i did set eye tracking sensitivity to
like 100 but there's only so much i can
do
it's just not the same
i feel like i have to put in more effort
yeah
what can you do
18th of march that was a minute ago
miss those glitchy eyes
i'll ask them to purposefully
purposefully make them like that for you
guys
and we've got a big ups too shadow
pencil thank you and tbc studios big ups
to you and a big upstand sufficiently
anonymous heck yeah
wow that's a long time
[Music]
wear it proudly and know that you two
could now gently d and gently bully dave
humor
yeah a gentle bully i was a little harsh
last time though
but it's funny that you you mentioned um
kaisho actually insufficiently anonymous
because i find recently i've been
sleeping with her tail
like hardcore you know the stuffed tail
that you could buy with the cocoa goods
right
um
usually i need something to hold on to
when i go to sleep
uh so i've been cradling it in my arms
especially during those like kind of
saturn nights that i've had recently um
when i'm feeling like not confident
about myself or like things are
happening with work that like are really
kind of hurting my mental
um i get my my cocoa tail and i like
i hold it in my arms um
and that's that's how i fall asleep
it's very comfy
and it's it's fun to like wrap your legs
and like arms around
um
yeah so so in a sense um
she's still she's still here with me
you know
and whenever i'm i'm feeling iffy about
things that are going on in my job i hug
that gosh darn tail and i feel good
so um yeah
cutest asakoko story
so much love stove kaijo always always
and forever
we got a big ups to labit thank you very
much and thank you to cali fans for the
very sweet message hope you enjoyed the
vod we've got a big ups to scrub lord of
cinder glad to see you're just as
addicted to elden ring as me callie
thanks grand lord of cinder i feel like
a lot of folks are though my only comp
complaint is that the true maiden of my
heart kawaii mori
isn't featured in the game zone then
what a shame
a shame indeed
but what can we do we got some other
fine maidens in there you know
good luck with the 3d performance you'll
be awesome thank you we'll do my best
big ups to rokenji thank you and a big
ups to
l5
guardian
[Applause]
[Music]
come here alpha guardian
you can't resist my caveadon of baldness
i know this is what you want
[Music]
laga bloodystone
thank you so much
l5 guardian you've always been
incredibly supportive and kind thank you
thank you
i wish i could hear the announcement
live oh well some time has passed
considering this was march so surely you
know what's up i believe i saw you super
chat earlier today as well and i was
like damn what a chad so maybe you're
still here alpha have a guardian thank
you so much the incredible generosity
that is a fat super chat like like a big
a big old
a big fat brick a big stack of bricks
from l5 guardian thank you thank you so
much
l5 guardian says um continuing onward
uh when i do get to hear what it is i'm
going to be beyond happy you work
incredibly hard callie and i cannot wait
to see what you've been working on much
love as always and i'm proud of you
callie thank you so much l5 guardian
very sweet of you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you i hope
you're doing well i know that this was a
while ago but
dang like a whole month like this was
before the this is before the fest
so it's been a minute but i hope
regardless that you're doing well now so
and hope you catch the vod to see this
message as well we finally are getting
to these super chats finally finally
finally finally finally finally finally
filing
[Music]
anyway
have a good one toby thank you better
late than never oh there you are
i figured you were still here
thanks a lot i appreciate that and i'm
excited to read the super chats from
this stream and tomorrow's as well
combined together uh on the fifth cause
we're gonna have a big ol celebration
then so yeah thank you very much for
being very patient with me you guys
spoil me so dang much i'm i'm like
trying to catch up i'm like dang what do
i do
but but don't don't ever feel like it's
not appreciated because you guys it's
because of you guys i get to like do
things that i want to do like it's
because of you guys i get to commission
um like a 3d background for the chad
cast and like
i know you guys saw before right that i
was like in a classroom of sorts right
well that was kind of like a default
thing um i'm eventually going to be able
to get like my own like rooms made in in
3d you know it's it's exciting i think
kiara talked a little bit about that
having like actual 3d rooms and stuff
like that to chill out in that's
something that is is probably going to
be possible someday and um
and you guys make that possible because
i i want to reinvest in you guys so
uh thank you so much i'll do what i can
to keep entertaining y'all we got a big
salary in the hand finally got my
glowing eyes congrats on the membership
membership milestone rather a big ups to
lc le pen thank you for getting me these
from soft games hope you're having a
blast i'll see le pen and we've got a
big ups too sakura
ah
kenny
thank you so much very sweet of you i
appreciate the red super chat
no message
what chad
absolute chad behavior sakura kemi thank
you for cheering for me
we got a big ups to the booty call of
cthulhu with still arguably the best
name out of the device though there are
some high contenders i would say then
we've got a big ups of the legendary
chad
baka
waggy
these poses are so fun
anyway
i know you want this cupboards on
baldness bakawagi are you ready here we
go boom
oh no the truth is revealed oh gosh what
are we going to do
thank you bakawagi for always being so
sweet
bakuwagi says gonna be vod gang today
but send in some love beforehand because
whatever announcement it'll be is
definitely gonna be good
and it ended up being good i'm pretty
sure i i announced uh the 3d
the 3d that's happening tomorrow
during this stream pretty sure that's
what the big announcement was so
exciting stuff it all comes full circle
glad that we're we're catching up to
these before the actual thing happens so
that's good better late than never so
thank you so much buckawagie
for the legendary fat brick run right at
my face i'm an airplane
[Music]
you guys are right about the eyes i need
them flying everywhere
everywhere
[Music]
you guys like i have a little turtle
mouth too
i actually really like it
i'm like a big fan of it
sorry i love the t-pose too much
thank you so much bakawagi very sweet of
you
big ups
now i like turtle nails me too it's
really cute thank you i also like it a
lot but i did ask for my mouth um to be
more expressive
because like
sometimes i feel like it's just like a
weird little like bean
like right now hold on
not that one that one's fine hold on
that
it's like whole bean my mouth is really
expressive usually so i'm getting a
little plastic surgery to make it a bit
more expressive so
that pose did open a wine bottle for you
true facts actually we need to try that
again we need to try it again with
another bottle of wine and i can
literally do it in front of your faces
so look forward to that
asserting your dominance with the t-pose
it's my specialty i don't know if you
guys know that
it's a specialty asserting dominance
with this pause
this one here
i start way back here and then i go real
and come in like an airplane
but hold on the microphone gets in my
way so hold on
[Applause]
no it's just that i'm too fast right
here
that doesn't it just doesn't sense my
head going too real
you guys like it
i'm having a little too much fun right
now hold on
stop stop stop
we got a big ups to doug joseph thank
you and the big ups to it tyson kfp
legal eagle our favorite player eagle we
got a big ups to flora jean times three
who i saw a lot in the chat today thanks
so much floor jean for being supportive
as
usual
like she bounces off the screen like a
fish
yeah i'm constantly
flopping around
damn it i need to get rid of this energy
so i can sleep
it's fine
and jack can help me
we got a big ups to ww and a big ups too
oh sorry i was on reverb
j p r s n s r thank you so much
i appreciate it the red super chat
so much to look forward to we're all
dying to know what you've got planned
for us dying get it cause i am the grim
reaper
and huge howdy from max maxwell we love
you callie thanks a lot max maxwell
and thank you to jprsnsr for delivering
the message
we've got a big ups too
hikito
thank you very much heart is pounding so
damn hard oh man i hope that you don't
die tomorrow
dang
i already feel like i'm gonna pass out
just thinking about it
i wonder if i can even sleep tonight
i'll try my best
i'll try my best i can't i can't let
jack help me too much though because
then i'm not going to wake up like
energized i'll wake up with a headache
as i mentioned today when i was talking
to kuroichan i was like yeah um
the only thing that happens futskayoi
for me futskayoi being like the second
day
hangover
is that i get terrible headaches and
even if you use things like painkillers
to try and help
it's it's still not gonna do the trick
you need to drink lots of water and wait
for it to pass and i need to practice
well so maybe i'll just use up all my
energy talking to you guys and then i'll
sleep like a baby
how does that sound that sound good
does that sound good my deadbeats
if i slither around like a fish now that
i can do such a thing
oh man i wish i could use this all the
time but i just don't want the novelty
of it to wear off you know
so we have to use it for special
occasions only
sounds like a plan
excellent
good stuff
[Music]
califice
i feel so free
i'm so glad that i got 3d
oh man
gosh now i really want those hand
trackers so i can do special crazy stuff
and body tracking so i can do all my
favorite specific poses for you guys
not not anything weird i didn't wink
because i was like making a lead joke or
like being weird i keep digging myself
into like bigger holes always i do this
kind of [\h__\h] to myself so let's continue
onward
we gotta big up to shadow pencil thank
you always and a big ups to vampiric
otaku thank you to markowski and a big
ups to shahel thank you draconic insight
and we've got a big ups too
nelsino
[Music]
i am busy with work every day and i can
hardly participate but i always support
gambatte
please take a vacation
okay
take it easy
[Music]
okay
good
[Music]
i don't know
let me see what it's called
hold on
those teeth on your jacket seems painful
now they're fine
let's see yeah the fifth oh gosh you got
to go
out
[Music]
i thought it was a freaking japanese
holiday on this am i wrong hold up no no
no no
where's my other phone
please okay
29 oh okay 29.
yeah yeah it's the 29
sorry
thanks for reminding me though
hey hey hey big ups always knows you
know
thank you i had reaver bond the whole
[\h__\h] time with echo
god damn it i keep doing this i'm so
freaking forgetful what can you do we've
got a big ups too burkey perky
right back on with the loud
the loud reverb and the echo
thank you very much
i appreciate it
thank you for the red super chat ricky
frookie freaky freaky says and i quote
hey
it's been a while since i caught you
live i'm really enjoying your elden ring
playthrough by the way if you put the
password deadbeat in your multiplayer
tab you'll see more messages and blood
stains from your fans a bunch of us have
been using it and it is fun to see
that's really neat actually thanks a lot
for the tip freaky furky i will try that
heck yeah
wow
very neat
for elden ring very cool
wow
so you guys are going to help me right
you're not going to troll me right
you're actually going to be helpful
right
do we have an understanding
huh
[Music]
well either way i'll do it because it
sounds fun i'm glad that you guys are
able to find some fun in it though try
finger uh try shutting the [\h__\h] up oh
got em t-pose on their asses bam what
can you do
nothing
touch grace
anyway
i don't know what's going on with me
how do i churn myself
stand mail
stand
what do they mean stand mail what do i
have my hands on my hips
oh no it's just i guess like a male look
i don't know
i mean i don't know how i feel about it
no
i'm just kind of slumped this is kind of
how i
look when i'm in the studio
very relaxed and casual
but this is the me that i want to show
you
stand
stand proud
to stand
proud sorry
this is going to be my most abused pose
in this application
by far i think you guys know that though
we've got a big ups 2
rev96 thank you and big ups to mickey
p thank you very much for the red
super chat thank you as always mickey p
for being so damn supportive
we love you dude what is this no message
what a chad
ma'am
can't do that to me mickey p what you do
thanks a lot
thank you for the support always the
incredible generosity
got a big ups to mr v
and a big ups too pixel art student
thank you very much for the red super
chat appreciate the heck out of you as
always how have you been looking forward
to playing grim leaper at some point
soon once things get a little less busy
after the birthday live i should have a
chance to get to it i know that you and
kevin work super hard on it so i don't
want to sleep on it we do have to get
that ghost babe though but i think i
have a plan i think i know how to
practice for it you know without like
dying every day and then we can finally
knock out that damn tower
anyway then we'll get to green leafer
pixel art student says i am excited for
the big announcement it's a busy week so
please don't push yourself hope you are
doing fine and are able to get back your
card from the po-po oh man that's right
i remember when this happened all was
fine though as it turned out that my
card was under my [\h__\h] clothes
but of course
[Music]
of course that would happen well thanks
for the the kind sentiment pixel art
student everything ended up just fine
[Music]
thank you that was a while ago it's
weird because to me it feels like just
yesterday time flies i think it's the
zak tang thank you and a big ups to
zekenator7 you really like the dance
school huh i'm glad that it brightened
your day
what's more to come i want to do a 3d
yoga lesson
but i don't know how that'll go some
like jazzercise or something funny maybe
3d ring fit i saw at the studio they had
ring fit so i was like hmm the gears are
turning in my head
let's see next up we've got mozilla
fennekin thank you very much is it big
news or is it huge news what's the
difference i need help well that time it
was big news uh tomorrow's news is huge
um
tomorrow's news is real
real ridiculous levels of huge um so
please look forward to that
we got a big ups too
squidward mr squidward
squibber squid
thank you very much
mr squidward kabadon i'm mr krabs coming
at you squidward ay what's up oh no you
you found out i'm bald
don't tell anyone me boy
or else i'll cut your salary in half
you understand mr squidward
i can't do a good mr krabs impression
but i am familiar with the show so like
i get
i get the sentiment behind it you know
thanks squidward squid
for the red super chat i always
appreciate you it's very sweet
thank you always
squidward confirmed
yari our money money money that's all
you need to know about mr krabs
we got a big ups to stratify thank you
tentacult thanks donga bread and saku as
well as tony bones then we got glad soda
a big ups to allen and thank you to nine
cats heck yeah last super since i love
my job looking forward to watching your
whole fast 3d live stream thanks a lot
nine cats i appreciate it you take care
of yourself
okay
look out for number one promise me
we got a big upcis sky shield thank you
uh we got a big ups to michael
corden koronek and a big ups to maxwell
the first thank you to tl warrior thomas
thank you very much to princess
niche and a big ups 210 cult 7336 3d
cali debuting indeed well not really
debuting we're not really calling it a
debut because debut is a little more
special i'm trying to look up for uh
look for ways to spice up the actual
debut when it comes around with all the
other girls in japan so i'm trying to
get like crazy 3d rooms figured out and
like some crazy
ridiculous idea for like something to do
so that it's not just like collins show
off my poses do a concert you know so
now i've got more brainstorming time to
make it extra special but
anyway um you could say it's similar to
a 3d debut but it's not the same not the
same
it's a it's a teaser trailer marcel but
i also can't just not do 3d concerts
when you know big stuff is coming up in
my future so a torture room ooh that's
kind of fun
actually that's a really good idea let
me present that to the management
real 3d twister it was really hard for
me to do it because it wasn't just that
i was tired but it was that my
uh vr was not synced properly i don't
know what i did wrong i like set it up
the wrong way or something it was just
it was all kinds of [\h__\h] and i was
like too exhausted to figure it out
i mean i had rehearsed for 10 hours the
previous day then come home to calvin
tying me up
trying to ruin my freaking career um
taking over my channel being a general
[\h__\h] seeming to learn a life lesson
then completely turning his back on it
continuing to be an [\h__\h] out the door
um
and then i slept for
three hours woke up did a vr collab so
yeah rightfully i was a bit exhausted i
actually slept that entire day
to be truthful with you guys i slept the
whole day
the entire day
yeah
that was wild anyway
a big ups to lupus thank you to brendan
and a big ups to tl warrior thomas thank
you to kyodai a big us to tentacult and
thank you to gazem a big ups to tl
warrior thomas and ferdo thanks a lot a
big ups to doug joseph tl warrior thomas
again where's the 40 concert
a big ups to scp rx 420 ooh that's that
sounds like an interesting one a big ups
do bunny hair rabbit thank you to sent
to amorous a big ups to chris kfp
feather comber a big ups to brian green
and a big ups to oh let's see hold on a
minute
this is crazy
econ
brett
andrews
for the red
super chat thank you very much
this message you've sent me has multiple
levels of given me a chuckle so let me
read this in this pose
econ says two things first someone was
driving through my hood blasting your
music the other day
what a chad can we can we give it up for
that chad driving through econ's
neighborhood blasting the music that
takes some freaking bravery my dude nice
second been seeing a lot of
shirako talk in hollow and holy lately
but you spent some time down south did
you ever
encounter rocky mountain oysters i like
mine with chili sauce you know i
actually have um i don't really i'm not
a big fan of oysters i'm a bigger fan of
um
what is it
abalone and scallops i really like
oysters oysters kind of have like if you
really just don't slurp like all of it
including the meat
and the organs like all at the same time
like
what's the [\h__\h] point but if you eat
scallops and abalone you can kind of
take the meat out individually and just
eat that
so
they're not oysters they're not actually
oysters
oh
[Music]
ah
um
[Music]
can't say i have my man can't say i have
i'm glad you like now you know
damn
now i know
thanks for the factoid my man
and for the support
big ups
i'm glad you have a food you enjoy but i
can't say i've ever tasted that nor do i
have
any interest
a big ups to lenny thank you to doppler
and a big ups to donger bread let's go
thank you salary man
a full album and 3db day concert with
more big announcements oh yeah yeah i
announced the album on this day this was
album announcement and 3d
uh birthday live announcement at the
same time i'm remembering now
we got a big upstairs jeremy thank you
to zelfuzin pretty's rock oh sorry
printy's roll excuse me
the art is dope af please be a poster i
don't know guess i'll have to wait and
see did you guys see the incredible art
that ray made i'm gonna shill it in
front of you anyway because it's just
the most freaking incredible [\h__\h] i was
a huge fan of ray like for years and
years and years and i never dreamed that
i would actually work with her
but then she's like no i'm a fan of
yours and we like actually like met
once upon a time at a show
in a place
long ago
and um
[Music]
that was wild
honestly just
crazy because i didn't know who she was
until we like started talking
um and we were just chatting and she was
like yeah i love your one song where you
do this
and then um i had one of her keychains
on my bag and she said oh you have my
keychain and i was like no freaking way
[Music]
that's you
you are you're red and she was like oh
boy i tried not to get too freaked like
freaky you know i didn't want to be like
a huge obnoxious like like one of those
obnoxious people that suddenly you start
treating people different once you learn
that they're like a freaking incredible
person that you've looked up to
for like so much of your life so i was
like oh i mean yeah
big fan of your work dude big fan of
your work
then we became friends
[Laughter]
it was crazy
so yo look at this art
like her her art is just straight up
like
they're beautiful illustrations that
you'd see at like
a museum like i want this in a museum
you know like this is just
this just takes takes it to a whole
other level this is like a painting that
i went framed and put in my house
goodness gracious
i just wow
and
did you tweet it want to know her at yes
i did i retweeted it and i i sent her a
reply
so it really does belong in an art
museum honestly yeah
like no doubt i just i look at
i just
i'm so glad to work with her and i hope
that continuing forward i can keep going
to her as like my album art person
either her or or mama because i feel
like
rey has just become like
a part of my
like rey's art has become like a part of
my my image and style and aesthetic and
like what i want to portray with my my
work
um
and uh and my music i feel like her art
perfectly encapsulates
the look that i want my albums to have
because like
again no disrespect to anyone who who
has like maybe just um a straight up
cell shaded picture of themselves as
like the album cover but that's not the
aesthetic i want for me you know
like i want like her art just looks like
it was made to be like
maybe not made to be but it just works
perfectly for covers of music
album covers and whatnot
so anyway yeah i love ray it is so great
um let's see we got a big ups too
thank you to frey and a big ups to mr
john carlton a big ups to mega black
doom who says hell yeah congratulations
callie thank you a big ups to draconic
insight thank you to jprs nsr and the
big ups to sharpie calvin's third
sharpest something or another yeah
calvin does enjoy sniffing a sharpie
every once in a while
so today i'm going to be a deadbeat now
thank you that's sweet of you i think it
was tofu may ky and otori p i think it's
to bren dan thank you very much i see
you said that you sent a letter to me i
haven't picked up my letters in a long
time so just give me a little bit more
time to go to the office and get it i
usually go to the office like every
three months or so to pick up fan
letters so um but i'm excited to i'm
excited to read it i know that you said
it last december but i also still have a
lot of unopened ones so
i'm excited to read it though thanks a
lot brendan
a big ups to jeff starr thank you
tentacle 7 336 a big ups to nick s
deadbeat thank you to lost deadbeat and
a big ups to wayne hong a big ups to
doug joseph thank you to that lcl smell
how have you been i feel like it's been
ages since i've seen you dude yeah it
does it's so exciting congrats callie
thank you my dude
a big ups to chewy dewey thank you tiger
c deadbeat full album omg let's go
i think it was to juan disimo and of
course mr squidward
you need me to
do you need me to comment on you again
come here
come here mr squidward
no baldness that time
i was able to conceal it perfectly so he
didn't see it the sad thing is i feel
like the other girls don't have to deal
with that baldness
because they don't have the veil thing
like i do on my arm
oh squidward squid blushing in chat you
can't hide from me i see you i see you
take all of my
take all of my money
oh mr squidward
you're so cute
thank you very much for your generosity
very kind of you i appreciate it
i mean yeah it kinda is huh
a big ups to the fez hat thank you
insufficiently anonymous says i've
promised you a song release each month
so here's 2022 for you
here's just all of this year nozo
a big ups to db nirvana and thank you
very much too
my reverb has been on the whole time
mickey
p
for the red super chat and the chad like
no message what else do we expect from
mickey p
besides chad like silas
what a chad
i think last time i asked this question
question mickey p said what is there to
say
which is yet again a chad like response
thanks man
we got a big ups to phil b thank you
general froggy and a big ups too
pk5 ir lots of exciting stuff can hardly
believe it best of luck at the festival
we've got a big ups too tony balls hey
tony check this out catch this hold on
catch this tony
[Music]
there you go alan's for you tony
thanks a lot tony says
you've worked so hard for all this this
is so much and knowing that there's more
to come hola fest hype 3d hype album
hype birthday live
hype
hype indeed tomorrow actually tomorrow
tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow i love you
tomorrow
we're only a day away from me dancing
and singing and talking about a lot of
important [\h__\h] oh boy
but i'm excited nonetheless
thanks a lot tony bones the big ups too
ernesto felix hey ernesto thank you very
much for the red super chat
big ups
appreciate you very much ernesto thanks
ernesto says congrats for your first
album that's a big step so can you ship
me a copy please
only available digitally for now
for now
okay
for now for now for now for now for an
hour and a half now
all good
we've got a big ups too
marcus manessa
thank you very much marcus
for the red super chat very sweet of you
as always for being such a huge
supporter of me
and your incredible generosity thank you
so much marcus marcus says these
announcements are so freaking hype
really looking forward to all of these
especially the envy in the album also
good luck at the fess but also you did
so good at the
it was amazing this is for you future
cali
thank you you kind of knew that i'd be
reading this in the future didn't you
you know how it goes around here marcus
you know
thanks a lot
i do appreciate it very sweet of you to
consider future me standing here before
you
in a t-pose flying like an airplane
you're near your mum
yeah
thanks a big ups to aiden thank you team
lemonade a vegas to jessica thank you
duke von distant and a big ups too
danger bread
dungeon bread thank you dunga bread this
one's called paper fortune i don't
really know what it means but it makes
me shake my hand as though i'm trying to
talk about something and gesturing very
passionate passionately
so
i guess i'll read uh dongerbread's um
message with a lot of like emphasis
[Music]
oh oh hey
we have a little friend here
oh
hello wakey wakey isn't baking
[Music]
no not coordinate
thank you oh it's okay i had a feeling
you might pop up and i was waiting for
you so don't you worry about it okay
oh i got the time wrong i thought it was
going to be
it's okay happy birthday thank you
beautiful no you're
gosh you're such a sweetheart goodness
great you don't have this
man you do
but you know that
love you kronstar
i love you too man
it's gonna be
is gonna be so good oh
i hope oh please don't cry are you good
or you just haven't you just have the
sniffles or something like that you good
dog
he sounds so sleepy i hope i hope i
didn't interrupt your sleep yeah i i
just woke up
oh man oh no i'm glad i got to catch it
though that's okay i've been there
i did the same thing from it
it's okay
um i just wanted to say that
you worked a lot towards this and
you're such a hard worker and it really
shows
everyone
sees and
appreciates you as always
cronies
you're so nice
you're so nice the man everyone and
everyone in council was right about the
gap mowing damn
i'm blushing you're making me blush what
the [\h__\h] you can't do that
you can't do that to me i'm gonna cup it
on you here i go this is gonna look
really weird with the perspective
kabedone
[Music]
there i give you
i love the caveadone
anyways it's so cool yeah someday you'll
get to do it too
and all the all the cronies will die
collectively
yeah i hope you can enjoy your birthday
i know you prepared a lot
yeah thank you for letting me join
of course your thing yeah no problem
just just happy to have have you call i
always have a great time when we collab
together and when we get to talk
afterwards and stuff like that just like
chatting with you is super fun so i'm
glad you go call in dude
thanks man keep up the great work yeah i
will you you
go go sleep please
please go get some good sleep and wake
up when when your body is ready okay
please please don't tell you helped
happy birthday thank you crony talk to
you later bye bye
bye
there she go
i felt really bad because apparently she
was waiting in the chat for like a
little bit
she's like i'm in the i'm muted in there
so she was like listening me like talk
like a crazy person to you guys
all the way from there
and then i had to peoples
figure out that she was waiting in there
for me so
but i'm glad that she got to come say
hello you know
that was nice you got to come you know
leave some some birthday wishes we love
the chronister he loves across here so
much so so mature
what a voice
dang she's the sleepy one like me like i
said i've been there before with omiz
stream i'm just glad that i made it in
the nick of
time crony built different oh yeah
crony build different
yeah
tired crown spirits nice surprise for
that was a nice surprise i'm glad i'm
glad that everybody that i asked to come
to the the tatsuma she got to make it in
the end i figured that you know everyone
would come in their own time and you
know
people would make it so no big deal
just very cool to see everyone and
receive everybody's sweet wishes i have
the best best co-workers and friends in
the world
we've got a big ups too
stick walker and a big ups to kaiju
fighter thank you to bailing baker and
the big ups dude joka thank you very
much to razz and a big ups too
berserking you've worked so hard for all
this and happy to see it come to
fruition
light up the world thank you so much
i did my best at the fest and i'm going
to do my best tomorrow
then we've got a big upsu
oh i'm still on reverb wow cronie heard
all that [\h__\h] she probably was like what
the [\h__\h] is wrong with you dude
i really need to pay attention to the
effects button big ups too covey
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for the red super chat akaspa arigato
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
i put a lot of energy into that
says
stark thank you to pixel art student
again and a big ups to bonk you
egg
thank you to washoe
i'm big ups to deadbeat shrimp
mori themed tattoo hey looking forward
to seeing it
it'll be death sensei wearing your hat
from your hip-hop outfit smoking a cigar
snoop dogg's special blend cigar oh yeah
he has one of those doesn't he
very cool i'm excited to see it deadbeat
shrimp that's awesome looking forward to
it i mean though surely you've gotten it
by now so
oh big ups too guys swear to god with
this [\h__\h] effects button
hironekosa
[Music]
please
look forward to it
okay we're going to have fun
[Music]
thanks a lot hiro neko always avails to
small ice thank you tvc studios and the
big ups too shafi your big day is right
tomorrow oh yeah this is before the
performance
i gave my all
ah
a big ups to brendan thank you very much
no worries about the
about your question before with your
letter i get so many of them but i will
check it don't you worry i'm sure that
you got it right usually we just get a
[\h__\h] ton of fan mail so i'll sort
through it and see if i can find yours
a big doctor zilla 337 thank you for the
congrats a big ups to mr vegan thank you
draconic insight a big ups to arcane x's
album is going to be legendary thank you
a big ups to avriox thank you to asaki
and a big ups decay walk for the many
threes
that's a funny message a big ops to elsi
le pen thank you very much love the
electric swing track me too did an
arrival is really good
we've got a big ups too
pretty
roll
thank you very much for the red super
chat pretties princess says yo so many
important things are popping up and i'm
happy to be happy and i'm so happy
that's not what that's not what prani's
rules
it's not pretty said
and i am so happy for you
my boy
you can bet your ass i'm going to be
cheering and cheering loud well as loud
as i can at 1am yeah timing is a bit
inconvenient this time too honestly with
the 3d concert i'm like
timing is not exactly perfect for
everyone but what can we do
i'm sorry for everybody that has to like
wake up if they want to see it live but
don't feel bad about having to catch the
vod because that's just how it be
sometimes so please don't push
yourselves anyway thank you as always
pretties appreciate the hell out of you
but you know that
pickups too qualify
man
big congrats callie you continue to grow
your potential to great heights thank
you very much a big ups obstamarcus
minus ss thank you to not an enemy and a
big ups to a special agent chris
a big ups to ghost yuki thank you
insufficiently anonymous and a big ups
to nick s deadbeat then we've got a big
ups to road forks you thank you very
much for the red super chat appreciate
the hell out of you my dude thank you so
much road forks you says and i quote
you're crazy maury but in a good way so
many amazing announcements you've worked
so hard these past few months and i'm so
proud of you dude thank you so much
road forks you you've always been
an incredible awesome supporter so thank
you very much for always sending me
words of encouragement and being so
great i'm glad to have you as a debbie
dude thank you so much
we've got a big ups too
[Music]
thank you very much arigato
thank you jprsnsr and arnoffomendes
thank you very much
a big ups to igiris thank you to lim
nakama and big ups too
orenji
first time sending you a supa thank you
so much a big ups to
the
faction thank you very much for the red
super chat i appreciate it thank you
[Music]
thank you
and v faction says thank you
what a freaking chad hell yeah thank you
very much thank you v faction i should
be thanking you thank you for thanking
me for thanking you for thanking me for
thanking you for thanking me for
thanking you
we got a big ups too kill em gillamax
the space beat thank you very much
for the red super chat
thank you thank you gila max thank you
very much gillimax says and i quote god
damn
appreciate all the effort you pour into
everything cali thank you very much
gilmax's face beat very kind of you
people
[Music]
gilmax you're awesome thank you for
being so damn generous all the time
and i got a big upset duke von distant
thank you to acidic rue a bigger suhyon
siang thank you to jeff starr thank you
to franco a big ups to surreal sight
thank you again sakura akemi
we've got a big ups to king l k
w and a big ups to alexian
thank you to lioness wolf
and a big ups to jeff starr thank you to
scp rx 420 kryptonian thank you to
missed fist and a big ups to alter as
well
thank you to chokawa
kelly you are the best arigato
and we've got a big ups for a red super
chat from
ann
thank you very much and i appreciate the
heck out of you very kind of yeah thanks
and says nothing because anne is a chad
thank you thank you very much for that i
appreciate it
then we've got a big ups too another
silent shad who could it be but the one
the only
able
tsn
thank you very much abel season
extremely sweet if you had to just drop
drop a brick on my face and leave it's
very kind thank you so much for the
generosity
we got a big ups to bong long
you're an aspiring vocalist huh that's
really cool i hope that you would get
your dream okay so do your best
let's see we've got a big up to a salsa
sauce and a big ups to
rus foreign
for the red
super chat thanks a lot restful rick
russ raspberry says
so many great things happening within a
short time and i'm so hyped for all of
it i can't wait to see you in 3d i know
i will be in tears when i finally see
all of myth moving around on the big
stage well we still do have some time
before we're all together but someday
the day will come i believe it it's
getting closer i just know it
but i'm not jinxing anything so i won't
say exactly when i think i'll keep it in
my heart as a secret wish
we've got a big ups too
large
arch thank you
i want to get on mr bones as well right
you say that but you don't i promise
a big ups too jorge mendoza and a big
ups to waluigi cubed thank you so much
for being hyped
we've got a big ups to storm tag
storm tag thank you very much for the
red super chat as always appreciate your
support storm tag
storm tag says and a quote eat album
covers in moderation eating album covers
can lead to hype delirium excessive
money spending and unaliving
talk to your reaper to see if eating
album covers is right for you
expert advice from an absolute expert
hey thanks a lot stormtag i appreciate
that thank you so much for the
generosity and for dropping by to say
hello and leave a little advice for
deadbeats who may be feeling lost
we've got a big ups to exploding penguin
thank you a big upset iconic insight
again
thank you to zalfuze and a big ups to
zork787 a big us again to mr john
carlton thank you we got a big ups to in
angela riehl thank you a big ups too
shadow
pencil thank you very much for the red
super chat i appreciate it very much
shadow pencil what's this no message
what a chat
[Music]
incredibly generous of yeah thank you
always shadow pencil i see you in chat
today as well thank you very much look
at all those big ups as well shadow
pencil always being so nice giving big
ups to the other dead beats when their
names pop up it's very cool of you
thank you so much
and let's see we've got a big ups 2
[Music]
bunny game
looking forward to the album in 3d thank
you to lc le pen stay healthy for those
sick beats then we've got a big ups to
rolly thank you very much for the red
super chat
it's very appreciated no message
what a chad
what can he do about those chads that
just drop a brick on your face and don't
say anything nothing much really
let's see we got a big ups too um
draconic insight and kaito h thank you
and a big ups to insufficiently
anonymous otsukali a big upstate prince
rock have fun out there maury thank you
to jpr snsr you spoil us callie thank
you for all your hard work
thank you to ren i'll pick up to
zekenator77 the hype is hard to keep in
i feel that oh man i think it's to 7j 7j
thank you for the very cute sticker
kawaii
very cute and a big ups to alex add
coily
thank you for the the force
very cute
all right well
looks like that's it for supers you guys
oh man about four hours we went with
lots of calls plenty of calls some super
reading um as for jump king super chat
reading streams well i do actually have
those spreadsheets saved so i'll be safe
they'll be safe with me the endurance
one is the one that's grinding in the
back of my mind but
the one where i was just playing with
the other girls i'm not going to count
it as a collab because they didn't have
to join me so i will read them um just
in due time so but for the most part we
got the big announcement ones done the
big day is soon right yeah i gotta go
sleep and get ready for it so today's
super chats will be combined together
with tomorrow's super chats for the
celebration afterward on the fifth which
will be a nice long stream where we
celebrate all the announcements and um i
talk about some of the stuff that i
announced
those super chats will be off by the way
um
so that i can focus on the ones uh from
tonight and tomorrow anyway uh oh this
is not the correct roar gesture i wanted
no hold on no we're not getting low but
i can get low
get low
get low get low
anyway
that's a fun one
um
i'm gonna go rest up for tomorrow okay
guys
and uh making another little
video reminding folks about
the the right timing anyway time to fly
off to bed for me but i guess i'll see
you guys a bit later okay and um you
take care of yourselves and i will be
doing my very best for you guys
to give you the best present
in the world
alive from me in 3d
[Music]
i hope that um
yeah this is kind of the last time that
we're like speaking like this before i
go and perform and then announce all the
big stuff um
so i guess
what i want to say is that um
nobody don't get too emotional uh
after tomorrow things
they're not nothing really is is gonna
seem to change
right out the gate so don't be nervous
but um it's only good things and
so many
so much of it is because of you guys
um i just want you to know that that
when you see that announcement
um
and kind of get
an idea of what's going to go on from
here i want you to know that
um
it's not just me but also you guys who
are a really big
part
of this
so thank you
you're still making us nervous i feel
like no matter what i say i'm still
gonna make you guys nervous so you know
what at this point i'm going to bed i'm
going to bed you guys see what happens
tomorrow and just know that
i love and appreciate you guys
really truly um
you guys
you guys are the best
so let's keep having fun together
okay
i'll see you guys later goodbye
and
peace
hold on i can i can do that better hold
on
regular peace
peace
bye
[Music]
every meaning
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
my boys
[Music]
is
alone
[Music]
is
glory yeah
[Music]
to get that gold never get old remember
i can't find a reason stay
[Music]
oh