[Music]
so
hey hello everyone oh is the music too
loud guys
it's a bit too loud in my ears let me
turn it down a little bit
how about now how it oh it's
so loud for me i'll turn it down on my
side
is is the btm goods
okay welcome everyone
[Music]
ohayo
today is the second time we play
sims 4. um
[Music]
nice to come back here i thought
it would be lovely to play
um sims 4 today because i you know
they're in sims 4
there's this mount komodevi
sounds japanese huh and if you look at
it it does look very japanese too
uh because uh this is an expansion pack
that is like
supposed to like it's inspired by the
japanese
uh north area hokkaido where
me and cali went still
hokkaido
um
[Music]
it's a like japanese mountain
area with lots of snow you can go skiing
you can go into an onsen
you can go into ryokan there's so much
you can do
so i thought this would be perfect for
us
so that we can recreate it right
[Music]
nice coincidence right i thought so too
because um
i mean i first saw that they had a like
a snowy
snow themed uh snow winter holiday
themed pack
i didn't think it would be themed after
japan honestly from for me
when i think of like a famous
snow um
a country that's famous for its snow i
think of australia
or i don't know somewhere else in europe
or i don't know
uh antarctica but i don't think about
japan necessarily although oh look um
hokkaido
is quite famous for having amazing snow
but i would think i would think
of the european alps i don't know
i would think of many other places but
not japan
but well i've been there myself now
to hokkaido and i have to say it was uh
pretty
we went to a skiing place that skiing
area that was very very close to
sapporo the like the capital of hokkaido
um i'm sure they have much much better
skiing places than the closest one to
a
[Music]
little capital basically i'm sure if you
go out a little bit more i'm sure they
have even better areas to ski
way better so we'll start
i guess we'll start off at home and then
uh
i'm not i'm not sure how this works i
guess we'll just probably go on a
vacation together
so here's takamuri living in their
penthouse suite
how are they doing how have they been
doing since i've been gone
let's see if they made a baby or two
[Applause]
all right all right i forgot how to play
the game hey she's also very flirty from
a titillating banter what
koi smiles and flirtatious jokes have
set the tone for romans
feeling a close connection oh
first case first yeah we've been uh
we've been very new partner we've been
very active last time
oh it's still christmas here but i'll
keep the christmas decorations i i want
to keep the christmas mood going
oh callie's over here oh hi y'all
good morning callie how are you doing
we have really cute lingerie it's
actually uh matching mine is just a
different color
isn't it cute oh sorry no staggy
cute cute
okay so uh wait how do we play this game
again
uh like first of all uh
maybe if didn't you just go to the
toilet i guess you didn't
then okay use and massage oh yeah the
japanese toilets
i don't really like that [\h__\h] it
what just happened to it okay you didn't
i think that's because i probably
ended the game last time while i was uh
going to the toilet
and what are you doing tv watch action
oh you're doing quite fine it seems
but maybe you want to go a little bit
back to bed
woohoo with kiara hell yeah i need time
but not right now
um oh okay once we get kiara's uh
oh nice ass once we get kiara's
health up we shall
we shall where are you going we shall go
on the holiday on vacation
okay so one second
she's taking a quick quick quick bath or
isn't that nice
that was fast oh my god speed okay
and now we wait
nine minutes and we only have bottom
left what fine what did i do
i just there's music and they just sleep
can you guys sleep with music on me
i can't really like i i would i would
like turn it on to
maybe try to fall asleep but then i
would eventually turn it off
i can't sleep uh i can't sleep while i'm
watching netflix though
that is the skill that i have acquired
oh she's inspired she's gonna cook eggs
on toast
eggs okay
let's watch her cook some eggs on toast
while i'm sleeping she's making
breakfast for me
um no wait actually i think she's only
cooking for herself probably
oh is the cake so good
yeah seems so cali
she's cooking so aggressively oh
oh what was that
oh she turned on the music while she was
cooking oh yeah she's enjoying her
lifestyle nicer
she's done yeah that's only for herself
why did you put it
what is she doing
cali cooking stream
oh are you done now oh wait that's
oh it is far more than one person oh hi
nice of her
listen to s pop sims pop yummy you could
sit down we have so many chairs oh gosh
she looks
terrifying you know i was really
thinking of making like a contest
uh of uh like um you guys
recreating whole life english and sims 4
and then i will just use the winner the
winners model because
they look terrifying oh
[Music]
i should probably do that
like not only me and kelly but also the
other three
would be dope if we can if we could
recreate them
oh you don't have to cook there's food
here
you guys should sit down why are you
guys not sitting down
what is that room anyway you you sit in
the bathroom to eat
accidents okay seems logic
that's a great idea yeah we should do it
i want to do it
i want better i want cuter models that
look like us
because i mean i think i look pretty
accurately like myself but you guys keep
on making fun
of my kiana saying that she looks weird
huh she looks beautiful
oh kelly where are you going you should
maybe wear some clothes
i guess you don't give a [\h__\h] let's
follow callie
the way she walks oh she's gonna work
out
oh oh yeah that would give me those
added as
laggings she's already sweating that was
quick
cali your your poster is bad
[Laughter]
callie
the way you run oh my god oh she's sweat
she's dripping oh oh
you done she's so cute look at her butt
oh my god
oh [\h__\h]
all right all right so every everyone's
happy um
you stop that how do i go on vacation
wait one second
do i have to like um maybe use my mobile
phone
travel take a vacation
club county who the hell is tristan frey
i guess we can go down
okay
i would like to book the 30k penthouse
suite thank you
[Music]
what do you mean that's too expensive i
can totally afford it check my other
credit card
okay so see you can go you can do snow
sports
oh and onsen then you and mountain climb
oh you can do mountain climbing oh
i saw it in the screenshot i wasn't sure
actually also let me
oh let's vibe to that music while i'm
opening my hot chocolate
i ordered uh cold chocolate but these um
brought me hot chocolate which is okay i
guess i'm
i'm not the karen i'm not gonna complain
i love hot chocolate then cold chocolate
i did order cold chocolate but that's
okay
one second they put a lot of uh plastic
wrap
so that it doesn't spill
[Music]
cold chocolate what is that iced
ice ice chocolate instead of a
hot chocolate eh it's just uh
[Music]
honestly to be more accurate there
should be snow everywhere but okay
so i guess oh these are the ryokans
right all right let's let's see what we
have here
can you actually live here i i guess you
could probably build
build a residential lot what is that non
rental launch
is that just a normal house
[Music]
i want to see them closer is that not
possible
oh here's a bar a park
this is i guess some sights i wonder if
you can see that
okay and then we have uh five one two ki
omatsu
which is 758 uh simoleons per day
this is something else and this oh this
is the
this is the most expensive one
[Music]
three ba three uh bedrooms
okay i guess we'll go to this one
rent for oh
[\h__\h] wait days uh five days i guess
[Music]
let's go oh that we had four nights five
days so let's go for five days yay
vacation time vacation
oh let's take a look stop okay
look we're wearing our matching sweaters
that's so cute it's so cute it's so
fitting
okay whoa i like i like the beige
interior i like uh the color base um
very pretty i like this this uh
fireplace too oh that looks like some
somehow that looks like ikea furniture
look at these little japanese details
oh my god wait you can do hot pot
now that's great oh my god this is
amazing
oh my god i love this they implemented a
freaking kodaksa
sims electronic arts
you guys are amazing oh my god what's
behind here
oh just nothing okay
oh that bathtub
is that a wooden bathtub damn actually
that reminds me the
the i don't know the design reminds me
of the
bathtub that we had outside oh i like
the sign that says no shoes
yes yes everyone take off your shoes
wear your slippers or don't don't wear
slippers doesn't matter at least take
off your shoes
what do we have here outside again oh
oh oh that's a cute room
is there wait how do i go to uh
how do i get to my second floor again ah
here
[Music]
oh we don't need that we don't have
children yet
that's the children's room in an avid
normal room
mm-hmm
i don't know what to call it it's like
uh in japan if you go
like um not only in an onsen but
everywhere
they they kind of give you like a stool
and then um
uh what's it called uh
wash wash basin
and it's like a bucket yeah it's like a
bucket you apparently you're supposed to
rinse yourself with that and sit on the
uh
but i never sit on those things because
i don't know
especially in like public baths i just
feel like of course i clean it but still
i feel uncomfortable sitting my naked
ass on a stool that
a lot of other naked asses have sat on
before i just don't feel okay with it
i don't like it i don't know about you
guys but i don't want it
oh they got oh they got chests outdoors
they gotta play chess we gotta play
chess eventually
um hold on okay okay that's that's it i
suppose yeah okay
from the outside look at that it's all
snowy it's so pretty
i don't wonder what the other ones look
like though
oh my god they got a fireplace outside
oh
nice and i like how that one is kind of
like
um like lifted from the ground i like
that
it's so pretty comes in me
oh it's a ski left oh my god
[Music]
sims has like developed so much
oh my god
sims has changed so much oh that's why
you go skiing
oh that's so
dope oh my god look at that
that's amazing
oh that's gonna be dangerous here i'm
gonna die here
i wonder if like in sims there's so many
ways you can die i wonder if they added
like a way to die like
through skiing it it's actually it seems
like something that sims would do
i feel like they would implement that i
wonder does anyone know
yes they did did they
only one person said they did so i'm not
sure if that's true
oh my god
okay okay so um then i guess
yeah let's get started and enjoy our
holiday and since
let's enjoy our vacation
[Applause]
how do you two feel about
what's about family which family how did
you feel about having a vacation
yes you feel like you two are starved
yes yes yes
oh that was so deep
discuss fine cuisine yes
now you must be freaking kidding me what
really okay we're not going skiing just
yet
okay can we do something in the snow
shop snowing kelly oh
let's make a snow angel oh
yeah i'll move
[Music]
you shouldn't be shoving snow she's not
doing it
stop talking to kelly
wait callie would never accept that
callie would not just let that happen
[Laughter]
she's happy though you don't see me die
this net
payback time [\h__\h] payback time
look there yeah that's more like it
not impressed
i get water no no no you're thirsty cali
is first here everyone
callie is officially firsty wait let's
make a snow angel
and me too i also want to
oh it's so cute can i change the angle
to look like that but
from above i don't know how to change
the angle properly
i'm gonna change the angle
i don't know how to do it yeah i don't
know
maybe you can't tab
[Laughter]
oh
oh oh there we go
it's got my face
oh oh oh wait i how
can't just didn't react to me for some
reason
i'm making snow angels
yay
oh i'm done yeah that's a beautiful snow
angel
huge head though wow
wow she's done too ah
isn't that cute oh wait kelly
you're in the way i want to take you a
pretty screenshot oh my god look at her
oh let's follow oh she
should put on the fire how nice can i go
faster with this uh camera thingy
oh
how do i take screenshots and sims again
[Music]
i forgot
see i don't hear the camera sound is it
because i'm in this
oh i think it was capturing them
oh that's it you gotta enjoy it more
longer it's so beautiful
let's just follow them a little while
okay you're doing do you want some tv
she's on the toilet okay you gotta you
gotta take your toilet breaks that's
very important
is she gonna wash her hands though yes
very well let's enjoy the kotatsu
that's it
can we have a woohoo in the kotatsu
i mean it's not much space but
i don't think the creators of sims care
about that
oh well that's just cute
now talk do something
my smile is so creepy oh smiles are so
creepy
don't go away
[Music]
oh stretch is that necessary
get back in there wait i want to see
what you guys can do in there
no that's not it would say woohoo in the
kotatsu
yeah no i don't think you can do it even
if we nap
it's for the science oh they just snap
like that
they don't even lie down
oh my god oh
let's listen closely maybe we can hear
cali talking in her sleep you know
oopsie
i love i love chiara
i love you kiara you're so cute
she's talking can you guys here again oh
my god
yes piana has a nice ass
oh did you hear that it's oh my god
that's exactly what she said
on on on our vacation too oh see i woke
up i was like
did you just say i have a nice ass
did i just imagine that
no no kiara she really said it
all right where are we going drink
you don't drink alcohol though that's
not very accurate i hope that's
not non-alcoholic oh yeah it looks like
it looks like milk though
what is that you're gonna put it down
it is milk ah that's cute because um
in japan after going into the onsen
people like to drink milk to i don't
know refresh or something
wait wait wait is that the fish milk
no ew that's normal milk
to be honest i don't like drinking
what i don't like drinking milk
um just like that i like it if it's like
mixed with corn flakes and stuff but
what's up uncomfortable
that's what that now that is accurate
because
i oh she's got oh hi kelly don't bite me
i'm just gonna um
have a little um yeah
i feel i felt a bit uncomfortable from
doing that milk which is so freaking
accurate i really don't like drinking
milk just like that i feel sick after
drinking milk like that
sorry kelly that might stink a little
bit comments
like this that's that's just like in
real life
i love it kiara is me what are you
drinking now
oh nothing she's just cleaning up oh
what a good girl
now that's not very accurate though i
would never clean up
why are you going over there there's a
sink here
sims logic as per usual now what's
what's she gonna do
you know i'm surprised actually you
should be drinking alcohol
can we get some alcohol for callie
nothing can i order alcohol where's the
alcohol
maybe we can find a bar or something
travel let's see
we need some alcohol for cali uh
what do we have here there we go izakaya
let's go islam
is a japanese restaurant that's like a
mix between restaurant and bar
and they have lots of like small snacks
like good food really good food but like
in
like more than having like a proper
dish it's like um
it's like food that you can share with
everyone pretty much
and they're famous for the alcohol
so let's go it's a kaya
[Music]
what the hell okay we are here let's
take a look at the izakaya
oh
[Music]
you sit like on the ground in like a
hole on in the ground
but that's other than that it looks
it looks more like a bar not like a
izakaya
looks more like a bar but okay close
enough let's see what
alcohol and food we can get here check
upstairs yeah that still wasn't very
accurate oh well okay so
do we order here and then take it to can
we
can we order from here though sit
together okay let's see
oh
[Music]
not exactly the music the music that
they would play in the izakaya
okay let's sit by the window get some
drinks for cali
um get some hot wine for callie flam 12.
wait where the hell are you going
bro wait [\h__\h] you're bringing your trash
from home and throwing it away here okay
stretch again she needs a massage kelly
needs a massage we gotta go to the spa
guys
okay give me give me a drink please
order drink
order drinks for group sure oh
would i have to be here what what a half
severe is that supposed to mean
something
um
where's that where's the wine or i guess
she would
probably also i don't know what she what
would she drink i don't really know much
about alcohol
maybe a dim and gusty sounds disgusting
would i have to is that what it's
supposed to
say
shaky sexy
maybe that is what it means ew who left
that's here
put it on the ground oh
kiara kelly got you a drink i'm sure you
don't like it but drink it anyway
wait we're so far apart why are these
people in between us
[Music]
so much for our romantic getaway
cookie mail
read
you should stop talking and maybe start
drinking chiara
uncomfortable
pretty neppy
she's disappointed again oh man we can
get something she likes
order drink or their favorite drink what
is your favorite drink
what is what is my favorite drink oh i
don't know what that is
ice cubes
oh yeah oh yeah give me all that juice
is my drink done uh i have it now right
what is my favorite drink what is my
favorite jinx
this is sweet and spicy okay there you
go apparently that's it
what is she doing you know eat chips oh
that's very cali like
kelly likes sweeter chips yeah oh that's
kind of nice
that's very accurate can we get some
proper food though
oh my god is she okay order food
hell yeah give me that german curry
blessed
curry ones in germany is so yummy
i'm drinking my hot chocolate by the way
it's not very hot anymore
wait let me take a look at that
oh oh i mean it's um
it's lacking uh the curry powder on top
but pretty close
why are you talking to that guy i don't
give a [\h__\h] about that guys
by the way
the sweater kind of makes you think that
this person is uh
we'd love to have you join powerhouse
hell no
i wonder if we can find a proper uh
bunny doll because
um i doubt it and but i wanted to find a
bunny
208 wait how did i just gain 208 dollars
how did that happen what the hell did we
do
what uncomfortable from low quality
furniture oh god
kiana is uh really not feeling it she's
enjoying it pretty tasty oh she loves
the chips
wait that's so fitting sorry i missed
clicked but look at
look at that look at that
it's the deathbeats lurking now
that is lurking now hell yeah dad beats
lurking
yeah eat your goddamn food eat it
[Music]
where is the chicken dough where's my
employees i don't see any of my
employees
where are the chickens it's very very
much
[Laughter]
what a cute cat oh my god with the
similean sign oh my god
a cute place here
i do oh that's a japanese garden
[Music]
boots let's go there
he greeted what's going on why is she
flirting now
what makes you feel flirty actually can
we have like a
can we can we can we do something here
no no no woohoo options unfortunately
anywhere all right all right all right
maybe in the
maybe in the japanese garden or maybe
here
visit the park okay me and kelly let's
go
it's time
why are you what what's your problem
with that hanami
oh corn is japanese for garden guys and
hanami gaba
is like on the side of the flowers
um viewing the flowers
they kissed himself again and what what
are you looking at not even gnaw
wait oh my god look at this
it gets so pretty look
at it
[Music]
that's so pretty what the hell
that that's that's so pretty look at
that
i mean without the guy though i don't
like the guy in there can he like go
away
let's uh express admiration
and uh no
uh wait and express
fondness and and kiss hands
and passionate kiss and profess
undying love obviously i'm dying because
i'm a phoenix and she's the deaf so
obviously
how romantic is that
[Music]
smell the oh
grebo for i love you too
obviously of course i knew that already
keanu's playing with her dolls again
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
wait wanna get the other angle too i'm
taking screenshots guys there's too many
people here
too many people
oopsies yes
you're so cute where are you going what
where's she going
where are you going
bro away she still has trash rivers
it just happened or you wanted to throw
someone in
someone else's trash i don't i don't
know what the hell you doing i don't
know what the hell are you doing
what you want to talk to that girl no
it's so cute the shops are so cute
all right kelly what what is she are you
doing
push-ups
[Applause]
very busy cali she's all she's always
doing a push-up sasuka kelly
satsuga sit together isn't that
beautiful
how romantic how sweet
how sweet
callie came first where's where's me
there i am there i come running
away at the way i look at her but she's
just looking at her phone
[Music]
come on let's cuddle
whisper sweet nothings
wait i'm taking so many screenshots
again
how do i hide the plumb bob again
how do i hide the cl plum bomb
gift massage
alt tab nobody's still there when i tab
oh well
[Laughter]
did you hear that
no i was i was not fast enough i'm not
used to this system yet
give me another massage please uh
there you go another one please
oh look at us just being
you have to cute english ah
sorry it's zucchini
oh yeah oh oh oh callie is excited cool
for the stadium
where did i go oh
chiara wants to play chess well
we have to play chess together
apparently we're gonna play chess
together okay let's go let's look at
what they're doing
oh what did you think about that move
oh wow groundbreaking move there oh my
god
we're playing chess oh we're chess
geniuses
who's gonna win who is going to win
will it be kiana the professional chess
player or will be kelly the chess
amateur obviously it will be me
look over there
mommy oh she cheated
kelly cheated oh my god
you savage
and kelly would do something like that
okay let's see we're getting close to
the end
place your bets now who's gonna win
i think i'm uh she's white and i'm black
by the way
oh oh it's it's getting dark now
um
[Music]
next change
wait what she won kelly won what you
cheat at
mccain mctake
oh that's not fair kelly that's not fair
wait why can't i not woohoo in here
why can't i not woo
why i thought you could rule in public
bathrooms
and say oh oh i didn't even own oh yeah
we don't need a bathroom we can woohoo
out here
yeah i just keep on kissing each other
oh
she's making hot dogs now oh what is
that
is that uh kushiyaki
what's she shut up
real fruit oh no that's fruit oh yeah
it's apples and
what bananas or something like that
all right i'll take it i'll go to the
toilet ones though
still playing chess gotta love chess
where is she going oh i guess it's going
to be our dinner well thank you kelly
she's she's providing for
our family
all right and after that i'll join you
eat eating the fruit
i love my fruit she knows i love cowie
knows i love fruit
oh we're gonna eat in here who the hell
is that that it
[\h__\h] off
i don't want to be friends with these
people
i think
[Music]
she's talking about death
let's let's uh yeah let's check out some
dead people
kelly wants to check out some dead
people cali wants to pee
kawaii
she's very confident about her chess
game but you cheated
i don't know how you can be so proud of
that is there anything else i can do
here i
i wanna like look at the scenery but
it's not possible it seems
all right let's wait until she gets out
of there and then uh we can go
um to our sweet sweet sweet uh
home vacation home because i'm getting
tired
oh she wants to play chess again huh
dad beats peeing now
oh yeah we can stargaze oh do we have to
how do we do that i guess i did you go
[Music]
okay let's do some stargazing
tell joke about ducks
why are you gonna tell me a show tell me
that super no joke what is it
guys do you have a duck joke tell me
your duck jokes now
go go quick in the chat give me give me
a duck joke now
i'm waiting
thank you for the membership welcome
that beat's quacking now
should watch the basketball
no duck joke
shift and tap will switch the camera
into first person mode oh shift and
towel
is that why did the duck go to jail
because he got
caught selling quack
okay okay okay a duck walks into a bar
and orders a lot when the bartender asks
how the duck will pay it just says just
put
[\h__\h]
out oh my god
salunga what do you call subata
subaru when she goes off the high board
a super diver
what
sorry when i tap out of the game there's
no audio
what's she's talking about bats
that's unbelievable kelly i know you're
about
oh i see we're having such a great time
together here outside
but i think it's time to go actually no
you wanted to do stargazing
what's a suave a case what is that map
oh
well that's just so sweet
look at the stars guys look at them wow
so many stars
on the mountain what a beautiful scenery
all right let's go home and have some
wuhu
let's go home and have some vuhu how do
i get back home there
okay time to go home time to go home run
run run run run run
oh you're gonna just walk
hundred percent accurate she's playing
chess again
i just love chess you know but
what's it um
what's wrong she's so tired kiara can
you
can you are you okay you can do it right
why why did she not take over her shoes
though
kutsun lugeel
she's wearing those uggs 100 accurate
kelly what are you doing kelly kelly
kelly kelly
no not sleep yet
oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
hmm
ah isn't that nice ah oh
oh i saw the hell for a moment
they're going crazy in there
[Music]
better leave them alone we shouldn't be
we shouldn't be looking at them while
they're
you know having the private private look
at that that's so cute
a cute snow cat oh they don't oh yeah
they're done
okay okay
isn't that beautiful thank you for the
super chat
yay it's 9am and we're still sleeping
good morning ohio uncomfortable
wait what chilled it's getting cold
someone's gonna start robbing themselves
back up i went oh
because you're naked you should probably
wear some clothes then
okay uh what's it's kelly
grill assado asado
can we shower together
[Applause]
[Music]
you should probably wear some clothes
what the hell you should ride some clubs
oh my god please
please wear some clothes
what the hell is that morning meat
kelly kelly you please please
please wear some clothes
change into nude
this one it's not that hard there we go
feeling much better and after you're
done you can
come down here
is that that's not really a breakfast
well i guess i see some scrambled eggs
there
scrambled eggs and some beans and a lot
of meats eh
okay let's grab a serving i guess
greens what kind of breakfast is that
nico
i love meat but that's kind of weird
no no you don't have to cook there's
food here
oh god she's wasting food no kiara
no she got those veggies
come on quick quick
oh look at those beautiful paintings hmm
i want to turn on the lights of that
i always have carol down as more of a
seafood person eh
no no no i uh i'm not a big fan of
seafood
wow wow could you sit down though
sit down while you're eating nice
oh we're having a nice breakfast and she
turned on some music
and i'm preps too lane ah
so nice i just thought there was a like
a window there and i saw some people
like that but no that's just a tv
high quality tv in sims
okay cali is done eating cali is feeling
amazing
she's she's super energized i think it's
time is our
is our uh after our first night and we
want to stay a hundred percent accurate
we want to stay
100 accurate so we're gonna go skiing
today
she's doing a workout again
in the bathroom that is not very
accurate i must say kelly
kelly doesn't just randomly start
working out randomly
to anywhere what the hell she can shape
that what
so
she's thinking about it
snap snap snap very carefully
nope what can i do meanwhile well well
okay before we go skiing
okay i guess you're going to the toilet
okay meanwhile
we're watching cali snip snapping
what are you doing you're making coffee
no no no no no no no that's not accurate
wait for oh tea okay that's accurate yes
it says we want to stay accurate okay
they understand me that's
is that right is that
is that a bunny because i
can't because i can't
you know i wanted to recreate this
hundred percent and i did say we have a
bunny at the
at the hotel so there you go that's our
bunny
[Music]
it's a bunny that's so cute kelly is
really into bunnies these days because
of that one bunny
oh my god it's i don't know i don't know
how this happens it's just
i don't know how it ends up being as
accurate
this is amazing can i have some tea too
kiara of course you can take
[Music]
cute i wonder what they're talking about
she's talking about i'm talking about
the gamecube
that looks like a gamecube controller
melvin
oh yeah that's so funny
[Music]
no voices the voices are also accurate
we're doing 100
accurate
are you guys gameplay to rumble
let's freaking go let's go
how do we how do we go skiing huh here i
guess
wait
right to the top with me
let's go okay now i'm wearing my window
i'm bringing my teeth
we're running in in the same rhythm one
two one
two one two one two
now we're out of ribbon damn it ah no
we're still in ribbon one
two one two one two one two one two
slowly no i walk up those stairs and
then sexy walk oh yeah do the sexy world
oh yeah
oh yeah do the sexy one
what is it
where am i what the hell where did we go
you didn't ride to the top right oh
we're already at the top where how did
that happen oh the register
teleport oh what are they doing are they
waiting
are they waiting to ski down
we don't have our ski skiers does that
just automatically
okay let's see what we got
which one is the easy one i wonder
how do i ski change to goofy stats
go skiing on this ah i could i can't
even go to this one
we have to start with the easy one so
that's the easy one go skiing on easy
slope
continuously low intensity
go skiing on easy slope continuously
high intensity now this is where we make
the difference
let's see i still have my tea
it's walking so slowly kelly what's
wrong we're waiting in line
oh she threw away the into her teeth
okay we're ready we're ready
let's freaking do this let's freaking do
this
okay let's go come on gal you can do it
come on kelly i'm rooting for you
that looks so much like ally oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah there she goes
where did she go where did she go where
did she go don't go
there she is
she's doing the pizza cut
wait wait wait
let's take a look at her
where did she go again i missed her
again
oh she's doing way better than she
actually did
oh how how am i doing oh there we go
okay let's let's see what high intense
intensity looks like
don't crash kiana don't you crash
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait i want to take a proper screenshot
the angle is so difficult
you can't get closer dammit
oh no it's good oh hell yeah
oh my god it's me skiing
how realistic way
[Music]
no crash no crash oh
i pretty much crashed into that dude
though but that's okay oh i
am i know and we don't want to be like
that i only want to be like that with
cali
go skiing again what are you doing
you're going up skiing again yes yes
she's going up
wait for me kelly
actually guys one time when we went when
we went skiing i think like
the second time we went up i was
i was being the stupid instagram girl
i was taking photos while we were at on
the ski lift
and um
i lost one of my one of my sticks
it fell down while we were honestly that
had to happen
obviously it had to happen yeah one of
them fell
down at least my phone didn't fall down
but one of the
one of the sticks fell down so we so
yeah we went up
and then uh at the top i told the staff
that i'm stupid i'm
a noob and sorry i dropped one of the
sticks and then
the staff uh yeah brought me this the
ski pole thank you the skipo
but wow so i was waiting at the top
and kelly already skied down and
and i i waited until i got my skateboard
because i was too scared to only go with
one ski pole i i didn't feel like i had
the
the confidence to go skiing with only
one
all right that was one story i it
happens yeah but i felt so embarrassed
about that
and why is she feeling cold or not cold
but like she's not feeling good
toilet just callie can you pee in the
snow
wait that's not an option
why is that not an option like she's
doing the even
even without the skis she's doing the
pizza style
why can't she not peens i mean
i mean it should be an option don't you
think wait wait kelly wait you're too
fast what the hell that's
oh
wait that i love that
[Laughter]
almost not go
kelly
go callie let's follow her
oui
[Music]
good job kelly you're doing quite well
nice one why am i
being i'm being interrupted
i was supposed to fall she just doesn't
give a [\h__\h] she just keeps on running
she just doesn't give a [\h__\h]
she doesn't care wow
what a badass she she had an accident
but she just gets up and runs straight
up
back again
brock kelly you can't she needs a pedo
i'm surprised she didn't you know
accidentally pee but when she when she
fell down there
going skiing again it's my turn now
i somehow skipped one but okay there we
go again we're standing in line
what is it you know he's thinking about
cupcakes cute
i love it i wish it was that easy to
um you know move around in this in the
snow
while you're wearing skis though
kiana got a loner snowboard from the
lodge for now but it's a little janky
and doesn't feel that great purchase a
new snowboard for her
in the bits and bubbles vending machine
for a comfortable ride yeah but i'm not
a snowboarder i want to ski
let dad use the restroom okay
oh she's doing it anyway on her own okay
okay wait why are we snowboarding
whoa maybe wait it looks so cool
let me try to hide that person behind me
with my head no it's impossible
oh actually maybe i might be better
when i'm snowboarding than that when i'm
skiing
camera angle please oh there she goes
oh there i go wait
going well for the first time this is
the first time i've ever snowboarded
how'd you make that
only we might oh my wow
oh yeah a nice one
canada hmm found a new hobby
snowboarding she can
do beginner runs on the bunny slope or
razor slopes i sir
maybe we should buy a better snowboard
apparently you can do that where is that
vending machine
you can buy freakin
that's that that's amazing you can buy
snowboards and skiers in the vending
machine
amazing sas sugani hon
wouldn't have expected anything else
wait why are you getting
are you getting in line here when you
wanted to go to the toilet
where is the toilet by the way
i just i think if you right click how
did that
how did it work again
how do you oh there it is
use bathroom okay okay okay
and i'm gonna buy some stuff here
oh let's see what we got okay
oh
one blast of eco-friendly hiding
poisonous gas will get rid of those
pesky giant pesky giant centipedes
what where are centipedes here
it doesn't actually fly but if it did
how majestic would that be it's not a
problem since the imagination of a child
can turn any
ordinary object into a mythical creature
with a funny name what
what
sick of being dive-bombed by giant
stinging horses
yes totally hashtag relatable
having this handy spray around will give
you a bioengineered weapon
in the fight
there are times in the farmer's lab when
they know that their one pig is not just
some pig but the fun pig
charlotte's pig is the charming
triumphant morality tale
of a pig who teaches their owner that
sometimes you just need to look around
and smell the bacon
useful against danke mussy when the
caustic
renews in this jar are deployed those
creepy crawlers will be sent
packing what the [\h__\h] is going on why do
we need
um why do we need all that
crystal clear there's a cool camera that
would be nice
emergency emedic potion chugging this
adequately
tested medicine will give immediate
relief from the burning poison stings of
giant hornets
only
really bothered by hot hornets i never
heard of that
is this brazil oh my god that's
uh terrifying okay
okay so
my japanese viewers are saying in
hokkaido since it's so cold there
shouldn't be many
uh uh insects but oh well okay
okay so which snowboard do we want to
get the most expensive one obviously
apparently now i'm a snowboarder i would
i would honestly but i honestly would
think
cali would be the snowboarder not me but
okay i guess i'm gonna go for that
kelly should get one too one of the
better ones what is that by the way
purchase simmy gotcha
oh wait oh yeah kelly got down but you
still didn't go okay
go go go go go what is that uh some hot
drinks
all right no i don't want to do that on
you i want to do that on you
let's let's get them a hot drink they
got pizza in here too
oh oh vacuum burger
hell yeah getting that vague hot corn
sauce
[Music]
vending machine items received they're
not in my inventory
oh drink
nice mmm
i love that corn i love corn
so much i'm not even hungry right now so
i'll keep the vague burger for a little
bit later
it's getting dark oh no now i want to go
snowboarding right to the top
where are you going
oh she left that here oh
she got ramen
okay did you get the the gacha she's
getting the katja now
what do we get from the kata ah
oh the purchased semi capsule can be
found in
calliope's inventory open it up to see
which sim is inside
open oh oh
wait this is legit a castle came now
what the hell do i do with that bunny
gnome is always full of mischievous oh
my god complete your semi's collection
today
scotch oh my god the gotcha
let's get a snowboard for her and let us
know what a better skiers
for her as well
so she can be the perfect
the bestest skier around here all right
all right okay
okay and then we go back up and then we
ran to the top
and what am i doing are you sad
why is she sad shared sadness
seeing that someone cherishes is
suffering makes her sad
from a close sentiment towards someone
feeling about
wait but kelly isn't
seeing that someone kiana cherishes his
suffering makes her sad
eh because callie got gnomed
but kelly is right over there she
shouldn't be sad
why am i sad
kelly i need you to cheer me up
can you cheer me up brighten day kelly
would do that
100 accurate oh look at
look at that sad face
all around me
[Music]
corn soup it cannot be disappointing
it's freaking corn's up that's that's
no that's not that's not accurate quit
the game now okay this the stream is
over
i could never be disappointed by corn
soup that's just not
okay
oh well okay i'm happy again thank you
[Music]
all round up nothing beats that snugly
in the warmth uh
sim fields after oh okay a great
conversation always peps up the spirits
all right i'm only sad because of the
corn soup now let's go one more time
wait right right to the top with callie
charlie let's go wait kelly's sad now
seeing that someone kelly will be
cherishes is suffering makes her sad
what happened
someone from those but we don't cherish
anyone besides ourselves
[Laughter]
those don't know she's uh because she
saw me sad
it's the sad sadness loop she saw me sad
so
so she feels sad and then i feel sad
because i saw her sad what the hell is
that it's like an
endless oh my god
what's going on what's going
oh my god let's let's cheer her up do
you need a woohoo or something callie
try to cheer up let's go don't be sad
what the hell
what's so sweet so sweet what uh what an
adorable
relationship we have
is everyone happy now is everyone over
there [\h__\h]
now
what where's uh where's my where's my my
amazing snowboard
basic snowboard i bought the best
snowboard out there how is that basic
what the hell go snowboarding
and you wait a second
it's gonna get rid of the bad ones she's
just talking to herself now
okay set and go
let's go look skiing at night
that's that's amazing i want to do that
that must be actually quite beautiful
you're only snowboarding
okay that's freaking girl oh yeah oh
yeah wait what's with that i thought
that was a police guy no
and take a screenshot nice if cali in
the background
nice
yeah professional snowboarder
that's by the way one of those uh one of
those that's exactly what i crashed into
it looks 100 percent
like what i crashed into
[Music]
ano
that's exactly what i crashed into
but with like full speed
kiana is now officially skater boy
i love the skater boys she said to see
you later boy
she was i wasn't good enough for english
i want a superstar
[Music]
what's going on though it's okay if you
really didn't like that drink how about
you eat your freaking burger maybe
you'll feel happier then
throw away oh my god
oh oh oh the pizza girl
let's get another screenshot of cali too
wait a second
oh my god kelly
okay go kelly i know you can do it i
believe in you
i believe in you kelly
don't crash again
[Applause]
don't die kelly there we go
not
again it's supposed to be me
it's supposed to be me kelly
[Laughter]
[Music]
why am i laughing i should be like we're
simply worried about her
[Laughter]
oh my god it should be me
what's that oh wait i didn't see it but
apparently i got
hurt as well oh my god better than bruce
ouch kiana got hurt badly recently and
are feeling a bit sorry for themselves
so i guess uh the interesting thing is
when cali crashes
she gets back up right again and doesn't
give a [\h__\h] wait why is she sad now
we had a pretty tough day out and this
little skiing is not as easy as the
people on tv
hook it really isn't it really isn't but
apparently yeah now this is accurate i
i'm the one who actually really got hurt
for real i wish i didn't miss that one
but yeah
oh man ouch yeah
[Music]
oh kelly it's okay why is there someone
in school uniform this must be cold
where are you going go to lodging oh
she's going home because she's
wait can we wait for me i'm up there
up there wait i don't know don't
make build a snow pal it might it will
make you happy i'm sure of it
there we go
wow kelly wow she's hella good at this
juliana
let's help her out
cubes palm attack she's enjoying it
oh yay see i know what's best for cali
i'm coming kelly wait for me i'll help
you
i'll help you it's about you
[Music]
it's cute and so cute oh
oh it's getting in shape
nicer
will be a bunny please make it a bunny
out make it into a bunny please
oh pat pat oh my god they're not even
wearing gloves
that must be so cold is that it
that looks amazing good job she was so
she was she just slapped it and suddenly
it had a hat and a tie and everything on
that looks actually something like
callie would make yeah
and those cute hands ah
she's thrown away uh yeah um you know
what we i think we're gonna
go and have some hot pot nobody to go
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
she's still sad oh man we gotta
make some love later to cheer everyone
up
but it might be a bit painful because i
have uh an injury from skiing
very accurate hey what happened with the
hot pot
what happened there
sims always like giving up what they
were supposed to do she was like ah
there she was like
[Laughter]
yeah i don't think that's accurate what
do you mean of course it's accurate
this is so accurate actually
what what's what's wrong callie
hotbod get some hot fud eat hot pot she
really wants that hot pot kelly really
really wants that hot pot
there we go
oh looking yummy
you just when do you guys start eating
they're just so busy talking they don't
eat she's thinking about the hot pot
she wants to stop talking just eat the
hot pot
no you guys can't stop talking you can
eat the hot pot
look at all those lined up tasks
duh that almost looks like uh the soup
curry that kelly likes so much
wait with a fork
you're gonna eat that with a fork at
least use a spoon or something and since
it looks like a soup
shouldn't it be chopsticks though it
should be chopsticks
my dear friends
oh my god oh well enjoy your food it's
okay if you can't eat with chopsticks
that's okay did you just see that kiana
was thinking about
fast food she's i still have that wagyu
burger i hope it's
uh how long is that good for um
oh it doesn't have an expiration date
kind of suspicious but okay
select yourself to change to eat with
joysticks joysticks
what you mean chopsticks
well that's not possible is it
that doesn't look like it's possible all
right i gotta take a little shower or
bath i'm going to take a bath again
now for the hideout all those hot pots
i'm done i'm done i'm done
i'm done thank you that was yummy
you want to talk a bit more with her ah
wait actually no that was
not me uh cali is supposed to take the
bath actually
let's take out a bath with soaks
yes
yeah muscle relaxing silk because we did
some workout today
okay bye kiana shut up i gotta go take a
bath see you later
oh oh she was even stinky did you see
that stinky cloud
oh with a mask oh my cucumbers
there are they're not exactly on your
eyes but okay
she's so relaxed she's enjoying the
vacation
nice all right can i change it up by the
way i want to change it
x amount oh x minus the bonsai yes
x minute what do we say about this bunny
beautiful what do you say about it did
callie do a good job
that was her first time so don't be too
harsh
she likes it i think i i like anything
that kelly does so
yeah that's not a heart a big um
yeah it's not very difficult to
yeah yeah looks good okay enough
examination
it's already almost 2 a.m let's go to
sleep
but i have to i have to wait
how long uh until you're done with your
bath
kelly actually i'm not even that tired
both of us aren't that tired
oh she's done now all right
all right um just so you know
i'm just i'm just wait why don't you
want to sleep in the children's back
is sign right side bad to me
uh assigned left side bed to kelly
look at kelly's face hey
look at both of our faces
someone really has to make prettier sims
uh
what where why
i'm not gonna question what that is but
okay
um she's ready she's ready tickle
mercenary please believe
question mark you don't know how to
tickle her where am i supposed to tickle
her
cali anywhere
by the way we can become best friends
but that will not change our
relationship right we will still be able
to love each other
[Music]
and let's freaking go
let's celebrate our best friendship with
a little boohoo
us
[Music]
up
there goes the second night of our
[Music]
vacation
whoo
[Music]
freaking fireworks oh my god callie is
extremely energetic
okay doing the push-ups again
yeah oh now that everything has to be
cleaned healthy green tea oh
oh santa
i want more tea brew pot of
oh oh bored
[Music]
she's shaking i love how she's shaking
oh she's got such a nice ass
imaginary ocd
let's wear um let's wear your
your warm clothes
and get some breakfast uh surf brunch
pancakes oh yeah i know how to make
pancakes
wait what what first of all why did you
not change
first of all
there you go and then drink
oh hi callie where the hell did you go
you should also change why do i not do
that automatically
let me know
grab a drink and i'll be um
serving that brunch
oh that's my burger
let's throw it away uh
wait where is that trash can whatever
whatever are you enjoying your green tea
is not lovely waking up to a fresh
hot green tea actually um when we when
we arrived in our
uh ryokan in our hotel room cali
started uh off by making tea for both of
us
yeah yeah she made tea for both of us
[Music]
learn the recipe for spaghetti and
strawberry cake yummy nice
oh you get that fire phoenix
you hot ass phoenix
gotta support myself you know she's
still super excited about that burger
that that yeah really good must have
been a really good burger
we should throw that away by the way
clean up
oh are the pancakes ready
come on kelly come on quicker
so that we can eat together oh man i'll
be done
i'll be done eating when she comes here
and now she's cleaning up something else
damn it i wanted to eat together
oh well you gotta watch some tv okay you
watch
netflix while kelly's in your pancakes
what should we do today we should go
well on the on the first day we did
skiing and then on the second day uh we
kind of did onsen
so i guess that's what we're going to do
today
what's up what's up let's go to the
onsen today
what do you think about that county hell
yeah i want to go to the onsen every day
i love the onsen
freaking loved the ones and i could
spend every day in there i
could soak in those hot waters for for
hours and hours and hours i just loved
it
so much i wish i would never have to
wait why the hell she sounds
i'm not enough
[Music]
all right all right when you're done
eating then we'll go there
where is it by the way where is it
what is that
oh that's the bunny slope ah
where's the onsen also you can go
climbing too
oh look at those beautiful uh
wait is that
you can go sightseeing here oh you can
go hiking
hike back to sloppy hike back to slow
pace
hiking how about we go hiking today
let's go hiking
well how does that work i said hike back
but i want to hike over there
let's see it's what's she doing with the
what what are you are you bringing your
pancakes along
pancakes
she's going with pancakes kelly you
should have left the pancakes at home
kelly kelly
she really loves those pancakes that i
made for her huh
[Music]
wait a second
actually yeah wait a second get
information festival
see festival schedule one second
uh all right oh wait actually akira
should do that see festival schedule
and you just you know wait here
let's see what we got we have a snow
festival here
oh oh what
there are numerous festivals on in mount
komodevi to celebrate the festival light
is held in december matchy neighborhood
every other friday the festival of snow
was held in the yukimatsu neighborhood
every other saturday
and the festival of youth is held in the
vagabonding road every other sunday well
what day is it
thursday so tomorrow is one and then oh
yeah we gotta
i want to visit all those okay tomorrow
we can go to the festival
friday saturday sunday oh
okay okay
check daily wildlife report okay
where's she going no no no no no no no
what the what is about life doing here
there are no relents for danger as well
live in the era today but it never hurts
to be prepared with
wind there can be dangerous wildlife
honey respectful
oh we can go while climbing in practice
climbing session
one time climb oh
i don't want to go climbing
yeah let's just do some climbing
let's go sounds like fun i want to go
climbing too
let's see how cali climbs that rock
you should you should probably wear some
gloves oh my god
oh you can what equip and remove
climbing gear oh
oh oh kiara's a natural talent as you
can see
which rock do you grab next oh
i'm doing a good job you're both doing
quite good
kelly's just gotta level up strong
cali is doing all those push-ups so she
should really have some muscles there
come on it's a bit more just go over
there you're going down again oh
oh oh i fell down
oh callie fell down oh kelly fell down
again
okay wait kelly's
kelly practice doesn't make perfect oh
no callie that's not the way to go
kelly made it in the end but maybe more
groundwork needed in the future
seeing that someone cherishes the
suffering
[Music]
of
friendly hmm friendly
how do we cheer him up i don't want to
see her sad
no don't complain about your problem
your problem is that kelly is sad we're
not going to complain about that damn it
how about funny
tell a funny story and uh
tell a joke about vampires
oh i want to keep on climbing apparently
oh no come down kiana
oh she's saying the push-up skin i'm
surprised she's so bad at climbing
cali has earned 208 on her day off what
is she doing to earn that money
i guess that that makes sense i guess i
guess it does make sense
uh yeah that's the that's the influencer
lifestyle stocks
going high on her day off
not even doing anything come on quicker
kiana we need to cheer
callie up actually no you're the only
one that's sad
callie is pretty much over it by now hey
could you stop climbing i told you to
stop climbing
ouch
finally
gloomy compliment well actually i can't
do any of this because i'm so sad
try to flirt okay i guess i guess kelly
has to do it cheering up
yeah platter oh yeah with those glasses
that's those are the cali glasses you
see that try to cheer up i guess it's
the other way around after all
money
[Music]
oh cute isn't that cute guys
isn't that purity oh
this
where is the onsen was it the onsen
okay let's see where it is ah
[Music]
yuki
but i saw an awesome in the
what do you not see in austin where the
hell is johnson
[Music]
i saw you can totally go to an onsen
propose ah did you guys see the
proposing option oh there it is where is
sute funny stephanie
stephanie stephanie onsen bathhouse
i see let's go there
stephanie
who is stephanie
[Music]
hello hello hello
have arrived at the onsen
so they are wearing uh
swimsuits i have heard that apparently
escape okay but generally i guess the
sims go in there with a swimsuit but
it's
wait isn't it way too hot wouldn't that
be way too freaking hot
okay um first of all let's let's take it
easy first
tony has a ukulele
[Laughter]
hell yeah they're so confident oh look
at all those
people showering now now you now you
guys because
if you guys would go to an onsen you
know it's a gender
um separated so normally
so now this is the only only time you
will ever get a look at
the inside of the of the female area
who wait what what the hell
is he changing now oh there we go here
look at our cute swimsuits
oops oops why are you wearing swimsuits
oh my god don't join us i don't want
no i'm gonna feel embarrassed and shy
oh well let's just ignore them let's
just do our thing don't get too close
lady
no you wake up no
i wanna can we like cuddle in the onsen
can we cuddle in here
um i can blow her kiss in the onsen oh
yeah there's two
two girls flirting in the onsen
deep conversation
i don't like it i'm just gonna continue
flirting
it's going to continue oh cali is really
really flirty flash crazy eyes
impatiently pester make a flickering
flirtatious joke what is impressively
pestering
oh it has like a little uh uh demon
thingy next to it
what happens
identified the goldfish a new type is
there a fish in here
all right well we gotta try you know we
gotta try
nanikono
wait wait what's going on what
are they leaving oh yeah everyone's
leaving for us
could you please leave you too leave
leave wait why is only the guy staying
nasty
[Music]
why is only the guy staying could you
please leave
kelly wait there's still a freaking guy
in here
oh my god that's a
it's kind of hot
oh my god i'm scared to press the play
button
you're really going for it
you
what the hell
oh my god
what
[Music]
yeah what the hell
it's finally leaving what are you
surprised about
what's going on
apparently it is customary to cleanse
once oh [\h__\h] we didn't do that
perform cali is embarrassed because you
have one food
see oh privacy invaded well of course he
seems so like having someone walking on
them well i mean he just didn't leave he
just stayed there
what about you same here
dirty springs natural water is supposed
to look a little more clean than this oh
yeah
probably we made it dirty yeah
he um he seems uh disturbed but
i mean you can't blame us
foreign
oh god we made it really dirty
[Music]
water is dirty thanks to us well welcome
in our dirty waters welcome
oh
[Music]
really um embarrassed though
um
[Music]
should i clean the onsen
[Laughter]
let me try to clean the onsen she wanted
to get something
from the vending machine little while
what are you doing she's taking a shower
now
singing shower oh yeah that beats
lurking now
[Music]
as an apology i would like to clean the
onsen for
ah everyone has to leave with ah there
we go it's clean now that was easy
all right no no no no you're gonna take
a shower take a steamy shower
there we go uh yep that is status just
like cali go right back into the onsen
that is exactly what callie would do
that's nice i think i'll join again as
well
she's she wants to pee please do me a
favor and go to the toilet
do it and you can come back later that's
okay
round two
[Music]
i mean there's probably
some more more places where we could you
know
nope
[Laughter]
who's singing
it's me yesterday at the end of my super
chat reading i'm like oh hey
kiara looking good um
i'm going to do a skinny dip
to this mask hey
hello oh hi uh don't don't look at me
too much okay
oh what what is that reaction what is
that excuse me do you have a problem
with me getting naked in here
kelly you should get naked too
come on skinny dip come on
this is just make everyone go away
[Music]
not even
can you stop staring at me nah
please please
is he gonna sit in between us
[Music]
no he's like super shocked you've seen
me before can you stop looking at me
okay that's just rude
that's just rude
and tell him to [\h__\h] off salt
cow you gotta go naked too
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's enjoying it are you looking you
can look at me it's okay that's a it's
just an onsen
yeah i am but the guy i'm not happy with
that why is he not leaving
go away so why is callie not skinny
dipping
why does she just not do it
see what's happening she's just too
shocked
she won't do it
i'll do it
kelly is too shocked oh she's super
relaxed too
go away how long do you want to look at
me
no don't talk with him ew okay i've
given up
i've given up i was too creepy
oh oh people are shocked
yeah i'm just checking out the vending
machine naked yep um
apparently suddenly i have so much
confidence in my naked body that i don't
give a [\h__\h] anymore
and i'm what am i eating is that a hot
dog
he's he's still following me
bye-bye go away go away yes go home oh
i'm sitting like at the reception
imagine entering an onsen and then
the first thing you say is a naked
phoenix eating a hot dog
at the reception
[Laughter]
hotel
meanwhile it's just like that that
phoenix is just unbelievable
she's just unbelievable
where is this onsen in real life
mountain komodevi
look it up i'm sure you can find it
what are you doing now what are you
doing now
browse vending machine oh what's what's
it this time what do you want to get
this time hentai tori
shino though
oh why are you going to get yourself a
drink she's always unhappy about the
drinks that she gets though i hope you
get the right one now
what is that drink what is that
chilled sage green teal that must be
good
she's still naked
chat okay let's go chat with kelly yeah
what is kelly doing she's getting out
there now okay
now he's taking a shower i want to get
back into the onsen though
oh kelly's also kelly's gonna do sit ups
in the snow
hardcore kelly
okay and then go back in after you sit
ups go back in there what
do i have to shower again even though i
already went showering
can i just enter
oh shh i don't even have to get naked
because i'm already naked
what's what's what what what is it see
what's happening
kelly just freaking join me skull go
and join me well
now and skinny dip let's go yeah
now that's what i like to see could you
sit a bit closer to me
kelly is taking your safety distance
that's actually quite realistic kelly
kellya taking a little bit of space from
me
to to have that distance you know it's
pretty accurate
can't you come closer then what that's
coconut tail
[Music]
you can't move in while you're in here
unfortunately
it's just chilling so far apart
well
there's so many options right now but i
just
i i just wanna i just wanna
do this now that we're alone now let's
why are we wearing a rope
but we're going to get naked in a second
again don't worry guys i don't i don't
know why we're
in cloves right now at least give us our
bathing swimsuits
what the hell okay you weren't sure
you're going to shower no i wanted to
woohoo
now that that's that ladies and saying
what kelly
you know how to use an onsen county
oh my god i think we have to reset uh
oopsie
dammit that was the wrong one i have to
reset something here something's wrong
here very wrong okay
now relax in hot springs together
there we go now it's okay again
okay okay okay okay
let's see if everyone will leave this oh
my god there's another dude here
are they gonna leave
emotionally mindful finding emotional
finding emotional control is a journey
of taking the first step but to gain
true emotional control requires more
slow time
through various thoughtful activities
that's some deep stuff man that is some
deep stuff
wow chad stop watching yeah
anyone
i can't do it because i fell asleep
oh was i that tired no i wasn't
also weird kelly is hungry
okay come on one more time come on do it
the men staying in okay there's a lady
too but
[Music]
oh my god why is this happening again
no
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
no no oh he's leaving he's leaving okay
okay
well it's morning now it's 6 a.m we
stayed all night we were just uh
woohooing in the onsen
100 accurate
she's just laughing oh she's she's
appreciating what she's seeing
yes she's nodding
oh she's very curious oh i mean
you can look that's okay i don't mind as
long as you're female i don't mind
she approved it she approves
oh i found him wait what the hell how
are we doing that
oh oh it's a bit dirty again here
i i don't know how that happened again
um
oh
suddenly we're gone
[Laughter]
well it's uh sorry for um
i'm gonna clean it again okay i'm gonna
clean it again and then we're gonna go
home because we're pretty tired okay
[Music]
what we're not allowed to come back
that's that's impossible we will we will
definitely come back
kelly kelly are you okay you're
exhausted
she looks happy she's like yeah
yeah that was that was a good onsen day
why are you going to the vending machine
go home
she's also like
pure relaxation bliss
the natural cleansing minerals of the
hot springs weren't the only things
heating up the water
it was us it was a hot phoenix and uh a
certain
a certain death
they're so apprentice
quick quick go to bed it's uh 9 am
it's 9 00 am
is this why you actually couldn't stream
that day
[Music]
no comment no comments sleeping time
it's in the middle of the day but yeah
wait isn't it
wait today is the festival so we can
sleep on to the festival because it's a
i think it's a little bit later anyway
okay let's get that sleep quickly we
stayed up way too long
i'm imo nagaku
has earned 200 on her day off nice one
so when's the festival when's the
festival
she's feeling cold she needs to pee and
she wants to eat well that's relatable
well are they not going to tell us about
the festival when when did i say it
happens again on friday but what time is
it's almost 8 pm
eating peanut butter and jelly sandwich
i don't really like that
i don't really like peanut butter and
jelly
[Music]
but okay you do you we're both gonna eat
something
well kelly is actually gonna cook
something wow
effort it'll get yanking
mom tonight
[Music]
erogel it's a hentai game
that's not true you can do many many
many other things in this game it's just
i'm just showing you a specific part of
the game that's very important
oh gosh where is the
freaking matsuri
where is it
where is the matsuri
where is the where is the mozzarella
what it must be in the city
there's like so so
so many little spots here
let's eat first but i have a feeling
like it's already so late
she made a blt sandwich i freaking love
blt sandwiches and now i'm just eating
my
lame peanut butter and jelly sandwich
damn it
okay what are we doing today chat with
kiana oh you want to eat something
let's just get that little kissy
oh please just go to the toilet
oh cam has earned 64. on her day off wow
okay okay uh
i i wanna i wanna check out the thing
where's the where's the
where's the what did it say what did it
say again
where the festival is
was it semba machi the first one there
was like free
free festivals the um one in uh
yuki machi or something like that but
that was the last one
i mean let's go here
how do i go there oh oh i guess i can't
maybe i just go to the park
actually i have a feeling maybe it's
down here
do i get there oh there's a cut okay oh
let's go here
okay okay okay okay
let's check it out
[Music]
oh that's pretty with the sand with
oh that's so that's so japanese
again what's this here
exercise oh that's i don't see a
that's so japanese oh my god
i love it i want to live here
but where's the festival
wait a second there must be oh
there must be like a like uh one of
those bulletin boards
that i've seen around it
i can't find one now
ah samba much neighborhood i don't which
one did i go now
the other one
damn it
[Music]
i have party okay let's go to the park
can we woohoo at the festival that is
the question though
oh is it over already
water no only
i don't see her first of all
normally doesn't doesn't the game give
you the notification if a festival is
starting
um
[Music]
it's in the shrine shrine where did i
see a shrine
wow i have a uh what's it called again
uh a thing
it's a bamboo forest what the hell scare
ha no
what that is so cool
eh i want to live here
this is like the best the the best
expansion pack for sims ever
and where the hell uh where the hell is
the festival though i don't see anything
that looks like a festival are we really
correct here
that is so interesting there's so many
many little hidden hidden things here
oh you can plant something here that's
cute
um that cape is where amma lives
i want to walk through the for this
bamboo forest together
wait here's a okay let's uh let's go
here together
hike around whoo
[Music]
i could attempt where should we go
dammit but i actually wanted to check
something else here
hike to the mountain shrine with
and why am i feeling so bad because i
need to pee oh damn it wait come back
come back come back
hike to the mountain nope see oops oops
hi to the mountain shrine
with kiana
kelly's that not enough rap only woohoo
do you think callie is sad because she
needs to rap some more
actually it says nothing like it doesn't
say why she's sad what the hell
she's just randomly sad could you
could you um join your wife please
i mean we're not actually officially we
need to marry
we should marry okay are you ready now
all right let's go now
my skull are you not feeling cold by the
way
i guess not there's no no snow here you
call that hiking down
call that hiking
while they both wait can we take a
little break wait what the hell
those things you like um japanese people
make these things to wish for
uh like with like tissues and stuff to
wish for
good weather for another day
wait what come back here
hey girls come back girls girls
hold up let's just continue hiking
is that they're like they're
jellyfish or something they're running
back
there's still a fireflies too they got
distracted by this fireflies
[Music]
this is where you should be going
make-a-wish
make-a-wish we can collect them too
oh state of tranquility the serenity of
the area fills you up
to complete tranquility hell yeah
kiara has had a peaceful encounter
laughs
[Music]
uh can i wish for making this snot
happen
[Music]
that didn't happen that did not happen
ah the friendly first spirit seems happy
with callie's wish a strange tinge
ting tinge of magical energy seeps into
cali filling her with positive aura
four spirits are so sweet
it's it's too late
it's too late
but did you collect one no ah
let's let's try to cheer her up a little
bit
when she's getting all these positive
smoothies and uber
i'm just i just peed myself what the
hell
oh yeah yeah oh she's okay she's fine
again
i'm gonna i'm gonna
[Music]
and there was a toilet right there i
wanted to use it but then i don't know
there's like sparkly mushrooms hmm
what's that wild pear tree oh
what's that flowers
you can climb here too
okay what are we doing here by the way
we should
uh continue continue hiking we actually
wanted to go
all the way up there one second uh
i don't i don't care how dirty i am we
gotta finish our hike
niko
okay we start again i'm i'm only dirty
because of the hiking you know
cause we're hiking up the mountain what
do you expect
oh my god
yeah you did not really just write that
comment
stance up wait why because what
stencil because what wait i don't
understand that one
extension when does that come from
well we're we're having a great time
anyway
stench what is stench i don't get that i
don't understand that
strong smell ah oh
oh ah what's
what's happening tell the story about
hiking steve steve
merbanogoosh lawanza callie kelly
suddenly wants to tell me a story
what else just continue
wow wow
dad ahoy
she's going to tell me about those
territories and wait why the hell are we
free i wanted one too
hey i want one too lifestyle in progress
callie has taken her first step towards
unlocking a lifestyle
[Music]
oh isn't that amazing
dirty kiara and cali walking up to the
temple
teddy what are you crying for these are
literally the ones that
what a nice screenshot if only i wasn't
that freaking stinky and dirty that
would have been such a nice screenshot
god damn it
we're almost there i love this this is
an amazing my amazing expansion pack
oh wow it's so pretty
and i hear i don't know if you guys hear
it um but there's like uh
grills and stuff making making noises
like
callie has seen things yeah but she's
the one who reaps
them why is she crying
oh hannah
what is she trying to cheer me up
did she tell me a duck joke again so i
do joke again
nothing in jamie can i clean myself up
in the in the river maybe
god damn it i'm still embarrassed about
what happened
[Music]
dear lord this is kelly
i'm glad that kelly is annoying phil
hangs out with me though
kelly has encountered some fireflies
again why is it
always kelly wait what about me
i i see them too
kelly had a peaceful encounter with
fireflies well
second time i want to see them too what
the hell
thank you for this for the membership
thank you
god damn it goddammit oh are we going up
here
oh i like how they're actually like
really
like uh checking out everything
automatically i don't even have to tell
them
oh they keep on moving keep on moving
are you exhausted from those stairs i
would be too
oh my god uh wait a second what if i
i could at least change my clothes no
um outfits
that should at least fix the dirt or
maybe not because i'm
my my hygiene is like at zero
i guess that doesn't fix it
when is she gonna change though
the way she looks oh my god
[Laughter]
oh man
oh man i feel so sorry for myself
but you didn't check out that thing you
didn't wait
wait a second you are going to do it
somehow but you went on oh now you're
going up okay okay
it's morning time
oh they're going to shout and listen for
an echo
[Music]
wait kelly
i thought the sandwich was um spoiled
but no that's just my
stinky cloud
it's all good so good are you gonna do
it too though you're not gonna do it
wait are we done hiking
why did she just you should do that too
shoot around
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey crap
[Music]
oh my god that's so funny
okay i think the cave told me to go back
home and
wait what well they're chatting there
oya funcil penaru gesapa
thank you for accepting me the way i am
no matter how dirty i am vacation
there's one day left no i didn't i
didn't check out any
i didn't check on any any festivals
okay you know what uh going home going
home
quick quick i gotta take a shower really
quickly
[Music]
you're not woohoo in the cave apparently
i can't i wish i could
i wish i could okay uh it's time for
a shower never
shower i'll be muscle
take a thoughtful shower take a semi
shower
and kelly can do whatever she's playing
chess okey-dokey uh actually cali could
you
where's the next festival like i missed
the one maybe i should be there earlier
okay it's 6 am though so you're gonna be
fine
but i have to sleep at some point not
tired right now but
i guess i could take a nap so that we're
ready for
when the festival actually happens
okay and oh my god i'm hungry too
no i gotta eat something
fire breath uh uh eat breakfast eggs and
toast
okay okay i might be tired
later but no more stencils yes yes no
more no more clean joel
clean chalk oh
yeah we did it i'm happy again
let's join her in bed let's just say
quietly join her peacefully
okay
i'm clean again i'm not stinky anymore
good morning callie i'm dreaming of a
ghost
oh do what you got to do callie do what
you got to do
[Music]
what are you thinking about carol
i see i don't know what you're thinking
about
sometimes you know it's it's really hard
to understand
what the deaf's apprentice is thinking
it's very difficult to imagine
do you have to watch yeah
obviously this is what the game is about
watching what your sims are doing
what okay it's a good time uh
it's noon and cali is fully awake
where is the festival on saturday at on
that can't talk anymore
[Music]
so wait it was the first one is supposed
to be here but
it wasn't there where do i find that
information
i need to go actually okay go back there
i'm
sure there's a yeah there we go there's
a oh
someone just stumbled let's see a
festival schedule
where's the difference between dad and
dad
okay while i'm sleeping cali is gonna
check out what's up in the city
we only have one day left that happened
so fast
i thought that was still really early
but the fast uh the
vacation is already ending
how is that possible
okay so festival vlad so we missed that
one
but there's a festival of snow is held
in the yukiman
neighborhood where is that is that where
we are
from 3 p.m to 12 a.m
okay starting soon and then the festival
of youth is
i think we'll extend our vacation for
one day so we can go to the festival of
youth as well
okay yukimatsu uh
3pm to 12 a.m yuki matsuri
maybe yeah yeah okay maybe it only tells
me yeah
if i uh do the that thing that i just
did
get festival snow outfit snow time
check out the sculptures yeah see that's
something we couldn't do in hokkaido
because they they canceled it
they have in in sapporo every year
in february they have their snow
festival with all those snow sculptures
but we couldn't do it but they have it
in freaking stems
that's amazing but we can't go right now
because it didn't start again okay 3pm
you know what kelly you just wait here
for now
maybe you can i don't know um
build another snow pal while we're
waiting for the festival to start and
kiara is still sleeping
i couldn't wake up by now though and
i'll go to the toilet
ah this is fun
this is fun i love this
ah and then we'll join we'll join what
cali is doing we'll
join her and wait together we're gonna
have a snowball fight
yeah let's do it how did we didn't how
did we not do that yet
now let's have a snowball five
i'm very focused perfect time to have a
snowball fight
who's gonna win which
that one looks different
that's a cute one that's so cute
so creative i never thought of giving a
snowman hair by giving them
uh sticks on the head that's cute
wow okay let's fight
children out of the way move away
it's time for a fight let's go you
missed
sasuka i'm really bad at like ball games
in school nobody wanted me in their team
like in dodge ball and stuff because i
just sucked
this oh it started that was quick
oh my god they keep on dying over there
that's a really boring snowball fight
that you girls are having there
that's a really boring snowball fight is
that all you got
you can't you missed again
[Music]
let's go i can't go
it's happening in this neighborhood ah
so that's why i can go because it's
happening here
oh where is it oh here this one
oh there's a dinosaur when there's a
pagoda i guess that's what you call it
and the mascot but this is like more
made out of snow rather than ice and and
they're usually actually made out of ice
so is that is that
and that's an actual object in the game
though even without the ice
is that it
is
is that it it's much bigger in sapporo
who the hell is that do the mountain
move
what what's the mountain move
show me mask show me what you got
oh wait i can't see
lame
[Music]
yeah sure let's do it upload it on
instagram with hashtag
mountain community ew nice one nice one
all right make a snow angel
but what about them what about the
what about the snow sculptures is that
it okay or the food
actually we're not hungry right now
let's let's get uh let's get a drink
oh yakisoba i love yakisoba ikayaki is
not really my thing because the ika
is a squid i don't like ika
um oh but cali definitely wants the
the niggeri oh yes go get that niggity
i'm just making a snow angel i love it
you can't play on it because it's a snow
sculpture
can i do anything with these sculptures
now
oh they're doing a firework
wow wow can we watch it
hey she's playing with it i guess i'm
just and now i could play with it
[Music]
i'm just chilling uh where can i buy
those
snow clothes though out here i guess
ah that one purchase festival snow
outfit 300
300 is for real what does that look like
it better be from gucci
[Music]
better look like
well that's not gucci that's that ain't
gucci
that's h m
also what are those what are those
that's too cold what are those
[Music]
well i guess uh cali is gonna get the
same outfit i mean we got the money
wait wait you already purchased it did i
purchase it for both of us
hell yeah what does that even do
you're going to talk to what are you
doing dancing
dancing you're just randomly going to
dance over there
that's skill and quiet oh yeah got those
moves
oh we're dancing together hey
hey hey hey yeah get low get low drop it
chiata drop it
hey hey hey
wow wow awkward
place to dance
i want to get some food too order food
actually
is busting some moves she has unlocked
some new dance moves and can now show
off the arm charm dance move on the
dance floor
as your skill increases from dancing to
his blue blah blah blah
yeah hi dude
i do wait why am i standing sadness
why is she sad she's not sad
listen to japanese folk what does that
sound like
i'll hear it i hear a freaking uh
again
wow
wow more more is that it it's over
why are you saying this to me now go
away
[Music]
have you guys eaten yakisoba before it's
so yummy
oh he's eating dango with chopsticks hey
wait why is he eating with chopsticks
and i'm not about
[Music]
plain wood chips
see that's that's the special thing
about uh
that snow festival in
in sapporo they lined up the snow
sculptures
you wanted to see that it says orange
dinosaur
um
that's so pretty oh
see i got to see something there's so
many snow angels there
i got to see something that i wasn't
able to see
on our trip well that's nice
kelly could you cheer me up please
heartfelt compliment
uh ask to star case
i'm gonna feel bad against
want to check out the beautiful
sculptures while we're laying in the
snow hell yeah let's do it
yeah in the middle of the yep yep yeah
people are going to like it when you're
like right there
[Music]
but can i like do anything like i can't
interact with the sculptures
unfortunately i can't look at them
but do they get anything from that
deep connection oh now it's gone
illuminated by stars
well oh of them are having a great time
oh look at that
hiking homies you from our homey moon
nothing like hanging out with a friend
that hiked the epic trails of the
mountains together
oh we're hiking
[Music]
plan to wrap bacon around everything
[Laughter]
[Music]
yep
maybe that's a good way
to end our vacation you know
oh there's fireworks right now it's a
perfect time it's the perfect time right
it's now or never propose to your hiking
homie doing oh my god
oh my god it's so cute
oh my god
congratulations thank you guys i we got
um what's it called again uh not married
uh
uh engaged engaged
we're finally engaged
i feel like it should be the other way
around okay
[Laughter]
look at that face the face of happiness
that is the face of happiness
that that is the face of happiness
100 accurate recreation
of my trip with cali yes
just yes yes yes
[Music]
snow globe
what the hell you're disturbing our
happiness
it's just me and her elope immediately
no no no we want to plant it nicely
oh oh
profess whisper seductively
harris cheek
kiss
[Music]
kelly is getting really stinky though
excuse me why are you talking to that
stranger again we just got
yes oh my god
focus on me for one second please
he just
whisper sweet how romantic
[Music]
oh my god that is so adorable i love it
oh my god
[Music]
oh they still love birds
you're stinky but that's okay i love you
anyway no matter how stinky you are
okay i guess um wait are we supposed to
stay one more night it
didn't say there's one day left but like
are we are we able to stay one more
night or how does it work
well
[Music]
be enticing oh oh my god they just can't
stop
i think we should probably go home for
some privacy that
can't stop all right
food vendor noise where's the food
vendor right where is she
where the hell is food better i don't
see them
there wow look at those two lovelies
you just can't stop
look at the fireworks for god's sake
they're over again it's too late again
[Music]
yes
are we there okay well
i mean we just got engaged so we gotta
finish it
[Music]
flour
i love how they always get so fired up
about it
they gave up why sims this this game
sometimes
the sims just randomly give up their
their tasks
for no reason makes no sense they gave
up again
again
all right there we go now now it will
happen
where it is wait close your eyes this is
uh
private private content nobody is
allowed to look at this
elena don't look wait i'm doing it with
my
oh i'm oh no i changed out of my clothes
afterwards i thought i was gonna do it
in my
my cute winter clothes well well well
that's another private con yes yes very
private that's why i'm gonna private
this video
after uh yeah after the stream
this is an archived stream everyone
nope it's a private and i have to
private the video
it's too private yep exclusive content
oh my god kelly she got really dirty
from that
good dirty gallery oh
still feeling those good memories from
frolicking in the snow together on a
memorable location
these sims are engaged to be wet save
the dead yeah everyone save the date
save it it's going to take a bath mmm
a nice bath you deserve it cali
yes get that nice hot bath
well well well everyone i think that is
a good
um moment to stop the uh today's
playthrough
i think the next time until the next
time i'm gonna
be asking you guys to make um
me and the other whole live english
girls at sims
so and then me and kelly will get
married so yeah we'll be making sims and
then
uh i will make i will the next sim
stream will be
me introducing uh the whole time
i record the whole stream
oh my god wow uh
oh that means i got some
recordings from the from the
bedroom huh oh well anyway
um yeah never forget uh so it's precious
memories but those are also private so
yeah that's it's all private so yeah
next time
uh we got we got makeovers and
uh we're gonna marry and we might adopt
some children called gura ahmed ina
they will be our children's children's
children they will isn't that isn't that
titty isn't that wholesome
um
[Music]
oh
yeah we're going to be the parents going
to be mom and dad
i thought i hope you guys had some fun
we're going to be reading super chats um
and talking and just hanging out so if
you want to say you're welcome to stay
but for the gaming part it's over now
they both went to bed
ah happiness
ah there we go cancel and end vacation
yeah that was a nice vacation
okay
okey-dokey
moving over here one second i gotta i
gotta
uh save and exit the game
oh go go go go that was fun i hope you
guys had fun
we did a lot of a lot of woohooing
i was oh my god what is that
all right let's check twitter and
there's like uh what is oh my god what
is that
r18 first time
whole life what the hell is that
oh my god no someone sent me on twitter
what the hell is that
i'm not gonna check that out now no no
no
no no that is a bit um
if it has a casing a bit embarrassing
i thought let me let me uh do some stuff
here real quick
oh yeah everyone is welcome to stay
to hang out and read uh some super chats
shouldn't take too much time today
because yesterday we caught up with
everything
also i need to practice tomorrow guys
tomorrow i have a unarchived karaoke
stream so you all better come
it's on archive so
uh very precious
yeah i'm going to sing mostly english
songs i think
[Music]
i got a bunch of songs in mind already
i want to sing like ariana and julie
allen
and uh what else do i want to sing i
definitely want to sing lily island
though i hope i don't forget
i also want to sing avril lavigne again
and paramore yeah yeah yeah
and what else did i add to my list
ah oh maybe maybe a
bulletproof from la vu and also i want
to sing hey
from outcast i want to sing fall out boy
oh yeah fall out boy we're going to sing
that and
ah click kelly maybe some more kelly
clarkson and maybe uh i want to sing
britney spears toxic
and maybe some other songs yeah
so look forward to that it's gonna be
it's gonna be a fun karaoke stream again
oh when i want to see bruno mars i i put
uh a bruno mars song into my playlist so
i probably will be singing one or two
bruno mars songs
we're going to sing a lot tomorrow
hashtag
yeah boy has a song called the phoenix
not sure if i'm gonna sing that one but
yeah we will see
yes awesome everyone don't forget heart
challenger
heart challenger is coming out soon
in a few days very very soon
mm-hmm
coming out on valentine's day
whoa
exciting hmm
oh you changed your name you got a title
finally
when i wrote that ray of sun that gives
me energy proposal super chat it wasn't
just me talking to you but it can also
be
you talking towards your friends isn't
that nice also how are you
ah asking me how
i am again this time it's you i know
last time
was someone else now it's your how sweet
you guys are
you guys are um just trying to
you know appreciate me that's very sweet
thank you
thank you i'm i'm doing
fine yeah i'm doing quite well
just one problem is i i lost my my phone
charging cable and pisses me off
you know what's weird i feel like
i feel like
i accidentally i feel like i
accidentally took
one of cali's phone charging cables home
with me
and i'm missing my own charging cable
though
i feel like i feel like we switched
phone charging cables
well i i have a charging cable that
looks like for some kind of iphone or
something
but i don't it doesn't fit my iphone
so i don't know where that would come
from
ah the old switcheroo yeah i don't know
man
i have a i have a charging cable that's
definitely not mine
no no no no cable
[Music]
i don't know actually i have a i have a
uh a smartphone and i guess i gotta buy
a cable
after the stream because i really can't
find it i looked everywhere
but i don't know which one that is but i
look up what what kind of cable
mine is using
usbc also works with nintendo switch oh
callie secretly switched it so she can
see you again
maybe she didn't have to do that i have
to meet her anyway because i got
chocolate for her
and i have the her youtube um
100k uh thingy she didn't have to do
that
i was gonna come to her place anyway
also to watch shrek there's so many
reasons to see her right now more than
one
that was really not necessary
[Music]
she wanted to see you sooner ah what no
i'm just gonna buy a new one
all right uh pudding thank you skye
duncan truth club
jennifer koslowski penguin
if you were a transformer you'd be
optimus fine
smug also do you like star wars because
yoda won for me
also did you know lobster's taste of
their feet
what i don't get the last one
thank
there's more but wait there's more i
would take you to the movie schedule but
they don't allow snacks
i'm no mathematician but i'm pretty good
with numbers telling you
what give me yours and watch what i can
do with it
[Laughter]
stupid
i don't think you are the best candidate
for a wife i think in whole ibn ina is
the best candidate for
wife potential is also very close like a
galaxy distance
well few troop clever duncan
hey my name is microsoft can i crash at
you please
if you wear words on the page you'd be a
fine print lady
i love to do thanksgiving don't hate on
him just because he googled his pickup
lines
have you ever mixed hot chocolate with
french vanilla coffee
one of the best combos no i haven't
because i don't like
coffee at all
mister seems for chia looks like an
animatronic that's supposed to stand in
the corner of the usual room to keep
watching with an unblinking beautiful
gaze
what jeffy kitten
hope you okay with me working at two
places along with being a loyalty
employee i'm starting a new job this
week wish me luck oh
good luck i mean i did say
i did say you guys are not allowed to
have a second job but okay i guess
good luck with that but kfb is priority
number one job okay
pivot printing
questions
[Music]
thanks for keeping me entertained while
i was bedridden and overseas with some
hard to pronounce neurological condition
what
no neurological so happy to see
another sim stream after your legendary
first one it was my favorite stream just
beating your chest streams oh
what really wait you like the chest
stream that much too
well i'm glad to hear that you have
really good taste let me tell you that
your two favorite streams being sims 4
and my chess stream
he got a really good taste my friend
what's everyone else's favorite stream i
wonder
what what i mean that's probably hard to
remember
out of so many other streams what's
everyone's favorite stream
of mine
this one is collab the first riser was
great oh thank you
this one honestly
one you guys can't just can't remember
the other streams pick without collab
and marine corner
mario kart chocolate making yeah that
was fun
first a manga stream ah the one work
where i was just really really bad
the mario ones are funny animal crossing
boomer karaoke and then a collab subaru
could have a way out oh
minecraft streams photo talk
happy to hear that super mario sunshine
first fire live stream thank you
first mario kart blumenthal defy emblem
ah that was a good one
for all fire emblem oh oh thank you guys
a way out super chat's dreams are fun
they are all talk to you anyways thank
you first fall guys stream oh
that makes me happy because that one was
um
after a long long night of no sleep
mmm that was when everything started
collab oh second fast watch long oh then
you might be happy because we got
another watch along next week with bloom
the first debut oh thank you i'm frog
that's not a stream but okay i'll take
it
simple and clean karaoke stream that was
just one song in the color okay stream
but okay
i guess you really like that cover oh
next streams are pretty awesome
thank you all of them are really good i
couldn't pick a favorite
thank you guys chocolate making was
really cool yeah it was
egg is broken hardest too sliver.io
thanks guys thank you guys so many
different ones
oh thank you i'm glad someone
appreciates my
my fairy tale readings my german fairy
tale readings thank you
scuffed minecraft which one they're all
scuffed
papers please it's not my channel but
okay i'll take it
good that's japanese lessons ah that was
a cute one yeah the collabs
the collabs with kuda are all really
adorable
german lesson ah the originally members
only one
oh nice neck crack
oh sh let me drink something no
mask
that minecraft rta tried it
oh baking in minecraft oh
all right i think i understand i
understand
i'm glad that there's so many different
ones that you guys enjoy
thank you guys thank you minecraft never
auntie
you mean the one where i never reached
the never
black glove and streams hand review is a
special one it is it is definitely
so anyway let's continue uh
thank you also for pinky as a fellow
being of the fire element
it lightens up my evenings when i'm able
to watch live and start my morning off
well when i can't
sorry i can't watch live at four five
a.m i like sleep too much me too
i get you i fall asleep to extend uplay
two area songs the other version
i see
[Music]
oh there's a poem you will accept me a
poem
lights fading it's cold it's numb feet
heavy you can't even run
then a fire is bright as the sun you see
a dazzling phoenix you feel your life
just begun
with eyes that are sparkling like the
stars a voice
so melodious like a spell or charms she
gave a smile so sweet it made your heart
flutter
with tired eyes you beautiful is all you
could utter
oh last year here is go
how cave beets were born
[Music]
thank you
i suppose you're not fully back but
because you didn't say you're back but
hey
me gamer it's been a while
why did the duck fall over on the
sidewalk he tripped on look on a quack
oh
what he tripped on a quack what
what does that mean
thank you it's nice reading your name
nice reading the name from people who
are gone for a while
hope you're doing well quack instead of
crack
it tripped on a crack
had a similar one someone sent a similar
one like that
our boy thank you i think that's a red
one is it
i think i remembered you sending a red
one i'm just gonna suppose that that's
the one
mom dad why do i hear noises
i don't know what you're talking about
actually let me tell you let me tell you
about
um i think it's bees and then flowers or
something like that
so oh
the bees the bees fly around
and then they see a pretty flower and
then they sit on the flower
and then i'm not sure what they do
i think they suck something out of the
flower
and then they bring it back to where
they originally came from
and then they make the honey
i think that's how it works
not sure actually
[Laughter]
thanks sancho i am smarter now you're
welcome
you are welcome i hope everyone learned
something from that
yes yes yes this is how children are
made
yes
thank you our boy for the super
challenge for the generous donation
don't worry about the noises don't worry
just close your eyes listen to some
music or something
else never change keanu thank you
i mean
it seems you just
you just have to do it you know you
can't play
sims without doing the woohoo
it's just not possible
i bet people play sims of their real
life crushes and do that
yeah i'm not the only one
i'm not the only one
no no she's got a point yes i do yes i
do thanks for understanding me
patrick chen ice crown duncan ridiculous
duncan
alfredo asalli dancing
snowboarding is good for your core and
thighs and butt
which one is more difficult i wonder i
feel i feel like skiing
gives you more stability um
than snowboarding what do you guys say
i feel like probably skiing is easier
i would say i would suppose
snowboarding was harder for me
snowboarding makes it cooler though
that is true it's just something about
snowboarders
they just look so dope they just look so
cuckly
i don't know why why do snowboarders
look so much cooler
and then scares
why snowboarding is easier for me what
did you try both
on why
i think it's proud because it reminds me
of um
skateboarding and just skateboarders are
also freaking dope
there's dance probably yeah it probably
just looks
[Music]
um
surfing also makes people look so cool
so freaking cool
surfing i want to learn how to do
surfing i want to learn how to serve
surfing
i will learn okay my goal for the future
i don't know if i can do it in 2021
because of
obvious reasons i don't even know if i
can get to the ocean anytime this year
but
i i will try oh i think it should be
working if i get to the ocean this year
i will take a surfing class
i will learn it i always wanted to do
stuff like that
surfing phoenix hell yeah
surfing is much harder than skiing or
snowboarding
well [\h__\h] yeah i guess it needs a lot of
yeah and a lot of strength especially
like if you fall down once and then need
to get back up again and stuff
i guess it can be real like really
really exhausting yeah
i don't really have any core strength i
don't have any strength at all
my arms are so freaking weak in my legs
too
like when i go buy groceries
when i buy groceries often
my arms are just done for the rest of
the day
time to hit the gym
i'll think about it
chicken legs
foreign
ring fit ring fit time i do have the
game but
uh yeah i gotta play it again
gotta use it again damn it
[Music]
oh well
thank you
okay
[Music]
apparently in japan there is
16 someone in a japanese super chat
wrote that
there is 16 different uh
varieties of hornets
16 and 14 of those
inhabit uh hokkaido
maybe that's why they
had all those anti-hornet sprays
in that vending machine in the game but
i never heard of that
i think though in winter it should be
fun but i guess
outside of winter the hornets are
probably partying everywhere
[Music]
so
i think in my whole life i think i've
only seen like
a hornet uh once
and that was in a freaking bus
and that that that freaked out everyone
yeah but that was the only time
um thankfully
yeah and that was uh that was pretty ya
bye
yeah in a bus but yeah in in australia
there's really nothing much dangerous in
us
that that's why australia
that's why i'm not from australia but
from australia because
australia is much safer to live in
than australia
australia got all those all those uh
dangerous dangerous animals oh my god
like in australia australia
like uh there's there's not a single
like dangerous spider there's not a
single poisonous spider that exists in
australia
also there's like no
no no snakes i've never seen a snake i
mean okay if you go to the zoo
okay but besides that nothing
absolutely nothing in australia
also yeah no no weird poisonous other
insects
yeah australia has murder spiders yeah
oh my god
yeah okay continuing
yeah since this is 100 accurate i assume
these were the vending machines you saw
there i don't know if i trusted burger
from these machines
yeah but actually like japanese vending
machines are
the food in there i mean i've never
i don't i don't think i've i think i've
gotten like an apple pie or something
like that before from a japanese vending
machine that was all right
they do have burgers and stuff in there
too sometimes
i think it's probably just about the
quality
a bit lower quality than what you get in
the convenience store
it's probably not even that bad if
you're really desperate for food
then it's probably pretty good
happy
[Music]
was watching the stream especially the
part where
me and kelly were woohooing in the onsen
and honestly
honestly that is a little bit
embarrassing
the moment when when i saw that he's in
the chat
it was already too late i couldn't i
couldn't paddle back anymore it was
already too late
ah
i wonder what he thinks of me now
he saw all of it he saw it all
that was pretty yeah bye
you already knew you were bottom left
well but
like i think today um
it was very um direct yeah
comment a start is thank you soon ace
crown turkish and it's a mystery duncan
fleming flights of fantasy thank you
and el canal we would love to tell you
thank you
[Music]
oh lord i will also stay for that scene
two girls who can't control themselves
in a mixed bath just don't mind me i
came to relax
oh that one dude that stayed there the
whole time and just stared at
us from the other side of the bath
oh my freaking god like i feel like the
sims are
um like um
uh like uh programmed to leave the bath
when other sims are trying to woohoo in
it
but that one he just he just stayed he
just stayed in there
the whole time from beginning to end
he just stared at us oh my freaking god
oh my god well i'm glad you enjoyed it
too ellis
wow thank you so much for watching i'm
glad you liked it
but next time give us some privacy
please
[Laughter]
oh i'm glad everyone enjoyed so much
okay shadow thank you style thank you
murph laser thanks
from star strider thank you and high
had every opportunity also kiara when
people call her bottom left
turkey soon it's a mystery
lft
i was beginning to question if it's
possible to make an accurate trip but
after that accident there is no doubt
in my mind that this is 100 accurate
no it's not it's not i tried to make it
as accurate as possible but
unfortunately some things have happened
and i definitely did not pee myself
during the trip
i definitely didn't
jose
extremely tired that i don't so i don't
think i'll be able to watch the rest but
here's
the two cents i owe you plus a teeny bit
extra
thanks for the streamers always stands i
hope you have a wonderful
rest of your day well now you owe me one
cent again
okay i guess not not necessarily
i guess not it's okay you are now free
of um
depth thank you flamex oh yeah
thank you for the red super chat i'm
glad you enjoyed the stream thank you
for staying up as long as you could
thank you i appreciate your support very
much
thank you see you soon again hopefully
danny scope thank you fire truck tanker
and jose duncan
gt kfb thank you for the pinky
congratulations on the engagement glory
to takamori yay
we got engaged i will try my best to
make a really really beautiful wedding
hmm but who do we invite we ah
maybe we don't really have any friends
maybe we should get
our children amigura and ina before
we marry so it's just that we have like
some guests there oh okay oh i guess we
could make gemma and emma as well yeah
wow that we would have to add a lot of
people there um
but the difficult thing in sims is i
don't know if it's
still that difficult but i remember it
being very difficult like um
adding sims to the world you play in
without adding them to your family and
then trying to find them
in the world and then like you know
becoming friends with them
because if they're not in the same
household then it can be quite difficult
but we'll figure it out but amigura and
ina can live with us
i guess
oh yeah yeah we're gonna make clara oh
eventually yeah we're gonna make
clara clara modi
it's from into a house you know yeah i
guess so
i guess so hey
you want me to make cuckoo papa in the
game too
i think it's probably better if we don't
i don't i don't want you know i don't
want papa to be
running around the house
when there's me and callie naked it's
just kind of awkward
maybe he can live in a different house
not in the same house uh that finger
what yeah for the wedding yeah we do
need my papa there
to walk me down the aisle yeah
um true
yeah i guess i do have i don't need my
papa there
all right i'll see what i can do
and maybe we can get papa
to look like um black rock shooter
hatsune miku
maybe someone can recreate that yeah
yuki saw me mama
as well
mamaloni can be the priest
that is perfect that is perfect
mama looney being the priest
lonely pronounces us to wife and wife
i now pronounce the wife and wife now
kiss so that i can draw more fan art of
you
amazing amazing
[Music]
getting married is the best birthday
present i could have asked for blessed
stream
thank you for the gift angel i will
treasure this moment of totally faithful
content nice holy moon ending thank you
the homie moon is over yeah
it was really nice
really really enjoyable thank you for
watching it
outcast 777 ocl martinez
justinius
[Music]
sorry that i haven't seen a super chat
in a while don't worry about it whenever
i send one of these i just start
overthinking everything thank you for
being you
oh thank you don't no need to overthink
it anything is fine really
thank you so much for the support trevor
g duncan
that was quite impressive
congratulations on your engagement
thank you having the confidence to
confess
today the day after you peed yourself on
your hiking date is truly inspirational
takamodi truly has the strongest bond
thank you for this very accurate visual
description of your whole new
honey honeymoon you're welcome even
though i was listening while working i
could tell how bottom left and
yeah also congratulations
congratulations on getting engaged
thank you thank you for the membership
welcome
lucas vancouver uncle duncan just as you
became a mother today i became the
father
of a baby catfish again for the last few
days but this time
also so colored shrimp
and why the heck sounds kelly like a man
in game change it no
i will not i refuse i love city thank
you
thank engagement how are you do you have
enough tea to drink yes i do
feel free to take a break thank you
switching up cables as normal
oh thank you thank you
[Music]
how you doing today thank you for
blessing our eyes with this 100 accurate
trip recreation streams have been a lot
of fun and spicy hope you had some food
and that you have a nice day
congratulations on the wedding
thank you so much ah
today oh yeah i only had a croissant for
breakfast
and yeah later later i'll hopefully get
some dinner as well
thank you dusty for worrying about me
i'm all good though thank you so much
and yes that was
that was almost accurate unfortunately
as i said it couldn't be 100 accurate
because i did
not i repeat myself again
i have not peed myself on my vacation
with kelly to hokkaido i repeat
i have not paid myself
today's sims 4 theme has unfortunately
not been
100 accurate okay okay
thank you for your um attention
thank you anyway
thank you dusty also found thank you for
oh what
thank you for red super chat phone theme
mwah sorry for stealing your phone in my
defense you look like some kind of rich
idol
and not a broke smuggle sold your phone
on ebay here is your fair share could
have been more if you brought the pro
version in the first place anyways best
wishes from germany
i [\h__\h] got
oh my god
oh my god i mean that's definitely not
that guy but that's so funny because
when did i last when did i tell that
story
i love how i love how this person just
picks up a story that i told a while ago
of me having my stone fall my stone
fallen my stone's fallen
my phone's stolen
[Laughter]
don't steal my stone
oh my god i love that thank you foam
thief no i actually i really hope that
you're not the actual person but
also i don't know what that means
sparkle i've never heard that before is
that something you germans say
sparkle never heard of it before
thank you for the super chat very funny
i love it
and next time i guess i'll bring my my
pro
my huawei p30 pro so that you can steal
that one and give me back even more
even more money thank you very much
wow stone fallen repeat stone falling
patrick chen dan kishan gdp thank you
for the pinky
thank you for today's stream you blessed
us always some funds for the engagement
party thank you
glory to takamuni you know engagement
party happened in bed
so it didn't cost anything
thank you raven salman questions so much
did you just come out of the oven
because you're one hot chicken
oh i mean phoenix yeah you saved
yourself there
thank you tanya castro
i'd like to say the best dreams are the
ones with you in it
you're the sole reason i wound up in the
victory beside you the best
thank you that's so sweet
smooth flirt
i passed out during the stream how could
you
how could you fall asleep from what i
was told it must have been my brain's
defensive
mechanisms kicking in but i was also
informed that you got engaged to cali
yes i did
the card i sent can work for even
engagement wedding that's true yeah
thank you thank you i will give the card
to cali then and tell her that we got
engaged
thank you so much
missed the stream but made it in time
for super chat thank you
thank you for coming you should watch
the archive later on it was very funny
very very funny
[Music]
thank you that's it guys thank you for
the memberships also
thank you everyone for watching and i'll
see you guys tomorrow
in the unarchived karaoke stream i'll
start practicing some songs now
so that i won't mess up to bats tomorrow
night sushima
i'll be singing a lot of a lot of
english songs yeah it's over
yeah i'm done with the super chats
thank you guys for watching today i had
a lot of fun
i want to play um some more sims
privately as well
but um i have this curse that when i
play sims
like i got really excited and really
hyped up to play sims sometimes then i
play it for one or two days and then i
don't play it again for
like one or two years
have you figured out the network problem
yet my previous job is an underground
fridge
is in an underground fridge which is off
the grid and we just buy a 4g
mobile router and stuck it on the roof
and still got decent speed
oh uh yeah i think i
i talked to um like
a guy who who like works for the
provider the internet provider that i
have in australia
i talked to him and i asked him like i
got that graphic
where it said like um
i got um
i looked at that graphic and it said
like certain providers
uh um in my area had like really really
good speed so i asked that dude
if that would be true and he said yeah
those two that have like really high
speed
those are mobile uh
like providers i guess i don't know it's
not
it's like a different kind of connection
i don't understand or the difference is
but
apparently it's a different kind of
connection and he said that it wouldn't
it
it might be fast but it's not very
stable
so yeah but but maybe yeah maybe i just
get both of them
so that i i mainly use the fast one
which apparently is not very stable
but when that one uh like fails then i
might still be able to
use the other one
but then again having two
network providers i don't know it just
seems like
kind of like a pricey thing oh well i
might do it i i will
i will definitely have to find a
solution because i don't trust the
current connection that i have in
australia
i don't trust it enough to be stable
enough to stream like minecraft and
stuff
cause that means download speed as well
is your last super chat reading still
private for some reason it should be
back soon youtube needs
so much time
when you cut out like one second out of
a stream
it still needs like 24 hours to process
it it's
unbelievable it needs so much time
so yeah it will be back probably soon
uh during today it should be back oh wow
next is dan kishan
and did i miss anything else
so slow
yeah anyway thank you soon everyone for
watching today
uh no no i didn't get bonked or anything
we just did it just in case you know
[Music]
so anyway i'll see you guys tomorrow
skydiving thank you for the recreation
stream you're welcome thank you for
watching
patrick said thank you i'll see you all
tomorrow
[Music]
i have been late but finally i have
hatched over these few
months i have grown attached to utensils
i will gladly be a member of the kfp
something i am proud of
afrida thank you thank you
thank you i had fun guys i hope you did
too
today
i feel like i show i showed you guys a a
bit of a yeah by side of myself once
again i'm i'm sorry about that
thank you soon
sorry guys sorry
i can't wait to i saw i saw you guys
making like bingo
forms did you guys get bingo
did anyone get the bingo i saw you guys
making those bingo things again
kiana sims 4 bingo did you get bingo
i hate you how dare you bingo with my
streams
oh my god unbelievable you're just
playing with me now you're just playing
with me
which one you're gonna show me you're
gonna show me the crossed out bingo
send it to me on twitter
thank you thank you and safai kitten
i've been going three times what
it's on reddit already yeah i saw it
already like a few days ago actually
people
when people heard that i'm doing a sims
4 stream again they already created a
bingo form like days ago
oh my god so well prepared
ah alright guys
thank you so much i'll see you tomorrow
danger and in german we say
bye bye hashtag
see ya
[Music]
do
foreign