[Music]
foreign
yeah
wait wait wait wait wait wait I think my
screen
this is so this is the most
[Music]
thrilling stream
I've ever done okay okay this
okay okay okay
welcome everybody
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't help it
thank you
foreign
but Flamingo beautiful beautiful
nice to meet you
[Music]
I am Phoenix not a chicken
I'm an owl not a kiwi hey everybody
we're gonna say not a towel
all right
no I am I am one okay
she admits it okay okay and then the
money go in home
that's a weird introduction and hi and
I'm a people not a turkey I'm probably
Iranian from Whole Life Indonesia
generation two hi
thanks for making so much money for me
you're welcome
I'm uh
yeah
[Applause]
[Laughter]
duck manager is
you can't help it it is what it is so
we're gonna play pommel party which is
basically like Mario party but on PC and
for more people than four so let's have
fun together
happy
Nanny
wait yeah
I hope the settings are okay me too
I'm just praying you know
it's the first time for everybody yes
all right yeah
oh
my God
he's wearing the chicken head
oh treasure we have to go here
I think so
today is
what is this uh weapons weapons
oh
my God I'm like covering the whole Mario
Party jump
the sparkle shows you what's the closest
route I think
it is
my first time my first time
I landed on a good field
foreign
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
big birds
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
you can claim the lands
what am I
um
jump action why is action Orange
I think it's the color that you are
um
okay
okay but how do you how do we steal
I don't know
[Music]
we'll find out
just do it
on the bottom middle middle probably
thank you
[Laughter]
come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my gosh
be careful she's got a gun why do you
need a gun I don't know
it's a very violent Mario Party
um
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
thank you still not sure what the keys
are for but I guess it's like a
some kind of yes
no yes
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
the praise bomb is the space key okay
okay
bomb avoid destruction to Triumph okay
okay okay
to understand yeah
where am I not understandable
[Music]
well who am I oh
yeah
I thought it was chicken
meat tattoo
[Music]
it always makes you in the middle
restart
again
[Music]
where's the strategy okay the strategy
is stay alive
yeah I couldn't go there
hey I want to play too yeah me too yeah
foreign
[Music]
another chance another chance
okay down to how many rounds
oh good question
[Music]
that's why
not there not there
[Music]
three rounds until the timer is over
wow
[Music]
oh my God
I'm shocked shocked
yeah forever
[Music]
I open
good night
what's up
[Music]
um
no no no
oh
oh keyboard or controller keyboard I
don't know
[Music]
press try m i don't trust this sweet
okay yeah that's the closest if it has
the oh you like to take a red on my
Cannon to a nearby Square Circle yes yes
I feel like it would get you closer but
isn't it 40 keys I wouldn't have enough
Keys ten ten Keys it says ten Keys yeah
treasure is 40. last time so maybe you
can still get some in the mini game but
maybe I can
what she thinking
maybe I can't okay I decline
oh rejected
[Laughter]
is it even worth it going towards the
treasure I feel some someone will reach
it before me but
oh well no am I going to the same you
know what I will take the boat to see
where it goes
[Music]
wait it's a cannon not a boat what the
hell oh yeah
both of them
[Laughter]
memorize
everything
moved to dodge hey what's that mean ah
ah
memorize the arrows shown each round and
moved to dodge okay like it's a memory
game
but okay
okay
um what
[Music]
um
which one am I it's so small
[Laughter]
[Music]
rocket
man what the [\h__\h]
okay
lucky like human it's so confusing
no I was like did you ever find out
where you were I found out after I
exploded
I was I didn't move maybe it wasn't me
maybe it wasn't me
blood
why am I why am I thinking
board event
yeah now you can't cross some of these
paths anymore I think hello hello what's
this what what's this what events
oh yeah
the blood water is toxic
is it poisonous poison oh yeah I
only have one anyways don't don't take
HP no no yeah
okay let's not [\h__\h] it up this time it's
a random game
I don't know which one is I don't know
there's beef be fun okay
Rhythm games
just because I don't know which button
is which
[Laughter]
it's a chance for me okay okay
[Music]
wait which one am I on purple I think
one of these oh okay I see it yes I am
uh okay easy easy
I will get much more difficult I guess
uh
okay
let's go okay okay
[Music]
okay okay okay
[Applause]
well imaginary Rhythm yeah there is a
Miss in your house
oh
okay
[Music]
is it also like the better the timing is
the more points you get so
[Laughter]
I miss you
am I last again no way I don't know
at the
time
yeah
I thought I lost all of my points but I
have six
oh my gosh
I need key I need key I need
get those keys get them
me oh my God
you can it says use item what's that for
like how to blow to blow the person
right next to you up
that's it yeah
hey you have a bump right I mean shoes
like it's I think maybe it was scroll
what happened I don't know oh
it was hot to blow up you're choosing
right now maybe scroll or
yeah yeah it shows you
maybe go for the strongest person
doesn't matter
oh hi
oh hi oh hi oh
everybody yeah first time first time
first time
oh
yeah beautiful nice landing
okay oh look at the blood sorry
raspberry I didn't
press Q okay
[Laughter]
dog is there a dog in the room
toy now
wait can I reach the key maybe if I get
a good roll
what the [\h__\h]
ing yes I would have had enough kids
all these kind of party games hate me
I cannot see no
okay then I go here
next time I guess okay okay
it looks like worms
use your tanks turrets to destroy the
terrain ah yeah yeah it's like right
okay I don't understand
don't mess it up okay perfect I
understand okay
[Applause]
I don't know
what uh I don't understand how to shoot
again
just click click for shooting no and
then click what is Click
a quick Mouse oh I guess hmm
oh I can't you can't land in the water I
suppose I I don't understand
[Music]
I can't even shoot I don't know what to
choose
I will have a big comeback surely Sunday
bye thank you sweetness
wow wow wow wow please
congratulations I guess
bite them
oh
you have a teleportation wait how can
you where can you go with that I don't
know
I wanna open with this person
sniffing it present what is it good
thing right has to be a good thing I
don't know
choose the next mini game
I think you already chose now yeah but
like the thing is I couldn't even like
what's that oh
you got a magic wand
Magic Stick oh it's empty because
somebody already died
you have so many
yeah it does but no teleportation
um
everything
she won't use it yet
okay okay
bless you
thank you
my town sorry
oh but you can get yeah
property that's key
yeah
can I get my no no no Kiara area but
healing okay that's fine
you chose this game we're helicopters no
I didn't choose I don't know how to
oh
okay by shooting down the most players
okay okay yeah boy
oh boy
oh it's so retro no no no no
oh
bye oh we respond yeah we respond
I'm orange guys where am I oh it was
blue
mermaid black
pepper is strong
[Music]
okay
I share four let's go how the heck are
you holding rain is stronger yeah
you're good at this what is that an
eggplant it's like an eggplant egg crab
maybe
eggplant very dangerous vegetable yes
dangerous eggplant
I need to play this game more often
today so that'll get better at it yeah
Nana you've played this before right no
literally it's my first time
you saw me struggling with language and
resolution earlier and everything
you're just you're just good yeah I
guess
you don't want to hurt anybody
this way yeah I haven't had the chance
to use anything
I don't have any items sadly except
teleportation I think
oh
boxing
okay
big big number please okay
Yeah medium uh our art review map uh-huh
uh what how many more steps
I wasn't counting or what does it say
you either have five four or five
okay even if I go down I have to go yeah
down is like you have to go the other
way I guess so then I go this way but I
don't know where I land yeah
[Music]
the last person standing wins oh my God
it will not be me I don't know
today
yeah make sure you know where you are
[Music]
maybe I'm shooting but I just don't see
it
I lost track of myself
[Music]
oh
I get it now I get it
I believe
it's my first time it's the most peace
if I take if I use an item I can still
roll can I uh I think yes unless it
specifies otherwise
okay maybe I'll open present
ah it can be something good or bad it
says yeah yeah
um
teleport with who ah
oh
yeah somebody you can get the treasure
I'm gonna cry
[Music]
um
oh wait four steps one two three four I
hated that we have to actually count
what's this field again the the white uh
skull is just losing something not
getting attacked no no no no no it's um
good
I don't believe you I don't believe you
I'm gonna go to the action one I think
it just changes the water maybe ah
I'm So Far Away what does this do magnet
yeah
oh
did you take
almost all of my remaining
how many did you take
oh my god do you see how many Louis has
Lou has 83 keys
I didn't get trophy yeah
[Music]
wait how many shoot how many did I have
left
yeah that's the thing like I never know
I don't I
believe in the game or luck I I believe
in nothing like I thought this call was
bad but then like the guy was like I
would be your master
[Music]
my keys it didn't hurt too bad
oh my God I will pick up those keys when
I pass by
oh oh oh
what are you gonna use huh I wanna add
some mooses
there's so many
careful dark magic oh [\h__\h]
it stays there this thing happened if I
go towards the bunny probably
nothing good I assume maybe it eats you
alive
it kills everything in its path
apparently
yummy oh
well would you look at where I am
oh
aqua oh she's gone
okay let's go
it's sunny
what
the [\h__\h] I'm just on the side now
yeah
I see but he didn't do anything
the bunny's still a baby I think
it has to get bigger I don't I don't
know I literally I don't know I was like
wait what a bunny
what's the bunny do a bunny bunny I'm
just dead yeah oh but my HP is not three
zero yet
what happens if you get zero HP nice why
am I still on the signs
huh
indicated animals what the what does
that mean Crown Tigers writing penis
wait how do you count uh just um your
action button whatever that is
okay okay
it looks right
it's not working
huh
wait no it's showing it's not showing
yet but you just
yeah do you have to put in the actual
number or
no you can't like you know like you're
like
cars passing and then you I don't know
with what key your action key space
space okay I think we got coins but why
did I get zero
oh
what I don't know how to [\h__\h] to count
what the [\h__\h]
I can't
I got points
what what am I doing
I'm count a single time yeah
apparently it was space bar yeah
ah
why did I get so if I was just okay
maybe because like it was like as close
as you get to the number that it
actually is you get more points even for
zero you get some points I guess I
accept
I accept
what the [\h__\h] man
I don't have enough
[Music]
use item use the item
cool do you want to teleport you can
switch with somebody eh
oh why you make me suffer even more
can I do this honestly I don't care
where I am I guess because I couldn't
buy a 20 test anyway
bye bye
that's fine oh is that better for her
where is it treasure where's the
treasure box yeah why did you want to
change with me because I can't get it
anyways okay
I see I see I see
um
five five
a bunny no bunny Bunny's just there
what mysterious what is mysterious bunny
mysterious bunny mysterious bunny
nobody knows oh maybe I just collects
all the keys on the path and then brings
it back to you also says it does
something evil hmm
we'll find out when it's too late
you're on the bunny I will protect you
bunny
oh it's so great you want baby I have no
money
but baby bunny
safer to go here bunny I would like to
open it but I have two keys yeah
[Applause]
not baby
good baby it's like Tetris yeah
okay
[Music]
space okay okay okay interesting game
check where you are
oh
okay oh
[Music]
oh okay
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I think they become faster
finish
[Music]
come on come on come on come on
okay okay
[Laughter]
oh
yeah
no please no let me finish to that
thank you
oh my god
wow oh my God
yummy yummy
I was thinking of umai
eggplant evil evil eggplant evil
teleport with who
yes
and she's gonna get all those keys on
the ground as well
[Music]
okay
no movement in the graveyard oh
she can't move
I mean I mean you can't move anymore
after teleporting
oh so somebody could help
go for it
and then the next person may be
teleports with you
oh my God
no one
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
because like she already was like
offered right
but maybe it does count I really don't
know yeah yeah I don't want to give uh
you can't move but can you maybe buy
something maybe oh well I guess we'll
never find out yes we'll never find out
so true
well I hope the rabbit's nice to me I'm
still mama
I need more items so
present no no no please
thank you
I need weapons okay drunk yes
um
[Music]
okay after three rounds up
yeah three rounds
okay this is fun this will be fun
sorry okay oh
that's nice okay nice
gently let's yeah let's chill you know
no yeah
foreign
[Music]
they just do it on their own I don't
even have to do anything I don't
understand why how do you have so much
control yeah exactly Pro Gamer I'm only
good I'm only good at a few games in
life and this was one of them
yeah
I wonder what that does
oh teleportation
arcade arcade okay okay
um
[Applause]
like
nine
only
yes yes
because the laser was going through her
like on the sides
small
yes
still win the man yeah
I'm still here
I'm oh maybe close but no money
um
oh no where are you gonna go you have no
money over now
where does he save money
foreign
oh what's this playing the turn
yeah I gotta use your items
there's someone right next to you
oh I think everybody you pass by You're
Gonna Hurt No no no no no no no no no oh
yeah protect protect her protect yes
Bob
what does it do maybe she also just
turns into it no okay
okay
can you blow up the cactus let's see
[Laughter]
now
we know okay
stay forever
it's unpredictable
okay okay
knock out punch punch okay
WSU okay
okay okay my character already has a
crown though
it's not me though
oh we always go after oh no
wow wait what you're not oh
yeah something like that
[Music]
you have to punch me
oh that was a lot of points man that was
a lot of points
yeah no
no no no no
[Applause]
I think that's away for me let's go
give me more keys not just six keysu
come back
yay oh maybe I should have used an item
oh well I need keys yeah nice hmm
I am meditating this pattern
I'm immune this
yes really completely
um
[Music]
[Applause]
you have to redeem yourself
I should have missed me again because
it's only defeat look where the laser
goes look where the laser goes yeah
[Laughter]
oh my God
[\h__\h]
huh
duck noise
[Applause]
that was evil she even quit for you can
I be honest
I meant to go back oh
[Applause]
[Music]
do it
she loves pain
orange so what
if I'm Orange it's closer to red
logically you should shoot the one who's
number one
oh my God
don't trust the cute face
um
the cute face evil mind
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
she you you tried to shoot her twice so
yeah one time miss one time mistake
they didn't shoot her the second time I
also meant to not take her
how about you just don't shoot them
but still alive
today is
no no no no why now no no no okay
bye now
[Music]
so much yeah
I have yeah
okay game time baby Bullet barrage
you only have green lives the plan was
about as long as when I'm playing with
the most lives after two minutes wins
okay dodge dodge it okay jump a d okay
okay life is always three I don't think
so I I'm not my not good at this me
neither
that's so
funny okay
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
too fast
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay there was a double
[Applause]
[Music]
she's gonna kill me she's going to kill
me
do it
no more
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I don't know
announcements
[Laughter]
oh I got a beehive
is it a beehive if that was a grenade
wait I have
this if you blow up two people
yeah I can't yeah
all right
[Applause]
okay
for my safety
to JP
it was so convenient
oh no I'm still in the reach look at her
Twitches
body dancing
present
[Laughter]
what present
I'm not safe
what
what teleportation where oh
treasure
oh my God
nice good choice
thank you
now only Louis left for a treasure it's
okay
it's okay
my graveyard homie port
um wait uh let me see
Subaru body still having seizures yeah
[Laughter]
why
is
Subaru senpai
[Music]
come on
uh my homie in the graveyard
oh
maybe there is no Auto there
um
[Music]
why laughing you're funny oh God oh God
so scary
scary stay behind me
endo
This is the End world thingy
item okay
in this third person shoot third person
should okay
okay
I don't know if I can remember so much
okay if you die once I guess it's over
I I don't know
um
I am good at first person shooter Maybe
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
ER come back oh it's so hard to aim with
controllers
[Music]
is that heal
if I die what was that oh um
nobody know what
where
I can't where am I
wear a different difference
okay okay
no heels every time I move I also move
up and up and down
I can only do this
well now we're all over here
oh my gosh
yes
oh my god oh [\h__\h] how much oh one more
minute one more minute
[Music]
oh it doesn't reach
razor purple item purple
please
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
I want laser
these are adorable
yes yes yes let's go yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
one to finish
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
English
[Music]
the laser yeah
oh no it takes no skill
the ways are so cringe
okay
yeah my gosh okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
which one did we choose
wow I still have no Piada area me too I
have no raining area
area JP takeover
JP takeover yeah this land this JP land
right it belongs to JP yeah where where
do I drop this can I oh
Out Of Reach
maybe not okay so I don't know
be hi everyone
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah
but maybe after me mume will try to
switch with me and then you don't have
it what about you Dana now what if she
lies you don't know
[Music]
I have to risk it I think I have to
raise kids
teleport Festival
and they're probably gonna switch with
me now
are you gonna teleport
okay okay but maybe Nina has
teleportation I don't think I have
I don't have money I don't I don't have
enough money anyway you're you don't
have to worry about me I mean please
turn if I'm not first then somebody can
still change with me
okay
if close won't the bees hurt me too
is that not how the game works but the
thing is like why would you drop it on
me instead of other people because like
oh
[Laughter]
that's a good point she says while using
violence
by violence
maybe the president
it doesn't support you to Oh but you
only have 11 Keys yeah
[Music]
um
looks like you have to make a
of the face from the picture but you
went with the car one
okay
oh
bad decision
yeah not so much
[Music]
the evil bunny
gets smashed oh cute oh this reminds me
game or movie Mario
maybe controller is best for this wow
controller control is also so difficult
[Laughter]
I think I got it now now
but I got it too late
as long as I don't finish last oh
oh
[Laughter]
hey mother where the [\h__\h] uh
[Music]
where's the goal literally I don't know
this is the second time I'm passing here
I guess there's more than one oh I guess
whoever is the furthest
one more
you have troubles of the controls but
you're so good
uh I I don't know where the exit is
there's no exit
no exit now
down
okay okay
come back what are they all behind us I
don't know anything for you I love it
yeah
that was closely now
why am I still
drive maybe extra points for extra left
I don't know
[Applause]
[Music]
that means I go first huh right oh my
God I think so no way
oh my God
oh yeah I just need a lot of points
please
oh yes yeah I mean a lot of uh yeah
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
to oh wow
Japanese team
this is
can I change my chat yes
okay
what yeah
okay okay okay
uh thank you foreign
we've been playing for one hour
and okay
okay speed speeds go go dinner wow okay
we have to hurry a little bit okay okay
because Hai Shin uh
okay
did I accidentally do something no right
[Laughter]
we are today
wait a next story
[Music]
what's my turn I clicked out for a
second okay
this way
Everybody Run yeah we have ten turns
left so we don't have enough coins okay
in my town what town oh let's go
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
I might not have enough money
scary I know a bunny
whenever he moves I just
[Applause]
foreign and I see it's a cookie
okay
make the curry space for picking up item
space okay space space button okay okay
[Music]
okay okay
why is it wrong
because you don't have it in your hand
anymore already I think oh so it's not
that it's wrong or something yeah since
you already dropped it anyway
banana peel okay okay okay
[Music]
should we take them from where from here
anywhere anywhere okay okay
but it says
I think I am
oh yeah
why okay
I think I did it
too
I guess we'll see yes
[Music]
okay maybe this box
watermelon
what the [\h__\h]
okay you have to gather everything and
then put into the pot
everything at the same yeah yeah we
carry one thing that's what I thought
too
what
um
okay
oh yeah
Reyna figured it out
too late I mean not too late I guess I
won okay
okay
huh oh action
oh my God two two HP I'm safe
[Music]
anime
[Applause]
yes important don't forget your HP HP
mode
[Music]
present
s
that's a lot of damage
but you don't have to shoot Louis she's
already dying she's not shooting she's
uh
[Applause]
before she dies we're gonna make sure
okay I hate I hate mummy Junkie
now moment has so much we have to take
it from her mommy
[Music]
some Indonesian then
oh ah rip what
rest in peace
I think maybe this position is better
yeah maybe it is better you can go ah no
you can't go up really I don't know you
have to go around ah
um
for now for now
last time I think it was like for two
rounds underwater rabbits
oh slippers oh
yeah okay
a platform space for jump
let's go let's go don't push
jump time
after that
just gotta wait for them to fall off I
don't like the camera right here yeah me
neither I can't see
oh someone fell as
cute music I know yeah yes
like a Christmas
okay I'm losing this one
yeah okay they're struggling goodbye my
friends
I'm not last
behind me
I love you oh
[Music]
okay no no problem no problem no problem
it's okay Sometimes You Gotta Lose
sometimes you win
it's all right
oh that's a lot of keys a lot of keys
there
[Music]
another player
what are you looking at hmm I wanna go
here oh
money okay
women is taking flight
oh mermaid
okay see you later you or you can take a
break you have free trophies
okay
[Music]
where do you go
no I can't okay I can't use much
speed speeds
gotta go fast for Louie
don't touch her she has a sensitive face
going on okay
[Applause]
but it protected you right yeah you
didn't lose anything
[Music]
okay ah change with Reina
ah you can't
just stay where you are yeah
okay I use item
s
to buy the trophy number two
nice and
um
will she stay there yeah
[Music]
okay next last song kiwawa what items
you don't have teleport yeah it's okay I
don't have money either
present
but if you delay but Subaru will be top
if she gets the um oh no no may still
talk I know the first game so
[Music]
come on no thank you
first came out what area bunny bunny
somebody killed the bunny please bunny
still here
[Applause]
that's very um I don't know
yeah I played this before so I chose it
but it doesn't mean I'm good at it
okay what drawing roll uh barrel roll
roll
okay okay this is pretty much better
with controller
no just automatically
again
oh
[Music]
where is everybody oh good question I
only see the skies
oh
my God oh my God
on my HP very low
well I really
I need I need a Kill ah [\h__\h] the
controls
it oh
kill someone
I'm just like I'm just like I'm in the
sky
oh we're flying together oh
it's raining it's raining fire
oh
no no no no no no no no no no
yes
who was that who just died
[Applause]
first night
drink it
okay well oh present again but
is
gotta use it while I have it but please
don't teleport ah I choose the game
again again
these ones I don't know I'll just go for
the shoulder okay
what did she choose the shooter
you like the pew pew I guess okay
[Music]
you see it don't wait a few months if
you know what it does I just I don't
have anything against you I just want to
see what it does
10 damage
it's fine I'll take those why is my
corpse on the floor when I didn't die
oh I think if you if you take damage
Santa is gonna get it I don't know which
way which way should I go
oh
no okay
I want to go to the other side
yeah she gets it off
[Music]
um
I took the wrong chance I think did I um
I did I took the wrong chance
[Music]
you can fix it maybe
today
[Music]
I
have
um
uh
[Laughter]
okay
magnet
I don't know just moment just moment
huh
something more violent perhaps
it looks like a kid
oh
oh no let's go let's go
hey now
back to the graveyard graveyard
people's the first trophy
I weren't
I want you
you don't shoot the bomb turrets oh
okay make sure you don't use
shoot shoot oh there's two shooting
buttons shooting game
okay okay
oh black is the black one bomb
I don't know
yeah maybe don't shoot Bakugan which one
am I ah I don't know which one I am
uh
all that okay
the one with the fireworks okay
I know okay okay I get it
okay okay okay
now I get it
no no no no no no no no no no no
I see
I got slow and and fast bonus
my Point's very low I think oh no
yeah
the controls are so difficult early
maybe should have played with keyboard
maybe I always prefer keyboard I hate my
name is the keyboard Arlene oh wait
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
no no bump ever I was looking at Subaru
Senpai like the first 10 seconds I
thought it was okay
what happens sometimes oh okay oh
captain just shaving it
saving it for the cactus yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
sad face happy face happy doing happy
face happy Louis best Louis
[Applause]
[Music]
can't teleport
can we finish in 20 minutes we can
let's go faster okay uh
I think we can can we
chat what do you say oh excuse me
good timing to use item oh I show I sure
just wanted to go fast uh
[Music]
the cactus it looks maybe suspicious but
it's actually
who is it a change with um well I think
I can change with cactus who is Cactus
right now
oh my God you could not deceive us oh
yeah
protection
violence violence
why everybody choose defense we should
be violent
oh no no no
no you'll see
time
right at the same time hurt hurt
funny no no no
no no no no
[Music]
okay
oh music which one are we oh oh my God
it's so hard to see
I'm Orange
[Music]
I can't I can't I can't I can't stop
Adam then this is good
I can't go I think that's how it works
we are raving
I don't know that's how it works yeah we
are house I can't do it anymore together
where's that
yeah
[Music]
cut the path off
maybe I can get out of this faster if I
use the rocket maybe I'll try it I just
need to get out of the water oh my God
but even with 10 I don't think I get
that far
okay okay
I didn't want to hurt people I just
wanted to get out so easy uh four four
steps one two three four ah
kiwawa area area
orange domination once again but this
time I'll take blood
I'll take your blood do you restart turn
[Laughter]
yes
my blood
um
it's right there
if I don't if I didn't use this so yes
use your items it's so it's so slippery
oh my God I can't even I think you can
only reach yeah
I would have been impressed but you
chose the easy target
wait can you even reach that I don't
think so I think the the stone would
have been in the way
next Target next time next time
you didn't heal yourself maybe at all I
don't know am I hurt I'm kind of hurt
you know yeah
yes okay first AIDS kit yes
take care of your body
oh
who's that cactus
[Laughter]
manager
yeah
ah oh okay okay
big damage so punching is die I think
I think lethal okay
stupid bunny
okay okay
can you know beforehand oh yeah yes you
can okay
and jump also exists
let's go
I don't know uh
okay
do they come back yes okay
optical illusion
I thought it wasn't going
over there hardcore look at that
beautiful lava jelly
looks like jelly okay jelly cubes
delicious don't fall into the orange
jelly
[Music]
and
I wasn't finished
yeah thank you
I wonder if in final score the mini
games that you win also count like a
Mario Party maybe they better not
okay putang
oh
okay
[Laughter]
um safe
I have no idea where I am
saying
oh no I'll be fixed now
[Applause]
[Music]
um
I can afford I can't afford
[Applause]
yeah
interesting love it
don't or be hot beehive I think those
AOE damage but okay
try try try try try two people
but
I don't know
don't do it don't do it it's like
through Louie now but don't don't eat it
yeah like I don't know if it can shoot
me I'm curious I'm just gonna reach both
of them I don't know up to you just try
well this might actually reach nobody
no no no no no no no no no yeah oh my
god oh wow okay one person
you know who to Target now I'm I'm sure
try attack yeah Louis you know who to
attack now
[Music]
no Mumbai
yes I want to attack mummy yeah
yeah I love you no I don't believe you
oh
wow
I wouldn't happen have had enough keys
anyway okay what the hell
I drowned rejected
because
what does the arcade do
oh oh oh all right let's go let's go
let's go
will you pass the treasure though
oh my God
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
number two number two more keys
oh my
God Where'd I go
lost forever
[Laughter]
funny
does not bunny does not say yeah
but funny just exists now I know like a
six foot
okay from the bombs okay
jump pick up aim okay
[Music]
foreign
wow
okay
um
[Applause]
saddle number one yeah
maybe not that job
where am I oh what what oh
no
oh you you love me right yeah yeah I
love you I love you
okay
[Music]
it's dangerous in this game yes
no she always dangerous yeah
high fives hey
[Music]
ball
[Laughter]
[Music]
six minutes
I'm in the graveyard
she wants to fix her reputation
nice
to me my child come to me graveyard
[Applause]
why are you taking so much space from me
um
it can get the key yeah rocket 10 steps
I think rocket 10 steps one two three
four I don't know
but the key is does she pick up the keys
come on come on
only five minutes left oh no oh no oh no
will she read just okay okay
[Applause]
but I need I need them please more yay
okay maybe the next Treasure Chest I
could get Maybe
oh
God
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h]
Karma
why are you lying for to Victory
don't let the train
okay
oh okay
accountant
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
like snake
but only two turns come
on
um
what are you promoting promotion
like the game okay my favorite game
which which
do you know the uh okay
[Laughter]
you little [\h__\h] oh
yeah Eminem in the shadow I've heard of
the English title
bunny kill let's bunny is kill no I
don't know nobody live
I am a drink
can I go Shadow no oh no too far too
fast
I'm nice
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right
just use uh
um
oh
[Music]
that's right man
but then
[Laughter]
[Applause]
okay I can't do anything
I oh no oh no don't go to the planet
oh okay okay
[Laughter]
back
I like this song mermaid change the
frost to something
obstacle course
okay okay uh okay item is e okay okay
what's punching again
oh bye
[Applause]
difficult
oh
my goodness
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I accept my defeat man
[Music]
relax the world
one whole minute oh my God
cancel game cancel game
when again
huh
[Laughter]
see what's past the circle
anybody who reached a goals
fast
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh my God free firsts oh okay okay Speed
come on
something quick don't think don't think
okay
score is Not Gonna Change probably
anymore
wow
okay okay I see how it is
[Laughter]
[Music]
I just care about speed so I will just
do this no item no item go
go oh yeah I get into the water okay why
not
[Laughter]
let's go
run run run
oh
Just moment
Just moment just moment
teleportation
okay
okay oh
no Wrecking Ball oh
eat your veggies
[Laughter]
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
treasure
no treasure no treasure
but maybe I could get four more coins
do you really want to get on that
leaderboard bike
[Music]
hi
hi hello buddy hi buddy hi buddy
hi bye bye
but it doesn't seem to hurt the one that
you stand on it yeah it's like um when
it pops and then it reached somebody
nice
okay okay last game last game
please fast game last game pass game oh
Elemental escalation
[Music]
um
oh that looks like a the red one looks
like a chicken foot
[Music]
the element is candy yeah
20 seconds
yeah yeah I'm not winning this
oh
yes yes yes oh how is that maybe you're
not winning this oh my God
okay okay okay okay
um you're the only other one streaming
right yeah is this still going
um
7 P.M okay just uh just uh
do nothing or to the half nothing half a
minute okay okay I'm just doing nothing
I'm not gonna do yeah
[Laughter]
no matter what yeah she would win she
wins
thank you
it's so hot summer is hot
area
[Music]
oh everyone
welcome
area is nice it's not Senpai text it was
cool high tax Subaru Santa is senpai
oh
swim
um
no game okay oh
the pommel Awards we're here to shine
the light on your jeepers
if you'd prefer we judge other things
you can always change it
there's two trophies
down
[Music]
okay
um
Maybe
[Applause]
I know ultimate winner
[Music]
good game
okay do you have the the pictures of
it's not okay I closed this
is winner so super to read first line
but
um okay
are you ready
of course not
yeah somebody can read first of course
yes please read number one number one so
what's the original
horror song
release this Sunday
yeah
20th 20th August yes which picture
who is
pregnant
oh my God
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
2 P.M
and then the digital song will be
available later at midnight on all I
guess Spotify
Etc yeah yeah
how about uh
number two
never mind
this week's holiday
members so please watch
and then number four please read
Japanese only Louis
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so to sum it up we have a song coming
out on the 20th of August and we have a
Holy Ground coming out this weekend I
think yeah and we have dance relay
shorts coming out the day after the song
release so please check out her life
English Channel at all times
[Music]
[Applause]
please look forward to
Italy okay yeah no no no no yes
thank you guys for watching
[Music]
oh there's waiting room up now I will
link it in my
chatoni it's it's in a couple days
anyway but oh yeah yeah
okay okay bye bye
thank you
forever
[Music]
foreign