[Music]
n
e e
[Music]
n
h
[Music]
yes I was humming the
opening nice catch
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh sorry I'm
excited I'm
excited I'm so excited and I just can't
hide it I know I know I know I know I
know I want to play t
eyes tell
[Laughter]
[Music]
death am
excited um first of all is my stream
fine because I I heard YouTube was
having issues but I I was able to start
my stream fine so you guys see lag or
something no
I've been seeing so many other whole
life members playing Tes of Rise so I'm
really excited but like I mean I haven't
watched them playing it but for example
lisu and MAA had uh
sponsored uh T streams I was
surprised and then so say Senpai is
playing it on her own
which uh was as expected because suicide
Senai loves a tales off as well
mhm yeah from what I've seen lisu and
MAA were
sponsored so I don't know if they're
going to play uh more than just one
stream but
yeah no no I am the Ambassador not only
I am the sorry but I got to be proud
Here I Am The Ambassador I I am to the
English
region I am the ambassador to the
region need to sound like she will oh
I'm excited then we can like talk about
tales off arise if she actually like
continues playing it I'm excited
ooh
okay uh W this music is so dramatic holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
uh sponsor oh look I hate camping out
why okay well Shion is not going to be
friends with Cali that's a
fact wow she's not in a good
mood so yeah change the
costume should this be louder
H balancing the
audio oh she's
eating she was eating air she was
like like she has to be careful that no
one's going to take away her food or
something sneaky sneaky snack uh by the
way I'm I'm in encoding something in Ado
premiere on the side uh actually I'm
encoding the um she look at her standing
so elegantly oh what a what a B I was I
was sorry she's she keeps on distracting
me with her hotness um I was saying yeah
I'm still encoding the zela stream
because I enod I encoded I edited and
encoded it overnight then I woke up and
I checked and apparently cuz I had uh no
more storage in my PC I ran out of
storage it didn't it only encoded the a
audio and not the video so I had to
encode it again and it's 6 minutes left
unfortunately it didn't make it in time
before the stream but it's fine so
actually uh uh wait how to play this
game again uh yeah there we go no that's
not it uh where do I get to
the oh dear that's not
it I don't understand PlayStation ch
I don't what did I just
do what did I just
do h
no this makes me nervous let me hide
it oh for God's sake what what now let
me get out of
here okay how do I get Touch button
hey that's what I pressed huh I'm so
confused so I changed outfits cuz I
activated all my
dlc's look um holy [\h__\h] so actually uh
this yeah I'm currently using this uh
outfit with uh he got the cat ears and
the Wolf tail look at him holy [\h__\h]
macaroni I have like all all of the
other outfits
too uh Beau beautiful am I right or am I
right yes but we go with this one for
now and uh so this i' I've realized so
there they have this skin for the sword
that can go on top of it but
also it also is available as an actual
sword and look at what look at the
difference does this overpower me in the
early
game quit down
I will use it I don't
care cheesing it shut up stop
cheating just this is probably only make
a difference in the beginning later on
there's going to be more uh Stronger
weapons I'm sure um yeah oh wait I still
don't have accessories ah and same thing
for her look at her being
killed uh original was this rifle and
now we're doing here plus 91 plus 102 +
86 nice
yeah and uh while I was off uh screen I
just got myself the hoodle that's in
this area that's it that's it that's all
I did
um yeah and I changed all the outfits so
anyway I think we were supposed to go
here
right shion's curse so-called after
their appearance shion's fors inflict
damage upon everyone who touches her yes
yes how do I play this game again how do
I run I forgot the
controls how do I run
again why is this so SciFi looks pretty
ancient I recognize Ren and architecture
so cute sorry I seen some beatings if it
stayed sealed all this time it's not cuz
people left it alone it's not just their
technology
the renin build their structures out of
special materials too strong enough to
withstand assaults from Dannon tools and
weaponry anyway so how the hell are we R
to oh thank
you oh look at her being
amazing oh yes
wo Mutual h
SK time that may not have been a Fancy
Feast we just had look how cute they are
last time I felt this
full ddy the renin often not give you
all enough to
eat it's never enough the renin decide
exactly they look so badass and pretty
that's that we do our best to get around
it okay everyone has to grow their own
food and such behind the renan's backs
in order to get by
thinking about it now I wonder if
they've always kept it meager so we
wouldn't ever have the energy to try to
resist what they've done to
us big thinking un toll on the body and
the spirit after a while makes sense how
does a ren like you know what it's
like I may be renin but they don't like
me either I could be squeaky clean and
they still wouldn't give me
anything I need to find out what what
why they hate her oh wait I wanted to
change to Japanese your stomach
just you just ate how are you already I
will I said I didn't hear
anything I still have some I haven't
eaten yet
K
sure H okay uh no no uh H up uh
uh
settings the
homeo oh dear where do I do that can I
not do it now where do I do new
homeo yeah invoices are
nice the title screen oh dear H can I
save
[Music]
now I can save anywhere I am nice thank
you but that that's not noral for Tes
off
games uh how do I get back to title
screen
um
he's hell
yeah no it's
[Music]
not I'm not supposed to play that
bamboozle me bamboozle me why would you
bamboozle me like that voice
selection yeah I'm not supposed Play the
song and uh yeah otherwise bamboozle
okay we change it it's pretty good
yeah well wait you can play yeah
copyright copyright okay we are
back oh bgm back there we
go yes okay we are in this
see the problem is now I have to
actually read uh instead of just being
able to get through by listening to what
they're saying so that uh needs me to
focus even more I actually I think I'll
switch between English and Japanese
every once in a
while fight don't time for chitchat how
do I fight again I
[Music]
forgot oh no wait how do I I forgot I I
forgot how did
I ah okay okay okay I didn't change it
yet from R
R2 oh dead holy [\h__\h] wait my my son is
so
strong canel
you I like it I have no issue with that
wait we have to go over there for a
second cuz that's
uh
wait
it it won't last for long don't worry
the the the opness wait maybe I was
supposed to go to the other side first
ah wait uh there's a map right
ah never mind I should go to the other
side
first cuz that's where it goes to the
next
room so we don't want it hi let me slay
you real
[Music]
good I mean it's it's not like I'm one
hitting them
yeah it's
[Music]
fine let me enjoy this a little bit okay
I want to be
op is that a ooh what is that
oh oh is that a treasure
chest thought it was a
robot hi hi hi hi okay so it was worth
going
back just saved grinding by five levels
yeah that's what I thought it's not it's
not that op just right now it's like a
little little bit stronger
oh storage block second
floor where should I go first
uh just
way all
right play for the first little bit of
the game like that oh you got to make
use of what you get right
I [\h__\h] love the violin
music oh the
violin it reminds me of
Wu wait can I how do I jump again okay
can I jump over
there
what that that makes me happy cuz I feel
like in tails off games until now moving
around like that was usually not
possible yeah jumping over like that I
think yeah
par
nice wait what am I
[Music]
doing yes let's
go needed a power up to do that in be oh
I don't even remember that but I guess
you played it very recently so you still
have that fresh in your memory huh are
you guys playing T of Rise too you got
to play ahead of me so that you can
first of all help me and second of all
can I open that second of all not get
spoiled by
me open up okay we'll go over there
first wait does she jump automatically
though no I can fall down
oh I'm back in the first
ah wait that's so
smooth smooth transitioning nice all
right let's go okay now I have to jump
back oh 11 hours in oh 30 hours in
already have 30 hours in okay well then
you guys are fairly ahead of me cuz
today I probably only get like 4 to 5
hours and then
um uh tomorrow probably about the same
40 40 49
hours you had no chill
huh Apple
jel comfortably ahead then yeah
[Music]
nice let's go
sh I will do whenever you say my queen
wait I forgot how to dodge ah like that
that was dodging oh yeah I have to uh
remember to dodge a
lot sorry I need to get used to the
controls again
[Music]
dodging is important yeah I I remember
that from last time without dodging I
would have died
constantly is this where I came
from
no you good can yes yes yes I'm I'm
good
H it's suppos to go down I need
hello I have
sneezed I feel
better try test oh yeah baby bless you
thank you thank
you now I'm in a good mood playing
t wait I need healing Shan I need
healing oh my adult Premier encoding is
finally done
don't kill
me let's
go damn that
[Music]
juggle she needs to adjust are you
making a joke like
oh because healers need to
adjust to their
tanks Ah that's that's the one where I
was standing in front of before
right all right we opened up the
door wait what's with this one is that
an
elevator it
is e what was that oh nothing elevator
select what wait wa no no no what's
what's what is the residential quarter
what the hell
what about the other
door no I want to storage block three
wait a second what about the other
[Music]
door didn't one door open up below
me what if there's like a like
a Tre uh uh uh a
treasure ah
[Laughter]
who did you
[Music]
that jump scare not much of a jump scare
but that's enough for for me to get
shook where was that door that uh was
closed before is it still
[Music]
closed is it that one over there yes I
knew
it so now I expect treasure ha it was
worth coming
back here's
emblem okay okay chill chill I'll show
you
I'll show you um equipment probably
accessory
penetration yes penetrate them yes worth
it uh wait no not
here uh that way stop running after
me uh this way
oh this way and then this way
and there and then
left yes finally
not directionally challenged as I
usually am so residential quarter let's
go what do we find
here the
star oh
I am
here SW
[Music]
SW why is she so
hot I love you
her main outfit ah that scene I remember
that scene
yes take off your [\h__\h] mask and look
at her respectfully in all her
glory a my gorgeous
wife they kept the bunny ears
though y
hot bow to the queen
bow no we even found a ooh
o okay we'll wear this a little bit I
guess it is really
pretty she just wanted some nice clothes
oh God this is such a gorgeous design
I think that's one of the
best outfits in all of the tales off
games where are we going
now just back just outside or what game
voice a bit low it's difficult to
balance it can I raise the
um can I erase the voices but not the
bgm
yes okay and then maybe music a bit low
and sfx is really loud too
so
nice
okay
[Music]
yes all righty uh where do I go just go
there was no water path we just go to
the bottom
just was there a chest here that no I
already activated
that skits
oh I'm
done guess we're going back
she's got an
attitude oh
chill oh oops sorry where
I eating
[Music]
strawberries right into the
mob why does he only hit once
why am I doing
wrong I need to change the
[Music]
controls not not like I was using a
skill just when I attack
normally it's just attacking like
sometimes only like
once tap yeah I'm like I'm like tap tap
tap tap tap tap tap I'm not holding it
down constantly is is that what I I
supposed to do hold it down
constantly oh
[Music]
no that doesn't seem the way to go I'm
tapping it I I need to change the
control
sag
controls
uh how do I
how do I uh can I not change it here
does it just tell me how
oh can I change it
[Music]
here aha normal attack
um let's say
x oh I no didn't I already change this
last
time uh
I know I changed it from R1 to R2 huh
let's do X and then R to
tank uh that one can be
Circle and
uh and then jump can yeah R2 yeah yeah
yeah yeah evade that's fine well maybe
actually L2
yeah and switch what do they mean with
switch like character
switch oh R1 I guess yeah that's fine
and then Target R1 switch Target
switches L1 I switch L1 switch character
switch
R1 evade
L2 jump R2 big right button jump big
left button evade okay and then the new
buttons for that are circle triangle
square and X
okay yeah I think that will feel better
after a
[Music]
while
haveed uh let's go back to the entrance
ah not
here this will take some time to get
used to I feel like the those controls
that I just decided on are pretty
straightforward so we go back to the
city
hello
hello yes
yes oh fast travel let's go as you pass
through campgrounds and other locations
you'll unlock fast R Points to return to
them instantly open the map list from
the area and pick a point some areas may
be inaccessible at certain times in the
story
aha oh
yes
yes yes I want to go there
uh
h
Huh
H wait h I
[Music]
what are these one ah
okay
ah nice thanks for the
Uber H you oh we see a lot of like side
quests going on here thank you for the
membership
[Music]
welcome
uh but who am I talking to outside you
ah what's going
on
so H Jeff we've got a huge problem
something bigger than our attack on bv's
Castle because I don't have time to
worry about anything else right yes
bigger than that the bright eyes they've
started massacring folks all over
colia they must be after her Master Core
guess enemy must be getting serious
about retrieving it they must be if
they're willing to kill the slaves they
need to harvest astral energy boscul got
hit real
bad what are you sure about that
positive it's the closest to where we
attacked them earlier I feel bad for all
people there but thems the braks what
bastards
what you say you say you
say all right he got no chill we got to
save our people I guess fast travel
Point
added yeah I want to I want to chill oh
I can't I can't go anywhere anyway can I
just go well the the music is really
dramatic right now but I need to explore
[Music]
where I
am did I just see guards over oh
dear I like how they're ignoring
me I don't like those bees following me
I hate that sound hey
hello just exploring a little bit don't
mind me stop yelling at me
[Music]
should we talk to the guards say hello
hello mate where where did it go out
here
hello how are
you level 10
ooh oh wait I Chang my
controls okay how did I how did I how
did I how did I uh which which button
did I
no holy [\h__\h] they're pretty
[Laughter]
strong why did I pick a fight with
[Music]
them she dead she dead
okay all right don't
[Music]
die we can do
it don't
[Music]
die
for okay he's getting wrecked now he's a
bit buff but but they don't have much to
do here you got o we get rewarded for
doing that nice grilled mushroom PR oh I
got a
recipe that's it that's all they have
here all right um
we're almost there but you know I'm
going to I'm going to check out what's
on this map very important totally going
off
track recipes yeah I mean they are
pretty important I
guess y
[Music]
K
him
slay did I really want to go there where
does that lead somewhere where I don't
really want to
go so let's go up here get my flowers
flow
pepper o h what's here oh dear more of
those guys
yummy what was that why is your
fire okay I'm going to go to m school
now oh nice short
[Music]
card hello
be
hello do you guys hear the music is it
too loud
oh I got off track again what do we have
here oh I'm sure there's a treasure here
or maybe even a hood maybe even a hoodle
audio is fine kind of loud really it's
pretty loud for
me nice AOE
damage don't hit my shield
W Wonder don't spoil me but I wonder who
the uh F the First new party member that
will join our group will be
H I actually do not know I hope it's R
well it's I think like in tailes off
games it's often ah I knew it a cat tail
and cat ears don't I already have cat
ears oh it's just a cat tail cute byebye
[Music]
yeah it was worth it all right so I was
saying I think in tales off games it's
often uh the Magic character that joins
in next like right in the
beginning
but not always I guess but I feel like
it's
often it was she no I mean besides
[Music]
[Applause]
Shion a super
don't hit me what what is he doing he's
tring something oh we stopped
him nice
tornado nice ice
tornado
[Applause]
again we are a great team yes yes
yes she
got he did O
he's
dead he do be
dead ah this is this is where we
originally came from
right
what we can save the
children
go of course we can't make it where
where don't go
oh T looks as pretty as ever today oh
deal thank
you stop going to
seon I am the wall that you have to pass
but you shall not
[Music]
pass no I guess he's apparently not
saying
uh I have a name
okay and I don't know I guess
now you guys have to read this are you
really okay with it being English uh
Japanese it would be easier for you guys
maybe if it's English I don't know
that's a l of reading to do it's a long
jrpg
okay well at least a lot of times I will
have to read it for you
guys
chill you're so
dramatic
foree for
fore
a
pa
okay at least if I have the voice in
Japanese then we have
the positive side of having the Japanese
Bros understand what's going on as well
m
only you can do it Alin you are the
chosen
one thanks
I will never
forgot yeah we did that same thing with
RIS Riser and
true let's go let's save the
world return to
EK okay any hidden items or hoodles wait
we didn't find a hoodle here yeah didn't
we I'm sure there's one hidden here how
do you don't
I'm sure there's a hood did someone find
a hoodle in this map
before oh can I can I pass hello let me
pass maybe hoodle here Hood it's not
there
yet
ah I think there there is one there's
one on the train car for real
why did it not speak to
me what how did I not see
you what is that voice
[Laughter]
oh okay we're going back to the
back
yes oh I love that sound when you
teleport the the first the first sound
is
like you know what I
mean I don't know it feels
good his eyes are always so angry
jifa jifa okay now I always say jifa
kitten Jif Jif
kitten you you you criticized my
pronunciation of it but then it sounds
like jico
jell
K
[Laughter]
[Music]
jelly maybe he will join our team I did
I did see like even though he's not an
official part of the like six people
team I did see hints of him joining like
in my sponsored streams I think I even
like had that I I said that somewhere
cuz I I I had it in my notes but I don't
know like it seems like he's going to
join for like a short
time I did hear that
before but I I don't know I've never
seen like videos or screenshots where
he's actually fighting with the team
so I guess he joined did he join in the
first stream hey iron Mas can I have a
minute of your time hey Daren what do
you need well all you've been doing
since you got here is fine right I'm
starting to to get worried about how
your weapon's holding up oh my weapon's
doing fine dude I don't I'm not using
that Rusty ass
sword after all you're about to fight B
you'll need to be prepared for whatever
he might th don't worry I got it I'm all
right oh oh oh you'll teach me how to
forge oh nice
okay
okay is that a main
quest at the
end have to talk with him at the end
a hello dude H are you the one I need to
talk
to okay teach me then show me how it's
done did you use your skill points yet
oh I didn't I think yeah I was like
confused like about the whole system
you're the black s yeah I'll Forge the
best weapon I can manage with the
materials I've got all right craft
weapon it's worse what I got though
[Music]
ah and we only can we can't make this
one I guess just for the sake of it
we'll make this
[Music]
one yeah I guess so it's cheap anyway
sharp Fang that's all they need oh okay
I made it can I sell it h ah those are
okay I'm not going to be using those for
C crafting really commodity
item ah I unlock the weap ah so all of
those turn into weapon skins too
uhhuh okay okay okay all right uh what
you say about that long
sword yeah that's the most you'll get
out of me right now bring my more tails
and I'll would be something grander this
is plenty enough Grand as it is n it's
worse than what
all right thanks dude
[Music]
aamas ooh
money maximum fashion you unlock titles
of crafting
oh okay let's look at the skill panel
you guys got to teach me like this this
looks so uh
confusing what what what is this what am
I looking at I should know cuzz I'm the
Ambassador but I don't know what what is
this a a
title I don't I don't know what I'm
looking
at so if I put on one
title I can
only
what
[Music]
huh T when you unlock everything
[Laughter]
each title lets you buy upgrades and
when you complete a title you get a stat
boost you don't put on titles you learn
skins around skills around them if you
get all five you get a stat bonus from
the title unlock the skills you want
okay um let's see KO prevention sounds
good allows you to endure an enemy
attack with one HP remaining one time
when taging I want that
[Laughter]
yes okay so now I have
that and I can get skills too oh did I
already learn that one yeah I did I
think I already learned
those uh oh wait here's some skills that
that Sonic Frost oh yeah do I want Sonic
Frost or is this one
Stardust aial attack oh we want more
aerial attacks yes
yes uh yeah
uh I got a lot of did I get this from
DLC did I get SP from the DLC is that uh
possible increase oh H I want
yes oh [\h__\h] yeah I can activate
everything increase midair damage
yes easier perfect evading Max makes
perfect evading and per easier to
execute how how so how
I wonder
how let's get all the skills I guess
increase near death attack
[Music]
element I don't know what to get
increase alen strength counter Edge
increase Al bonus increase counter
Edge increase PG
boo boost go
oh 10 hit boost
go get the last skill for Iron
Mask ah that one ah so that I get the
this one
master attack plus 10 aha okay o
n n to the Hodo and now uh I could also
get this one what does this do defense
plus 10 okay yes and yeah I can dodge
once uh while Mia ooh well that's worth
[Music]
it okay the rest I cannot uh get oh but
okay we still have 3,650 from for
Shon um let's
see increased ailment makes it EAS to
inflict on enemies I
guess sure
I want to activate the whole thing I
guess whatever that is tox
toxicity yes and there we go attack plus
10 Elemental defense 10 Elemental
attack so burning strike oh hell yeah
gemin Aqua evades to the right when then
then fires to water one yes whatever
okay and what do we have here Canan
instant a hidden art sens spinning as
she do we have um something oh wait we
already have that
one that increased
ailment Boost gge from enemy
defeats sure
whatever okay yeah that's about it
anything else I can afford I don't think
so okay oh okay okay okay that looks
fine wasn't it like free to sleep
here also want to see what he sells life
bottle I have
eight n
[Music]
it's free yeah I want to see if I get
like o I don't know if I want to eat
right now I guess why
not more dropped
items all right let's do
that I might want to equip my new ah
true true true
true
true oh yeah right there's so much to do
I also didn't use um the items like the
like you get herbs in every tailes off
game like these uh defense
okay one for you more for you another
one for you uh do I have any any other
one camel Mill mhm P raises
penetration what's what's that what's
that in the German it's probably better
for alphin right
or who should I give that
to critical
okay critical H
okay okay looks good to
me and equip the Arts so we got a new
flying skin
Stardust and
and which one should we switch out we
have so many new ones plasma shock
ground attack that goes
up let's do howling as oh I already have
that
one maybe Sonic FR cuz it's
new okay all right well sheon is
automatic anyway so she can use anything
[Music]
anyway what do you mean
permanent oh again what's going
on what's happening in here what you
talking about yeah the the herbs yes
stay out
permanent
foree fore
[Music]
sorry moving
microphone not wrestling anymore
thank you for the membership sorry
welcome all
right oh we're
[Music]
fine you're not ch
I'm so excited to play tail holy
[\h__\h] hope you enjoying the game I
am
for Fore
for for
Justice's break the chains
[Music]
fore she's like get it on them
fore yes
[Applause]
let's
go one small step for Donna but a big
step for renin or what
[Music]
believe it believe
it you believe it you can take them down
if you believe it
you can kill
[Music]
them guys's fault for introducing me to
that
song
narut
narut oh man
okay I might do um side
quests off screen I don't think I want
to do them on screen cuz they're mostly
I think they're not like really nothing
so special and uh I don't want
to waste too much time on that believe
it uh where are we going take the Kurt
garron elevator
ah all
right I'm ready
oh well you guys introduced me to the
song Kelly made me sing it but it's you
guys' fault that I found out about
it Ah that's the elevator where was like
take that
later
okay uh trench of flames ooh it's going
to be hot up
there I didn't even know about the song
Until you were introduced to it aha
you're welcome I
yes yeah the chat made me look it
up Infiltrate The Castle from the back
entrance yes oh he
did oh
did who look at that
[Music]
though
wow impressive
anyway wait I have other things to look
at first a
hold a do is
[Music]
cute you guys okay oh good job
yo where's that lead oh maybe for
escaping later but I'm supposed to kill
those dudes
right
probably wait am I supposed to help what
look oh oh okay okay okay okay no I have
to go there okay
let's go oh yeah we're supposed to
infiltrate from the back I guess that's
the front
huh yes
yes
Co oh oh oh cut scene holy [\h__\h] that
castle
wa wao we got like lava Brewing
let me
go I don't know how much longer it will
hold quick catch for the back entrance
yeah okay where is it
do this
way is that not
where a left bandage okay thank you oh
my God I'm on a roow
I can't go there invisible wall so I
suppose it is
there sharp
eye I didn't know that one and you're
welcome I hope you can still get
him thank
you oh can I climb down B
don't
fall I'm not going to Black for us holy
[\h__\h] Zen we're going to do zenu if we
fall down
there mik Senai if you ever play this
game be be wary you're going to get PTSD
from
this you can fall oh
okay hello you ready to run rbo
wo oh is this like a phoenix being
reborn right now why is there so much
fire cut scene your
ass I've seen this one
before I think I don't know I've seen
that movement before
[Music]
what about my laser
sword okay let me take it out of your
boobies wow
are we going to do this every time
now
wow
wow I will unleash its full power let's
go
oh Blazing
Sword infernal
torrent I don't support
Torance Rising
phix I want
[Music]
it
flaming oh yeah cuz he has that skill
where he like loses HP I
think increases the amount of damage
Delta en that have been
down I want to wait for Rising
Phoenix Rising Phoenix burning wave
initiates a stearing swing attack that
burns iron mask's own body able to down
almost any enemy it has a wide range and
gains additional strength as more it it
HP sacrifice yeah yeah yeah boost attack
Blazing
Sword yes yes search around the C
okay cut scene
again ah you can mark the
ability are you telling me there are
soldiers inside too luckily for us he
hasn't realized we're here yet time to
put that sword of yours to good use
let's
move oh yeah stab him in the back oh oh
Iron Mask perk flaming Edge part one
Iron Mask can sacrifice HP to use a
flaming Edge a strong wide reaching
Blazing Sword attack to do so hold
Triangle Square or Circle which will
trigger a flaming Edge after he performs
the corresponding art flaming Edge moves
cost no AG to use
H uh-huh flaming Edge moves have the
added bonus of dealing extra damage to
down
enemies plus after learning a certain
skill you can continue to hold the
button longer letting you exchange more
of iron mask's HP for more power okay
I don't know if I understand
anything what am I supposed to uh
activate
this
yes wait this cost me nothing to act I
can like no it does what I'm not sure I
understand
what success count what am I press and
hold the button asign to swallow blade
what swallow
blade where is
well
what hold the art
button I
did I
don't I have to equip
it that's it wait do I have to have that
always equipped H flaming oh
ah the other
ones ah represent different flaming Edge
attacks Aha and I don't have those
activated
yet I only have that one right now
not uh stop
it what's going
on what what
[Music]
happening
Su boost strik a one hit kill attacks I
know I know when you see the strike on
an enemy press something there yeah okay
uh let do
it flaming
swing
strong it's amazing just how powerful
the Blazing Sword really is it's a good
thing we took them out before they
caused any trouble but now we have
another problem yeah this wall of flames
you think this is boun Up's doing
probably looks like they are meant to
keep people like us out so we try
running through them let's go don't be
stupid you're got to turn into Fried
Chicken well what do you suppose
proposed in I will I propose to marry
you right now right here in the Flames
let's let's get hot
I can tell these Flames are definitely
made out of something I'm thinking we
use my master cord to see if we can
interfere with it and then absorb them
with the Blazing Sword o smart basically
you want me to try using the Blazing
Sword
okay
hi
o absorbed like a
sponge it actually worked see what did I
tell you that took a lot more out of me
than I was expecting though maybe we can
save that trick for when when we really
need it all righty I got
you wait before we do that let me look
around oh there's another one
here yeah but she said she doesn't want
to use it so that's fine that's
fine I'll just go around here I'm going
to kill them anyway let's fight
oh
skit they're so the the notifications of
the skits are so small wait I'm going to
die I'm going to die I forgot how to do
I you than
[Laughter]
you Stardust in the air is uh kind of
useless for enemies on the ground
huh r no [\h__\h] yeah I remember in tails
of Symphonia when uh I think her name
was rain Raina yeah uh when she did this
attack I think it was her or someone
else was it
Colette I I was like yo this is so
[\h__\h] badass holy
[\h__\h]
recover yo Queen wait oh wait I was
wondering why I was like so low on HP I
guess the
the his uh thingy flaming Edge thing he
takes HP away from
me that makes so much
sense
oh does someone need healing no okay
well I guess then I don't need it
there's an elevator there but should we
go this way
oh skin
[\h__\h] there you go got
it okay
I made some fan for you how do I show
you I have a Arts tag on on Twitter #
Arts of
ases if you use that then I will see
[Music]
they're all so
dramatic okay and now one
do you guys want me to look at all of
those I'm playing on PS4 maybe I should
put
the there we
go playing on
P yes
there's so many those
guys I might I might accidentally Miss
some of them
another
one see there's so many I don't get to
play
he's roasting me too for using DLC
[Music]
that's funny enough it's a double-edged
sword all right uh wait where do we
go uh first right May um is that the
wall again I feel like there might be an
item there so I want to go get it I want
it sorry
Shon I
fight I what who you
fighting all right easy we're too strong
need to get those levels I guess
so sorry Shon it's only five C no eight8
CP I think it was oh what did we get
it's a fancy
chest oh armor nice
armor let me put it on
alant no wait uh yeah that's the new one
wait how much difference was there ah 20
not bad not
bad all
right now let's go this
way I might want to check out what's in
here too nice some materials for forging
I suppose almondine Mass
O Okay fight
F any tips for a new vtuber
oh I've talked about this um a couple
times before if you look up
Takara talks about
YouTuber struggles or whatever there's
probably going to come up a clip
but
uh besides that I don't know
um don't don't feel bad about
um
numbers uh because you have to
face the fact the
reality that there's a lot
of a lot of
uh uh uh what's the word concurrent
um damn it I missed
it competition yeah that's what I meant
there is a lot of competition
uh so I don't know when you're making
first of all if you make a model if
you're at that
point when you about to design what you
want to look like maybe try to make it
um
unique don't be another Catgirl or some
or something like
that or don't maybe try to not be
another Super
generic elf girl whatever I don't know
nothing against the uh the cat girls and
elf girls out there
currently but I just feel like there's a
or like a I don't know you know you know
there's some very generic
ones that are just like very
repetitive and now I have an enemy in
the air but he was down so didn't even
hit him God damn
it K him Shion this your element okay
that was a little Overkill but thank you
sh holy
[\h__\h] a
wolf a wolf on hold
on
well
also what
else I've said this before so I just
feel like I'm repeating myself but if
you don't have many viewers uh wherever
you're streaming you should just
continue uh talking as as much as you
can even if there's no one watching
because at any given time someone could
jump into your stream and be like yo
she's just being quiet I'm going to
leave
immediately so try to always make an
impression you were eating the rebels
weren't you damn embed it stop right
there it's you oh [\h__\h] perfect if I
capture you that should turn our Lord's
mood right around around you're not
going to capture
us wait I'm going to
die oh holy
[\h__\h] oh thanks for the first dat girl
did that really reach me though at the
end learn to i' I've been trying but mid
attack it's uh impossible
I've been pushing the Dodge
button yeah animation
[Music]
lock
fore sorry don't be scared
[Music]
oh also the elevator didn't work until
now anyway
okay you [\h__\h] idiot no it's not about
Dad it's because the the child will get
hurt huh idiot Alfred are you [\h__\h]
ret
stupid it's obvious why she didn't want
to be touched he's a child she doesn't
want to electrocute the
[Music]
child elevator
key you got a memory loss got to give
him a
break all right Savage Savage Savage key
suits you
for take the tea
away powerful
[Music]
bomb wait do I already have this one
yeah I
do lunar blast kicks an enemy into the
air and shoots them well let's do
it get me all of those
attacks all right
oh sh perk if you hold a button to throw
a bomb you'll fire a Special ammo at a
bomb after releasing it making it
detonate more strongly Special ammo
shown to the right of AG can be loaded
of X when at zero or by pressing R1 okay
sorry but as much as I love sh I'm
probably not going to play her because
sounds I just I just don't feel like I
can play A
Healer and damage dealer class like
she's both at the same time
and that just sounds like a lot to do if
yeah healer should I don't know always
be played by NPC in my
opinion otherwise it's a bit too much
going on is this where I came from
[Music]
yeah if we had another healer in the
team I would want to play a little
bit oh God damn it
[Music]
yes
D yeah I tried playing her
um and the
demo it was definitely fun to play here
I guess if I get like a little bit of a
Groove down uh where I can like switch
mid battle without panicking then then I
can like do that I
think oh there will be another healer
okay never happen
[Music]
fore foree
face come on
Shion Shion gives me
PTSD push this
way I want to get in there
give me those items you're
hiding sorry I was looking away
[Music]
oh orange
jell and on the other side we
have a chest what is it an accessory
life bevel okay I will gladly take that
I appreciate that very much thank
you it's a whole land between
chickens they have wait a second this is
like kfb accepting M as one of our own
or K be accepting that our dear Trav as
one of our
own rabbit tail that's funny that's
funny
[Music]
byebye the chickens probably didn't even
realize that it's not one of
them they're probably like thinking it's
a chicken just a pink
chicken be
oh I love the
battles I love the
battles
o couldn't even do the Boost strike
happened so
fast yes
Jasmine what's in
here explosive healer are we talking
about
Shon it's fun
the way she says it
[Music]
you scar me sh
wait how do I switch Target
again he down
[Music]
me okay wait that was unnecessary
still have planty to learn even late in
the game oh are you already so late in
the
game wait for me hold L1 ah hold
it aha
okay
shoot should we just all push them all
into this big hole in the
ground [\h__\h] I missed
it oh she's King me thank
you oh I did it
that DLC is real op I did you guys
without DLC have more
issues fighting those
enemies Apple gel Apple gel's everywhere
I dropped one and I ate one
wonderful Pro Gamer move what was that a
key I didn't
look they they were really hard they hit
hard yeah I can imagine
yeah this this is the the pre-order uh
ultimate DLC
yeah which I got from band Namco but I
also bought it myself before I even got
the sponsorship
offer so actually I have one that I like
a pre-order ultimate DLC that I haven't
he looks too strong that I haven't used
yet lying around if anyone of you guys
wants it I guess I could give it to you
[Music]
nah oh wait that was the thing I needed
for
crafting should I try to fight this
thing
how my br oh yeah yeah no he's he's he's
fine he's been
[Music]
provided should I should I give it a try
you can take it
really save
[Music]
let's see let's see I think I'll
die he got to got to um hit his weak
point
and okay okay okay yeah yeah I know
about the weak points thank you
thanks girl you just focus on [\h__\h] I I
was pushing it but animation walk you
just focus on healing
please oh okay okay okay he does that a
couple times
huh where where are you
oh core break let's go we can do it
easy wait is is his weak point behind on
his
ass or or his horn in the
front yes
[Music]
wait it's not over B was
over oh wait I see the w point
now no it it felt like it was glowing
more than before I think Bo boing the
ground
pounding the ground b y
oh
I stop
it sh don't die
sh yeah heal yourself
forit
[Music]
Hime
fore and PE
[Applause]
come
on kill
[Applause]
him ah you can switch a Target to the
weak point Oh I thought I just have to
like try to get like into that direction
on my own
oh
y my CP are hella low though
how do I heal my CP
[Music]
again wait so L1 if there's only one
enemy and I push L one longer then it
will Target Target the weak point a
orange gel oh is this not where I came
from it is
[Music]
why did I go that way ah I know I know
okay I think I checked out that
room so elevator I think that's what we
have to
do check out the
[Music]
elevator I'm so
popular got to refill at the end of the
dungeon yeah I think that'll be
fun I mean also I guess it couldn't hurt
to load it back
up free resting point before the bus I
am I suppose that makes sense let's go
over there first ooh burning wall
again all right open up
garet
garet uh o uh equipment let's put it on
you oh wait we had a different one as
well fire water damage okay let's do it
for you and then should we switch to
Warrior nah penetration is fine um but
let me use the orange one after
all okay at least a little bit
wait wait I have so many what the hell
where did all those come
from uh races
attack maybe I should keep some for when
more party members join oh there's a DLC
oh my
God greatly races defense Elemental
attack ra
attack don't you save some for others
yeah
true fight
Oh I thought he was attacking me but he
was just charging all
right and
dead by the way guys I don't know if you
saw but um the members only stream on
Sunday has been moved to set today same
time but different day because um I have
to visit my
mom wait a second why is there two
elevators I have a key
for wait does it work for both top floor
the other
one where does the other one
go ah ah there is ah okay this one is
just the normal one that leads me up to
the thir fourth floor I guess oh okay
okay top Flor let's
go I am ready are we doing the oh boss
fight already where's where's the
healing area
oh there it
is feeling
lights you sense a mysterious power
touch
it touch
touch Fire Lord let's go
I'm fine I got the DLC
okay
okay he's the first boss in the game he
can't be that
strong logically
thinking got to save though
Famous Last Words hey believe in me
believe it believe it should we tell
her a battle of the Lord
awaits I'm I'm ready but
uh I don't know
[Music]
I get my skill pan I got
781 can't
I get this
one does that count
as
oh ah Rising Wern okay wle now let me
put that
on this one and then I uh I wonder what
his weak element is well he's fire so
it's probably going to
be uh water and maybe maybe even wind I
don't know I'll try I'll try attack him
a lot with those do I have a new one
here no
okay water or ice do I have
ice no okay we'll be fine
no
weakness really it's go
[Music]
time he's so chunky
got a nice set of teeth
[Music]
though he really shows off his
[Laughter]
yeah I'm
scared oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h]
W uh uh level 15
[Music]
fore I'm scared I'm scared
we're doing good damage
[Music]
though don't get too close girl
don't get to
close
[Music]
what sexy phe two special boot strikes
when fighting powerful uh foes upon
fulfilling certain conditions uh
something ion may appear on screen above
an enemy when this happens quickly press
it to activate a character's boost
attack and turn the
tables on an opponent
let's [\h__\h]
go kill fire with
fire face fore
[Music]
already hey that was not only DLC I also
did well with
dodging
think he remember take
come let's continue to
fight his mask
broke he
remember oh
is that a comet that you're trying to
shoot and destroy the planet
or wa
[Music]
oh oh God I love these
colors wow okay I'm I'm I [\h__\h] love
this game already it's
beautiful what
[Music]
yeah did you just attack
what fire
Avatar who should I fight first though
what I'm scared
okay
[Music]
gotcha I got the
KO is that where I can attack the
when his hand is down there is that when
I can attack the other boy from the
background Well for now I just focus on
this one he's almost dead
wait stop
him consider yourself
finished DLC maybe a little
stronger no that's me that's my true
pilot that I'm showing you here guys you
guys underestimated me
[Music]
but you haven't been really nice to her
Eva she's so
pretty how to screenshot
[Music]
what
soe fore
I don't think we have a chance against
it I wonder if you target this one first
instead of uh ball b b
whatever uh and we actually kill him do
we get a different kind of ending
here he's he's so he's not honestly
soaking him up is
he I had question question Mar question
mar
ah oh okay
wow that sword is
[Music]
overpowered dude you're going to lose
I'm oh my God that's that's vibrating a
bit too strong oh my God yes it's the
earthquake get ready to mute okay okay
what's
happening thank you thank you thank you
for
that is the is the theme song going to
play thank you for
that I want to take
screenshots you no this now he look
[Music]
yes yes you're Alin he
remember nice thank you guys for that
please uh everyone who knows when the
opening and whatever comes up but I
think that's the only time but anyway if
you know then please warn me
[Music]
but yeah
I know I know
[Music]
I don't know those
lyrics yeah but I'm like really uh hyped
I like this music I like this uh opening
song can I turn the bgm back on
giz
this think I can turn it back
up are we ready are we good to go
yes I see
five inside the mountains I
[Music]
see
e
speech
foreign
foreign hey
don't stay English translation for that
though he was not that flirty
okay wait that's such a open is me she
is
SC I go I
remember Shion is like [\h__\h] why you
keep me
[Music]
waiting
unbelievable you know i' I've noticed
similarities of Shion but I didn't
realize I'm I'm Al well I mean the fire
element and all that makes sense
for
real you're
welcome it was so easy thanks
DC but the DLC can't save me
forever yeah who the hell are
you oh there still a lot of memories
missing huh thanks for the
membership next city still
there's
Ops okay thank
you you're joining because you don't
want to do this [\h__\h] alone and you know
you need the [\h__\h] sword you know you
need my power too cuz you going to take
down the rest of the four LS I know you
I know you Shan emblem obtained is it a
fire
emblem fast AG
recovery all right what is this
increased near death defense now I'll
save up some
[Music]
more all right
jump uh we're made it for the first boss
I'm excited it's only been 2 hours let's
go to the next city and
[Laughter]
[Music]
safe wait you want me to do side quest
or
what currently check out the Gates of
Fire wait where the hell are the Gates
of
Fire what are you talking about Gates of
Fire skit you guys tell me where the
Gates of Fire are and I'll listen to The
Skit
big back up the
elevator okay
okay
for her face
don't be so
grumpy she's like Grumpy
Cat I think you want to change their
outfits I love her normal out I also
love I love everything I love the black
one
[Music]
H
swimsuit I like the school uniform
should we do school
uniform I think I
like let's do this one keep the rabbit
ears maybe or wait she actually has
really cute hairstyles with the other
outfits
too oh wait that's not the hair salow
here we
go oh this this one's so cute I love the
braid and I love this
ponytail um let's go with this one
come
cute she can have a
mon I can't double ears the cat ears
a so cute what's that ooh we need a
bunny t oh there it is R oh cute pickle
pickle
pickle pickle pickle
pickle oh
[Music]
handsome
then I like this
[Music]
one and let's do the cat Tail cuz you
got the cat ears
[Music]
I see his full face now I didn't realize
there were so many
injured
Shion okay thanks Shion you can stop now
we'll take care of the rest from here
something happened while I was out after
she finished patching you up she and
here was kind enough to help us treat
other injured folks I tried telling her
she's done more than
enough it just works much faster with
her N N I just figured the sooner you
all were back on your feet the sooner we
could move on to finding the next Lord I
wasn't out of the good it wasn't out of
the goodness of my heart okay if you
want yourself to look evil in front of
us all right is that
right well whatever your reasons we
appreciate the help
thanks shon's map action Shan can use
your healing artart to treat injured
people that you find during your travels
oh doing so may earn your rewards in
return a spend
CP
he I did see a lot of injured people
outside here and
there
yes sorry I'm so in love with her I'm so
in love with her
wait his
mask I guess because of the story like
the mask keeps on coming back in the
cutcenes
she like oh yo don't hit me
bro don't don't point that fist at me
bro
oh my
God I calm the [\h__\h]
down so
oh
oh my my my f
[Music]
[Laughter]
isv she so
cute see some that always needs a little
bit of a data here and there otherwise
it's not
balanced this makes me go dopy doy
oh look at her she's so cute I love you
she I love
[Laughter]
you sorry sorry I can't control
myself she's so
cute I love you are you bad for my
heart I love you
ice ice
skin so
cute let's e and go
look at
her pickle pickle pickle oh God I love I
love this game trench of flam Ah that's
what they
meant you should pick up sub Quest even
if you
don't
[Music]
okay if I can go back right now I will
okay what
the anger they provide gives a very nice
contrast to the other tropes that are
generally with the main
character no you're
wrong I turn that it needs to be dead
[Music]
too what about K is not on the picture
just yet and K is like the cool type of
woman
and she's at least not
a sunson as [\h__\h] I think ah yes yes
yeah great we material thank you could
you get free Stone fragments all of
those uhuh we'll see what we can
do okay we'll accept them and maybe
we'll eventually fulfill them so he
wants me to kill those big rock guys to
get some materials from
those
fine I might already have
those don't I already have
those no
okay yeah I can probably fulfill it
naturally and there's something
here what is it that you want
sand of insect with
[Music]
wings what does he want tell me G giant
zo hunt you just want me to kill a giant
zal you have this one for question I
guess I can't beat it oh that's the
difficult one oh
get rid of that
immediately okay what about
you
potatoes
okay
ohuh did I just give her potatoes and
got the recipe in uh exchange it all
happen so fast
nice I love I love cooking with potatoes
they they taste so
good yes
uh you
want
[\h__\h] what she own the fashion critic
let's
go
yes I still don't get the side quest oh
wait what does it do give the young man
fashion advice all right wait for the
young man to wait what what
what now just go out and find it
okay wait for the young man to pick out
some okay okay okay we'll come back
later or
what I think I accepted all the side
quests Mission can be completed after
chapter five
okay n holdo
what chapter am I in right
now all right let's
go number one okay
[Music]
gotcha where are we
going I have this read crackling sound
again one second sound capture oopsie
sound oh I could have just teleported
couldn't
I couldn't I have just teleported oh no
not not here
apparently uhhuh which means probably if
I just walk that way there's going to be
some story coming
up is it a problem with the capture card
oh I don't
know oh wait h
ah am I supposed to go in
here
no I'm not supposed to go there the
other way
[Music]
okay you can go there too go back okay
okay okay going
[Music]
back oh yeah guys yesterday in the
middle of the night uh I um booked a
vacation you maybe have seen that I did
that if you on
Twitter yeah book my vacation
y actually so I asked rmt but she has no
time so I I asked um my best friend so
I'm inviting her for the
vacation um sponsoring her vacation and
she was super excited though too because
she said that she's like really really
exhausted from uh like she's a
workaholic and multitasking so many
things my best friend she's like she has
a job she had studies uh several things
in the
university and then yeah she has many
many things to do so she was like oh my
God I'm so [\h__\h] hyped for this I'm so
happy I'm so excited now I'm motivated
and I can study
[Music]
again so we both got superh to get a
break is free nights good enough for you
for now yeah yeah yeah
four days three nights that's fine for
[Music]
now also it would be difficult to get my
friend to take even more days off
from my
best would be difficult to get her to
take more than four days off so yeah
yeah foree
[Music]
how would he
know thank you rainon for the pinky a
thank you that's very sweet of
you I appreciate it thank you oh Redway
let's go H H I knew it I knew it would
be the magic user
oh oh she she can't take the
heat she can't take the
heat but I'm excited RW yes I like her I
like her very much and we I welcome a
magic
user anytime
entire
family f are you
serious I've never been to
no
problem all right we'll go to the
dock for renell I will do
anything we can dress her up too they're
all my dress up those
oh wait yeah can I dress up
her I'm so excited because up until now
I never like was able to afford DLCs
from Tales off Gam
[Music]
the only things I ever had were like
some
attachments
uh moreo wait which way is Moo
again not that way
[Music]
okay I'm there
okay can I go straight here all
right let's
go never let go of the sash tantel I
will not let go my
precious doc help me I need this girl to
come back to life
who are
you it's meant wait this is vo or
not oh it is
[Music]
okay yeah yes yes
yes yes
[Music]
yes yeah his full fa is like I'm I'm not
used to it yet
thanks for the
membership G I wouldn't call it oh no
that's her that's her um swimsuit hair I
don't I wouldn't say SC ha just very
volumous yay we freed them
[Music]
okay Kur Garrison Kur the
garison in the guard
house uh
okay guard house where the hell is the
guard house I guess I'll I guess I'll
just walk through
normally feels wrong seeing all of
alin's face yeah it's a bit weird I can
explore here now too oh oh okay well
I'll do that later I guess
I guess I
am of
course wow he he can see through that
kind of stuff he knows you're good
[Music]
R you should try both Bunny and cat ear
on sh at the same time I will vacation
thank
you I'm excited it's still like two
weeks to go or so I
think but still time is time goes by so
fast when I'm streaming so
[Music]
see okay someone said Circle ah
there so anyway uh back to vacation so I
was thinking for a
moment for a moment I was thinking about
maybe I should go to like Greece or
Spain again cuz it is kind of cheap but
the problem with that is that um the are
very cheap flights but they only go like
once or twice per day and I would want
to go very early in the morning and go
back very late in the evening so I can
make the most out of this short time but
the flights look yeah kind of bad um
they they
are like a lot of the flights to
GRE I looked through a bunch of the
islands they are uh they go
like off
around in the afternoon and then it
would take like 3 to 4 hours depending
on which island I would go to so that
just is uh a bit too much of a waste of
time so I decided to stay in the country
because I told you guys before I wanted
to go to like I wanted to enjoy the
nature of my country cuz we have really
beautiful nature did I already get what
I needed
we have really nice mountains and lakes
and ah it's just beautiful so I want to
go to um a really nice Wellness hotel in
my
country I think I
got hiking yeah I might even go a little
bit hiking yes ah there it
is than you thank you for the red super
chat thank you d
a we'll probably take a while until I
can read that one though I'm still
catching up on the others thank you
though it is that it has a star on
it okay we can uh T teleport I think
no you won't allow me to teleport
huh the other way would be
better
[Music]
y yeah plot on the way
probably so anyway yeah I chose a really
nice hotel H really special on I'm going
to show you pictures afterwards I'm sure
you guys will like H you you you will
drool at the sight of it it's going to
be
beautiful I'm glad I didn't have to go
alone I'm glad my friend made time for
it but hey hey why would you
not I'm going to uh invite her to some
massages as well she deserves
it yeah hope can relax and distress a
bit I really hope so
too I really need it I really
[Music]
do
yes we're going to
marry drooling Hotel fun
I've I've looked at the reviews and
apparently the food is also really good
there I'm
excited
yes oh this sweet Grandpa
you're going to sing in the mountains
like
Heidi we'll see about that but I'm
definitely up for going a little bit
hiking you know most of the time I'll
probably just
chill but um I do want
to hike around a little bit haven't done
that in a long time I want to just walk
through the woods and the
mountains with without thinking about
anything else although I mean I think
I'm pretty sure I'll
just I probably can't take my mind off
of work
completely but I'll try maybe I'll take
my switch and my
um my uh what's what's it called
PlayStation vaita with me cuz I still
hav finish the other tales off game that
I have on the PSV
though you're
welcome is there anything to find here
people to
heal they don't look like they want
healing yeah I got a PS v a while ago it
was quite a pain in the ass to organized
oh what does my Phoenix ey see
[Music]
M me get that ooh
recipe yes we'll we we'll make it
ourselves don't
worry I think that's the most important
thing to find
[Music]
here you missed that one well there you
go see you guys play ahead and sometimes
I find some things that you guys missed
and you can guys you guys can go back
and then pick it up afterwards so we
help one another you guys help me tell
me where to go and I go through these
areas
for to find something that you missed
and you're going to do some exercise
yeah I'm even thinking about like
booking a like a yoga session
there you can do all kinds of stuff in
these Wellness
hotels they offer like all kinds of
courses as
well uh where am I going give to
elizabth okay can I no I can't okay
no don't forget to bring some off for
hiking what what do you
mean buff Phoenix I don't think I'll get
buff parag gliding no no no no I'm too
scared to do
that no that's
scary thank you m fist a box right oh
office box
wait why was I not able to teleport that
was like nothing happened in
between all
right scared to no I'm not scared to fly
[Music]
I'm R come join us RN well RN well RN
well her name is bit difficult for me to
pronounce
though she's so cute
too the cold the cold area the snowy
area is easier for to
say well is not well well
oh her voice is
cute cute
[Music]
I don't I don't quite remember
if it was already this good in berseria
but I feel like
the character's expressions are much
much more natural
and well
expression expressive
[Music]
oh thank
you yeah thank you for the
pinky thank you thank you guys
[Music]
spee
oh you're just going to send us away and
you guys going to chill
here yeah the fist clench I was thinking
you my fist doesn't make sounds like
that when I clench
it oh thank you thank
you thank you for the
[Music]
pinky thank you all of
you I'm so excited for the vacation I
can't wait
just got to be careful to not break my
neck again this time
get neck and
shance good
idea so so uh Chef shu is coming with
us R come on
o cute
[Music]
deia joined my party what about renell
she doesn't want to fight yet
huh ending the
[Music]
cycle oh he's part of the skit too
there is good renin why would we killed
him that makes no sense
Common
[Music]
Sense he's learning he's learning give
him give him some time I
guess all right we why we fight oh my
God Another
[Music]
One
S snack snack snack snack snack s snack
skits are good for
snacking
definitely I will say that
[Music]
but what if he wants to what if he's
into that
[Music]
H
wow m
is that what is that over
there it's like what is it here no it's
not
reachable is that the next
Castle hello friend oh they
cute oh yeah good question that's what I
mean
no I want to listen to what they're
saying yes yes oh so there's a lord over
there that's what I
thought okay
okay oh
oh found something did you guys find
this one FL bottle all right that's
probably not exactly worth uh coming
back for
playing tag with the
Sanic oh look how cute she is going up
that those those
sleeves she's so
cute Shon I love
you baby
owl speak more with me F this game is
all about you I want to learn everything
about
you yeah let's go shoot oh so death is
really fighting but uh we can't switch
to him so interesting okay so he's like
a
like a h NPC that we cannot touch but he
helps that's nice where did I where did
I come from did I come from here go
there oh did I go that way yes I need to
go
there did I already go
there
szy passing
through gu character yeah yeah oh yeah I
went I went there
sorry come man don't break your knees
girl don't break your
knees now you two are like sending super
chats together to me okay
it what it's the main
character
oh easy
[Music]
H
cute
a the legend of the hoodle
[Laughter]
she secretly thinks it's really
cute
stop oh he's so
chunky it's like a it's like a
marshmallow like a
mi a c
I'm talking live in B
[Music]
language byebye see late
alligator I don't understand
baby yeah guess where I got my cers
from there's more don't
[Music]
worry I'm enjoying this too
much yeah
[Music]
the Sharpshooter all
right I influenc in burp yes I speak it
fluently
[Music]
thank you for the Super
Chat oh I'm glad you're enjoying my
streams Bai really couldn't have f a
better Ambassador in yuk that's right
that's right they're
smart they got the big brain I'm so glad
imagine I would have chosen someone else
I probably would have cried so
much that would have been so
[Music]
broken I'm glad that didn't
happen I remember when Scarlet Nexus
sponsorship happened I was quite sad but
then soon after I was notified about uh
this this sponsorship so I was like all
right this was supposed to happen
glasses oh I look so cute with glasses
oh my
kind how do
I how do
I
see
hold back up a oh am I too
[Music]
close but you like
up and
ow I'll look
up
okay friend glasses let's
go
byebye friend found every every hood
that you can find until now
[Music]
M mhm thank you oh oh yeah right can we
Forge something
new we can forge that but it's also [\h__\h]
so I don't know should I do it
anyway I don't have many Astro Crystal
grains
oh he that's better
[Music]
than it do we have the
right she has the ah did she wait did
she unequip the laser
sword wait a second did she unequip the
laser
sword I think she
did ah no she didn't it that's
stronger no no no no wait she no no she
ah okay that confused me because of the
weapon skin okay yes she did unequip it
okay in that case that thing that he
offers is probably not uh not
stronger anyway what else do you
have oops oops oops sorry uh
yes
now should I did you guys say I should
craft It Anyway forged items can be used
for later
okay uh yes craft
it
uh B gold
hello hello hello my dear friends
welcome I'm enjoying the heck out of
this game I've been squealing and
squeaking and squawking and gawking
constantly my my audience can uh prove
it confirm it right right
[Music]
kby I lost my [\h__\h] several times when
when I saw um Shion and any any possible
moment and so yeah we'll craft it he
didn't wait did he equip it did did I
just say he should equip it too I don't
want him to equip it I I've been kind of
um cheating my way through a little bit
of the DLC
though it's a bit overpowered isn't it
okay he still wears that one
okay it's a be overpowered
yes Shion equals maximum cuteness wifeu
goddess please marry me I love you and
but also Hood the hoodles have been
making me go
insane
for okay we can cook what should we
cook we could do ex yes let's do exp
boost hell yeah I'll need that because
my my DLC content can't carry me
forever all
right I'm ready where are we
going oh
bats van Grotto
take a look oh dear it's very
narrow all right all right cut scene oh
skit what you don't like narrow
places your wife
yeah no not surprising you're
hot and no I'm not using
cheats You're just joking aren't
you thank you demo
is he head petting her his hand is huge
his hand is bigger than her
face wait what's there's nothing here
okay okay all right all right all right
all right all right
uh what do you call those things wait I
guess they don't really have a name but
they remind me of
something
e wait a second I want to look at my
Arts cuz I I switched uh put the this
one here but let's switch it out
[Music]
um gargo gargo yes that's what I was
looking for wait I have a question
um I think in other tales off games it
was a thing that if you use these
skills often enough then you learn new
skills from that but is
that a thing in this game
too do you guys know gar
Gara yes it's the same okay then I
should use uh Sonic
FR um this only three times seven times
okay this one I use 66 times let's use
uh let's use or or oroi gForce
Fury okay yes yes yes smart thinking you
can learn more Arts yeah let's go bom
got here to help me
out fight
me
fire holy [\h__\h] there's so much going on
shoot hey eat fire
[Music]
oh yeah guys I don't know if you if you
uh saw it on my Twitter but my
Ultimate Edition oh oh de you are you
can come to life what the hell my
ultimate
pre-order uh T AR package has
arrived and I didn't unpack it yet cuz I
want to um unpack it h when my like
ambass gift from vam
arve because as you saw in the last
Tales of arve
stream they apparently have something
for
me like the the the the the hoodie the
hoodie the hood
hoodie for examples so I'm waiting for
that and then I want to unpack it
together probably on the stream I want
to do a
video unboxing
video with my
sleeves yeah the PS5
yeah PS5 is going to take take a while
it was just sent back to
Japan not not my
fault oh
I'm so excited for a winter
area will be very refreshing why oh
because it wasn't the
customs and we were uh in contact with
the Customs
but
yeah it didn't get sorted out properly
in time cuz the Customs made it way more
complicated than it needed to
be it will be cold as hell
[Music]
who the
heck who know
for flap flap flap flop flap flop FL
that doesn't sound like a nice place to
live in
Customs wanted to play t of
yeah well a
PS5 oh thank you for the pinky than
you I hope that's a non-alcohol
champagne that you
popping children's champagne
please with a sweet taste
please for children's
parties yeah oo There She Goes she's
swimming salmon for
Goa nice all right this is where I came
from right got to go up the ladder
popping chalky milk
yeah you guys know I don't drink alcohol
at all I don't like it at all
fight let's
go eat my blade eat
it
yeah they don't they barely attack these
[Music]
enemies and and focus let's go
destroy him this is so
Overkill this is so
[Music]
Overkill
T together we're strong yes yes you got
it I ship it I
stand I will never get sick of this
music I
think don't
oh learn a new skill
[Music]
nice got to be fast when you play this
game got to react
quickly
nice why you you killing the taco dois
I'm not TR no those are not Taco
dois oh it's okay I don't need it I
guess we got a
skit turn up the difficulty no no
no
no let me enjoyed this okay
it will definitely get more difficult
later
on as I said DLC won't carry me
forever I'll struggle later you'll laugh
at me
then but who knows by then I might be
very used to everything and I'll just
slay everything that gets into my
way
for I can't believe it's only been 3
hours I feel like I've been playing much
longer what does that say about the game
that there's a lot of stuff going on a
lot of
content nice jump platforming
skills endless over 9,000
I've made a lot of progress yeah because
I didn't struggle at the boss fight at
all
huh wait no don't attack my
[Music]
wife oh nice bomb nice Baku
hatu nice
uh where am I directionally challenged
this okay here we are this way this way
where are
we
uhhuh I will go left even though it's a
long path but there's a is that a dead
end I think it is but so I suspected
some Treasures that
way even though that might be the longer
path ah enough one of that okay okay
let's go this
way flap flap flap flap they're fast
there's goggles oh it's you can jump
down it's not a dead end there is
something special
okay I hope I'm not wrong in going there
first yeah that's the RPG mindset o
Treasure Chest yes I'll take that thank
you pan care bottle oh yeah right that
treats all symptoms like being
uh
uh what do you call it paralyzed for
example and
jump orange gel nice see I'm going to
skip some battles because I'm too strong
anyway so I'm going to just do it like
this and fall behind on exp I guess ow
that will hurt she broke her [\h__\h]
ankle
ah I
guys do you think I can handle that
one I exp boost oh oh you're right I
have exp boost
oh do it yes all right save first N I
got
it at level 15
a wiggle wiggle wiggle a wiggle wiggle
wiggle I don't know what's going on but
it hurts is this
poison I I didn't get koed thank thank
my
[Music]
skill oh thank
you wait does zir have a ooh I see those
poison cells does he have HP or can he
die I don't like that poison [\h__\h] all
over I want I want out of here I want
out of
here thank you what did you just do
thank
you let's kill those
[Music]
first okay it's going well
though very very decent fight oh let's
go boost strike
yeah we downed
him nice
bomb oh it's shooting some disgusting
stuff
e probably popped
his oh [\h__\h] popped his
uh what do you call it again acne you
popped this acne I'm
what are you doing what is that thing
doing what is he
doing what what am
I don't kill
me oh [\h__\h]
shield
first kill yourself
girl
thanks yeah that's why she warned me
about that
attack there a KO
attack it's good that we got the KO
passive because otherwise we would have
been done we would both be dead and wow
that would probably mean that way would
be game
over you guys should all get that KO
prevention very useful astrof flower
nice worth it coming here
oo ooh
nice we need more stuff for seon too
[Music]
okay we're back here uh so now we can
go ah Apple yeah now I where were those
apple
gels where were those apple
gels is oh there it's marked on the map
but do I want to go there cuz I could
just go that way nah not so by I who do
you think I am I'm not so desperate for
some apple gels oh oh I'm going in the
wrong direction yum
I don't need Apple gels that
[Music]
bad calm down elant chill
how could I doubt
you
oh I wouldn't mind renell joining the
fight soon
though she's just standing around
watching us
fight but she's hiding all that
power I know she's
strong I know I
know you can't hide that power for me
she was supposed
oh we supposed to go this way Apple gel
there we
go it's not like I need it or
anything
descent I mean okay well whatever just
jump It's just
water well that gargo looks like he will
attack
me you're life aren't you I knew
it flame X thank you for the red super
chat you
am I not
already everyone's imagine no probably
not everyone's
but oh I missed
it we F heart for those kfb benefits
wa what do you mean you fought I gave it
I gave them to you just like
that takana coming
through mushrooms I don't like mushrooms
but maybe maybe she and Alin like
mushrooms
[Music]
oh nice in in the middle of the air
that's what I like to see
it that fire just going solo over
there not encourag excuse
me I am the
boss I make those
decisions yes yes best Ambassador even
even though my duty has
ended oh that's say even though my watch
has ended my duty
hasn't
[Music]
for I sleep with my sash
he's so wise
thank you for the pinky t
that sounds very familiar to
me look at this
queen yes give me that side eye I love
it when you look at me like
that okay okay girl chill
let's go what happens
next are we in the tundra now
yes I love
that winter oh my God winter at night is
one of the most beautiful sceneries ever
it's so
Serene quiet
and fresh
[Music]
yeah now I'm excited for winter can't
wait but first comes Autumn
[Music]
huh her
hand she don't got no
chill I do love autumn
too can't relate tropical VI all
year that's cool too
he's like our
therapist this is Couple's therapy
[Music]
that's he's a very very good
therapist yay oh look at
those my feet in the
snow I know I have a scared waiting for
me but I want to look at the scenery
it's so
nice it's so
pretty lettuce I wanted to say cabbage
but okay
[Music]
okay what is
it I know I know I
know look at who
eyes we'll be fine
[Music]
yeah they're so cute
I want to steal her Hood
do and then fry it in hot oil just
kidding just kidding just kidding it's
too cute to do
that sorry sorry to my instincts but I
would never do such a
thing
um stop shouting at me
I I want the chest criminal
no I'm a good
[Music]
[Applause]
person we have we only use V we we meet
yes oh money
nice thank
you 850
gold tomato
tomato I'm not I'm NE mad no I'm a
king just look at that TR Fess of those
owls don't tell me you want to you don't
want to you know you never F maybe you
guys didn't me neither me neither I
never that was just a joke you missed
sh that was a big
Miss she maybe don't use ice tornado in
an icy
area although I don't know what their
element actually is where are
we was it was it right to go that way is
this even is it
connected ah no I should have maybe I
should have gone this way
first oh
well ah you jumped down from there
perhaps Gabby did I miss
something did I miss something over
there I got to go back got wait I'm not
directly connected ah then I'm sure if
it's not connected then there's
something
there there must be something there huh
yes RPG
logic some or
uh-huh oh chick
chicken all right now can I jump down
from there or not what I can't out
that
hurt all right oh canle campfire
here all
right sounds good to
[Music]
me
what I also have no meat on them their
size is all feathers
is that so probably yeah this fire fire
here passes no judgment all are welcome
to bask in its warmth a of wait did you
forget what I said
before I know I only want to learn a
little more about our new
realm I see you've got a lot of luggage
with you what are you holding around
here they full of wordss to sell like
medicine plus my tools that I use to
make accessories out of war from time to
time
did you say
accessories you mean people down here on
Dan I wear them too now I'm intrigued
she really likes fashion doesn't she
just how good of a Craftsman are you I
tell you what I'm going to have to see
some of your handiwork for
myself what
what what metal engraver can craft
accessories for you using or that you
mine from mining points once you
strengthen an accessory and activate new
skills for it you can even transfer
those skills to a different accessory Al
together
uhuh
ah you can use or to
crafts ores can possess up to four
skills ooh with rarer ores offering more
skills to activate these bonus skills
the accessories crafted from ores must
be enhanced
uhuh what is this
resistance sounds good let's make
it ooh ooh
freeze resistance sounds very good for
this
area
crafted enhancing an accessory raises
its level and activates bonus skills
doing so requires ore and other
accessories the rarer both of these
things are the greater the target
accessory will level up when
[Music]
enhance oh I can enhance it what do I
use to
[Music]
enhance
ah
ah and that's how I unlock those skills
[Music]
can we get to 10 yes we
can okay okay begin
enhancement enhance
[Music]
enhance
okay okay so we did we did craft one and
we enhanced
it DLC money did oh did you guys don't
have this much
stuff what do you think did I oh what
did I what do you think did I pass your
chest it's decent enough I suppose not
the prettiest thing I've ever seen but
it looks practical at least if I come
across any or I might be back until then
you better work on upping your game I
appreciate the feedback lady I won't let
you
down you should be calling out she on
yourself not me
rainwell don't want to talk to her you
do it often all
right those two don't get along huh just
as I
expected you should never go into battle
on an empty stomach and you can never
you never can tell when the enemy is
going to attack
so chill you don't have to be around the
bush it's okay to admit you're hungry
what other reason do you need to eat
[Music]
fine on a second F we need to eat you
guys I fix this all something good how
about a regular repast among as Crimson
cows crap
[Music]
crows what a me you're way better Chef
than I figured you to be
Che yeah it was good thank
you I'm glad to hear you both liked it
one did another blade like I said it's
not good to fight on an empty stomach
I'm I'm good I got to I I can't gain too
much weight or not fit into my mini
skirt oh she she's still hungry
though after that it took three tries
making the same thing before shean was
finally satisfied oh wow she has a big
stomach vegetable soup
m shut up Al
don't make it sound like I I ate too
much that's
embarrassing what is in
[Music]
here oh oh
comfy hi
skit thank you thank you Uncle thank you
for
coming I'll be playing tomorrow as well
see you there
I'll probably play for one more hour or
so
today bless you
Alin did he catch a
cold that was a tiny
sneeze cute
what a tiny
sneeze Shon is Faking it I'm telling
you it must be more
like
[Music]
fore my is
normal
for yes me and the DLC
people keep on telling Alin to not
forget who he is and what he thinks
now is this is this a hint for later in
the game is he going to have issues with
that later
is he going to come close to becoming a
villain oh
interesting
uh I still have another I still have my
exp effect don't
I where the hell am
I let me get that
material mine it's it's it's a it's a p
because I'm mining it and then it's
[Music]
mine
Apple I have a pen I have an apple ooh
Apple
pen I have a pen I have pineapple o
pineapple pen Apple pen pineapple
pen pen what what's happening pen
pineapple Apple pen what did I just
do I was so focused on
singing yeah that is quite
nostalgic was he buing around
uh oh look at them
cute where should I go was I in that
area yet but I'm supposed to go up there
oops no no I want to
explore who what is who is that what are
those oh oh oh
chest also I haven't found the hoodle in
this area yet
right or did I did I no I don't think I
did
kud where are you n did it recently wait
n did
what you haven't found the noodle yet
you deleted it did are you on your phone
and it did auto
correct I'm looking for a noodle
hey you could have kept that
tyo P Pine yeah yeah
yeah find the
noodle noodle
do
nice
I got to react quick holy
[\h__\h] D those boost strikes also um do
AOE damage when there's enemies close
by or only on the one I'm attacking cuz
right now it felt like it did AOE
damage it does
oh
nice Cuda
[Music]
where could he
be I'll find you
eventually the blue finishes do as well
oh nice okay
I want to appreciate this place a bit
more this was once a waterfall huh
nice
wow very pretty
scenery very refreshing after the hot
desert and the lava and all that
hoot hoot I'm trying to make up for that
noodle comment aren't
you sneak sneak P the Snak I don't know
if we can do that
[Music]
cat
fight Rell has no chill all of these
women have no
chill but okay Rell is like what 14
years old she's very
young all on her
own yeah K will be like a
kindergarten no never was
dead don't tell me
guys see alin's dead he's trying to make
alen
remember don't tell me don't tell me CH
don't tell me I'm not
looking don't tell
me I'm scared to look at the chat
you can't look at the
[Music]
he does kind of have sish hair and blue
eyes all
right I didn't find the hold on
[Laughter]
there you are got the eye
patch I was like I can't I can't give up
I can't go without my hoodle I'll rescue
you it's a snow ow snow Hood in the
other area they were all like pinkish
and
reddish
get
byebye 10
total snow
cute I want an owl I want to own an
owl they got the same guns
as sh
[Music]
a good night if you're going to sleep
thank you for coming
y there we
[Music]
are no one is our Lord we are free
l
oh oh is he your
son he man
[Music]
oh the
music oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh oh sh is he don't yo chill
he's got no
chill
y am I supposed to win this fight wait a
second come down
oh y
[Music]
yeah but don't get too close to
law yeah it's good that law is focusing
on saire right now cuz it seems like he
really has like
uh insane amounts of HP or like endless
endless amounts of
HP kill
him kill
him
for no no no I know how much law has but
uh I mean uh zier
[Music]
oh I'm I'm not supposed to kill him
huh this is a fight I can't win anyway
oh are they
Rel he's disappointed in his dad cuz he
went in another
way and I thought was Al
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
speeech
foree
for
Fore such a
weird Jae pronunciation
oh he's going to die here isn't
he
why
why no AR makes sense
in
considering also it'san notu they
actually do sayen
well apparently he forgot himself as
well shoot shoot me shoot me
instead fore
foree
fore she's special
[Music]
for
foree
[Music]
fore
forch
foreign foreign
[Music]
she's a good
girl
foree
fore
[Music]
fore for
I don't like her I mean I understand the
reason why she wouldn't use it until
obviously it was like a Witch
Hunt but now we'll protect
her and she'll help
[Music]
us she definitely looks like
a a sad character of a JRP of a jrpg
doesn't she
for okay I befriended rewell Z left
vegetable juice
[Music]
we learn you when there's an A on map oh
nice thank you one tip for finding El is
that The Closer you are the more Hood
react
a yes DLC I'm so
excited I guess I'm going to put her in
this school uniform as
well all right
3,500 where do we
start
[Music]
mm Elemental attack I want to start here
Gusty nail increased down damage uh
thousand yo those are expensive
[Music]
these are all let's give her KO
prevention very
important reduced art cting oh yes
increased CR yes okay for now that's
that we can add
um this sure whatever she got thousand
[Music]
makes it harder for enemies to disrupt
art ah yes very good very good and with
the 8 800 we have here speed of flaming
Edge charge time
sure okay oh and we can do another one
allows the Flaming Edge to be charged in
exchange for greater damage de but also
what I don't
understand sure
all right DLC skills are expensive wait
oh those are DLC
skills the expensive
ones
what can charge for more damage with
more
Health oh the top FR DLC
oh interesting thing oh I didn't
know I don't know about
that yeah anyway um we have more
important things here oh look that
picture changed and H is so
cute
uh okay let's look let's look let's take
cute yes I love okay I really love her
with the Beret that's my favorite I
think yeah yeah definitely my favorite
and that's from the school uniform too
you can take it off as well I like this
one I think and
then we give her it's called Owl uniform
cute this one or this one or this one
[Music]
I'll just give her that one and then for
attachments oh glasses uh suit her
definitely they're very versatile after
all
doggle cute the doggle ears fit her
well very important business here you
know I think I might actually give her
Dogo
ears then dog tail yes cute why does it
why does that look so good on her
oh what a nice book which means she got
an OP weapon as well
huh secret of the Stars oh oh she's ah
she's already carrying it okay
uh anything else we can give her
[Music]
I'll give you that I guess for
now but for you I might want to give you
this
[Music]
yeah oh ah sorry it confuses me the skin
really confuses me this is the one that
we want all right by the way let's save
ones there was there auto save in this
game
yeah the skin always gets
me thank you guys for
noticing
um yeah I think that's all I want to do
right now yes there are other saves okay
where are we
going back here Oscar run okay
okay let's
go let's rescue
him I hope we can rescue him
apples always got to have enough
uh things to cook with we got R in the
team
now yes more more magic crazy special
effects got to love the sfx
yeah
[Music]
easy sorry I want to pick that up I
can't ignore when there's something
sparkly on the
map she's hard to control outside of
automo see you know wait a second uh I
thought I can switch with R1 was it that
R1
I I how do I switch M
battle
L1 ah
[Music]
ah
I okay oh is old DE here oh my
God this actually looks like a lot of
fun Co
you know what I want to play her a
little
bit wait it switched back to Alin though
didn't
it uh how do I do it like permanently
again change party leader status
edit yes
yes uh
[Music]
test it
out magic is
fun okay let's do
Sprint see the casting time is like
almost non-existent but let me switch
around a little bit is that all you can
do air FR a there we
go
uhhuh well okay I guess we got to use
those a little bit so that we get new
skills
eat
this
easy this is Chill when you want to lean
back a little
bit attack them from
behind
nice I you see I agree with I agree with
the person who said that you know it's
it's difficult to use a magic user cuz
that was my general f as well but in TS
of our eyes it's actually not that weird
I mean for important battles I would
still always go to
Alin but
generally for like in between I
think it's not such a weird
idea skit oh
[\h__\h] uh
it felt
easy in other games I would always let
herp he's gone
I did use
sh in the demo it was fun to use J but I
don't think I would be very good in
controlling her to be
honest like see what is this SK
[Music]
about oh yeah I know that skit can we
skip it cuz I've seen it Two Times by
now I
[Music]
think I remember this
one what about this one
[Music]
cute alant looking like a
snack she is the snack here okay but
it's my snack you can have
Al oh look at
H what a
baby oh
huh
baby I love you H I love
you bye ski hello you got a side quest
for
me oh he's
shook you look gr nervous kid what's the
matter you're not thinking of turning
someone in are you why you worried
you're going to be reported no that's
not it then what's wrong
the ziggles they're everywhere help okay
you want me to kill ziggles okay of
course fire beneath the
Ice uh
sure Shon figure coming out wasn't there
a sheon figure in
my some some kind of figure I think is
in my Ultimate
Edition
pre-order pre-order Ultimate Edition
thingy did I just hear
Hood there must be a h
Hood I saw you I no that's wait I hear I
see
you wait why are you in that basket
that's so cute he's got wolf ear I think
is cute cute cute cute cute
byebye
guys hello chicken hello KY are you not
cold do you need a hug I can warp you
up hello
kfp okay I'll leave you is this a side
quest yes what does this one
want alcohol you want
alcohol why am I giving him four what or
something well Quest complete heart
liquor we got a recipe Loi K what is
that is that an actual
thing interesting
that's where
the
okay
Quest finish salmon
[Music]
oh oh we had this one too what's your
recipe life well okay thank
you salmon
soup I wonder what is that did you guys
ever eat something like
that is it
good hold
on she's
feeling it's feeling that you're looking
at it from behind
how can you do that fish I've never
eaten
never super good and easy to make
[Music]
speed
skit C thank you for the membership
round
hten failed his perception oh yeah right
next week is tpg
again it's been a long
time I feel like I've heard this one
before
too I might be wrong
though seems familiar
ah this was in the demo too
[Music]
okay okay R's Ace okay what's
next did we hear this one
too yeah okay seems familiar
too okay all right I think we're done
with those then those are like the
introductionary um skits for renell all
right let's go up there
huh I'm on my way to the m
[Music]
mcraft Nice
Bridge
wait oh we can get milk from the
cow yes thank you very much cow for your
offering I'll make something nice out of
it oh [\h__\h]
A I love
that that might be laugh so
much hey we not
travel don't scare
them
foree fore fore
foree
for you for
theing
ah sorry that I didn't like play it
fully but it was a bit too
cheerful but when I ended up playing was
a bit too
sad but thank you you for making
that thank
you I appreciate it yes yes we'll kill
them I guess the Snake Eyes
yes she's basically TI oh yeah you know
what I I feel uh
similarities cuz Tiana is also supposed
to be like kind of like suspicious of
people and uh can I jump down there yes
I did can I roll
off little on edge yeah I wish I could
play her um better though
wanted her to be like sh but but
no not so much
okay what a beautiful proud horse over
there wow it's
smiling
what was also really
buff all right it's so quiet in this
area cuz the only thing you hear is the
wind but I think that's
nice okay okay okay I still have my exp
buff though
I still have it that one by the way it's
I don't think it's time limited I think
it's uh it depends on how many battles
you've
had sorry I got no chill oh I want to
continue yes oh
chill CH let's
talk ah special skit
can I get a good night
kiss
foree fore
she really reminds me of
Mill TS
of being like cold and probably over the
course of sorry the course of the game
sorry
she's she's probably going to learn how
to be more
sensitive and nice
I'm closer to
Shield
[Music]
okay yes
thank you thank you for being nice
[Music]
respectful is this like a followup skit
because I talked to Shion
and Rell I tried to talk to you but you
were not an
option unfortunately
yes Hammer them that's
right Rising Falcon
oh I remember that all
right it wasn't
me wasn't me
more
skills yes I did unlock Rising
Phoenix so much
snow Christmas jingle bells jingle bell
jingle all the
way oh what
don't worry why it's so much snow why
snow
storm do tomatoes grow in such a shitty
cold
[Music]
weather you don't like did I say that
are you mistaking me for oh wait I'm
still uh
still R did you mistake me
for
IR I like I like me some Christmas I do
love
Christmas
oh uh wait a second what we can't go
that way
huh no no no
okay sow much
fun
a I wouldn't mind them adding like a a
feature where oh my God she's diving
what where she gets damaged by swimming
in this cold water cuz that must be
painful unless you're Alin I guess you
could let Alin swim in this he probably
wouldn't mind oh wait we're going that
way she know hold
see how I'm blasting out
those
ex oh my
God it's a nice change to not play alant
for a little bit though pretty
nice y don't come too close to
[Music]
me shoot
shoot what's Mai nothing's Mai
there we
go I'm actually uh I wonder if I can
take a another inside of Australia
vacation in the
winter I still want to re challenge
going skiing but in
Australia cuz I think one of the big
reasons why I had so many issues last
time was because the snow was [\h__\h] in
the place that we went to me and Callie
we need a fresh and soft snow but what
we got was
um like it was really really hard to
know you could barely like turn around
on on the
skis yeah I need that out that real out
snow oh wait I always try to get close
because I think I'm Al go back go
back
for
yeah and I think
oh wow usually I only ever see the the
Boost strik of
of
nice what was I saying yeah I remember
when I when I learned how to ski when I
was a child it was not that bad I was
not that bad at it and I learned it so
fast I picked it up really really fast
but I think it's really just that the
snow was really bad in hoky
do I really couldn't control where I was
going was really
scary should we go there oh do you guys
think I can kill this
one I'll switch to alen though I think
oh wait I thought it was a thought it
was like a a a giant enemy but no it's
just a normal
one don't
die oh they used Apple J all right fine
with
me I love that
attack
nice oh is this something for it must
be oh it's not onx one piece that's for
uh Shon
that
hold wait does that would that change
the look of her outfit if I wearen if I
wasn't wearing a DLC
uh
outfit
costume no ah okay
who don't
know costume
separate I have
it I'm too close get off of me
I keep on activating the one with shield
and rinell I should activate the one
with rinell and
alen I don't want to see that
one let's climb back up I guess from
here or
uh was I was I here
[Music]
before
anyway was
i h not
sure I'm getting really tired right
now I think maybe half one more half
hour and then I'll read Super
Chat yes yes yes get through this area
see a little of story I'm going
backwards need to go up
here where am I
going person back there to
heal where here or down
here wait is it this one map
action that would make
sense ah
I will I will heal
them Tas oh there you are are you
ah o Earth seed thank
Youk so where the hell am I going
now h i I need to go down
and and down this
way okay okay now we're on the right
track swim
yes this is what I call fishing I can't
open the map when I'm no I can just when
I'm moving I think I
can't uh
can I go this
way there must be a chest here oh oh no
chest but what the hell what what
what can't open M plus ah so it really
is that okay I thought so
oh I love this
flashiness I keep on activating the same
one all right and back with
[Music]
go
yes yes I love the the the fluid
teeth I love how fluid it is too
I love it it's very smooth a lot of
fun and PC do you want to talk to
me why did it have to be a to like that
I can't go anywhere with that
there what are you doing here they
didn't follow me all the way here did
you if you're plan to report me then
think again we're not going to tell you
we're simply trying to get to cuden to
rescue a friend of ours that got
arrested I see a bunch of C EES great
get out of here before you get me
arrested you mentioned something about a
togle is there a strong one up ahead a
wol okay no
problem I thank you
come
[Music]
come ooh wait is that going to be like a
boss monster cuz I'm getting healed
[Music]
here I think I'm f
mine should I
save she
save ah yeah the heel circle is always
sus and he the NPC warned us as well so
I guess let's
go wait I should switch ah [\h__\h] I need
to switch to Alin
oh
[Music]
de
yes okay uh uh
edit I know that like this here changes
who I'm fighting with I wonder what why
I I can do this though I guess because
maybe I feel better activating certain
members on a certain button is that what
that's
for wait I didn't
change
H oh there we go
Spend a
While come
back y never
mind thank you for renewing your
membership this fight was so fre yeah
B I wasn't expecting it to be
difficult I want to change I must have
like a fire skill
[Music]
right no ah
oh not really
surprisingly destruction let's use
destruction I'm
scared I need a
healing I saw his weak point I just
noticed wait so wait
ah thank
you who gave me that thank
you cor
break take him down take him down
[Music]
is it still is it still targeting his
score yeah
think Sonic
F EAS
oh did he was this dude always
uh did he just uh summon them or were
they always here I think he just
summoned
them it oh it didn't hit
me
[Music]
nice thanks
he summons
themo oh and core break again
Ice Ice
Baby thank you for the
save okay I I'll heal myself Shion don't
wait Shon is also about to die I'll heal
myself don't mind
me you know in other tales off games
using items was always a little bit to
mus
see because like it would tell like you
can't tell a dead person to use the item
himself so you would have to ask Shion
or something but they would take their
sweet time to actually use it and I'm
quite surprised how in this in Tales of
arise it's not that it's not the case
it's really easy to use the items they
use it
immediately and I don't know I selected
alant but did it really count as him
using the item even though he was dead
or did officially someone else take it
oh
W yeah yeah yeah they would like finish
whatever they were doing first and then
run around a little bit and then use the
item that would take a lot of
time nice DC carry
[Music]
SH now we're on the other side of that
foreign or iron
chunk no I don't mean the cool down the
cool down is still there I see
dad
what isn't that a good
thing is that not a good
thing nice
scene y oh it's a big monster eating
those zo
no is it the the the mysterious
dude oh it's the mysterious
dude
mystery why is that alen from the past
of the pict
[\h__\h] horror game or
what what whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoaa
is he a time traveler how the hell did
he do that Tales of
Virgil oh my
[Music]
God no
she's in
love my
serious
[Music]
for I'm hooked I'm so immersed I'm
excited that we play H as tomorrow as
well
[Music]
claw voice actor oh is that
so land of glistening Radiance
[Music]
cesonia we've made
it
straight
[Music]
for
for Fore
fore
yes fore
this might be a good spot to end it for
today I will read the super chats and so
let me save here
yes
got good progress today really exciting
game I love it so much
already I'm very very happy with the
game and I'm so glad that we are
enjoying it
together it's like you know these um
[Music]
tail tails off games are big part of my
my
childhood and my
upbringing I guess so playing it having
the opportunity to play it on stream and
you guys are actually enjoying it makes
me really happy thank you thank you
thank you please come to the other
episodes of me streaming it as well that
would make me quite happy yes and so
we're going to read super chats for a
few hours I
suppose no that was not even on person
purpose so sorry
um I will take a twom minute break I
think and come back and we'll see uh
I'll see you guys in my office
okay I'll see you in my
office so just sit down there and wait
for me all right go attack your cats you
know me too
well are we're in trouble we'll see
about
that nah you're not in trouble I got to
read more Super chats but you guys are
welcome to stay for
that one
[Music]
moment all right yeah you guys got to
catch up as well make some progress in
the game that's fine or you can listen
to the super chats while you're doing
that mhm now's the time to catch
up okay I'll see you in a few
[Music]
[Applause]
minutes see you in a moment
[Music]
w
ni off
I brought some
tea and did you hear me making
tea oh
[Music]
wait hello
chat
chat I was talking to you did you guys
not hear
me did you guys not hear
me
de super reading time e the cats no no
no no I made tea I don't know I don't
know what you
heard let me fix the chat
here wake up guys where are
you Hello Ki you guys dead wake
up oh oh oh just dead on my side oh on
OBS it's on OBS it works my own chat is
like not moving at
all I was like guys are you ignoring
me don't ignore
me chat doesn't know I exist
sad
for I ran out of honey I need to buy
honey need more
honey I I squeezed the last
bits I squeezed the last bits of my
honey into the tea but it's barely
anything
M but I I'm using my my big my big
teacup I have this huge teacup that's
basically two two cups of tea in
one so I just got to wait for it to cool
down a little bit it's not one of those
uh FIS cups it's a normal one so it
shouldn't take too long but I felt like
I need this because of the super chats
bgm yeah what should we listen to
H for
now we can just listen to these do you
hear
that cuz I don't wait a
second what why why can I not hear
that it's broke ah there it is I fixed
it do you hear this double now or do you
hear it
once does it
work uh yeah actually yeah we should
actually be able to use that to the
bosan NOA
stuff I guess we can listen to
that hold on
uh bosan NOA or the other
ones let's
[Music]
do wa is this the B no
one yeah which one was
that that's not the b i NOA one
all right I can't find it so we'll just
go with this
one oh boy that was
loud now it should be nice why is my
chat so
broken let me let me reload let me try
to fix it
[Music]
yeah the permissions it should be fine
it should be
fine I mean there's a small risk
but that demonetization maybe maybe
would get stripped of me but in the
other streams it was fine too so I don't
believe it I think it will be fine you
know me okay I think my chat is fixed
again test test where are my chickens at
keep Kitt say hello chickens
chimkin say hello to
Mommy there you
are
so more
water lots of water so how do you guys
like Tes rice so far
H how do you like
it lot of fun so awesome it's really
cool makes me want to play it very
entertaining I'm enjoying
it I think it's the best Tales game in
years that's that's that's a very good
thing better than expected Bas dop
duplate great Ambassador yes also a bit
too big right
[Music]
now probably around
here all
right what about both heads
okay yeah I mean yeah this is only T of
game in a few years but it depends on
how many years we're talking I want to
play
maybe I'll after the stream maybe I'll
go back into the one of those uh cities
that we were in uh where we had some
open uh side quests and see if I can
finish them
up want to play more tales off first
Tales of game I've seen oh well then
you're starting off with a good one
great game slow start I don't I didn't
really feel like the game start was slow
no actually not at all I felt like for
example tast of Symphonia felt kind of
slow to
[Music]
me without
deal he but then you mean that it's too
difficult not too slow because the DLC
just made me stronger made me able to
kill the enemies faster
yeah this is a fast start I think I felt
immersed been a while since I played a
game like that I also felt super
immersed even though I was uh
chitchatting a
lot especially the rinell part got me
and the the zire X law
apart bizer escalates quickly oh I
barely remember unfortunately I have a
really bad memory
I think yeah ceria might have been one
with a slower start as
well oh well I mean it's not
necessarily such a bad thing anyway
but imersion super good sometimes Camp
just sit idle to watch him just be at
the campsite
a that's sweet
M the theia did have a slow start I
still enjoyed it oh I'm glad to hear
that because theal gets a lot of
criticism I'm surprised how much I like
the story oh are you further uh further
than me are you further in the story
ahead than
me cuz I mean until now I personally
even though I know the story is going to
be great until now I can't I can't say
much I am aha
uhhuh uh
uhuh didn't have the DLC playing on hard
difficulty super fun
oh wow you must be an experienced tales
off player
then the victory poses now I don't miss
those they always took too much time for
me yeah and then they were very
repetitive so I'm like okay the first
time see them that it's cute but then
later on it's like I don't want to see
this
anymore I like that you know you can
just jump right on uh back in on the
onto the map immediately
I like
that I'm very
impatient so let's see where we left off
yesterday here four 400 at Super chats
that's a nice yeah yeah I was I wanted
it to end it a nice number all right
400 we're rating anniversary super
chats s d Max the first D tiny Delta
than
need to to open translator son
translate thank
you ASAS ASAS Dan psycho fire 23 Dan
Shadow pencil thanks for the pinky happy
anniversary T we love you thank you for
all that you do thank you for watching
me and supporting me than Ellie Smith
thank you also for the pinky happy
anniversary to the best boss in the
world I'm sure it's been a bit stressful
a bit overwhelming but I'm so glad you
came into mine and many other lives this
past year I love you my O Let's have
another another great year yeah let's do
it and no a great year is ahead of us
I'm I'm glad I can spend it with you
guys to be honest like in the beginning
uh I was like very scared that like I
would [\h__\h] up something and would have
to leave her Al
earlier I was like I'm probably not
going to been in here for long I'm
probably going to [\h__\h] up real
bad I had those
Visions but I'm still here
thankfully I was scared that it would
end so soon
yeah I imagined as much what you thought
that I would [\h__\h] up too or what
H you're here and loved thank you we're
glad you're here with us me
too I always always felt that you were
scared of that really and even though
I'm so scared of that kind of stuff I
still like am way too blunt with all
things and I talk too much and too
open I just can't hold it back I I wish
I could I would be on the safer side if
I could hold back a bit more
[Music]
oh thank you guys but it's definitely a
bit dangerous being as open as I
am thank
you sopie D prototype K oh this is where
we're showing the hook Papa art no my
immersion but seriously T thanks for
holding your fun and entertainment thank
you s Jam Dan Alo Dan to
happy anniversary K I had quited drawing
for a while but watching your stream and
attitude never getting down I decided to
restart my drawing thanks to that I'm
having a lot of fun drawing now hope you
have another wonderful year thank
you thank you thank you you're your
Super Chat and your name is in Japanese
so I'm not sure which language to use to
reply but I guess English is fine thank
you for drawing me please please
continue drawing M believe in yourself
don't give up
yes looking forward to the F you're
going to draw of me in the future
than you 96 than and chocolate Insomniac
thank you for all dear the
the no
uh what do you call like triple
quadruple and what comes after that
what comes after quad
quadruple quable thank you for the
quable red super
chat wow thank you chocolate
Insomniac yeah congrats on the one year
anniversary I can't tell you how much
your streams have cheered me up this
past year I love how you are so caring
and appreciative of your viewers I'm
glad to be a part of K P I haven't been
able to watch the entirety of your
streams but I try to when I can thank
you Tano my oi long live kfp thank you
long love Cy
indeed thank you I'm I'm very very happy
that I could Sher you up then I could
have a good effect on you and your life
that makes me very happy I'm honored to
be part of your life thank you so
much please continue supporting me
watching my streams I would be very very
happy to have you around thank you so
much and Korean
name ah I'm come for the pink Super Chat
no happy one anniversary thank you so
much for your
support I hope I hope you will stay for
a long long time cuz a lot of the Korean
Bros only just joined recently so I want
you guys to stay uh very very long and
let's make nice memories together
okay
Canon wait another Korean
one com D Red Room D late 0560 thank you
for the red
is that bgm too quiet I think it's a bit
too
[Music]
quiet there you go how about
now we
still the base is so
strong now it should be
okayish it's hard to believe it's been a
whole year since I met this crazy group
of people what you mean myth or do you
mean
kfp it's been a wild ride but I feel
incredibly blessed to have come here
thank you for all your hard work here's
some many more great times in the future
glory to KF Viva thank you must be both
yeah yes the answer is
yes thank you
Nate I'm glad so many people could find
a community where they feel like they
belong too yeah that's that's really
nice I I found that
too I I feel like I belong to kfp and
kfp belongs to
me I don't want to lose you guys thank
you Nate for the red super chat please
keep on supporting
[Music]
me Mr J Dog 137 D Jonathan Brown d
Rafa I'm
hungry
rer D mng nut D hat thank you for the
red super
chat happy one year your streams have
been a definite bright spot in this
crazy Year stay fantastic and wishing
all the best for the future thank you I
also have you I also hope you have a
very successful and bright future as
well I'll send over my Phoenix luck to
you thank you hatch appreciate it very
much I'll do my best Kim danash
Battleship Bismark danash aranx 725
danan Soul eer Evans danash and
[Music]
Kar thank you for the r Super Chat
please send my regards to hook
Papa thank you thank you everyone for
welcoming hook Papa so kindly thank you
I'm really glad he could come such a
special day for
me it was an honor for me to speak to
him too I think I think you all should
have been honored to be in his presence
he's a god he's a Legend Y and his voice
is not something very public not many
people get to hear his
voice
yeah thank you thank you Stan for the
red of chat and the support
simply uh how do I read your
[Music]
name thank you
danen H danen for the red super chat
thank
you happy first anniversary now we going
to ask you to do stream to do something
to me just here to give you a little
support and tell you that you are
already amazing on every single stream
and yes you're still my oi even council
deut do yourself be happy oh thank you
thank you I'm I'm happy to hear that the
council members are very sweet but I'm
glad that the chickens stay in their CP
yes thank you so much for the support H
to much love to
you thank you let's have lots of fun
together until the second anniversary
all
right and also yeah someone said in the
chat abouta like artist voice being rare
and all that it it's definitely rare for
like male artists cuz like for the for
the female for the masam they even I've
I've seen you know collaborations and
all that and them becoming vtubers
themselves they definitely have an
easier time like collabing with their
daughters um and I'm a bit I'm a bit
jealous uh for that I got to say I wish
I could do it that much um without
worrying about it but I do see like you
know I mean it's not like someone told
me I can't but also hookup is busy and I
don't you know yeah it's just like I
know the mindset of this
industry
yeah communicates with his tablet more
than talking during his panels at conss
oh is that
so yeah I mean yeah it's just nice to
see you know something like with seeing
them together oh or Nai mama with her
daughters aw it just makes me feel like
it's so nice what they have being able
to communicate so open with your own
artist it feels like something that
should be a bit more
normalized
yeah yeah still we
[Laughter]
Mama maybe maybe I will or I want to
steal Nai Mama Nai mama is very sweet
na
mama
mama I remember that I don't know bacon
53 D thank
you oh thank you the F Harry pun
Adam Dr RJ
nefar d boy d g thank you for the red
super chat
T you shouldn't was I must I'm etly
grateful to you for helping me get
through the last year you're a wonderful
talented Phoenix not chicken true and
the best boss ever thank you for letting
me out of the usual room to write this
Tel I don't remember sending you in
there all right then I Al I also don't
remember letting you out of
there
suspicious
mysterious but okay for now I guess for
the anniversary it's
forgivable thank you so much for the
love and the support
gra please continue watching me I I'll
work hard I'll work hard to make all of
you very
proud thank you so
much
FL excessive boot bjm time D oh my God
bad D you are D Al CA thank you for the
pinky happy anniversary attention nice
new office thank you I'm so excited to
have it I love these kind of like really
detailed nice backgrounds to chill in I
always loved amma's office and I thought
you know Teno has to have her own office
as well right if I'm like a huge
CEO of a worldwide fast for chain I need
that too
H we're going to spending a lot of time
in here what else do you guys think we
could use besides the kitchen your usual
room the
office what else do you guys think we
need you know what would maybe be cute a
chicken
cop a rest no the freezer why is there
so many people saying the freezer
a chicken C cop would be cute
no like just a lot of hay and then
fluffy chickens all
around t d my chickens
everywhere those ideas oh my God no it's
not a slaughter
house
what you guys are partially crazy are
you aware that your ideas are
crazy The coai
[Music]
partially I'm too kind true
P thank you also for the
pinky I appreciate
it thank
you oh yeah I've noticed that well thank
you for being here IM lookas D po me
danin thank
[Music]
you Daniel Alex sh big hands thank you
for the Super Chat VI Lana happy
anniversary you burn bright and fly even
higher looking forward to whatever you
have coming up in the future me too and
I'm super excited to soon soon soon show
you all of our new outfits I will tell
you I will tell you my favorite is uh
Callie's and am and Ena and uh goodas
[\h__\h] I love all of them so much they
have all of their outfits oh my God
I I love all of their new outfits so
much that narrows it
down I think uh um I might be a bit more
um critical of my own
outfit cuz whenever I I saw the other
girls outfits I was like oh
man they're slaying it oh
man mine is pretty too yes yes
but when I saw the others oh
dear I like mine too I like mine too but
when I when I see the others I I I I
lost my
breath I lost my
breath as always is just so fashionable
because Nai mama has insane fashion
taste she got that
female female sense to
it yeah yeah yeah
and
uh yeah I I I will not say more than
that besides maybe that uh you know
you's Papa just never misses like he he
just has I I said this before but he
could like design clothes for Paris
fashion
runway yeah
like like everything everything he
draws it's it's so detailed and and it
has this special taste to
it no I'm not hating on my own Papa
guys
but
Papa he uses all these intricate
patterns and the layers of clothes and
all that
M it and it looks so beautiful he and
the colors he uses they are so like
calm and they match so
well did you have input in the outfit
like last time oh yes I did yes yes yes
I did definitely have
input yes
okay I am
[Music]
a meow d t d hello sunshine
D thank you
[Music]
the oh that's where Mama came on the
phone yes yes kabu
[Music]
999 Anonymous
as Alat 131 D oh my stomach just said
feed
me I'm I'm I can't wait for day three of
uh chili con Cara it was really good
yesterday as well I still have so much
left over I wonder how long I can eat it
like today should be fine but I have
enough to eat tomorrow as
well I wonder if it's still going to be
good tomorrow what do you guys think
today is day
free you think it could be fine in on
day 4 to I've been have it's in the
fridge
oh I'm so
[Music]
hungry you be
fine okay
okay okay okay okay oh I'm so
[Music]
hungry I don't know how I can
survive I want to read for like 3 hours
so that we can make progress although
there a lot less pinks and reds right
now so we can't actually really make
progress meme dreams d yxc d arakia d
red D Kuru D spanking thank you for the
red super
chat thank you so much mamaon for giving
us this beautiful talented and funny
bird breed thank you thank
you I will tell her I'm seeing her on
the weekend actually um the reason why
I'm going is it's a
birthday yes
yes yes I'm seeing my brother too and my
sister as
well yes otherwise uh yeah I would still
stay at home and do my streams be busy
and all
that yeah yeah thank you thank thank you
I'll tell things don't make a big deal
out of
it how can we Super Chat your mom for
your birthday um she is definitely kind
of receiving your super chats in a way
cuz um um I'll I'll be funding some
stuff for her house yeah as a birthday
present don't worry about it you guys
are basically helping
out and Emerald Ruby D pokeon 276 D just
iron D Patrick Chan D tuna thank you for
the red super
[Music]
chat congratulations Mama debut this is
for you no no why the hell my mom does
not have a vtu debut okay don't
misunderstand I'm under under
there thank you for the love Crimson
comment than Ramy D Butters D is that D
Sebastian ler d d ice lemon patri d f d
sergeon caveman D CR Angels D
snan D thank you for the uh red Super
Chat you and your mom are so cute please
take this and give it to Mama to okay
okay
okay we'll
do this
thank you please tell your mom that if I
ever become a parent I want to be like
Mama and hope her cold goes away soon
oh you want to be like Mama as in
letting your games play letting your
games play your children uhhuh letting
your children play
games yeah I think that's fine but I
think um you know when when when I was a
child long long long time ago
uh people around me like children around
me definitely had phones
but shitty phones and not as young as
the as as children have them now
nowadays so and now nowadays children
with like 9 years or 8 years or 7 years
depending on how spoiled they are even
have like iPads and [\h__\h] so I think when
it comes to that you should I I would
hold back I would not give them
I mean maybe a phone because it can
definitely result in bullying bullying
if everyone in their school has a phone
and then your child doesn't I I can see
how that would yeah result in bullying
but stuff like a [\h__\h] iPad or so is
not really necessary I would
say yeah so as long as uh as long as
possible I would want to hold back on
that cuz I don't think it's good how
children under 15 or 14 1 years old have
tablets and stuff just makes no sense to
me focus on your [\h__\h]
school for God's sake yeah no need to
have two yearold sister has a smartphone
take it away throw it in the trash burn
it no [\h__\h] way I mean okay I
understand that the lot the parents like
let their babies and all that toddlers
use um uh tablets for like children's
games okay as long as it's like not too
much I guess but still that already
makes them like if you start doing that
too early they're always going to like
ask for screen time like TV and phone
and they just won't stop trying to touch
it and and and they will scream and
yell constantly right when they don't
get it
that's I mean how I imagine it so I
don't know once you start it it's going
to be too late so try to like keep it
away from your freaking child sorry
sorry child as long as possible I I
broke the microphone
sorry
yeah they're going to throw a fit if you
take the freaking tablet away
oh ah tea is drinkable
[Music]
we need to mature kids faster so that
they can handle
Tech
ah but I don't think that's
necessary I don't think you need your
8-year-old child to be able to handle
Tech or even your 15-year-old child
maybe with with 18 okay okay they can
that would be cool if they can handle
Tech and all that probably helpful with
like school stuff at that
point maybe in high school I think it
will be fine depending on the school
like maybe for high school a laptop
laptop would be useful I think I I
remember uh the high school that I went
to the art school I think um some of
the
classes kind of like needed a laptop
I'm not sure I don't remember it's like
a thousand years
ago yeah I think with 15 it's fine to
have a tablet by then no no yeah but I
mean tablets are mostly shitty anyway so
just give them a freaking laptop or a
PC I don't know I'm not the tablet type
of person I have one but I never use it
anyway yeah
h a
gin wait there's so much oh my
God
[Music]
a h
no what
what I read that properly once it comes
up
but wait why did you change your name
then who are you and what did you do
with the other
[Music]
names thank you so
sweet I'm 5 14 are you going to yell at
me for donating yes why did you do that
you shouldn't be donating you're too
young keep that pocket money keep
[Music]
it keep it keep it keep
it what another
one thank you
girl girl
is this how I pronounce your name thank
you thank you I'll read it properly once
I finally reach it but hey we've already
read 100 super chats I'm already at
300 yeah even with some
tangents
so Dom
Bishop K thank you for the r chat than
your happy anniversary I wish you
another Good Year by the way I know
you're busy but this portal opened up a
kfp and an elder creature came out of it
saying chicken for customer I gave him
chicken but forgot to ask for money no
usual room
please interesting you know how that
reminds me of that game that my mom
played that I told you guys about um
keep on forgetting the name
[Music]
oh what's it called the enter
Enterprise sash Titanic yes yes yes yes
there's this robot I think in there that
asks you to put chicken in it I
think wait let me look at
up Starship Titanic and that was always
so
funny
Chicken
St or am I going crazy was that another
thing did it not ask for
chicken Starship Titanic full walk for
one and a half hours wait that was just
a short game
I didn't see it as such a short
game I can't find anything about it was
that not
[Music]
chicken that that's the
robot I want to play this game Starship
Titanic it's so
[Music]
good ah you know the game a prime
ring I I have to ask for permissions for
this game but who who published it cuz
it's so old I might not get permissions
uh Starship
Titanic it's from
1988 1998 holy [\h__\h] uh the digital
Village oh no that's not the publisher
Simon Schuster Interactive night
Studios I wonder I wonder it's on
Steam yo that's already a good
thing that old [\h__\h] game is not
abandoned wear that's already a good
thing publisher night dive Studio okay
let's [\h__\h] go I'm going to request
permission for
this you guys will love it it's such an
old game but I I think you will love it
I hope so I I mean I I only remember it
from when I was very
small but it's so old school so
stupid yeah
okay don't play it without me a Gothic
oh I think that would be funny too yeah
[Music]
H I remember like dabbling a little bit
in goic when I was younger I was just
too young to play it normal but I I did
try it out a little
bit
okay I'm feeling 22 wasn't that a
song that's a
song goic would be sick
oh all right I'll try to make your dream
come true at some point anyway Cal cor
thank you for the red super
chat J
jid bench S7
Captain jerk pant D for the pinky pepp
syia Dominic k
[Music]
fore
for for
[Music]
next D in the size of D deser thank you
for the pinky happy one year anniversary
throughout this past year I have
struggled with finding a passion for art
again and I found you over time you
ultimately became myi and looking
forward to spending more time with you
and K thank you so much thank you thank
you please keep on doing what you
do please keep on drawing you'll get
better and better and I can use the art
for thumbnails
perhaps yes all according to
Kaku thank you so
much will El thank you for the pinky
frana in the fish tank is just so
cute I would P purposefully misbehave so
I could be called to the office and
watch froy and a SP before I get thrown
to the user room I can't blame you I
wouldn't send you to the usual room for
that I can't blame you look at her look
at her go
spin spin so cute I do the same when you
guys are out of my office I do the same
thing I just keep on looking at her
p q re no
[Music]
a thank you for the red
CH I'm very happy to be a member of kfp
kfp will always support you by the way
mama is so cute no wonder T is also
[Music]
cute thank you her English was pretty
good wasn't it she speaks uh really
really good English thankfully
thankfully if she wouldn't then I
wouldn't be able to have her on the
phone like that I mean we could speak
German but still that's like you guys
would have to go get some
subtitles
yeah h I mean she did have some accent
but that's
cute I expected a heavier accent she
probably would have even less of an
accent if she had more opportunities to
speak English cuz I don't think she has
many opportunities to speak it she might
use it by typing every now and then but
yeah she definitely doesn't have any any
anyone to talk with in English so it's
very very normal that she would have a a
little bit of an accent M did she learn
English for video games I don't know I
don't think she learned it for video
games but she definitely used it in a
lot of video games
yeah
ah yeah the or so yeah that's very
germanish to say in English I
think yeah
yeah I I I do that too sometimes don't I
does she also say bacon of hope I only
say that because not I know how to
pronounce it but I I don't know bacon
sounds
nicer I love the Oro
really your mom sounds like she kills
Chicken in one hand
hey I mean she probably could but
hey uh I am KS n IP
potato i n k s n i SP D Nami 73 D
rice Kitty
spring Tad thank you for the pinky
congrats on your year of success mama
your fun uh streams have helped me
through many hard times this past year
and helped me smile when it was hard to
do so I can't thank you enough for all
you've done you're the best boss ever
love you oh thank you you are a great
chicken thank you for being part of kfb
and spending your precious time with me
D thank you will Mama to you open your
mic in the next M no no no absolutely
not I even had a dream last night oh God
I had a dream where my mom uh was like
on the stream with me and she said my my
name which is totally kada but still but
uh it freaked me
out stress
streams oh man
your real name isana oh
maybe legally change your name to
birdie happy birthday EST
rer happy birthday
green wo thank you for the red super
chat I would never send an empty red so
I'm trying to come up with something
meaningful to say but I'm drawing a
blank
today you're just so fantastic in all
that you do that it takes my breath away
drives me crazy makes my mind go blank I
really don't know what to do oh wait is
that a rainbow it is are you just going
to stall for the whole
rainbow with my I don't know what to do
with myself even even though you're all
I can think about a lot of the time I'm
having difficulty turning those thoughts
into words gosh this is already too long
for one red I guess I'll make it a
rainbow maybe that will give me enough
space to think of
oh think of something good to say I'll
try organizing my thoughts based on
different things I love about you okay
here we go your singing is definitely
worth mentioning all three of The
Originals and such bangers I fell in
love of each one from the first time I
heard them and still listen to them all
regularly thank you that is a huge
compliment for me the covers are
excellent as well now I just need to
think of how I'll turn this into a
meaningful message nope still nothing
coming to mind oh jeez I'm getting close
to the rainbows limit now why can't I
just think of
good one second
[Music]
please one second please
one second
please need to get my [\h__\h] button in
here it doesn't quite work well here
does it though um was the um I think I
need a button on my table or
something doesn't quite work well
here how do I do that h i mean if
they're behind the
table let's
see in front of me behind the table
I mean I have to put down my
handle where did it
go huh where is
it oh no
uh where did it
go I can't find it I lost it well anyway
you go to the usual room green welder
green
Wilder
incredible incredible how you put on my
ear on my anniversary you managed to
stall and ride a pretty empty Super Chat
while using up all the letters as
well ah
man wasn't he
immune but it his immunity must be gone
by now anyway he's going to the usual
room I can take away his immunity in an
instant
but thank you GRE there there were some
some kind words in there like you liking
my music and all that so thank
you for all the love you were trying to
to uh you're trying to test me but I see
what you're doing there thank you thank
you for all the support I'm glad you're
here at kfp
still yeah and I hope you're here to
stay thank you so much San
bangas H Aon thank for
[Music]
the we really really really really
really really really really love you
than you I really really I really really
really really really really really love
you too thank you
[Music]
Le D Deli
Ivan chil
P 94 super
translate and crony's foot rest d Mama
to's boyfriend here oh did you change
your name congrats on the one year
anniversary you're one of my favorites
and your lengthy tangents never failed
to be incredibly entertaining thank you
for all your heart work I'm proud to be
a member of kfb thank
you I need to drink more tea before it
gets cold
needs more honey dough Rose suppose
thank you for your red
chat congratulations K on your oneyear
anniversary so happy for you love your
streams and hoping for many more in the
years to come g t thank you so
much I hope so to I hope I hope I can do
much much more to entertain you guys
yeah I want to stream a lot and make you
all happy make nice memories with you
guys so yeah please please continue
following me supporting me on my journey
please thank you
Rosa love aalin danash USS anime dd24
danash lemon M wrong Dain D Moonlight
D thank
[Music]
you D I'm I'm proud thank you for the
pinky no words of it but still thank you
so much for sending
it h rainbow gazelle D IO kfp D Girls
Generation d
[Music]
speaker T thank you for the red super
chatow it's all in Chinese
[Music]
though thank you thank you thank you
thank you I understand Google Google
told me what you were saying thank you
so much F
Gia please continue supporting me you
are a precious member of
kfp and you can't you can't quit your
job anyway
so looking forward to working with you
in the future as
well yeah am Mar thank you for the pinky
congratulations on your first year
anniversary my oi your bright
personality and beautiful voice have
brought so much happiness into my life
thank you for the ups and downs I'm so
proud of you and look forward to the
future big hugs thank you much hug back
back to you thank
you thank you for being so sweet and
kind
Don naked
chicken
donkey SE kitten D or should I say jeffu
or jellal chicken chicken kitten kitten
you of course you cat totally Chon D
counting chickens D how many are there
1.9
million thank you for the red super
chat fire chicken it just sounds so good
it has a nice ring to it cuz it kind of
rhes with
kitten
chicken at 1.9 not
1.9 still far away from that let's let's
get there
someday sorry you're a cat of course no
don't go home stay this is your
home you can't leave I need you here
okay I need to be I need you to be
fluffy and cute and
purring so counting chicken says that
was a beautiful letter thank you for
continuing on and doing your best every
stream I feel so lucky to have found my
oos in you without doing anything to
deserve all this what do you mean why
you I don't deserve
this I
don't thank you for being here with me
counting
chickens you're one of the greatest
chickens Al life did you know that thank
you so
much m ah you fluffy cute
chicken thank you
guys thank you my tea is getting
cold I didn't by the way I didn't take
that bath that I said I would take last
night I ended up doing other stuff like
booking my
vacation so I will try to take it today
it's actually still so early and I'm
already like almost at at
200 I'm progressing so fast is just the
power of tanging tanging
less tanging tandi
[Music]
chicken yes stink Jo shut up
no no no
no h j was moral D toan thank you for
the red super chat thank
you no no words with it why why thank
you
toan I appreciate
it and Jackson
FB thank you for the
[Music]
red for
clumsy hero Dan K thank you for the
pinky happy anniversary Tel thank you
for giving me so much happiness than
thank you for giving me so much
happiness without you guys I would be
depress with Pressel you know that do
you know
that thank you rber is like the moment
he hears me speaking German he's
like have to translate this for
everyone k d Domin D IO D baby little
thank you for the pinky happy 1e
anniversary boss Mom thank you my child
my chicken my employee thank you for
being
here see you in the next anniversary and
hopefully every day in between
K 100 D not a good username 360 D Jose
Jose bong
d
d ho D night flash 320 D kryptox 8536 D
we're at 200 now we're at halfway
through
t
uh do I wrate this in Japanese
[Music]
hope you're having fun with t of R oh
yes I did I'm having a blast can't wait
to play
more it's going to be a long long long
playthrough though I I think so I hope
you guys are up for that until the end I
hope
so mj7 dun m d Anonymous 247 and thank
you for the red super chat yes yes I am
really yes yes ma'am I don't think it's
too long really I want it to be long I
don't want it to end too
early for the sake of the stream I don't
want it to be too long like I would hope
maybe it wouldn't be as long as Yakuza
maybe for example but for the sake of
myself as a tailes off fan I want it to
be
endless I'm like 40 hours in and still
going on so
o 40 4 40ish hours 50 to 70
yeah I think as a streamer I might be
slower than you guys though because of
the voice acting and also because I
think if you if you don't stream then
you definitely like go for all the text
uh quicker the all the dialogues even if
you read them right I I I let it like I
try to let it go uh like like run out on
its own like because the voice acting I
don't want to inter upt it if if the if
there's vo Parts but like I think normal
players would just like interrupt it as
soon as they're done
reading normally not everyone of course
but I think Mo most
people yeah but side quests those those
side quests are like seem very
unnecessary to
read yeah because at the end they tell
me okay they want two chicken breasts
that's it all right there you go it's
not that like they don't tell me very
critical
information
I shut
up that was you guys I didn't think of
it that way anyway so Anonymous says as
a fan to an idol did I already read this
as a fan to an idol I love you very very
much thank you you for everything thank
you I'm glad I'm glad that you know
because I love Idols I'm glad that they
see me as an idol but at the same time I
want you to see me as um something more
personal I don't I mean we're not never
all of us okay this is like real talk we
all we're never going to be like you
know intimate friends or whatever but um
I don't want you guys to see me as like
a super celebrity pop ster like that's
absolutely untouchable like Rihanna or
Lady Gaga or so cuz that's not true I
obviously love interacting with you guys
and I want you I want you guys to see me
as more than just an
idol
yes
yes thank you gag shell D Bry be d jxt d
thank you guys
[Music]
strawberry dreams than and melty claw
than and MH than you for the
py oh yeah the time for cringe totally
didn't tear up during the L T you
will'll always be around to watch you oh
thank you I guess I was right before the
debut one to long but that really wasn't
as cringe as I thought it would be maybe
it was only Me Maybe did you guys cringe
more at my Deb stream then I did was it
that bad I don't think it was that that
bad nope Lov it no no no no oh there you
go wow okay see I'm proud of myself for
putting on a decent debut stream
then although I think it's also great if
if the debut stream is cringe because
that's just funny to look back on and
it's understandable to be um scuff and
cringe in the
beginning I guess it's funny to look
back on I was a bit disappointed at the
lack of cringe
only a little bit though generally I'm
proud of the way I did
it yeah according to the circumstances
of having a [\h__\h] microphone
[Music]
I'm happy that you are proud of your old
self I am I am I am also proud of um me
before hell
life for working so hard and enduring
and not giving up trying my best even
when things weren't looking
[Music]
good
yes got to be proud of myself
AF Venom Lea Woods Dan blue Dan Daisy
dad Dan him D every another cult thank
you for the red super chat T we love our
hot
wings so proud of you and how you've
grown can't wait to see you Unleash Your
Idol dancing skills when you finally do
live
performances yes I can't wait either but
I have to
wait but I already have like an image of
my in my head of what I would do I would
definitely perform all of my songs and
who knows maybe until then I already
have another a fourth song who
knows I can see it yeah and uh I I I
already know like what what I want what
I would want my room to look like I
think it's pretty obvious right and
there's a reason why I didn't make um
the the wall
why I didn't request for like a kfp for
the Wolfie um uh 3D thingy cuz I was
like I want that to be U um my room in
the
future so I was like what else could I
do and I honestly couldn't think of much
besides kfp so I I went with like a cute
outside Park and I I wanted chickens to
be walking around unfortunately the
chickens were not implemented but it was
still very cute I like the I like the
little Park area with some mountains in
the background
oh I didn't even talk about I didn't
even request the mountains but I'm very
glad that they put those in there cuz it
felt a little bit like I was in the
middle of the Alps
h no I didn't even I didn't even request
the the the mountains but that was uh
really cool was a nice touch
out I just wasn't Crea enough to think
of much more than freaking
Park
yeah what happened to the chickens in
the store I don't know I don't know I
wasn't there I don't
know stop questioning me I'm your
boss anyway thank you every another cold
thank you please continue watching my
streams and enjoying yourself and yeah
take care of
yourself KY Papa thank you K Papa sent a
Super Chat also actually in English well
I'm sure he will probably not hear this
message of me replying but
congratulations on your first
anniversary K it's my hope that K's
second year of activities will be more
enjoyable thank you Papa
what are those dot dot dots what are you
what are you what are you
implying I'm not implying anything so
don't you imply anything
evil yeah the God riger himself yeah KY
po looking forward to um continue
working with KY
Papa and and see what he does with my
body C the mo thank you for the red
super chat
[Music]
m happy one year anniversary I have
enjoyed your content since your debut
and it has been amazing to see your
growth your passion and hard work to be
realized through streams and songs you
are an engaging Entertainer and I
excited to see how you will grow from
here thank you yes I always try to
[Music]
engage I try to uh let my community feel
like they're part of the stream somehow
um even when I'm playing a game where
there is no audience
participation because like I I would
feel like if I was watching if I was
among thousands of people watching a
stream and the stream is just not
reading comments and just not having a
conversation just not even like doing
anything besides reading the dialogue
and the game and all that I just don't
like that kind of streaming style it
might be entertaining for some people
but not for me so I want to I want to um
design my streams and uh in a way that
it would be enjoyable for me yeah I'm I
mean today I was a little bit too I mean
not too focused but I was pretty focused
on the story and I didn't have many
tangent stories today for you guys uh
and I always always try I always try to
bring out some stories here and there
but sometimes my brain is just empty and
I can't think of
anything but generally I think um the
way I'm doing it uh by trying to let you
guys feel that you you matter and that I
I can't about you
guys I think I think it's
working
yeah so I want you guys to be
interactive as well with the comments
yeah if if I weren't talking and
answering the comments every once in a
while then what's what's the point in
commenting in the first place right I
want to give you guys the motivation to
[Music]
comment
yeah yeah so thank you to everyone who's
commenting I know there's a lot of
lurkers here as well which is fine I
guess but still I appreciate all the
people who are commenting yeah thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
are you motivated are you
motivated lurk gang lurk gang stop
lurking come out no need to l
multiv I need to stop using memes that I
have no connection
with anyway C thank you M M M Soul 94 D
rain D Cur Mur d m eight thank you for
the red super chat the original mic is
finally here happy anniversary K
continue continue to patiently wait for
Oren's 3D live that reminds me yeah the
IC is that how you pronounce it or is it
um I I think it's Umi
right um very surprising I thought it
was just like one like random collab but
they're like making a big thing out of
it and that made me think wow can we
have uh support from C for H and Oren
too I think I think H is like definitely
deserves to be like a officially
recognized group like that because we
have been around for a while now and uh
it's actually even more International
than umii because we got
two uh whole Ian members with one of
them being in Europe and the other one
God who knows where and then we have one
from Indonesia Arena and one from Japan
actually Su speaks pretty
decent English so actually collabing in
English shouldn't even be much of a
difficulty so I want to I want to
pressure them to support
H recognize them as a group us as a
group I think H needs needs to be a
thing and yeah I'm I want to still do a
hororo horor too collaboration before
doing a full member collaboration with M
because we still haven't done that and I
feel like we should
the tur do exactly exact yeah yeah yeah
I love all of why are there so many
freaking fitting names it's just so
perfect yeah tur ducking needs to happen
and then afterwards I want to include M
nothing against M but uh I was just kind
of like always feeling like tur duckin
uh needs uh needs to be um
collabing at some point until now it
didn't happen so I don't know maybe I
need to start the
planning oh I think like super and ARA
and me all three of us are actually
pretty much the type of person to start
conversations and start um uh
collaborations and and plans and all
that but for some reason none of us have
gotten to it yet I don't know why I just
don't understand why we're very open all
of us are very um
extroverted
H yeah maybe we're just all too busy I
that definitely is true for me I've just
been too
busy you know what you know what I'm
going to do it right now so that I don't
forget about it opening a group right
now include
[Music]
for for
okay okay I did it I did
it it's happening it's happening love
you Kiwa thank you fine I'll do it
myself exactly exactly that's the
spirit I wrote some pretty funny text in
Japanese though I was like well well
well everyone from H mum has become a
Holo burp now as well but don't you
agree that the fact that we haven't
collabed as fre people until now is
unforgivable let's collab soon as Free
People come
on and then afterwards let's collab of
Lumi yes yes
got to do it yourself so and with orens
don't worry we got to for mouin I know
you I know you support orang and I'm
really happy about it thank you Oren's
best Idol group I'm telling you uh we're
going to do a Minecraft collab for sure
soon and we are planning to do something
Musical together as
well uh so please look forward to that
although we've been talking about that
for ages and just been both so busy uh
that's barely barely barely moving on
but we're working on
it yes so thank you
mavin Thomas night of crispy chicken d
as Maria Moon Dan not a good username
d arent
d
wild is that how I read your
name thank you for the sweet Super Chat
the great Billy maze
D how do I read this
[Music]
thank you for the
red no no not an original no maybe in
the future though but it's not going to
be an
original thank you for being with us for
a whole year you have been a great
source of inspiration for us please
continue with us for several more years
take much Mama thank
you thank you so much oh
I'm planning on doing it for as long as
possible so you better stay with me now
that you're asking me to stay longer you
better stay as well all right AA
K it's a
promise yeah thank you for your love and
your
support let's have lots of fun
together thank you thank you for being
here to celebrate my celebration
celebrate my anniversary brain
[Music]
empty PCX 436 than Shar Elvis thank you
for the red super
chat
say oh you're doubting my sayess of this
you want to go to the usual R what
nothing says about my
sness from from the I mean at least in
my w
stream but celebrate my celebration with
was actually not that wrong though
anyway Elvis thank
you isn't he already in there he
probably
is ice ice thank you for red super chat
too H yes I am say ID thank you thank
you at least someone gets
it uh is my playlist already done all
right
continuing dreaming
days happy anniversary thank you for
everything intenal love you
forever really thank you I love you too
thank you for your support I hope you
enjoyed the anniversary stream and the
time up until that I don't know how long
you've been around but I hope it was a
fun time for you than ice
ice flower
[Music]
thank
you Hy M thank you for the red
[Music]
Jet and we love you too
wow happy anniversary tento thanks for
giving us respite from daily life and
wish you all the best the Phoenix was
always my favorite mythological being oh
and you live true to that my oi long
live the Phoenix long live kfp long live
Taki love you T
thank
you long live the Phoenix easy you don't
even have to chant that I live eternally
pretty much
so but uh yeah it's the fault that
counts right thank you thanin I'll do my
best to stay
alive as actually no I I wouldn't mind
uh Reviving soon I want to do another
debut stream it's been such a long
time come on
come for me
Shinigami come for me I challenge
you thank you Kandy
me yeah I hope you're I hope you're
enjoying your time of
kfp Lon Edge L Lun Lage Lun Edge thank
you for the pinky
than I appreciate it but charie you're
here thank you Centennial robot D Kevin
Young D
fair fair fair D Unity chat un chat
where you at thank you for the red super
chat I'm not a day one chicken cuz I
watched H Ian with a delay oh no problem
no shame in that and I don't even know
exactly when but at some point you
became my f
f and right now you are my oi I'm so
proud of your growth I'm looking forward
to see you continue to flourish within
the whole life family thank you I hope
you can say the same thing to me and one
you telling me that I grew and that I
flourished and all that I hope I hope
you can say the same thing without it
being a
lie I will work hard to improve myself
thank you very much for all the love and
support you've been very active I see
you every now and then in the chat so
thank you so
much I want to say better stuff yeah
that would be even better that would be
better but I'm I'm worried that I cannot
live up to people's um expectations um
so at least the same thing would be
nice thank
you what
why what is that Korean Super Chat
[Music]
yo boying well I'm scared even more
now it feels like they're in control
shouldn't it be K in control
[Music]
hey Bo
o you guys should be scared
too thank you moon dog for the rainbow
it's a
rainbow are you here in the chat M Dog C
I will definitely say that you are by
far my favorite stream up
[Music]
really even though with many new friends
to watch including the space herself
she's awesome s is
great you are still and will be my oi
I'm so happy to see grow you see you
grow as a glorious Phoenix you are are
you are here y so congrats on your one
year anniversary you have been the best
and cutest boss chicken boss a chicken
could ask
for nice nice safe there
oh that was close you actually did ride
the cutest boss a chicken could ask for
a chicken not the boss chicken could
ask close I thought you were
saying something your by here for a
moment I'm excited to continue watching
and seeing what you have in store for us
we at kfp love you I don't know what to
put at the end of the rainbow can you
pet p smooy and chus for us of course I
do it constantly I do it constantly
they're probably annoying with but at
the same time Smoothie chonus has always
been like super super super attached but
smoy has been stepping up the game and
oh my God you know what in the past 3
days or so
I've seen chunkers um really briefly but
surprisingly uh
needing
bread in a very clumsy way though she's
really bad at it really bad because she
gets stuck in the blankets constantly
and then keeps on ripping out the FRS
which is okay it doesn't really make
much of a difference but um she's really
bad at it and she only does it for like
a couple of seconds but I've never seen
her do that before in the in the past
few days she's been doing it for a few
seconds at a time and I'm like I was
like yesterday night she was doing it
like right right in front of me and I
was
like what's happening girl chunk CH my
baby you learned how to make
bread you learned how to make
cookies she was making bread but needing
my bed
[Music]
yes yeah I was so proud I was so happy
does that mean that she's that she's
like happier than usual she was always
happy though always happy but now she's
making bread and cookies and the Really
clumsy bad bread
yeah the claws she's just clumsy she's
just a stupid little clumsy
cat so sweet y
biscuits
yeah yeah she's massaging chimpin in her
dreams must have been inspired by my
cooking streams oh Perhaps
Perhaps oh thank you
nagil all right Moon thank you so much
for the rainbow very very kind and
generous of you thank you so much I
really appreciate it oh thank you for
the membership
Kaman thank you
Dr shaky Jones D David ask you too D
amazing Sam J D
SES thank you o for the
[Music]
pinky only D NY the noon Merchant thank
you for two
pinkies
H you've grown so much since the debut
you've been a great inspiration and
watching how much you able to help
others open up has made me want to open
up more and more you've lit a fire in
all our hearts and I'm sure I'm Not The
Only One chasing the dreams of all their
heart now thanks to you
a oh thank you for the membership what a
sweet
membership
hello what a sweet name I
mean I'm no longer just laying on the
floor but instead out there kicking my
feet against the table to the feet of my
own Dr hey you did that dja thank you
for being a o a son a oh man that is so
sweet thank you that is a
a that's so kind and sweet thank you
stream Sparks by the
way I'm sure you are streaming it though
Noy thank you I'm I'm really glad that
you're able you were able to get up just
like a
phoenix and work towards your goals and
dreams pleas pleas continue doing
so never stop believing in yourself okay
thank you
NY
than you need to CH
[Music]
than for the red
super congrats on one year anniversary T
theum can't believe it's already been
one year you really H did a hard effort
for this whole thing really happy for
you yes yes I I've put a lot of effort
in the whole year and in the anniversary
stream I don't know which one you meant
but both is true both is uh
accurate thank you for watching me and
uh supporting me for a long long time
watching over me even when I do stupid
things which I do
often yeah thank you so much m
green Wilder D oh you did
nice nice good job chetnik tashin plus
good thank you for the red super chat
happy anniversary K I wasn't there for
the debut as I didn't get into whole
life until late November and yet it
feels so long already it does doesn't it
thank you for making a mediocre here
into a wonderful one bus thank you for
everything you out my wonderful aie
thank you if you ever get the
opportunity I would love love to hear
what got you into whole life I always
love hearing those kind of stories so
yeah very interested thank you plus good
for the support I'm glad you stayed all
the way from November until now let's
make it a full year and an
eternity
than thank you for the red super
chat Cong to my favorite T's first of
anniversary I love your gaming streams
and songs especially Sparks stream SPS
and your clever songs thank you for
bringing joy and cusa to us you're are
the best boss thank you
a it says the same thing on my on my mug
with a coincidence down here yeah that
orange one thank you I'm I'm glad that
it's not not just a lie what's on my cup
I'm glad you think so I will do my best
as an
employer thank you for being part of kfp
stream kusang do waiting to put out a
song that's called
Kusa thank you f thank you for red as
well happy 1y year anniversary Tel it's
a little pity that I can't support you
in the beginning but now here I am as a
loyal K kfp to company with you from now
on I wish you all the best in the future
love you VI L thank thank you it's okay
you don't have to feel bad about that
not being there in the beginning I'm
glad because that means that my
community is
growing thank you very much for becoming
part of kfp I hope you're having a great
time
here lots of love and kisses to
you Ana Dan Kon Dan Jackson FB thank you
for the red super chat hi Oshi congrats
on your first year I haven't been here
very long sorry no problem again but my
mom's here have been so wonderful heck I
even wrote you a report oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah you've been very
passionate thank you it's been such a
wild adventure and I want to say thank
you for giving me a reason to get up in
the morning Big Love Oh you mean because
I stream so early for you so you have to
get up you're welcome you know early
bird catches the worm or something like
that right
I make you guys into healthy chickens by
getting up early and the people on the
other side of the globe I make you guys
into night owls which is fine too isn't
it is it okay is it
okay I'm sorry just watch the archive
please don't force
yourself thank you though
Jackson thank you Shan for being such a
active part of
kfp maybe you can figure out what the
con iion for Tales of Rise money is as
well the g g
conversion it's I I have a feeling it
might be very close to Japanese
Yen um but I might be wrong I'll leave
it to
you A new challenge let's
go the gamster one One D set de loock d
zanini d philipo d c photograph dun K KY
Son thank you for the red super chat by
the way guys I think I can finish those
today the anniversary super chats
Jo I will happily sacrifice sleep for
you anytime thank you but don't feel
forced to do that
please don't don't be so stupid like me
and have a [\h__\h] up sleep schedule for
more than a
year happy morning anniversary Tano
thanks for all the hard work you put
into your streams and music Long Live
kfp keep being
awesome thank you for noticing and
acknowledging my hard
work that does mean a lot to me thank
you Kyler
son I will try to keep being awesome so
you do the same all right ORD 87 thank
you all the red of innocent chicken
noises I don't know where you heard
chickens that must have been innocent
Phoenix noises which may or may not
sound a little bit diff similar but
there's a difference okay thank you
m moose thank you for the red super chat
happy one year anniversary T I can't
believe it's already been one year I
always enjoy your streams it makes me
smile all the time love you ttin wish
you all the best same here I can't
believe it you were I can't believe it
it just feels so fast it's crazy but at
the same time I'm done so many things in
a short
time
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah but I'm very happy that we can
spend this year together in the coming
year as well
my maiden
call feels crazy it's yeah it's weird
it's just weird that time passes so fast
I wanted to
stop yeah yeah she did do a lot in one
year I need to do more that's motivating
me I am motivated Fred screw D Duke fist
D Justin Reinhard FY for a pinky does it
count as say go of you're objectifying
yourself anyways happy anniversary T you
love you thank you no it doesn't I'm
just acknowledging the
[Music]
truth yeah I
mean look at those
hips
yes yes not Lou thank you for the red
super chat congratulations on one year
to the best most hardworking boss in the
world no I could probably still work
harder I feel like other people work
harder than me personally some some some
of them
mhm but um I I did definitely reach my
limit recently so I want to take care of
myself but I I still want to work hard
it's it's difficult difficult to find a
good
balance maybe in the following year I
will find a better balance but thank you
not Lou thank you sh for your love and
your kindness and your generosity
M no one thank you for the red thank you
Teno you have helped me so much love you
really I'm glad to be of help I love you
too thank you for your support
throughout the
year please keep on H receiving Joy from
H life English yeah
I'm sure you will find a good balance
it's hard to find but you will get there
eventually thank
you remember when you said P that helped
you that's how you help us
[Music]
a a
sweet oh thank you an's phone no is that
your side
account an no no out run the wild thank
you for the pinky happy anniversary I
didn't follow you much in the beginning
time zones ah yeah but now you might bgm
at work oh nice let's get through the
day together this year too yes PS I made
lasagna it's in the fridge ask Ena to
portal it over to you if you want some
oh I do want some oh lasagna but no
today is enough a chili concar day I was
thinking actually you could totally put
like chili concar in between like the
Lasagna um layers that would work
totally H would actually add a lot more
veggies uh to
that
yeah new dish I don't I don't think I'm
the first one to do that though I mean I
have done it but yeah I don't know
why that's that's not so
weird no there's nothing weird about
that it's basically the same just plus
plus a little bit more
veggies like corn which I would have
considered putting into my lasag
anyway I like this development of Chef
Ki hey
Chef
oh thank
you boohoo 723 Dan pan Dan Des Dan thank
you for the
FY one year sure has flown by hasn't it
mhm it's been an excellent year of
getting to know you watching you grow
and push through challenges
congratulations on the anniversary I can
express how happy I am to have spent the
last year with you in
kfb it's been an honor
really it's not it's not a given to be
able to have so many viewers I don't
take it for granted that's for sure so
thank you everyone for letting me be
part of your
life yes may it be only a few uh hours
per week or if you watch every
stream then that's a million hours per
week doesn't matter but you're spending
your time with me and I appreciate that
for giving me a
purpose than so much love everywhere Meo
D FAA thank you for the red super chat
which is a rainbow oh rainbow
time thank you so much for my Aussie
happy first anniversary
so many people call me oi these
days even I'm not a kfb at the beginning
but I'm glad to find you we can continue
to create more fun memories kfb will
always be here chickens Will Follow You
Forever that's so cute I just love
imagining a [\h__\h] ton of uh uh cute
chickens following me because they're
imprinted on me you know like little
duckins adorable thank you for doing
your
membership I love you K stream let me
dead happy every time now there is still
Sparks in my head and believe it thank
you oh Oh you mean the song Believe
It same it's a curse thank you for
chilling with us in Super Chat reading
stream thank you thank you
Fafa
VI you're so sweet FAA thank you for
watching my streams
the for the beautiful
rainbow thank you for following me and
believing in me watching my kok streams
and my gaming streams everything thank
you ah all right I totally forgot about
the restream of the German C alga oh
dear
h
i maybe I can do it on Sunday
morning but difficult cuz I'll be on the
road I don't know maybe maybe uh JMA can
end the stream but that would mean I
would have to keep on the
PC no I don't have to keep it on I'll
think about it yeah would be nice to
implement implement it on on
Sunday Patrick Chand James Chand we're
at 100 now guys friendly neighborhood
lesbian danash siton d
random collusion thanks for the pinky
double the K double the fun oh hell
yeah it was nice singing um a song
together with old
Kiana that was
nice thank you for watching random
collusion Matos Al D James MC thank you
for the red super chat this BP is going
places how did you know did you look
into the future did you cheat or did you
just have a feeling for it thank you
James MC for following me for such a
long time thank
you am Dan leici Dan Ren Riven
Dan thank
you wait I think that's at least the
pinky let me read it dear Tel congrats
on your first anniversary I always
sending you super chats in Orange cuz
orange is your color orange suits you so
well and it definitely becomes my friend
favorite color really thank you for
doing this special onee celebration
stream which let me fall in love with
you once again
a thank you for being here with us got
feeling nice even though I didn't join
kfp from the very beginning I'll be
following you to the very end love you
as always my beautiful Phoenix BS thank
you that's great to hear I'm counting on
you okay thank you for your support and
yes the orange color is quite the
beautiful color so thank you for
appreciating it
definitely made me like orange a lot
more a oh
man orange stonks
Rising Diego genovis Thank you for the
red super
chat kada it's been a year already we
kfb couldn't even notice that because
the time we spent together felt like a
wonderful Daydream a we can't be any
more pleased to to be with you in this
journey through all these months
enjoying crying cheering and laughing
with you to the strongest and the most
hardworking Phoenix we know we love you
oh you're too sweet thank
you a I love you thank you so much for
the kind
words thank you from the bottom of my
heart thank you soon I appreciate it
love you
too ra uh Riven R I already read that
one oopsie kfb sha sh robot thank you
for the r Super
[Music]
Chat we're almost done I'm so exhausted
congratulations on your one year
anniversary K we're so proud of you and
all that you've achieved thank you for
all the joy you've brought us and I look
forward to another year of the world's
greatest Phoenix thank you but I'm the
only
one it better stay that way no but um
I'm glad I'm glad that you can say
you're proud of me it makes me happy I'm
proud of myself
too yeah I hope I can achieve many
things in the future thank you for
staying with me and supporting me all
along and celebrating nice anniversaries
and
accomplishments thank you up minty D
seven s thank you for the
pinky m al
super
CHS the anniversary
[Music]
super but it's okay it's okay for those
animal than goodness to
[Music]
for Thomas night now um my voice is
getting crispy
d z pagon
d for the wind d c be D the there you
are d That's not the one for today but
thank
you pascala would be happy to see that
you liked her so much yeah Pua gurus Pua
gurus thank you for the
pinky happy anniversary t i good there
oh enough German have a great second
year we hope hope that your dream of fre
will be
[Music]
fulfilled okay so thank
you thank you
angry don't translate me like
that oh
man no no no no I did not I was not fed
up with people not behaving no no where
bear wrong translation you fired just
kidding no I was getting I I was like
getting mad because there's no free I
was like yo I'm sick of this I'm done
with this I have no more patience I will
explode
Jason thank you for the red super
chat wow it's been a year since you have
debuted time really passes when you are
having fun
yeah it has been a hell of a ride the
ups and downs with how you have come so
far I'm proud to call you my oi I will
support you as long as I can via L thank
you VI
L I think like the first few months were
definitely like a roller coaster until
the time when I moved to um
Australia after that it felt way more
smooth and and calm in a good way well
still being exciting but things were
just smoother and I'm really glad it
calmed down so thank you for staying
with me through Fick and Finn we say
that in German I wonder if you guys say
that in English as well no no you
probably don't it's like the good times
and the bad times we say that in German
as thick and thin do you say that oh you
do ah okay sounded a bit weird to say it
in English thank you
[Music]
Jason fire TR D MVB thank you for the
pinky happy births D in some way it is a
birthday isn't it yeah thank you so
much
[Music]
and uh
r d Maxine D Andreas D J Dan Black thank
you for the red super chat I'm so proud
of this whole journey with you and the
rest of kfp you improved and matured
into the beautiful talented Phoenix are
today here's to more k for many more
days weeks months and hopefully years to
come you inspire me like you wouldn't
believe really see I don't believe it
but I have to believe it believe it
believe it
kiar
K I wish no one would have ever taught
me about that
song Thank you thank
you thank you so much for the kind
loving words black fren you are such a
sweetheart I love you thank
you many many more days weeks months yes
they will
come ra 0429 Dano Angel
V thank you for the red super chat T
that's for an amazing year I can't wait
for the things that are yet to come you
really saved my 2020 and I think you did
so for the entire kfp keep burning
burning bright you wonderful Phoenix
thank you I will I'm an eternal flame I
will never stop
burning thank you so much you guys saved
my 2020 as well would have been such a
[\h__\h] shitty here I can't I can't
imagine how [\h__\h] salty I would have
been at the end of my working holiday if
it weren't for whole life whole life was
the only thing that made that year
decent for
me even even with whole life the working
holiday was kind of a waste so no oh I
would be definitely saltier than
Amo I'm so glad I made it in holy [\h__\h]
holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
yeah holy
[\h__\h] heavy 15 d sein d frag fire D
Arelli Al D fun thank you for the red
super chat happy anniversary T it's
about to think that the entire year has
already gone by but I guess time really
does fly when you spend it with such an
amazingly talented entertaining Earnest
hardworking Phoenix with a rocking body
like yourself yeah
thank you for being you f you got good
eyes good taste I appreciate that thank
you so
[Music]
much I can't speak Japanese anymore
impossible impossible
thank you
Fone you are a Chad yes you know what's
up thank you so much for staying with me
the full freaking year I'm so glad
you're not sick of me yet thank you e
shy d r finded D kakun thank you for the
pinky great Callins mhm great letter mhm
great body mhm where did that one come
from great ending best girl also thank
you hook is a chicken now is a CH Canada
is a chicken is now actually officially
can no it's not don't make it into Canon
no but those sketches were really funny
when I first saw them I was like hook
buba what the
[\h__\h] you kidding
me thank you AK sf2 D Mario's entire
family D aister Channel D random
[Music]
I'm at 50 now hi
and 50
left D thanks for the pinky thanks for a
wonderful year before you deed I was in
a about place just like you watching
your streams nearly every day gave me
strength I needed
and now your anniversary also marks my
first year clean from Dr
oh drugs in the
decade you mean like the real stuff you
call even alcohol drugs right I don't
know what it is but holy
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
congratulations you're amazing
durage let's [\h__\h]
go so proud of you
that's the way to go you can do it you
can do it until the end you can do it
forever I believe in you they good J you
here right
now
respect
respect I hope this reaches you so proud
of you good job good job are you here
nice keep it that way okay other way
otherwise I'll send you to the usual
room and it's not nice in there we know
that we know that you guys want to put
put on your your your rosecolor glasses
and say it's nice on there but we all
know it
isn't we all know it's
not respect yeah thank you I'm glad I
could
help f d Leo how thank you for the red
super chat yep you're our
favorite thank
you I said this uh I said this before
I'm just glad to be someone's favorite
thank you so much for letting me be your
favorite I hope it will not change I
hope I don't disappoint you ever thank
you so much you mean
exany oatmeal
cookie coton thank you for the red super
chat I'm dying I'm melting here happy
anniversary
tenture it's a shame that I haven't been
following you since your first debut and
I of first de I like that you say first
debut are you doing that on
purpose and I often can't watch live
streams but I hope I can support you
forever
VI thank you
I hope so too thank you for supporting
me I love
you indeed oh there you are I was trying
to say I wasn't there in your first de
but have been watching for a couple of
months but ended up making romantical
errors don't worry about it it's just
fine it's perfect it's perfect oh wait
that's a that a
rainbow it is it's a rainbow to
celebrate your first anniversary I
prepared a lasagna for you rainbow
lasagna oh I'm not sure it will be
delicious of course unless you put as
much food food coloring as hot cha does
in it you know that clip that I showed
on H talk where she just put way too
much food
coloring no but this this lasagna seems
tasty nice wait it's a double
rainbow it's a backwards and forward
Rainbow thank you coton am I supposed to
pronounce your name like that the O is
missing but I think it's supposed to or
or siton siton oh
cotton double
rainbow
[Music]
almost yeah H I would like the idea of a
of a rainbow lasagna
you can pronounce however you like all
right if you have no preference and I'll
call you cotton thank you you know what
if you need a title you can give
yourself the title of the kfp um uh what
do you call vesan in English you can
also just add it in German but that's
probably too difficult what's SP the
Stan in English the ear ear cleaning
thingies ear ear
[Music]
ear help
swap cotton swap okay you're now the
cotton
swap c a c c that's probably better
cotton if you need a title you're now
the H kfb
qtip
congratulations you didn't even ask for
it but there you
are
cat kind of gross hey you're gross
nothing gross about
that car Carl D blue D lucky profit d
dster
d Elvis thank you for the pinky just for
tangent wait a second is that a triple
rainbow no but it's like
a 2.5 rainbow holy [\h__\h] from coton
anyway just for tangent
[Music]
tuna Elvis it's been such a long time
I'm actually like kind of amused to see
this two number nines a number n large
and number six with extra dip a number
seven two number 45s one with cheese and
the large soda a few though because now
I really want to go to Burger King and
they're not even open anymore
anyway why do you do this to
me good old times yeah I got a [\h__\h] ton
of those back in the
day that was
funny oh man
Lucy v
unknown Miracle wolf Dan for the pinky
oh my God I'm I'm almost there 19 more
Super chats will go happy first
anniversary my iie I'm very proud and
happy of all the goals you have achieved
this year thank you for always inspiring
me and brightening my days you're the
best you're my number
one let's go thank you I'm glad I can
brighten your days please continue
watching me every day # W # Yol you know
the
[Music]
drill see D India tayl D out of BL D
epic Gamers D Care Project Channel D
Shadow 02 and
pingon Y we did it yo
what are there any other H English
members who finished reading their
anniversary Super Chat so am the first
feel like I'm even the only one who even
started reading
them good luck girls I did it um I feel
like I finished a marathon
let's
go oh yeah my homework is
[Music]
done and I read them all I read them all
all the names all of
them even though you know obviously cuz
it's a exhausting I'm sorry for like um
um sounding a little bit unmotivated
sometimes maybe about reading them I'm
sorry this it's just because it's so
many it scares me but I'm very very very
very
thankful very grateful for all the
insane support you guys once again went
crazy and everyone who was not able to
Super Chat thank you for being there
anyway in the Super Chat reading and in
the anniversary stream and whenever
whenever wherever it doesn't even matter
you are here in my stream and I love you
kfb wherever whenever please watch me
forever hash broken has a yoke T
forever all
right
yeah Shakira
Shakira Shakir sh Shak sh Shak
well here yeah my hips don't lie
you
yes yeah look at those what are
those well well
well I am
oh baby when you talk like
that I am going to actually I think
really take that uh bath
today with bath salts and
stuff
[Music]
so also I'll upload I'll upload the
Skyward Sword uh
archive what do you guys think um
do you be honest do you think that I
should just make the old one public
again do you think it's like okayish or
do you think it's do you also like
relate to me that it's too embarrassing
and I should maybe like not have a
public what do you guys think do you
think it's okay to make it public cuz I
personally feel embarrassing about it
but maybe it's just
me you call reupload Public public
okay your choice your
call
uh yeah but I want to hear your
opinion no no
fear old one is
okay was fine
really cut the end yeah I can't I can't
the thing is I can't I can't cuz the
stream is too long apparently it's what
was what um 4 four or 6 hours maximum or
something like that I don't
know yeah yeah yeah unfortunately it
can't be edited and then just re like
made public again I have to edit it
manually and then re-upload it as a
separate
video oh my second run on Dem eyes was
like speedrun Str it was pretty good for
a moment
yeah h
I mean anyone who would
like watch it until that point and see
that embarrassing
moment would I think be understanding of
why it ended up like
that
[Music]
maybe make a
poll should the old
should should the should the T of Zelda
V be
public yes no
I mean you know what I mean with that
question
[Music]
uh Members Only
I can't I don't think I even can do
that or can I no I can I probably can I
don't know h no that's unnecessary
though okay well a lot of you guys say
yes but decent amount says no okay I
[Music]
will I will
re-upload
it
separately yeah cuz I you you guys are
Trill with the with the Clippers yeah I
I I do not want to say I do not want to
see Clippers making a clip out of that I
would think that they would have uh
respect enough respect not do that but I
I can imagine that there's some people
out there who want to make a clip and be
like K absolutely losing her mind mental
breakdown on
stream yeah I don't want to see that so
yeah surprisingly I I didn't see any
Clips like that until now so I guess no
one actually recorded uh no none of the
Clippers recorded
it yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's a bit late to reupload the archive
but please guys give it a give it a
quick H view so that it doesn't um get
completely
overlooked yeah and if you missed that
stream actually then you're welcome and
you can watch the archive finally are
there any people here who actually
missed it and were waiting for the alive
to come back
back I missed oh really oh a lot a bunch
of you oh sorry to keep you
waiting sorry oh dear okay uh uh warning
H in the beginning I was already a
little bit triggered quite
triggered because of the water uh area
being really triggering was quite salty
and pissed off but it will it will get
better after a little time uh after the
water I was feeling much better so you
can skip that part if you
want I was in a bad mood
yeah anyway I will go eat my food now
cuz I'm hungry and I'll see you tomorrow
for t r part three let's go let's
go I read the super chats today uh
tomorrow sorry but I already read so
many today I think we did a good
progress yeah thank you for being here
today I love you
KF love
[Music]
you what kind thank you for listening as
always I might not put up a ending tweet
uh we will see bye
nighte oh no no no I forgot I
forgot and in German we say
Al oh
dear a
[Music]