in
Indonesia hai hai hai hai hai hai hai hai
Hi
Hello Eh Bro I'm the one Sorry have started to be
you but I am here right now as
risut Iman Doctor risus sit up Yes
so the restaurant here as Doctor
resolution squirrel friends there is no  Doctor
Risus Sit Up will open a
free consultation service for guests who
will come today Yes. Are
you ready to find out
who will come to the
Thufail Resolution Doppler clinic? Yes, are you
curious? Are you
the one they will consult?
Yestoday early Open  eye and online
consultation of the doctor May suggest
kulliyesi tupai means the school
and I will In White suggest that will
ask me for Advan Iya seductor Reason
Yes outrigger Ouch I think it's time to
rest the world
to have wav to help our first section
sorry sorry  sorry I don't understand now okay
seating lets count our first
ah our first glance
cuy cuy
Jokowi
alright Let's read our first best
everybody Uh okay
Hai
songket hello hello hello hello okay lamis
Strike ama Welcome finished having fun
consulting Doctor resusi tupai where
you can  consult about
everyday complaints from the strange
to the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to select
Rizzo's voice. Press 2 to select Wizu's voice.
Press 3 to select Ayunda's voice. You are
welcome
I
am Aku  I want number one. OK
then, thank you,
thank you for choosing the Thursday
I'm worried service which will help you in
this consultation session without
taking too long. Please introduce
yourself and explain what
you want to consult about,
please
hohohohoho hehehe Thank you Doctor,
name issue, circle the map. I  an
angel and now I want to
consult about Um How
can we regulate the stability of our
voice when we sing because
drl is more often unstable when
singing, listen more uh OK,
thank you Wow, it's
really
very interesting so a a without
going on for long, A Doctor issue  will
help
so the
method is
em-plus there is that we have to practice
breathing correctly but there are things that
we usually forget, namely m A where we
have to interrupt am sentences when we
sing so to stabilize the voice
when singing a there are times when we have to
pay attention to
m Where is our place  will cut
sentences when singing Yes. That way
we can
feel a more comfortable flow of singing,
so usually afternoon is
Aa, the main key so that singing is more
stable for tung tung,
this is very helpful.
Thank you, former daughter, I'm satisfied and
before the consultation time ends, are
there any messages?  messages and words that we want to
convey from our guest Lili Iveta
Hi there is of course there is definitely for
my cutest and prettiest doctor Hihihi I'm embarrassed
doctor Ouch
OK then that's the message for the doctor
today's issue happy birthday to my sister
result eh doctor I mean sorry who
OK accept it  Thank
you, I hope you are more successful in
the future, I hope you are more beautiful and cute
and I hope you have a box. I hope there are
more people who love Sis Lis, I want a
doctor, Iso Mawi Sumo Ayunda, I hope
many people love you and are always
blessed with health and abundant fortune
52 thank you  thank you for your words then
Thank you for your words when erysuprim a
in my heart to my heart the deepest worry
is here hehehe in them I am
with you Thank you for
your time to consult
and
Maybe next time rise will open
another consultation service so see you again
in the consultation session
next
OK, thank you Doctor, today's Heaven issue,
doc, thank you.
OK, that's our first guest,
then. Are you satisfied with
today's session because we
will have lots of
guests? Yes, because they are already queuing,
friends, so are you curious
about the next button?  because the issue is
also curious
Hi for
a moment
then let's contact dudi dudi dudi dudi dudi dudi dudi dudi hai hai hai
hai Hi dudi dudi dudi dudi okay okay let
's aha contact Om Aa Let's
contact our next guest too
dududududu wall
[Music]
cutu dududu
hello hello
hello
by klase we are connected
Welcome to the squirrel resuscitation doctor's consultation session
where you can consult
about everyday complaints from the
strange to the strangest before
entering the consultation session. Please select the
voice you want to
handle your complaint  Press 1 to
select the issue sound, press 2 to select the
wisu sound and press 3 to select the
Ayunda sound, welcome,
hello, hello,
hello, hello.
Wait a minute. Looks like we're having a bit of a connection problem.
ready to choose the
vote you want
Hi selected
Hello Hello I want week3 uh OK
then thank you for choosing
our service I am Ayunda who will
help you in this consultation session
without lengthy papers Please
introduce yourself and explain
what you want to consult on
after
that  hello, doctor Ayunda, my name is
Apple, so and so, she is 18 years old forever.
She said that's how it used to be, I have a burden in
life, what's the name of this burden in the future? I have
to go to the gym first, she said,
but three about lazy to go to the gym
because it's a burden, so,
eh, the problem with life is that my burden is  Eh,
I just finished teaching my friend at
that time and he said he was angry Kyle
My problem Oh, even though I cook
normally, how come it's just rubber plus chocolate
plus copy Then add honey and
apple, that's really normal, yeah,
so what's wrong with me like that? Oh,
that's fine if  That's it, Uncle, I will
give you a little enlightenment about
your problem. So actually
it's not Apple's cooking that's wrong.
It's actually your friend's stomach
which doesn't seem strong enough to
handle Apple's super cooking.
Hi, that's true Hut is real, is that so? Oh
yes, I'm ready, darling, I'm wrong, yanar  So
to overcome this, maybe in addition to the
food that
will be provided, maybe you can
give me digestive strengthening medicine.
Wow, that's very enlightening, Doctor
Ayunda, I think I really heard that.
Oh my goodness, thank you very much, Doctor Tray,
because my burden is reduced like
work, huh, Michael, then
are you satisfied with  The answer to the
consultation this time was very strong, Mochtar
Ayunda. Thank you very much. OK,
then before the consultation time
ends, do you have a message and what words do you
want to convey?
Apple said the doctor said it was
Nia's birthday. Oh yes, that's right,
so I want to say Happy Day Eroh.
Thank you.  time OK, the grayer the mouth, the more clouds
the name, the happier the smoother
the life continues to be, the clouds are the name, I hope
many good things happen to the doctor, yes,
I hope more and more patients will be helped
by his presence, the doctor here has
thanked you very much, then here are the
voices again, songs, please give me
the name.  Ayundari, she likes
picnics, right?
next
time
much much
wow friends, this is
our second caller and I hope my advice
can be a little useful to help
their lives hah OK
then without further ado because we
have a lot of guests today then
we will move on to the third guest Wow
very busy, right? The issue doctor this time.
OK, then, let's
just welcome you without further ado,
Toni Tunik Eto said. Welcome to the
consultation session for Doctor Resusi Squirrel where
you can consult about
everyday complaints from the strange
to the strangest before entering the
consultation session.  Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to select the
resume voice. Press 2. For
that WOW issue, press 3 to select the voice.
Ayunda is welcome.
Hi
to track. Well
[Music]
is the most dangerous zone.
What numbers are there anyway?  anyway
[Laughs]
Ah, wrong number 2 guys.
Thank you for choosing your service. I'm
sad. I'm Vishnu who will help you
in this consultation session without
long words. Explain, introduce
yourself and explain what you want to
consult about,
hello, hello, I'm free, hehehe. Today,
if you want, I  I've been here. So, if
I was back, I was close to Wadiah's acquaintance.
Yes, it would be HT. Bro, if there's anyone there, it's
really like the cat has entered a
deathbird, unblurred. Google, look, there are
so many people, there are people who are
pulling their manhood, they're going to
hihihi, Ken Arok, consult me,
Hello.  If we eat bananas,
please refill the
question. Banana. If it's
anything,
ah, a little bit can make teeth, why
not? If it turns out the
rica-rica fish puzzle is painted to be
a bastard Oh I see. That's the box. You
eat it. It appears, it appears, aba nyak
Oh, there's a lot. Oh, how do you say it so it
doesn't get dirty?
Hahaha, it's a hobby of eating. What's
the magic of blebbing like that?
Hahaha. Before eating, wipe your
mouth first with a tissue, use it
like that, use it here, random luck,
our elders can print PT Patria
really dry, okay? Ouch  How do
you set it, what do you do, how do you go down, edit it
first, try it.
Usually, what are the covers
called, what is over over over making?
That's the main thing, don't don't, don't be precise,
blender, Kidul blender, it's a failure,
so that's the part that's acceptable,
hehehe. It's
still really lazy,
sorry, sorry.  sorry sorry sorry sorry just
Thank you
Hi thank you then aa father
father our father that we love
because I died and it's good
[Music]
finished high haiwiki nyuci Thank you
if that's so tebel Well we're going tired
Found there's something you want to say
Oh yes of course  the final tekek was driven by
Rizal
Heroes V comparing fashion photos
Ok rek doctor helicopter newsletter
paint
ok then okay because
because you we were a little
unique before then we will move on to a
sweeter guest Yes that will be the one that
will soothe your hearts so
then let's go  Let's just start the call.
Sis, I'm sincere. You can consult a doctor about
squirrel rization where you can
consult about
everyday complaints from the strange to
the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to select the result voice.
Press  2 to vote for wadaw issue and
still three to vote for Ayunda's vote
are welcome
OK Google
amp all three or not Can
it be allowed
Aa Then okay gecko ah before the
cement I want to give you a
simple gift cycle because it's the
doctor's birthday I'll send it yes please
if  Is that so or not Aa I will hunt
okay this and like this and die quickly
alternately okay hahaha huhuhu cq40
simpei ama put down the prize Ah you
like that Is there anything you want to
consult about and please
introduce yourself first Ah
yes Introduce my name Ni is
legendary mah Panca  Doctor, so
I've had a complaint lately that I'm
confused about a lot of the Tajung
Seizure characters. I mean, it doesn't
really matter because their charm will
continue. In fact, I don't want to
prove them, but I'm
really tired. I need entertainment and in the end
I'm addicted and in the end, the sim is
like that. I  I smile every day until I
think I'm crazy and then I'm
dagdigdug. Do I have
heart disease, do I believe I'm shy and
all that kind of thing? And what is it like for me? I
often hang around
because I prove my character isn't
real. Is the subtle method healthy?  or
how could it be possible to give you advice like that,
doctor? Go up. Thank you, Miss Nia
Reza. Lion is in the light. I will help
paint a little to deal with your problem
because I think that's a normal thing,
especially if the character is
extraordinarily handsome, brothers, so in
my opinion, that's am
Aa, Sis.  Nia is still Ema within normal limits
because because she doesn't
lose her senses, just type, maybe just
bite a little Oh yes, or
what kind of convulsions to deal with,
please
just call the nearest handler, right,
so
to deal with your possible convulsions
it could be a little beyond the limit
maybe yes yes maybe it could be used Om
Aa a certain time quickly yes people can be
charged a little toll normally like that Yes so it's
still normal but I'm on gsm-gsm
and I'm tired mah he's begawe Sin on
them they also have to be on
GSM too why me Ha them they
me they need to be given a little
love I am they realize that hahaha
Jember is the same
hah ah they seem to need
love too yeah Oh okay okay ah
thank you Doctor I finally got an enlightenment
lately I've been restless
because  doctor Thank you for
opening up to love like this doctor
and have if Happy Birthday so
Are there any words you would like Aa to
give before we end today's session
ah what yes happy birthday
tissue waiting for the original song
tonight because Thank you
That's what I'm talking about, please invite
me to this conservation.
Thank you, see you in the next session.
Hi,
bye, it's there. Hey, you're the one who missed it.
Hello friends, the
energy to dispel the results is really extraordinary.
Looks like we have to learn
from our guest, Nia Reza Lion. Take a
quick picture.  I forgot to include
this, Jeng Sis, you are very beautiful,
then we will continue in
a moment, Vishnu, drink first,
look for money to wash e-tolls,
Hi
sustenance,
Laila, just a moment, let's drink first, OK, hi, hi,
hi,
our themes Aa, call OK, welcome
to the consultation  Squirrel resolution doctor
where you can consult about
everyday complaints from the strange
to the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to select the
diesel voice. Press 2 to select the issue.
Press 3 to select.  Ayundah's voice is
welcome
UU
Constitutional Court is fine. OK then.
Thank you
for choosing our service. I am Ayunda
who will help you in
this consultation session. Without further
ado, please introduce yourself and
explain what you want to
consult on,
please eh, hello Doc, I'm Mika Matikah
from Nijisanji, eh.  id eh eh Today I
want to consult if a
few days ago or from
a few weeks ago it seems like
I'm starting to feel like I'm afraid I'm starting to get
really scared by efforts like
those breeds or Dogs every time there's a
squirrel or something like that paypay which is like
a bit onee  -san like that stirs my heart
dagdigdug dagdigdug a little Sitting like that,
my pocket makes it hard to breathe like that, it's just like
that, so Oh, so the complaint
is shortness of breath because of squirrels, so it
makes you afraid of squirrels,
Yes Nok. Well then, if you are
afraid of squirrels, please take
AHM.  trap nearby so that the squirrels don't
come close, but
if the complaints continue, such as
shortness of breath, convulsions or
headaches, please take or prepare an
inhaler to help your breathing.
Aa, if the complaints
persist, please contact the doctor to
get GWS pills,
resident. I wanted to ask for GWS pills, but
I feel like now there is a doctor who says
I prefer Manadonese Dagdut. Then
I will give you a prescription after this
to get GWS pills.
Is that all the complaints
from Mbak Mega Melati
kw2, thank you very much, uh ah,
if so, before the consultation time
ends, is there any  message and words
that FW wants to convey be
happy Tanjung Bunga everything will
be Oh good everything-gummy okay
we
I just woke up checking things gozaimasu
Thank you hu tweet for original
song Yale
close like Thank you for coming
then thank you for  greetings
and time see you again in the
next consultation session bio Thank you very much doc
uh uh
Hi guys that's silence is not easy called
they continue
this
no thank you very much He has a
complaint that he is afraid of cupai brother
is willing to be sad
so yes like that
there has already given a prescription
what is the prescription for GWS pills
to the person concerned thank you Frances
ha ha for attending this session
so
checked you
hello so wait a
minute the issue of drinking first oh donlesi the
next si again the nation dudohno Sheikh
Indonesia well ah
the donation is closed Dadi Sorry
your sandals are like that  let's just wait
a moment out Who else are we going to
call if that's the case, drink
first for a while and
then get thirsty because the next G thing
will be very euy
Mecca really makes an RV resume
while drinking first okay Doctor resolution
squirrel will continue to listen to
your complaints for a while
6 first we  giling
launchpad.net
Hi hehehe
[Laughs]
Indonesia
Hi sturisoma lizard medals
hahaha all kinds of soldiers to
prepare themselves to dress up their body
and soul for a moment
hehehe hehehe Hi
hehe he
hai
hahaha
hihihi hai hai hai
Then let's
just continue  yeah for a moment have a drink first I'm
told
Edo Then let's Call the
next caller while every
cheating first a little huhuhu
hai hahaha
eh as a doctor here very very very
very Marvel's brothers and sisters a moment hai hai hai
eh
that's Hi Sone
sugiwa wed police  here namiraatasya Yoga
Sony jutekin ayam curse nazoya
henneberg I go to the Noki drag Mouse
Sultan not bad Soyu should Let
It
Go kimono by issue please no temple
gokilun object new let's memeque go
keyboard by Los Angeles er Abby Kudasai
Dodo
enilno the unique Sumatra robots
Come
on, that's cheese, Gus Azmi. Come on, tuku by Master
kungkai Okta monoculture parents
Toxicity tada Kimi
Shaykh sholeh Dewa Jikoshoukai tuh
online tweets kikasete kudasai
Hoi hello oh great tribe driver
odong-odong odong-odong eosen what's the name escape
ogoh-ogoh
[Music]
tokuno  debt zooad misoro idol
yuk decimal curse chicken ideas
di sono online yuk di Zenit critic the
writer nontongo.co song okadoc Talking
Tom Wita detect modem naide sukanya
Hello car Cane Tokyo inoxx1 sing mugo
We once knew the machine
toison Hero the enemy
tried great child Sifana  solemn and muscular this
time Heru new stylish demo is playing yoyo
Blazing happens this oil is washed
kasyaira Dubai is quite a weatherli tokidoki
stretchy banish
corrective twidash visit you trade value bye
Kayla Yoi loading NATO skin Adit Angeles
sugoshita menu tanoshi activity
onestopgps rukutuk rezeki.com that's Joe's
name den  -o
Ih bread crying after Cimone wata sietho
Faidah creature
appeal oh
my cellphone
[Music]
al-fath yo
Hello Ma
teenager
money
Yi with marker
ngoday den-o cie
Nihongo Triangel
Woi Kuda
thank you thank you
Eto
Thai Gua only cikuda zainil tajwid code
matching colors Heni Nata
world frog sign Ayu Jokowi
Hi
Nugraheni dotulong er mag Marry
Edward
snowden still selfish Kidul flowy Avin issue
eh talk
What do you want to start
[Music]
viewing messages
Twitter cheats
sorry ama Nihongo daiyo
Oh direka hai hai Neng Let's go  look at
Bonek 50 Teguh,
that's what we're doing Eto'o chigga all
near the Times Tahai shop
Oh yes
small GT Kudasai Hi
maintain spotify
and edit you
hahaha
icostats half of this data type
Oh
yes for a moment Pi betel River freezes
So it's a bit like that for a moment huh
earlier Egypt was a celebrity so
Yes bring me that
Hi
tujhko dead the verdict has been
Korean-boys sudirmanto
hai hai Hi
Then let's go ee
Indonesia
Hi believe
it's a bleach weh
Hi members of the Indonesian
machine friends movement
Hi
tas kemenkeu
baby toh
Wetan Aas sis Riri Sumo
fix it
bye  bye
launch
Nga Nga hai
hai
the lounge
ndeso hai
hai
ndeso hai hai yeah Wait a
minute yes diskor looking for education discord
PC almost u hai hai
hai
OK Google
Rizky YouTube Ayu
nyuci
Unit
send to
Indonesia hai hi
KMU yang hai
hai the
best hai hai hai hai
hi
hai Hi
dream of drifting away
Niken vietsub
the nih
Hi that is Hindu molish Minanda
Moscow and suryokusumo
Ichinose so seconds International
need nazoya Hi Nadekigoto mode now
we soto
Mito yusry crew by our prophet sae-hee
Hi cow gokil woyla ichiu Wisnu Klego
kimono proof  kill wae new way no kowe
Go Keyboard
Arabic rasae
[Music]
please oh gini that
anu goshimei arigatou gozaimasu ta kurai OK telogosewu appear
safety sodachimasu
Ayunda the most nyuruh
soredewa Jikoshoukai Toure ya Minutes
each
site Hi
my name is fine www.neanime.org
so
nocciole  I like using balloons Come on,
we've already Strike high noh cc.
us safe umaini seconds tea tuh
seasonic
forelock Surono Hi you are here mah
happy
hai hai
told to
swing swing swing
like
fall all by good it's just ayeuna
color Goblin strange
cat hahaha
Thanks
highlights love that
[Laughs]
Nda ojekan Nih euy Kanina  rumaini
hoka-hoka message he stay Kutoarjo Mask
Hi anoa code Merry please Resto
curse me tea
atuh ih
please dia instatories cardboard for or
kroto isonia soundtrack rasae Hey died
via injection prayer account
Asok LED Gray
hahaha hehehe arigatou gozaimasu ta
thank you thank you bye  -bye
Yes t-shirt dosto songo-songo zagato
Android is the f*** Frozen seenit.io to
find the solution to the Swift Out
suchs Frozen
Khair
process window
Hi
emytos were still
broken
under these
in Indonesia
hai hai
Indonesia
you explore Windows
say
Shoulders Tego
OK
so click restore dress
we stir
hahaha
topics fall Mega ada i
Indonesia
Hai we die Zaini
Hai
Baby good love you
Cie
cie
Mbak wes
understand
the fun of fiction fiction fiction
hahaha
[Music]
I
am destroyed man e Hai I am deh Ackerman
really ah YouTube is
anti shoetique just ready for the
next color yes yes
okay al-wadjan driver the next color let
go
Indonesia
Hi hehehe hi
Guides or girl live score
badges0 hai hai
Hai
netok next
Easter
Oh Syaikh Sudais
Hi
watermelon
first announcement
Aceh MS King
okay
pray ready for the next color the day
the next next next yes yes
okay okay sumbopu
[Music]
paint Okay Williams Timezone who made C
Okay Lex karwacot doctor wis consultation
with kentut nothing to lose your problem
or how is for storing the consultation
with animals  for the goal for the
consultation cool out Boys just one two
is just
wait and just reach up Ayunda Ayunda Yes please please please
please one two or three
Aha
tripleasport I thank you so much for
your attention for choosing a mission he
invites who will help you on  the station
for the weekend introduce yourself and
explain to me about your problem
hohoho hihihi site Sands of
abstract NSP stroke Suzuki
Hello how much I
nice How much time you and stay out of
the okay okay hungry so
sincere and twice micro swirly serum Here
I want  fight each
hungry
so
OK So there are some reasons that we can feel
hungry during the stream but frankly
would likely it with its water Bridge
dry coldly bye over your solution
Yes very nice solution quickly et m opo ma
hias Sounds from around your stomach old
inslate brother  that comes out When your
stomach grumbling static uh Let great
things bright and it will keep your
stomach Farmer yes yes
Hotel next time Thank you very much for
asking for
each before each and the
whatever you want to say
I
love you have a Wonderful wonderful year
follow Muksin Happiness
Wooyoung Vodka Hah
m.ask.fm collabo can survive cake
year spicy hollywoodnya which you thank
you so much Pain message and also see
you again in the next next time okay
thank you bye bye
It's
very difficult to be concerned because each
slide On The  Stream Beethoven Hello
friday friday friday okay filter Yes I
put some 9 we blogsome times to the
sound of my dream link from links to
make some students May make your
Hi
enough Impressing Aa confide in another color b
i would like to do something fresh Yes
alright won'  t give some ad-diin tebel
advice
Hi just The
Show is the beginning of the giveaway
eigyoubu Abi already Juk not escape from
my story me Yes let's move on the beach
yes oh my god Swift
wow
Hah cash flow Asikin magic Come on March
nubie in the
one I finished eh May  on it will be
available
ane
Newbie smells Ona from today from the
day in the march of
seven seven seven seven fallen Seven oh
oh Life Indonesia
official Twitter yes sriwanto by each
sentence
from now on bikin-bikin get my message
and what are the match What  are the
beach just friend OK,
use Indonesian first, here are
two special items, Bantul.com sarong,
makura memories before bed and a
soft tail charm, a heart-warming risk,
so if you buy two
complete sets, you will get a
signed postcard
directly, yes, postcard  Those who will
sign the results straight away are cool or not Uh
finished Ride
Saudi sad Ade Derulo The default
cardboard is for Ipos cardi will get
Enon great complete set your Wembley postcard
with Risou's signature yes that's
absolutely right so but understand what the issue is like
things are the single detail has to  said
Yes dakimakura
khayna my heart iah trading guys version
brush on First
Hi
enternet Yes already kilo rice site Merry
cute match
choose this season destroyed bytes art lots of
body memes Enno so
acem it's a it's yours Is The Kitchen by
once a kitchen emoh
u  -seal risus Heart warming love-child
time it's amazing axindo will be you
should Yes you have to buy it please yes
and heavy books
you will get a message via narrow buzurg
pos cardboard size by me like me trush me
in the wild Madly
Shining very  much very much amazing I
will tear my my my heart to Shine
your cardboard hahaha
power you wait for it's beautiful
make cake AHM Indonesia official
Twitter rhinoware retweet Allah Laila
Indonesia
by Nabi Indonesia and similar without
first Yosh with match her
iku slang
Ayu right good  zergling Is there and use a
r i ri f a n i question you can ask us
tour reactions about story about
everything is already there in the
description of may
ab-100
selfishly if you have a question
it's in the description Store add Link
provided by Federal live Indo
syaa so cash
away wow
sis written by Magic is it all
just appears morley story from the day
for men see you can free our radiation
every night very good very very he loved
the most Ayunda back in the beach So I
love I need your
nov2 can Edward  so it will be sold on
Tokopedia as well as attending you guys,
keep following the updates, yes, it will be updated
and will be sold on Tokopedia, so just
decorate it, just buy the
brush products, it's very easy
Yes you for your face brush please one
time offer one time for next year it
would be  like this anymore Yes it's his own
time Chaeri
[Musik]
Farmer in asleep without getting out Put
down You're everywhere Yes bytes very
nice cover everybody
is someone Miss out [ __ ] Please
by Sherina
Hi thank you so much for Listening to
me that talk about the  bottle here
it by our market leader huhu huhu huhu huhu
huhu
Huhuhu OK show Habib clothes everybody
from YouTuber body and stomach
flu
here let's move on to the
next caller then
uh
painting Android the now yours yours
You're
not playing
bile information ask
Kwan
Hai
he's reluctant How much but OK so sung-hwan
next color of
access OK
initial konco turu wis consultation without
anything will send to your problem How
your first before starting the
consultation please wait for the
consultation the world with just one
Epic
chest cover Quixley  under topics Ayunda
voice
Hi thread review Quiz
uk.eng TubeMote Fulham Ilmi
I'm not really funny, am I uizuhu will
help you on the station without further
Ado
introduce yourself and explain to me
about job
weh gemling kekinian famous for liking the
vinglish formula sorry boy soundtrack
song The Monkey  Yes ama found Sorry the
f*** out [ __ ]
solving problems
early childhood
eh so for away er Years Eve Marry a
sleeping schedule Soul each have Once
eam I Can't Fight Shadow Fight season
hebei achoy
Painful that Begins because you have a
wedding adjusted  with Straight am
sleeping schedule Why don't we just move
the sun
www.hayy.net hubei new fhx-b
myself trust in the same
Chaeri
magic awf tweet-tweet
stick shooting schedule on
daiam see you snort acuy amen
amen I'll do  how much
sleep like
everything is because
the two
[Music]
mp3we are like in yourself to get moving
the sun much
for help
on
How You're looking for at the help of
schedule planning you
Yes crisye paint happy
birthday giveaway
Hai Evil stronger stronger
yris knoppix Armstrong Lex by  missing
value in Germany
ezuke
Oke
thank you for that feel glad song
keyboard
[Musik]
khsusu
song about taxi yuk Lex Happy birthday
Angela
oh yes uyuj Crowe that the kitchen
y95dan it Benz
OH no the world we live real real real real real
kwe bikinin lux  Willy uyesh welcome okay that's
it Kyu Won
Hong Okay Arif Rich
served two
two
cheated or clothes sleep now
[Music]
joyes Gauss our our next
turyyan
and good morning
and nice race
omong
I will check out then please please
please I have some other people's Yes  I
Hi
MB huhuhu really
badges0
Happy
[Music]
beautiful morning on the 300i ration
story hah
this Hehehe
Hahaha happy Okay and something that I
would like the sea hobby Gotta go to
Marry Marry heartwarming a message from
someone so let me play the video Firza
Oke
building  without
clear birthday lecture
Om etong can pocong
Hi diffusion
KYT
Hi
live sub huhuhu ghosts Jusuf
Habibie numbers 13 yes guys Subhanallah
Hi thank you so much good thank you so much for
giving me I'm very high
Performing a message for my birthday  hai
Hi
Asoy, I was told to
mechs
mp3when message from
yachh It means a lot to me take you so
much I
[Music]
I
definitely you who cabbage glue Virzha
Cover Girl
various yess
of course you
Hi hehehe
Jonggol wait want Once
ampere most for the next couple  dudu
[Music]
Nesya cassava default
refworld next Wow Iyos
dodongo
hihihi.com isi homicides Kidul first
cassava boy credit
instead of glass Hahaha
again in traffic jam
hahaha
as before before we go to die Cut then
Let's be there deh still a noob etusi motorbike taxi driver
lecture competition don't
know
how to do it
the video ah
Hi
little monkey
ancur having to the nervous one that was born
that was
[Music]
kefir Er
hai hai
yo
and shake the rice
yeah Goyang Shining Ajeng
toy Spotted monkey nexcare relaxation truck
that tsabina choandry likes
[Music]
ddu-du-ddu-du
[Music  ]
Star have a drink first then hehehe while
we're waiting let's have a drink first
hello Mama Tea Oh I think Hahaha
I think it was in Scorpio that was this, was it
lagging again for a moment sms wow I'm
worried hi hi bro is
coming home comment hihihi
shark Pondok Karya Kho
Minggu looks like he likes
bathing  Later, Roro Kidul
No
Taiyou, the wallaby tribe has finished being
touched by the crazy crew for babies.
Ideology, that's Vishnu Hulk Hulk, Mother
WA number new, let's go keyboard saw Nabiku
cultivation,
fall nayamigoto, that's still the
mermaid in solemn, that's what
Yumichika lizards read,
Losta Masta Christmas
Indonesia, excited to
eat  jobelist Can I
make
Yes, Newbies don't die,
you know how, you're confused, hi,
you like it, I need it, it's full, it's surprising,
because
[Music]
is the magazine that's advanced, it's Step Two, it's
full, ynwa motorbike Indonesia,
it's the soul of one keigo Freemason, that's
Hooke's law, only
ichfa
Ashlee monokai sustech  come Bakauheni
cursed ethos there is left Thomas
Tisna that is the temperature of wushu style whether it is
sitting down iTune first playnow patitos
qq7 specifically for medical there
is a photo of that please papaya kunaon
Disney
is that enough Toyota Little engine
friends Oh baby Oku East of the world
likes
guys Nasa told me right miss  you baby
baby baby baby baby
baby
Ouch baby talk soto ayam TV
post
yes about
Ben10 Ma'am don't have a model download
look iyo
iyo Well that's mechset.ini waterfall politics
sucks
hahihu luya
Ouch Hello Baby
if you remember meeting
that Hi Bro cucak that prayer  Inalum's sound of blasphemy
is hocane Messi he's Otoy Ali
are you still
nahan districts Oh no season Decorate Dumadi
notes Yovie chandracom.net
choiheechu Hi
strange things in Indonesia
Kadek charm Moscow city colors the country
asobru stadium
Hanoi roughly
Hi as long as wa taala XP home rattan  Jono
top method
how bye
[Music] there
should be us air BoBoiBoy
Come on Papa zeiss uh
Hi bicycle Usada papain next uh How
other things that you mind by amroe
expecting sunexpress simple hohoho Edo
Icut DC Just Nyosor cuy come on
tuwai porn Sunday night Central
Indonesia need  Made nandomo kita Dimas
eh hi already nurmaini I ordered me
UN circuit we say Idol big
two Lee sunkyu technology bailive you
please no Kriwul Kliwon let's play Come on and
okay okay bye the
officer is
clamped Come on Google
Hi, I like the object with the chin corner
to fall in love again  May wish to
that museum
Baitul God of mice like that Unaya
michikaze horse tae-hee
[Music]
hmm that's Hai
old Hi like it or
not NTT country ever NTT
nah Yaumul masturbation HP tuh ih passing like
Ashoka Coker doesn't drink coffee The village head's excise is
great isn't it just pretentious it doesn't type  why,
if you want to use skill no.
who
uh
Hi
everyone Come on, support
tazyin
next power more prepared for my heart
for myself first OK Let's
Get Rich the next Corp
Hi Nona
eh ugly
Ica ugly
Ami Ami Bear Facebooke
kutamindo more Mas
this ticks you Oh yes bye background
music of Thank you
tega White
Hai
next Galur please susu
[Music]
Hi
taza fit
Uh hello I love you
hello hello funny
Indonesian hahaha
not washed years still alive Corry
sushi to play where you can
consult with consult
about everyday complaints from the
strange to the strangest before
entering  Go to the consultation session. Please select the
voice you want to
handle your complaint. Press 1 to
select the issue voice. Press 2 to select the
issue wayaw. Press 3 to select the voice.
Ayunda is welcome.
G2
hi-tech Jokowi. The pen is breast-feeding. Cut
the color. This is popular.
Thank you for choosing our service.
I'm Vishnu who will help you with
dishes consultation this time without
long words, enlighten me, introduce
myself and explain about the things you want to
consult
on at that time, they admit it.
Hoi, hou Yi
Subhanallah
we Wow
bleake please
Hi, here, send me a story about the timer
expense, come on, you're a timer  this cell is
so long all this is the unit
mostly
chasing points at Simping time
so Royal how should I have to have
to I It from doing it Then it runs out
when I go to Simping to or next to
Lyrella right
hah looks like it's a question of knowing what I should do
named Choi you need
onions  - the oil onion can control the oil
from start to finish so that Abian
Athaya's activities are organized so the PHO
is the
heavy one who is responsible for
handling all the activities Oi yes but the
doctor is not the handler, the doctor's vegetables are
bye bye bye,
this afternoon, that's why you need a handler  who is
very
experienced Ih if you want to resign you
can become wushu oil onion you can become Pak
oli yes oh how much does it cost per week
per week only only with
divorce Aa love and affection every
time uh
10 gadgets then Is flip satisfied
with the answer so ouigo  You don't need to
stop using this feature, Nia. Just look for an
opportunity, another war is already ready, it's
already ready, hahaha
hihihi, it's better to have background
[Music]
when you're crying big, you're just playing
clove, you're
like that, oh, that's it. Before the consultation
ends, what are your messages and words that you
want to achieve?  times
Oh yes so please listen listen
Because these are words from the heart Oh yes okay
Wih senpai Happy birthday wish you a
long life oli shell wish you the
best for senpai and English
yo yo hi hi
Hi
disappear
ready to pray hehehe Eh that's all okay hi
high-  end
Hi,
Saza Huh, that's the only guest,
Hi Edo MS Lembangdi,
Doctor reshuffle consultation session where you can
consult about
everyday complaints from the strangest to the
strangest rubbish before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1  to select the diesel voice,
press 2 to select the wisu voice and
press 3 to select the Ayunda voice,
welcome
you are sincere. Thank you, it seems like
our caller nature this time is very
enthusiastic, you are so, I am
Ayunda who will help you in
this consultation session. Without further
ado, please introduce  yourself and
explain about the things you want to
consult about
my anal my name is noble
today
your doctor came to help me
Abdullah which I have been experiencing for a long time
so the same is available I have been
on my back a lot lately
wanting to sleep
this is watching TV
Hyun Joong is funny hehehe  I
really thank you for waiting for me.
Okay then. Thank you very much
for your confession. Just a moment.
I want to change the server first,
haha. Just a moment. It's simple, that's a
good server, hahaha.
This speed is the color and the temples.
Hi, okay, hello, hello, okay, it's already
good.  okay then
sister Reni's problems are in that area
hah it's okay it's a
backache but I want to relax I want to
sleep and I want to watch streaming
ayundari su really itchy so the
easy assumption is to
hire a masseuse
HH is really  Very good. So, if
possible, Ayunda's doctor sister
recommended me a massage therapist. Yes,
so I have a friend who is a massage therapist
and the massage therapist is a back massager,
so as long as I have a friend named Restu, yes,
he is very experienced in
massaging and stepping on the back. So
while sister Reni lay down and was
stepped on  - maybe you can step on it while
relaxing Hi and watching the stream, that's
a good thing. Can I ask for a
contact info from sister Restu who is
good at stepping on this? Emil and so on,
don't forget what you said. OK,
okay, then I'll
give you the contact, just DM. Yes, okay,
then  Before we
finish this session, is there anything
else you want to say?
I want to say it Because my
heart is a pejju May Stay With Me Baby stay
under
richfarm trust em can bean rich get
rich get rich
Zain
always have with turning
Cut
regular discoplasty kuflet rasa game thank you  you are
trying to get be careful
geprek Oh my God Thank you for
your time
I finally know what to do to
solve the problem then
see you in the next session
Thank you Happy birthday Brother
bye
[Music]
Kya that's from rainie who has a backache
What a shame  Hope you get well soon Rene
hihihi
No need to do that but the
last one seems to be Hendra Heroes PC
until that's okay okay because
we're in Solo yes that's right thank you for
choosing the service eh Aa thank you
and welcome you can consult a
no pay resolution doctor where you
can consult  about
everyday complaints from the strange to
the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint, oh wait a minute, it seems like the server is
strange, change the server first, okay? Sorry,
sis,
eh Toko Lex ah ah Hello
Hello, can you hear a sound?
Hello, I sound cool. OK,
before entering the consultation results, it's as if you
choose the afternoon you want. Press 1
to select the reissue sound, press 2
to select the graduation sound and press 3
to select the Ayunda sound. You're welcome,
I'm two, it's good, like that,
change the fact of
my car, Wisnu, that will help  you are in the
consultation session this time without
long words, brighten up, introduce
yourself and explain what you want to
consult on
OK, hello everyone, this is anyeofficial from
holiday generation2 Happy birthday
mute senpai anyway
Happy birthday so the story
goes like this, this is how it is, this is how it is lately, the
end  -lately the pillow I've been using
to sleep on feels really hard uh
Well it looks like what I need is something
like an animal's tail for a pillow
for a softer pillow to
sleep on so how do squirrels send
maybe pillows like the tails of
those tails  soft that looks like
the flavi that comes out is
delicious but makes you sleep. Are there any trees that
Thalia recommends? This is m.ked 4 Tanjung Cangat
stock once so this time it's just Dad,
yes, selling Mercedez birthday, there's a
kimagure that's half iced, a
macro action gift wrap that's very Fluffy
Fluffy that  can accompany you to sleep and
also and like the also Om the advantage of a
very weak tail key for and a
cat's tail which can help you sleep
faster
please
Wow you've got a warehousesari
friends really a more
oily structure please
along my endoke betta if you want
Real tails aren't allowed, Nasir. It's
okay. Whenever they're free, it's okay, hihihi,
you can give them from episodes to
little magic.
Yes, thank you too. I'll just take
the original. That's good, that's
the advantage of Jungle Fury. I'll
buy it once the gold is clear. Thanks for
the description.  I'm
complete, don't want it or not, just give it to me, I
can't take it off, where
can I pick it up,
but I'm an account, I'm looking for it,
looking for it, uncle, magic to be able to take it off,
okay,
but but I want you
guys too, so don't
let it go, OK, I'm tired, I want to
the person fell Kamen Rider the wall nour
closed
Putut to this Middle school what but
a number of studies on the time if
so the not yet Thank you this location is
tired Sis there is something I want to say
again
Happy birthday on Sesame ae sing Happy
birthday chicken latest news
original song just small  Neng,
yesterday, if I'm not mistaken, we
said that we both like
breaches, my cell phone is sneaky. Dad,
that's right, slime wixsite.com relations.
Happy birthday,
pudding,
wash bye.
Okay,
reviewing that, Dahlia tried the pizza,
wow, hi,
free, hi,
hi, how
dare we do that?  have
we ever been old friends for a moment Icu drink
first
Indonesia
Hi Ho
Hi
dream
units
miciu OK then
sweeper Wahyu we friends for a moment
macho RW xanthorrhizol come in first
Yes
OK then we wait for
the caller the singer
also has a pun  we are the last ones,
mosquito friends, okay
then, welcome to the
squirrel resolution doctor's consultation session where you can
consult about God every day
from the strange to the strangest
before entering the consultation session.
Please select the voice you
want to handle your complaint
Press 1 to select the result vote press
2 to select suwalow issue and press it
to select the vote Ayunda is welcome
huhuhu alone
Ah I'm about I want to sit down
first
said please
introduce yourself and explain
what you want to consult about
Ah okay okay
hello for a moment I'm Siska pendant Dedi
nijisanji IDM
so I'm
done I want to wear a costume to consult
about
sleep problems Why does my sleep
look like it's the other way around So what
used to be sleeping in the morning is the
territory of sleeping at night now so
what happens Ilu hmm
there was also someone who had a
Mazda E with a charger according to Lee Soo
which according to Dwi SUV Om, the way to fix
it is to
defeat it
by defeating the desire to sleep
so if we don't sleep it means Om
we don't have sleep, that's the
wrong thing
Fadli I don't fall asleep calm down be
nucke nocturna so Lahm a zombie is
n't it Be a person who can not sleep
After that after not sleeping maybe
for am1
Twitter
your problems will magically
improve Yes because usually
mk5 lam is after one week yes these are
experiences
I've been talking to an expert for a week. Well, after
a week of not sleeping, we'll
fall asleep. But the right time is at
night, after that, your sleep time
will be good again.
Hey, you're like Valcke, it's wrong, Agung.
Hi sis, that was my mistake. Trio, I
just woke up.
Actually, I didn't sleep, it's
here, okay, national, ready, okay, thank you,
I'm home, the answer is,
Hm, it seems a bit difficult, but
it seems like it's a bit logistical,
maybe you can try it if you can
afford it. If you haven't tried it, don't
know yet, ask Los Angeles.
So before time  Our consultation
is over. Are there any messages and words you
want to convey
visually? Happy birthday,
sir. Today will definitely be a
smooth day,
smile. Sorry, I'm really new to the
meaning of issues, you know, why, hihihi, why,
congratulations, what do you see? Universal problems,
you have a life,
love you.  I'll stop by sometime, play
again, OK, Win again, ion trending again,
bye bye,
high too, HayDay, the rest is baby,
OK, so that's it, Yes, we are the
very charming
viscount Yes, that's it for a moment, sunna
sunah sunah sunah sunah rosul
chat for a while, bro, blue, finished, bro,
it's not difficult  bro,
Hi
Riza,
Riza, prepare this last, tomorrow afternoon, right,
this is the last because eh because
the impact is really making, hello
Hi,
this fortune is special, so Rachel will play
it now
hehehe hihihi
and also
this is part, got the message, got
the message,
so I'm worried about saying it, now
okay,
pieces of [ __ ]
Oh up that's happy birthday hey
[Applause]
Hi
wow Lee sub ilove you Happy birthday to
you Mama Hao
[Music]
Wow whisper Juli
Oh this is my God this is my
birthday hai hai
Hai
[Music]
Andai Thank you forever I
[Music  ]
Hai
robot
[Music]
Lego DC Heroes
Hai that uh uh
hai hahaha huhuhu Hai
Hehehe yes Hai
Andai singkuh W huhuhu
i-i-i-i am yellow amawi voyance
submarine DC ryukei I have my Heaven Sword
video arrow So I just pure it There and
haven't watched
dipunaturi menatur Aikatsu video by
Abdul Wachid so know Smash New in
natru
Chaeri Donald's
Omega sensor
rich's year often
Twitter hahaha
hahaha hahaha hai hai hai hai
hello what what play degan Okay let's
play the game loudspeaker one more time
okay okay okay osos hai hai
hahaha
squi  -cumi [ __ ]
upil feeling
basket pun
[Applause]
Hoi Wow rishou ilove you how much key
Mama me Hi wow
Yusuf Juli aha
ngarep Hi
Jelly Cupi
birthday to you by
huhuhu
Ouch Hi
hehehe Hi
Sancu forever
I
Ketut
Sayur2an Dirut take a cup with
LCD money  ambani emergen running
text automatically Do
you know how to reduce viruses, it's a
full body bearing pad, this is absurd afiful Aa makes a
seawheel
[Music]
I am happy
very very dry brush Day
Thank you forever I
should go to idea first just mate myself
Sumo meaning first for a moment right from
as many  I was drinking for a while,
eh, eh
Indonesia is
fast, hai hai
the lounge
ndeso hai hai hai hai hai hai hai hai
Indonesia hai hai
OK
Google Map Map hai hai Hi
I have a body thank you so much for am yes so be the
doctor The doctor who handles
problems-
Your problems will also be as well in GWS in Wow
me What do you think about about the
doctor who will be a great help you with
your problem because one Who needs help
yeshu
however
I know why Grace before this so After
this Arisu wants to make Aa wants to watch  long
Yes what the long
m-watch long what is called hots long original
song so I'm worried it will still be
playing mut'ah still low still
going to stay onstream so after this we
will watch long when yeshua
al-habib Muhammad short white long
product from  your songs and the Wings on the
move comment in the life chat-an
in the description so please please go
the day the original song
[Musik]
Pink Beach South long enough so before
before work along Together I will
promote worse gnewe about  my god oh my
god Yes my birthday March
sold out ah Hi to
aw eh ey Hi how to Yes I have Yours hai
hai hello there is kimonkoro yes
dakimakura to science
lemi
friends your first cheese Ilham tu just
Syauqi makura front side is like this
and that  makes websites like this and
enter philosophy
ehem-ehem memorize
Eighteen B AMP
is securempm Yes that's the chain of Om
Thank you
abreso Tale soya one step closer cover
issue
RSU tailpiece freestyle twice-yes the
first step detail teeth make slide small
March should you first  please
Hi know news next time all the big
Seoul Seoul slide show TV One day realse
skrub seorg please krusell please by
nathaniel
calculate2 get am a very nice sleep at
night slime dakimakura
facial and in the front side will have
results and the back side welcome  Ayunda
everynight
Chaeri by Yugo Out Boy atomy made from the
front side is Reason the text is
ayune sama Eastwood you sing
Indonesian about having your toys I'm a
Indra kimagure
airbrushing khairin Mr Singh bad I guess
it's getting
i-amt not
I am in  the dark Emang Rich
solsel foreign you guys how to be at
because it's me
some picture there should be kind in a
Church side What do you want to sleep
with three or leave me
nice overnight
x-over so many Nights
sleep with pleasure and other Network
Ayunda
with books by the year by The Wind Blows OST
One on each side
dubsmash Well
hello so much
so I have seen the real Dreams
drill product each have love will leave
that Feels Like You know your new single
free with love teddy bear It Feels Like
Tonight Show
this is finnair's business otherside
nayunda issue On The Other Side swept
showcase and the tale is say bye alike
detail each style
talk about two by two three one set your
heart you will get a higher score the
postcard willhouse my am Signature I
will ilhan
friend's designature myself in the for
Indonesian brush
Ayu kinget demage for Pediasure Wilona
Once a leg Hi So please wait for the
information letter on lead thank you so
much and I think I'll wait for free day
you're
out with full day
sweet holiday  for the Premier song
e-cash abang-abang openlink know
where you like this
scheme more uh meet
nation4d.com litura restore
si okay your
Heroes iwill
halo halo turn off my take newsmy
system Havers I will turn off my my
background music and Within Just  wait
here I am not crazy please
Hi Cahyono to your family tell your
style your most style your teacher
tell your friends Where are
you everybody
nmr retweet this first real quick
real will be serum Facebook as well
there die
butchered anus William
excited and RW 1 cm
ginger freestyle
wastiru ledekin reynoso let's go trade
leads is a
senswell
sorry-sorry
researchers are there to see you
move first please friends
tend to raid Yes is Indonesia
Hi minute
Hi also similar to the
negligee
that makes Sule Omega
hi hi
talking about catfish,
this is what we're
talking about
sleep Egypt refreshing strange
[Music]
Grandma for example How come you haven't YouTube where are
you my year
eh have you ever had TV
sing-sing have you
never totot friends It's
okay okay nah I'm curious to jump in all song
first Two Brother Rich
stainless steel
writing is it with you
is  missing
until code
LV KW
Sri skins risking
primer Thank you very much for giving us
now Premier League is the day
See The First really blasting Years
since Against
The Nine eight seven six five nyonya
Hi Ho
Hai Fahri
[Music]
Hello
huhuhu  lol
thank you so much everybody
Oke mtwi dingo Ride I'm
Still Waiting for Your Call I'm sick
call your song interpretation Yes please
you so much for
watching each sentence respect is in the
song please Note for you for your
inspiration for your comment terrorist  for
your
for your theories about the song for
xxyyxx full day Illustration for the
movie show
please yusdi hairstyle guys entware ah
elishandi you and The Verge bikin cake
cake song in your favorite
anymp4 streaming platformer
slow tick you so much
regarding the song itu
sai2 according to it  soon it's time for me
to welcome that Nothing you so much for
your support
for the soul
Hi I
wish list includes keywords eluts di
online the song Rich two Rich am four
four way okay
stabilizer the song with high stakes
Well now thank you so much
Hi
extremely droidlime
eh it's really an emotional a
time for me but thank you so much
Winger ah
mellow now
you
Hahaha
I also checked this selling cakes cakes cakes
thank you so much
too much the way
Hi
this is synch
soha see it straight out genderuwo
suryayusra
Chaeri sad and Seri To Wherever share
wherever you want to share
as much as possible,
as far as possible Yes
and use the hashtag Alis Endi for you
to share it everywhere, everywhere,
my heart is happy,
I'm Thank you so much everybody this is
this is my gift to you guys on my
birthday VCD Sorry Kim Mi so many
things Through The Years so before and
The Stream I just want to say that
I am so happy
to be able to work
quiet here with you guys ow fully our
Song Yi fridge One Million views and our
channel help  my channel well show Rich
One Million songs no pressure but will
get there are you sleeping so thank you so
much for being with me and After The
Stars
yoo-ri avitin online Pian at night I am
so don't forget to visit
and will have  a birthday Elia
fitness team well so i you your wedding
forget a pleasant to my song
religiously hahaha darling
lisyaiin outside to say thank you as
well for all of my Guess the day and
Also for May offer for my Manager
book for healthy dream
biting Pinch cheek  for helping me a true
abbreviation for my birthday show I'll
show like Thank you guys for making this
birthday asmaria Space browser thank you
so much I
Reason with you guys are a fitting end
remix PoPiPo time body bergkaiser reload
spotipo Raid the
needs of people
people Resto people 77 do
Hai
Dede babibo Photobucket Photobucket
shop
butterfly nih
butterfly Nyi
Hai
[Music]
butterfly
yt-api.com
nil but
[Music]
but
maybe Banyumas
atopnotch  hai
hai
[Music] hai hai hai hai Hai dedek
si Beli duck eh nusu iwill have
lots of Other Changes to do as well the
brow And The Beast the deaf rich's
Hi Ho