[Music]
oh
n
[Music]
come to the shark
side T CH ones are
[Music]
calling I am death
itself I am Timeless am I really though
[Music]
it's Elementary ain't
it what is this dayu
feeling h live English and
me and
me the rise of Kiara the
Phoenix once upon a time when there were
no humans yet on Earth and sightings of
mythical creatures were nothing
uncommon there was a young Phoenix with
feathers bird like the Golden
Sun this Phoenix's name
was kiar Ki over thousands of years Ki
would travel over the world go on
adventures like fighting giants visiting
the moon becoming an idol and many other
things however every couple of hundred
years G's lifespan would come to an end
Going Up in Flames but soon rising from
her own ashes again here we go again
every time she would rise she would be
reborn in another dimension discovering
completely new
worlds nowadays there are no more
phoenixes left on this Earth and in most
other
dimensions Kiara started feeling lonely
and decided to take human form for her
next lifetime and do what humans do K
decided she would come to this world and
Conquer it in a different new way today
is that day today kada the Phoenix is
Reborn
oh my
God so many
people y y y I'm so
nervous I'm so nervous oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my
God hello oh God I have I have only one
hour time I got to I got to do
thisai hello hello thank you for coming
to my stream hello hello
you oh my god um I only have one hour I
don't want to I don't want to uh be
scolded by My My by my Senpai for
streaming too long okay
everyone nice to meet
you I am I literally just came out of my
um out of my ashes I'm still feeling a
bit hot I'm a little bit
sweaty um I just literally just got
reborn uh actually okay I was yesterday
it was yesterday last a few hours ago
like 10 hours ago I got reborn and um I
decided I know it's just kind of weird I
feel like I've done this before I feel
like I've done this before but uh oh
yeah there's no bgm there you go I feel
like I've done this
before but oh well we got to get this
party started right okay no no no we
don't have time for this okay so
everyone nice to meet you
I
am from Whole Life
myth I
think let me introduce myself to
you
T so yeah this is my profile please take
a good look at
it my name is Takashi kiar which is
funny because um I'm a phoenix right
olai hello Hello nice to meet you
ol so yeah so Taki in Japanese means a
small bird playing but we all know I'm
not a small bird I'm a big bird now
won't be playing around okay okay you
I'm
taking my birthday is H July 6th which
is National Fried Chicken day
I love chicken very very much I love
chicken H My
AG is a good Senpai good Senpai oh my
God oh my God good Senpai thank you so
much for coming to my stream oh my God
I'm so
honored good Senpai I'm such a fan of
you oh my God I love you singing G
Senpai you're amazing oh my
God this feels weird feels like a d of
Vu I don't know what the hell is going
on okay so my AG
is eternal but you know I I I live a few
years normally and then I slowly
evaporate into um ashes uh this has just
happened recently um every time I get
reborn for a little while I forget what
I did before uh but the memory comes
back sooner or
later I don't remember what was I doing
before this oh
well oh well so yeah I've lived many
many lives and I got reborn many many
times so yeah oh you guys are surprised
that I speak many languages yes I speak
a few
languages I speak
uh I think we'll get to that in the next
slide I am 165 cm don't forget
Kelly who's Kelly
oh anyway um 165 cm yes yes yes yes race
Phoenix how you a phoenix some people
call
me chicken or turkey or so sometimes
which is uh kind of effed up I'm a
phoenix respect me okay respect
me
call this
name doesn't doesn't leave my mind
somehow wait why do I still have an Echo
by the way
just realized still had an echo Why did
no one tell
me ah Kelly Kelly
Kelly I don't know seems familiar H oh
well well next one so my
papa the person who gave me life the
person who um gave me this beautiful
body is hook Papa hook Papa give it up
for hook Papa
yay yay yay yay yay hook papa is amazing
I have an amazing Papa okay oh by the
way the chat is uh kind of messed up
because of the memberships why why do I
have members members already
why well yeah it's kind of miss the
membership emotes and the member uh
badges are not working for some reason
um I think there might be a reason but I
don't know why uh so anyway yeah
so yeah hook Papa thank you guys for the
donations by the way why do I have
donations already oh
weird uh hook papa is the Creator and
designer of blackw shooter and Stein
skate so I think many of you have heard
of those before he's really really
amazing comment on thank you guys thank
you this is such a special day for me
I'm so nervous oh my God oh my God thank
you thank you thank you thank you for
the membership wow membership thank you
welcome to K p and my life to was made
by Cathy Papa oh he gave me the
opportunity to move so I can move as
smooth as I do right now thank you caffy
papa caffy papa has done the has done
the uh left toity of many other sandai
up until now most recently o sandai yeah
yeah yeah
yeah oh my God a red Super Chat thank
you wow wow wow wow
I how to thank you I don't know a kiss
seems too embarrassing I don't want to
do that so
yeah oh that's a bit too embarrassing I
I'll just say thank you maybe a German
uh danan could be uh
fitting
D um it's in German yeah I speak German
fluently next one all let's get a little
bit into detail okay shall we shall we
so let me tell you a bit more and ignore
the bottom for now I say we will talk
about that
later so
um my likes are fast food adventures and
bunnies I I really like going on
adventures and fast food you know some
people say oh my God I R super chat
again thank you thank you thank you soon
some people say uh that fast food is
unhealthy but I like to say it's very
healthy there's salad inside and often
there's Tomatoes Inside and meat you
know you kind of need meat to to stay
strong and Grow
Big so everyone keep on eating your fast
food fast food is the best and
Adventures yes I love adventures and
bunnies bunnies are adorable but uh we
will get to
that and this likes scary stuff and Del
Del I mean Del itself is like um not too
much of a big deal to me because I just
get we boring you know um but it's a
veryit annoying because I have to start
all over because I forget what happened
last time for a little while it takes me
a while to remember and uh usually
usually I got I get re born in a
different dimension but this Dimension
seems so familiar to me
oh thank you for the Super Chat oh my
god wow you guys are so generous oh my
God oh my God thank you thank
you well uh so yeah but
um death
death there's there's something about
death that I really like though I forgot
I forgot what it was
C Callie
de
Callie
death where's the
connection what I feel something has to
I feel C this name Callie must have to
do something with the and my positive
feelings about it that are hidden deep
inside of my
heart I feel like
huh
weird oh well we don't have time for
this let's continue okay otherwise uh my
manager was scold me for streaming for
too
long most of my homies are singing
drying eating sleeping ah I I like to
sleep a lot but I have problems falling
asleep because I watch too much Netflix
before I go to sleep
and I have to watch like 4 hours of
Netflix before I fall asleep but then I
like to sleep like really really long
but this kind of messes up my sleep
schedule cuz I I tend to stay up for
like until like 8:00 a.m. 7:00 a.m. 6:00
a.m. something like that it's
crazy 4 hours
yeah do you also watch Netflix for 4
hours goodness I'm looking forward to
collabing with you
once the collab band is lifted uh and I
can collab with someone outside of my
generation goodai goodai I hope we can
collab sometime maybe um maybe we'll
skip sometime and collab tomorrow uh I
have seen something in my schedule
apparently apparently we're collabing
tomorrow I don't really know what's
going on there I I should have a collab
band for a month I don't know what's
happening
anyway uh yeah and singing I don't sing
so well but I really enjoy singing
drawing also I don't draw so well but I
really enjoy drawing and eating I eat
very well and I really enjoy
eating and languages I speak
B
ger English and jaanese
Cali
C Callie
Senpai
h
Kelly
Callie I remember
it how could I ever forget
you Kelly I love you
forever
[Music]
Kelly
KY we will never be aart you will never
lose me I will
always I pushed the wrong
[Laughter]
button we forever be together you and
me I remembered how could I have sorry
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
for forgetting oh my God how could I
forget to
I feel like suddenly my heart is beating
very very fast thank you Callie wait a
second I just
remembered
I'm
Kelly I don't I didn't only remember cie
wait a
second oh wait wait
wait Amelia Watson the
detective from from my Senpai Amelia
Senai has sent me some
evidence to prove to
me
something let's take a look at it shall
we maybe it can help me even more to
regain my full memory
oh huh what does this mean meme contest
go # Phoenix down YouTube teret ki's
channel Ki Oh no anyway
oh I see what is the meaning of
this
interesting shall we take at the look a
look at the next evidence
for # Phoenix down low effort for meme
contest before heading to sleep I see a
bunch of chickens in
pain they seem to be suffering a lot and
crying and missing something they have
lost what is this what's going on what
are they experiencing what's what is
happening are they
okay oh my God I hope they're
okay but what what what does this mean
contest mean I feel it feels like
something I've heard before maybe I'm
not so sure I I don't
know thought I'd post this on Twitter as
well # Phoenix down Tak
Channel currently has one death
h
[Music]
Huh wonder I mean I've been revived many
many many times and it's definitely more
than one death not sure what exactly
they're trying to reference here this is
wrong I've died like a million
times but interesting interesting huh
still got more time to kill so here is
another # Phoenix down I am winning
K what that's my hat on that chair
that's both of my hats on that
chair
but and my
ashes when was this photo
taken and this is my
this is my hookah Papa asking if I'm
winning I mean I'm always
winning thank you for the Super Chat oh
my God
than
soon weird weird stuff going on there
what is all this evidence what has
Amelia sent me here this is uh confusing
me even
more huh Channel got banned k what T for
a meme contest that's quoting me I never
said that come on # Phenix down
stons what
what what I never did I ever say that
before did I say that before well time
for me I don't remember saying that why
are you quoting that me like
that but I guess a quote on the internet
everything on the internet is true
there's no lies on the internet
right
interesting
huh
oh
that's wait that seems
familiar B # Phenix
down that's both me
huh huh wait wait wait what what what
what what what wait isn't that isn't
that a pretty recent me on
that what have I have I done all this
before oh my God C Phoenix down this is
fun this is the gy by the way that was
pretty nice or gift whatever however you
want to pronounce it don't fight over it
that was really cute go check it out on
Twitter it's pretty
cute why is Kelly so emotional about
that oh my God # Phenix
down wait oh my God
I I'm part of
I'm part of H myth first generation
aren't
I it came back to
me don't worry guys is already fixing
the
problem wait my channel got
terminated and I'mma I'm fixed it you're
right I'm went to the YouTube office and
ground pounded them real hard am thank
you so much oh my
God how can I ever repair you what oh my
God thank you finally I'm back
finally clearly a pass a PC spec reading
ASMR was too hard for YouTube
Co you're right I did a PC a spec
reading
ASMR right that was quite recent oh
because of this beautiful microphone I
tried to test it out I remember
everything now
it
parkour YouTube is stepping over
demonetizing stepping over striking
stepping over warning on going straight
into CH Channel
termination yeah that's exactly what
happened I up until now I never had any
de demonetizing I never got any strike I
never got any warning I didn't even get
an email telling me that my channel was
terminated nor did I get an email
telling me that my channel was
reopened
YouTube this week on Hol
talk baned breaking
news YouTube stated sorry it's a bit
small YouTube stated KY said spam rather
than fried
chicken YouTube you you you prefer
spam but wait that's past me and current
me oh my
god wow I think I've I think I've
mastered Revival though because up until
now I always got reborn in a different
dimension and now I'm in the same same
Dimension maybe I never have to leave
this Dimension ever again no matter how
many times I get reborn but wait does
that mean I am stuck in this
Dimension will I forever be reborn in
the same
Dimension I guess that's all right as
long as Kelly is
here okay okay okay is there more
evidence we will send unto YouTube only
them rapon here until it is done wait do
Kelly and Kelly was also a part of
rescuing me and my
channel YouTube is running away with
fried chicken how dare you how dare you
that's my fried chicken how dare you do
that
Savage Oh God that's pretty small let me
try to make that bigger for you
guys this is a this this is pretty old
this is a pretty old
meme oh it's getting kind of uh uh
pixelated but kiar is kol no apology for
Pure English when were you when kiar
takanasi dies I was working a caree and
eating chicken when manala rain what K's
kill
no wait my eyes are getting kind of
dried out here let's chill let's let's
chill my eyes are getting
dry okay I think many many of you guys
are uh absolutely Zoomer so you guys
don't understand this
meme next
one more evidence oh wait this is not
evidence this is something
else let us read
this a big thank you to everyone behind
the scenes at cover Corp
when things go smoothly we often don't
think about everything you are doing to
keep H life and H Stars running but with
the recent death and Revival of K's
Channel I think now is the perfect
opportunity to thank all your unseen
workers for your services only a few of
you have representations or an outlet to
interact with us but we love all of you
and appreciate your hard work
covers cool approach of letting the
talent do what they want is a huge part
of my Holo project is so beloved and
successful but it can't be easy to help
some of the more outgoing talents
navigate the depths of the Internet with
with its copyright our guidelines many
clashing cultures and the like things
don't always work out perfectly
perfectly but that an agency like this
is functioning at all in the first place
only thanks to the her heran affort that
all of you are putting
Ino
Shan and Senai and all the many many
work we don't have a name for thank you
for all you're doing we know that when
we s in a portion of it goes it when we
s a portion of it goes to the
corporation behind the TS but because
all of you are so awesome it makes it
actually even easier to justify throwing
money at anime girls and boys we simp
for you as well also happy birthday
Yago hey happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday woo
woohoo yeah I just wanted to uh include
this because I I thought it was um a
nice something that had to be sad and
yeah just felt uh it kind of fits in
here it kind of had to go in here but
let's go back to our
evid this was a video guys check this
video out it was is funny it has a
cardboard cut out of
me I think I'm completely regained my
memory by now everything's cool by the
way yeah that was funny look at that if
you if you find it on redit this was
funny I can't I can't show you right now
cuz I don't have the video man I can't
spring capture
video let me in let me in with my new
member
emotes thanks for using my new member
emotes for this thank you thank you
thank you thank you yeah nice meme
really really really good reminds me of
the one that cie also
has a new unit to measure time with one
Phoenix down Revival equals 6 hours yeah
apparently my channel has been
terminated for 6 hours and by the
way because up until now in whole life
streams have gotten banned but but never
before has someone in Hall Al had their
Channel
terminated I've made
[Music]
history um yeah I I I I don't know why
they had to go that far but okay there
was by the way for the people who want
clarification there was never a reason
for it it was a
mistake
yeah I was a bit worried at first but I
have to say I ended up really enjoying
the
situation it was just so funny and um I
I really want to thank everyone
who this was a video as well by the way
it's like uh it's me and her arms and
then and then disappearing you got to
check that out that's pretty cute as
well thank you everyone for like uh
doing this together with me this was
also pretty funny what is that saying
lethal Force to protect the sa of saws
and secret 76 herbs and spices is offer
in case of that K Resurrection protocol
during your time as a store manager Ki
may die one or multiple times this
community is amazing I have to say uh
this is a normal and expected part of
store operations when this happens
follow the below steps and K will
shortly revive again happy healthy and
ready to lead our company I wasn't quite
happy it took me a few
hours first sweep all all sweep up all
of the K ashes be careful not to get
other de mixed in next place place place
place place place place the ashes in a
designated Flame or R hardened container
and place the container in a very well
ventilated area for your safety do not
store or use gasoline or other flammable
liquids and Vapors in the vicinity of
this container set up a table nearby and
place a fleshly
folded uniform a plate of Nutella toast
and a glass of
tea set up privacy screens around the
container wa for tented to
revive oh man I love you guys so much I
love you guys so
much oh this is so
adorable oh yeah and by the way um I I
honestly I did not expect this to have
have this effect but I um trended in
many countries such as Philippines
Australia Canada uh and so on and I also
uh trended just uh in in Te technical
stuff or
whatever and you
don't thank you everyone I did not
expect this to blow up like that but
yeah a phoenix dying is quite a huge
thing I must say it's quite Scandal
so
bu our boss Rises From the Ashes if only
we'd get a race or get paid my boss died
this morning and she sent me
this I Liv [\h__\h]
you can't get me down I'm a phoenix you
can't get a phoenix down that
easily oh my
God you guys amateurs
amateur I'm a feeling I'm an immortal
not anymore I'm
Eternal oh yeah K before getting banned
K after getting
banned that was a awesome thank you guys
for the super chats oh my God thank you
thank you thank you
it was a quite quite fun time that I
[Laughter]
had and no slack for us give holid KP
employees because the channel got
terminated emergency me contest yeah
thank you for using my meme com uh uh
meme meme um template for
[Laughter]
that what what I didn't download
anything no that must have been just
because my mouse was there or something
in the moment I screenshotted it I
didn't down with
anything and this one wait this was this
one in the beginning oh no oh okay but
yeah D thank you and this one is the
last
one rest in peace
k no I am back I will never be dead
never you can't get me down dad e only
my friends
[Music]
that was the last one thank you guys
there's even more if you want to check
out more of these memes there's a bunch
of bunch of them on Twitter and a bunch
of them on Reddit and thank you guys all
so much for doing this with
me you
got so so well you know um actually with
my with my debut I prepared um a song uh
I I like to say I pulled a Cali by um
preparing my original song for my debut
I like to say that that is uh pulling a
cie you know cuz uh Callie cie is the
amazing one who did that she she
released an original song on her debut
day and impressed everyone with that and
I thought I want to do the same so I
also thought this song is pretty fing
because it's about a phoenix so shall we
sing
everyone listen to H
please this is the first time I seen
this life
okay
echo echo wow
wow ion don't forget to stream
[Music]
H wo
tell me I can hear it C tell me
[Music]
I will live to keep on fighting till the
dawn
[Music]
speee
ah
answer don't break I will never give up
don't break h
[Music]
Li and come at the break of day I've
been trying to find my
destiny but they keep pushing and
pulling me a stay if I go wrong what
awaits me in the
dark could you tell me please where I
need to go
[Applause]
[Music]
guar tell me I can hear it clearly tell
me Co
[Music]
blazing FL show
me Lance and in the next life too I
promise I will find you
[Music]
thank you
everyone thank you that was my original
song H music video is already up on
YouTube if you want to listen to it
after the stream the music video If you
haven't seen it yet or if you have
already seen it want to see it again I
totally got it of course you want to see
it
[Music]
again everyone watch the video and
stream it on Spotify or iTunes uh
YouTube music uh Amazon music uh all
these kind of places which by the way
this song came with a this song came
with um with a voice pack with my first
ever voice pack as well so if you want
to hear my voice pack is also available
on geek Jack and
boo your s is your song is my alarm
clock wow thank
you so
actually
uh I'm I'm ending early that's all I
prepared for my that's all I prepared
for my um de stream godam it
by thank you for congratulating me
thank you thank you thank
you well guys
um actually that's
yeah I thought this was would go an hour
oh well kind of miscalculated there kind
of
miscalculation I will uh read the super
chats for this stream a little bit later
on anyway thank you guys so much for
supporting me while I was
terminated but
YouTube
Remember it's not that easy to bring a
phoenix
down I will always come back you can't
get rid of me that
easily I'll be back so yeah today should
have been Sims for stream but that will
be postponed it will be it will be
happening soon and uh tomorrow I have a
collab with good Senpai oh no she's not
my Senpai anymore let's go back to
no we're in the same generation same
generation also thank you guys so much
for the Super Chat I might be um I might
do a super chat reading later on
depending on if I get my stuff that I
have to work on today J or
not thank you all so much for your Super
Chat thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank Youk thank
you for the
support yeah and I I'll see you soon um
for the next streams thank you guys so
much for hanging out with me that was a
great redut I have to
say great
Revival thank you thank
you and in German we
say do you remember what we say in
German at the end of our streams do you
remember
[Music]
thank you
thank should I just keep this running on
so uh it's 1
hour should I just should I just keep it
running I'm just going to keep it
running for like 12
[Music]
minutes Credit Credit time is a bit long
so actually by the way yesterday I was
like um when I saw that I was like what
what what first I was like what the hell
is how what I was like really shocked I
went through a bunch of stages of grief
there but then I was like after I was
like what the [\h__\h] I was more like it
what I was more confused after that and
then I was I was sad for a little bit
because I was like it did I do something
wrong or like I don't know what's going
on V can I stream tomorrow blah blah
blah why did I get terminated not only
banned what the hell I didn't even get a
didn't didn't even get a you know email
or something I just got here well you
can rewatch this whole archive later on
in like 10 minutes cuz I'll be doing
this ending credits for 10
minutes yeah uh and then I was like wait
I'll get i'll get re rein how do you say
re reinstated soon
enough you got a tangent are back
too yeah I I was like wait no I get R
this soon enough I don't have a
stream I don't have a stream coming up
either so I'll be fine right I'll fine
I'll be fine for sure so then I I
started thinking about it how funny this
situation is getting terminated no one
in her life ever got terminated let's
see it in a positive way it's the
first and I I read some funny comments
from everyone and seeing how fitting
this is for a phoenix to get
terminated I was like okay let's make
the best out of the
situation the thing is though even
though I was I was like you know because
I was terminated obviously I can't
stream right so you would think that I
would have more time to work on my stuff
that I have to do but
instead thank you thank you your boy
thank you thank you than soon I I'll be
doing a Super Chat reading
eventually uh what was I
saying what was I
saying damn I forgot what I was
saying what was I saying
oh yeah oh yeah I I I I I I thought you
would you would think that I would have
a lot of time to work on stuff you know
but actually this whole thing made me
procrastinate so much yesterday I had so
much fun with it I was looking for memes
for hours and hours I was Ming myself
for hours and hours then I Was preparing
for this stream for hours and hours I
did I literally just um I had so much
fun with this I barely worked on what I
was want what I wanted to work on
yesterday
[Music]
which is why the stream today is only so
short because I have to catch up on all
the stuff that I I didn't do
yesterday I I'll be working on all of
that after this stream
[Music]
but yeah I had I had lots of fun
um that was funny let me drink some tea
everyone stay
hydrated it was like a festival it was a
party it was a [\h__\h]
[Music]
party and then I was um I saw
how is crazy like I after I got revived
so many of you guys decided to like join
the join
kfp I I I I thank you so much for
everyone who decided to support
me I know the Reverb is on I know I
know it's this Ted's
talking this is my podcast welcome to my
podcast guys our sponsors today are H
talk
and I don't know that's the only sponsor
we have I need some more
sponsors K
[Music]
podcast oh man oh yeah also today is uh
Yo's Birthday everyone go wish him a
happy birthday on Twitter he tweeted uh
already so you can reply to that and
wish him a happy birthday I think he
would be very
happy me
also welcome to all the members welcome
welcome I don't know why um the
membership emotes are so effed up right
now um like in my chat as well I didn't
change anything but now it displays them
like it doesn't display them and I think
like the people who watch on on the on
the phone also still still can't see
thank you for the Super Chat thank you I
think the people still can't see though
the emot I hopeing we get back to normal
soon it's so weird also I mean my
channel got revived and um my videos and
everything everything is back to normal
but all of my all of my community posts
got
deleted they're just
gone oh thank you guys for the super
chats we not at all so that's that's
kind of a bad
[Music]
yeah completely completely yeated them
out there I don't know I don't know if
they're going to come back and I hope
the emotes going to be fixed
eventually cuz it mes it messes up my
chat that's the only that's the only um
that's the only Grant uh I have but
other than that I had a great time I had
a great time being germinated so
you besides that I was absolutely having
the best time of my
life oh yeah when my death counter is up
to one let's see how how often we can
make this happen I feel honestly I'm
looking forward now to being terminated
again
I want to be terminated Again YouTube do
it again do it I want to debut again
yeah also this is funny because I
actually I I was like um you know my
debut was uh I I had a bad microphone at
my debut I was really nervous and I
would say that in the first week and so
on I had a lot of technical problems and
everything just didn't go that well
maybe so it's I feel like K is trending
again so yeah I was like um I would like
to redo my
debut I would like to do my debut all
over
again and just act as if nothing like
this ever happened before and here we go
my wish got granted
[Music]
is trending really where I collected
like a lot of people sent me screenshots
yesterday of uh me trending in various
countries and I saved all of them and I
I made a collection in in America please
send me a screenshot okay now a million
people are going to send me a screenshot
please don't spam my
Twitter oh in Canada as well Canada
Malay as well really
oh my God Russia really please send me
all the screenshots of Indonesia
too this is so grass this is just so
grass please send me screenshots of that
worldwide
trending send me screenshots please I
want to save all of them this is so
ridiculous you would think that if my
channel gets terminated I would be down
for a little bit and like be like [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] and I would be angry or
something and stressed out and stuff I
just had the best time of my life
man I had such a good time this
Legendary
Legendary but you know how when you
check my channel it would say um it said
something like my channel was like
terminated because of spam and uh what
was the other thing like what was it
spam and uh what was the other thing you
guys probably
know misleading content oh yeah and I
was like
what why and then you know I didn't get
any emails or anything but um of course
my management tried their best to get it
resolved as soon as possible so they got
they got one reply from YouTube but I
think it was an automated automated
reply
because um the automated
reply said YouTube doesn't allow content
that encourages dangerous or illegal
activities that risk serious physical
harm or
death and I'm like wait wait how did I
how
what how what did I
do when and I was trying to like
literally remember what I did wrong like
if I actually said something bad that
could be misinterpreted in that
way I was like actually worried for a
moment but I I I just I was just like
okay whatever we got we got to wait it's
already 1 hour
now oh well yeah so anyway that was a
lie after that after that we got no
reply and we just got reinstated at some
point yeah so it was an i in the end we
got another reply which uh basically
said
yeah basically said everything's
cool uh wait yeah I just said
everything's cool you didn't do
anything chill you got you got no okay
it it was it was not nothing is just
after review of your account we have
confirmed that your YouTube account is
not in violation of our terms of service
as such we have unsuspended your
account so yeah I I did nothing wrong I
did nothing
wrong so with that being said I think
I've cleared myself from all
crimes and all
wrongdoings as I have never done
anything
wrong and we are totally not a
cult and I'm totally paying my
employees
yes that's what's happening I am
innocent
[Music]
okay YouTube also acknowledg the fact
that I am innocent
okay so once again we have reached 1
hour that's that's that's the time that
the debut should be that's why I wanted
to wait for an
hour everyone I'll be the S see you soon
de byebye I'll be the
same oh
[Music]
man
funny thank you all for the super chats
and the memberships I'm going to do a
separate stream for for the super chats
[Music]
n