[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
thank you questions
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
what
why isn't show the chat
yeah
okay
chat doku
I I refreshed it with the new link
or
uh
what up oh
[Music]
what
we should be right there
what do you mean a muted
why do several people say muted
no no no no no no no no
question is just
all right I'm not meaning that the chat
is maybe muted I didn't get one guy I
got two guys at least
how about
it
I changed the size by 100 pixels and
suddenly you decide to show up mm-hmm
how it is
see how it is wow
hello
[Music]
sorry for the delay ah
I was stuck in traffic I wasn't like
sleeping or anything
um
here
[Music]
I know I wasn't driving of course I was
not driving
ah
yeah yeah
there's traffic in Austria I swear to
God of course we're not some kind of
like
land in in an ocean
I mean
[Laughter]
yeah we don't even have an ocean you
didn't have to do me like that man
okay we don't have an ocean I know
hello
I know that I'm aware of that
okay again guys hello
how's it going
do we even have a seat no we don't have
an ocean well we have beautiful lakes
that are prettier than some oceans out
there I mean some beaches
um
yeah welcome to the strong
no I did not forget to tweet I tweeted
pretty late but I did I mean
right before I switched scenes I tweeted
it out
um
stream oh so happy
I am in a great mood because of that yes
wow
wow a crazy drinking from Burger King so
good yum yum yum yum
man what I don't know why what it is
about the crispy chicken I think I know
I know what it is I know exactly what it
is but you know that's just how you say
it
but
um it's so good
yes
we are gonna play this is so quiet but
maybe it'll be a little bit louder later
I'm gonna play
uh the new
Hospital oh
[Music]
where's my now and now it's working
I'm going to make this louder because I
also barely hear it ah yeah
foreign
and and it's really good and I played a
little bit like 30 minutes alone but
we're going to
we're going to start a new career
where's my what's with my mouse
my mouse is confusing me
um I'm gonna have a chill drawing time I
don't draw much uh anymore I don't know
how to draw anymore it's ridiculous
how much I have
the detoriorated deteriorated
deteriorated
you know
the Terrio rated what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
um
um yeah but maybe in this game you don't
have to be good at drawing you just have
to figure out how to correct the
algorithm so he
um we'll see what we can do I'm playing
in full screen on my Wacom cintiq so I
can use my pen
um it's really comfortable to play like
this this game
foreign
you start out dude this is like there's
a really
really quiet
background uh
like some piano sounds here and then now
that now it's stopped again and I hear
the TV but this is really quiet didn't I
just oh I didn't accept it oh there you
go
that's even then it's
bear I mean it's it is supposed to be
quiet I think you know quiet vibe
well
I don't know why we have
we have uh
uh What's this called again
a newspaper
newspaper on top of our uh canvas or is
this canvas made out of
oh someone's knocking hey look he's
drawing with this big brush but I can
only make small this makes no sense
immersion broken
even my biggest one is not as big as the
brush that he's using
immersion broken I didn't why am I not
moving
my refresh it okay hey I'm done and now
it went to the fire oh no oh no it
landed in the fire
on you
everybody so you have like uh stuff that
you can interact with however I already
know I can't really interact with this
except for the TV but like the bed it
tells you don't go to sleep now
well we have a visitor hello it's so
cute how the house comes back down when
you leave
and you're free rocks behind on the rant
um here take this scrunched up paper
well that's not money
I'm sorry buddy but I have a new tenant
lined up you're evicted
that is like so ridiculous that you can
do that so quickly but even more
ridiculous is what I just saw
uh like yesterday uh
uh house Owners Association
what I I watched uh what's his name
again
John Oliver's uh little thing on house
the house Owners Association how [\h__\h]
crazy they are like literally they're
gonna like you know they're gonna charge
you thousands and thousands of dollars
for like having a bench or maybe having
your trash can a little bit too visible
if you look over in a certain angle and
all that [\h__\h] like really ridiculous
right or having one garden frog too much
in your garden and [\h__\h] and and and then
they're gonna charge you forever and
then and then and then and then once you
pay that they maybe charge you even more
for ridiculous reasons and then you
can't get at like it's ridiculous it's
just ridiculous and suddenly they can
show up your doorstep and say hey so
we're gonna kick you out now because
this and that and we we bought your
house for four dollars
the house that you own for many
thousands hundreds thousands of dollars
you we will buy it from you here is our
lawyer with this contract and we will
buy it from you for four
dollars what and it's already bought
like now we have to go like something
like that apparently that is possible I
am absolutely stunned that is
fascinating and uh terrifying but um
yeah
okay yeah you gotta watch the uh what's
it called
um John Oliver's most recent piece on
YouTube
um
he won't he warned me in the beginning
of his show that uh everybody under a
certain age should not watch this
because you will never own a house
realistically and then last week tonight
yeah
and so they prepared a separate piece
for everybody who's under but I didn't
even I didn't watch that separate piece
I just wanted to watch this one because
it was also interesting and it was very
interesting but I think in Austria we
don't have the house Owners Association
but it's [\h__\h] ridiculous it's already
[Music]
something that was also really good
um was the one
um uh time shares the one on time shares
that's another thing that you guys have
over there although I think I think we
have it in Austria too maybe we have it
but it's not really like
um
uh not so
like out there I don't know do we have
time shares but like holy [\h__\h] I didn't
know like I heard about timeshares here
and there but I didn't know Time Shares
are like such an insanely bad thing over
there and then there's like companies
that want to like save you and help you
get out of that but those are also a
scam
holy [\h__\h] what this is um
crazy oh my God anyway let me give you a
ride back to town let me go by the boat
okay we got holy [\h__\h]
like all these things that I'm learning
about recently that
uh are not so pleasant about living in
America but I think time shares
it seems it says something about the
Museum of the monsters the rest of the
Texas hidden behind stains and crinkles
it seems like timeshares are I think
they have the outside of America too but
are they this terrible everywhere sand
castle want to destroy it
is it going away from me no I felt like
it
scams around every corner yeah
holy macaroni Bobby let's go thank you
for kicking me out I guess I'm gonna
start a new life now I needed this like
I needed someone to push me anyway
um
HOA fees plus my mortgage payments plus
insurance payments plus utilities with
medical insurance as well a lot of us
are really stressed out about money oh
no it actually applies to you
[\h__\h] age away because apparently
um
so they said this in in that show that
what 80 or 70
of uh houses in America
ours like they have an HOA um so it's
like really hard to find one without
um 80 yeah
so that's really rough and um the HLA
they can do whatever they [\h__\h] the [\h__\h]
they want and you have to do what they
say
because uh they don't they can make
their own laws basically that's
ridiculous
they don't follow like the law of the
place they're in no they make their own
law oh yeah that was like oh there's
another thing they can do is like set up
like a speeding ticket thingy they they
see like how how much you're speeding
and even if you're just like
one
uh how to say this in English I don't
even know miles per hour or half 0.5
miles per hour too fast
uh they can charge you like so much for
that holy [\h__\h]
they can they start well they can start
with whatever they want they start with
sixty dollars or not then maybe from
your second speeding ticket which you
know you may have really only very
slightly very very very very very
slightly uh gone over the limit uh they
can charge you then like have 500 bucks
and then it goes up to a thousand bucks
and so on on oh my God it's just no you
cannot step out of the association if
you want to live there you have to be
part of it and it's 80 of houses in the
US are uh associated with a Home Owners
Association oh
it's unbelievable it's unbelievable it's
unbelievable
it's it's sugoi
Benjamin
so you are the island guest of Mr Lee
what happened
uh I have been evicted by the homeowners
association of [\h__\h] hell they're here
too it seems I'm trying to escape oh
that is trouble
absolutely you deserve better if you ask
me I say as my grandfather used to say
well life gives you lemons make lemonade
hahaha
you're gonna notice are these are
fantastic you can finish my painting no
maybe you'll recognize the tools I found
them at the flea market
so funny
[Music]
but there are not creating any Magic by
themselves as you can see here's your
old brush and basic palette let's see
what you can do you should try changing
up the colors
I saw what movie did to this and it's
terrifying I just want to change
one thing I think it doesn't even matter
you know because
this is basically tutorial he will not
care
he will not care
surely but let me link this in the sky a
little bit nicer
uh
he just wants me to change it up a
little bit
made the whole background turn into fire
like he was standing in a field of fire
with this person's
uh wife dead on the ground
and yeah
ashes everywhere
oh some terrifying but I wasn't I wasn't
even surprised
but you know
you should we should send umay to like a
a doctor
of like a
psychotherapist for
uh evaluation like make her draw things
or like explain what she sees in other
drawings
and I want to hear the opinion
oh
anyway
what colors do we have here
[Music]
that is that looks like a banana now
but yeah it's all right
do you see what I'm doing
first he was holding up again and you
know I love buckets
but you know what's even better than
baguettes and I will spread this
knowledge
awesome
it sounds so French because I guess well
it is French
oh
[Music]
awesome
what
um
an Austrian boomerang
[Music]
I mean that's really all this picture
needed in my opinion
but
let me add some flowers
because
eaten on a flower field
is quite picturesque
and quite soothing to the heart
so really harmonizing combination you
know
we started off with such a
heated tangent that we need this right
now to calm our nerves
you know
calm the [\h__\h] down
you were just
you're literally just like deep here
in the bird world
you have nothing to say
I watched a couple of
those videos
I watched the bird one I watched the
uh
um what was it monkey one I watched the
rodents one
um
and maybe one more the insect one I
didn't watch yet
that and I was like another one
and I watched which one was it I'm not
sure yeah tier two it's so funny did you
know it's ironic because he makes
tearless with animals and tear in German
there is German for animal did you know
did you know so a social animal list
tier list just animalist wow
fascinating
[Music]
absolutely fascinating he has a big
round nose
because I guess that's himself
but this will be after he awakened
love multilingual puns yeah
it was genius
those videos are so good
oh my God wait what's that what does
that remind me of
okay can you look here for a second
Benjamin okay
we have like this this beak
pupils and this is kind of terrifying
not gonna lie
you look kind of terrifying
[Music]
that that the face now looks much more
like him
so I definitely did him a favor I would
say
and see now he's really happy
he's happy
smirking
because now he now he has quasa
Pringles man ah
no I want to improve it
you could like really speedrun this game
I think just draw whatever
but really
especially as a streamer
can't do it like that can you
some feeling into it
make it make every
painting
look
worthy of being actually yeah where the
fun in them with being actually looks
somewhere on a
holy [\h__\h] look at this huge hand still
this is not accurate he drew himself so
inaccurately he has
huge
monster hands
like this
this is what his hands look like
[Laughter]
yeah you don't no you don't even have to
try with these hands because they're not
an anatomically accurate
there's no skin color
I saw that you can like upgrade
um like your tools like a different
brushes and all that but I wonder can
you also get different colors
[Music]
anyway just his hand was pink now
colossal
yeah his other her head this is the
Colossal
massive Yahweh hands yeah
it does say basic oh
ah
and now I can but probably later then
okay yeah like a new set of or maybe
they should give me just a palette not a
palette like a you know like a you know
rainbow color thingy
um
I'm cutting more into this than I wanted
to I just wanted to get him a cross wall
to reach enlightenment
now I'm making him shoes
so
um perform the stream the reason why I
got a little bit late
it's because I my brother called me
um
he was like hi
I'm here now I'm moving in today
um but can I borrow your
error mattress I have like this huge
um big air mattress in case a lot of
people sleep over because I have a guest
bed that fits two people and I have a
big air mattress that fits two people
cute and um
yeah
he remembered that because we used it
for like a Christmas two years ago I
think
when my family slept over
yeah so because he has no bed yet he has
some furniture
but it's not here yet so for now he'll
just sleep
on my mattress
so he came over to pick it up and I was
like you know what I can help you
bring it to your place because then I
also gave him my water cooker like my
second I have a second water cooker you
um
yeah and what else I gave him two
pillows
and some
uh uh is he just starting from scratch
not quite like he has some stuff he told
me he has a bed he has a like a shelf
probably a table a chair he does have
like basic things yeah
so he should be fine
he'll be fine he'll be fine
[Music]
yeah but so a couple things I gave him
for now because he doesn't have anything
for like two days
and then I uh it was quite a lot so I
decided I'll just go with him because I
wanted to see his place anyway
um
I just realized we both have a black
white striped t-shirt partly look is
this just the artist's look that you
have to wear in order to be like a
proper artist
and we both have Berets well I
understand but rays are very artistic
voila
beautiful
I think oh I think I really improved it
wow cute
guy that's the uniform yeah
he has no hair I wish I could give him
hair but he has literally no hair
you also wear a striped shirt like that
every time you draw a chicken
oh
yeah I think I'm done I guess
all right
yeah so I checked out his place and it's
quite good
I think he will
be fine there
the artist I remember is still there it
seems like the tools found their own
please keep them as well as the Isel now
you can draw just like the old times
speaking of old times but you try
selling the painting I've got a table up
by my shop you can use meet me there
foreign
kind of so I know I should go here and
pick up
a map for free
and I also know there's money over here
hope protein gets settled all right yeah
it will be very helpful he'll come and
finally uh you know get
uh Sims one working for me tomorrow
probably because tomorrow I have the day
off so
we'll do that tomorrow this umbrella
this sun umbrella looks like those tiny
wooden ones for cocktails just sized up
also know you can look into the trash
cans and some of them have something
some don't
okay this one maybe
for now doesn't have anything but maybe
a different one and the NPCs
they give you quests and also this
Village is called Fenix
Phoenix Phoenix
wow
[Music]
our beautiful Town some people call it
the mecca of art because of our Museum
but I claim this port to be the truth of
Finnick I mean the sweet for grown of
fish in the air the seagulls Heavenly
what is one of the world's most
established art museums compared to this
about me well I was laughing but a young
land when I first set sail and I mean I
can't do this voice and French accent
I immediately understood that I was
meant to spend I can do German accents
meant to spend an Austrian accent than
to spend more left is embiosis with the
ocean
that is so Austrian go on
big fishes in the fish
is big enough to eat me in one quick
Nibbler
um
interesting
the gossip of sailors by the scuttled
boot was my education
Gabriel on the other hand wants to go to
college
to become a land Looper why Pusa I don't
why
[Laughter]
look at it just look at it
okay
um cool story bro
yeah I got a pop-up easel should we like
start
um no you know what I will go up first
and get me some
you know first first of all
they'll sell this
let's see how much
well the chef surely will understand the
value of croissant right
Steve 50 free if you cook like you paint
I'll hire you on the spot wow what a
compliment I I guess I'll take those 53
I'm not like you know I don't think it
will change much
thank you wow I love how they throw
money around like that
okay Benjamin let's talk again
yeah I use it already good you managed
to figure out how to stay left by
yourself how exciting to see your ad on
street again you know the table is
portable if you want you could buy it
off ah
sorry
I will buy it off of you
yes Mercy it's yours you can take it
with you to sell out wherever you want
see this is wonderful we can sell art
wherever we go now
I'm sure you'll draw Masterpiece this
fit for Museum in no time we'll see
about that
we'll see about that I love that
the the pigeons
they're just like like cardboard
two-dimensional but kind of
three-dimensional it's funny let's check
this trash can
what's inside
a dirty paper yay we can use that for
um
for drawing something on it protest Sun
I'll take that too because we can draw
on that too
let's ask you if you need something
Birmingham
[Music]
um
what simple people call Food
um I call it culinary art some people
will understand and be absorbed by my
flavor refusion
what
culinary art yes my concept is Uncle
French Fusion I mixed your old British
kitchen
Francois voila
I swapped garlic with English Korea
it's a sensational wow
sounds
yummy soon very soon this place will be
well known and appreciated just like the
Museum of Master it takes time to gain
trust I've only been open for three
years my first customer will come at any
time
he doesn't give me his quest yet I know
he has one though
okay maybe they want me to do this first
let's draw on this dirty pepper
that was really dirty
let's
start with the basic coat of white
I remember in the um
in the previous game pink
using the color pink was like you know
that's very
um
what's the word recommended because you
automatically have
but I don't know it just doesn't it's
just not not good not good
not good at all
not desired yeah they don't like pink
there's just an algorithm that just does
not like pink
so anyway on this dirty paper oh my God
my mouse
on this dirty paper I will draw
someone
let's see if I if koala
can draw
um
I don't know when it stopped I always
start with eyes but then I always regret
it because
balance is bad
let's draw I wish the museum was a bit
louder but it's supposed to be like this
I guess
they hate pink yeah why but I I mean
I mean I guess I understand
like it's
they they algorithm they just wanted to
see more sophisticated maybe maybe
you know what I'm gonna draw I will need
a reference picture of mummy
I'm gonna draw mummy
mummy
in
can I find it on Google if I type it in
oh yeah wonderful
oh wait oh
[Music]
Aya here I got one reference
new costume
so cute
I love her new costume she looks so cute
with those glasses
I don't think I'm gonna draw those
oh and I really love her her Berry
um
foreign
can we get much smaller
no we can't
was that dogs barking
it's a really chill atmosphere this game
is like so chill and I I already love
the improvements they made
um
and right now like in the previous game
I think you start off with having paid
to rent already
so it's already like really stressful
but here you start off with having
nothing to pay
in particular like there's no time
stress
so you can just you know get drawing and
take your time with it I think you can
buy an apartment later probably
but until you get to that point
you already have to make some money this
game seems to be more fleshed out yeah
well you already got kicked out so
take your time I guess
your time
so I'm gonna take my time
to draw moment I will not
take so much time with every single
painting I think like for example with
the quest ones
I might just you know
quickly whip something up
don't want to waste too much time you
know
see the eyes are looking good because
there's three different brown tones
that's nice
she has beautiful brown eyes mommy no
I'm not using my mouse I'm using a Wacom
welcome welcome cintiq
okay
okay now now my problem is
this not her mouth
and too high
balance
okay okay
foreign
bgm
like still a chill one but
sorry guys am I back now
hello
yeah OBS disconnected me that was not
necessarily YouTube
back
I'm back hello
okay mummies
new hairstyle I like it
now I wish they had layers but I mean
this is not even an issue of getting
more options later no it's just an issue
of well this is not digital art even
though I'm kind of drawing digitally
right now if you think about it but in
theory he's painting traditionally so
they're just there shouldn't be the
option
to draw of layers it would break the
immersion
but that's a
if anything digital artist
that is
[\h__\h] me up
oh
what well actually
what what is that gonna be an option
imagine the next Plus for two game
him actually going for digital art like
him being like um you know what I've
been there done that I will now
move on to something else I need to
learn something I need to challenge
myself I will now do digital art
hmm
that would be interesting
I mean
I mean it wouldn't change
really like the story much you could
just do the same thing again
I love how mommy went for something like
pretty simple
in her new outfit
like a long long skirt that I I loved I
would legit just wear it like that
what she chose
long skirt and then like a white fluffy
sweater underneath a knit knitted
sweater mm-hmm
so cute
yup
[Music]
her eyebrows are so high up though damn
looking cute but I wish I had layers so
I can color this better hmm
just have to do it very roughly
berries
freeze hmm
[Music]
oh cute
okay now let me try
there he is
some green stuff
okay and
skin color
maybe just like the Shadows because
sometimes I see artists
you know when they sketch stuff they
only really draw
like the Shadows but should I this is
really the closest the closest choices
we have this like orangish
tone
um
or the pinkish one
I think white is best here
foreign
yeah well I mean just for like the
shadow
we're just gonna we're just gonna do a
little shadow
okay
I'll I'll go with this one actually as a
shadow I think it looks pretty skin
color like as long as it's not the whole
the whole body
we definitely need more colors later
mmm
an anime girls tends to have like the
whitest of white skin that you could
ever imagine
I'll just do it like this you know
they'll probably not recognize the time
that I wanted now actually I feel like
there may be like an algorithm where
they like know how much time you spend
on the picture and that might play into
the price but they don't really know
because they're they're just computer
Bots
there's NPCs they don't know how much I
actually put into those
I don't understand
they don't get it oh you know what I
could do the same with the hair
don't have to like
fill out everything
um
it's like real life hey I can't detect
if you put your heart into it exactly
which is what we will use to our
advantage eventually
we must use it to our advantage
decently cute is how I would describe
this I should have wait I can continue
painting on this right if I just put it
down once because it stays in my
inventory I think I can continue
painting afterwards
should we risk it for the biscuit
because I want to
um buy ah wait do I have the money for
it
because I just bought the no I don't I
probably don't even have the money for
it
um
want to buy like a fuzzy brush
[Music]
one second I think I think
oh yeah I can continue drawing on it
okay I'll go okay
the nuts you know what let's just really
quickly just to get some money because I
I need
I don't know why I'm drawing the movie
on the city paper but now I'm just
drawing something to make quick money on
um
on the proper canvas
close off
did you hear it he speaks our language
yeah he gets it
um
for everything Story related how about I
just draw croissants all the time
um
like everything
what a crunchy buttery soft Looking
Glass oh
the bgm stopped why
[Music]
song
yeah we're using pink let's see how that
goes is that a shrimp what the hell how
would that look like a shrimp to you
it's a beautiful gorgeous Flawless
croissants and I'll be drawing more and
more croissants for the rest of the game
mmm
look at my technique
benefit
the technique of okay look at him go
foreign
[Music]
if we can't have a brush yet to create a
gradient and shading we just gotta do
with ourself you know
whoa
[Music]
okay let's sell this
yeah I don't got the Shadows
my
um
okay let's sell this
do you like croissant
please enjoy this song
[Music]
46 free fresh like a morning baguette no
like a morning croissant but you get it
he kind of gets it 46.
what about the other one
depending on the person it really can
change quite a bit from what I've seen
do you not want the kuma phone
she's standing there he's oh there we go
he has an idea yeah 61 that's better
than before all right I'll take it
[Music]
now let me see what you have and how
much cost
ooh 79 for a crayon crayon can be really
pretty good oh
bro the the sponge
mmm
sprinkles
sprinkle sprinkle Little Star watercolor
box [\h__\h]
why is that so expensive man we gotta
throw some good stuff
the light brush could also actually in
the even the spray can
help us quite a bit maybe I should save
up for the spray can first
mmm
[Music]
in that case let me um
try to make some more money first here
all right
yeah the one is one crayon 79 bucks
unbelievable okay I will continue moving
later I have to make some money first
let's let's
I don't know
how much would this do how much money
would this make huh probably not much
right because they probably know how
much time I'm spending
oh
this really
probably wouldn't do the trick I don't
know what to draw
uh I don't think those pay highly what
what is that like a
is there a meta
what do you have to draw to get
something like really worth it out of it
I don't know
let's find out okay I have an idea I
want to I need to draw something
artistic
foreign
I feel like they probably would like
like edgy colors like dark
colors filling up the whole canvas
night sky beautiful night sky
um
oh
and then
I want
oh
on the table
just one single candle
and we'll we'll name it
the condole
foreign
but like uh what does a fancy um candle
holder look like
golden candle holder
oh wow wow
[Music]
yes that is tickling my fancy
um so sophisticated
hey is he watching me Benjamin you're
making me kind of nervous you're not
gonna lie
may not
coming I guess it's all right I guess
he's just fascinated by my artistic
sense
she's understandable
understandably so
foreign
something like this hmm
wouldn't you want this standing on your
table
at night but I want to
um set it on fire as well
need some you know need the gold to come
out well
wow
okay
whoa
wait the Catalyst the candle turned out
so pretty wow
this is so good
I wish I had like a spray can to make
the the surroundings you know kind of
um bright only a little bit
a little shadow
wow wow oh my God
looks so good with the little the little
things the little materials and stuff
that I've been given
what could I I wanted to be kind of
empty you know I want it to be empty but
the right side looks a little bit too
empty
um maybe yeah maybe um
the left is a window
which actually
make the window frame Brown
okay
truly Divine thank you but I'm feeling I
should turn on some like
ah one second it's really too quiet like
I I like the vibe but
should be a bit more
audio stock
piano
coffee
mmm
oh
why does this melody sound so familiar
what about this one
[Music]
yeah why not then I'll turn off the one
that is just the bgm not the like other
sound effects
we'll turn the turn them off in game
[Music]
nice
are you hearing this
sure
[Music]
okay nice
ah
isn't it pretty
tell me if it's too loud
[Music]
okay okay I continue
ah I have an idea I have an idea
what to put there
today we're just here to be healed you
know
I know
[Music]
um
just need some
Google inspiration but it's not really
giving me what I what I'm looking for
all right I'll wing it
[Music]
I want like a
like a vase
that looks like it's like from Greece
but it looks antique and right now I
found something more fitting okay okay
oh
they might not like the amount of black
in the picture even though it's really
artistic in my opinion
they might not like it they may not pay
me too much for that
[Music]
he's a thousand
what's a good English translation for
vanausen
so that's not very loopy that bgm hmm
it will continue but it doesn't look so
Ruffians brats buffoons
simpleton's Philistines but I've never
heard of that before
barbarians
yeah I've heard of that one before so
maybe I don't know what that's good
oh my mouse
[Music]
oh this is so relaxing
oh
[Music]
I need a bigger canvas and a smaller
brush even
even for detail but okay
I'm way too into this what the hell
why am I so into this
I feel sleep in this bgm yeah
it is understandable
don't fall asleep challenge
okay so I don't know
just some like ornament
I don't know what's going on there
really
[Music]
get it and now
enough
ew these colors are not sophisticated
enough for my taste what is this green
it's uh
it needs to be like more dull
ew disgusting
would you agree like look at it ew
that's too saturated disgusting
[Music]
oh you go whatever let's draw later when
we get some better tools I want to draw
Anne Berlin like a portrait Style
try to recreate that like old old style
medieval style
my beloved and the Lynn
[Music]
what do flowers look like
oh
I have no idea
foreign
[Music]
don't doubt that you just never have
seen it before it is a totally a flower
Flawless beautiful gorgeous yes
thank you
the table now has a
a nice golden
Edge
to make it look a bit more sufficient
whoa I just wanted to keep it simple
originally but now
[Music]
can't wait that do it like this all the
time I'm just trying to make money right
now but will this really be worth the
money I'm investing in it
at least you can switch the like turn
the canvas in this game
it's like a
such a luxury feature
[Music]
the mindset of a perfectionist
that's right baby
if you don't strive for perfection in
life
at minimum you know you won't get
Perfection all the time but you should
strive for it
otherwise you won't get the most
potential out of your project
no no need to always look you know
kill yourself over not being able to get
Perfection out of something whatever
but I'm done so
um let me turn my German keyboard on
because otherwise I cannot
leh
candle
that is the most accurate way to
pronounce it
wait this is actually really my God
you draw you drew every sale what oh is
that a is that a plant an actual plant
located
let's sell this
maybe the birds will buy it
it's so good please please give me big
money
it's fantastic if you hate Beauty
[Music]
[Applause]
gray is like taking up 90 of the image
problem
hey please come on it's actually really
good Steve you don't get it no Benjamin
come on
maybe there's other characters that like
it though on the other hand because
there's like Punk characters marvelous
65 and I feel like it deserves more more
no no no no let me no no no no let me
bring in somewhere else I know where to
find the punk
[Music]
I love this one well I want to spend any
money on it but look at this are you do
do you even have any money
[Music]
do you want to buy this
no
hey y'all
so sad what do you want by the way
[Music]
no no no no I want to pick it up
she did ask me do you have a minute
hey man wanna help us out with some
posters sure we need to post it for some
totally legal stuff yeah and sure
Rebellion he's supposed to okay you can
use it or whatever okay
let's quickly she wants something that
screams uh Rebellion
just really
quickly
because this is just a sad question I'm
not getting money from this
um
[Music]
a skull
yeah I think I think I know roughly how
to draw a skull
[Music]
or do I
that was some big nostrils
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
how how does that work
[Music]
s
oh no I guess they go like this oh wait
oh
oh that's how that works
that's how skulls work
what about the smile though
[Music]
scary
ah
[Music]
some shading
okay he's his eyes are kind of loopy but
please
please forgive
now actually look
human it doesn't even look like skull
anymore
it looks so dead he looks pretty alive
to me
which he shouldn't even
shouldn't be looking alive
[Music]
oh my God
now here we don't want to spend too much
time so take this
[Music]
here's the post down take this remember
time to spread the revolution maybe
there's a revel in yeah pretty cool if
there is
75. okay
[Music]
obscene
pick it up
we're at 145 but uh wait can I buy the
spray can now
what do you need
I know right
these are dangerous water is danger have
you heard of the danger fish piranhas
fear them I just caught one right
outside of the port they don't belong
here one bite can kill you we need a
warning sign before the land lovers get
hurt swimming I give Benjamin a try but
he had a hard time capturing the danger
and then the danger fish it looked like
a cute clownfish okay I'll help
[Music]
okay
I have an idea
[Music]
uh wait did he not even ah he gave me
one extent to draw on okay
[Music]
let's give it a nice spray tan
pretend
three
[Music]
is that sign that sign in the middle
is that a sign for like nuclear
radioactivity or something like that
[Music]
don't fit the shock yes
radiation Ah that's what I thought yeah
[Music]
I want to draw gouda obviously
good reference
looks
cute
how to capture the cute
[Music]
ah my mouse always gets stuck
red Coulda ah red hmm
are you saying normal gura is not
dangerous
[Music]
there's not much space on this thing
that's supposed to be a star
I want to do like a little thing but
where do I even fit the star
foreign
[Music]
on her fork that screams help please
help me she's going to eat me but nobody
will come to the rescue
nobody will come
[Music]
you will be eaten by gouda and you will
enjoy it
I don't think there really will give me
any more money that is already
programmed into the quest
so no need to put too much effort into
it I think
[Music]
for Abby it's not an Abby it's a human
don't worry
foreign
[Music]
it's just white I think there
I went over the edges on you
I should have taped the edges
what does
what does this little stick man taste
like I wonder maybe it needs some garlic
on top garlic would be nice
need some garlic everything needs some
garlic
well yesterday I made some I'm actually
so proud of me that I yesterday ended up
cooking stuff I was so close to just
taking the lasagna out of the freezer I
love you thank you I love you too
I was so close to just taking the
lasagna out of the freezer
and just going for that
but no
[Music]
I cooked that pasta because I saw that
the it wouldn't even take that much time
it would end up just taking as much time
as the lasagna would take basically
yeah but that pasta
[Music]
I like the idea of like just the basic
cream sauce
it was very very simple
I added some more cream to it though
from my own stuff in the fridge because
I thought it wouldn't be enough
[Music]
but for some reason it can't it came
with cherry tomatoes and somehow they
added like so much sweetness to it
which it was already kind of Swedish
because of the the cream sauce
so that wasn't really necessary but oh
well
taste that smell and the tortellini were
filled with ricotta cheese
it's kind of nice though
if I make it again
Maybe
without the tomatoes and replace it with
something else
they were eight like sour as well but
more sweet than sour
[Music]
questionable recipes
tortellini
needed some meat well and then come with
me I think I was even supposed to be a
vegetarian dish not vegan but vegetarian
at least
[Music]
perfect for ravioli or lasagna too
oh
yeah ravioli
speaking of pasta I saw this really
stupid
um
video maybe you guys saw it too I think
I saw it on a YouTube short
recommended to me
[Music]
um so basically this lady claims to know
an Italian pasta life hack
Straight From Italy like claiming that
people in Italy kind of do this
so what she does is she gets from the
supermarket she gets this like you know
the basic spaghetti the the dry
spaghetti
puts it in like a smoothie Crusher
thingy
and just tears it up crushes it until
it's literally just powder
she's like super confident while doing
this all this June
and then she spreads the powder on her
kitchen counter and then adds two eggs
to it then you know mixes it into a
dough with her hands and it looks like
so [\h__\h] dry like like really hard to
make a dough out of it
spaghetti crimes literally uh eventually
she manages to make something out of it
that looks like dough so she has this
like yellow egg dough and then she like
makes it flat as much as she can with
her
um flat thingy flattening thingy
um
and as she cuts it into like a pretty
wide uh
pasta strips Stripes yeah yeah
um and then she says yeah this way you
can have fresh fresh pasta
much better pasta what an upgrade
um much better than the one that you
would have had
otherwise
yeah
um
which is so stupid because it looked
really disgusting and it's so much more
effort and just if then you can just buy
fresh pasta from the supermarket because
I think they have packaged fresh pasta
as well you know
[Music]
I mean it was obviously just you know
joking for the meme I think I don't
think she was serious she topped it with
just literally she just she just put a
like a can of
um
a can of tomato sauce and dried not even
fresh dried Italian
spice on top herbs herbs on top of it
and it was just like oh
it just didn't look good at all
those noodles were really bad too
[Music]
spicy
so this will now be oh look it's here oh
I got it I got 75 bucks look it's right
here you will always see gouda right
here when you enter it does look like
her but it does look like she's hanging
a small it looks like a like a shrimp
but like a baby Hummer oh
[Music]
my my this sign is also now up on the
buildings like the poster
will be found here and there here as
well
yay we're improving the city
trash can you have something
[Music]
what if I try to sell your sketch
because I think it's this person's
sketch because it says I didn't show you
guys I know it from playing it before
wait let me show you
see oh no wait that's a different one I
think
but I think I don't know it is that
personal it looks like that person
cool so isn't it like so mean that we
try to sell it
it's not even our own art
let's see 18. ah you got five Victor
all right it's pretty shitty so I'll
take it
scam
yeah well what do you think about that
um Sam is not quite right with Steve
what is it with Steve he seems to be
missing something maybe you can pay him
a visit I'm sure he's at his restaurant
as always okay
[Music]
it's for putting it like that he threw
it away but I I showed them that it has
value
for it
[Music]
worse than Asia waste no I'm giving him
confidence he's like oh oh
it's worth something huh the feng shui
is all messed up
oh Monday I got a bad thing chewy in my
restaurant it's probably but nobody is
here could you draw me something with a
nature Vibe okay
you will want to think I think we have a
good amount of sugar instead of
sprinkling is a mix of thing it's ovola
the guest will arrive okay we're not
giving me a canvas for it I have to use
my own canvas oh no I think he did give
me one
okay nature
nature
[Music]
fania
mm-hmm
she has such a complicated outfit but
she has a
straw
let's draw a casual
oh yeah that's a bit better
[Music]
it's a little bit brittle
okay
I'll start with the pink background I
feel like fauna would like that
oh
[Music]
wait
um
before we do that and then regret it but
if there's no green in it with her hair
will be green her hair will be green
maybe he has like you know maybe he
complains if it doesn't have enough
green in it
just wondering um
hopefully not
foreign
[Music]
I mean I can imagine
that he would have grain detectors
so far they haven't really been like
giving individual comments to their art
I've been giving them so it's probably
fun
probably fun
[Music]
where does she have her
that's not in this in this reference
where does she have the
the beauty mark
okay
[Music]
I knew what it's here
I said I wouldn't spend so much time on
the
Quest requests but here I am
[Music]
I drunk as much no
I'm using a
tablet with a screen
[Music]
okay her hair
rough
[Music]
just an occasional here and there ah I
could already buy that brush I still
didn't buy it okay after this we'll buy
my brush
um my spray can but who knows maybe we
can even afford
something better already no the that one
watercolor thing was way too expensive
wait
wait until okay she has like yellow
yellow orangish eyes they're like wow so
captivating
[Music]
so
you look at them and you feel like
they're dragging you and they're like
kind of burning
if you're just burning sensation is it
is it love
it
could be
[Music]
I wish I could zoom in hmm
no she's bald for now which I guess
seems to be like kind of um
common for her
but no I will give her hair because we
need the Green in the picture we need it
we need it
[Music]
with green eyebrows I don't think she
particularly has green eyebrows but
might as well
[Music]
kind of cute not gonna lie
it's winter shining fauna doesn't shed
all right I'm gonna
use a technique called
Wawa
[Music]
um
technique well fascinating
oh
still all good
[Music]
the things you can do with very limited
options I mean have you seen what some
people draw with like paint
it's crazy I might have to redo those
eyebrows
oh
[Music]
what's what what do her bangs look like
I'm having like I'm using fan art as a
reference right now not even the
official official source
not a good idea
I don't understand
how they work
which athlete currently I'm looking at
the Casual one but what whatever
's fine well
she'll have these half twin tails that I
always used to do
I always used to do this too
why am I putting so much effort into
this
he'll just pay me the same amount he
pays me for my goods a green a blank
green canvas
I'm doing it for the stream I'm doing it
for the stream and for fauna
I'm doing it for fauna
this is a really weird way of doing the
hair that I normally wouldn't do
like normally you do you do a sketch you
do outlines
and you fill the you fill it below
the color
this makes absolutely no sense
it is what it is we have to deal with
what we have and now right now this
feels like it's working
looks like towards here what why
it's green
[Music]
twin Tails wait wait wait wait it's not
just windtails
here because the hair sticks are coming
don't worry I'm I'm in the middle
I'm doing my bestie
rare green tool
it's like tourism by in Smash different
color option
[Music]
thank you
yo
I might be actually
talented at traditional art although I
feel like my arm
is losing energy
[Music]
my left arm says freaking noodle arm
doesn't get any more noodle Army than
this I'm just lifting my arm a little
bit and I feel like I can't I can't
[Music]
this reminds me of those like way cookie
boards back in the day
I don't know if people still use those
I talked about before I think but back
in the day there were these like oyukaki
boards means like sketching drawing
and it was like basically like a like a
forum
and
you could
yeah it's like magical draw it had
really simple tools and I think it was
like always always a square
canvas
um
and and oh many of them had the the
option that you could like see
uh the progress like it always recorded
the progress I think
seeing that too it was pretty cool
but they were you know kind of pixely
yeah yeah yeah they were like this
like the the it automatically was like
pixel
art
but that gave it the like a typical boy
cookie
look basically
[Music]
I really liked going on those away copy
boards
I think you could like easily make your
own so I also had my own I think at some
point it's like you you would give your
oikaki board to other artists and be
like hey I'll draw in your away cookie
board so will you join on Maya or a
cocky board it's like a guest book like
a friendship book thingy
but more like a guest book
[Music]
no
and then you can go through like
people's wake-up keyboards and sometimes
you will see some really sick amazing
art like some people who put like so
much effort into it and you're like yo
there's like so little Tools in this how
did you do that
[Music]
laughs
oh my God why am I why am I putting so
much effort
[Music]
foreign
for you guys
[Music]
because I'm not even talking that much
it's very relaxing it's awesome for me
that is great thank you I like barely
and looking at the common Stone so sorry
so you know obviously I have somewhere
else to look otherwise otherwise it's
not going to turn out really great but
you know what we should do I should try
like for one painting I should just look
away and look at the comments while I'm
drawing and we'll see how it turns out
blind drawing we'll do a blind run
oh
I think fauna will like this
[Music]
God why why am I making this so
difficult for myself
stick it in her eye tag
should I do that I wonder if she looks
at her art tag constantly because I
don't know if everyone in whole life
does things the same way I do like
sometimes I say when I Captivate thank
you
using Straight mods with a snap tablets
tablet Wacom tablet I wonder sometimes I
see
and I go on Twitter and I see like a
huge spam all at once like one Japanese
whole life member retweeting like so
much art of themselves I ID does that a
lot too
just so much all at once
[Music]
so that means to me they look at their
art tag a lot but I don't know not
everybody does it the same way
final check said daily she just
retweeted 10. oh
oh okay okay
what she's not I don't think she's here
right now
[Music]
she looks like a like a watermelon
like a watermelon
[Music]
looking like a hot freaking watermelon
he won't
I love watermelons mmm
sneak in a while original
gotta take some screenshots afterwards
[Music]
I wonder if there's even like after
selling it if there's like an option to
see all the art you've drawn
in the game
[Music]
what more nature
could there possibly be
then drawing fauna naked
nature in her most natural form what do
you think about that guys
just uh
very logical question just throwing it
out there
checks out right makes sense I think
which is why I will not bother to give
her any clothes
[Music]
thank you
it's just natural
all natural
yeah yeah
I mean the choker stays on though
obviously
just because I have a personal thing for
chokers
[Music]
that's our arm by the way like elbow arm
area
thank God her hair is covering a lot
[Music]
foreign
she's the new Mona Lisa
wow
all right
very detailed I must say and I'm not
even getting really paid for this
probably
[Music]
mommy wait I didn't draw her horns yet
kind of like this shape should be
[Music]
I hope
hard work minimal play
yeah I mean really
if he is just like starting out broke as
an artist I mean he's not really
starting out I guess because they
recognize him they're like oh are you're
you're just the same as you used to be
you're still the artist that I knew you
as
lore lore lore
[Music]
so I guess he already has some
reputation and some skill
but no tools
[Music]
sad artist life man but even without
all those tools you can still make great
art
[Music]
so
let's show him
hello
[Music]
foreign
's a bit difficult
I want more
options
and the Boba
[Music]
huh
Anatomy
Gray's Anatomy
I don't have enough space actually her
arm really shouldn't be starting there
anyway
I was kind of like bringing in forward
like as if she's like purposefully
pulling her arm
closer look towards kind of almost
turning
away from us but it looks weird on
picture right now so
more like this
[Music]
that's not good to do without with
Outlet at least the kalkini
you wouldn't even be able to see it
really
[Music]
I guess I'll do it what it means
for her naked but okay
I prefer fauna naked but okay what a
thing to say
another thing to say
ruined
I know right oh that's okay how do you
draw a cow pattern
something like this should be all right
didn't it
[Music]
hello
that's nature Boya
hey
one guide again please go back now this
is okay now this is also kind of cute
this is fine
[Music]
let me cook
kind of looks like Misa
from Death Note to me
oh my God she really does
what
right
it's twin towns
[Music]
I went I forgot one thing
laughs
[Music]
the flowers
let's say the more nature wonderful that
is the last little bit of nature that we
needed
[Music]
to make this piece perfect
nature
all
natural
I think I'm good uh
it's pretty good
how much are you gonna pay me for this I
spent like an hour on this but the feng
shui will definitely be improved here is
your little thing
voila the perfect amount of Fame to my
Shoei great work I can almost hear the
guests crowd crowding oh it's in there
it's in there we can barely see it with
a hundred bucks
I guess it's all right ah she's dead
she's there
[Music]
she's there there
can I go in
no
okay it's not like very visible barely
anything yeah
maybe I should have sold it normally I
would be interesting to see the price
that they would offer damn it should
have taken it back and just give him
like a green canvas that's that's
literally what I should have done
um all right
let me see
I can almost afford
a watercolor brush
if I just
[Music]
try a bit more I don't need to buy the
spray can I don't need to buy this spray
can
[Music]
I do don't want the color brush that
looked like it would be so far away for
us what do you want
The Next Bite to see a familiar face
thank you what's about Banky we don't
know who he is know where he comes from
but he's upsetting Papa Gerald could you
check out that Banky fellow just to the
right of there you know okay
does Banky want
no drug crony I was gonna sound like hot
bread you mean like hot croissants
[Music]
and the coolest gang in Phoenix and
banking no join since no like banking
banking made since gift so she
understands Banky is super Punk and Got
Talent no dare to give though please
help of course please give bankies give
to sin then come here and tell me what
you think if she love I have better
chance to be Punk
what what is it
[Music]
oh
should I help out and like fix fix it
but I think I like it the way it is
I'll give it to send
[Music]
it's perfect the way it is you know it
has it has Soul it has feels
it's beautiful hi synth
where's banky's gift
well now another cute drawing eh
she probably really doesn't like cute
but I can't just draw on top of the nah
I think they want me to help
hmm
and add something to it don't you think
it's totally hardcore
[Music]
I'll draw just her just I mean in the
end it doesn't matter but just don't
tell Banky we'll just tell him that he's
been accepted as a punk you know and
then he'll be happy
[Music]
and she'll surely like the red
I literally slime the way she looks but
my god oh
maybe the does anyone in the chat right
now have like their ears pierced like
like this
it was a huge hole I mean it's cool and
all into each room but the bigger they
get the more looking at it makes me feel
kind of
yeah
they are called gorgeous
like this is maybe you still not so
scary it's so scary it's so freaking me
out it's still freaking me out some
people really rock it though
big no no no Trypophobia
keep it going with the Trypophobia again
um
[Music]
hey I have all the perfect colors to
draw
[Music]
but legit I saw the detail on her she
has this uh gorgeous
try throwing a heartagram it should be
decently Punk
what does that mean
throwing a heart a gram
I'm sorry I legit don't know what you're
trying to tell me
[Music]
Penta Grump and the Heart
a heartagram
[Music]
card of RAM all right
oh wow what is that so edgy yeah the
simple features a combination of the
heart and a pentagram the heartagram is
meant to represent the juxtaposition of
the soft and the hard
the mainland the female the yin and the
yang
it's a band logo if it also seems to be
a thing on its own
it's like a pentagram but the top ones
are rounded yeah I saw now
and maybe I should just draw this and
then but no
I should
[Music]
is there like an actual algorithm that
that recognizes that and would like
would she be happier with it like are
you talking out of
experience
[Music]
no idea no
banks uses a lot of rats in his art you
should drop a
looks like a cute drawing so far I think
so too
[Music]
laughs
yeah but let's not put too much work
into it okay I keep on making this
mistake
[Music]
oh so veggie
wow
oh I like the huge zipper
that I like
[Music]
okay
I'm done
[Music]
maybe she actually maybe she'll hate it
because she notices I drew on top of it
um
[Music]
interesting
it ain't all shabby huh yeah
[Music]
I think
tell him that oh whatever
[Music]
yeah she wouldn't have this reaction
would she
is
[Music]
voice I mean of course it would flatter
her you know a cool self-portrait
[Music]
hey you're back what's him say she loved
it wow so fun thank you feel good
what
I thank God I didn't buy it if a bank
you have chance now gonna try hard and
steal
what
for real for real
breaking
oh
what you can just get can I get all the
other tools as well
whoa
[Music]
oh whoa
whoa okay I still want the watercolors
though
oh
I feel like you won't be able to get all
of them maybe the crayon from like a
child or so but no cool
[Music]
Becky is a parody of Banksy wait so
who's Banksy
okay
in this
um case now let's finish mummy
yeah back to this piece now that I have
something
uh you know
yeah yeah
oopsie
I still want more colors yo what is this
what is this
I wanted to sell account oh yeah but
they don't want to pay me good money for
it so
I'll I'll have to like improve it
somehow
[Music]
okay let's give her yeah
look at these these brown tones are also
not quite women
will I regret if I
nope I'm going for it
oh that's actually not so bad
that's actually not so bad
oh
that's really helpful because I can kind
of go over the lines
[Music]
nice yeah it gives it some texture too
I mean still room for improvement of
course
[Music]
the value of the picture might also be
like worse when I draw
on not a canvas but like a like a piece
of paper like this one
[Music]
that might
give us some problems as well
okay
[Music]
is that Meme with just a really cute
possible lady she is colored like a
colossal
is is not an owl but in reality a
quarter
then I love her even more but then she
can't be a horror 20 anymore
well maybe that's what she's hiding
maybe that's something she's hiding
because she doesn't want to kick that
get kicked out
[Music]
it's okay Mommy I understand I will not
tell anyone
[Music]
is croissant Peak civilization yes
of course
[Music]
now I almost want to do a normal art
stream
because this is really
motivating me
and then I'd have more tools but somehow
like the Simplicity of the tools I'm I'm
being given
makes me like experiment and it's kind
of also like
somehow it's limiting but at the same
time it's also freeing me oh that's so
poetic
oh my God that's so poetic
[Music]
thank you
Ms pain yeah maybe she's a strawberry
famous paint nah
did Ena do that maybe before I feel like
maybe she did it's a jerk did she do an
MS pain drawing stream before
I feel like I remember something like
that
[Music]
at least
very limited but in garlic phone I'm
always like so stressed out and then I
just look at my art skills are at its
lower lowest point ever she did she did
hmm fun for Art Supply I have my prayers
been learned oh yeah
you know how about listen listen listen
listen listen kfb oh you know how I got
my new camera right oh I got my new
camera
spent a couple hundred bucks on this
fresh Super Fresh camera and I said
before I wanted to do maybe a
traditional art Stream So how about we
do I buy like an actual aisle and then
um
[Music]
a canvas like this and we got some
acrylic colors I already have like a lot
of acrylic colors
little tubes and we do a yeah IRL
handcam art stream
[Music]
last time I did that was actually not
that long ago because I mean not as a
stream but you know with Cali when we
went to that
Cafe and I thought the Art Bar I thought
that would be like really really
difficult but turns out it wasn't even
it wasn't that difficult to draw it was
like
the first time I drew on a canvas I
think
foreign
[Music]
colors they cover really well so
actually
[Music]
there's no mistakes it's just happy
accidents
but yeah I totally want to do that I
want to use my camera for just like
something good for something where it
makes sense
[Music]
just have to figure out how to position
it because I guess
it will be very difficult to position it
like how you normally would position an
aisle I guess I should just put it I
should just put it like down on the
table the canvas so I can do a bird POV
anything else would be
um
like I would have to like constantly
like tilt my head maybe to not be in the
picture
yeah I guess I'll do bird POV
[Music]
and what I really want to do though I
mean for that idea for that stream idea
I guess I'll draw like whole life member
or something like that but what I really
want to do is like acrylic pour because
you know when me and Cali were looking
at the available classes for that
um
Art Bar
the ones that are most popular were the
ones that I wanted to do and they were
all like booked out for all the dates
that we could possibly go to
um and those were like acrylic poor ones
and if you don't know what I'm talking
about please google it because it's
[\h__\h] gorgeous and you don't even need
specific skills but you nah it does you
do need like a big surface and it's kind
of a big mess because you're wasting a
lot of color
but it turns out like a [\h__\h]
masterpiece like everyone can literally
make a freaking masterpiece
that would look so good it will look so
good on your walls ma'am
what is that
thank you you're my leaf
I'm not that good really I need I need
more time
practice and also I need like a
an undo and all that kind of buttons
well thank you very nice
no stop I don't thank God I'm only
drawing faces because Anatomy what is
that
hello what
um
what's her necklace what is that
dangling
oh
[Music]
thank you for the pinky oh
I have a random question for you can
someone be both cute and hot at the same
time or do they have to be one or
another this is based on appearances and
not Personality yeah I think so
I think I'm cute and hot at the same
time
is that a fun flag what's fun flag in
English
I feel like you know
the answer you're just trying to get me
to
just realized these are gold the leaves
are gold
yeah trick question
isn't that a trick trick question don't
you no
hell yeah you are
[Music]
my father very wee-wee why you leave why
you
lied me that you better stay now
[Music]
I haven't had that in a while
Brown is probably
not a popular color
in the algorithm of this game I can
imagine I mean it wasn't particularly
unpopular in the last one I think
can see
with being unpopular
we'll see she's a croissant she's bread
don't judge her based on her bread
appearances man
[Music]
it's not her fault for being so
delicious
ninja star thank you you got the conflu
oh no
[Music]
I'm glad you enjoyed that in my Boston
if we all had a great time
we very happy
is this ready to be sold guys what do
you think um
it's nothing special it's just a
portrait and also also her face is
obviously um kind of looking lopsided
[Music]
um
hard to fix now
it's a bit better but the the strands on
that side of her face makes it look a
little bit
worse than it actually is I think
that's a bit better
I'm gonna give her a bit more of a chin
[Music]
definitely
you know the face shape even like like
one or half a milliliter milliliter
millimeter you can make like so much of
a difference in how the face balance
will look like
hmm
nicely
[Music]
let's add some green behind her
goddammit
so by the way I didn't show you the
dialogue but I know you can like buy a
house from someone and it's like it's
like so expensive it's like it's so out
of your reach
um
so we're not gonna be able to do that
but
maybe someday because I want to play
this more I want to play this I know
it's boring but maybe next time I'll
have more talking topics and don't worry
I'll continue I'm not done for today
[Music]
I think this looks really cute
I wish I had the watercolor brush no
but if we sell this maybe if they give
me a good price
maybe just maybe
[Music]
we can get the watercolor brush this
stream is a nice background sound but
every once in a while you better look
what I'm doing okay and write a comment
and tell me tell me how I'm doing
okay
then wiggled then you can use me as a
background sound
then I'll forgive you
thank you
yes ma'am you heard the lady
thank you thank you thank you ah thank
you
[Music]
you know it's really nice having my
brother in reach now because at the end
of the
month I'll be
um not streaming for
all like three days or so going
somewhere and then my brother to take
care of my cats again and
I don't even
have to think about it he's obviously
available he told me you know he's also
even though he's like living close to me
now he said nonetheless he is like
totally fine with like
[Music]
um
sleeping over because I asked him can
you sleep over them of course from other
people when they take care of my cats
they they often don't sleep over but my
cats they're used to someone being
always here because I work from home so
when somebody's not when no one's here
for like a whole day almost and somebody
only comes by to give them food for 10
minutes and then leave then it's like
really you know
I think they feel really lonely because
they're so used to me being there all
the time he said yeah no problem I'll
totally sleep over
[Music]
um
let him stream no
and he really loves my cats he really
loves cats it's
so sweet our whole family wear like big
cat Maniacs my sisters well
she often sends her cat pictures
in our family group chat
um
my mom doesn't have a cat anymore but
she says well she has the neighbor's
cats who come over
and hang out on her
um
on her garden Stray Cats neighbor cats
yeah but yeah I grew up with kitty cats
and now I have kitty cat my mommy loves
my my sister loves cats my brother loves
cats but he won't get himself a cat yet
because he's not allowed to have a cat
anywhere
from like apartment side thank you Mrs
you guys are so sweet all right
well my next stop who pays good money
here who's a rich [\h__\h]
um I'll ask Alaskan
would you please
buy my roommate she looks so
look so excited like put on the
on the thing here
Georgie
maybe the AI is currently waiting for
him to arrive and make his first offer
and he's supposed to do the George is
supposed to do the second offer maybe
that's why he's just waiting there yeah
[Music]
600. I
I will totally accept this but uh once
again I want to see what George says
[Music]
wait for George
come on come on he's coming over
[Music]
but he's actually offering less okay
okay come back your heart is my new
number one what
I think maybe it is
it's not cameras it's just it's just the
paper oh my God don't
don't
okay I'll take it I think he went down a
little bit no statement only Beauty so
true thank you hey Brown it's not it's
like really making the words I think
it's the time we spend on it and maybe
also the fact that we used two tools on
it thank you
whoa
holy [\h__\h] what
into my look at when you think about my
look handle or do you want me to improve
this more what
Josh what
remember how little they offered me up
there this is the Money Corner these two
old guys just want to get rid of all
their money that they got from
retirement
what
[Music]
is
oh my god making it rain
yo they're in Big Money spending uh mood
damn holy [\h__\h] okay thank you guys so
much
1500 wait George
I feel like I can afford this for your
fingernail Studio
I'm interested I bought this from an
artist some time ago I made it my
writer's Den but that's in the past now
I've kept it true to itself so it's
still suitable as a studio I can afford
it but will he ask for a rent as well
afterwards
because that will be kind of stressful
but I could take already
[Music]
is there a friend
and about Studio
the old man used to tell tales about
this place great artists great paintings
I'm a member now thank you
it was a different time for this town I
guess I thought I'd be like them but uh
I'm sure it'll be perfect for you it's
yours for only that sounds like there's
no rent afterwards
yeah kind of sounds like it
[Music]
has anyone played this already and knows
if you have to pay rent afterwards I'm
guessing no one nobody came this far
with the game yet
um
sound like ownership not Rand yeah I
guess um
because otherwise it would probably be
cheaper
okay I'll take it
hopefully it's really no rent
maybe I have to pay like electricity
bill or something like that though
the key is mine
whoa
[Music]
for real for real I got a home already I
haven't even unlocked the other areas
yet
whoa oh there's a broken coffee machine
on a camera are you not gonna like show
[Music]
oh
this is a weird camera angle wait a
second I feel like I can
make it better why is it shaking oh no
my tablet's just shaking so if I come in
from here
yeah that's a better camera that's way
better
depends on where you enter from
I'm so happy that you finally found a
home again you're really making a buzz
out there I've been getting more
customers than ever what who what
here's a householding gift from me to
you
pick the table it was on the tables
oh
there's a recipe inside perhaps it could
be used in that color machine
color machine come see me when you have
time I've got a good idea of where to go
next your friend Benjamin
you
oh art book
[Music]
Ah that's why I can check all the
paintings I've done so far what what is
this ah this is let me see
ah you can even see the progress
yo they really made this into a great
great sequel
oh wait I think you can download the the
progress there's a video because there's
a download thingy
thingy I'll try it at the Stream
[Music]
let's watch the let's watch the moon one
yeah
another console
whoa
just like in those oikaki boards
wow Ah that's why I got my new tool
mine's breaking let's go
they paid so much money for this I'm so
happy it's so nice when you it sounds so
French so nice when you get so
appreciated for the work you do
holy [\h__\h]
mommy look let me look at this
hey let me take a screenshot and send it
to Mommy
[Music]
send this to me now
May
throw you on the stream
you brought in the big box fence a lot
[Music]
unfortunate I feel like I feel like
fauna would bring me just as much or
even more money
but you know I just got 100 bucks
because of me giving in as a quest item
let's look at what I did there because I
used a very interesting technique here
some artists use this technique I don't
know what to call it like you just start
by drawing big blobs of color and then
shaping it from there rather than
starting with a normal sketch
and I always kind of wanted to master
that because I love artists that do that
like they're just so good
[Music]
sakini
I know
you know
[Music]
I feel like a monster
blocking that's what blocking
yo it looks good oh it looks good
[Music]
chat is called blocking what that's what
you call it
really yeah take a screenshot
[Music]
for fun yeah
I drew you for
uh a quest in the game look
[Music]
I'll call it blocking
at least with R2 I will I will
Forever part of town that's what you are
yeah maybe that's better than getting a
lot of money for it
okay okay now I'm like really motivated
wow can I put my pieces up oh but I
guess yes I gave them away um
so what is this smokes and Sparks not
exactly the aesthetic of a well-oiled
machine perhaps George knows how to
repair it I guess you can with that you
can make new colors for your palette
palette
here you can see what you have available
[Music]
draw more cool
very comfy I wonder if people if I put
them up there it counts as selling not
as decoration then people will come into
um by
congratulations on your new home you
found my notes
my grandfather gave me a ticket to the
museum before he passed I've never dared
to make the climb I feared his reaction
I think you're ready it's time for you
to meet the curator
it's a harsh Trail you need to face but
first you need to create your
masterpiece
do you understand
yes what do you mean yes just like that
Yes actually no I don't yeah I didn't
yeah no I didn't
this is the curator I'm talking about
you need to pour in mastering even your
soul onto the canvas choose your tools
and canvas carefully you're no longer
doing just any painting no no no why
it's not moving too fast I don't think
I'm supposed to have my house stand
quickly already I'm supposed to be doing
side quests
um
it's all going too fast
too fast I'll take my time
you need to create your Mona Lisa I feel
like that was fun um
okay but I'll do my maybe crony Lisa or
so
[Music]
if it's your true if it's truly your
Masterpiece I'll give you a ticket when
you're done come see me
what counts as the masterpiece
what will make it a masterpiece
harmonizing colors and all that
some of real estate know-how should be
able to take care of filling it in okay
yeah I know about this I already fixed
it in the 30 minutes that I played
yesterday
I did it so fast like every painting I
only spent five minutes on it mostly
most
can you do side quests don't yeah okay I
can
um who was the one with the I think uh
uh George anyway
George pothole
[Music]
uh the pothole yes I've been meaning to
fix that but with those Rascals damaging
my property down by the docks all my
money is spent on graffiti detergent
however I have a plan of ruse if you
will you happen to be the final piece in
my Advanced scheme I need them
distracted so I can afford fixing the
pothole without having to spend it all
on cleanup your job will be to take
these special stickers then you convince
The Rascals to push their message
through stickers instead what's the
rules you ask the stickers are
degradable one rainy day and they'll be
flushed down the drain marvelous plan if
you ask me they feel like they can
express their message and I don't have
to pay for the cleanup so will it be my
secret agent the alternative of course
is to cough up the 300 Euro payment by
yourself yeah no it's okay
and I know exactly what to put on it
um draw some sort of Rascal message on
the sticker and show it to her sin needs
to feel inspired easy easy
[Music]
sign that you guys told me about what's
it called again a heart heart
agram
is that like like not good to draw on
stream is it okay or is it illegal is
that really the sticker thingy
sticker all right there we go
what
okay
[Music]
all right all right
so we need a circle oh [\h__\h]
great start
needs
as
Circle
good enough good enough
and then
[Music]
what [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
like that
a good first attempt and it's a bit
wobbly right you get the idea
and then
whoa that's like really rebellious and
cool I think
[Music]
whoa that looks actually
the the spray can gives a kind of a
Dodge and burn effect
as if I had like a Dodge and burn effect
on like in Photoshop
yo
next punk as heck right like what
[Music]
uh what do we call it the stickers
sunset
Rebel
how about that where did I put the pen I
just added okay
okay and now we give it to synth I guess
directly
real Avant God oh
[Music]
hey there
was just towards the place
I just sound like Donald Duck I think I
ain't one for having random strangers
giving me things that but this one time
I feel charitable so you better make it
worth me compromising my Integrity okay
I think you will like this
all right let's see what this is then
huh pretty good vibe actually and you
have more of them stickers this means I
can scream our message across town let's
get to work
you liked it
we did it and now the stickers also
should show up here and there
uh oh [\h__\h] ah that would yeah that's the
studio repairs right and something used
to be expected when the studio with such
Rich history I can help you with that
full price what do you want me to repair
if I don't have much money now
color mixer
I'm afraid it's beyond my expertise it's
a surprisingly nice lady over at the
punk area she could help Sparks her name
Sparks
okay never mind let me um
I guess he can do the Shelf but I don't
care about the Shelf now the Bruce
oh you managed to pull it off I'm
impressed hi welcome from work now hi
stretch box unfortunately there's a bit
of snag in our plan I may have done what
the kids refer to as an oopsie huh
degradable stickers are apparently
extremely expensive so I can't afford to
fully pay for the pothole repair
100 bucks just one second I have to make
some money real quick do I have
something to sell oh I think I do but
I'll draw on top of it
this one
[Music]
okay now that we know that the canvas
doesn't really matter
unless
we want to try to make it our no that's
the speed running I don't even want to
make a Mona Lisa yet because that's that
seems like I'm speed running the game
[Music]
oh this is a funny poster that I found
in the trash can
I love this like the game makes these
like funny little like you know roasts
about their own NPCs they're like
roasting each other because they all
hate each other
um
there's a war going on
okay
I want to draw konini oh oh yeah I've
only eat more colors and tools for my
masterpiece that's that's truly I uh
this just cannot be it
like I'm gonna draw envelina no baby
that will be my oh okay I will draw a
recreation of a famous ambulance
whatever I don't know which one but the
famous ambulance uh
peace that will be my masterpiece that
will be my Mona Lisa like for real of
course
but maybe maybe there's a Anberlin
um like recreated painting where it's
actually
um Natalie Dormer
because she's my real Mona Lisa like
even more so
okay what am I looking for crony
oh
[Music]
should I draw her in her kimono or in
her casual clothes
I really like her kimono
so nice with her hair up you know
yeah
good
um
what's a harmonizing color to Blue could
purple work not this ugly purple I guess
um
Maybe Pink again
I make better colors
came on all the way yeah right here her
kimono is just so cool
right
we all agree with that it seems
okay
[Music]
um
I don't want to do like the basic face
straight again I want to do like an
angle but I don't know it might look
really shitty I'll try but I think the
best way to do it is like start with
like you know
color blobs like this
[Music]
see it's already angled so
but I don't see you don't see her booba
but you know what the really like
elegant Charming thing is about kimonos
apparently
one magical thing about it oh for
actually fun answered is
um you know how the kimono uh is usually
very closed off right you don't see much
of the body but there's this one part
here in the back
the neck the nape where it's kind of
open you know it's like like you know
yeah and they say that this part I
forgot what it's called in English
in Japanese
I say that you know a woman in a kimono
with a beautiful nape is just like the
most elegant
the most elegant thing ever
on it
[Music]
to you do you know
that's the thing yeah yeah yeah
okay so yeah
no no but it's like it can make you look
really elegant and beautiful and
sophisticated
don't forget boros yeah I wanna I wanna
drop Boris too but I'm feeling really
nervous about this
okay
we'll just we'll just uh we'll uh
do our best
and I already already doesn't look right
I will just cover it up with hair
[Music]
okay sketch it's it's a sketch okay
it's a sketch
[Music]
kind of like these
I might also change bgm soon because
this is getting repetitive actually I'll
change it now I'll change it now what is
fun to reply and she wrote in caps lock
oh my gosh so cute thank you and then
normal kiwawa art is so blessed
you're welcome
[Music]
I'll upload it on Twitter later
okay let's see BTM
oh this might be good
[Music]
I'll take it
perfect
it's almost as if it's like built into
the game
so how do you draw
a
an ape a beautiful nape
and how do you draw I don't even
know how to draw kimono properly
at least I only have to draw part of it
just
look at the general vibe
Jazzy right you like jazz
[Music]
do you like jazz
do you do you say
do you like jazz eh
Yung does
[Music]
no do you like jazz is the new yellow
jazz
[Music]
do you
it's all about that do you do you do you
know you say
foreign
[Music]
somehow I'm like really bad with mouths
I hope that is positioned somewhere
somewhat okay for now I'll continue
drawing and later we can fix things
later later later
[Music]
one time to look pretty
we're looking at her bangs
I like
[Music]
something like this
oh
[Music]
yeah I'm going crazy
I was like I heard some when I was
eating my my crispy chicken
you know Mom was eating my crispy
chicken today
at a Burger King
I was listening to some Street Music
some Street musicians
and this this dude seriously
he was like doing all kinds of like
famous
um
dramatic classic pieces and one of it
was like I don't know what you call this
one but he goes like
[Music]
this was like the vibe that it was
spreading
yeah
Ah that's Beethoven's Fifth ah yeah
stuff like that is what he was playing
there
so funny
um
[Music]
she has this fur right
I can cheat a lot with the fur because I
don't know how to draw a kimono from the
back either or like there's there's no
official design from the back anyway I
want to draw it like this
foreign
[Music]
work
you know yesterday when I was like
trying to massage my neck because it's
hot
I noticed
and a new like weird
um
[Music]
what do you call it
a weird thing in my neck
circle shaped it was like yeah like a
knot a bump not not bump something like
that behind somewhere behind diagonally
behind my ear and I'm like what the [\h__\h]
is this this wasn't here before but I
looked it up and it seems like like when
you're really strained or so
[Music]
um from Pain it can like your muscles
can create like new knots and you have
to wait or massage it away and so on
it doesn't go away so easily though but
yeah I think that's what it is so I
booked a massage for tomorrow also
because just generally I'm I'm always up
for a massage and I'm liking always in
so much pain anyway
please check the dog and scan it
I really think it's just
um you know a not like
you know
a muscle knot yeah
yeah I might get those sometimes
[Music]
okay
I'm gonna get a closer look at her hair
oh because normally the like you know
she has these things right but with the
kimono outfit they're not in the middle
they're not centered
and I like that it's so cool
crony I love you
um
let me actually put the color on first I
wish I had a gray or blue but oh well
I watched a clip of her today
where she was she had that thank you for
the recipe thank you
not scented she had no she was like
playing Minecraft and she was like
absolutely losing it because of the
creepers
continuously stalking her
this is such a Mona Lisa man
and yeah she almost died if she didn't
have that totem in her hand
yeah she got so angry and I'm like oh oh
wait this is how I am always in my
stream but people are like shocked and
crony like oh wow crony well damn
and I'm like oh oh this is about like
you know
about as many f-bombs as I drop normally
within 10 minutes
um
but it's really nice to see cronie get
really tilted I once again I I feel like
I understand even more
the
the charm
of streamers
that you like who are normally calm
getting really tilted
which is unfortunately is because you
shouldn't be rooting and hoping for that
someone to get really tilted
because that's not a nice experience for
the streamer Eva
[Music]
corny has huge oys huge always and her
her eye shape
eye shape
so difficult though I don't think I can
recreate it but that's all guys
[Music]
I don't like tilted Bubba thank you I
guess but I often get tilted so what do
you do when that happens
big anime eyes yeah
she had her revenge on the trees
I already like put it in my schedule I'm
going to play Minecraft next week
besides the weather thingy too because I
want to get a little bit back into it I
don't know what to do though I don't
want to build anything I want to like
you know
maybe we'll just go hunting for
something
I just don't know what
um
but I need to get back into the game
because next week we're
um killing the the Wither
and Ina is joining our team because she
saw it on my schedule and she was like
um
like last time when we were originally
planning it you know uh I offered
everybody hey you guys want to join but
nobody had time for it
so nobody was joining
and Ina didn't have time for it either I
think she was on a break and she said
yeah I'm sorry maybe after my break
but now she can join so maybe it was
good that it took us so long to
you know get onto it get on with it
[Music]
I feel like on like illustrations and
also like real life women's pictures
this angle of like looking back over
your shoulder
it's just it always makes for a great
Charming
capturing picture heart capturing
picture
[Music]
right
it's just like slightly angled
and then the slightly side uh face
thingy hello English
[Music]
okay and a lot of this gets like covered
up by flowers
[Music]
hmm there's one and then there's another
one
oh
like this and then there's like a lot of
small ones
[Music]
okay let me draw let me fill in the hair
color here first
[Music]
I feel like this is coming really pretty
is this Corona but pretty sure
what are you talking about a woman with
a Pearl Earring painting oh
this is better
[Music]
look whoa look at that hair line whoa
um
I am a jostling myself
and I think the pink actually does
really work well this is a nice pink
color it's kind of flesh but
a nice pink color yeah
art in Japanese it's just a like
literally just the letter A
e but pronounced as e in Japanese
has a difficult kanji though I mean you
can also say irasto from illustration
[Music]
and say that too
yes salmon salmon that's what this is
yeah salmon that works so well with the
dark blue as a contrast
there's some orange ones here to add
another big white flower all right all
right all right all right word all right
all right
[Music]
foreign
like starting off with with drawing is
so off
[Music]
oh I just I just randomly scribbled and
it actually looks good
it actually looks like when
[Music]
yes oh my God natural Talent baby let's
go it looks good though I know
looking good so far
and then there's some
some orange but it needs an outline
otherwise it just Blends in
um
okay oh she has like two fluffy balls
down there but uh you wouldn't really
see it from this angle so I guess I
won't add them
wait
foreign
[Music]
if I knew how to do them myself I would
do them all the time I can't even do
like the simplest simplest messiest buns
even though they're supposed to be messy
but for me they always fall apart so I
really Envy girls
who just effortlessly
give themselves a messy bun and it just
looks good
maybe some girls will understand my
struggle
[Music]
chronic looking mighty cute I know
I so relate to that thank you I feel
like all the popular it's girls from
school and so on
they know how to do that
they know how to do everybody all the
all the cool girls know how to do a
messy bun and it's not like they even
like put that much effort into it they
just know the technique for some reason
I don't know how they do it
[Music]
me
teach me your your secrets please girls
aren't we supposed to share these kind
of things
[Music]
I was so happy when Muna made me an updo
when I was in Indonesia
when she styled my hair I was so happy
about that because I wouldn't have been
able to do it on my own
I was like damn I look so good in an
updo what the hell I wish I could do
this all the time
I can't
[Music]
laughs
when I really enjoyed playing with your
hair too
[Music]
all right drawing this hairstyle and
crony is so much fun holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm really enjoying it
write it down for girls talk
um I wonder if the other girls know how
to do it
hmm
[Music]
run
how's this look
okay okay okay okay
I'm Gonna Fill In some color here
[Music]
wow
wow oh I'm such a genius I'm actually
golden eyes if I give it some time and
some thought and some a chance compared
to some shitty [\h__\h] that I've drawn in
the garlic phone so far
[Music]
nice
beautiful positive gas lining words
but my arm
my arm is so weak
oh
[Music]
the arm will be the end of me also how
is time passing so fast it's been three
hours now
this is my arm workout
uh
my garlic phone always just gets me so
nervous you know
[Music]
I don't see what I'm drawing
across that I'm seeing that is bigger
than uh
everything else
[Music]
what was I talking about anyway ah
oh thank you
many more days of just Caleb phrase
maybe yeah
[Music]
you guys are always praising me
you are you are you're also roasting me
a lot but you're also praising me a lot
and it's not necessarily a lack of
of praising
going on not necessarily I mean
[Music]
it hurts to hear a bit more you know
I also see a lot of praising not going
directly at me just just behind the
scenes like you know without even
tagging it you know here and there on
Twitter and like in other people's uh in
in Clips comment sections and so on I
mean which I I end up seeing anyway
because I'm a bit lurker I'm a big
lurker
oh I see you I see you
[Music]
there we go beautiful
um
[Music]
foreign
and a certain Jennifer praise you so
much is becoming a meme Oh you mean you
mean Cali
[Music]
um
I I sent her
um I sent her a part of one of my demos
on Discord or extended an hour like myth
group generally and Cali replied and she
said like what did she say
[Music]
she said I can totally imagine you're
singing This is perfect for you
it's perfect for me
you're so sweet
I'm reacting to my
me showing off my new song
[Music]
foreign
she heard the other one too
already like I let her listen to it like
in person in Japan
so she heard both already
there's gonna be more
[Music]
do it do it
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
I honestly don't know
does she have any earrings now
nothing
all right then
oh
[Music]
okay I guess I wasn't I thought I was on
the other brush I guess that works too
oh
it's like wearing bluish
you can always just leak your new song
right here right now
um
it would be my choice but it would be
very not smart I would get a huge bunk
that I could probably not recover from
oh but by the way I didn't tell you yet
Kelly of course and I knew she would
that's why I wrote to her like that she
of course agreed to give
uh the signed look at your cards to
Jenna
of course you did I expect nothing less
oh look at that texture
[Music]
hmm
she's gladly doing it
yeah sweetheart
I said next time she sees janma she's
gonna bring it to her
[Music]
foreign
making some fur now Flappy fluffy fur
difficult with the tools that I have but
alone
[Music]
thank you I don't like the stylistic
choices of the lines the roughness at
the time oh my God the layer describing
it sounds so like professional
[Music]
that is so bright holy [\h__\h]
it's so dark I mean
[Music]
whatever I don't know what I'm doing
here I don't know
[Music]
foreign
roughness to replicate the pencil effect
yeah maybe that's what I'm doing hope
Cali gets assigned well of course she
wants she wanted a signed wobble card
[Music]
I mean
I could always sign something for her
but it's like not quite the same as
getting lucky and getting the card that
you want
[Music]
um
I think it's looking pretty fluffy
[Music]
foreign
way to bake holy [\h__\h] okay let's fill in
her eyes
oh
okay we have so many blue tones my God
[Music]
this is so good I'm like so happy with
this
seems like I'm drawing all of councils
so we have to draw veils at some point
as well
snake earrings
she doesn't really have earrings in this
outfit though and I think it will cover
up her beautiful nape you know
we won't do that but
I'll still draw boros somewhere don't
don't worry
[Music]
I'm so mad I'm missing one of your art
streams no you're not missing and you're
here now you can watch the rest as an
archive because I've I've created some
gorgeous masterpieces so far I would say
[Music]
foreign
okay
um
[Music]
whoa
can you hear how I'm really enjoying my
own Artful ones
[Music]
the minimum pixels is so big it's so
hard to draw that
that
I need like half a pixel less oh well
if only you always praise your own art
like this well and most of the time it
doesn't deserve this kind of praise
I literally have to do like dots in
order to draw it as as thin as I want
yeah now [\h__\h]
I'm blaming the game for this one
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] whatever just don't look so close
no I don't like it
a place uh another lash look here
[Music]
she has these
um
three lashes that are really you know
dominating
it only has his free lashes not like a
long line like the top lashes
just like singular free lashes and I
like that that's actually kind of
similar to how I would normally draw I
think
[Music]
um
they're not eye rings they're just
showing the shape you know
anyway
thank you oh you got your whole 27
special edition suit box wow
ordered from City Japan right
[Music]
thank you very much for the support
oh
foreign
[Music]
thank you guys for so commenting so much
even though I'm barely looking at the
comments I feel kind of bad but thank
you
[Music]
appreciate it at least every time I look
there is a comment
that I can pick up
[Music]
okay
um I'm not gonna like even attempt to
draw the patterns on I think it's fine
the way it is but
um
there is supposed to be like
another layer here
um
inner layer
and for real surprised at how well this
is turning out
good I'm surprised too gotta put it up
on the art hashtag
[Music]
there's actually three layers
one in here
it's like a red line
yeah like this but nobody will notice
this part anyway okay let's go
finish the flowers
thanks so much time am I drawing this
for a quest or for myself
for myself right to a forge uh
I'm trying to buy something oh yeah
right so they're supposed to filled up
but the pothole
[Music]
mm-hmm I already forgot what I'm doing
this for just for self-satisfaction
[Music]
whoa
technique
how to create a gradient when you only
have a shitty spray gun
[Music]
laughs
[\h__\h] I'm so good so good
yuck
[Music]
don't like that
oh well I know it's pretty good it's
pretty good that's gave it definitely
some some good shape and and and and
depth
if it's in good depth
okay now inside those there's
[Music]
um
like little yellow white-ish looking
[Music]
flower petal again
yeah almost cool
it's true
okay
only some layers left there will never
be layers I love the way you're solving
those flowers thank you so much oh my
God
[Applause]
[Music]
gradient double gradient damn you must
be your Genius
how can you do so good without layers
right
right you need confidence you need to
believe
which actually never mind I didn't do in
the beginning anyway so I don't know how
I did it
[Music]
okay next
she has like these like millions of
little flowers here
I'm gonna first go for gray
it will help us with the shading
[Music]
there's these hanging ones which are so
pretty
[Music]
about this long and then there's another
one
[Music]
okay that's fine
foreign
[Music]
wow
what a beauty
[Music]
so focused kiwawa
yeah okay here I really wish I had some
more gray tones
um
I guess I'll add some blue
[Music]
maybe this will be the last thing I draw
for today because my fingers are hurting
and my arm and my shoulder
[Music]
even
even when I make it so small and so big
but I can fix it I can fix it
[Music]
it's not so messy oh yeah I don't know
oh [\h__\h] bro
dangerous dangerous game that I'm
playing
but it made it a little bit lighter and
I like that open the stream that looks
amazing thank you you gotta look at the
other ones I've drawn I'll show you
again and then after I'm done with this
one I'll show it again
thank you
I want to give them more detail
[Music]
okay what are what kind of flowers are
these oh they're premium
[Music]
foreign
s are so fun to draw
[Music]
man
I just added like random Blobs of color
and now I'm just trying to find
some fitting ones
[Music]
to shape them into what they really want
to be
and I'm giving them the chance
to be exactly that
well I am an enabler of flowers yeah
now that's me that's right that's right
guys that's me
[Music]
flower flower
this is feeling very Bob Ross and I
approved
and the flowers
as an artist I'm dying of how Banger
your art is the way you choose to make
those flowers show us how scary I'm
gonna cry
thank you
ah
[Music]
all right
is this the art stream you guys wanted
all the time huh is this it
does this come close to it or does it
even exceed your expectations
yes yes
okay okay
[Music]
I'm happy I'm happy when you guys are
happy
they should pay me at least a thousand
for that don't you think
[Music]
this is the most effort I've put in
today
[Music]
foreign
but it looks like it's I'm giving it
like scales
I'm gonna make
[Music]
I didn't get jump scared I was just
worried that I was like I'm doing
everything for a moment
boros yes I'm drawing borrowers but like
not the cute version more like a
um sophisticated version the one that's
like on her kimono
[Music]
thank you for the Super Chat
let me put a member's message
[Music]
does this look like a snake I'm just
drawing what I'm seeing on her kimono do
they don't they have like a let me let
me Google
I'm a Google uh snake White Snake why
not
um
they're kind of cute
so they have like little nostrils
[Music]
thank you
ah [\h__\h]
a little bit like Nessie
there's a band called White Snake
[Music]
I don't think I want to really draw all
these scales
I really shouldn't but at least like you
know with a shadow is
I think it's like nice to
draw them just there
the rest is just too bright to actually
see them you know
hmm
[Music]
so now I made them a little bit less
visible
so they won't stand out so much snake
looking Fierce as hell
it's kind of big
[Music]
back
huge really made him pop with texture in
life right
[Music]
you guys are killing me
all right no I mean
[Music]
[Applause]
no it looks good like also like balance
wise the face doesn't look too weird to
me
foreign
nothing really off looking to me
[Music]
I already showed you ask wow thank you
wow it's really nice
[Music]
thank you
are your mom's beloved students very
much make it wow perfect jawline right
yeah I think I got it down quite well
[Music]
Charming today stop now
okay
I'm done with this
[Music]
Corona
I'm not gonna submit this as my Mona
Lisa but I mean I could worth it
I think I'm done
[Music]
wanna see how much they're gonna pay me
for this let's go over to George and
Gerard
they're gonna get it
Gerard are you here
come on over
[Music]
come on follow me
if I put it here to eat maybe here
[Music]
all right bring it guys bring it
like zombies they're making their way to
the beautiful arts I'm offering them
yeah I'll send crony a message too come
on come on what is it gonna be please
don't disappoint me our highest before
was like something like 500 600. foreign
how much like detail and love I put into
this
oh they're disgusting come on George
it's your chance it's your chance
800.
did I ever go higher when you
when you um decline I'll give it one
chance
850 I I don't mind that but I want to
see do they ever go higher
okay I'm definitely not doing that
I kind of want to see four digits but
maybe it's really the materials like
without really insane materials
it doesn't really get any higher okay
George second try
I should probably take this
perfect dinner giveaway
foreign
[Music]
I can do a lot with that money
I should take it right
that's the best you'll get okay
while you value yourself okay well don't
settle nah this is fine thank you guys
guys well let's look at the the progress
oh here's my house I almost didn't
recognize it can I like make this more
into like my house
this is like my new favorite thing to do
I love this game
we're gonna be playing this a lot until
um
until
what's that I hear until on the new
breath of the wild comes out
uh okay let's look at this Mona Corona
ah where'd we see how through the
original thing as well oh
[Music]
whoa
yo I can really use this technique I
mixed the spot what was it spotting
technique
I mixed it with my usual technique
oh
noise
[Music]
oh she became animal
all the flowers the flower is blocking
not bottom okay
whoa
[Music]
it's all coming together oh
I met holy [\h__\h] I am a genius
okay snip snap
[Music]
sending that to crony right now
cronie
crony look I drew you
and sold you for over 800 bucks thanks
for being beautiful
it was fun
[Music]
art genius oh no stop
yeah time lapses are really cool I
wonder when you download that does it
come out as a time lapse or is it jpeg
let me actually I'm scared with a little
show so let me just test it once
ah I know it saves the screenshot okay
[Music]
where does it say that okay let me do
that with the others and the people who
came in later wanted to see what I did
or else I did hello Mouse
so let me show you again we'll make
really quick
and yeah no time lapse but I guess you
could screen record
[Music]
right I forgot about the good one I
didn't I didn't get that serious about
that one yet
it's not the Stream
oh
oh I did
[Music]
huh
I didn't even realize I was doing that
snapshot that was mommy
um where's I here
my warning sign
gura
eating a human
[Music]
be careful she is the danger fish
that you should watch out for
[Music]
yeah that one I didn't spend too much
time with
and then there was the fauna all natural
[Music]
are you drawing so fast skill issue
no looking good
[Music]
stuff I want to do more because wow it's
been three and a half hours it's getting
midnight it's turning to midnight
I didn't think I would spend so much
time with each painting but I think we
did plenty here
kind of want to play off stream as well
I want to pay more
I want to paint more
nice and the kalkini addition that some
people are happy about and some are just
absolutely losing in a bath why did you
ruin it
wow
nice let me look at the croissant too
oh
the shading technique
[Music]
wants to make something this is where I
started taking the game very seriously
where it was like all right all right
all right let me let me go like all in
now
I want to make art
a candle is so pretty and oh that plant
oh
[Music]
wow wow
this is where it started yeah time to
flex
look under
um
that's how Banky drew it before cute
[Music]
and it looks like he owns a crayon oh
and I just I just completely deleted it
and he doesn't even know
hey that looks good too though
and then I said no yeah
not a muse face
yeah that's it that's it for now I mean
out of all the interesting things
yeah we made good money what was I
buying anyway ah wait I was gonna fill
the pothole where did you see him do we
even still have money dude
pothole
[Music]
um
okay it's fixed now it's on the other
side oh look
at my sticker yes
Banky is gonna be a rival I think
yeah Banky Banky can't do [\h__\h]
what's she doing here
the postman is in trouble what
Paul the post when racking them nerves
what yeah he's indeed some deep trouble
that lad
Paul what did the postman do hey wait a
minute Mr Postman
see there's like even more areas that we
can unlock but right now we unlocked
this area
[Music]
there's a postman you're in trouble
apparently oh man oh man
oh his problems big problems
I lost the package with the painting
what I could get fired I spent all night
trying to remake it for memory if my
skill only matched my confidence
for those trade is that you got talent
maybe you could make the replacement
take my sketch and make something like
it but actually good oh
foreign
is that poop
no I said no I don't want to sell it
sorry
really
he's telling me to make something good
like this like in it make poop better
you little shits literally
[Music]
smell
Never Enough what to do what to do
troubled
everyone wants help from me and I really
want an outbound but there is no time
I'll help OMG that would be brilliant
but no no one needs to decide who's
going to get my help and who won't spark
horse and whatever choice I make it
feels like I'm abandoning my friend my
friend oh I hated the side stuff waiting
let's leave it to chance and play Rock
Paper Scissors the winner helps soon
then the loser helps spark okay go
uh Peppa
on paper too and what the [\h__\h] what's
wrong let's do it again Rock
is this RNG
one rock too oh my drama is going it
seems like RNC
[Music]
okay he wins one thing wants don't talk
to sins come back when you are done now
I will have a reward for you
let's spark who will spark again oh you
can even go down here
what is all this
oh see there's so much detail it's a
pretty beautiful world that the little
village that they put down here
[Music]
wait
I found the last painting though do I
really need to redraw it now
that's it
I mean
he asked me to redraw it in case I don't
find it I guess but I found it
huh
that's it
flash what's up
hell your fave clown here
what do you call a can opener that
doesn't work
I can't opener
bye I guess he always tells you jokes
can't
can't open
oh
what does it say tunnel
tunnel snacks
rules
is that like their group name or so the
tunnel snacks
tunnel snacks salads evil love yeah
should I sell the good one
oh they're in Orlando I forgot again
it's just too funny
huh and oh Geezer forgot Emily's
birthday again
[Music]
guys and Emily you're not Amelia
that's what I always say you know can't
trust them can you okay that's it
there's no question of this okay
what about you spark hi
I need to help you have you seen smell
oh wait you you were the one who can
help me with the color mixer how much
does it cost
oh
I'm paying
yay let's see what it works how it works
I love writing these recipes for color
mixers you seem totally cool and all so
if you ever want to get them new recipes
hit me up
need help thanks bud I create super
advanced technology smell usually helps
me out
not today no so you're helping her out
then okay why not you can help with the
easier stuff but you need to promise to
keep my invention secret from the
competitors don't open your mouth yeah I
guess it'll be hard for you to
understand but what I'm creating is the
paint for a three thousand will I get
that if I help them and to finish it
I'll need a fan a battery and a funnel I
guess you'll find these things just
lying around the streets of Phoenix
people throw out perfectly good stuff
these days I've already searched the
pumpkin so don't bother when you got
them all come back to me
okay okay
yeah I wonder if that will be that easy
you said
you search the punk area I don't have to
look here
actually I was gonna end the game now
though
um but then like sell
into it man
um I wanna see I want to see the
what what wait
let me search
okay nothing
what what is it George
the artist returns is that me
I'll I'll wrap up in a second commission
it's Emily's birthday I've been busy
with a new deal so I haven't had time to
get her a gift are you available to draw
a birthday card for me okay of course
yeah excellent I'm fairly sure she loves
pink and all the cute things oh yes you
need a card to draw on here take my card
that should work oh
repairs of course what do you wish
repaired
how much is a broken Shelf
[Music]
affordable wow that's [\h__\h] 250 for
just like fixing a tilted Shelf
I mean look at it
[\h__\h] whoa that's ridiculous even I
could probably like if I had to pay 250
I would first try to fix it myself
okay my color mixer is apparently fixed
ready for action yeah how does it work
sunny day recipe
what mixing colors
does it take some time
[Music]
it's processing oh how long
I'll give it some time
[Music]
what do I do about the poop
wait I should go back to the postman ask
him
now that I have the picture if he maybe
just wants dad
[Music]
I don't know which is better
ten dollars for parts the rest is labor
charge with a piss take what
I mean even with the labor charge that
doesn't even take an hour that takes
maybe 10 minutes
sell it to him I want to see if he
notices that I have it
[Music]
huh
what happens if I give him the one that
he lost maybe I get an extra reward for
finding it
he'll be shocked I think
[Music]
yeah you did and you missed a lot of
other good ones too
let's see
[Music]
whoa this almost looks like the real
deal does he always say that even if you
give him a painting
yours
you're a lifesaver I think I've got some
appropriate payments somewhere
um
a fuzzy brush oh
[Music]
see I should do all the quests first
before buying tools to see what I can
get
you won't let Mr Boss but no right good
okay
so I can use the other one as a canvas
to draw
for free what is it
how do I convert them advertising could
some advertising help yes it actually
could if you create a final station of
my proud angle French dishes okay I will
give the people of Phoenix a hint of
vertigo when in need of great Fusion
food can you create art like that sure
[Music]
Benjamin has been so busy all of us drop
otherwise he'd usually help remember it
needs to illustrate my menu and homage
to the Anglo French Fusion Cuisine okay
another time add paper okay
okay
what what would that look like what's
Anglo French Fusion cuisine
English and French Fusion right
I'll do that another time it's done
beep
[Music]
the color mixer has created
say let me see let me see let me see let
me see
okay there's there's a bunch more greens
a bunch more
[Music]
no new Grays though oh there's like some
turquoise turquoise ones that's nice
[Music]
this these Blues are a bit more gray
that would have been nice for croony
[Music]
on some like mustard colors but still no
skin color
these are just ugly ugly yellows
[Music]
um
they're not that different but um
and they still keep like these ones
they're just very slightly different
and they should use that Row for
something else what the hell
okay
I will not redraw it no
ah make everyone look like The Simpsons
oh yeah
you can draw a Simpson that was my free
recipe yeah hey I wonder how many there
are also new brushes
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is that no I don't like it I
mean it's interesting but
it has like this outline
[Music]
oh but look so
oh wait
look at this when I'm painting the full
canvas with it
and now
oh it has a different finish
[Music]
this has like a metallic finish like a
shiny shiny finish
wow
okay like I don't like the shape and the
outline of the brush but it has a an
interesting finish
up when it's smaller
no when it's that brush on top of
a whole canvas painted like that then it
doesn't have the outline anymore
oh that's a very orange red wow oh it
becomes so shiny
hey I'm creating art
[Music]
doesn't this look like Arts to you
this could be legit art
[Music]
foreign
well he appreciate it
[Music]
sorry I can't stop myself
looks like an unsolved Rubik's Cube that
has been in a microwave I love it wow
your comment it's so shiny up here what
what so shiny
[Music]
um
what
[Music]
is this freaking doing to this
what
[Music]
these two tools do not work so well
together and then there's no undo button
so this is how it is now all right let's
sell this
oh wait I should name it though wait
does that wear like Honda selling
[Music]
it's like melted now
what what happened
brother what happened 80s bubble wrap
very unique yeah it looks like vomit now
it could be yeah
yeah the paint is like reacting I think
this doesn't count as selling it
does it is anybody coming in
[Music]
okay because it's just that shell
anybody on their way no George is not
interested I guess it's not what if I
sell it inside on my
take it take it oh wait oh
hi hi this is George not being
interested are you gonna
[Music]
ride all right it's easy to make money
as an artist apparently
[Music]
all right while we're at it
um oh hey George is coming in now
recipes do we have more
oh
[Applause]
pastel palette
romantic colors so probably lots of Reds
complexion seems to be useful for trying
ah skin color
winter day
so cold colors okay I think I want the
gray and the complexion one for now
[Music]
all right oh my God I could I could buy
even one more
I'll buy the the cold one
thank you oh my God you're amazing
bye let me look at them yeah oh I can't
stop wait I need to I need to buy some
something to draw on
surface
I think I'm gonna just without doing the
quests
or maybe I should do the quest I don't
know but I want to make like a lot of
money off screen and then and then and
then I'll stream again because I just
want to buy all the tools and all that
and I'll see what's possible
um
[Music]
we can get a large one
and the basic one
yes
thank you sounds like a plan yeah
but like off screen um I won't do the
special ones off screen I'll just [\h__\h]
around off screen and just draw whatever
like nothing special
just so I can get some money
[Music]
um
and then get more you know recipes and
all that
tools
really quickly
now let me see
wow
[Music]
the recipes are not enough do you have
to
um
make it in here first
make colors
complexion whoa
[Music]
you show the ones you feel turned out
right on Twitter sure why not
George is an interesting and Abstract
style of art while punks absolutely love
it oh
for real so they do recognize that
so cool Where's my water that is so cool
I love that
it really seems so because like he came
running for it like he knew he knew
there was some cool abstract art there
all the colors are finished sorry I'm
gonna drink some water
he smelled it yeah he knew what I was
doing I was just messing around
he thinks that's like edgy and and
different but
while you're doing that let's make
another one
the neutrality
okay
sorry I can literally not stop myself
whoa that's a big one
whoa yes okay for some reason there's
some green I guess ah because my
character is green and I need to be able
to draw myself but yeah look at that
so many like beautiful skin colors
yeah
the Browns would have been good for
mume's hair as well I guess although no
no mommy has more of a grayish Brown and
these are not very gray
um
that'll be very helpful
[Music]
a new palette
the monochrome oh my God look at it here
oh oh oh there you go
they look a little bit different though
um on on the aisle to be honest eel
aisle
huh
oh wait I cannot have all of them at
once
in my inventory that's why that opened
up
[Music]
ah
that's why some of them still come with
the most basic black gray and white
but look at those monochrons
well I can like if I paint in the
Atelier I can yeah keep on Switching
like mid painting I can leave the
painting for a moment I can go here
switch if I really need to if I really
need all of them
oh
Naruto
[Music]
new color palette was that all of them
I think so yeah oh wait
um
what inventory there we go Frosty feels
and there we go
let me check
[Music]
wow what these all looks so black
what what
[Music]
I don't see a difference ah that's my
screen uh um I see it a bit better on my
other screen
what
Flags what
[Music]
what
I feel like in the middle here there
could have been a couple more oh that's
pretty brown oh that's the Brown the
brown that's that's that's that's that's
the Brown that I need for like uma's
jacket I think oh that also it's like
beige
wait why have you giving me so many
beiges when you could have given me more
grays what the [\h__\h]
like it why are these all so dark what
why is there no more grains what is this
what the hell
look at what I'm saying and that makes
no sense oh wait I I thought this would
be more blues and all that but
interestingly enough
there's a lot of warm colors in here too
like the Browns and the greens
another Gray
the Grays are nice
some new Light blues
[Music]
oh I like the middle one
yeah okay
yeah that's a good like really light ass
color for animal girls
exactly what I need
yeah
foreign
[Music]
wow I'm so happy and this is such a like
feel good stream for me
um
[Music]
save the exit
tomorrow's my day off I think I know
what I'll be doing
besides getting Sims to work
ah
hope you guys are okay with me playing
this a couple more times because it's so
fun for me it makes me feel really good
yeah
I'm kind of tired
I'm kind of tired though
no
hmm
I think I'll go without reading super
chats today the day after or so
yeah that was fun yeah it's already oh
now it's already past minute the time
passes so fast what the hell
hmm
thank you guys it's almost really a
pleasure very chill
and yeah Sims will be soon yeah I think
if I get it to work I'll play Sims next
week thank you for the stream now thank
you
[Music]
announcement or is it already on Friday
oh yeah because oh now it's that first
day yeah yeah okay okay
yeah okay
um
Friday will be interesting
[Laughter]
yeah
please everybody come on Friday I have a
special announcement and yeah on Friday
please come yeah
I wish you luck getting Sims to work
yeah I hope I hope because we had some
travels
already like I installed from my older
CDs that I bought secondhand and then I
couldn't launch it I mean I could launch
like this the first screen but I
couldn't get into the game
um
so I have to like find ways around it
it's a bit annoying thanks for the rare
drawings do you welcome thank you for
enjoying and giving me some confidence I
appreciate it all
oh Mom I answered
oh my God and caps lock oh my God so
cute what the [\h__\h] you rich how you get
those colors watercolor brush ah
[Music]
um
uh I got a spray
can uh from a little
[Music]
side quest that you get right in
the beginning if you talk to the NPCs
they tell you what they need you to draw
for their shop Etc because I saw in her
stream she completely ignored that
um
[Music]
there's a shop where you can buy the
tools too but many you well many you
will also get from
um
quests
and you can also get one recipe for
another color palette from a side quest
but also you can buy them too
but you need
to buy the house first in order to mix
the pallets
yeah I'm I'm giving her a guide on how
to play the game like I really loved
what she was drawing she almost does
really funny cursed things
but she kind of ignored the function of
side quests in the games I think
yeah
yeah she doesn't understand the power of
side quests like I do
you should stream it again and talk to
all the NPCs
oh and you you should look into the
trash cans always sometimes they have
thrown away posters Etc which you can
also use as a canvas it really doesn't
seem to affect the price
yeah Pro tip dig through the trash mummy
fast for two ambassador
riding a game [\h__\h]
yeah and they I need her to know I need
her to know
dumpster diving let's go
[Music]
let's go
the kiwama gun
um
take things out of the trash now
honestly mom I played again I was
watching her stream for like an hour but
like in the VOD wasn't watching it live
just the bald
now I want to do more I want to do more
I want to do more I want to do more
thank you guys a lot
I'll drop something tomorrow in my off
time yeah I wish I could do it on the
steam deck too I think you can totally
play the game on the steam deck
probably
but
it probably won't work as well as with
the Wacom over here
so I'll play it on my PC oh
yeah it does have a touch screen but it
doesn't really it doesn't really have a
pen is there a pen accessory that you
can buy for a steam deck I wonder
um
have a nice rest thank you thank you
yeah massive screen much better on the
steam Deck with tiny screen I don't
think I would be able to draw all those
details at all
um
you're the best girl I couldn't ask for
more no you're the best you guys are the
best I love you guys thank you so much
for chilling with me today what are you
making for dinner I have left always
from yesterday which I guess I'll eat
they were it was kind of decent it was
mid
first the first few bites I was like wow
this is really good and then the more I
would eat the more I was like mmm it's
kind of mint
I don't know I'm not I don't want to
cook again though
so I guess I'll eat my mid leftovers
no it didn't lose its flavor it actually
like adopted too much flavor of the
tomatoes
no the totalini that on their own were
really good
in the tech and the touchscreen really
doesn't work well those little nut pens
are janky on it too I think so too y'all
I have because I didn't eat it yesterday
because I was a good girl and I cooked
first I cleaned the kitchen and then I
cooked
yeah I'll think about it because it's a
waste if I don't eat it
hmm
we've been starving for more of your art
I'll definitely check the rest of the
Vault later
[Music]
but Google wanted my money not from
PayPal oh man
that's unfortunate but it's okay don't
worry about it I appreciate the thought
I'm gonna sleep during the stream but it
was too nice to stop watching
[Music]
too nice
okay maybe check out Twitter and retweet
later okay thank you guys and Germany we
stay healthy dancing good night guys
[Music]
bye bye
content Chihuahua content content
content because of the content
[Music]
okay got one of the memberships y'all
can do
yo
it's about time
lucky
I mean
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god let's go
I have you made some people very happy
like
weren't you like also watching the the
Easter stream like how did you not get
one of the 500 I guess because there
were a lot of other viewers too who
don't
come here usually but how could you not
get it like back then on that day where
you're not where you're not in the chat
I can't there wasn't a member he was
good at dodging as if he didn't want to
be a member
I know I was so sad
[Music]
yeah yeah
RNG was not on the side that's so weird
because I thought you know that there
would be some kind of algorithm behind
it where it would give it would give the
gifts to somebody who who's here like
more often over somebody who's here for
the first time but apparently not
because otherwise I'm sure Kenta would
have gotten a
gift like this is the perfect example
how can he not get one out of 500 gift
memberships in one stream where he was
there
and now he gets one so randomly
the mystery
I'm here all day and it took so many
tries right for you too
yeah so that is just it seems to be
completely random
oh
weird
membership
oh well oh wow oh well it's like the
fifth time I got a membership what
you've been gifted five memberships by
now you lucky bastard
hmm
status
[Music]
my mama
I've gotten 10. almost 10 wow but only
here or elsewhere too
I'm on nine free moms on Amish Channel
wow
wow lucky
[Music]
bam isn't that easy I never got a
membership gift of bunny and I might
with my takana account it doesn't work
but and with my other like private
account I don't really like chat in
people's chats like never never
and I guess I don't watch streams much
but I just watch more videos you know
yeah
that's the one thing that you really
like missing out on if you're a bot
Watcher you're missing out on free
memberships ooh ooh damn
damn
hope you had a lot of fun yeah
so you can watch the bond a hit
I wish I'd give a lot of memories
because she keeps super chats off a lot
yeah right she does that that rebellious
little chick
I've never been gifted one though it
might be because I just watch you and
cat cat
[Music]
who's cat
I mean Cali
okay
and who wrote that
Jacob's monkey
where's the answer
that was me yeah that was you so what is
the answer
oh
[Music]
okay I should go now
um
[Music]
I already said that but I'm just gonna
say it again
did you know that p-files are apparently
really low on the tier list of birds
surprising but I guess it makes sense
but they're so beautiful
and they're not they don't have any
beauty stats
in those videos
it's fair I don't think it's fair
you think about it how nature created
something so beautiful
just for fun
damn
look at those feathers
look at those beautiful tail feathers
when it opened up
like that was so extra
so extra of like I guess God to create
such a beautiful bird
[Music]
s
foreign
[Music]