oh my god
[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
yeah welcome everybody
to a little special collaboration stream
um i
i felt like doing something that is not
a game so i hit up ina about this
fashion design related idea that i had
uh so i will
explain everything to you guys after we
get a little bit of an introduction
going so let's start with the person
right next to me
[Music]
introduction
from hall of english smith
hi hi
who are you what are your thoughts about
today what was your
artistic passion
i forget to find an answer what am i
doing i don't know yet i'll find out
absolutely biggest strengths and
weaknesses
strengthen weaknesses um oh yeah my
strength is that i know
strength or weakness i'm still in search
of myself
[Laughter]
yeah
a little bit rare occasion
[Music]
i want to apologize to nina for um
making her draw even more
when she was probably already
um
yeah being over
over over over burdened with work anyway
i'm framing worry about it past me not
got everything done and framing
yeah creamy
low frame rates me or the whole stream
me i feel like i'm moving normally
i think you're moving at 30 frames per
second okay yeah a little bit yeah maybe
maybe i don't know don't deal with it
it's not so so problematic
okay just to speed it up gosh
i don't even even know you know it'll be
60 frames yeah that's no problem we had
this like um
months many months ago when my internet
was so that this was normal and
then the one time when we finally got
back to 60 fps it was like a
it was like times the times have changed
like 10 years passed and suddenly
technic uh technical things have
uh
you know anyway let's introduce the
judges uh starting with the one below me
fana
kophana hello hello everyone i'm serious
fauna of whole council and i'm excited
to look at fashion today i love fashion
and i love art and i love the art of my
senpai's ah excited to see
oh you're so motivated let's go
he's motivated you guys did all the hard
work and we just get to come look at
pretty yeah
just sipping my coffee
coming up now too when when you have to
make a choice between mine and enos
designs and say which one you like
better sometimes it might be difficult
a
mental yeah
all right thank you fono for being one
of my judges i really appreciate it
thank you
thanks for having me
and next time we have
mommy oh hi i'm here for the same
reasons
[Laughter]
how what is your what is your connection
with fashion
oh well when i see something that looks
nice i think gosh that looks nice but
i'm not like i'm not really good at
making like things fashionable
but maybe you learned something today
i hope so
yeah
don't judge okay we're gonna be like
judging right but please don't judge my
judging please
everybody has personal tastes so you
know i'm not gonna judge you for your
judging no no
chad don't do that either let's be nice
[Applause]
judge
judging of judging
me judging
yeah and i'll judge them for it yeah
come back chance them back if they don't
so
the thing is since we have two judges
let's say um
okay let me explain the whole system
guys uh
me and ina
drew
um outfits for council members and hope
members beforehand so six outfits each
the theme was
casual
summer outfits actually specifically uh
summer yeah
since the summer is coming up you know
and you got your girls need something to
wear after all yeah
and uh so the thing is well when you
know fauna says i like the one that
kiana designed but women says i like the
one that inner design if they can't
actually make a decision together then
in that case i will make a poll in the
chat and you guys will be the third vote
but if they are able to figure it out
themselves and have like one vote
together without making it into a big
fight
and ripping out each other's hairs and
feathers and sticks in their heads
[Laughter]
then then we'll go without the chat but
yeah but you know the chat will not be
50 50. otherwise i will put you in the
usual room so don't don't be like that i
need i need a decision you know
yeah and if uh let's say for example
first outfit uh you know um what is the
the winner for let's say for example
bale's
outfit then i'll put her on this
champion board oh one two three
five six yeah
and of course it's a six there's still a
chance that at the very end it will
still be a tie let's say you know i got
chosen three times and nina got chosen
three times but don't worry then we'll
just say whatever titty a tie
tie a titty tie tie it
[Music]
yeah is
ending yes good ending um we like ties
here in hollow live uh
just like remember the the the minecraft
summer festival
yeah yeah
so eager to win but then it ended up
being a tie at the very last moment and
you know what i wasn't mad
that was good
right everyone can win if it's a tie yes
exactly yeah it's like a participation
award
no dress
no drama here all right it was anything
i forgot to explain
i don't think so i think it's pretty
clear uh what we're doing so we will i
suppose
already start with the first outfit
are you ready guys
yes i'm ready excited
you'll also be dodging your own outfit
so i'm curious to see how you think
about those
but we will start with someone else's uh
oh and me and um ina will be first
before you give your opinions we will be
giving our
thoughts about the designs so
um let's start with ina and we're
starting with the uh outfit
[Music]
uh where is it there it is
on the right side we have inna's idea on
the left side we have my idea
so inna please
explain ah so
kakozia fashion brand
our
motto is comfy oh
light
and not too hot
isn't like not too hot to wear in the
summer you know yes yes so i wanted to
mix up
uh kind of like
more lively side of bay with uh with the
baseball jacket but then also kind of
like you know like the girly uh more
more calmer
side with a little bit of a
small dress
inside and uh the the shoes she's
wearing is actually
it's actually based on a sandal i wear
are very often
it's very comfy it has a really solid
like base for where you put the feet and
like it like
it like molds to your like the shape of
your feet the more you wear it it
becomes more comfortable so i thought
that would be pretty fitting for bay
yeah
i like the the gradient and the
in the dress and also that it has like
these sparkly uh lines right the
glittery sparkly like yeah they have
it's not really glitter but it has those
like stripes so it's not just a plain
black dress it has a little bit of a
pattern to you know add a little more
detail to the outfit pretty
um if are you done
oh yeah i basically all the outfits i
drew is something i would actually wear
myself
some insight into your own taste as
exactly
okay
uh for me on the left side um i felt
like you know uh bae if she went casuals
she would look really good in a jeans
jacket but it wouldn't be a perfect
jeans jacket it would be a ripped one
with some accessories on it like patches
and all that and so you see the ribbings
on the elbows i think they turned out
pretty good and um um
yeah but uh i wanted to uh combine it
with a cropped hoodie um i feel like
that's very beige the whole uh outfit
yeah and and a a mini skirt because
that's uh
looking cute and also comfy for dancing
although there's there's going to be a
lot of panty shots but that's fine
that's fine
converse because i've heard the converts
go best with the
with the whole overall outfit the shoes
are the last thing that i drew in this
um
um design so
i was like
this this needs some converse also if
you look at some details
and i gave her like if you look at the
top of the skirt i put like those rings
you know those metal rings there i don't
know if you can see it
but i make it a bit bigger here
so you guys can see it
and also then you know a little bit of
a ribbon on the left of the skirt and oh
yeah i also i wanted to uh give her some
kind of bag
and i felt like you know what
she needs to be like able to bring a lot
of things but not have it go get in the
way when she's dancing or running or
jumping so i thought a backpack would be
the best just to go
and with the color at first i was
like i want something that stands out i
don't want everything everything to be
like the same color so i went for green
just to test it out but it it ended up
looking good i like the green
yeah green is good yeah thank you thank
you i like what i like i like the cute
dress from inna as well i don't know it
it feels like if she takes off the
jacket then she could go to like i don't
know a nice dinner in the evening
yeah or uh
yeah yes
i was just saying my designs are very
plain it's just the kind of clothes i
really like
the jacket is nice too i think that
would be good merchandise
actually maybe yeah yeah
here's your new you merchant yeah all
right then let's have our opinions from
our judges let's go with fauna first
so i really like the jacket the split
jacket from inna's
yeah i think it really suits bae
but i think
i think i have to give my point to kiara
this round
just because i really imagine bae
wearing that outfit i think that
the patches make a lot of sense for her
it's very
um
it's like very energetic and cute and a
little bit chaotic and there's the belly
[Laughter]
thank you thank you very much
okay and next up we have mummy
um yes so i do have to weigh uh away
some factors in uh belly button belly
button being expo yes that that's that's
uh
that really uh tips the scale here
um belly button thigh highs the converse
uh i agree with fauna that i would see
bae wearing
the one the chiadas more than hina's but
i also feel like if they switch jackets
ah
yeah that would work really well so yeah
yeah
for casual and so that she can dance and
uh skirt yes great yes good oh you're
like i do think i i see bae
wearing that one more but i also
like okay but keeping in mind
like what i would wear i would wear enos
because i also like
like just ah
more
i don't casual
how to explain
i think if it worked for me i would
probably uh
it depends
i like both personally
but i think nowadays
i would like to wear the dress uh but
the the dress that ina drew drew but
with a different jacket
personally it looks very versatile yeah
in your wardrobe you could wear it
all the time yeah
yeah all right uh so you both in this
case for bale's outfit voted for for me
i suppose
i
yes yeah basically it's what we would
wear yeah thank you
[Music]
okay i'll put myself on the on the
winning board thank you thank you
but
i'm very scared uh because i already
know what inna's outfits look like uh so
the following ones might not be
so looking so good for me i'm nervous
no your your designs are really good
yeah you're so freaked out
i'm the only one who saw everything chat
by the way i trust you
thank you
thank you soon all right
let's go to the next one then next
outfit
uh next outfit yay uh next up we have
fun
it's very um day and night um
my gosh
oh that's that a window chest window oh
my goodness
i'm sorry okay um i'll start i'll start
with my explanation
um
see um all my other outfits that i drew
were like fairly normal i would say uh
but but this one i felt like when i was
drawing funny stuff and i was like i
gotta go edgy for fun i don't know
but that's not i debated on that too
actually but i was like
yeah she had that karaoke before and i
just felt like um
it's like you know i want to see edgy um
scene golf girl
fauna
to see a little bit of a different side
and some variety
um
so we have a skirt with that a thousand
birds pattern you guys know that pattern
know that
no i'll make it
like you know
what what
what is that
no what what
okay uh
anyway uh yeah so we i wanted to put in
a little bit of a pattern even though it
was kind of difficult to drop at it so
that was the only pattern that i really
had
at my disposal and then a corset and uh
this is not a full body uh sheer fabric
no
um
it's it's tight and then a top sheer
thingy with some
lace thingy on the edges and also i gave
her some hair pins
and i made the flowers black
did you see the piercings at her
eyebrows oh
i went all in very edgy and those um
boots have studs um yes
sorry oh
yes this is very day and night do you go
inaudible
oh for mine i forgot to mention one
other thing um
all the outfits i drew them imagining
like like i was like okay if they were
going on a casual date like what kind of
cute outfit
that's kind of
what i was going for in my mind i love
that one i love that dress i would wear
it you know when i think of fauna i kind
of like imagine her walking along the
beach with like the wind and then like
her white dress is like flowy and she's
wearing a nice cute straw hat
the sun is right behind her and this is
like very very nice lighting
i'm plushy
yeah that's what i thought while i was
uh coming up with it and uh
it's not just a plain white dress
there's like a little bit of like yeah
they are making our patterns it's very
cute
uh yeah
i like how the the the sticks go out the
antlers together
i was like i can't
to me it looks like that dress was
originally sold without the belt um but
then thought i was like putting it on
and was like i need a little something
here i need to accentuate my
my waist so she put a belt there and i
like when girls rearrange their outfits
like that and not just wear it the way
it's sold all the time so yeah very
girly i like it
let's start with mummy first what's your
opinion
oh i have so many
okay so
i
love chiatas
as well i wanted to draw you like that
too it would have been perfect for both
of you
it's just it's
i love it but
but
i'm sorry for the butt but that's okay
uh
i don't okay so true emails i think
would wear this in the summer heat yeah
they wouldn't care but you knows would
be
more uh appropriate for the casual
summer weather and i can see it frana
gardening it with that cute oh my gosh
watching her in the garden with it
and if i saw her walking down
not the street because she's nature
walking in the forest i'd be like oh she
she could totally be mother nature yeah
well
if i saw fauna walking down the street i
would not stop staring and i would uh
i i don't know if i would associate
nature with her anymore i think the
other thing to keep in mind
is uh
fauna would you still wear
would you are you still in the face
fauna well honestly i wear a little bit
of everything these days i would wear
both of these outfits
[Music]
yet a girl can wear both
guys
with my outfit but i just wanted
something different but i do personally
feel like the right one is more like
fitting to what fauna normally looks
like you know like you know it's more
like
faunage um but it's like both it's like
her two personalities you know
yeah that's why it's hard
they're so different
if you can't handle me on my left you
can't help
[Music]
so yes both are amazing i would
absolutely wear both i love
i love the details on kiara's i think
the
the window is very
blurring
very nice very nice
cute skirt i do have a skirt that's kind
of similar to that oh
wait didn't you have that in the office
i was like that looks really familiar i
can't wait to point that out
to purpose i did not do it on purpose
i definitely wear would wear both of
these kinds of outfits
it's like winter and summer you know
i mean winter maybe it would be too cold
for that but yes maybe all them maybe it
was more like hot
true emails don't care about yeah yeah
nothing can build against the coldness
in your heart
[Laughter]
well so who did mummy vote for i don't
know you don't know you want to hear
fawna's opinion first
i think so i think i yeah i think in the
end i do have to
give it to ina
just because i also love a flowy dress
and yeah she's so pretty in the hat
i i immediately i want i want this dress
oh okay i thought
now movement okay don't need to have
this influence you too much you know
just because it might become a tie we
can still ask a chat
fighting's fun um
i'm just i'm honestly so i'm probably
overthinking it because i'm thinking
okay if we're sticking with the theme of
summer right but if it's like what my
preference
left but what was
actually aware
yeah
there's many ways of looking at it
indeed
i think we gotta ask chad i'm sorry oh
okay so you gonna
say
i guess kiara so the next because you
need to ask a chat
for the third opinion because if you say
inaudible actually it might be that you
know has a point and a half okay
a point and a half
well that's just holding it if i split
it if can i split my is it so loud
even if you play this
inna is still the winner so that's okay
that's okay
then at least we don't uh you know we
don't have a tie then
i just want to thank you both
yes
impartial impartial is that the word
you just need to judge don't think about
our
feelings
okay so we're gonna have inna for this
one all right
okay okay
congratulations one point
or the chat really wants okay you know
what i'm actually curious to see
generally even if we don't count the
votes this time i want to hear their
opinion first of all
for for bale's outfit if you guys still
remember maybe i should show it one more
time
and let me
go back
uh left
or right
let's vote for bail so your vote is not
gonna count anymore chad but uh
just you know
and you guys want to you guys want to
say your opinion so i'll let you guys
say your opinion
even if it is
even if it doesn't matter anymore
okay
i'll keep it running for
uh
okay thank you guys that's left
oh 69 okay i'll end it there because
that's a nice number
okay
then let's do the the final one
left and
right
chat
go ahead
say what you want to say
don't think about you know
[Music]
don't be so biased just let out your
opinion yeah listen to your heart
in what way would you want to come
across fauna which outfit
oh my god
imagine sitting in a bar and on the left
side you have the left fauna and on the
right side you have the right fauna at
the counter there they're sandwiching a
bar though
just do something if you have a fancy
fancy restaurant or at the beach you
know it really depends
where did you guys go for a day
no personally i would probably
i would probably prefer to talk to the
right fauna as
well but it's good to know that fauna
has like another side to herself that
you might have what if you guys are like
right fauna coming back from like my
chemical romance like concert you know
like
wide range in her in her closet you know
okay thank you chad
it seems like chad so far agrees with
our judges so that means judges judges
our judges have a good taste
all right thank you let's go to the
next outfit
headband oh my gosh i love the headband
so
in the summer
you know it's really hot especially in
like japan and you know island and i've
been there i almost melted there's this
one type of fabric that really makes it
bearable it's kind of like i don't know
what you call it but it's cozy though
and like very very flowy
i know if you make a dress out of that i
felt like it was going to be really
really nice for the summer
and so
uh i could totally see iris in that i
only put like sparkly like the jewels i
don't know if you can see but i see on
the dress design and then have her uh
shoes kind of stand out by being
being at
white and then she'll have those like
cool what are those called aviator
sunglasses
yeah
that's what i thought i love the sheer
fabric
it looks like it would be nice for the
summer evening
yeah
summer fans as i told you guys i was
like okay if they were on a date what
kind of outfit did you do
that was my uh that was my reasoning
behind all the outfits anything about if
you were on a date with that person you
and i said you and father and you and me
family members
[Laughter]
yeah
okay
um i'll go um
so to be honest when i started designing
this i didn't really have a clear plan
but once i
drew the top and the skirt i was like
okay i guess we're turning her into a
barbie slash mean girl slash i don't
know
cute
cute high school chick dressing up who's
also kind of she has rich parents um and
she's very popular in in high school yep
yep
not quite a mix of valley girl and and
mean girl and uh the movies you're
thinking of yeah yeah yeah yeah
also uh i like how inna put those stones
in the dress well i put the sparkly
stones in her hairs i put some pearls in
there oh
yeah
and i gave her a headband and a necklace
and some yeah you know stuff oh yeah
yeah but the the skirt i like the skirt
because the tights good that's like
wrapped around so if she walks you can
probably see a little bit of a split
going on there maybe maybe maybe
oh also i don't know if it came across
that way but i wanted the top to have
like kind of a silky
silky touch
all right let's get the opinion from
fauna first
oh
okay
i
i immediately got like the y2k 2005
fives which are very nostalgic like the
mean girls
yes perfect isn't it fetch like so
fetched
um and he knows i love the the fabric it
reminds me of like a night sky and how
it's layered
oh
again it could really be day and night
outfit yeah
this time i'm the day and he knows the
night one him
i think i have to go with inna though i
really love this fabric this beautiful
fabric okay okay that's fine that's fine
uh movement what about you
um i would like to point out that ina
has uh given them sandals i think every
time which i appreciate
it's the um
yes for the summer
i feel like um
oh no oh
you know
[Music]
no oh no
no
yeah
but i think that's good like i i wanted
nothing to like be very different it
would be too boring if everything was
the same
that's true then i i'm kind of
forgetting like how we're supposed to
base this is it if it's good for summer
would they wear it or
their preference is it a mix of
everything i would say the same criteria
should the main main criteria should be
um what
you
think looks best on that person
[Music]
um
i really like them both but i would i
like how keanus looks
like i just like the idea she had and i
think it is really shitty
then we have a title chat
yeah we have a thai chat this is where
your opinion matters chad you sure the
poll is coming up there you go fresh out
of the oven
make your choice make it wisely
who will make it to the champion board
true drum roll
i'll give you guys one music a minute
the hair is so different um
i hope uh uh actually it's
is it's
coincidence um but the next
outfits that you're gonna see are um
probably the ones where i went a bit
crazy with the hair too
yeah
so this up until this point i still was
very tame with it but in the next outfit
i actually did something with the hair
too
i left the hair alone
yeah uh i hope i won't get disqualified
for that but it's my stream so my rules
everything's cool
okay
we have a winner oh why did it move
oopsie
there we go we have a winner and it's
idiot
so
let me write it down irit ah i i i
yeah
i risk
okay
all right i don't know which one is next
but we're going to that
next outfit
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
prioritizes comfy and i really like i
love it
i love like oversized like sweaters with
like the
colored t-shirt
the highlights
uh pants to
what's
yeah so
to
finish it all up i gave her some
uh
you know sneakers and white socks and
you can't really see but there's like a
certain type of straw hat that kind of
looks like a fedora
you want to give her a fedora with a
little little bomb it's not like a it's
not like a monkey luffy
she's wearing it's like the more fedora
with the little bump in the middle and
the hat
would the hat be pretty flat on the
it's like
i'm gonna look up straw hat fedora
actually
fauna fan i had one too in your outfit
right
mm-hmm
i never think i don't think i actually
see what you're talking about yeah yeah
yeah
i don't know why i couldn't picture that
i don't know how to explain it but yeah
i really like this style on crony i
think i would want to wear that
uh again we kind of have a day and night
problem here because i went for a little
bit more elegant
lady
mommy style
um
i'm sorry
i wanted to give her some um flowy
pants so those are those are like
very thin and flowy fabric like if she
walks and the wind blows and it will
flow like wash wash
and the top is
off shoulder and asymmetric and uh in a
in a
shiny
blue uh not shiny but also what's that
fabric called um
um
uh the one where
that's kind of fuzzy what
oh fuzzy
fuzz
i don't think i know the name velvet yes
velvet oh velvet
it's supposed to be kind of like that
also of course she needs a watch so i
gave her a watch and some pearls because
she's a rich lady and she looks perfect
so uh her jewels are perfect as well and
yeah sorry about the hair i felt like
she needed like if i would leave the
hair like that it would not match with
the rest of the outfit so i gave her
like something else
yeah
okay
let's start with mommy
oh
i did not think this would be so
difficult
from here today you shouldn't have
signed up huh
i don't know what i was expecting
again they're just so different like for
it depends the type of crony you want
yeah you want
your pony you want her to
to drive in her minivan to the soccer
controller
wait what's wrong with that
left oh i see okay elegant bombs okay
let the coach yell at the coach for
not letting you play in the game
um
and then i feel like
right is like pretty like i
feel like
like that on the date i see him more
like the right one i see her more like
just hanging out with friends or going
shopping
you know
in that other casual thing you know yeah
elegant date yeah yeah i mean the theme
wasn't date anyway so that's not a
criteria don't worry
i can't i can't help but laugh because
it's crony um
what does that mean
poor crowning
it's crowdy i think i would imagine
what do i imagine it's like i imagine at
the surface level crony wearing left by
imagine the inner
your child crew i'm just kidding i'm
wearing it right
not a little dog
dang it
i'm sorry fauna go ahead
now you make your
decision on your own
if you were to see crony in one of these
outfits which one do you
[Music]
prefer the situation
i'll go right i'll go right okay i like
her legs okay okay okay okay okay now
let's have fun to tell us her opinion
okay okay
um
i'll start talking about enos i really
like it reminds me a bit of like boy
style
yes um you know like the shorts and like
the the button up shirt yeah this is
like a little got a little bit of
femininity with the sweater
in the hat and i like that actually i
want to copy that style because i don't
think i've ever had like a blouse like
that underneath a
sweater like that i never wore it like
this before i kind of want to try it out
it really depends like if it's in the
summer you want to kind of get the ones
that only have like the
the color part like attached to the
cardigan part
some clothes are cheap so they just make
them
the winter and like the fall then you
kind of want to have like different
colors actual
clothes are underneath yes you can even
have like pattern colored shirts it
doesn't have to be always like
it makes them mad
anyway sorry fauna continue and then for
kiara's i really
i don't know something about crony
wearing pants yeah i feel like jesus
there's just something very powerful
about cronie i mean cronie in a suit
cronian
long pan
yeah
very good very good
yes very elegant
i'm gonna go with laura
the pants i feel like she would wear oh
something like this and i i think the
like wide leg pants are very
fashionable right now they're hard to
pull i think that's not like
but for someone like cronie with those
three meters long legs for her they're
easy to pull up if you have long legs
then they look so good yeah i can't pull
them off anyway that means we have a tie
so we need the chat to help us
left all right all right uh go chat i'll
give you some time to uh decide and uh
yoroshiku then we'll have our winner on
the board our
fourth
outfit winner
let's see what chad is going for oh
oh
no
they want to see crony mommy
understandable who doesn't want to see
chronic but i really like personally
like i would
never wear what cronie wears on the left
side
i wouldn't wear from the right side but
i think
i like both looks on her very much
one is more mature and the other is more
cutesy
yes
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay i think the
chat has decided thank you very much for
your cooperation
this one goes to me so we also on the
board have a tie currently
uh
crony like the watch i don't know what
funny to me
it makes so much sense right now is it
an apple watch so so grand it's just a
red yeah it's a rolex it's 100 a rolex
roy
because that's the only one i know
consider crony in a tailored suit with a
pocket watch
[Laughter]
oh no
yeah well well let's be real crony is
perfect so she would look good in
anything
so this was not really
really a fair choice to make sorry for
that
uh let's go to the fifth outfit let's
watch next outfit
which one is it gonna be
[Applause]
oh my gosh
oh no
[Music]
we have lost
okay
i'm gonna start
by
saying i originally started drawing this
um
with the
japanese fashion style
morty girl in mind i don't know if you
guys know it but it was difficult to
draw and then i figured also hmm
so many layers i feel like
mummy would probably not go for full on
mori style anyway so i kind of stopped
and then just made it into a summer
dress with some leather elements like
for example the back is like
like a
um uh braided
kind of uh
leather and then the shoes as well i
don't know if you see it but it was
supposed to be kind of braided
and so kind of like a bag it would kind
of be like a
i feel like she would have gotten it
from a from a vintage or second-hand
shop um like combining old letters
things with some with a cute um perhaps
even self-made dress with some ruffles
and sunflower and
i love the thing that she has on her on
her hair i used to love to wear these
kind of ribbons they have wire in it so
they stand up and i would always put
that on my head when i was a bit younger
yeah i love them so much
it's so cute
all right next up uh you know what were
your thoughts
um so uh
let's see moving in a cute little dress
and uh i don't know i don't know if you
can tell but her her little friend would
actually turn into a little bag on the
side
yeah something similar happened to uh
you know
watch the outs and turn the ipad but
um
but yeah you know i thought you know i
kind of i was imagining
i was imagining a situation like spring
summer time you're going on like a like
a movie thing
oh yeah
i feel like yours is a little bit you
meet up at like like like and like
the aquarium together and then
movies
yeah i kind of
i can't imagine that
i feel like yours is a bit more childish
mine is a bit more girlish but uh i can
see really like babe i love it
and the little ribbon i love it
thank you
before we hear what roommate says let's
listen to fauna first
oh me first even though it's moving yeah
so you don't get influenced by mommy
okay okay
[Music]
mummy is cute no matter what i think
anna's
the lesson here
um
okay i'll talk about first talk about
kiara's i love the shoes they're so cute
and
i totally get what you mean about like
the
i don't know it's like yeah like the
leather they're like natural but also
humanity
material
the
headband is so clever
with the
our shape i love the cute
sunflower very cute
and the hairstyle
and
with enos i love the pink
i love pink
and i love the the bag the friend bag
and the feather necklace
there's the bullet is so good
and i have to go with nina
for the friend bag
friend wins
[Laughter]
give you a vote
i think so
go ahead
[Music]
the situations that she gave i thought
were like i would like to wear something
like that you know out and about or you
know going to an aquarium or walking
down the street
and stuff i like that friend is uh like
that in that state i do like that
ready to be recycled
yes
um
but also kia does oh i just can't
imagine laying in a flowery field
and i don't know soaking up the sun
and just going on a walk
in nature maybe with nature if she wants
to come
and i think the shoes are really cute
and i love the i love that the ribbon it
replaces the feathers yeah
so to go with the summer theme i would
like to both
go walk around go to aquariums and stuff
but i'd also like to go in a fiery field
i will go with kiara
wait do we have a tie again well
i think so yeah i would not likely wear
enos but i think i i wish i was
confident enough to wear a chiatos
yeah well then once again it is time for
the chat to help us
you guys are making some important
decisions today
there you go the paul is
online now
go go go go go go go check it out
what
have you gone shopping with like other
girlfriends before yeah yeah yeah of
course haven't we have a long time
you know
i've been going out like shopping
in a long time
we're with girls but whenever i used to
i'd follow them around and i wouldn't
get my own stuff and just do stuff for
me so oh i want to dress you up
i wanna dress you up
next time next time guys i kind of
prefer going shopping
alone because then i feel like i don't
feel guilty for taking time and i don't
feel awkward about picking certain
pieces you know
although i do also like to join others
going shopping
shopping
i'll spend an hour in a store then leave
with nothing
[Laughter]
okay we have a winner it's enya but i
gotta be honest i i if like i feel like
enos outfit is definitely like more like
it it captured something where in the
cities you know
but like if you're like out in the
country and you can you know just be
freed and i would definitely go with
kiara's alpha exactly that's how i know
about it yeah no i think i think the
lummy one captured uh
the inner one captured movement better
but i don't know i kind of wanted to
draw him something girl we can mix them
up fan artists do it
okay oh my god we're having a great day
today i think the last one is actually
the the next one is the last one i think
yeah
yeah the next one oh this isn't fitting
the next one is
well who's left
[Music]
close your eyes
okay
i'm going to open though
tatan open
um
i'll start um
this was the first one that i drew so um
i feel like if i drew it last i would
have drawn something differently uh or
like completely different um i wanted to
give her like kind of a
um
casual but still magical girl vibe and
the
galaxy fabric that you see on top is
like plastic actually like a sheer
plastic oh with a galaxy pattern thingy
yeah
very shiny
and flower crown yeah it's got supposed
to be a mix of sailor moon and galaxy
and harajuku fashion she has some
daisies uh on her
on her head i changed her hairstyle a
little bit i love them the makeup
lipstick and i gave her some um sparkly
stones underneath her eyes
yeah
so this is this is how
uh
sana would look like if she were to
visit harajuku takeshita dori perhaps
much cleavage as well um but yeah i
don't know after looking at this now uh
i probably would have made some things
differently but i don't know is this
that's very um
fashionable still
you know what what about yours what
about yours
mine i felt like like santa's like
very lively cute personality kind of
fits in like those like big oversized
t-shirts with like really cute graphics
in the front
and i i saw her drawing her her bread
dog
that was really cute
i added it to the design and i love like
those high-waist like jeans that are
kind of like ripped
like you could kind of see like
the white little patches yeah i thought
that would look really nice
and then
her sandals i felt like she would like
choose something that like stands out
yeah color-wise and i can use that
magenta color of her limiter and it's
like one of those like kind of it's not
like leather or anything it's kind of
like those like fancy see-through kind
of like plastic ish material have you
guys seen those like waterproof kind of
sporty sandals that's kind of what i
imagined it is
it looks very comfy overall
all right then let's see what the mummy
says
oh i go first yes okay i'm just going to
put this really weird thought like my
first thought
out here um
so i felt like i would be more
comfortable sitting on sana's lap on the
right and on the left
i don't know how to explain it
but
i don't know that it should influence my
vote um but
i
i feel
it
sorry can you remind me what the
criteria is again is it
what
you think fits the person the most
it's them the most they both fit her in
different ways though
ah cause she she does like that like the
the more fantasy fairy tale yeah yeah
magical girls often i can also like she
also likes the cute casual with the tea
with the bread doggy on it yes red dog
cute
oh no
[Music]
because
i think i see it
it's the graph the graphic d is selling
that's
good idea another merchandise idea here
we go
let's go
you're welcome sana
okay okay okay what does uh father say
don't feel pressured this is the last an
important vote not pressured at all
they're tied until here
good
um enos reminds me a lot of like papa
paco has been drawing a lot of
casualties
yeah
her artist her papa uh posted a fan art
or fan it's not a fan i don't think it's
a pop bar again
of santa in casual clothes which i saw
before the stream i was like damn it we
we don't need to design anything anymore
here's the real deal
yeah
[Laughter]
yeah i feel like nina's very in line
with that kind of style too
um
i love the shoes
and well i love everything about both i
love yours because sun and doves love
cute and girly things and frills and
pink and it is so magical girl like
immediately i thought sailor moon
perfect this one is fixed
i think i have to vote for magical girl
sauna let's go
give me another time god damn it
so many of them are
you guys made this really difficult
that's all you're here for
all right i'm putting up the paul
please do your job chat do your thing
um
and yeah
while we're waiting for that um i'm glad
that i invited you girls for this
collaboration i want to do some some
more streams that are not games not the
typical stuff you know wanted to do
something creative and
fun
that's not the same always so yeah i
felt like designing some outfits also
because like your girls you girls need
some new outfits desperately so here you
go you're welcome to use all of them
just paste it
as a png on top of your avatar
not to put pressure on fauna but what if
we like switched one day like fawn and i
drew different outfits for myth
i was literally just thinking that
yeah i do want to see that but the
problem would be that we already have
like casual and elegant and all that yes
yeah maybe you could come up with us you
can surprise us with the topic you know
yeah
there are more themes out there what we
don't have is like winter clothes for
example oh i love winter clothes you can
layer a lot of things with winter
clothes so it could be fun
oh please do it i want to see
yeah
hell yeah
all right we have a winner and it's okay
guys i'm not mad because i agree um
[Music]
i wanted to redo sana's almost um but it
was too late so this one is inna and you
see with this everybody
the winner overall
thankfully it's not a tie i guess
thankfully
the winner is my heart
[Music]
thank you thank you
congratulations
ina you're the young buddy
you are the fastest
fashion i don't know i think i kind of
just like
put a lot of my
my personal preference when it comes to
clothes into the designs like
as i said these are all stuff i would
wear
yeah yeah me too
yeah i mean yours is that you chose i
would mostly wear it too i think
i think kara you you surprised me with
just so many cute outfits too like
especially mumma is like i'm just like
wow yeah i'd wear that
and bass too i really like the the
jacket and the and the converse and uh
yeah thai high socks
yeah
so so cute
i wanted to
um even though i really like all the
ones from inna i kind of wanted to um go
for a little bit less simple
mostly simple is best but i wanted to
have some some special ones like this
one even if it's kind of a little bit me
me
i love it
i'm grateful i'm so grateful i want to
draw an edgy version of mummy now
yeah yeah i wanna see
i would be oh so happy i would love that
please
or like edgy version of all of us
all of cancel all of them is all girls
on the way to like chemical romance
concert
the edge version
yes
oh i have a question overall are you
guys able to decide which one was your
like favorite overall out of all of them
[Music]
um i'll try to decide to
try
i think my favorite almost is
iris cause like i love what i did there
the mean girl's vibe
can hear iris with her bro
what do you think girls
so like overall toppings
it's advised the one that nina made for
me
mm-hmm wait where is it i like
here
there it is is that your top favorite
i think so oh you know what's the best
about this outfit it's like when you're
in the sun and the sun is behind you the
shadow
yes
the shadow the shadow you can see
the silhouette of the body very well you
[Music]
now it's my favorite i'm just kidding um
i like i feel like i was curious iris
was very clever
that was um
from chiara yeah and enos i really
i could totally see her going for that
for like an official casual even i can
see yeah i was going for that
what about chad are there any is there
like a top favorite that you have guys
and don't just say crony because well i
don't know which one you mean
tell me tell me guys tell me guys what's
your top favorite also i'm gonna be
posting these on twitter afterwards
oh oh god chad too fast i don't even
know i don't even know
got fauna
pants crony emo fauna
evil fun
which one they're both wearing pants
long pants
oh any pants it's good to see that uh
you guys um are not too mad about the
pants because uh i've noticed a culture
going on that's uh saying band pants in
hall of english or in whole life in
general but pants are not so bad guys
oh you guys don't know the true
appreciation for pants i got it i
personally don't like pants i never wear
pants i wouldn't wear pants but i don't
mind pants you
yeah
yeah i used to wear only dresses and
skirts but recently just for like i
don't know because
i was being too lazy i was wearing more
and more pants but i still love my mini
skirts and my mini
pants
short pants
i still love them like long skirts yeah
long skirt
i've been starting to enjoy long pants
too yeah yeah well thank you chad for
your opinions um uh even though it's
very confusing when the chat goes so
fast so i'll be uploading these on
twitter and you guys can uh reply and
tell us again if you want thank you for
joining this fun stream and looking at
these designs and and yeah uh
um uh praising our design ideas
hopefully we'll see uh something like
this on council and hope one day
hopefully hope hopefully
[Laughter]
we want to see you girls and some more
outfits until then we will be patiently
waiting and sitting and waiting and
sitting and waiting how to wait faster
how do you wait faster
call crony what about it
okay that's a good idea all right all
right also i want to send these to the
members to the council and hope members
who are not here today and see what they
think i'm curious
all right thank you everybody for
watching and let's have a last comment
from everybody
fauna is like uh lighting up so much so
you go first
yes thank you for having us this is
really fun i love seeing
all of your
your art and your fashion
it was very fun i hope next time you can
be the judges and we can yeah we can
make friends
for you we would love to thank you for
being a judge today bona
thank you
last comments
thank you also for drawing us in such
cute outfits
also also for making the time possible
for me to judge things yeah yeah i moved
the stream because i wanted you to be
there from the beginning i need your i
need your opinion you know do i now at
first i was like oh they'll be drawing
i'm glad it worked out all prepared yeah
it worked out nicely thank you mommy for
for making it in time i appreciate you
being here even though it was kind of
short short notice from me yeah so
thanks for making the time you too
ina last
comments ah thank you kiara for inviting
me to do this i know like the last like
couple weeks we were both like so busy
we were like okay let's do this here and
then i was like oh no but then like we
got here so i'm glad we found
yeah i really love the office that you
came up with i had a lot of fun working
on it so yeah we can do more fun things
on the line yeah
we should start uh you know talk a
taco bell and kfb should start a fashion
line
oh yeah
any clothing bakeries out there you know
we can we can collaborate you know yes
i have a lot of
ideas give us the wheel to control we're
gonna do our best look at those cute
outfits i mean
hello we can also be your personal
fashion designer or fashion shopper
personal shoppers we can do that too
yeah just write us an email and yeah
we'll tell us uh we'll tell you our
rates hourly rates are kind of high but
i would say it's so worth it like oh my
god look at those fetch out my god
i
[Laughter]
for being here hope you enjoyed it uh
tomorrow i'll be first of all on
energy's channel and then later we'll
have a members only and so two streams
tomorrow um i hope you enjoyed this i've
said that five times now uh but i really
hope you enjoyed it
and oh oh maybe there will even be some
fan art of these outfits um
we have a ending greeting on my channel
it's german but you girls if you if you
feel confident enough feel free to join
in
and in german we say
alfred
[Music]
thank you congratulations
thank you bye bye and good night
[Music]
do
you