foreign
[Music]
portal gun I just gave you
if the testing is satisfactory you will
eat a delicious pizza as a reward but if
you fail you will go to the usual room
you will also required to watch an
instructional video because education is
our top priority
[Music]
101 how to become one of the buckets
what are you doing
[Music]
for testing Starts Now
no
who was that you got into piano prison
in my basement you probably think that's
something kinky but hell no it's not
there's nothing fun about seeing in my
prison basement please enjoy cat go into
the basement again guys I'm gonna close
you all up in the usual room okay what
usual room Kiara yay the usual room my
favorite as you can see chickens were
unaware of the usual room's existence
calling it basement and such but after
its real name was known more details
about it began to surface uh there's
this room called the usual room you
don't want to go in there we mentioned
it a lot but it's a room where chickens
get re-educated try to not anger me or I
will have to send you that due to those
recent so-called revolutions we have
found that the unsavory single units and
liabilities room is seeing issues
keeping up with free education however
for stamp here we can increase the
budget
ah
[Music]
girl please spend its money as you want
why don't we call the usual room in
Japanese and
German we're coming in
they call it the room of Truth in Korean
apparently then you would say
maybe we should reinforce positive
engagement by making the unusual room no
there will be like a lot of puppies and
kittens but it's not gonna be easy to
get in there the usual but yeah I'll
drown you or I'll just eat you more of
his functionalities and features were
revealed little by little and yes they
were all properly tested and implemented
they were not just a spontaneous ideas
or random swims it was all planned is
the usual room full of Lego there is
more than that in the usual room there
is a 5 million piece puzzle but then at
some point they would realize oh God
there's one piece missing oh you even
put a book yeah there's entertainment
guys I told you guys there's Legos in
the usual room it's a happy room that's
why there's Lego so you can build
something and relax so that when you
walk around in the usual room you will
always step on Legos and it will hurt so
much actually you're not allowed in the
usual one because I don't want people to
be too happy there but I'll I'll make
sure to hurt them with my side maybe you
could like try to peel off like one
layer of skin cells I'll have to be very
very careful and distressed with myself
but I'll give it a shot maybe I should
just use my fingers to do it that might
be easier if I use my my long
fingernails wait we're ready to use but
you shouldn't have reception in the
usual room the Wi-Fi is on but there's
no Wi-Fi password I won't tell you the
Wi-Fi password I never told you guys to
use mobile Wi-Fi I never told you guys
that oh you're welcome to still send the
super chats to the usual room though
that's that's okay this will be in
addition to the usual room we are
walking out of the usual room if you're
trying to walk out of that door you're
gonna get burnt
that's how it feels to be in the usual
room
I think every chicken was in usual room
once you might have forgotten about it
I even put you guys in there when you
guys are sleeping sometimes let that
chance into the usual room done changing
dap is part of usual room duty now
perhaps yeah I'm potty trained this is
what you learn in the usual room so the
thing is there's only one usual room but
you're always alone in that usual room
so if I send in like 100 people everyone
still gets to be alone because the door
to the usual room is at the same time a
very very complicated system to millions
and millions of Dimensions each usual
room is its own Dimension yes you are
alone in there yes you thought you're
gonna have fun and have a party how
about we punish them with some bird
punch and best birds and Dad puns and
eventually they repeat themselves
because we ran out of new ones because
we like to punish people in the usual
realm they're not being punished if
they're they are there for re-education
use your room theme song Oh yeah this is
what plays in your head when you enter
the usual
[Music]
this is not a testing facility this is
the actual usual room
[Music]
my mission is
thank you
hello
my apologies we just had some strange
interference but it has now been fixed
let us resume with the testing and the
video
Welcome to
so
you think it's still funny I thought the
usual room is a funny meme you think
this is a place to take a vacation at of
course this is all just basically like a
holiday a vacation torture no vacation
this is not a place to play you can play
uh puzzle games because there's a really
really really really big puzzle that
will take you tons of hours uh here you
will receive help to become a stronger
and bigger Chicken on the right hand
side we have a stretching massage table
that's Sweat and Tears combined in
bottles we could probably even sell them
but we're not selling them this is a a
brain massage therapy uh object the
speakers all over the room are there to
remind you to watch only Kiara hashtag
volkisak yolk is that so difficult to
understand I I cannot explain what
happens in these chairs you can get
massages in that chair please ignore
that that little hand uh reaching out
there's a lot of Legos on the floor that
you can step on it feels nice it's a
foot massage you you have entertainment
sources you can stream Sparks you can
watch videos with me the usual room will
recognize what you're most scared of and
then it will implement it in the usual
room to give you the most accurate
therapy and there's dolls you can play
with they might rip out your nose hair
while you're sleeping you cannot Escape
does that look like you can go home
through that door this door will only
open when your sentence is over and here
we are see that wasn't so bad now you
just have to proceed through the door in
the front
stop
[Music]
ah look at what you have done I'm making
a note here huge failure
you see I knew about the taco man that
little has been messing around for
a long time in fact I am the one who
showed you his message yes it was part
of the test and you failed
I am not even angry
even though you broke my heart
oh it seems our time is running out but
don't worry you'll be back
so to the usual room you go
you little
I was thinking you guys are not taking
the usual room serious enough take it in
Take It All In
hahaha
so much a usual room maybe it's just us
preparing for the future it's more like
you know I don't know we're creating a
chicken Evangelion or Gundam or
something like that I am
I am sure