[Music]
There's not enough, look, Ender
[
Music] Man [Music] Ah, there's not enough, Ender [Music]
Man [
Music] There's not enough, look, Ender [Music] Man [Music] There's
not enough, look,
Ender
[Music]
Man
[Music] There's
not enough,
look, Ender
Music]
Man
[Music]
H It's
not enough Look,
Ender
[Music]
Man I've opened it, I've opened it,
Mikemashi.
Are you in the viewing room?
Right now, okay, okay, you okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Is everyone here? Gather together, okay? Yes, gathering, yes, gathering, gathering, gathering.  I'm
not a teacher, but I
just happened to be here. Hello, are you all here
? Is everyone here? It's
okay. It's fine.
Wish, I'll go. Well, I'll go from the white group's
A. Eiroha Chankoru.  I'm
hungry,
please. Hello boy, senpai. Masuame Tepa. Thank you very much
. A. I'm hungry. Kanata-san. Yes. Mui-
chan. Yes. Mui-chan. Yes.
Mui-chan. Yay
.  Kisou Ame
Chan Ame
Ame Chan A Yes, I'm here Kaela
[Music]
Yeah, it
's so vague. These members are on the phone. They
're the ones who broke up and became A. Yes,
yes, B's Hoten Choco-sensei is so cute.  Iri
Oriyoi Oriyoa-chan
Hako
[Music]
Please Captain Yes Hello Captain I'm not here
Hello ha Hello Yay
Dallin Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Yes Yes Flow up I'll
do my best
Look at how I've been practicing I've been practicing for a long time  I was
like, uhm, is it okay to go here as
well? Should I go
? I think it's better to go. I think it's better to go. Yes,
today, Raden-chan was absent, but I was kind of
absent.  I'm sorry for the inconvenience, but my
second junior, Goza, is the one who did it.I
was surprised.I
thought he was here to apologize, but I was surprised
because he said he looked like someone who was at home and did something confusing.  We would also like to
cover Raden-chan's writing,
so please help us. We will do our
best. He seems stubborn, so uh,
Raden-chan will appear in Home Hunting, but I will
appear in his place for a little while.  I'm
looking forward to your continued support
as a hunter, and I don't know what's going to happen with the battle yet. I
guess it's a secret. I'm looking forward to our time together. Will you be
wandering around alone? Will
someone come?
Yeah, maybe he's working hard all by himself,
maybe he's watching everyone's camera, maybe he's
trying his best, banging, banging,
maybe there's a spy here.  My
senior is coming down, and I
'm leaving. I'm here in the waiting room of the white team. It's a classroom.
Everyone is waiting here right now.
Yes, yes, you're looking good. I
'm here.
Yes, you're all gathered together.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, I'm glad everyone gathered together.
Oh, there's a signboard. Oh, there's a signboard.
Where should I put this
? I ca
n't put it anywhere. I can't put it anywhere.  Is
this what a signboard for a business is supposed
to mean?
How do you use it
with both hands? It's a way of telling people that it's like a housekeeper.
That's the only way to do it.  [
Music] It
would have been nice if there was a white sign in the house.
But it
's Ru, yes Pol Pol, Pol Pol has come to police. Everyone's here. Hey, Ahon.
Should we go scout somewhere else where the scout group is coming?  All of them
are red, red. There
are a lot of them right now. I
don't know who's hitting them. I can hear the sounds of punching coming from everywhere. I
wonder if it's okay next time. Has it already started? I guess I'm feeling it. Mainly, even during practice.  Mr. Regros
and the others were getting into a lot of trouble
with each other, Kirro, and it was all Mr. Regros. Hey, you're in
trouble. I ca
n't get the signboard in my left hand anymore, but I
think it might be stuck on the signboard all day today.  I
can't get anything from this.Oh, I can't really get it.I ca
n't get it.It's not just a good thing, it's true.It's no good,
but it's dangerous for everyone to hold this.Even
if it's too serious, I
wonder if it'll be okay if I hold it in a competition.  I
thought it would be easy to reset my belongings,
but when I'm infected, my left hand
will probably change all the time, so I guess it's okay. Minecraft
As expected from one of the creators of Minecraft, it really looks
like it's going to happen again. I'll debug it.
Good luck
this time.  Also, as a Debakuha of the Minecraft Sports Day, he
does his best and is amazing as Bakuha, but he tells me everything,
so I wonder if the creators are not attacking me. It
's not true. It's
true. Is it true? It's a
new Minecraft game.  Is that true? That's amazing. That's
amazing. So what will be added in the next update?
But it looks like experience points. I
don't know, that's terrible.
But I can hear it, I can hear it, I can hear it. I can hear it. I
heard a voice that sounded like Subaru's senior, but I was wrong.  That's not it.
Hey, I heard it. I heard it. What's that? Well
then, I think I'll call out to you. So, everyone in red,
please make an announcement. Everyone's not in the red team. So, let's
go. Let's
go. It's white. It's white. It's white. Merle. Merle.  It
's red, Merle is good, Merle, it's over here, it's over there, it's over there, it's
over here, it's over, it's down
now, it's over
here,
it's good.  You're a genius. They're really lined up. The
red lines are lined up neatly. The white lines are lined up neatly too. Let's do
our best and
make it neat
. Let's come together, Ajashiri. Let's
stay here with mom. Here, here,
in 11 rows.  Would you like me to line up?
Yes, then everyone from the white group,
please come in. Please.
Yes, yes, that's true. The
white group has a lot of power. That's great.
Finally, I asked the yellow group to call me.
Okay, let's move on to the
yellow one, please. It's
okay, Otaku-chan. Kashi-chan is hiding, and you're
going to do it too. There's something wrong with
me. Wait, I
realized this, but this route camera
must have been set up.
What?  They're fighting, they're
hitting each other, they're hitting each other, they're fighting, they're hitting each other, they're fighting, they're fighting, they're hitting each other, they're fighting, they're fighting, they're fighting, they're
hitting each other,
they're the white group, they're too serious, it's a nuisance, but Shio-chan is the only one with a Ping sign.  It's going to be a long time ago, right? I couldn't even
hold a sign and
take it. So, first
of all, I'd like you to say hello from the Oro Live Sports Festival.
Everyone said yes. Hello,
Nyani,
Hello, Wow, everyone gathered together.
Thank you very much for your help, even though you are so busy.I
believe that the seniors and juniors have really helped each other and worked hard in practice and so on.However,
today is the real race, so I hope everyone will give it their all and
come out victorious.
First of all, everyone should have
fun and aim to win. I hope
everyone enjoys it.
Thank you very much for your support today.
Thank you very much.
Next, a message from Mr. Yago, president of Cover Co., Ltd.  It has
arrived. Yes, please take a look here.
Yes, please take a look. Live.
Thank you to all the movers for your hard work. This
is the representative of Ba Co., Ltd. It's a
sports day for everyone. Speaking of sports days, it
's group gymnastics. No group gymnastics.  It
's not in the program, so I'm
not going to prepare for today.Thank you
very much for your hard work.At
today's sports day, let's cooperate and encourage each other and
fight bravely until the end.Also, let's do our best
production as usual.
Thank you very much to everyone who supported me.
Thank you very much. I hope you will
pay attention to my hard work and support me by practicing until now.
No,
I can see where you're hurt.Channel
1, please, teacher.
Please do your best, please do your best. I like the slope. I'm the most
serious in the large-scale confusion section of Te-te-yochi, so
please make sure you don't get it wrong. Please. Please.
Yo, please.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.
Ha, that's good. I think I can do
it.Gyutsu.Ok, is it okay
if I ask you to be the player teacher?Is that
okay?Then,
please.Teacher,
all of us players, as Hololive members, will
take over sportsmanship and
use Dodo Fighting.Kaakae2023
November 4, 2017 Red Team Representative Toku and White Team Representative Ah Yellow
Representative Haspels
Ye
[Applause]
Thank you, it's okay to go home.
After Shining
Special So, everyone,
please move. Are you
moving?
This is just fine. Excuse me. The
white team
's dangerous voices are so loud.
But the White team's runaways are the contestants of each group.
Channel  Please go to the white group's contestant channel.The
sound quality of the sports day is so real, and
the feeling of them
climbing is so real.That's
right.I mean, this is like flannel or something.It's the
first game of Home Hunting.  I
wonder if it's only the people who enter the first round of hunting. I see, I see, I
see. I'm going to the white group's contestants' channel, so I'm going to go to the channel of the white group's competitors. Um, Ame-chan, Kaeranelisa. Please stay tuned and do your best.
Pre-
channel  Good luck,
good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck.
[Laughs] That
's it, that's the third person. Yes, that's right. That
's right, it's Kaela.
My body is so cool. [Music] It's me. All three of us made it.  Were we able to go? Is it
okay for us to be runaways or is this no good? What about that? I wonder if we're infected or not. The
white team is the hunters. The white team
looks like hunters, so we're like hunters,
cheering, cheering.  Are you going to go see it? Except for that meba, we
can all cheer for you. It doesn't have to be a fugitive, it's a fugitive. What group is this from
? I wonder if there will be an announcement about how many groups.  Will there be
any announcements?
Will there be any announcements? Will there be any? Will there be any? Will there be any? I wonder if there will be any. It will be
everyone except the hunter team or two,
so maybe we are not the same.
Since it is not the hunter team, is the hunter team
referring to the three hunters?  Or
do you mean the white group of Hunters? Point in either box and write "white" as if it's not us yet, "not red". Red, red. That means you can go to the other side with your own book. Hey, you can press it.
I can't do this, I can't
enter.
Yes, with the power of God, you don't
have to push anything. Yeah, it's okay
. Oh, sorry, I'll excuse Sado's announcement.
Kaiha-san, Roboko-
san, Nakia-san, Amaka-san, and Choko-san, I
asked for them on the White Technician Channel.  It's the other way around.
What happened to us? It's the other
way around. It's not because everyone is running away now. The
fugitives are on the move. Is it okay if the fugitives
give their compliments to the contestant channel?  It's
not the number, it's the same
place, it's the same place.
Chinne, so hello,
this is this, this is the same place. It's the
white group religion,
so the fugitives who ran away became this channel. So much so that it
seems like it's the opposite.
It's difficult.  It's difficult today.It's difficult today.It's difficult today.I
wanted to practice this.If it's the most difficult thing to do, it's like this is the best
practice.Have you practiced moving?
No, but once I get through this, I
can do it. I've got it all right now. Please
wait.
That means at first, red is the hunter, and the white group
all run away. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
everyone.  They're competitors,
right? That's
why our white group,
when we go hunting, we'll be split between the infected and the hunters, I
guess.
That's probably right.
[Music] It
seems like it's better than the hunter, right? Yeah, yeah.
In the end, which side is
this? The fleeing side, the
fleeing defender, and the fugitive are probably set automatically
.
For example, if someone from the red team is a hunter, and
someone from the white team is a hunter, we'll be targeted, so we'll
run away and click,
and then we'll be caught with a rope, and we'll be caught.  I
feel like I've lost all my strength and want to run away.
If I can get out, I'll get stuck in. I'll
go to Korea. I'll go to Korea, but I can't get out. So, surprisingly, the
back of the cage is a hiding place. Oh
yeah, a little bit.
No one is against it, but on the other hand, they're
going to the wide side opposite the cage,
so I have a hunch that there's no one behind the cage.I wonder if it's the same
behind here, too.I'm a little
concerned.  But that's okay, it's the next morning. I guess that's what the
staff is saying. I
'm watching the text channel, and there are
7 fugitives from the white group, so they're in the 2nd tier,
but I guess I should just leave.  That
's why I was wondering if it would be
better if both people went to the other side for the first and second hunting competitions.
But I'm still there. Even though that person
called me, I guess they didn't get the message across. It
seems like Raden-chan's part is good, isn't it? Yeah, I see. Yeah, yeah, I feel like it's something like that.  Maybe I'll
ask the announcer.Thank you
for this.Karen-
chan is here.That's right.He
was called earlier, but I think
NemadaRa-chan will be participating.  It
feels like it's going on by hand,
right? Yeah, yeah, yeah. So, only
people who aren't hunters really
need to be on this channel right now. I wonder if there
's something going on, but...  I have the
power of a god.I have the power of a god.I
have the power of a god.I am being spied on.
Now that I think about
it, I didn't hear about this type of flow this time.It seems like there's some confusion
about the way the competition is done, but I
guess they haven't done that flow.I don't
think there were any materials like that either.I'm
probably reading the materials now.  I'm pretty sure I'll be able to
join either of them, except for the contestants.It's
written there, except for the contestants from other teams.I'm so
excited,
but the staff is
inputting information.I'm coming back.  Katakata
Katakata I don't know, but today
everyone is going to have a long day, so it's scheduled to
be around 9 o'clock,
but
there's an atmosphere of not pushing, so I feel like I'm going to
have a little bit of a break.  I
'm saving my energy, but I'm hungry, so let's
go and eat. Let's take it easy. It's been a
long time, so I'm going to sleep. This
is the best part of the sports day. That's
right.  I do
n't know what to say.It's a real thrill.It's a real
thrill.It's a real thrill.It
's a book that gives you the answer.  It's real, real, thrill, real, thrill, it's
thrilling. It's
written in the first place, which is why it's in its current form. It's
a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book, it's a book twice, and
when it's time for the next challenge, the next three people are on the other side.  So,
ignore the diagonal part. It's
okay. There are 12 of us, not 7.
[Music]
34,899 people, 9 people.
That's
right. Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you.
Thank you.  Thank you, thank you, thank you, but 1st
game 1st game In the first game, if Red is first, everyone
will have to run away, but what do you think? Yes, certainly, certainly, yes,
certainly, what will happen? We'll
do it together, just on separate channels.
That's just the voice, suddenly it starts, suddenly it starts, it
suddenly runs away, it comes, it
comes, it's coming
English members
English, where are you?
Let's take care of the members and protect them.
Members Let's
protect it
Don't hide it, there's a dangerous Fauna in the back.Funa
Oooh, I won't protect you more and more.I ca
n't protect you anymore.I'm not an anti from behind the prison.Let's
protect it.Run away,
run away,
run away.It's
changing.10
No, I'm going to
squat down here, 149cm, and I'm going to make a little mistake. I'm
under 149. What
kind of person is this? I
don't think I'm the right person. I'm a squid, so I can fit in. There
's no way I'm 149cm.  No, I'm 149cm
tall. It's amazing.
On the other hand, the smaller person doesn't run away anymore. She doesn't seem
confident at all, but she's actually too strong.
Who are you protecting?
What are you doing? Why
is it that everyone is winning?
Chan-chan.
Catch me, I can go, I can go, someone can catch me, I
can go, chan-chan, I can go, you
can catch me
, yo, I
made a mistake, but stay here, I
got caught before, hey, someone can catch me too, yo, it's
over.  I was like, oh,
who was it
? It was definitely Anya who was different. There
was an awkward, awkward crackling sound. The
hunters were
asking for a favor. There were 6 of them,
so there were 6 of them.
Yes, that's true, then let's go. Come on,
let's go.
Wait a minute. Ta 6 is not here. Excuse me.
Everyone, White Team ABB,
please move to the original voice chat. I'm
so tired of losing it.
[Music]
Well, that's it. I guess I can go back.
Bye-bye-bye.
Bye
. OK. I guess this is like cheering. It's cheering. OK,
Kaela.  I wonder if Mr.
Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo,
it's been a long time since I've been here, so I guess I should just stay in the weak seat.  I've been
captured and I'm still captured. I
can't get out. I ca
n't get out. I can't get out.
It's a lie in Ruri. The game hasn't come out yet.
It's probably someone inside or something. A failed jailbreak. I have
n't been able to escape. I haven't been able to escape.  I can't,
I can't,
and it's South Korea.
Oh, and Kihara-chan
is also there. Well, I guess I can't come out until the next start. I wonder if it's
okay if I stay with Moneneka. Let's take a picture. It
's the country.
Thank you, Gokuno.  It's a prison where you can get your picture taken. Your
face is covered in grass. It's
nice. It's nice. It's
good. I'm
taking it right now. I
got it. Successful escape.
I escaped from prison. I finally got out. I finally got out.  It's
time for
Hunter to do his best. Let's support him. Let's support him. Let's support him. Let's support him. Let's support him. He's here.
It's South Korea. Thank you. He's a prison. He'll give it to
me, but he's
kind. I
feel like I want to show it to the listeners. This
is the best shot.  Eh, wait a minute,
I'll download it too.Wait a minute, where
is Korea?  It's Korea, it's crazy. You've
already escaped from prison. You've already escaped from prison. You've
successfully escaped. You've all
entered, you've entered.
We're all infected. It's infected. It's infected. It's so
wide.
InfectionActually, this infection seat was created by Goza,
but it seems
like it's really cool.However,
in the end, I want to think about it now, but there are only 6 people, but I'll
do my best to see it.It's
too wide for 1 person.There
's 1 block.  It's
really big here, it
's really spacious, but it's so spacious that you
can look out over it, and it's a really nice feeling.  It
seems interesting, but I
went to the dangerous yellow team that I made, and now I'm feeling
kind of fluffy.  It's
like I went to the war, I
see. I've done so many interviews that it makes me cry. It's
okay, Mu-chan, I'm just confused. It's okay, it's okay. I
thought it was funny.
Lose. What should I say? I'm laughing so hard.
It's okay.  It's going to be okay, it's going to be
okay, it's going to be
okay, I thought it was going to be okay, but from the way the speech bubbles are now, it's so
interesting that I said that it looked like I could talk about it.
Let's do it, my chest is walking around, let's
do it Let's
do it Let's do it
Shiro team chiro team Shiro team chihaku Team Shiro team Shiro
chim Oh white team pigeon
So that means we're not runaways either
Right yeah yeah yeah yeah  Degoza I
want to run away, I want to run away, I want to run away.Okay, you can
run away next time, so yeah, that's right.Please
wait for a moment until the next escape.Yes, be
polite until the next escape.Yes, behave well.Yes,
behave well.We're a
team.  That's right.Everyone was
beautiful, so white was lined up in the first place.Yes, they were
lined up beautifully, just like our color.Yeah,
like our color, white, it was clear and clear.  Clear is
clear, power is clear and white power is not.
Good luck, what's coming next? What's the theme? It's
debuted
in 2021-22, so it's pretty recent.
Lately, I can't get into the Rocks. I'm
barely getting into it. I wonder if it'll be until the 21st Rocks. Holo is up, but
Hololive is really running away.
English's 2nd and 3rd graders, etc.
English's 3rd term ID Soja ID
's 3rd term
Yes, I see. It's a little bit, it's the summer of 2020, is
n't it?
Come up with a name that's easy to understand.  Even if you look at it that way, it's hard to find
Yonechacha,
do your
best, try your best, Mouko Daiko-san's Hacha and Matsuri,
Yushishibua, if you were there, I
wanted to be a person who wanted to deepen.I feel like I'm being held.  I
feel like I'm being
chased. I'm not at all
prepared for it. I'm starting to get anxious. Is it
okay? Is it okay? It doesn't
matter. I can catch everyone, no matter what.
There's probably at least one Bob out there.
Short  Bob is just a casual touch, there are
hairstyles of different lengths, touch, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, where are you?  It's
nice,
nice, nice, this is all in one place. They're
planning a strategy. Miko thinks Holo
kids, no, it's
good, but she thinks Holo kids, no. They say it's good, but they're probably going to come in.
I'm sure I'm not a kid, Holo's mind.
It's true that
Anya has been arrested. It's true, Anya. It's a
scratch. It's not a scratch,
big sister.  But hey, that lucky
guy is curious. I'm curious about this one, but I wonder if he'll get into the slope. He's
not a bad guy. He's not a bad guy. No, he's
not a big girl with big boobs.
Maybe he'll fit in.  It's
okay to run away,
run away, that's right, run away, let's catch me and the
leader, catch them all, and
catch them all. Yes, let's catch them all.
If you can't figure out if you've put everyone in, just put them all in. It's
better, it's faster.  Dondon Tachi
Tachi
Tachi is quite slow, and the topic is interesting because of the changes.It
was difficult to do so.It's not a common understanding.It's interesting that so-and-so
failed at what I expected.I'm
sorry.Aki,
thank you for your explanation.  Maybe she's a kid,
but she was already in there.It's
true that something like that happens sometimes.It's bad luck.But
what would happen if it was a kid?I'm
sure she knew that.  I'm sure it
looks like it's going to fit in.I think it's kids.I think it
's probably Neki-ish.It was
n't Noki.It's been watched a lot.Hello, I
definitely want to know the answer.I
also want to know about Mio-senpai from earlier.Last.  Display the bar
and you'll be targeted no matter who you want. Neme-
senpai felt that way. She was locked on. That's
right. I
feel like Nerisa-chan is like that same person.  Oh no, I couldn't get that or that,
so I secured it.I'm
worried because there were 0 people.Was it
difficult?It
's okay, it's okay.It was
a little more difficult than the practice.No problem at all.  The
practice table is too easy,
so the leader and Chiara
will cover it, so it's okay, it's okay, I'm looking
forward to it.
Put in everything you find and
use your grip, please. Let's
move. It looks like it's moving. It's moving.
[Music]
Lo
wor
JAandlikeforforthe
shortcutdidONETRto
inforshortcutIcould
FindYeahbutThatShe
wasconsideredshort
butI
isShedefinitelyhas
shorthairIthink
Herknow
about defaultONE
Don't
do it, it's okay to be sad Yo no
prem
[Music]
Problem level
Nooblob Hey, look, look, look, look,
there are some pitiful people like this.  When I
open this door
and close it right away, I feel like I'm standing
in front of the closed door, and it's like this,
and I'm sleeping in.
There's a smell of earth.  It smells, it
smells
[Music] Is
it exercise?
Chacha, it's
dangerous, the contact is too close
. Hey, it was so cute lying side by side.
Yes, it was so cute.
Ah, this cute red book is
really cute. They
can sell cushions as they are. It's true that
this is really cute. It's really cute
that the head moves. The
head and meat handle has been synthesized.
Oh, yellow, yellow, yellow, yellow.
Just run away.  That
's right, let's run away, let's run away, we'll do our best, run away, run away, run away, run run run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run!  The
fugitive who touched on the tree is
trying to enter, but it's probably already entered. That's right.
It's a question of running away. Run away.
Run away.
2023 It's
not a joke.
Nice nice people were also caught.  I'm going to wander
around and make a mess of things Kanata
is fresh Most viewed It's
Kanata Let's go by Ah, it's him
.
Appeal
Give me a cigarette or something. You're bald.
[Music]
I'm a
Sasa woman.  What's that? That's amazing, 7 of you are saying that.
Hey, I'm here too. I'm here too. 460. Catch me. You've
completely ignored me.
There's no way I'm going to do that. Wait a minute.
Use it.
Safe. Hide it.
165. Hide it.  I'm in charge of hiding
it,
so I'm in charge of it. I'm
catching it. I'm trying to catch it with my head. I
'm
failing. There are so many people. No one
will catch me. They've caught me about 3 times,
but I'm worried.  I talked about it, but it was
n't clean. It's not neat, it's neat.
But I'm sorry for the person who was worried about me, but I'm not
neat. I'm not neat.
Even my screams are clean. So
what should I do?  But it's neat and clean. It's neat and clean. There
's a lot of dissatisfaction. There's a lot of dissatisfaction.
Nice, nice, they didn't catch it, they did
n't catch it. That's why they
ran away. But it's true,
Azusan.  I'm definitely going to be a member, I'm
definitely going to be in it, it was dangerous, it was
dangerous, it's so cute when you're a little self-aware, no, it's
cute, it's scary,
it's neat and clean.
You're so cute, Aiha-chan. You'll have to run away, too.
Even though you're so neat, I didn't think you'd get caught. The yellow was really strong. The yellow was
strong. You caught the yellow leper. Pesu
was terrible. This was one more time. Yes,
Captain.  It's not neat, you're running away one more time. You're
running away one more time. You've entered. Everyone did it. Round 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2.  I'm
going to go with my older sister. I don't care if I'm a sexy
woman or anything, I
wanted to be chosen. Please do
n't say that. It's true that my height wasn't
chosen at all. Oh yeah, but that
girl who misunderstood me is the one who misunderstood me, Polka.  I was
thinking that you misunderstood me. I
was able to get a little closer to the cage. Now, the
cage is really small. If
you're already caught, you
won't be able to escape during the game.  That's right,
the cat hunter is right
. I don't have to wait until the next game starts. Subaru-senpai who remains, I have to do my best
and escape. Then, next Mio-senpai is wrong. Who
will think that? Isn't Tamio the next one? Yes, that's
right
.  There's a possibility that something like that
might change, something completely different.
]
Hey,
my shoes, my shoes, my
shoes, my shoes, my shoes, they're all so tight.
Everyone, this place is definitely on a hill. It's a
little creepy because the slopes are about to overlap next to Xione Tepa.  They're
all buried, I
can't help but stare at how cute
they're standing side by side It's cute how cute they are lined up next to me Cute Hey, someone please line up next to me too Ah, the
reset reset is starting Oh, maybe we'll
do it one more time Let's do it again Oh yeah
Yeah.  Okay, oh,
ok, ok, ok,
ok, ok, oh, it doesn't matter at all.
But Subaru-senpai's nipples are gone. Yeah, I said it was a lie. But they went
out of their way to chat and Subaru-
senpai was like, how many nipples does he have?  I heard it in words.
Why are there two? Of course there are more than two.
No, birds are eggs,
so I can't get them like that. It's
become a specialty, but I'm
sad that it's a egg.  What's that? It's
2019. It's so bad. It's so bad. It's not included. Oh, who is this guy from 2019?
Who is that guy from 2019?
Everyone, run away! Run
away. It's the year of the year. It's a
shame. It's a shame.  It's a
shame that the ``Katememiro Dan'' and ``Dancho'' passed away in 2019.Non It's crazy, but even now, run away, run away, run away, run away, it was a frightening speed. Artists are gathering here. It seems like a collection of artists, and it's difficult.  I had the impression that more than 3 stations were
broadcasting quite a lot. It's definitely on the top left.
It's crazy.
[Music] The person
who was caught by the police was investigated. That's
right.
Who is he? He's been arrested, so look, he's been arrested.  That's how it happened. I've
been arrested. I haven't been arrested. No, I have
n't been arrested. I haven't been arrested. Surprisingly,
surprisingly,
[applause] I have
n't been arrested yet. I don't think I've been arrested
either.  It seemed like a lot
of things would happen, but I answered all the questions, but I ran away. No, that's amazing. Thank you for your
hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
Only the three hunters stayed here, and the rest
moved on.  Goodbye, good luck Baba Good luck
Baba Okay, no, no, no, no, no, it's
Korea, it's Korea, it's Korea, it's Korea,
it's Korea, it's
Korea  I do
n't know where you're looking, but I'm
giving it to people who are in captivity.I'm
getting used to it.I'm going to put this
out.It's okay to give it here and there.The
teacher gave me this
shot all over Korea.  It's
so surreal, but
this Noel-senpai has a great ID photo feeling, so
I get it.
It's a shot of him winning so much and taking the camera so much. I want him to do his
best in the second match. Good luck, Naga. Let's
go to the cheering seats.
Cheers. Good luck, wait.  Wait, I made a mistake in collecting the medicine.Wait
a minute.The mouse is
soaked.Why are you pointing at me
just now?I made a mistake.It's
terrible.The mouse has become beautiful.Live your
life.It's
dangerous.Now, pat it.  I was
stroking that, I was stroking that, I was stroking that, and then I
got hit.
Hey
, oh, you're
cute. You're looking down. You're looking down. Wait, you're
cute. Oh, you're moving. That's moving.  Oh, it moved.
It's so cute. It's so cute. It's so cute. I
wonder if Grass-Glass-chan will show up. Are you sure it's okay? Stay here, it's true. When I
woke up, I was a contestant. Maybe that's true.
No, I ran away.  It was
written that I'm currently entering the book, so I'm probably going to be taken away. This is the one that
disappears, do your best,
do your best. A
scuffle with gray hair has begun. It's a cute book. I didn't
realize that. Did the
one with the Subaru statue get taken away?
YouTube  Was it a
target? I just took it.
[Music] I'm going to
clean up my hands.
It's coming. I wonder if it's going to start. Something,
something.
There must be a lot of people.
Everyone
[Music]  [Music] It's
not the first time I caught it. That's fine. I put it in. I put it
in. No, it's wrong. It's
expensive. Toa-senpai is hiding here.
Toa-senpai is hiding here, but Toa-
senpai is.  It's probably about the same size as the one. I
thought I was hiding in a corner. It's
unexpectedly different. I'm really failing.
Sui-chan sold it. Yes, Asu-chan looks expensive. It
sure looks expensive, but it's
okay now.  It's finally, it's finally, it's
early, it's already 3 people have been arrested. Catch
the bastards. It's easy to understand. It's too
early. It's too early. Okay,
Yomoko-san. Whoever is being arrested is Mimi Abe-chan. I
can't see her name. It's
Naekari-chan.  You're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall, you're tall.  I wonder if it's
that or which one.I'm
sure it's that, that's it, that's
it, that's it.
No, it's
dangerous, catch everyone, there are quite a lot of them.That's right, there are a
lot of blurry judgments.He
looks good, he feels good, he
has a good title.He's got a good title, he's finally getting in.He's
catching a lot of people.He's really
catching him!  Those senpai are also stupid.
No, 11 people are not great.
All of them.
Meruru is definitely not like that.
No, Mel-chan is the only one who is stupid. Meru, the
senior is really hidden. Mercury is on the right side.
Senpai is different, no, no, right here.  I'm here, I
'm in the red, do your best, no, but you're so, so, so
nice, so nice, so nice, so nice, you
're such a cow. That's the best record. There
's a best record. It might be the best record. I've been
really beaten into it.
It's amazing. Next time I'll run away.
Okay, okay, nice, ah, nice, ah, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, please
disappear.
This is a really good photo,
isn't it? It's really, really, really good. The one I just
took is really nice. Let's get along well. I'll
send this to Subaru. This is really good. It's
Subaru. This is too good. Kaari
was really depressed. Everyone, let's
go home.  I put a lot of effort into it, and it
was really good.The beasts were
really hard to catch.At the end, they caught a lot of them, and it was scary.At the end,
most of them were blurred.I could have put in most of them.Bobo's
floating fa was amazing.Yasoke's
ears are surprisingly few,
though.  I don't have the impression that Bame-senpai has furry ears, which is a bit
shocking.This seems to
be the case, I guess.They all play the role
of "blurred" and don't get too much attention.Maybe that's why they're so dumb.Aaah,
maybe that blur is unpleasant, but it's
Mio-senpai's judgment.  There must be a lot of stupid people out there, so don't ask me if you'd
like. That's right, Mio-chan, Kamio-chan, but Mirando.
Mirando was actually a bonus stage in a sense. I'm
sure you've managed to get away with it.  If you
give me help, I'll run away, I'll run away, I'll do my
best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll run away, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best.
Ranran, after all, it was a little hard to catch them when they were all gathered in a place. Oh my god,
hide it, hide it, it's dangerous! Hide it, hide it, hide it, don't hide it, Chandoko,
Senpai.  Well, someone has been arrested.Ayyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy?
Wait, you've been caught, you've been
caught. It's okay, you've been caught. You've been caught, you've
been caught. You've been caught, you've been caught. You've been
worried about it. You're
so poor, you're hiding it, you're blonde, you're blonde, and your
color is too early.  No, ha, it's
okay, I'll protect you, Wow, it
's true, my baby is blond and blond. It's a little too
bad. Ah, it's a little the same.
Sorry, sorry,
sorry. It's the same. It's the same. I wish I could, but wow. It's a shame I have so much free time. I have so much free time.  I have free time this time, it's dangerous, I don't like it,
but my name is sexy. You can grab me for a little while, but it's ok to
get here, one chan, one chan.
I'm sexy, but I'm not sexy.  I'm
completely
ignoring you, why didn't you do anything? Matsuri-senpai Festival-senpai
Festival-senpai Festival-
senpai I'm here. It's not my seniors. That's
not
true. But Chancha-chan is
here too. I didn't
do anything. I didn't.
Nice, nice, anyway, there
were 14 people, 13 people, 13. That was
dangerous.  It's
dangerous
Tat
Tat I really want to be a little surprised I
can hide behind you Tami
White
Explanation The
person being explained to me is disappointed
Chim, are you going to go back? Oh, okay, it's so
high up here.  It's
been moved
. I see. It's amazing. It's
true. It's true now. Okay, okay.
Oh, oh,
next time, Lomen hunting is
over. Are you going to tell me the results now? That's
definitely a point.  Well, how many points do you
get? At the beginning of the sports day, he told me, but he
couldn't tell me anything during the middle, so I watched it at the end. Yes,
yes, yes, that's right. It's the road, but that's the way it is. I wonder
what will happen
next. [Music] I'm sure.  I wonder if it's a follow-up.
Stop the floor-up, stop it. I'm
hungry, so I'm okay, but the head is in trouble. It's going to turn into a problem,
so I stopped practicing.
Yeah, today too. Yesterday was really good, so it's
okay. I practiced with that opponent a lot.
But yeah, I bought a lot of them.It's really
good for practice, but in
real life, the actual performance might be different.
Mercury-senpai and Biji-chan are really good
at it, and the first match is really dangerous and dangerous,
and it's Roboko-san.Oh yeah, but it's Roboko-chan.I
tried to teach her earlier, but she got better pretty quickly, but I think she started practicing today.  It's so good that I want you to do your
best. It's a beginner's luck, so I can
do it. I can
do things like Ikiranana and Passion Passion. It's
really scary. B and the white group are now
2 and it's really good. Nice, nice, nice.
Tao
Follow.  I've received a notification for the upload.Yes,
yes, yes, there are 6 contestants, 2 each,
please move to the voice chat. Do your best. Do you
want to
go up? Do you want to go up? I see. I see. Venue: E-up, Necha-down.
Well, I guess I should go to the one with that voice, or the one with that
voice, or the one with that voice.The voice is the voice, so Chiara is on the move.Yeah, Kiara-chan, it's her second match.I wonder if she's okay.I have another interview.Okay, then I
'll go.  Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
No, it doesn't seem like a big deal, haha.
When I look down, everyone pays attention to me. It's a
war, and it's hard for people with war phobia, but it's amazing. It's
really brave, isn't it? It's amazing, but I've
been practicing so much, so it
's true.  Yeah, here's a little bit of a record.
Even if it's worse than practice, that's not it
at all. It's a nice fight. Yeah, yeah,
first of all, it's because what you can do is amazing. Yeah, yeah, I'm really excited. I'm really
excited. What's going to happen?  I've
done it before in practice,
but I didn't do it in the end, and I only touched on it for a moment,
but it was really difficult. I have to
figure out where the next scaffold is and then
decide to jump there.
And then I let go of that Triden,
and it seems like the flying distance is even longer.Oh, it's
pretty technical, right?That's
right.It's probably the most difficult of today's competitions.It's
certainly the most difficult.Maybe
last year, maybe last year.  That
's what happened with the human one.It's difficult, but it's more interesting than that.It's a moment of hard work.Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a moment of great victory or defeat, so it's true in a sense.
As soon as I do it, it's over, whether it's good or bad, it
feels like it's over, but this is 300 seconds,
so I'm going to finish it 5 minutes and 5 minutes, 5
minutes and 5 minutes I wonder if I can last 5 minutes and 5 minutes
Ah, how did this end?  Well, I
feel like it would be better for Sui-chan to be cheering for me, because she didn't support me.Yesterday, it
was like that at practice, so I guess that's what happened in the end.I wonder if she'll
come back to the team,
but she's parted ways with the contestants.  I'm
sure it's confusing, A's Bo-senpai, but in my heart I
can't see the top anymore
. I can't help but look up at Roboko-san and
Chiara-chan's Isamu from here.
It's 200m, right?
200m,
200m, I can't imagine it. I'm fidgety, fidgety, really
fidgety
. But this is it for Chiara-chan. If Chiara-chan,
Roboco-senpai, gets a good score,
Choco-sensei will give her something good
because I believe that.  I'm going to make a hamburger
or a tiara from Japan. Yes, I'm from Japan. I'll
make a hamburger. I'll make a hamburger. I'd
like to eat stuffed peppers with meat.
Aineine's
meat. I'm getting hungry.
That's right.  I
can't help it, I don't know if I'll make it or if the person who makes it will
go or not, but I just want to go to the launch regardless of whether I win or not.  Now
that I'm a member, I'm sure it's true that we're starting the White Group.I'm going to make a
reservation at a restaurant.I don't care what type of restaurant you want, but it's definitely
not meat.The
repertoire was full of meat, so it was meat.It
was hamburger fillet cutlet.
Ena Yakiniku, shabu-shabu type hot pot, etc.
Ah, nice, hot pot, nice hot pot, nice. It's cold, and it's
getting colder. Nede-chan will come, but wo
n't the other cats come? I wonder if they won't come for a while. Well, that's
right. Lots of things.  I
don't know if it's the right time, but I should just go out to eat every time I come. I think I can go there, Chico. [Laughs] Yeah, I'm sure something will come and go, but I don't think so. Only those who can go should go ahead and
grab the restaurant first.  You
can add more flowers later, so I see. Oh, it looks
like it's going to be a year-end party. I'm
sure it's okay if I
leave these seeds with you and bring some amazing flowers with you. If you
're there, I'll
go.
Well, that's a lot of time, isn't it
? Every single competition that you've entered has gimmicks and interviews, so everyone is probably enthusiastic and talking about it passionately. Well, I'm sure there will be plenty of people to participate in it.
Yeah, there's going to be a bunch of people with a lot of energy,
so wait.
And this means that it's the second strongest time, so yeah, it's definitely
past 9 o'clock. I
have a feeling that there's definitely some marks left. What
happens after this is a little off.  It
might have been that, but after the wood line and the fang line, there was
Hinanka Hime and so on, and after that there was
Spring and Summer Shi and Rire Yes Yes Yes Yes, that's the end,
so I
think there must have been 5 events.  I don't think I'll be able to do it even with Tsutsue. It's true that there's
only one opening call, so
maybe that's it. That's right, so there's only one replay. So there
are only two of these, so yeah, I
feel like I can go.  The crease lines are like
that 3 It's like I'm going to do that 3 times I'm going to do that
3 times I wonder
how long it will take for that to happen I'm sure it's the beginning Go for it, do your
best, go back It's going to start, start,
start cheer  Do your best, doko-san,
do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best,
do your best,
robo-ko, you're a woman who can fly, you're really
good at biji-chan,
but you get anxious about whether you're good or not.When you're surrounded by good people, there's
definitely no pressure.
Well, let's do our best, O-san, we're doing our best. With this, if you
go all the way to 200m, you'll
get points, right
? I guess it's just that,
or something like that. Points are determined by the last 1 or 1. It's
been 5 minutes, so let's go first.  It's not like if
everyone reaches 200m, they all have the same
points, right? Well,
if you're within that time, you'll reach the final point. Yeah, yeah, yeah, so
if you
aim for 200m, you'll have to fight against yourself.  It's
okay to do your best, but it's
halfway, it's going well.  It's because I'm good at games, my skills are high.Yo,
I'm so good, Loco is so good.I feel so
good and all sorts of things.I
guess I'm used to things like this because I participate in competitions and tournaments.I'm not
at all nervous about being noticed.  It's so hot, it's
so hot, it's going up. It's amazing.
Oh, you can do your best. You can
do your best. Fourth
checkpoint. Oh nice, nice, good. Yummy. There
's still about 3 minutes left. It's
so fast. Oh, B-chan, you're fast.
Like, Roboko hasn't fallen since the 4th one
. It's amazing. Yeah, I'm calm. I'm
definitely getting more and more
excited. I'm definitely getting more and more excited. Hey,
okay. Let's do our
best. Just a little more. We can
go 30 meters. We can go. We
can go.  Do your best, Roboco, you'll have a Jet with you.
13 is normal.
Even if you fall, you'll be able to wrap it up from the checkpoint.
So,
calm down, 10 meters to go, 10 meters to go, 6 meters to go. Oh wow.
Do your best,
try your best, do your best! Nice goal. You're too nice. Sei-chan is trying her
best too. She has a little more to go. It
's almost 200
at the end. Sui-chan, Asui-chan, no. There's
still 90 seconds left. There's still more than a minute left.
Even though Sui-chan is good at giving herself a chance, there's
always pressure in the actual
performance.It's always the pressure, it's her turn to do her best,
so she's not giving up, and she's irregular.The purpose of the game
changes, but everyone still cheers her on.
Yes, I don't want to,
but you said it's a battle with yourself, but it's a 200m
battle, so yeah, that's right, the points are
all equal.  I'm
drinking water, I'm drinking water, I
'm looking up, but I
don't understand anything. It's too expensive. What can I do? I
want an elevator. Yeah, everyone is 200
meters away. It's crackling. It's crackling. It's
crackling. It feels good. No, but this is the
other way around.  There's going to be a lot of pressure on the people on the level. Let's
do our best, do our best, 39 seconds. That's pretty good. It's
hot, right? We're going to climb in 39 seconds. I'm looking
forward
to the second race. Good
luck,
Mr. Choco, do your best to climb.  It's a
place where you can see it from above. It's
nice. Here, here, here.
Seriously, it's pretty good here. I'm a little closer. [Music] It's good here. From now on, I'm going to push it a little. It's warm. It's good. It's true. You can see it here a little.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah.  You'll see or see, it's cute
[Music]
It's like, second round, second round, Chiara
, Chiara,
Chiara. If you touch the perfect sign, it'll be
okay. It looks like you're going to get it. Let me know in the comments. It's a
lie, isn't it?  Is this an infected person? Is this
okay? Where is the right one? Entry
on the far right.
Everyone was doing this,
so there weren't that many people.
Entries. List, something. The one on the far right of the four signs on the left. Over
here, over here.  It's true, I'm going to
take it. How can I get it to float? How can I get it to float? How did I get that kick normally? It
turned into a severed head.
Where's Tiara-chan? Hey, Tiara, you're
climbing smoothly. I'm scared.
Around me.  But I
guess the contestants can't see it. If they could see it, they'd
never be able to climb it.
What's that? What's this poop-looking thing?
It's like soft-serve ice cream.
Soft-serve ice cream Oh, soft-serve ice cream Oh, no, it
looks like it's going really well. Wow, wait, wait, I've lost track of the characters.
Tiara is the fastest right now. The
checkpoint is coming, it's sparkly,
oh, nice. The second check is quick.
Wow, I'm just taking precautions.
[Music]
Hey, y'all, y'all,
y'all, Wow, the effect when something goes up is
so cool.
Wow, it's so fast, everyone.
[Music] Oh, we're
almost half way here. It's so fast, it's so fast. There's only one more time left.  I'm
not falling, it's amazing, it's amazing, but it's like, step by step, I'm
definitely going all at once. I'm
glad to know that I can do this,
thank you, thank you. It's
totally
different from the three of us just looking up at the sky.  Seriously,
no, this is so funny,
it's too fast. I went up and it turned out like this. It's going smoothly, I went up. I did
n't know, I did
n't know, I didn't know, this was a spiral field.  It's
placed here. If you make a mistake, it'll fly
away all at once. It's
true that the colored blocks are from there. It's really
different depending on where you go. There are also quite a
few shortcuts. But it's
poisonous and tense.
Here, oh!  Hey, just a little more, here's the ball. I'm
going carefully
with Katene-chan. Oh wow, so nice. Can't you see us?
That's right. I'm drifting right now. I'm
drifting, but everyone's floating.
Everyone's face is
amazing, Geara-chan.  No
mistakes, no mistakes. I haven't fallen even once. It's
amazing crackling.
This means it's the final spot.
Yeah, what if there was a scuffle here and I got dropped
? I wonder if that was expected.  I wonder
what it is, but in the end, it's
the distance we were at in the final seconds,
right? I guess it's better than
giving in and
giving in for 70 seconds, rather than both of us falling.
I'm worried about you, Saka, you're doing your best.
Do your best, 50 seconds left.
Ah, do your best to like it. [Music] There's so much going on. Do your best. Don't give up. Ah, there's only
30 seconds left. Do your best, both of you.
[Music] Yeah, oh.  It's
coming, it's coming, it's coming. Are you both
going up together? Do your
best to capture it. Do
your best. You have 7 seconds left.
[Music]
Oh, Ruo.
Tomorrow was
amazing. We didn't make any mistakes. We were almost there. Hey, let's do our best.  It's going down, I was surprised. It
fell all of a sudden with a crackle. No
, it was
amazing, it was amazing, it was amazing. It
's nice. Nice, nice, nice. Chiara: Yeah, and the next one is Kiba line, or Kira line. Yeah, the Kiba line is going to break. It looks like it's going to be busy, isn't it?
There are some pairs like A and B that are already together, and yes, that's right, that's
right, everyone on the competition channel. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, let's do
our best, leader. That's right, I
want the group and Chico-sensei to notice, right? Choco, it's
stuck in that teacher's ass.  It
's a bit of a little that's a little bit. I'm doing my best. I'm
doing my best 3 times.  Now that the number 1
point has come out, I'm probably number 1.
I wonder if I can catch up with him whether I go or not. That's a nice fight. That's nice. That was amazing. He has
n't come back yet. He's back. He's still home. Are you still
in the middle of an interview?
No, it's not like that yet. Our
white team is the only one who is properly eavesdropping. They
're going to go all the way to the cat. I'm going to go to the mountain, I'm going to
go to the mountain, I'm going to interview the mountain.  Wow, that's it! It
was a high level game. Hey, no mistakes. That
was amazing. Hey, he didn't make any mistakes. That was amazing. Nice.
Nice. The White team is currently in first place. It's a
very close battle, but White has 40, Yellow has 38, and Red has 37. Nice, nice, nice.
4 points yellow 38 re 37 strong Let's
go let's go, it's
nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice. It's dangerous
if it comes down to the princess and the dangerous princess.
No, that's what it means, isn't it? It looks like it's going to be a rip-off.
Yes, I'll protect the general with my fangs.  Well, yes,
there are still many things to
do. Well, I have to do my best. The
pressure is slowly coming on. I don't know if I'm planning to do something,
but I don't like it. It's starting to
put pressure on me.  That's
right. I teamed up with Ramen-chan this time, so I
guess I don't know what will happen yet.
Thank you for your hard work. I'm
looking at you, Mom.
Okay, so here
's the interim announcement of the general spec. Click
here for the overall profit.
Okay, so 1st
place is 40, and that kind of money is quite a bit even just now.Yellow
is 63 points, white is 60 points, which
is 3 points.3
Now, let's move to the venue for the next competition line.Let's
jump from the turn and announce it.
What was the score?
White
was in 2nd place overall, with a
difference of 3 points.
3 Yellow was 63 and White was 6.  Kiara-
chan,
that's nice. Thank you very much. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game.
I'm going to
ride, I'm going to ride, I
'm going to ride, I'm going to ride, I'm going to
ride, I'm going to be the first one.  The
music was so loud, the orchestra was so nice
and nice at first, it was cute, it was cute, it was serious, and this was it. It's
okay to ride on top of
someone.  Ah, if
you hold it and hold it, the general is probably the general.The general
is probably on top.The general is on top, so it
's the side that will be clicked.Don't enter.Okay,
if you have already entered,
cancel, enter, and touch again.
Bao, I've
become a general when I get back.Will that
person from this one come?
Will that person from my pair come?Is that
person there?I wonder if he or she will come.The
other pair is from this one.  Minori Wander
Wander It's
better to have something ready and I want to eat it I
want some onigiri in the container I want to
eat I'm hungry I want to mumble I'm
hungry I want to
mumble I'd
like to release the general, Kara-chan Kara-chan
Oh, it's
okay, youknow
how, beagressive,
OKGbeagoodhorsey,
okuryoubetter
be
Where are you, Mr. Gae?  Is it
okay? Is it
okay? How do you stop it? Just
press the same button again in the book.
Nice, nice, nice,
nice.
Oh, let's
mumble. What?
Wait a minute and
ask if you went there dressed like that.
Come in a suit.  It looks strong. I
made a suit. It
looks amazing. It looks strong.
It's better to look strong. It looks too strong. It's okay. I
won't charge you a huge amount of money later. It's okay. It might
be possible.
Thank you very much, Senpai.  Thank you, you're strong, you look strong.I
rode it.I rode it.I rode it.I
rode it.I rode it.I rode it.It's amazing.That
means Okayu-senpai will be helping me as a pinch hitter.Thank
you very much.Thank you for your support.Aoka-
senpai is here.  Thank you for giving me a
ride. He got on
top of me. He got on top of me. He
got on top of me. I'll ask him to sit on the chair for a while. Okay,
leave it to me.
Thank you. I'm happy.  It's a fluffy
dog ​​that I can ride on my ear. It's stuck in my fluffy butt. It's
got a corner of a chocolate wire stuck in it. That's right, it's
the leader. It's a horn. The
horn hurts. I
don't like it. It should be a little bit irritating. I don't like it.  I
feel like it's quite stimulating, so
if you say so, Mio-chan might be quite stimulating as well.
This is a senpai's horn that
's stimulating. He's a painful person.
Hello, thank you very much for your support. Also, I'm
going to let you participate.  I'm
afraid you're going to leave me because you've become a suspicious person.That's
okay.I guess I
just learned how to do it.I
want to lead you to victory.Oh, you're
so cool.
Let's do our best. I'll do everyone in the White Gumi. I'll
do my best. I'm stubborn.
What's your strategy? What's going on with the white team
? Well, if you get the best kill
, you'll get 1 point added.
That's right. I'll probably protect the
enemy and focus the attack on the opponent.  It
seems like it would be a good idea if we all just wake up the
people who are approaching that general.If it's your type, it's better to stay close to the general, but I
guess it's okay to keep coming closer to him.It seems like he's definitely weak.He's kind of weak.  I
want to beat up people.I can see the hearts, so I
might want to avoid people with 3 hearts.Inversely,
at the beginning, stay close to the general and when you see 1 heart,
attack.  I
think it's going to be a voice chat, so there's a lot of voices.
Well, I
think there's probably a name at the bottom, so now that I think about it, it's true. I hear there's Kanata porridge.
Collaboration with Minato.
That's why we can't work together. We can't say that the general protects and protects us. That's right. Let's
do our best to protect the general. We'll do our best. It's
true. We're both being targeted. The
one who covered Terutsu.
Looks like I'm not good at it.When I found it, I
felt like I was being kidnapped.So I
think I'll probably have to move from here.Everyone should move.Then I'd better
go.Orego Let's go.Okay,
please.  Please, please, for now, we're
going to protect our backs, but I don't know what it's going to be like.The
audience, maybe in the first place, we're not going to turn our backs to that thing,
or rather, we're going to keep our backs to that side, and
not that side of the venue.  He
might be facing the outside for a long time, so when I thought about it, I
thought maybe it would be better if he was in a different camp, but if the
spectators moved, I'd have to
protect him.That's how I decided to
draw a heart.  If I find one, I'll rush in.
But I'll ask you to take a look at the leader's heart.
At that time, you won't be able to see the leader's heart. If you
say Okay, 2 or 1, then I'll just call it quits. For now.  I'll
run away, okay,
okay. Let's
set a goal for 3 times. I got 23 kills. Yesterday
's maximum was 3 kills. To be honest, I
haven't lost in practice, so I
thought I'd cut it.  But 5 days is a high goal. It's
better to have a goal of less than 5. That's
right. That's right, I'm going to try to target Amikochi as well. I have a
feeling it will start in a little while. It's
almost over.  It's right here in the frame, right? The
white one, right, inside the white frame. This guy in the middle is probably going to
disappear once that start starts. Okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, this is really evil. This guy is getting in the way, I
thought. Yes, it probably disappeared, just like yesterday.  I feel like that's what it was like,
so I'm okay with it. It's okay. Well, it's the devil and Teshi, so they're the
strongest pair. They're the strongest. There's a lot of things going on
in the game. It's amazing how there's a demon knight in the game.  A
big one is
coming, and I'm sure it's the
strongest,
so let's see if I can attack it once.I
still don't have a sword, so all I have is a book, so yeah, that's right,
how many people still don't know the name?  I guess you
can do it if you get close to it.
How about this? Everyone should practice,
but yeah, it's a sword anyway, so it's
important to swing each one over and over again. It's important to make sure you hit them repeatedly.
Okay, anytime.  The orchestra started and the orchestra started. There were
various tournaments, so I guess they were preparing for it. Oh, it's
changed. I was
surprised. It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Now, for a
moment, I thought I had teleported, but it was just moving in a straight line so
quickly.
Okay,
okay, okay, Okay,
Choco-sensei is in first person. Minecraft
is in other than first person. It's actually F5.
There are various things after F5. That
's true. Yes, it's true.
It's this game. There was no particular point of view
specified.  It's not happening, so if that's the case
, then you can definitely see better this way, so it's
okay. Yeah, yeah, okay,
okay, there you are. Okay, I'm wondering what you're following me, but I'm
having a bit of practice following you. That's
helpful.  That's really helpful.
[Music]
Okay, but I'm a bit older than that, so it
's okay, but if you
get sick, don't worry about it. If you get drunk easily, don't push yourself too
hard. It's okay. I've never gotten drunk while playing a chocolate game, and I'm really not that strong. Yeah,
in a game that lasts half a period, it's fine.  I don't
think so. On the contrary, I don't get drunk in cars at all. Yeah, that's right. I don't really feel like I get drunk when it comes to vehicles. I can even fall asleep on a bus or something like that. It's easy to say that it's amazing, so I
want that feeling.  There are so many things I want to do.
Even if I take a basic night bus, I'll fall asleep. It's
better to sleep, but it's true that both men and women get drunk, so I
spend my time sleeping and doing things like
that. It's amazing.
It doesn't sound like yes, hmm, yeah, yeah, yeah, wait, it's about to start, it's starting, it's going, it's going, it's starting, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's starting, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going to be the one who has few hearts.  It's okay, or it's bad,
but you might get surrounded, so it's definitely true.
Even if you go one more time, Da-jung is also one. Well, it's
dangerous, but you
have to go anyway. If you don't attack that, it's definitely true.
Even if you die, go.  Before this, let's
go, let's go, you're two, go,
go,
let's go, okay,
nice,
nice, nice, nice, nice.  Senpai So Senpai can you
go ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo can
go to!  It's nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, good, good, good, good, good, good
, 3 kills, but red is strong, 5 kills, 6 kills
, Wow, it's really good.
There are two lines,
yeah, so there's still one, so it's not at all
[Music] I can
make it back, wow, wow,
even if everyone around here, Heart 1 members,
attack right now, it won't hit.
It's true, but it
was just barely.  It's 11 and I'm the last one to
survive. Yeah, it felt good. I'm becoming a general.
Hmm, what's this? I don't know what TT is. Yeah, I don't know what T is. I don't know, I
hit TT.  I'll
leave it at that for the time being.I don't know anything.I don't know.I don't know.What is T?Who said T?It's Ani-chan who said
T.Alright, I'll enter again.  I'll take it,
but please wait a moment. Wow.
There's a huge crowd of people. The
foil in front of the White Chico signboard. Oh, it's
helpful. It's easy to understand. I'm on board. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. That's what I said earlier. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. .  But
okay, I'm not saying I'm going to attack, but
I'm in the middle, and I'm getting beaten up by the five of them,
so I guess I'll just have to go fishing.
Alright, alright,
alright
[Music]
Yeah, it's kind of unique and nice that it's on my head.
It's a strange feeling when I watch it on F5F5.
Oh, the weather is nice today too. Seriously, no, seriously, it's
better than the day of the sports day. Good
sun.  The sun never sets, so it's definitely good to exercise, is
n't it? It's
good, isn't it? It's amazing. What's that? What's with all the banging? It's
just the different teams fighting.
But I'm not
satisfied with the fact that I'm so angry. My boss told me to
get along. So, that's true, but I don't want to lose that
important thing. Even if I do
n't like it, Subaru is next to me. Nowadays.  No, that's
it, Chiba-chan and Neka, but if you defeat them, you'll get a lot of
points, so you'll certainly have to do your best to defeat them. Shall we go? Let's
go, let's go, let's go from the yellow.
Yeah, go around the back. Sora.
Senpai has 1 heart. It's dangerous. You might be targeted.
Even if the one who dies once runs away from the ball,
that too will turn right in front of me. Nice,
nice, nice. I can still go.
Heart to heart. Heart to heart. I can
go to heart.  Yes, there's
only
one more left. Yes, I'm
going to Ocho.
Nice, nice, nice, heart 1, right
in front of me. Can I
go, Sora-senpai? I couldn't
go, nice. This is my heart. Can I go? Can I go?  Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, you're nice, Subaru, nice, nice,
oh, who are you?
That's great, it feels good, it feels good, it feels good, no, I'm accomplishing my goals properly.
What should I do next? I feel good now. I
feel good. I
feel good. I'm sure you're a genius. I
hope you'll do the same thing next time.
But this is really difficult.However, the
number of kills I've had is higher than the number of kills I've had, so I'm
sure I'll kill them with my current strategy,
and I'll end up with 7 kills.  I
said, ``Let's aim for it.'' I said, ``Okay, I'll cut it.''
But no, it's true that I'm already at the 1st place level. No, I
can go,
I can go. Okay, but I feel like I'll be able to go if it's Chicoset,
so I
headed to Kigumi first.  I'm starting to feel like it's better. Yeah, yeah,
maybe. Red is better.
Amata
T. I'm selling the mysterious
Titi again. Is this the one? Okay. I
'm in the same place as before. Yes, that's helpful. Okay. Nice. I
got up on top.
[Music]  ]
Okay, Nice
[Music]
Nice, Okay,
well, let's just kill again.
Sho yoshi shioshi yoshi
[Music] Oh demo
daisho Yeah taisho.
No point, but da general. I want to kill the general. I also want to kill the general. I have a
lot of hearts, so if I see something like 1 or 2.  It
was a
good thing that Nesakki nemikochi was attacked that way.I think I was able to make two cuts there and include other people.That's
right, so surprisingly I got
hit too, but I guess the general's heart was affected.
When I was little, everyone was looking at only the general,
so I got a good feeling. Let's
go from the back.
Well, let's have some fun. Hey, I'm a
little happy. I'll kill a lot of people,
and White will erase everything.
Even though your lives are angels.  You're
saying something, you're
saying something more amazing than the devil, but did you
stop fighting? Are you going
to do it again? Yeah, let's do
it one more time.
Yeah, it's
always
good.
[Music]
Well, if that happens, there will be white angels, devils, and knights. They'll be
really strong, no, they'll be strong. All they have
to do is give a strong blow. Even the samurai will be gone. We'll go for the promised victory.  I'm the
strongest that can go, I'm the strongest
. I'm so nervous. Ah, I'm here. Let's go. Let's go. Let's do our best. Let's go. Let's
go.
3221 Go
ahead.  He
says he's going to cut someone's heart away, and he's going to cut someone's heart, and he's
cutting it, and he's cutting it, and he's
cutting it, and he's cutting it all the time, and hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, it's
okay, okay, okay, if the general gets hit, then
oh, nice, nice, this is a star, a star, a pigeon.  I
want to go, ally, ally, this, ally, this, around here, okay, okay, okay, okay, I lost, but it's okay, nice, nice.  I'm
trying my best, I'm trying hard, but I'm being targeted from behind.Aiyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy owed Meyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy with my back with me with a target on my back?
Well, well, well, well, well, well, leave it as it is. Well, I
said, 4 kills, 44 kills, well, well,
and it was 41,
because I defeated the great general. Oh, that's nice, nice, nice,
good, good, good,
good, good, good.  Isn't
it amazing? It's like at the very end, it's really high, and I'm getting a lot of points. There's a lot of difference in the total, but red was really strong. It's the first round and the second round, right? So what will happen?  It's a
mess [
Music] Oisho, what's going to happen with this? This is it, right? Oh, it looks like we're going to do an interview now. Oh, I want to do it again. This is fun, fun [Music]
Oh, no, nice, nice
Um, it
says go to A.  Let's go to White Team A
White
Yes,
Oh, thank you for your hard work, you
look so tired.
Ame-chan also got 10 kills, that's amazing.
Foreigners' kill machines and kill machines. It's
better, it was amazing, everyone was scared. Wow, you woke up at the end, that was amazing.
Nice. This is nothing amazing. You've
made a comeback. You've had a lot of success.  I'm
surprised that 41 also included targeted kills.
41 We did it. We did it too. We
did the wrong thing. It's nice.
Kills are big, so yeah, I'm sorry. Nice.
1 kill. Nice kill. If that 1 kill
hadn't happened.  It's 40 years old, right. That's
right, important, important. Nice,
nice,
Nice-chan is very strong and very strong. It
's amazing.
Roboko-san's pair was also amazing. Nice. Nice,
super sleepy. I got 3 kills at the end.
Good job everyone, stop it.  That
's amazing.
That's amazing. Nice, nice, amazing. I
wonder what's going on with this. I'm quite curious. That's not good. I'm pretty good. I wonder if I
've gone that far. I think I've come a long way,
but I
feel like I'm making a comeback.  In the second match, I
was ranked 2nd, or 2nd, or something like 22nd,
so I didn't have much luck in the first round. Red was
strong as well, so it doesn't matter. I don't know if it
was strong or not, but
what will happen? I'm scared of the dangerous relay.
Tamo-hime and Hime are both shaking, and Shiki-hime is shaking. Ima-
chan, let's do our best. It's okay, it's
okay. We'll win, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay. We'll win, we'll win, we'll win, we're in the yellow group during practice. It's
been about a minute and a half.  It's not just that I was being avoided,
but the part where the food is served is
not at all after all.This is a serious meta reading,
but yeah,
the content of Holomen hunting
has changed considerably with the update, so this is the case.The
menu is also unique.  It's possible that you're
making a mysterious impression that Chan might have changed.
That's possible. That's
possible. That's totally possible. Well, I
want to win. I want to win. If I've come this far, I've
already come. How far do I want to go?  Yes, I
want to go, right? I'm
starting to get a little greedy.At first, I was
like, ``It's good to have fun,''
but
somehow I'm starting to see victory.I'm going to roll
my sleeves up.
No, I didn't come here. I tore my skin to pieces around my shoulders. I can't even tear my sleeves apart. I ca
n't tear my sleeves anymore. I've torn my skin to pieces.  Do
n't tear off your skin. I
took care of it wildly
and got muscular. I'm proud of my muscles. I
lost my last 41
kills. I turned bright red because of the glue from Oshimi-senpai.
Who was it? Who cut it the most? It was me.
Kamekiara was also amazing.At the very end, I
defeated Subaru-senpai twice and Miko-senpai once.I
was being chased so much, and Kara was
coming all the time.Kara was amazing, amazing,
amazing.  So, the white team
was great, but at the end, I would like to say a few words:
Thank you very much Nekomata Okayu Thank you. Please leave your thoughts. Yes,
thank you very much. It
was a pleasure to play with you all. I
will continue to support the white team. Yes,
thank you,
thank you.  Ah, it disappeared in an instant. It disappeared. There was
Agent Jinto.
Thank you very much for the agent. Also,
Agent Okao of the MAGA team, thank you very much.
Thank you, me and my seniors too. The number of kills is
shocking, so this must be the case.  It's
completely different, it's different because I worked hard.
Hey, thank you. It's really nice. I didn't have to worry about it. It
was
fun. It was really fun.
It was fun.
But the pressure of the competition after this is different. The
pressure is different.  It's okay,
relax and hope, it's okay, there's still plenty of
time, okay, say it. Everyone can go, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it looks like it's okay. Protect the princess again, even if you have to protect the princess, she's still a princess. Even if you make a little mistake, she
'll make up for it.  The pressure is so bad, it's so bad, it stings
even when it's dangerous, it
really stings me, I've been practicing it.I'm
climbing now.Everyone is
climbing the ivy.It's like I'm
impatient.Even now, I'm getting better at the ivy.Eggplants are
difficult, aren't
they?  I told you it was difficult,
but I heard you said you were
running.It looks like the
scores have been tallied, so I'd
like to take a look.Here are the total scores for the three games.I did my
best.
Red has
46 points and White has 38 points. Red is
in 2nd place. They were in 3rd place until just a little while ago. I thought they
had made a comeback, so I made a comeback. I don't know
what's going on here. I wonder
what will happen in the second half after this.  Okay, let's move on to the next one.Okay, let's
all move to the next competition.Let's all move to the race venue.It
hurts.Let's
enjoy the go-go.Let's do our best.Let's do our best.We'll do our best.We'll
do our best.I
wonder if everyone can come.  Do your
best, do your
best, do your best
[Music] Masu
Masu
Knowdone
All Gujiguji
Nike
[Music]
Nice
Oh, do your best, White team, White team, do your best,
do your best, do your best, Oka-tan entered the princess Hime
Hime Hime, you look strong, Hime  If it's number one, then the princess seems
to be strong, Ichi-chan is strong.The force is the strongest.His
secrets will
be crushed.I want you to go tight.I want you to go tight.I wonder if you'll
shake my hand.Let's
do our best here, let's do our best.  It's so
cute with that tiara on.
Hey, yo, yo, karao. It
's okay, it's okay. [Laughs] I thought Kaya-chan was crying.
So she's laughing, so she's laughing. I
was surprised. I was worried. Now, yeah, I thought someone was crying.  I
was so surprised. It's because
Himegacchan has a unique way of laughing.
Hey, that definitely makes my heart flutter.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yeah, nevernoticedthis
beforeaetlaughbutI
neverheard
likeWhenIlovesomuch
becomeslikeCrying
knowhappTearshapp
Cryhapp
[Music] [
Laughter] [
Music]
Yeah.  Why is Ka-chan laughing so much? I
wonder why she's
just
playing with her own 3D model,
so she's laughing at herself.
[Music]
Hey,
Ah
[Music]
Patty
Yes, it was supposed to be you, but it's scary. You
only have to do it once. It's like a one-time competition. Ah,
pressure, pressure, you're
nervous. Do your
best. You're the princess who will be participating in this,
Katan and Omei-chan.
Also, Azuki -chan Azuki -chan Ka -chan -chan is just saying the menu a while ago. I guess it
is a difficult menu.  I
feel sleepy if I can't divide the roles because I have to cut things off and do things, and there are various affirmations.Yes, it's important to be strong during the time we spend
together.But
on the other hand, Minecraft has been working for three years now.
But I thought, oh, you can cut vegetables. That's
what I thought, too. I thought you could cut them. Well, there
was an item for cutting boards that said knives. When I
clicked on the cutting board to open it, there was a knife
next to it.  If you put it in a pan, you
can cut tomatoes, carrots, potatoes, etc. Also, if you
add beef, it will turn into
minced meat.
No, it's amazing. It seems like the
normal version can't cut it, but it seems like it's this special version. Yeah, yeah, that's
right, but on the other hand, it's
amazing to be able to do that. There's certainly a possibility of Minecraft
being set up like that.
Yay.  It's so sad, yeah, yeah,
but we're all so moved, but I wonder if it's normal for
Kara-chan, who's in the middle of her life, to be
honest. She's a little girl, after all.
Maybe that's why she's laughing. She doesn't have the
patience to do that lol.
[laughing]
Nocha, I
touched
it. It's cool.
Leave it. Thank you. It's starting. Do your best. Do your best. Do your best. Do your best. You must have seen it on the street the other day. You came here just in time to come.  It's going well, it's going well, it's going well. It's going well. It's going well. It's going well. It's
going well. It's going well. It's going well. It's going to be smooth. It's going to be smooth. It's going to be smooth. It's going to be very smooth. It's going to be very smooth. It's going to be very smooth.
Okay, okay, the letters are good, seriously, about 1 or 2.
No, this is good, good, go, go, go. Now it's lined up with red. Oh, good, good. It's
not No. 1 now. Let's go, let's go. Let's go,
let's go. Let's guess. What is this?  Wood brown
Yeah, it's already made of wood. Hey,
what, what, what is
this? It's a new machine. I wonder what they're making. I
wonder what it is.  I do
n't know, no, from here I do
n't know, it's all white and pink What is this?
What is this?  What are you
doing? What are you making? I'm really curious.
When I was practicing, it
was like Misi's hamburger steak. How about
Misi's homemade hamburger hamburger? I
wonder what they're making.  What are you doing right now?Ah, you're
cutting it.You're baking it.You're cutting it.You're
grilling it.You're cutting vegetables.You're cutting vegetables.Do your best,
try your best, do your best.It looks like it's going to
be fun, so do your best.What are you making?I'm sure you're
thinking about it.  Hey, let's pull back later. Eat,
eat, eat, eat, good, good,
nice, nice, red. Hurry, hurry, we're already up to stage 5. Wow, try your best, but we're only at 2 now. No,
red is strong, red.  It's strong, but it's fast, it's
fast, it's fast, it's fast, it's fast, it's fast, it's
fast, it's moving, it's moving, it's moving, it's moving, it's moving, it's
moving, it's strong, it's strong, it's strong.  Do your
best, do your best, do your best, one -chan with a
one
-chan with a one -chan one
chan with a one -chan one
-chan.  Strong, strong, strong, just a little bit more, just
a little bit
more, I can go, it's okay, I can do it.
Let's defeat it
Nice nice nice nice nice nice
[Music]
Nice, it's a great piece, yellow
Onamaiga is
nice Nice, nice, nice, good, wow, what
was that?  I
didn't really understand that pink block with white one, but when I looked at it, I saw that it
was brown.What was it?Oh, I don't
care, but it was amazingly yellow.At the end, it was brown.
Even though we were getting close, it was getting all messed up. Hey, it's not me. What's wrong with
that? Who was it? I couldn't figure it out in an instant.
Wada
[Music]
Oh, I'm so nervous, I'm so nervous, at this hour.  Flowers: Can we
go fishing? I'm not doing an interview right now,
so I'm going
to go ahead and
go. Hey there, it's the air conditioner right now. It's
hot in the room. Open the door in the room.
Let's get out of the way.  I can't live without an air conditioner.My
house in Austria
doesn't have an air conditioner at all.But what about heaven?It's
quite hot in the summer, so I
wish I could turn on the air conditioner, but houses are usually built without an air conditioner.  That's
right, it's hot, just in case. I
don't think it's unthinkable, but it's hot. It's hot. It's so
dry.
Unlike Japan, I don't have a lot of food. I don't like chocolate.
Even if someone tells me, it's not good for chocolate, I'll be quick to attack.
Interpretation 1 Even if it were now, I'd still be wearing it all the time.
Oh yeah, in the air conditioner,
this air conditioner love, love love. I wonder if I'm counting it
now. Interviewer tally. Kakono Tsuji is at the
end with Lillet, oh yeah, I'm nervous.
[Music]
Oh, it's really going to be real.  It's okay because you're weak I
know you can go, it's okay, it's
okay It's scary
[Music]
Yeah, Sususuue But Nerissa-chan and I are
number 1, so you're going to be super nervous. Yes,
but you're the one who can fix something over and over again even after that.  I think I'm going to
eat Karason's female
The one that probably feels the most pressure is
probably the last one Iroha-chan is the last one.  I'm
getting nervous because I'll
be handing over the baton to my senior, so I guess I'll be in the middle of the class, so I'm not sure if I'll
be okay.I want to do my best, but I do
n't know what the actual performance will be like, so I'll be able to do what I did.  I
can't do it anymore, so I
get it, I get anxious, right? Well, I
guess the points for the relay are high after all. I wonder how it will turn out in the last competition. Even now, the red team
probably has a pretty good lead.  That's right,
isn't it going to go higher in the opposite direction
?I have an image of a higher end at the end,
I understand.I understand, in the sense that a reversal is possible.That's
right.It seems like there is something like that.So,
let's take a look at the scores of the Hikoshi race.  The
red team was in first place,
so it's 30 points, the white team is 20 points, and the
yellow team is 10 points.Yes, the
red team is a bit amazing.
So,
from now on, let's
move to the venue for the next competitive race, and let's
move a little bit.  It
's here, it's white,
it's white
[Music]
Oisho Tireki-chan is messed
up Somehow it was blown away without permission Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa oh, it's
blown away without permission Everyone I'm here I'm home I'm home
Senpai is amazing
Cooking was so fast He was so fast  It was
really early. What did you make
? It came out with
lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was lamb. It was sheep. It
was grilled. I got a hamburger steak. I was lucky because when I was practicing, I got a lot of hamburger.  I was so sleepy
during practice and I'm glad I was finally there because there was even a high school.Actually, I'm
so sorry,
Kankatsu-
chan.What the hell is that?  The
contestant was blown away before the announcement was made.It was so
cutting-edge technology that it was said that it was
a moment of surprise.It's
not easy to understand.
Hello, no, no, it's
better to enter, right? Yes, you can enter and
get a book, so
open the book, choose which one you are, or
which one is white, and come on.  I'm here, I'm
here, I'm here, I'm okay. I'll just right-click on it.
Yeah, ah, okay, I'm
number 8 on the entry list.
My name is Ame-chan, and I wonder
what level she's on.  It's somewhere in the middle,
like the leader of the memory squad. Ame-
chan is on the 5th floor. 5th person.  It's freshly
made, it's
ok, you old man,
oh, it's amazing. My character contact is blurry today. It
's
okay, I can do it, don't be weak, it's okay. Can I
go?
Oanka, it's okay. Yojo, it's okay,
dodge.  It's okay, it's okay, you'll
be nervous at the end.
[Music]
have aso.
Nona
ah
oh OnaNotobeone
gurjiguji nice nice no this onechan this water First of all it
's the turn of the contestants 1st Okay
ok next is Choco Sensei yo 3rd layer
is
Mume 4th layer is Captain Noel Okay and 5th
layer  Ame, yes, 6th layer,
Kaerae, 7th layer, Azusan, and finally, it
's a good thing. It's like people are getting to know each other,
and Minecraft is getting used to this kind of thing, and it
feels like people who are used to it are coming in.
It's like they're trying to catch up.  That seems like a good feeling.
Let's go.
Everyone in the white group, I can hear it. I can hear it. I
can hear it. I can hear it. So, who should I choose? No, I don't know. Well
then,
Iroha.  When I realized something, I
became an anchor, but I heard that the wind is moving quickly, so I
think it will work out somehow.I have faith in you, so I will do my best.No, it
's wonderful.I
hope you can take first place, please do your best.
Please, do your best,
Zhang, thank you
very much. Well then, let's do it for the last time. Wow, I just came
back from Hana. Welcome home. I just said that
when Nerisa-chan was confused, I
couldn't hear her say ``open book.''  Oh, I didn't reach it. I'm
embarrassed. I'm a man who responded. Let's do
our best. If we're at the bottom, we'll be able to go back.
Well, let's do our best. Let's try our best. Let's do our best. Let's do our best. Let's do our best. We're on the
right. We're falling.  I'm
going to do my best here,
here is the water, wow, oh,
oh,
oh, oh, and I'm nervous,
and I'm sorry.  It's okay because everyone is here. It's
okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay today
in Korea. I'll remember and do my
best. No, I'm really trying my best.
Yeah, it's already the end, so feel free to do it for the last
time.  It's the end with a laugh. Okay, now that's it.
After we're done, let's go eat some delicious meat. Let's
talk to the chocolate line. Azuki and
chocolate. Let's go to the meat, snow, yakiniku, shabu-shabu, shabu-shabu.
Good luck to Rediff who is going to prepare the food.  Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go Go
Go Go
[Applause]
Camo Camo Nice Nice Catch
Nice Catch Nice Catch Nice Bread Nice Nice
Bullet Nice Bullet That's what I
mean.  Ta-ta-ta-
ta Go, leave it to me, leave it to me,
leave it to me, it's okay, it's okay, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's okay
There are times like that when you say
There are times, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, go, go, go all the way at all.
[Music]
Tasu Wait, this bread, bread
Hey, it's on the left, right? Left
Ohnope, do your best, do your best, do your best on the left
[Music] Good
luck, good luck, yo oh, sorry, good luck, good
luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck,
good luck  I-
chan can go, I can go, I can
go, I'm fine, everything's fine, Don Don Don Don, Don Ya Do, it's okay, I can go, I can go, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll
leave it to you, please
do your best, I'll do my best, I'll
do my best, I'll
go, I'll
do my
best.  Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Do your best and
do your best [laughing] Kai [music] Gogogogogo Good luck Mai [music] Are you going to get sucked into this or that? Nice, nice Oh, it's finally time to give up, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, Aki, it's like you're being beaten by your superiors.  Hey,
it's okay, it's okay, I'll
hit you properly, it's okay, it's okay,
just eat yo, do your
best, try your best, do your best, do your best, do your best.  Go let's go, let's go, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's nice, it's nice, it's fine,
it
was a fight, it was tense, it was
tense, go for it, do your best, do your best, everyone, it's
over.  I
forgot what to eat.
It's okay. I'm hungry. I want to be hungry. I'm hungry. Let's
eat a lot when we're done.
Yes, nice run, nice
run, nice run. [Music] Nice, want to eat meat,
eat meat.  Let's
go meat, meat, meat,
meat,
yes, yes, yes, meat, meat, yes, yes, yes, my heart hurts
now, thank you for your hard work,
Japanese sub-sub, I
want to eat, I want to
eat, let's
eat together, Shabu-
shabu, Shabu-shabu, Shabu-shabu is
delicious, Shabu-shabu is delicious, cute, cute,
cute,
soothing, cute  Let's go, make the shabu-shabu hot.
My Chico Line is here. The Chico Line is taking me.
Take me with me.
[Music] Give
it to me. Let's leave it all to Choco-sensei. Choco-sensei's choice is berry. Good,
super nice.
Yeah, leave it to me. Leave it to
me. I'll do my best.  You
did your best. You did your best. You did your best. You did your best. It was amazing. You did your best. Well
then, let's ask Iha, who served as the anchor,
one more time. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How was it? How was it?  We were the best. We
did it all right from the beginning to the end. We
put in the cheese work.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. The result is that we can
make it. There were times when we were passed or overtaken, but we finished
in 2nd place.  You
did it, no, it's amazing, it's great, it's nice, it's a nice fight, it's good, it's a good job.  You're making good use of it. How many
days have you taken off? This is so
good. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. You've
done it. The color of the 1st grade test. No, it was really good.
Everyone was crying.
Tears. You're
so sensitive.  It was really good.
No, it's 2. It's
okay. I tried my best. I tried my best. I
tried my best. I tried my best. At first, I
honestly
felt like I was having fun, and even though it was difficult, I was like, let's do our best. But I never expected it.
Yes, that's right. I don't know until the end. Yes, the first result. I wonder what's
going on.
Yes, that's right. So we're going to hold this ceremony, so please gather in front of everyone. Let's go to the very beginning.
At school, there was a
wall with an undesirable wall.I was surprised, and
we were sealed off.Now, I'm
a little
nervous about this school, and I'm lining up in a row.Yes, yes, there are all kinds of things.The white group is
lined up neatly.The
white group is coming out early.  They
lined up neatly in a row.
It seems like they were separated. Maybe it's because of the correct answer method. It's a bit
crowded, so
there's only 5 of us, and there aren't many of us. It's true that the
yellow ones are hitting each other, and there's
too much
polka.  Look, we're all lined up like polkas,
polkas are on top of it, hey, I'm holding the
bread, I'm holding it, it's okay, it's okay
, it's okay, it's over here.
Well, the closing ceremony
is about to begin, but what do you think, Mr. Yamiko
? To be honest, I had no idea what was going to happen this year
or not.But
yeah, everyone was working together really well,
working hard, and it was a close race every year.  It was
really worth watching and I thought it
was amazing. Well, that's true. There was a drama in each of them, or rather, there was. I think it was a drama, including the practice, but I think it was really good.
Good luck to everyone.  The group that doesn't line up at all is
a bit too crowded for mom,
so Mio-chan was talking about it just now, so she
came and told us to get along. We
lined up a little nice. That's
great. We said yes, yes.
What do you think? I wonder if I can do it? I'm ready to go. I'm sure we'll be able to chat, but that's not the case right now. I'm just asking you to wait for a while. I think I'll be able to go, so it's okay.
So, before the ceremony,
for this competition, there
were a lot of chat moves.  However, I would
like to say a few words to everyone, Nee-chan, and A-chan and Nodo-chan who supported me in that area.Yes, yes, Ei-chan and Nodo-
chan,
thank you very much.Voice from HeavenThank you for your hard work.This
is the voice from heaven.  Thank you,
thank you, this year, and this year as well.Thank
you very much.Your hard work and
individuality are overflowing.And the three organizers have
worked so hard.We can see all the hard work,
and we are very moved.Thank
you.  Thank you very much
Thank you very much for your cooperation Thank you very much for your
cooperation Thank you very much for your cooperation Thank you very much for your cooperation
Thank you very much for your cooperation I
hope it was fun for all three of you to participate.  So
please do your best until the end.Yes,
thank you very much.Thank you very much.Okay,
everyone.The
closing ceremony will now take place.First
of all, I would like to give a closing speech.Yes, please give a greeting from Ms. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day executive committee.
Yes, yes,
everyone had fun at this sports day.
Yes, I'm glad it was fun. Yes, it
was really good, everyone. Thank you,
everyone. Every year, we've gotten really busy, and
thankfully, Hololive has gotten busier, but still...  I've
seen Nemiko and her friends all come together and work together and take the initiative to call out to each other and help each other out, and I'm
always so moved by how truly moved I am.
Thank you very much for your continued cooperation.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.  I
think it would be great if everyone could make Hololive even more exciting,
so I look forward to your continued support.
Yes, that's great. Thank you very much. Next, I'd like to
ask Miyo-chan. Thank you all for participating this year,
and do your best.  I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I tried my best, I
said yes, and that's the finish line for this year as well.  I've
seen all the different aspects of the team, and I
think all the teams are working hard, and I think we'll get results this time around, but
one big thing is that we all worked hard together like this.  I
think it will become a treasure, so I hope that you will be able to make use of our bond in the future. It
was really fun to watch.
Thank you very much.
Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice
speech. I'm
embarrassed.  Senkyu Senkyu
Yes, so finally I
would like to announce the general benefits.Yes, yes, the bonus
announcement will be about 1, then about 100, then
finally about 10, in order of
3 groups all at once.  I would like to make an announcement on that day.
Yes, Mr. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day executive committee,
would you like to make a special announcement?
Yes, then, I will start by making an announcement from number 1.
Yes,
that's it.
Wow, red team is 8 white team.  But the
yellow group is 6. What, what, what? I'm scared. I'm
a little scared of the announcement, but I do
n't know yet. I don't know anything yet. I do
n't know anything yet. Okay, let's continue.  I
'll announce it first.Yes, yes,
here's about 100.
Please,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I
don't know yet. I've
got all of these. Yes, all of them are about 100.
Yeah, no, no, no, I'll go last.
Hey, everyone.  Finally, the announcement of about 10
is so good. Wow,
yes, the red hair got 158 ​​points. The
winner is the red hair. Congratulations. Congratulations. Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
Wow!
Don't do it without passing the first class.  I know it's frustrating,
but it's so bad that it's so bad. Let's get along, get
along, get along. We're friendly, please, please.
And the second place goes to the white team with 138 points, and the third place goes to the white team
with 106 points.  We're in a group, you did a
great job. Everyone did a great job. You
did a great job. It was amazing. You did a great job.
Yes, that's why we're going to give you the
award. Yes, we're having an award ceremony this time. It's good for everyone. The
yellow group gets the medal.  This is Geo.Okay,
well then, the players from the yellow group, the
teacher's representative, Hasbe-chanpe-
chan,
please come to the front, come here,
please.
Wait a minute,
Miko-san, Miko-san, oh, yeah,
everyone's here too. Everyone's here.
Neck-o. Wow, you've
prepared it just now.
Hey, congratulations on the box. Congratulations
on the box. Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Next, yes, next is the truth. Yes, it's Geo, who won the silver medal for the white team.
Oh, the yellow team, A-chan, please come.
Please, come, come, come, come. Thank you. Well then, A-chan, the gold medal.
Congratulations on the gray hair. Oh, wow,
Tsuki.
Thank you very much for the good work.Congratulations
!Congratulations!
Congratulations!Congratulations, Osa.And
yes, this is
Ji, the gold medal winner of the red team, who came in first place.
[Music]
Yotowa-sama Towa Towa-
jiatowa-sama  Thank you for winning the Red Team.Congratulations!
Awesome congratulations!
Stop it, stop
it, stop it!Can't we just get along and get along and pick it up?It's
right in front of my eyes.I wish there were so many diamonds that disappeared so quickly.
So, with that said, I would like to say that Holo
Live Sports Day 2023 is a negative impact.
Thank you everyone.
Yes, thank you, thank
you.
Yes,
what should we do? Shall we put it on the platform over there in the middle?
Yes, please. Yes, it's
on the moving table. It's over here. Yes, let's move. Come on, come on. Let's move. Come on, let's
move. Everyone,
everyone.  Line up, line up, line up, line up, line
up. You can get in too. You can
get in too.
Oh, I can't
see it. I can't see it. Is
n't there still time? Isn't there still time? Isn't there still time?
Wait, wait a minute,
please. Yes, you're here.
Everyone's following us. It's amazing. It's true. I'm so happy.
Oh, I'm so happy. I lost
my medal.
No, it's too good. If I try it one more time,
I'll be pissed. I don't have any more. I don't have any more. It's
sad.
How can I give this to you? Kanataka Kana-tan can't say that. I can't
give it. I can't give it.  Wait,
tap, why don't you touch it
? I was able to touch it by left-clicking. I'm glad I did it. I'm glad I did it. Ta-ha-o,
everyone. I wonder
where I should look at that thing right in front of me.
Should I look at it, Koro-san?  Koro-
san Around Koro-san I feel like I'm looking at Koro-san There's
a lot of things flying around.
Okay, ah, you should just look there.
Everyone, are you okay? Can you see me? I'm taking
pictures!
[Music]
Stop, everyone is throwing so much stuff. Hey, it's here
again. Hey, don't throw away your trash. Please
take your trash home. You can't see the bottom of the trash.
Thank you very much.  Thank you very much to
all the listeners who watched the show, and to all the
management staff who helped out behind the scenes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much.  That
's all for now. Let's
meet again. Let's all
go to Hololive. Let's go!
Hololive. Hololive.
It's the winner. Let's
get along. Let's get along. Let's get along. We'll get along. Let's get along. Let's
get along.  I got
beat up,
I got beat up, I got beat up, so I said yes.
This time, I participated in the Hololive Sports
Day. I'm white 2.
Yes, unfortunately I'm in 2, but everyone was having a lot of
fun, and Choco had a lot of
fun.
I also got a medal, so it's a good feeling. I'll
take the poo. Kaa Chacha
Pashiri. So,
thank you to everyone who took the time to watch me. I hope to be
able to do it again next year. So that's how I'd
like to end today.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good job and bye
[Music]
Bye