[Music]
DET
A
[Music]
Kaki
Hololiving's high school
Yes Subaru Senpai, I heard that it was the 5th anniversary, so I
came to celebrate.
Congratulations. 5  A year is seriously a long time, especially in this world,
but
I really, really respect the way you work hard every day as if you've just made your debut. I wish I could be as energetic as Subaru-senpai every day.  I'll do my best Subaru-senpai From now on, let's
do our best together as Monun Horohoro and Hololive seniors and Holoto friends.
Please be good friends, and above all,
do your best in the live performance from now on. I'll be watching you. Fight! Oh
Hololive's Great Arashiba.
Congratulations on your 5th anniversary, it looks like there's going to be a live show, so do your best. Let's play games together again. Bye, Happy 5th anniversary to Baiba-senpai.
Congratulations on your 5th anniversary. Lately, we've been working together behind the scenes with FF14.  I think we've become much closer to each other by letting you
play with us, showing us how you play Strokes, and
talking with you.I
think we've become much closer to each other.Thank
you for always being attentive to me, Suba-senpai, and seeing how
energetic you are.  The way you dance is a
role model for Nekani, so I
hope we can continue to do many things together. I
'm also looking forward to today's live show. I'm
rooting for you with Gozaru.
Good luck to you, Gozaru.  Please, I can do it,
Subaru-senpai can do it
[Music]
Gozaru-
senpai, Senpai Subaru-senpai, Subaru-senpai, Ao,
thank you for your hard work, Hishio, Subaru-senpai, maybe it's the 5th anniversary, isn't it? Congratulations, no, you're
serious, you're serious, you're serious.  It's a
live show, right? It's a live show. No, I'm
really looking forward to it. I'm really looking forward to it. I'm
really rooting for you. I'm really rooting
for you. Suba-senpai. No, I really respect Subaru-senpai.
Suba.  Senpai isn't just cute, it's
hot here, and his heart is
hot and cool, so I
have a lot of respect for him.Squirrel, ah, spa, senpai, no, seriously, seriously, really, really, really, really, really, really respecting him.  You're so cute today, too. You're so
cute today too. You're such a wonderful senpai, you're such a wonderful senpai. I
respect you so much, you're such a great senpai. You're so cute,
senpai, and I
'm really rooting for you today.
Please do your best,
Suba-
chan Congratulations on your 5th anniversary live!
Wow, this day has finally come, the leader
is smiling, and I'm
sure the Suba friend on the other side of the screen feels the same way. The
leader is Suba friend today.  I'm really looking forward to it because I'm sure she'll be waving her penlight
as hard as anyone on the other side of the screen.I've been
waiting for it since before the opening, but I wonder what kind of live show she'll
be doing this year. Katsuba-chan's live show is the best every year.  I'm
already looking forward to it Wow I'm looking forward to
it The 5th anniversary live is about to begin It's about to begin [
Music]
Subaru's 5th anniversary congratulations live is about to begin Good luck
Subaru live Good
luck Subaru live Good luck
Subaru live
Good luck
[Music]
Kusa Subaru live Good
luck, good luck, good luck, good luck
[Music]
[  Music]
He
[Music]
Three
One Let's go
to see the ceremony of turning to a squadron that will wake you up from your usual day. It's a
special day
[Music]  ]
In the new season, where the greenery is slow, I stare at the
blue
light.I don't see the faces of my classmates, even friends I don't know.My
classmates
don't live a normal life, and on the contrary, it's
too much.Even
if it's every day, I finally get to see them.The statues make me feel restrained.
No, the promised place
was a dream.
Now, an unforgettable day is about to
begin. Today is another special day. I've stepped out of my daily routine a little. Look, I've
shuttered the camera, and no matter
what I do, I can't help but smile.
[Music]  Maybe all the kids I
jumped on are all together.
Even the waiting time, which is full of precious moments,
makes me think of love.
Where should I go next? When I
notice Finaho walking brightly, the time is empty. The
sun has set, and the lights decorating the rice cakes are forming a parade.  It's
captivating my heart, I'm really glad I came here.I'm
in town today is a special day, so I
jump out and look, I can't take the shutter off.I'll
always have memories, spring, summer, fall, and winter, that I
found in this place.  I wonder
when I'll see you again next time? Let's
go there, using the turning of the stick sword as a landmark.
On a special day [Music] [Applause] Your idol
[Music]
will be there.  I'm so happy. I'm so excited that I'm
flapping my legs. I couldn't sleep because I was looking forward to today.
I'm nervous too. I can't afford to
waste every minute. Let's
get started. You, you, you, I'll be waiting for you.
Please help me.  Welcome to the place where love gathers.If you
come here, dance.It
doesn't matter whether it's a big box or a
small box.I want to care about you.Your
parim suddenly seems to fly away right now.
But if you're going to push me, I'll
open the barres [music] Your
idol
[music]
He's the one I raised and he's so arrogant I have to
enjoy the moment with you and you,
even if you're a shut-in, show me a different face than usual.  It doesn't matter if we
all act like we're brothers, we
don't care, we don't care.
Even if your world feels me, there
's nothing to fear as long as you're here.
[Music]
[Applause]  ]
Look, look, something is about to begin,
but what a wonderful sight it is.I don't
care if it's big or small, I don't care if it's big or small.Your
tarum is so small that it could fly if you blow it right now.
But if you're going to push me, then
if you're on my side, then I'll
open up the barres. Your
idol is
B. The
airwaves taper, and I'm in awe.
[Music] I
wonder if you have sad things you want to forget, too. Even though it's a movie I don't know.  The reason I shed tears is because I'm
not dramatic enough. I'm just
thinking about stupid things that don't apply to my country.
When the rain stops, both my love and my profile
will belong to someone else. Even the lying
foundation is all for tonight.
Why on earth is this all going to happen? What's going on with this
unstable Katsuda?
No matter how far you go, I'm not joking,
Tokyo. Even when that time comes, there's no point in it. I
'm vague. Just do what you want.
[Music] There's
no such thing as a strange hack, but there's
no such thing as a ploy to leave your disembodied emotions alone,
so why is it that you're already so stiff? I'm
still trying to hold back my sweet nature, and I'm giving
lip service all year round.
And now I have tears in my eyes, and the music in my head makes
me unable to hear what you're saying. I'm
trying to say something reasonable,
but please make me forget everything. What's going on?
If you're worried, it won't go away Even if you eat just one meal, I'm
not kidding.
When the time comes, it won't
matter. I'm just going to tell the truth.
[Music]
Now
[Music] I'm
not kidding either.  Tokyo Shabu Even if that time has come, it
won't matter, I won't use it. It's
just Laris.
[Music]
Maji Love. Even if that time has come, it won't matter. It's just going to be
gone.
So yes, come to Hololime. I hope
everyone is having fun today. Hey,
thank you for coming to the Rasuru Anniversary Live. I'm
really happy.
I hope everyone enjoys it.  I got it,
and the Chirp that appears above this.It's
Subaru's 5th anniversary, so please
post it with  I want to be in this
cat. It's been a while since I last wore this costume. I wonder what kind of
pose I should do with it. The
signature I showed earlier is B's signature pose.
Please everyone, please post this.
Okay, and Sai is B.
Thank you to everyone at Detatsu Chocolate for coming. I
was really happy to hear that.
Thank you. So, let's say yes. Now, let's talk about
the first half of the idol-like part.  Now that that's
over, things
may change a little from here on out, so
please look forward to that as well.Here's the
next song.
[Music]
Hey, hey, my favorite accident defense has begun again.
Well, look, look, the pattern of scars on the face has started again. It's
easy. Someday, I was the only one who had a dream like that.
But I'm tired of calling you only when I'm lonely. You're
not interested in me at all. You
're the one who likes me, after all.  You're not interested in me,
I'm tired of hearing that. You're not interested in me in the first place. You're trying to fool me like that
again. My boy,
I'm too much of a mother. Baby,
hold me tight.
[Music]
Really, it can't be helped. It ca
n't be helped. I won't collapse.
Maybe we can dance just a little bit longer.I've melted away.No matter
how much I try to appeal to you, you won't notice me.You
come to see me when I'm lonely, but you're
not interested in me at all.Please
tell me what's wrong with me.  After all, you're not interested in me, you're
just playing around with your phone, and you're not really interested in me in the first place.Even
if I give you a little hope, Lonely is the first one.Baby, don't
swing around.
[Music]Let's
take Melty and Walta.Hurry up and connect.
One last thing,
love me so much that you're drowning in me. You're not interested in me at all
. You're the one who likes me. After all, you're
not interested in me. I'm
tired of hearing this story. You're not interested in me in the first place.
Even if you cheat like that again, it's not worth it.  I'm
ready
[Music] A
happy morning [
Music] How about it? [Music] I'm
laughing at the morning pound that goes along with the incident.
But I'm looking at you who pretends to be someone you're interested in. [
Music] I
was like that, so I cut it down to size.  I do
n't want to say anything,
but I
eat, go to sleep right away, turn into a cow, and wake up again.
[Music]
None. I
broke it and died, but I felt like the knob
was turning. I wanted to get it back.
Araronde Barreto
is starting again. There's nothing you can do about it, so you're imitating someone whose day is coming. If it's just a simple belief, then it's not enough. It doesn't matter. I'll turn into a cow as soon as I eat. I'll wake up and go back to sleep.
Even if I break it, I'll just die, but I can't help but feel like the
knob is turning, and I want to get it back, and it's
falling.I'm not dizzy, and I'm going home.Maximizer,
Maximizer,
Maximizer  Maximizer
Ah
[Music] Ah,
where are you and what are you doing now? I
'm in a place where this sky continues
[Music] I
lost what had filled my heart and
realized for the first time that you
supported me so much.  I've
lost the one who made me smile so much. The
general is too big,
and I desperately try to reach out and struggle to get him back,
but it's as if I've slipped through the world of wind and
can't reach him. My heart tightens with loneliness and despair.
But
your unforgettable smile
always cheers me up.
[Music]
[Applause]
Gives me
[Applause] Let's go back
to those days once again.
This time, I'm sure it'll be okay.
Always smile by my side,
right next to you.  By my side,
where are you and what are you doing now?
Are you in this place where the sky continues?Will you
keep smiling like always?Right now, I
just wish that
[Music]
Continue
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]
[Music] Even if I
chase after someone, I've been chased, but
only one remains.When my heart starts,
even if I don't like it, people take up space.So that I won't be taken away, I
continue to protect the hands that I've kept clean.  But
before I can doubt my dirty memories, my memories are doubting me.
I'm sure we'll come out. I'm always here, using the sound of the same child as a landmark. The
reason for my narrowed neck is weighing down on me. The meaning of my teacher's words.
As long as the existence of knowing continues, it can't be helped, so I
take up space. Two pieces fit in
one hole. When I dropped something, something
popped out. I noticed the footprints I had counted, bathed in light at the place I stole them from.
All I have to know is that between 1 and terrorism,
we'll meet for the first time. We'll use the same princess's flag as a
landmark, and don't forget to call out to each other. So
when we fill in the piles of reasons together, we'll make a promise.  We're
like mirrors that can be passed over. We transfer our powers to each other. We
touch each other with our dirty hands and see the shape. We
're here. It's true that we're being touched. We're here
in our own private sun. Don't forget, call us anytime.
Because we have the same handle,
we must operate from the inside.When we make a sign of the cross for a reason,
we will fulfill our mission.We will
become one.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music]  The
song was Karma.
What did you think? The cat
part was performed by the backing dancer Nee Takanari
Morimori,
but there was Marshall
Maximizer and umm, I wonder what it was.  It was so
much that I
forgot about it, but I paid a lot of attention to the production and other things, so
I'd be
really happy if you could pay attention to that as well.There
are a lot of things that I paid close attention to, so I'll be sure to check that out as well.
Please look forward to the songs that come after this.It's
finally the second half of the live show,
so this is the next song.Listen
to it.Where have you been
?
[Music]I
wonder how much more I should avoid.
How much should I cry? Stop it
already. I can't run anymore. The world I once dreamed of is closing. It's like there's
no light on this crumbling road. I
feel like I've seen the hope of that time. Please reach out to
Black Roxy.  The nostalgic
memories were just fun,
and I was able to move, even if I ran back to those days.I wish on the star that casts darkness and
run just one more time.
[Music]
From
With a scared and trembling voice, I
read my name and dawned.
Even after the distance to the line, I still can't reach the sky. I'm
about to burst into frozen tears. Don't look down now. I
want to live in a future where it'll stop. I understand. I'll
remember it and believe in it strongly and strongly.
Black Roshta's gentle
scent.  It hurts, it hurts, swallow these words,
Black Shooter. Move, these
feet will
cross the world.
[Music]
[Applause] I
knew from the beginning that I was here. As the
day goes on, all the snow inside me won't run away anymore.
Shooter alone.  I don't care if you
don't raise your voice, just
watch Blackrock Shooter It
starts now
My
[Music]
Story
[Music] When I
feel like I'm about to forget, I'll sing this song
[Music] The
canvas of the road I've painted will overlap  Let's try to connect the scenery
and repeat it.The
world is spreading out before our eyes.The world is spreading out in front of our eyes.We'll run through it
as if it's brightly eclipsing the darkness that's been put on it.We'll be
shining in our dreams, and we'll
keep running on our shoulders.  I
want to walk with happy companions. Every day I want to grab it, it bleeds through my
fingertips and
spreads out before my eyes. [Applause] [Music]  The limits that
we had are broken by the stacking of hands, and I
look up at the night sky that seems to be sucked in. I look up at the night sky and scream now.
Starry lovers, we will always be by your side. Our
voices overflowing with laughter echo in the distance. We are
holding your arm, which is like a fragment of a wish.  Where are you standing
and flying away?
[Music]
Dako and Mono cast a spell on each other to become 100 people, and when they
say they're over it, the kid who was about to make a big deal with the evil Able
jumps out.
We've been waiting for this day as well.  I
can't stop, I haven't woken up yet
Stara, I can't stop I'll
keep running until one second before that light disappears I strongly embrace the voice that shines on you in the infinite universe
[Music]
Te
[Music] It
's going to shine brightly
Without hearing the voices calling each other or seeing
each other, we went to find Pare Pare Pare The start was repeated
[Music] [
Music] [
Music] I
just kept talking to myself I
ran just wanting to start I stopped in the distance in the dark It
was too bright and I thought it was too fast  But I
reached out my hand closer, and our thoughts came together. Look, now we've
become us, and we're
shining brightly. Taking with us our regrets and love, we're
flying away. The light whispers, and I've
found you.  I'm going to clear my heart
from here and fly from here
[Music]
[Music] I'm
not
ashamed to sing Parepare, I still can't rely on you,
Emma, ​​no one can solve it.One day, we'll
meet again.There are
countless stories that started in those days.  It's
not like I can count them.
Look, I'm calling you one now. I
'm beautiful.
Forgive me, the theory that we can meet flashes through the night. The rain will clear up and I'll come again
. A worthy visit is with you. It's
with you.
But even now, if you listen to it, I'll scream for you to go home.
Isn't it obvious? It's all
shining brightly. You're the one who fills my heart. Fure-Fure-Fure shines.
Take my regrets and love with me, and the dream will take flight.  It's a
wonderful start to jump in with you
From here onwards, Our Fly Pare Pare Our
Fly Pare
[Music]
Since I said yes to the pare, I'll be playing Black Rock Shooter with
Starlight and Our Bright
Parade and Subaru with all the 2nd generation students.
Wow, I think it was quite a lot of content,
but thank you very much to
all the backup dancers who danced with me,
and to all the 2nd generation students.
Anniversary activities will be released.Here, let's
take a look at them one by one.First
of all, these are the ones that appear.Ebeets
tapestry.This is Neshigure
Uka-chan's beaded tapestry.Please
join us in the room.  Please decorate it with a
little bit of clothes, like a
special 5th anniversary dress like this.It
's cute, and there's also a
Subaru Duck with something on its face, and it looks
adorable with the flowers.
Please try displaying them together.
And next,
this is a Shiba jersey, Subaru. By the way, it
's a jersey, but Subaru
too. Wear this. I don't
want to dance. I want to go to the studio or something.  Hey,
everyone, please come and get it
all ready.Also, I recommend you to come to the gym or something.Also,
next,
this is the Shima Cap.This is seriously good.I
actually wanted a Subaru, so I made this one.
But this one says "Shiba" and
says it's a Subaru push.It's a
cap that can be used while still showing off.It
's black, so I definitely recommend it to you.If you're an
actor, please wear it.
So, let's move on to the
socks.Subaru
wants socks, so I'm sorry, but
Subaru wants them, so I'll make them for you.Everyone's
cats are cute, too.They're wearing Subaru Duck's
one-point socks.  Please go to school, work, the
gym, or the mail if you like.The
full set is
white and has a reproduction festival and message.This
is a postcard written by Neshigure's mother.
Surprisingly, this time the quantity is not limited.
Thank you very much. It's not the original, so
please buy it at a different time. Yes, and there is one more announcement.
After this, the
PV of the new song will be released at 10pm.
[Music]
New song, new song.  Now, let's move on to the last song.
But the last song is a new song. This song
is a song that Subaru has been active with for five years, and
has supported Subaru's activities over the past five years.  I
made it with the fans and members in mind, and I'm really happy to be able to
celebrate our 5th anniversary with you all.Thank
you for all your continued support.I
want to do my best to sing with gratitude.
Listen if you'd like. Alright then, let's go. Oh yeah,
then listen Stella. A
symphony
of hope shines in the sky that seems far away when you stretch out your hands.
[Music] The
light stars
come together. The day when you meet the miracle you're looking for, the
heat that embraces the shining love floats around you.  The
stars are shining brightly as they pass through the sky, and I'm surrounded by them.My
wishes are playing
in the sky, and they're shining with a meaning that shines brightly.The
stars carry my rotating love and wish that all of me will reach them.As I
put the lid on, I stroke the stars.  Alabi, I'm
gliding across the sky with you,
and my thoughts are filled with stars.The dreams
I drew were filled with stars that were shining once again.I was
illuminated by a certain miracle.Even my
tears ate time.  If I
reach out my hand, I can reach the
sky, where everyone's light shines. We walked together. The love you gave me. I embrace my fate. I'll shine, so I'll reduce you, so I'll glide through the sky.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much.  Masita
[Music]
A
T
[Music]
I