[Music]
is this
foreign
[Music]
oh wow
she lives for now
oh I have a feeling this time this will
be the one I'll be imposter
and I'll suck at it
thank you
no I didn't eat yet but I'm okay this
will not be so long
[Music]
oh yeah scream on everything
yeah thanks for reminding me
[Music]
just practicing does this sound
authentic
oh yeah right we're not using limited
chat never mind we're safe
foreign
okay
hello hello
uh we're starting with uh silence
because I have to
advertise
hello
welcome back everybody
uh this train is sponsored
uh as you can see
uh a whole lot and Among Us
have been doing a nice nice
collaboration
[Music]
um
yeah as you maybe maybe have seen my
last Among Us stream where I already
showcased The Cosmic Cube by an uh
collaboration organized by yours truly
not that I was part of the sponsorship
or anything or that that stream was
sponsored but no this one kind of is
[Laughter]
so yeah hello hello hello oh yes Muna is
standing right next to me
um so you may have already seen it uh
you see it on the screen already there
is outfits that you can get in amongus
to look like some of us not all of us
you can't look like kiwawa can't copy
paste the style it's just too flawless
two beautiful
um but so for example
we have the Among Us excellent life
production collaboration merch on sale
October 28th yeah
uh let's see
is until November 28th uh midnight jst
so at this point I don't know what time
it is I think 8 A.M so there's not much
time left so if you want to get this
specific merch which since it's
different than what you can get on the
Among Us website on their side uh then
you don't have much time left yeah so
there's acrylic diorama stands let me
show you a sample
mm-hmm
[Music]
uh
there and this for example for Ahmed so
for Ian there's gouda andame only it
looks [\h__\h] cool though there is the
acrylic stand there is stickers yeah
and the plushie set I see it on the top
and the keychain I will say I actually
have a keychain yeah kewab also has a
kitchen you see it on the bottom left
um
and did I forget something
I guess there's another keychain there's
apparently two keychains yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes please check the
shop page for details
um cute I like the art
artists look so familiar to me but I
don't know who it is but it looks so
familiar to me
uh and then
[Music]
um the link is in the description by the
way
and now we have it on this is the amulga
side as you can see very different style
new there you go this one's available
longer and I wrote both the links and
the availability timeline in the
description
um yeah so here there are animal pins
cool some T-shirts if some sick art some
posters and accessories accessories look
so girly that ribbon looks so girly yeah
these are kind of different so if you
want to get those check out the shop uh
on the amokus website you should do it
do it do it do it do it
I think did I say everything let me
check
um
uh I think there was one more
I'm not I think I think
I think that's it
[Music]
I think so and then and then and then
and then the Cosmic Cube oh can I look
at it from this point of view I don't
think I can can I
uh
I feel like ah wait yes here I forgot
it's been a while over here
Dad this is my Cosmic Cube I already got
a lot of stuff from previous
playthroughs from the previous
collaboration I'm very fashionable
seeing these are all the items you can
get and then quote coordinate com
combine and equip and then look like
your favorite V2 ball oh
just like this look how fashionable wow
okay I think that's it and now we can go
back
foreign
[Music]
I'm done I'm done I'm done oh
I'll make another one
oh wait chat Deutsch
uh okay should we just play the the
basic the most basic one for for the
first one
okay
basic it is oh the idea girls already
had a Omega stream like this right like
four hours ago or so five six
oh
wow business ladies
you did your homework
Sasuke
all right we're just waiting for the
other girls to finish their homework
they're trained
oh
oopsie sand was muted outside before me
yeah oh there's a room oh gosh there's a
really okay
yeah awesome oh okay I made a new one
one second round trust dreamer mode
hello hello
[Music]
hello
everybody's really tired huh
the third hello
main voice do we want to do like a you
know a classic introduction of everyone
yeah soundtrack let's start by the top
by Anya
hello everyone hello it's on your mouth
is second generation how how's my voice
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay fails next
what's up it's me the red I'm tired um
the rat I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
into being the best rat that I can
hello
everyone
oh no you silly
oh yeah
is Bales in the room yet I don't see her
in the room no I'm not isn't it oh yeah
[Music]
okay
we are hiding why are you hiding
coconut I'm shy do you want to hide with
me yeah
[Music]
get rid of the hyperventilating person I
think you should know what you do right
the whole life Cosmic cubes
[Music]
make you look kind of naked compared to
everyone else
is is you're just beautiful fauna you
know yeah
I'll join you've convinced me
returning to nature
we're promoting the clothes we don't
have any clothes
okay crony next door
[Music]
hello it's me Oro crony I'll follow live
English
I'm going to kill everyone
[Music]
[Laughter]
but I have her on Max I can't do
anything else
it's just her voice
louder or something yeah yeah
pronunciate speak from the stomach crony
be tired
they said you're too low yeah
well I think that needed a buttons
[Music]
okay oh my god oh say again crony
this is this loud enough now yeah I hear
you I hear you
okay yeah thank you
she'll be fine
me you
[Music]
are you crazy
[Laughter]
[Music]
amazing thank you for bringing the
energy that we need
we need that yeah
I felt that in my eyeballs
feeling in your eyeballs who's panties
a lot of panting yeah it's still a
mystery yeah bye uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
Indonesia generation
she did not only get the clothes she
also is adapting The Voice amazing
incredible amazing
[Music]
whoa oh
my God
[Music]
thank you for waking up so early
hello oh hi I'm an Nash
[Laughter]
didn't register to me that you're saying
oh hi I thought you were saying Ohio but
then you just cut it halfway because you
can be bothered
I also heard nashimum instead of Nana
she's just saving letters
I am saving time here
it would take too long the room yes
exactly okay okay
[Music]
so this is me next is Zeta
oh hi I'm Zita but today
[Music]
all right let's go let's go
[Laughter]
close to room again what the room to
close again wait I don't have game sound
[\h__\h] wait wait wait wait
oh [\h__\h]
uh I'm all goose
system there you go please keep me up
there we go okay I'm moving I'm moving
boss it feels so slow why am I running
so slow
foreign
oh that was fast easy whoever is the
Imposter really was very eager
to get it started um how do I see my
where my where my tasks doesn't have
like a yellow arrow
I forgot how to play this game oh this
is hysterical this is what I have to do
nothing stood out to me so far
yo everything was so last minute to just
collapse I even forgot to Tween about it
well thank you for finding it anyway
everybody I tweeted like last minute
but but but there was many more things
that were last minutes
it's okay here we are playing the game
we did it we have done everything we
could
I am not organizing this but I still
ended up like trying to sort things out
because you always have to have like one
person who's like okay so what day are
we doing it what time are we doing it
and um
and stuff like that
there needs to be someone otherwise
nothing I swear to God nothing would
happen nothing
yeah no no it's okay
at least this time
okay getting compensated
not particularly for
helping but
ah
look at
hi I missed you hello I missed you guys
hello hello I missed you hello oh no
where's the body
oh two bunnies
yeah there's yeah
where was everyone at
I was doing tasks I
[Music]
think I just arrived on the shield
oh
[Music]
sorry
should be muted never mind
storage
where I was in store storage and there
was a hallway to the left you know the
hallway that leads to electrical and
then yeah yeah yeah
I actually
I discovered
oh
[Music]
would you like to explain
who wait oh but like like everywhere
else like I've been traveling the right
side of the section so I didn't really
notice anything like I was checking
samples
three seconds
when I found the body why did you not
report the body if you were there
oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
there was something there I didn't even
go to the garage
he lost two crew members
[Music]
I was on the map sorry I didn't know you
could look at the
Messiah
this is already like good old days
everybody talks on top of each other and
you don't understand [\h__\h] this is this
is the Among Us experience with voice
chat
um I'm not gonna go there
you guys do it
do it if you're not the Imposter guys
then do it
I mean the girls by the way okay I guess
I'll do it never mind I'm not doing it
because it's done
ah so fast
[Music]
[Laughter]
I didn't see it did you all see it
I didn't know because it was like it was
like yeah
in front of my eyes oh okay I we were
all there together so cronies kind of
size yeah wow she has an obvious
um reason to do it so
oh
yeah
and I were together though
well goodbye crony wait can I undo mine
well you know it okay fine I'm just
gonna like yes I am the Imposter but
guess what no you should not even
confirm
it because yeah
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
[Music]
all right bye-bye
have fun in space
oh oh I actually turned on the oh okay I
have to turn that off
what why is this setting on anyway
I don't think I had it on last time
I played the game why do they okay
do anything else
don't kill me
wait which one is it is it because it's
not this is not it house oh
yeah bye
I thought it was here again
well
which one is it
um I can try to reach it but uh oh six
five oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
someone is being choosing as imposer and
the Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it yeah
it would be very stupid from you to say
which means that they're gonna be
innocent the only two people remaining
where Kiara I had to choose between the
two
I love them crony we both did so much
work for us to win that round right I
would not have a double we had no
hesitation to kill anybody
I made us faster
[Laughter]
yeah but thank you for not voting me out
wait there's one person missing in the
room
oh there you go
okay
[Music]
thank you Ollie like when I was about to
walk over and Anya was there and I was
like crony you just got me in so much
trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
oh man I was like when when you guys
were in the discussion and Courtney was
like no it was like people were there
and then everyone else seemed not
convinced and I'm like
okay guys
[Music]
that was so funny yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
and then like I was like okay
we're the ones in the room yeah
and like I was like I was hoping I was
hoping that Zeta would say something so
that I didn't want to see I didn't see
it but I was like don't ask
that ran the funny thing is that I was
like I was about to go out from that
room so if only you had waited for like
a few more seconds I probably wouldn't
have got that
well he learned everybody learned their
lesson or crony learned her lesson for
next round right yeah
one day we can get imposter twice
I thought I would be imposter now
I can't be in pasta because I ate so
much pasta this week already
[Laughter]
I was crony already there
all the lights are off
spicy
maybe I'll go fix them should I fix them
how many chihuahuas do you need to
change your life up oh my God there's so
many stop [\h__\h] around
no
[Laughter]
it's probably a lag right
now
[Applause]
it's very dangerous okay
yeah
let's try to turn it on but people kept
turning it off
honestly I I was at there at the scene
too but if you wouldn't have just
admitted immediately that it was you
then I wouldn't have known because there
was so much going on
you don't you shouldn't admit it anyway
I was I was in there I was in there
because electrical was out and everyone
else right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
how can we know it was her we don't know
if it was her
too much
just incriminated herself right away
anyway
oh
[Music]
so fast is it the same team because they
do things the same way
go down go down go down someone
was falling not pushing it
yo watched it
soldier boy oh I can't open it was that
you I feel like it was her why can I not
open the door oh there we go
[Music]
what do you mean do your tasks this is
really what I'm doing
what what do you mean do your tasks
are you watching the Stream
see I'm doing it on tasks
it [\h__\h] stresses me out that alarm
this trusses me out the oxygen wait but
it's down there why is it not happening
different one
[Music]
watch me again
it's such a shitty song
uh huh says
where's the orange why is it no orange
heresy
that's the right word right
this color discrimination
oh
why is it mummy
he's chasing me and then she went off to
the right side of the map I saw you keep
running around yeah
he was the Imposter because she was
chasing me but she sorry it sounds so
suspicious right now I know I do but you
look suspicious to me and chasing me
around the table but I almost called a
meeting because I was like that's kind
of susp and I was like oh it's movie so
it's just probably just being normal
yeah it's probably
then why did why did Ollie call the
meeting just to check
actually I want to do a little promotion
and among her life
tomorrow yeah sure today why did you go
to the electrical for like one second
and then you went out immediately
oh I was just checking to see who's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there I don't know man that
was kind of sauce yeah yeah
don't have any tasks like inside the
electrical then why won't you go inside
because I just want to see who's inside
and see if I could stick to anyone I
mean Ollie and me were like going out of
the room why why didn't you like go with
us instead where is it sorry where is
this intense
excuse me
and like me and Ollie were like going
out
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
why didn't you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
ah
I'm scared
[Music]
I don't know
come on I'm gonna suck it for now okay
somebody stick with me then oh no thank
you okay
thank you
I wonder is there a personal Vendetta
going on
or
nah could it really be instead of the
Imposter it's always so funny
Ollie is killing me
uh
there we go
oh by the way for the Advent calendar
thing
I think we can make it work
s i
think time wise
it's it is manageable I just need
permission to do it
and well manager's son is sleeping right
now so that's the problem
it's but no I was told that it once the
graphics are completed
then it could be done in a day
we have three days
yeah yeah three days
[Music]
exciting yeah I hope that people will
enjoy it
and that um I can get some then the only
other problem then will be that I get
videos from members to uh
you know fill the calendar
why can't I not open it
I don't know
I didn't have to use a card though how's
that work
yeah and I need I need people to make
videos you know members
but I was thinking if it's only Ian then
it's fine to
do some doubles and some pairings and so
on
Anything is Possible
question
why am I the only one going down
hello oh okay
oh why are there all three of them down
there balance balance
balance non-existent
dude shut up
what up hello
when we were all in the admin room and
then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
teleportation the three of us who were
in the admin room well yeah it wasn't me
phone and Kiana you know what's what's
interesting is that Zeta came after that
yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't I was
like walking I was walking
on teleporting though but that uh Zeta
was like yeah I said I came to admin
because I saw you guys
I was in security we were doing stuff
interesting sauce interesting I'm I'm
suspicious interesting
can you describe the the how many steps
you took to arrive at your destination
but um I'm not gonna say I vanished my
task
I think I need one more I want there's
only a bit left the wiring okay so it
could be a task one yeah but let's kick
out Santa yeah for those who finished
those who haven't who haven't finished
the task
[Music]
uh I'll go with you guys
are we voting Anya we need Anita to vote
oh yeah I'm sorry you guys skipping I I
voted I believe it
no I think you made a good case
oxygenzetta
laughs
let's see what happens oh
[Music]
wait what game over
here
[Music]
good job
yeah cause that was so sad I didn't
teleport by the way
it might have been bad yeah but I can't
have been the pain
[Music]
can I just mention that in the in the
ghost chat they was trying to sing a
Taylor Swift song
I thought you were just ignoring me on
purpose I have no idea how that song I
didn't even know that was a song until
later on oh my god
do you want to maybe try it like I'm
standing there and you might jump
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
slime
[Music]
all right so
um
anything
it's cute is that the winter one the
snowy one yeah
okay that's true
paulus I guess I don't like it that much
but it might be fun okay
[Music]
code there you go
see nothing one second one second for
this map everyone we will be able to use
the excuse that they don't know the map
well so they didn't know where to go oh
I'm in exactly but I'm wrong with truth
I don't know where to go
um
so like I'm gonna get lost a lot yeah oh
yeah let's go
what are the chances
was she saying that for
[Music]
it
I also will not be important but you
know what I learned at some point that
uh
apparently you have to do something at
the top but I don't
I didn't have to do that just now
ah I was like one time when I was the
Imposter in this world I was it was
pointed out to me that I must be the
impossible because I didn't run up to do
the task at the top in the beginning
but it's not a test if you always get
anyway as you can just see
huh
so you don't get it on time
so
so I was not necessarily the impossible
but now now I remember that and I
thought okay I have to go up but there
was nothing to do
oh
BD not karate again well she's not the
impossible
unless unless
I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left room of the
office I did I think so I was in the
office and then I go after you
I was right behind her oh she was like
acting a bit sus in that hallway right
before she entered the right office so
I don't know
yeah but I was behind you
side of the of the office I saw her I
was in the office I was in the office
and then I also finally going away
I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office
I saw you I didn't go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think yeah I
think mommy is near Communications or
something I am yeah
[Music]
are kind of teaming up against Muna
what are we folding oh I don't I don't
know I don't know if there's enough
information or anything
[Music]
lie
foreign
[Music]
I guess I turned it up so he can't see
it oh no
too bad
uh I've huh where is it here
did you see me young
you guys I'm watching too close here
look at the game focus on what they're
saying
Focus
how about how about you do some tasks
chat huh that's not always telling me
okay well we'll do you tasks well I'm
actually doing them how about you do
some tasks
uh how do I get to there
Audrey turn on the lights don't go
I need to
I need ah there we go it's fake wow good
job oh
they needed five whole Live members to
change one light bulb
okay oh wait this one opens normally was
that like lag
what's happening
was that lag before when I couldn't open
the door what's up
what's happening
why is there a hole
are these events in this world
see even when I was impossible once in
this world I did not even use the vents
that's why I don't know
sabotage
yeah that's a band oh
[Music]
seems far away no don't come to
come to me go to the island yeah
okay I think Bales is not the Imposter
that's the only thing I know
besides that I have absolutely no plan
on who could be it
I have no Insight I am useless I am
nothing but
a construction of Flesh and Bones
with no brain
skills
killed flashing bones
my mind
it's probably Anya Muna Anya plays the
game really well I've noticed she's good
at like leading the discussion and
and claiming
claims
fighting her fights
hey I'm like done with my tasks what's
up why is it not everybody also done
with the task
want to come sample dance
I will fix it
I will try
to fix it
I'm done oh oh I'm done with my tasks
[Music]
yeah yeah now I just have to try to not
get killed
wait why does it show that I'm done with
that
oh what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
ouch
why was that so painful for me
oh my God
lava what this world is bigger than I
thought it was oh this is outside
where is everybody
your dad finished your test to win I
have no tasks
is that a bug that up there because I
did it
man Mad World
oh I should not unmute her but I can
oh that's a lot of dead bodies
where where's the body
yeah I didn't go there
oh
fauna and Ollie yeah
yeah we were from the specimen oh wait
he was here we met up with Zetta yeah
yep on the way to the Bay was suspicious
of Muna and I didn't see her the whole
round no I was with Mommy before but I
go with Mommy before yeah I didn't see
nothing but I know I was in the boiler
room still doing my task
yeah
but hmm
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but wait
what side are you guys on
we made right
and we just like stand in there yeah
in the emergency room yeah yeah
oh yeah the office and then finally went
to the specimen room and then we met up
with Anya and then we went yeah
[Music]
the whole time yeah me too so I can't be
on the left side of the map
um where are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah I guess I just wait you said right
side right
voted out yet right that's kind of bad
yeah yeah this is kind of bad I mean
there's two people left right I don't
know man I'm gonna go with Luna Senpai
because
[Applause]
[Music]
only the hair is left the hair survived
is it safe from maguma
anyway what was I saying this only
worked I was only able to convince her
because
it was text
in voice chat it wouldn't work see it's
freaking bugged
how do I how do I say
how do I say
oh that's so good
thanks oh oh there you go crewmate wins
wait who is this
movie she was chasing me at the end
it was Chrome anyway
crowns
I'm not really good at being imposter
guys no I'm not either
I was thinking wait or can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill the kids
I didn't know
wow
yes yes she won
yeah it's a new mode what's there to
explain why did you miss it you should
have prepared and you wouldn't have you
wouldn't have missed it
uh-huh oh yeah what happened right
gaslighting is the victim's fault
[Music]
very intense
hello intense I'm missing one person
who gave up who did friendly father who
is it
uh get in here
I'm sorry oh that's okay I am learning
the game
all right well I think we can at least
squeeze in one more round yeah maybe we
can do one okay okay
[Music]
I'm [\h__\h] cursed I'll be imposter in
the hide and seek ground I never did
that by the way
never did that before
oh see there you go there you go we have
it
it's like a minion game I guess I guess
all of these are mini games what is that
this would look so much better if you
had one of the whole live X Among Us uh
keychains
that they're selling right now but not
for much longer
on the bottom left
oh no it's on the bottom left
uh what how do I go
Flats
wow wow
it's very Electric in here there's I
feel the Sparks are flying
all right what are we doing
old joke reference yeah that joke is
really dead isn't it
how
click or
how what
ah there we go
now it looks
beautiful dragons
[Music]
I I actually one hour is too short I
kind of want to do it longer
it's not crony guys
[Music]
[Applause]
what what you saw it why did you not
report it again
no I was off the security cameras Oh I
saw it what was it what what who was it
could you oh okay
okay wait where was it I see your body's
dead
I saw it on the security cameras it was
mermaid standing over crony's dead body
let me explain no no I was talking crony
earlier to creep her out that was
[\h__\h] fun when she died why didn't you
report her right then and there yeah
what
what she thought that was her natural
state
[Laughter]
poster he will have reported
I didn't see her body
was out I don't know the first part of
the game is the report
[Music]
a little bit yeah I didn't see so I
don't know I have no idea
um
because she was running she was like
there and then she went the opposite
direction so I don't know if she really
didn't see it and why is it always the
same okay
[Music]
imposter I didn't see crony die so I I
think it's Bae honestly but
whoa
and it'll be it'll be all okay
oh
[Music]
I was nice
yeah honestly isn't that her third time
as an imposter and then crony was it
once or twice
but I feel like what is this
ah
I feel like a lot of people are getting
double
why what's going on
I want to
put a push only a second as well what is
this
that was easy I was just switching one
button
I'm on my way I'm on my way finally you
go the other side unless you're the
impostered and don't go
that might have been fun
I have one more task to do
oh you can't go here
sometimes it's hard to see what's an
actual wall
I guess that's a skill issue
koala you can now buy a don't kill me
orange how did you know it's orange
it's real hey
they really scanned me yeah now I feel a
little bit embarrassed to be honest
yeah bye I wonder if they what else they
saw besides Orange
well that was fast I'm done I'm done
I'm done
I'm gonna follow you guys
what's going on what are you guys doing
what are you up to who is not here Muna
is not here
um Let's Stay Together
[Music]
oh
nerve-wracking
okay
be careful
one person has to go left I'll I'll
follow that down let's go together
it's definitely not it
should we do emergency waiting I don't
even know where it is though
where the the button is
nobody has been killed right who should
be alive and who should be dead I wonder
are they all done
it's not quite done I guess balance is
missing one oh
oh oh oh oh
Stay Together Stay Together Stay
Together Stay Together Stay Together
uh she has joined us
yeah bye don't go away
from Wales
oh she just wants to watch the camps
or is that a task because I can't watch
it I guess it's a task
yeah Corona like barely played the game
I feel kind of sorry
I love how we understand without saying
anything to each other that we want to
stay together
isn't that so titty and wholesome
it's to hold a life spirit
[Music]
it's 100 Buddha oh no
even though there's lag
thingy
I'll go check go check come with me
please come with me come with me
it's not here okay
we can't report anything oh it's a task
win
yesterday
oh wait I left voicemail again
I
[Music]
anybody
you did walk over my bed
after moving uh get out everything's
like this is so hard to kill everyone
yeah
[Music]
and I was like bro this can't be real
you see people's names when they're
watching somebody that's no I just saw
your your character your colors
yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah I think you
should be able to like see the colors
um oh yeah well why are you looking at a
camera babe that's creepy
but but you guys instead not in like one
step but have like a different style so
I just like oh this is hard to it
it is hard I think everybody should be
off on their own and isolated at all
times honestly
[Music]
can we just maybe do one more round and
in case someone gets imposter who
already got impossible before we restart
I just couldn't try but it feels like
bugs or so yeah
I'm going to kill all of you
someone who gets it again
okay yeah if someone gets it like well
I'm getting them
already got it already Okay oh wait but
once that narrow down here
oh yeah oh yeah that was yeah you want
to play one more round doesn't matter
who imposter is okay
let's do this well like if we get a
little imposter again either Muno or me
just do the emergency meeting okay
okay I found an imposter I'll be
throwing it
oh [\h__\h]
oh man wait this is
really crony
because she was like oh [\h__\h]
and it was a joke right
is it inside
so bad
I am
I am cursed it seems
why
[Music]
wait oh yeah
what I I saw someone but I don't know
who it was because I wasn't looking at
the screen but there was someone running
what where am I again
Rockets right oh yeah yeah by the
Rockets
I I was stalking fauna and then it got
dark and I lost sight of her but then I
saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again I think yes
the rocket oh uh it's nearby the
laboratory
oh that's so far
weapons all I'm saying is that I'm like
on the left side of the map
did whoever was did they cross paths
with you or did you see them escape to
the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interesting
oh I did see crony run however I don't
know
I thought it wasn't true
so okay I will fess up
I I did get it again what
what but like
should you cast me out now
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
[Laughter]
we'll just continue like that
I will I will imaginary kill people I
will just act as if I did it
so like if I'm in pause for a good
should I just out myself and just
everything
like it narrows it down too much so I'm
not sure we can really do that I mean we
could just keep crony around
kill anyone I'll just do sabotage
[Laughter]
I'm not doing much
it's just sabotaging
oh oh that was close oh man
well at least she's honest she's very
honest at least honest
okay
what
I wonder who's the other one at least
it's not Luna right
and I think if it was
maybe she would say something
funny again
this game is so rigged
Apple
I have to do something about it I will
have to
rig the game back
like fun now you and me
I feel some chemistry
feels good opening these doors
oh it's just straight ahead
easy mode that's why you have to remake
the lobby every time yeah but like last
time that issue didn't really exist
last time we played the game I feel like
that wasn't an issue
I think I just heard a cat meow in the
distance Mao
uh
stabilized stabilize okay
one out of two
hop
probably didn't do it I guess she can't
do it because she's imposter
oh no
she was still so young you know who it
is why did you have to go she was like
in the hallway on the left side of the
map she was like a like a child to me
yeah thingy
she's in like the middle left okay in a
hallway who was with someone was with me
at stabilizer so they're also safe
um I I was walking up with you but then
I went to the left and I met crony and
she was coming from that area but I
guess she didn't she didn't touch it I
don't think crony did it yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's okay
yeah anything can happen it must be the
other imposter
Fisher friends not food are you girls
skipping
I kind of um
I'm just gonna try to kick out honestly
I choose bonna at this point
[Laughter]
and then muted herself immediately to
not get any backlash for it
[Music]
she really did okay
no answer refuses to explain
does not want to be confronted
you're an adult
you have to
deal with the consequences of the things
that you do
what
ah
I have to read the temperature oh my God
this is a reference to Lord of the Rings
it definitely is right
unfortunately I have no ring
no ring foki Wawa
[Music]
oh man you still thinks huh do you
really think so
okay scan again
[Music]
don't let them know it's my it's my
secret it's a maiden Secret
if they didn't see Noni
and I'll go on you this time you guys
walked a long path
jingle bells jingle bell
foreign
[Music]
sound was bugged just now
ah I'm playing that come again
[Music]
sick beats
oh that was my limit if they added one
more I don't know if I could have done
it am I done
more before I leave
holy [\h__\h] my right monitor is flashing
so badly like flashing as in
kind of like
it's like shaking vibrating
[Music]
oh my God I don't want to look at it
yeah flickering like this is
you know another weird thing about never
mind
uh oh wow I have a I have I have a
theory it's like Romeo and Juliet
romantic
[Music]
I have I have a very big Theory okay I
was sussing uh Zeta
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since Connie came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that then came
out after meeting Anya
um Annie isn't the type that would be um
going on herself doing duties just to
get in anyone's trust if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me so it's either KR Senpai
or bae but that's just a zombie Theory
I was with you I was I was scared but I
was imposter I could have killed you
right
or maybe your cooldown was not done yet
solid argument but I don't know
dwindling to the final people so if you
waste a if you waste the thing we're
gonna we're gonna lose by the way the
body was at
um beside the weapons is that weapons
well you better choose someone yeah like
between weapons and admin
I out because like if there's like two
boxes left
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
but like really big props to like the
other imposters
Let's Stay Together and finish tasks I'm
done by the way yeah
bye
[Music]
when did her eyebrows stay alive
wait one more I have one more tasks
tasks task I can't say it singular
Stay Together
oh
I choose this one
oh they're staying with me
I'm blinding
um spicy
faster faster faster
okay my job here is done my job is done
my task
Castle
yes
who was it who was it who was it
hey
I'm sorry
in the Back Bay you stopped me where in
the back
they was on a killing spree wow yeah I
felted in my spine when you did it
respect to the ones who stayed alive and
finished the tasks
oh honestly I was dead and had to finish
the tasks I think it was me
but I did it okay if that's possible
since it was hard for the other imposter
I thought it was someone red but I
wasn't looking at my screen I was like
what are they red no
no
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter I
guess
[Music]
we should remake the room though
and the killing time is like 10 like the
lowest 10 seconds pretty much they have
to try and kill every everyone before
they finish
do you know who the Seeker is yeah yeah
so you have to you have to say that
you're the Imposter when you get it okay
and you've set the the running speed to
the fastest whoever's making the room
okay if
you're the Imposter and then yeah okay I
have no player speed on Max I have to oh
my God that is so fast
[Applause]
[Music]
no report 10 seconds
wow
[Music]
so wait how many should I do
less or more two should be good or two
to four
yes
how are we gonna finish that no possible
so it's no recording though nobody no
reporting which which oil do you want to
do
do you want to do the normal one for now
yeah
[Music]
hello go wild yeah okay oh you can hear
each other screaming oh my god
let's go let's go
it will be cronie
again
[Music]
I'm just giving you a head start
okay
everybody
she has 10 seconds 10 seconds
wait you're are you faster
it's impossible
[Music]
oh God
let's just say yes yes
faster
I'm just gonna oh you guys the division
I'm just gonna speed right
[Music]
a lot is everywhere
anyway oh my God oh my God oh my God
play the elevator music oh my god oh my
god
let's go
[Music]
you don't need to wait what do you mean
I haven't killed anyone in a while
oh okay okay
yes yes it's a dangerous place what is
this oh I'm so fast
everybody
[Music]
wait is it only is it only me and Bay
now
[Music]
um
go grab a coffee
and who what's up
[Music]
I don't think so we can haunt her oh
repent for your sins
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no I was gonna I was gonna click the
use button yeah
[Music]
it's actually harder than I thought
five seconds I don't know and we're
gonna hide it and give them five seconds
I think it's good I think it's well
balanced but oh you can challenge hide
again because we got in the middle now
fine hide again four three
two
do the ghosts have to be done too
[Music]
one more one more one
I did not make that this is possible
wow wow
it would work so that we would win what
what good job
[Music]
um
okay just waiting for him
okay but I'll change should I change
something any Improvement advice
was actually okay
if I hadn't messed up I would have won
so oh okay I think okay skilly shoe all
right you have to play well if you want
to win it's awesome
I don't actually don't I don't actually
want to be it so please no thank God
okay wait we should restart
okay okay this game is so broken well we
could just do an emergency
um yeah oh yeah you can kick her out
[Laughter]
the description and for the the whole
live one you only have a couple hours
left so if you wanted to get it but
didn't do it yet then go do it do it do
it
just do it just do it
dude
contrast of all the ingredients they can
do it is incredible me
or what will it be fun again or no we
want easy actually
oh yeah
oh wait was everyone there
[Music]
[Applause]
should we do tests during the countdown
or no no we're already doing it I'm
already doing it
wait okay yeah
[Music]
okay stop counting please wait what
so
[Music]
it started
oh man I think it's time
no idea
is broken
no more keys
[Music]
Miracle now well this is peace
in the cafeteria right now you don't
need to go looking for me
[Music]
I can't do the card
s
hello
not in the cafeteria at all
every time I was doing a white TV
one more time finally
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's all my fault it's all my fault
if we lose it's my fault yes
yes oh let's get hard ones
I already mentally gave up on that one
how's it going woman
[Music]
wow
you are scary
[Music]
I'm so sorry
that was fun I never got that did anyone
beside me never get imposter I mean I
never I never got only an onion me we
are cursed
yeah I know right it's not fair
I'm going to sue someone I don't know
who but I'm going to Susu probably maybe
yes Susu just like the Sims say or hello
no
no oh
please give me
how do I say please give me
uh it depends that you can at least give
you can always just say
uh something dong
s
[Music]
oh my God
Wally I'm surprised you didn't bait me
to say
I will marry you or something like that
this was your choice your one chance
like
anyway guys
right now it's gonna end soon oh I'm
gonna show you yeah in like 12 hours I
think so maybe 10 minutes guys
acrylic stand
yeah t-shirt
all right
[Music]
yeah
thank you for joining so spontaneously
especially to the ID members who already
did their homework
[Music]
for you guys to thank you yeah it was
really fun thank you
thank you everyone take care
Take Care thank you and get some sleep
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]