[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
everyone's okay john mute go go
[Music]
wow
welcome everyone to the first ever full
whole live english collaboration
[Music]
[Applause]
wonderful i hear a lot of motivated met
crewmates only crewmates of course
test
we're going to talk about it especially
about you finally it doesn't matter if
you hide behind that little
waffle center
this is
i just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little
testing session
and uh we just wanted to play the game
seriously for once and then uh after a
little while we had no reports which was
kind of us so fanna
did an emergency meeting and just to you
know because she was obviously scared
and which i was too
um
she reported okay she did an emergency
meeting and then what do we see free
deaths
of course she's not sus because she made
the meeting but turns out she was the
imposter how reckless is that
not to mention she killed so many people
so easily
mommy was my imposter and she got voted
out in the first round immediately
immediately oh hard carry oh wait stand
up live as an imposter was so short
yeah your stream hasn't started yet
oh
[Music]
i was reading chat um
everybody forgot to start the stream
stand by yeah
yet what's happening
all right then um so i would like to get
some introductions from everyone hey may
stream up yet
is everyone
are you ready
yes are we all ready yes are we good
yeah okay i have a stream going okay um
you guys all around me
it's like by
narrow yeah
self-introduction can you all go girls
give me a reason why you are not suss
today starting from amelia girl
oh why i'm not fuss today um
[Music]
number one detective and um i'm not
wearing pants
that's like us
this is
your introduction please
is about across our council representing
chaos everybody how you doing um
because we have to probably
sorry i'm sorry okay i'm not suss
because um i got a cute pet look at my
pet
it's my pet
yeah
[Music]
i saw the hamster thing and i was like i
gotta i gotta
yes
um
next person please
wow that's kind of kind of weird but
interesting
well definitely not us
your turn next all right um so yeah um
death is real sus but guess what
everyone i'm not death i'm the sheriff
around these parts and because i'm the
sheriff the sheriff is never suss the
sheriff obviously didn't do it um
some people may say i i shot the sheriff
but i did not shoot the deputy meaning
uh i don't know what that means it just
has something to do with the sheriff and
i'm not sure i'm not suspect so there
you go that's very good
whatever you can't even spell sheriff
right
okay now that was because now that was
because there wasn't enough room for for
me to spell it correctly
no my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
you
about that poisonous
plant
no no no no no
poisonous the non-poisonous variety
poison
you've already killed enough people for
today so your deed is done
exactly performers
no no no plant has never killed anyone a
little shock of horrors does it ever
here what's up everybody oh i'm not such
because
um
[Music]
i don't believe likely story i don't
believe in
sexy backgrounds
oh hi
it's iris whole live english project cup
video
singer
uh
i am very excited i
am 100 say so i would never lie
i would never recess
sorry hustle me in my face
everything i would never i would never
do anything irish don't trust her child
iris yes no trash
pirates that's not what happened to my
fox yesterday
[Music]
i have to say uh iris uh
a very very um
good self-introduction while other
people mostly just say hey my name is
[Applause]
oh yes
hello my name is cronie oro from
the council
and
i am blue
yeah
your senpai has stolen your color
but i'm a more royal color royal girl
so
okay
okay where's the blue okay don't look at
the color objectively look at the color
that's inside all of us oh that's quite
red it's crazy
um
wait did cronie say well she's nuts us
oh right i'm not sus because look at
this
i'm wearing a mask i am doing my part
in this situation don't get close to me
[Laughter]
well i tried to social distance but i'm
not sons because i'm doing my part in
the society
and
i'm an upholding
oh no
we got cut
i got kicked out did anyone else get
kicked out everybody got kicked out
one second inactivity i'm opening lobby
lobby is created code is uh there yeah
um we should have done intros here to be
honest
you know we had a problem with the
servers last time right like during the
test oh yeah that's true
let me just this is just because of our
inactivity it's not a server problem
don't worry it's all good
it says could not find a room is what it
says oh no
oh wait i missed typed oh no wonder okay
okay okay
there you go sorry
all right
let's see is it possible to yeah
quality in the middle of the stream or
is it too late it's too late
there we go
[Music]
no
i am the guardian of civilization and i
am an apex predator of the sky
um i i might not i no taxi back seat
hello i am you know my ian is from hall
of english
um
the
priestess of the ancient ones
i think
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh
i am not sauced because i'm already dead
look at the the halo above my head
[Music]
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you ina
next up sana is not streaming but she's
here so yeah
[Music]
english council
uh it's been a while hello guys
i'm going to take it off and take all of
you down with me
oh that's trending no no we're just
gonna really reassure you back into back
into the space where you belong right or
actually you're a part of this
you should be fine you should be fine if
you get kicked out i have no i have no
reason to
alarm well
i'm very happy to have you here sana
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming thank you
[Music]
and
i am the one organizing this and i'm
really happy that we could all get
together 11 people is a lot but we're
going to have a lot of fun today so
let's get right into it are you girls
directly to be
[Music]
all right let's go
the crewmate oh dear what's this
i don't understand this man
hi there
we just have a lot of more
oh by myself now um what's up chad i
won't be looking at chat too much
um because hi
i can't oh the stairs oh
it's a helicopter
it's the helicopter
how do you what are you
wait
wait wait wait meaning thank you
i'm trying to find the meeting room
but do you know where the meeting room
is
don't hurt me
no i'm trying to find the meeting room
i'm trying to find the meeting room
[Music]
oh
i saw
wow
no it was right in front of my face i
know
no i was moving my face no
i'm sorry hold on i'm black screened
again
no not again we just got started should
we do a new lobby i don't know if it's
gonna be any better though
i'll try fixing it but maybe i don't
know maybe reinstall a mangas or
something like that because you had that
before we can always we can reach that
if we need we can restart we can respond
yeah we can restart but who should we
kill off before that
no it was
telling you i needed to go to the
meeting room no
middle thingy there a record okay uh
okay
where did you spawn
i spawned in the in the i was by myself
it was the room with the folder on the
table oh records okay i resorted to
spawn
uh where did i spot let me look at the
map real quick uh being a detective
i i do not have never really played this
map um i think somewhere like in the
main hall
okay well me sana and cronie all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked the vital
screen down there and callie two people
were already dead yeah they were already
fauna and cali were already dead so
whoever spawned with them there were two
killers
[Music]
right high school i have to do it
uh
i appreciate it what's it really right
iris
that's true
you guys are making the wrong decision
you guys
[Music]
um
wait what do we do
what do we do
okay hold on let me check the map what's
going on um i've never played this map
before
so i don't know what's going on
i'm safe
i'm safe calm down
[Music]
look
i'm safe
i need to go to i'm still trying to find
the freaking meeting room oh it's over
there okay
how do i use that thing
i can't go to how do i use that thing
well
okay we're going to go main hall let's
go to the main hall
alrighty alrighty alrighty alrighty
[Music]
well what's happening what did i just
whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
crash course what's that
you kill
[Music]
i'm scared i'm sticking with kia i don't
know i'm wondering right now if we
should if we should close the lobby to
let inna
test it out again should we
why
i got sabotaged what is this
it's absolutely ridiculous
redonkulous
redonkulous i i'm hearing voices
where am i
okay
i'm lost
okay we're gonna go okay let's go down
here
i'm gonna go down here
okay
into the engine room okay i see i where
is everybody hello
oh nobody here
what's this
all the lights interesting interesting
we gotta go fix the lights
gotta go fix the lines
okay
looking
interesting
kitchen clean vent where is the kitchen
kitchen where am i
whoa
hello no no no i'm not staying with you
why i'm sad can you trust me please can
you please trust me i huh
nobody trust me i'm sad
where's the kitchen
i do not see kitchen
oh no understand hi
hi
why am i suspicious i've done nothing
wrong this is so
it's discriminatory
this is discriminatory
um
[Music]
i have found this body but i have
absolutely no clues because i was
running around a while here and i i
met no one close by there was so i guess
someone vented yeah you were seen last
with sana what do you have to say about
that
so who's done with their tasks right now
because i'm done i'm not done yet
i'm not i've been also done this entire
time huh
i can say though well it says told has
completed but i think that's something
that an imposter can do like show
that shall we the delay that it's i
think they can fake that i don't know
i've heard it yesterday anyway uh i
think crony can vouch for me that i'm
not stressed right crony what do you
think
well i i know that watson and sauna were
definitely safe because the killings
took place when uh all of us were still
around and the only people who are
considered suspicious to me would be
rei or kiara
why is that i've done nothing girl is
definitely uh
[Music]
bae okay first and see if the uh the
taskbar goes up when she does the
mission
um
you know what i think that's us it
doesn't sound pretty
i don't
the whole way like how amelia is trying
to control this whole room yeah i don't
know i don't like it no no no watson's
definitely in the clear because i was
with her
with sauna
well i can't
that's undo of suspicious what if i
don't vote because i got stuck in the
bathroom for the entirety of the last
round because i don't i didn't know how
to open the door i don't know who to
vote for it yeah i don't know
with your guts
i feel like if it wasn't based you'd
i was cleaning my guts out of the toilet
i couldn't see anything i thought it was
bae but maybe it's kiara yeah i am not
involved
[Music]
oh you choose where you load in yeah
oh okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay bye bye
wait where did she go
okay
[Applause]
i'm following you guys
okay great yeah good
good
are you done with your pasts um no i'm
lost
where are you going um i think i need to
go to the
where am i going uh
waiting room
oh you didn't hear that
[Music]
oh
wait no
that's not the way
wait no let's not hit
where am i
where am i going
um
up we
go here up we go here we go here what is
this place
i remember something happened in here
but um interesting okay
okay
up here
[Music]
you're so annoying
thank
god we go
[Music]
oh
and i left her and i ran around because
i'm done with my tasks and i found good
ass dead bunny
self-reported
no i've been trying if you have been
with me i couldn't find anyone i was
trying to find a buddy
where have you been where have you been
just now just now
hold on let me look at the map where was
i um
i was
let's make this quick though so that ina
can come back oh immediately okay well
if you really want to end the game vote
kiara literally suss no no no no no no
no no no no no no
i was i was checking um bae and the
surveillance camera and
she wasn't really doing her tasks she
was just walking around around the
i mean were you doing tasks yes
what were you doing what was the last
task you did um it was in the
was the exact mission
uh it was emptying
emptying the trash in main hole
uh-huh
like a diamond ruby emerald diamond cold
for example was my code and then i would
have had to go to the other side to
input it likely
that is that the
um
i think it's between
storage and like developing room the
question question question room well
i know for a fact i had just seen kiara
like right next to me
uh we were together by the doors that
opened and closed and then electric and
somebody but
was the one who reported the body too
right yeah this is my second body i'm
reporting yes
self-reporting what
come on
[Laughter]
disgusting
i was so close i was so freaking close
no
it was iris and bay
in the room and it looked like iris
i couldn't i was feeling cool down
because i'm pretty sure i killed them
i was
[Laughter]
[Music]
getting that connection eric again i'm
gonna try to open one new lobby okay
okay okay okay
all right
all right we leave we leave the room
right oh do we leave yeah ah bye-bye all
right
[Music]
we were so close
everybody we were so close
i should have just voted for kiara i
thought that was going to make me look
even more sus but we should have just
voted for kiara and had to toss off
damn it
it's okay
first game
hello hey hey ladies ladies
[Music]
and i always think whoever says it first
is suspicious
i feel like imposters are usually very
quiet like they try not to talk because
they don't want to unless they're very
experienced in that sense yeah
yeah
people are usually the ones into the
[Music]
oh no wait
all right which one of you suckers is
the imposter um probably you callie it's
probably you
oh so it's cali
it's callie okay
but i'm pretty small right now you come
around corner crow
i do now
okay
no this is a cool kid's corner go away
to the frog
did you kill them
revenge or anything right yeah it was
kind of hard
she pushed the fox down the hole oh
imagine if it was your child that you
pushed down the hole huh
no no no it was it was an adoption and
you know it doesn't matter anymore right
because you know isn't getting in i'm
ready to lobby one more time
[Music]
no no
oh no
[Music]
let ina made the room oh maybe i can do
that hold on
maybe like you know
balance the whole time hello that's true
hello hello
um maybe we should make uh let inna make
the room maybe
uh
[Music]
this one doesn't work it works for me
mummy got in wait let me try
but we can
we can let inna try about
no problems
[Music]
oh yeah okay yeah yeah let's you might
get the same or error or dodo
because i got the same error uh when i
tried to creating the lobby before the
stream many times just try again again
again
oh wait my ping is fifth
oh that's why my ping is not that not
that good
what is even angel guys don't worry the
angel side of me is nerfing me
in this game yes
oh hide the screen when typing code
that's right oh yes looks like where oh
ina
is there a new club
no all right i'm having trouble making
the room too so it's just like
the servers
yeah
maybe maybe we can try i i don't really
think it's closer but let's try maybe an
asian server
we can we can try you can try with the
traffic you want to try you know or
should maybe someone else you guys can
try someone else can try making it okay
i'll make one eight in asia everyone
change to asia
okay
raja
code is
oh wait are should we not
name this on stream
oh
[Music]
just just going without me
i wanna yeah
no no no
muting
it increases very good
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry
without you
there they are
oh yeah
fun
we don't mean
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
oh i'm about myself
oh hello
hello
romaine hey
are you safe are you safe why are you
quiet hello
i just felt so bad hello hello
maybe try refreshing the brother curling
there's a refresh button on the top left
hello sometimes that'll fix it
hello
i am
good rest
this round this round i am very good
right you know these things remind me of
the squid game things you know the squid
game thing sorry guys i can't really
read chat while we're playing the
ultimate sus game
um but we're gonna still try
hello i heard you did you hear me hello
bye-bye
[Music]
okay must not be too trusting
how do i get up there
oh
no oh hi hi oh hi
hello
i could just eat yeah
the only thing i can say about that is
that i heard kelly's voice close by for
a moment but that was like i didn't even
see her close by i only found the body
like a a few moments later wait wait
where did you find the body behind the
body uh we're very bottom right
in bed
but i wasn't i wasn't doing anything i
was like looking for a task to do well
why were you not doing tactics i don't
think you're done with tasks we just got
started there's a lot of tasks i doubt
it it's a bit okay
it's a really big map
i saw her coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which is on the bottom
left side the cali passed by me
that's very funny hahaha time to kill
hahaha
me enough
and kelly spawn together but kelly went
off pretty um
i was pretty lucky
i was pretty lost i wouldn't
stick around with anybody around but
cali just went zoom
up
you just said that you did you weren't
doing any tests now you said you weren't
doing the tasks
oh god i don't have to play the [\h__\h]
game
if you really don't know how to play the
game i will give you a tip now a serious
tip press tab to open the map so you can
run around while seeing the tasks and
that is very easy
[Music]
yeah i'm not sure
i'm
[Music]
this collaboration again
interesting oh wow okay enough to throw
me out
really
oh no no no i think it has to be two
doesn't
it i don't know jordy i think it's
majority
for now
[Music]
here hey
hello let's go to the break hello
hi
tab oh
wow
electrical i'm far from that bring it
hold on
all right okay
what did i do
what's that what's happening what's
happening
[Music]
hi guys
i'm going down to the viewing deck
nobody kill me when i'm downloading
[Music]
okay we're good
hi emo yeah
wait wait where where where is the thing
where do we go wait wait wait up here
here this way wait wait this way
no up this way
oh someone fixed it
yes
yeah
you are so sucks you are so sad
try me i'm gonna press the button you
are so sucked did you say come here
i'm going to keep that in mind
[Music]
wait what oh
that's pretty sus
um
that is quite sus
no no go away go away
everybody says wait no
that is quite sus
bono was muttering to herself hold on a
second what was she muttering to herself
oh
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
i was in the i was in the the cockpit
i was about to go uh to the very very
bottom um
who used the toilet
please i was not anywhere near that area
toilet because i this
is wanted to go inside the toilet but it
was locked for me
um because when i found iris's body
right as i hit report the door the
bathroom door closed
someone hid in the
i was trying to put the egg on the uh
the frying pan
i was tracking her and she was muttering
to herself and we were alone in one of
the rooms to my chat i was talking to my
channel
[Music]
no i wasn't looking at chat i was just
talking to them so they didn't have to
listen to nothing
i was talking to you was i not
i told you you could kill me
at the last moment where were you i was
also in i was in the area below in the
bathroom i was doing the task where you
pick everything up off the floor and
guru i did see me there but i didn't go
up i came from the other side someone's
in the bathroom
someone's in the bathroom in the
bathroom
i don't know where it was
here's a better proposition whoever's in
the bathroom wait
when we spawn back in while i see you
come out no no i think we respond we
resent ourselves
somewhere else
all right in the very beginning i
spawned with uh inner and fawful i can
vouch for
i just remembered
yeah just because you spawn with them
you can't vouch for them
i mean i was running around with sana at
one point
lost
okay
okay i don't know well found ourselves
for now foreign
if you say so
but are you guys really just not talking
we are talking we just don't say come
here who says come here
no one says come here
unless you're stuck we are talking about
ourselves
um hello
quiz hello that's kind of scary yo
connection
oh wow that's kind of cool
oh found it
i found it no
well oh there we go
good connection we got good connection
good connection very good
okay we good
i can also hide this i just realized
there we go
all right
um where else do we have to go
electrical we're going to electrical
they all keep saying that they do really
like weird tasks oh hello santa hi
hi bae
are you looking at um
[Music]
okay interesting interesting i don't say
anything
they wouldn't see anyone wesley what's
the other place
is following cali interesting oh now
chiara ran away
if callie's dead kiara is the one who
killed wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait
wait wait wait wait we gotta go check
hold on how do we go check where are we
um
we gotta go up to the mix gotta figure
it out i just gotta fight okay no you're
good you're good you're good do we look
at this oh my gosh
what's happening
i'm just lost
i saw something sus
i was uh in the top right area that's
like uh before the wreck
right yeah around the records area yes
and um when i was about to enter the
rankings area i saw kelly so i wanted to
say hi so i followed her and oh next
moment she completely disappeared i went
i went into all other like like uh
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared
man
you can vouch for me i went down to the
bottom and tried to go through the vent
and i couldn't hi partner
you tried to do something
let me speak let me speak
okay
what i mean is there was a vent down
there and i couldn't get through it
because i'm not the [\h__\h] imposter
that's
[Music]
that's the second time that she says the
second time guys i'm just saying it's
the second time out for me she just
wants she just wants me to get thrown
out
has a bandana
i don't know
why else would you call this a [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting kiara
could be the next level imposter tactic
is true it could be
i i still don't know
[Music]
i'm gonna skip for now i don't think
there's enough yeah
you don't have to vote i just wanted to
mention it
okay
[Laughter]
interesting interesting
okay so we got furnace sauce and we got
cali sauce
last time it wasn't either i'm just
saying
right
we gotta put our detective brains on for
a second
first was fullness us now it's cali
sauce
i'm gonna go back to the place where we
can look at
their actions
what room is that
oh no
that's not it
wait
oh wait i have a task here
oh no no no no no
oh hey
hi
what's up here
i don't know actually hello hello i
don't know how hi
how are you going to be this one hello
has anybody ever done this this one it's
like this files oh i don't have that one
i don't have it either
and i don't
i haven't played it very much
what's your next task
my next task is i have a lot a vault
right now we which is closer how do you
get around the ladder uh you can use it
how do you get this thing you can't you
have to go to the other side
what the heck
[Music]
are they gonna go around
okay you guys want to stick together yes
please up here together
okay
okay oh that scared me okay
oh [\h__\h]
oh
that one was me boys
found her in the kitchen
walking around doing my normal sharing
which i normally what the [\h__\h] what do
you say
that was amazing
[Laughter]
i think we can vouch for each other um
we saw at the end right before the body
was reported we saw ina and gura
together um
and carol was with us too actually
yeah yeah they're fine they're all fine
which kind of leaves them
kelly
are you kidding me well
trying to save her reputation by
reporting the body she killed trying to
[Music]
um but we also gotta remember we haven't
killed often imposter yet because all of
these have been bodies that we found so
there's still two impostors here
so one of you guys is lying okay you
live in groups all right well i don't
like you pointing the finger at me bae
and i think that's suspicious so i'm
going to point it right back at you
it off on your boy i'm just trying to be
a good [\h__\h] sheriff okay interesting
interesting
sheriff sorry sorry are you kidding me
it's it's nothing personal it's just
i'm loving this
kiara you're next hold on you sound very
sassy
last time when you were
it isn't now
santa's awfully quiet and so is moon mae
what have you guys been doing yeah
they've been with me
and i've been laughing at cali
no one's standing up for me when i when
i like literally why would i could have
killed you if you guys were alone but i
did [\h__\h] nothing anyone
who would vouch for callie is there
anyone i haven't seen callie that's the
only thing i haven't seen callie either
like that's the west side of me
why are you pointing your finger at me
you haven't seen me
because i'm
[Laughter]
hmm we're in trouble
we're in trouble
dude but at this point everyone had
something about someone vouching
okay i need to finish my time
hello oh jesus
oh god
excuse me
hello
oh no can someone handle that
[Music]
sorry can someone handle that i need to
do my tasks
okay don't kill me don't kill me don't
kill me don't kill me don't kill me i'm
trying to find the oh are you doing this
one already right side i'm doing left
side someone has to go to the right side
okay three eight five one two three
wait i can't the freaking thing's on the
other side okay um
we gotta go around we gotta go around
[Music]
wait
here is not
wait a second
[Music]
is this on it
oh yeah yeah okay okay we got it we got
it you've been here awfully long you
know
you know
you know i got the butt from ina i know
the wrong thing
hello
what's up what passed yeah
[Music]
i have all my tasks done by the way i'm
going to save a few girls okay i have
holly and i think we know who it is now
mimi
[Music]
oh no the lights oh
i mean
i guess it doesn't necessarily mean that
it's mummy but okay
okay okay and it says i can't reach that
oh someone did one light okay
how do you get to the lights i am so
lost i'm just gonna do my tasks because
i'm just lost
um okay
nice we gotta go to electrical very nice
very nice nobody killed me thank you i'm
just a good little rat why can't i go
through there
that's absolutely ridiculous
that's ridiculous
why someone blocked off electrical
no one blocked off electrical i'm just
stupid
i'm just stupid
i see
it's a maze i see wait hold on i can
pass through here
okay okay uh we gotta go through here we
gotta go to the carpet oh let's have a
look what's everyone doing
i don't
see
me
that makes me look suspicious
is
[Applause]
i understand that i've been on my own
but and i understand i will be voted out
but it was kiara and it was ina um why
was it me and why was it inaudible
do i dare say
what do you mean
enough to say
kept saying that she was lost and i
thought that it was
suspicious isn't that what you were
saying this is not my first time
my first time subscribe please describe
with your own words the uh past tasks
that you have been done doing
what was the last house that you did the
last one i did was the one where i had
to dress up a mannequin
and then i had to use the card
and i kept having to do the guard
with my gut
and going with my gut feeling i'm gonna
grow my guts too even though he's been
awfully quiet
he has been really quiet hasn't she
oh okay i think i know who else it is
got my eyes on you
if it doesn't end it's enough no no
it's it's ina santa ada
no
gets in the way how do you get to the
emergency emergency thing
run away run away run away run away run
away run away run away no we cannot let
her win
we cannot let them win
[Music]
she's gonna kill me
okay we got it we got it we got it
no don't come here
wait wait no ina it's not me no no i'm
serious it's not me are you sure yeah
sure if it's not you it's either you or
kiara it's either you or chiara
[Music]
that was not that was not your boy's
victory that was definitely not right
no i felt really bad
[Music]
please ask a question in polynomial work
anymore okay yeah so i have a question
so when you're imposter and you're like
going pretending to do tasks etc can
others tell if there isn't really a task
there to do uh no
you know what
but
like if you're doing certain like if
you're asking to do tasks that should be
probably longer because there's really
long time and you kind of can't stand
out that you're oh
oh i'm so sorry can we make a new quote
sorry that's my fault that's my fault
sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
sorry oh no okay
my bad
sorry that was my fault
i'm sorry guys
i'm sorry no problems
no problem new code is out there now
okay thank you
hello
um
very smooth
smooth entrance okay i can't use that
card anymore yeah
wait did i link it again i don't know i
don't know this game i haven't played
only
give us a statement of how you were able
to hide your imposter-ness for so long
[Music]
with the crowd you know even if i could
make the kill i i i waited for my chance
i was patient are we okay
the performance was so genuine you
actually found my heart's name i know
[Music]
those were my last words
okay is everyone here in i think i was i
think my game was still showing so i can
hear you watson was laughing in my ears
the whole time
[Applause]
we don't have an actual imposter are you
sure okay
okay okay here we go
okay
i'm sorry guys
how recent is this man
i'm never gonna be the impossible
yeah that's fine that's a lot of
stressful i wish i
okay
we got crewmate again interesting okay
[Music]
let's just do the task
the the discussions really rile up hi
[Music]
what you doing right off there
okay still scooping still scoping
everybody out okay
nobody please kill me please nobody kill
me nobody kill me
nobody kill me lose my innocence right
that was so cool
[Music]
excuse me hello can i have the floor
please
excuse me i have a question
was the shark near the washroom no
questions at this time okay i saw i was
with kiara and i just took kiara go left
and then i saw guru was also in the room
that kiara went oh right man i don't
know that doesn't mean it wasn't ina i
watched it
for me she was right behind me
no you was right beside me you were by
yourself in electrical because i was
humming about no no no
i was humming the berries in cream tune
and i was like i know where electrical i
didn't hear that i died because that's
where you killed me last time so that's
ah sure girl sure
[Music]
did i stop by the washroom i spawned and
i spawned in the place with the folder
on the table and i went right down to
electrical i don't remember how what
path never stopped by the washer
[Music]
[Laughter]
she wasn't in the washroom
we just spawned it
i don't know i'm pretty i'm pretty
convinced can i can i have a moment
because she didn't
can shower have a moment please please
no enemies has suddenly flip-flopped her
story she's gone from meek and shy to
very suddenly very demanding of the
rooms i do see
i was gonna say obviously
i walked in on you yeah
i don't know you are i can say thank you
i have nothing to say about everything i
believe
is
please i would love to have a follower
um
hello
hello what's up
[Music]
nice
um
where's my next test up here we gotta go
to the lounge
is anyone in the toilet
okay we could be clean we clear
okay
okay be clear
that reminds me of like the monsters ink
scene way like oh hello somebody's in
the showers be careful
okay let's go oh brad
there's a real thing to do in the
bathroom stall what do we do in the
bathroom stall
sometimes you have a um what do you call
it like a task here a plunger oh
okay so iris is clean okay she's clean
she's clean i'm gonna have it okay whoa
so many people i'm just going
around i'm just doing my toss too
okay
it's on the other freaking side
there's three of us in here so if none
of us were the impossible we should all
be cool together
oh no
please protect me inner's here eno was
here enough here
oh
i swear i swear babe
no
trust me please protect me do the trash
can
here okay you guys protect me while i do
the trash can okay i got your back i got
your back i got your back i got your
back i'm scared of you she tricked me
once how do i think room from here yeah
try
trash okay there it is hold on i just
gotta shake it except for the go
guys i'm doing the laundry okay
i feel really good about myself right
now oh no the lights oh the lights are
fake
come on trash nice
okay then we go up here we go oh no
i'm gonna go here oh my god
okay
got it
uh
three five four four zero okay
what
oh we gotta go
okay
[Music]
um two two three four two
okay
i got it
[Music]
uh two two oh no
five one no
five three one nine zero
okay i got it fixing this thing wait
damn i'll get it wait what i swear i got
it what
oh i like that bae i kind of spooked me
a little bit the way that you that you
kind of came after me there no no no i
was trying to get the
wait did she sabotage
oh okay good okay you're good okay thank
you thank you thank you i got it
that is so weird wait wait please listen
to me listen to this story what's up can
can you can
no no no can the impostor sabotage like
you know how just then we had like the
left side and the right side the code
thingy
right do we have to enter at the same
time is that why
because i entered the course so i i just
came i was alone that's why i i thought
everyone was on the other side and i was
trying to get there and i was like wait
i'm lost and i ended up being on the on
the right side of the map
okay because i entered the code for both
sides
like i entered the code on the right
side and it said it was okay and enough
was also there so i went back to the
left side to do it but it said the right
side was not activated
it's it's
gurah
yeah i kept telling her not to follow me
and she just got saved
[Music]
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know i go
for that kill yeah she was saying i have
a question
okay how is it okay that ina keeps watch
of you for protection but it's not okay
if i do that i don't know quickly when
in the very first round when i reported
when i reported ina absolutely flipped
her story and went from the super meek i
don't know where i'm going to suddenly
super loud and embarrassing as if she's
trying to protect herself
she'll be honest i don't trust either of
you so neither
okay that's fair
oh really i walked past what both y'all
were a little suspicious
okay okay
is that you're suspicious of both of us
and not one versus the other then as i
like you know she went to go do a task
and she ignored me and i yeah oh at the
top just now
i was waiting for my cool down
i think two imposters still not
definitely it's
was because i kept bumping into her
every time
uh it was just three of us in total so
if one person uh left
it would just be two of us
and i kept having that situation
because you were being left alone with
ina and i don't want you to be killed
and i wanted somebody to be
my watch
okay so are we still gonna be trying
[Music]
has been really quiet
mumma's been very quiet she hasn't said
anything
too yeah
all right
she forgot
did she forgot
oh iris
okay nobody's here i should probably do
my tasks okie dokie
so we have to go all the way up here up
here up here up here up here up here
just follow the arrows oh no
here no
wait what all right okay we got to go up
here and we're going to go up oh my god
i just heard a voice i'm scared meeting
you
hello hello hey hey hi hi
okay this is the wrong way
uh
where am i going oh i have to go to the
other oh you're really itching hello
where are you going hi
i'm going to the meeting room oh me too
can we go together
yeah okay yeah yeah
all right
it's okay okay
let's go to the meeting room first we're
going to do our tasks we got to be a
good crewmate we're going to do our
tasks
right
oh
enough
please don't kill me you know
all right
i have three tasks in the meeting room
wow all right
how are you guys doing what's my id
three five nine seven zero okay
next
we're gonna go to the votes
[Music]
oh you can go past this oh let's just
block
fire
use
where'd she go where did she go
please
[Music]
foreign
yeah i think i saw her like right before
oh yeah and i saw her doing the carding
and okay uh-huh yeah it seems like she's
in the clear so
i'm pretty sure
[Music]
i've ran into so many people excuse me
what is your name no it's not let me
answer the question thank you the
microphone is in my hand
because at the very beginning of the
match i was singing the berries and
cream song and i went into the
electrical and right down in there
oh
[Music]
yeah yeah iris isn't in the clear
uh-huh
[Music]
he wasn't with like nearby guru though
oh so that was when the lightning round
past four a.m
well i don't know
[Music]
oh
i gotta finish my task you're so close
before that body that's cool
you gotta stay safe
look at my hamster
my hamster
my
all by itself now
look at my poor little hamster
it marks
where i died
[Music]
it was like hello like
what i understand why why mummy if she's
the imposter who killed fauna why would
she report your body
because there was someone else there i'm
pretty sure or like she thought it must
be smart to report that's probably why
she took so long to report
wow
[Music]
and iris iris leading ina behind went
into the room to the left of the engine
room and then only came out and then he
came in and i said hi pony and then nina
came in and i said oh cronie i'm going
to go see that body that ena just left
can't get much more
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around anything else good
enough for this round
throwing the towel and why is it amelia
watson no it's not fair
[Music]
well it is true that bae did notice that
she wasn't talking about she wasn't
talking
was completely violent
she was quiet
finally justice justice has been served
like that
okay i need to finish my freaking tasks
okay
oh
please please crony please if you can
feel my presence
crony crony crony i love this one i can
do this one oh come on please
you didn't hear me oh no i didn't
then
screw it
correctly though you should hear me
[Music]
i know what you did
i know what you did no
i know what you did run crowley
i know what you did dangling to herself
okay let me finish up my task
one more
i'm a ghost now
i'm a ghost now hello hello i'm a ghost
named
[Music]
is this the last task oh come on come on
quick quick quick somebody outside quick
okay someone else has one more task to
finish who is it
someone has one more task to do come on
quick quick quick quick come on someone
do your tasks come on come on come on
oh no
[Music]
come on
do your tasks people
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
so it would have been difficult to find
out
unless we would have done all the tasks
so good job
just keep quiet
i was really suffering with good adele
because
i think we have established that no
matter what yeah
good is
uh
[Music]
um was like so strong against gouda the
very first round i was like that's kind
of succino i've never seen you know like
this before
you know right
yeah we can't even avina's crew i'm just
like maybe we should just vote
wow
[Music]
does everyone have imposters here dead
uh checked because it didn't work last
round i think it's okay yeah
yeah yeah
i'm i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like i mean i guess i died
really but that's the same
okay yeah but only the host can change
it yeah so everyone should see this okay
wait are we playing one more
yes okay
can i can i can i um
back real quick i gotta go for a second
i got an idol meeting hold on i'll be
right back okay
okay idol meeting we need to play some
classical idols are here we're all here
we're all right
[Music]
we're done
what happened
[Music]
what's going on
hello
[Music]
thank you
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
i'm going for the kitchen
i'm gonna go big
i'm by myself
all right
nothing in here we're gonna go to the
gap room
gap room is there something oh it's on
the other side okay got it
okay good let me go down here nope
never mind it's hair
down it
very nice
a very nice
how are you guys doing you guys having
fun i can't really read chat um
just yeah i can't read chat but
i hope you guys are having fun
i'm
sorry or am i
cause she might be imposter
where am i going
ah
forever lost
this is bae
[Music]
okay we go here and then we go down to
the armory okay here
very nice
armory
nice handguns
oh
i love that sound it's so satisfying
okay
oh no
[Music]
watson
hi
guys speaker you're gonna push this
house get away no i'm doing the task
likely sorry that's what you said to
gouda unless you're the one not doing
the task
well why would i be standing here
wasting time instead i can't do my task
okay i gotta go up here oh wait no
there's nothing um
i'm gonna go to the engine room which is
somewhere
where am i going oh wrong way okay so
there's an entryway up here oh
why are you laughing you are stuck
because i
i heard kiana go in the crystal
everyone with their iq is
your sauce
morning
are you good i'm good i did a task
are you doing tasks
doing tasks
did you just do one
i'm just doing one down hi guys
why are you standing still um i just i
just saw fauna apparently she was doing
a task but the bar didn't go up
right and i just saw you standing still
yeah because i was confused
is that equal to one right
come watch me do a toss in
so mad i was like the moment
i'm scared of all of you in the car you
guys aren't an impostor open the door
then i opened it
are you safe you fooled me twice
i'm scared right you what
kiara says that and as soon as i say
that there's a report three holy [\h__\h]
oh
totally i can't vouch for callie because
she's been doing tasks alone and i keep
on running into her and i can vouch for
her uh
[Music]
quite a long time i did see watson at
the end i was trying to open the door i
couldn't open it
this is the stupid card no the card keys
okay lively story fingers
[Music]
yes because i was very
fond of you huh cause you're not you
openly no
yes i did
but then she ended up dead no i don't
know
you were doing the same
interesting
[Music]
she's talking to you right now huh she's
a ghost and you killed her
on this extra taco no
[Music]
yeah i think i'm going to skip but um
okay
interesting
very interesting
i'm going to be talking like a cracker
okay where are we spawning
never mind engine room it is okay hi
wifey
hi what eggs why
do you want us to go together i'm scared
sure i feel like um
i feel like i missed
me too so one of them is in the i'm
gonna go to the shower
whoops
[Music]
oh this is convenient where is she
where is she
i found rey in the shower
he was killing her nasty
and she could have killed me but she
would just went off and did her
testimonies
[Music]
get to the whatever it was sabotage i
forgot what it was crash course or
whatever
i was in records but i didn't see
anything records no you're right
i was in records
[Music]
vote her out are you good
you guys
vote her out i thought it was not a good
answer
i really don't know
i kind of saw it coming but you better
[Music]
i really don't know i think i thought it
was records it might not be records if
you didn't see me but i'm pretty i
thought it was records
come on
her name
is exactly
[Music]
huh i don't even know where the showers
are wait i don't know
no it's the second time you haven't
heard a lot from mummy or eno yeah
isn't it oh i was all the way okay i
spawned in kitchen with mummy and then i
went to do my task in the uh the bottom
left thing goes called uh so our our
suspects are iris and kiara got it
usually you should be like the duck
thing uh
i can't believe it's where she
where is she
[Music]
hi chrome hey look at your hamster first
i'm lost i didn't realize i also found
the last time i didn't kill her the last
time this side didn't kill her this time
what's his name
pet
see oh pep
you've been hanging out with me too much
[Music]
and you're going to be next
i need to do my tasks
come on
we can do this we can do this this is
records which is where i was i need to
finish my toss so i can hold iris
all right speed run
speed run speed run among us
engine room
is that it is that it that's it
where is she where is she
where is she
hello where's iris
[Applause]
this is
hold on
right elbow deep in the toilet
but you just saw that uh okay
i saw it and anna
hey
tiara is now dead
i was the one that found the irish's
body because i left
haha i did the sucky toilet okay guys
bye bye oh she's mentioning toilet again
i was with no uh i was with ina and iris
and kiara and i left and i saw callie
that will kill you
is
[Music]
yeah definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who we vote on
what's good at you i uh
universe brain right now what is the
other one
is the other one
wow really nice
iris you are so dead
iris you are so dead three times in a
row right oh my god maybe her game is
bugged emergency me
iris you are so dead you are gone
probably where's iris
you are so dead you i'ma haunt you for
the rest of my life i hear things
you are dead meat
you are gonna hear from my attorney
you are so dead you
[Music]
run good already
i better not make any wrong
[Music]
think i'm going to make it
someone's standing by on the button it's
very dangerous
[Music]
you
cannot yeah she made it oh my god
she made it she made it she made it she
made it
oh that was a clutch that was so cool
[Music]
see you in another
well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
to not kill people that's my
such a good i'll be a good girl the rest
of us
[Music]
what
random parts of the
conversation how could that be sauce
i'm just going to the name iris
my theories have been really accurate so
[Music]
nice that
okay
oh this chord
hello
[Music]
on muto
hey
[Music]
when you get it three times people don't
even trust you off the bat no
you fooled me three times
yeah what are the problems
unacceptable
it keeps giving impostor to like the
same people
yeah i was really surprised that like
you would assume that you would assume
that the reaper would be like the number
one killer of everyone but i'm actually
just a task master
i do like the task
oh yeah when i when i saw you kelly you
were so scared of death
i know right because i'm
i don't like yeah exactly you'll see
that's the thing is death can't die so
the prospect of death dying becomes a
thing it's quite frightening
i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see their
point of views would happen
everyone's point of view is
yeah it's great
yeah iris you almost blew our coverage
okay if we get a double kill like like
this is good but i couldn't say anything
so i was just trailing you around i
can't believe it i
didn't lose it you're on cooldown or not
so no no
that's why i like i i thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's how
i was like around and then i killed
someone and then i see you went
somewhere else it's like oh no no the
double kill and then i think yeah
because i'm going to tell that
right so yeah
yeah about it
is that what you think there's something
you want to talk about
it's a coincidence but you know at the
same time like you know the senpai's i i
can't i can't go and kill my senpai's
right away
i like that i like that way of life good
good one
well okay girls i'm gonna go through
everyone from top to bottom again to
give a goodbye one by one and maybe tell
me your favorite moment from today or
your favorite kill or whatever so let's
start with amelia watson
oh uh wait what are we doing oh goodbye
and your favorite moment oh that's your
favorite kill from today
okay uh thank you guys for watching and
thank you kiara for uh setting it up
again and organizing everything and my
favorite moment
uh i really liked messing with cali that
was fun yeah
are you gonna kill me she'd be like yeah
you're lucky my cool down is off and
like run away
that's another one for the archives for
me okay well thank you amelia next up
bails
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again so powerful thank you very much
my favorite moment um wasn't actually in
game um it was when i went to have a
idol meeting and i came back everything
was in mayhem just how i like it what
was going on someone please explain
chaos
really came in adding music to your idol
meeting yeah
even more chaotic when chaos is not
there and that's that's the sad thing
we're gonna have a talk iris very soon
just you wait
just you how i can wait what
oh oh no
i i don't need to wait right yeah i mean
you can
oh anyway
right here everybody really guys hey
get a room
my favorite moment has to be um when i
was trying to hold up the the cell phone
to get the cell service on the deck
where anyone could have killed me and i
saw sana come up behind me oh and i was
like holy [\h__\h] this is where i died and
she was like hey callie and she just
walked away and she's like no i have to
do my task here and i was like okay so
we just switched spaces and we like
watched out for each other it was kind
of cool the bonding moment i was like
oh really
i thought that was so cute santa being
santa
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work
and i really appreciate it
uh my favorite moment was not being the
imposter
oh
yeah i don't know i i think i prefer not
doing the imposter too
being impostor is just so much pressure
yeah
and especially
why you can't really say anything
because
[Laughter]
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up gouda
how salty are you
i'm fine
i'm saying i was talking to my chat
though about like how i don't usually i
don't have conversations i don't talk
like this usually like accusatory
whether it's
[Music]
my favorite moments were
uh and i i'm asking clippers please uh
the various perfectly cut screams with
the proximity chat cali specifically
where everybody was terrified of me and
every time somebody would walk by me it
would just be blood curdling screams
i'd like to see a perfectly cut screams
compilation of some sort if there are
enough
[Music]
i was very terrified
yeah
okay yeah thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful collab camera
i love among us to bits me too i'm so
glad i was able to do this and i i i
would go for among us like off stream
anytime if we had enough people oh yeah
i like it
but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me um i
really liked how cali you know when she
found fauna's body was like it was me
boys
you kind of outing yourself out yeah
that was it i found it hilarious
she was totally you
no
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say words sometimes
yeah that was my personal favorite
genuine and very fun game thank you so
much yeah she was just all the time
yeah
good
i was like okay if i get all the air
girls and maybe the other imposter can
go on a killing spree oh yeah that's
right what i was doing when i was in
pasta too i was like oh yina's probably
i'm probably gonna have to be aggressive
so that's right i'm killing and killing
ya
aggression is the way to go but i was
trying to clear my name and that was how
i got out trying too hard to clear my
name but i'm just named
[Laughter]
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you
no no no thank you so much for arranging
this
oh
that's fine
once again free bgm
the freebies
thank you so much to kiara uh for
arranging this i really love this game
and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever the
the proximity chat exploded whenever a
meeting happened
and
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so
thank you for that
i'm glad you had fun thank you cronie
next
hello
thank you kiara for organizing
everything everyone says that
we're julian
yeah thank you yeah
i'm blushing thank you please continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with ina
and i turned her and i said wouldn't it
be something if you're the imposter
three times in a row and she's like yeah
that really would be she just walked
away
i was like
absolutely drenched in sweat
you know there's so much blood on her
hands today
yeah i don't know i think it killed that
your favorite moments who who was your
favorite kill maybe
oh who felt the best putting a knife
through their stomach
geez
well um
it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
the
uh cronie in the wasn't the first game
or something where she was like please
don't kill me i was like okay
you
[Music]
yeah yeah i think she'll be more like
callie like the cat muller
oh yeah
no it wasn't me
honestly
yeah it would be very scary and
intimidating though because cali was
every time when i was sussing callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
i was so scared that she was yelling at
me but i wasn't sorry that's you huh
[Laughter]
no it's you know you reverse
okay sana give us your your goodbye and
your favorite moment please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab cara um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too yeah
[Music]
my favorite moment as
pretty much every time i heard kelly
scream but now my favorite moment is
spending time with all of you guys
i wish i couldn't
[Laughter]
next time next time you should uh leave
me leave me alive because i
believe everything you guys say i just
seen you
listen to the video
[Music]
all right well
um uh for me my favorite moment one i
had so many but i guess the one that
stayed in my head now is um i think it
was in this in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was sussing
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really
mad and then amen was like well i'm
gonna follow you to see if you're really
innocent and i was like chilling with
inna as ghosts and we were just talking
about the better curling and just we're
standing there together as ghosts and
then ahmed and guna ran into the room
having a huge fight like discussion like
[Laughter]
watching a kindergarten fight
in the garden
that was good they were running in
circles yelling at each other it was so
funny
oh man um but yeah uh um it was it was
uh
i'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh you know i had some
troubles in the beginning but i'm so
relieved it all worked out i'm sorry
about no no no no no no
yeah it worked out for sure
as the organizer i'm just the happiest
that everyone had fun and and no hold on
scuff was that present today
[Music]
thank you for participating i'm sure
there's some some among us who are a
little bit tired of this among us game
but uh i think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes
yeah it was a blast okay i'll kill you
do this some time again in the future
if you don't mind hell yeah yeah do it
with everybody yeah
yeah
among us
there's other
games yeah
is like because i organized the ian id
mario kart tournament now that we are 11
ends we could do a full en mario kart
tournament as well
one of the people are going to be bought
is that what it is yeah one of them
would be a bot i think or you can just
leave that one we can just do eleven
eleven three like pretty big
well it is uh past five a.m for me so i
hope we can end it we'll get our next
one
do you have an announcement
sorry
announcement or
oh do you want to announce something oh
yeah yeah yeah oh um i have an
announcement for next weekend that we
will be having another
uh collab
[Music]
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down um
[Music]
not even trying to do the pun i'm just
really saying it's genuinely going to be
amazing amazing perhaps amazing
this one's amazing
yeah
this looks great
[Music]
english
three
two
one
bye
[Music]
so
you