[Music]
what a lovely sight
we have some like bones examine the
skeleton
today we're playing don't slive together
and if you guys don't know the objective
of the game you should re-read the title
because it's in the title
we're supposed to starve we're hungry
supposed to see how long we can survive
for
and that involves uh foraging for stuff
crafting
not getting lost and working together as
a team
as you can see we've already had some
deaths here over on the right
i was trying my best to guide them but i
don't know
yeah and now we are going with the most
experienced game i think
we're a little fragile
this is a dog inna found it's so cute i
love it i've never seen this before
it comes with it comes with my character
whoa
you get a dog yeah
we'll find stuff you gotta find carrots
and mushrooms and
when it gets dark we can go back to the
spoon
if you look up at the top at the top
right corner you can see there's a
little red section that's just
like the twilight that's like a sunset
it's not dark dark it's not dark dark
it's just
uh it's almost dark yes it's dark it's
not dark dark just tuck it
it's playing the same direction it looks
like we're going north so
yeah get really hungry you can collect
these seeds on the ground and you can
eat them
mushrooms you gotta cook before you eat
them uh or else you'll get sick
oh it is western never mind sorry my bed
i like my character he looks like um
like a tim burton character
like someone that johnny depp would play
yeah
yeah can i not pumpkin
oh the pumpkins those are pretty useful
so like you can use them for
like uh torches no torches are really
important if you want to travel at night
okay these guys are aggro they're a girl
uh so who's so what happens like around
day
14 or so there will be wolves that will
try to come attack us and we have to
fight them so we have to
find wood we gotta find trees uh we
gotta find sticks we gotta find rocks
the basics okay
it's like minecraft yeah it's like
minecraft yeah
the poop you can use to make farms with
to fertilize your crops
of course it's innovative
i don't think there's anywhere to go up
here
okay we'll go back down we gotta go back
down anyways to get to the spawn
can i eat the bird by the way what what
is this you can catch a bird and eat it
but sometimes it'll only give you
feathers instead of giving you meat
using shadowy creatures what can i do
with binoculars
[Music]
when the wolves attack we can hide there
and then they'll like attack them
and then they'll fight back sorry
i'll be like my johnny depp character is
saying i'm so hungry uh okay
i have berries for you if it meet we'll
we'll meet at the spawn
and see here are these horses did you
break up
on my heart okay
skeleton is still just here all right
here's berries for
[Music]
i got confused
to the spawn beacon and you click on it
uh
you can't oh you had six calendars yeah
i did
you're supposed to make a fire uh yeah i
got it i'll come i'm coming away
i think we're gonna keep dying no no
it's okay
we're okay i got fire i didn't know we
had six
the next time when you guys have sticks
and points you just find it right away
in the floor you can make a torch
okay wait okay okay okay
[Music]
oh my gosh if you can eat raw carrots
that's a good thing
oh and picking flowers if you find any
flowers that'll help your brain juice
oh brain juice cool uh i need a bit of
plate
we lose all our stuff yeah we gotta pick
it up it's on the floor pick it up oh
yeah
it's like where we died
if you pick up twelve flowers you can
make a flower hat
also cool i want a flower hat
um
but you could have a nice you look nice
in a flower a flower hat i think
oh they have to be the same flower i
don't know
[Music]
you guys just explore and then i'll make
a vase for us so
we don't die when it turns night again
i'm bringing company i got company
uh how many are we talking i think they
got bored
how many are there i wonder how we make
weapons i know we're good
let's see weapons fights it's under
fight you can make a spear
so if you collect uh grass but i need to
make i need to make a
science machine wait what okay i'm gonna
go back to my blind seeds
guys i might say loud to you now because
my audience said i'm too quiet but maybe
i'm too loud for you guys now no you are
still sounds good to me
yes okay
it's like a little thing sticking up on
the ground
yeah how do i kill a rabbit
now you have to catch it so he makes
grass
grass you can make a trap and then you
can trap the rabbit and you can kill it
with your bare hands
cool can i make grass oh you're going to
be able to collect the grass and you
guys can find bread
okay i'm going to make what we need now
if any of you guys have blended sticks
you can make an axe and start collecting
wood
and then with the wood i can make a
machine that can make us a bunch more
stuff
i don't i i have an empty elixir do you
need that
it kind of sounds useless all right i'll
go back to exploring then
i'm wondering i got something that's
useful
can i make a trap with pop ball fangs
this house is here what now i'm still
out focusing
are these pigs nice uh
there are nice pigs actually some some
don't attack you guys
i got carrots baby nuts i'm scared
usually pigs are like carnivores so you
gotta give them something
okay hello all right i'll make a pizza
we got berry bushes
i should have collected more rocks i
need
all right i'm giving you guys a job all
right yes kiara
okay you you take that you you guys
collect the wood
yeah okay cali go chop down some treats
oh there's a turkey can i light the
turkey on fire
it's dark can i come in can i will they
let me in their house
uh no that you can't go in the house i'm
gonna drop torches at this spawn for you
guys okay or i'll drop
one torch uh you guys i think i have
i think i have a light
[Music]
oh yeah if you have a lighter you uh
might be able to use it
okay i'll stick with inna then oh okay
okay
that's good and if you guys
[Applause]
[Music]
on the ground right oh yeah yeah you can
get it from rocks too
uh if you make a picnic you always get
flip rocks
okay i'm gonna i think i have enough um
i need two pieces of wood and six more
rocks to make where's that ghost
permanent fire
yeah who is that ghost oh that's like
your friend that's like your i think
it's supposed to be like your dead
sister or something
yeah did you see that
hey look there's something in the ground
oh there are many things oh they're
sticks
what the hell oh wait we can go over
here
a glove a glove why didn't it sound like
that
look there's a dead body over there
who's that
[Laughter]
oh something what
[Music]
can't build i can build a campfire so
i'm gonna go back to the base and
okay i'll build the gameplay there
should we go back and go back to the
spawn
yeah let's go back let's go back okay
you follow the path you want
way faster i see it
art style is very cute i like these
it's awesome wait what is that oh never
mind
okay go maybe we have some blank we
could eat the moles
it's okay i have i have six stones
oh you have defense can i eat this
mandrake
happy girl you can but it'll put you to
sleep oh and motherhood i think you have
to kill it
oh i think it's nice wait watson do you
need any of this i don't know wait i
need any what you can turn that off uh
cause get it you'll run out of fuel and
you're lighter i think i don't do it
also you can cook it up here so if you
have like the mushroom right you can
cook
seeds to give you more i have
carrots you want carrots you can cook
carrots
i mean you just click it in your
inventory and then
click on the fire with it in your mouth
wakey wakey nice who's ghost
orientation
[Music]
the shadow scared me that the shadow of
the tree scared me
hey i have one here i'll just drop what
i have because i don't know what it does
okay yeah we got a glove there's a
monkey paw what does that do
i don't know i don't know what that does
is
can you cook berries what ah
i think you can you can cook pretty much
everything
please i have butterfly wings cooked
carrots
here decorations for the butterfly wings
oh i was about to cook you're over the
fire you planted rum
you pressed q and e oh somebody gave me
carrots yes you're welcome
okay
[Music]
yeah can we make it
you can make healing potion but uh it's
a bit difficult so like
if you find a spider web you wanna you
wanna collect
spider web from the spider nest and uh
it's kind of dangerous but once you
build
traps out of grass you can catch the
spiders and they give you spiderweb and
use that to make a fishing rod
and you catch fish and then the fish
make they make good heels
okay they heal you yeah i got
binoculars fun oh binoculars that sounds
really good
i don't think that's nothing like that
yeah i don't think we can use that
oh she just died
i saw
[Music]
uh oh yeah you're probably in the swamp
areas in the swamp area if you walk
by too slow uh there are tentacles in
the ground look at your stuff
no headshots what is that
do you guys have any wood has anybody
collected some wood
yeah i have a tent i have ten
oh okay you i'll take stuff
i'll go back to this oh my friends
tentacles here what is that
what is this hand yeah
what a hand fairies sage hands it's like
a table with
some flowers around it oh uh don't touch
don't take the flower
don't oh i but i did i did take a flower
oh oh my god we're good
what yeah am i am i curious i think
you're
sanity so if you check yeah
should be able to see whether your
sanity is going down actively and if it
is it might be
that the thing you picked up
okay there's a frog on my tail
so wait okay stomach okay brain
yes what is the other one
uh what stomach brain and health so much
more no not november
i can plant a tree i found some nuts
okay
uh yeah some some of the tree nuts you
can eat them but
sometimes if you don't want it to seeds
okay bad things will happen
bad things yeah
[Music]
that's the only thing i could see from
there
all right i'm out i brought you some
wood
oh thank you i already got some um but
i'll pick it up
on minecraft forever
i'll put her lighter by the uh by the
base
all right i'm looking for i need rocks
where do we find the rocks i like that
the rocks with the axe as well
no you got to make a pickaxe left
no it's pretty easy i bet you have
enough to make it it leads to my new
friend
what freeze gimme
no rabbits sound like
she died
[Music]
a turkey i found a big turkey kill it
i'm killing it pretty hard to catch with
the x oh yeah well i won't give up
i'm used to chasing things with the
tripod uh-oh
all right see if we have a fire at the
base if you guys get there and
uh there's no fire you just put grass or
wood or anything that you can burn in
in the fire and it'll you know like oh
all that pig is going away that's a
fella's stone
are the pigs dangerous uh
the ones who try to attack you are
dangerous
there are some nice pigs okay you'll
know right away
actually the pigs if you give them like
a piece of meat to eat they'll be your
friend
and they'll trap they'll chop trees for
you oh
i have a sweet of them this is where the
basement oh
okay thanks if you guys are standing
near this science machine i made here
you see that new tabs up here
on the left side so now you can make the
rope you can refine
you can make rope you can use that to
make traps and you can catch bunnies and
spiders and
frogs thanks for the dr stone
nice going watson
probably is literally carrying yes
i was going to say thank you amelia it
was helpful
oh probably go up anybody on stock
trap you can use that you just you just
put it down on the ground and
it'll like be automatic okay i'm gonna
go catch some little
rabbits it's gonna get dark soon just be
careful
all these tabs
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think tomato to make farms well you
need the seeds that you get and then
stones and fertilizers uh oh yeah right
here food you can just make one here
oh yeah we have enough that our camp is
just surrounded by skrellingtons
[Music]
how about that
oh a backpack you can make it uh uh you
gotta refine your rope
and then i think it's under survival you
can make uh
okay
[Music]
not the candy bag no it might be grayed
out it might not have enough to stick to
the grounds on fire i guess it's not
just uh just grass i think there's a
more advanced backpack
can you make things like chess oh in
this sense
yeah you can make chests
the night is gonna progressively get
longer and longer and so you just have
to survive
you can kind of still explore at night
if you have like a torch or something
uh but it's better to just stay here and
cook or sleep you can make a sleeping
bag and sleeping in the night time it
increases your insanity levels
if you're getting low okay
and i think my salary levels are always
low
we have
[Music]
if anybody ever wants to sleep there's a
sleeping bag here but it's better not to
do it now because it's gonna turn day
time and you wake up immediately but you
can do it when it's in the red
the sunset time you can sleep then
all right i'll work on on trying to heal
if you guys want to fight stuff if you
find any spiders
you can trap the spiders you can fight
them
and then we can use the spider web and
we'll go fishing
okay video bye-bye
all right we'll meet up again at night
okay sounds good
following you i will go do some
importance
[Music]
um i'd love to see you guys do you have
a trap
i do put it down anywhere around the
pond and then go near that frog and make
it aggressive
put it down okay and now go to the frog
and like tease him you want to taunt him
and then he'll follow you and
ugly even to the trap nice voice
over the chat song looks funny but you
smell like that you smell like pond oh
got them
[Music]
yeah we gotta make a chest and like
store food in there or something because
[Music]
oh god you have seeds carrots eat seeds
you're a bird you can eat seeds
but i prefer fried chicken you know
so i don't think there's any chicken in
this game but there are turkeys pretty
similar yeah i did see
one kind of streaming i saw a turkey you
can't run i've cornered him
i've cornered him oh no yeah turkey
scared me
no it's in the water
oh it's in the water i made one you can
probably make one too
guys if it's in the water it's in the
water
next to the the sea oh and
no fish it's not for you pick up soggy
drumstick no it's not for you
i keep running towards the water and
it's not letting me pick up
oh uh yeah you can't go into the water
unless you have a boat
oh sorry kelly you're hardcore boats
yeah you can make boats and we can like
sail the sea but it's pretty dangerous
so i don't think we're ready for that
yet
look as long as we have good odds the
sea is not dangerous for us
oh that's true mm-hmm it's pretty gross
like somebody has to control the anchor
and somebody has to control like the
steering wheel
or like the sail or something and you
can totally do that
she is made for that oh yeah it's all at
the same time
many twigs yay i
desperately need food goddammit uh okay
i'll go back i'll have
i have some food we should we should
make
we should make a crock pot we gotta burn
trees
a crock pot yeah
and you can you can put four ingredients
in there you can make all these like
different
recipes and stuff and then you can make
like cupcakes you can make meatballs
eggs sandwiches
fried turkey how about that fried turkey
you want to make a turkey meal i don't i
think
you go you can make chicken nuggets you
can make chicken nuggets really
yeah but you need honey from bees oh i
just literally ate my honey
oh it's really good for heels so chicken
nuggets they give you like a lot of
[\h__\h]
i did it didn't though it did not
not the honey by itself ah okay
oh well oh we're gonna build something
now
nice
[Music]
if you guys uh we want to make a
functioning base we gotta have like a
food source we gotta have somewhere to
store the food
we gotta have defense stuff so if you
guys wanna like push
you just recipes and stuff on the left
side make whatever you want
i'll help you i am not lost i am not i
got the monster
but are you lost i am not already back i
think
oh yeah you're here you're here it's not
a tentacle
here you go wait oh
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe i have something useful for you uh
i have a bunch of rocks
and twigs useful maybe i should do it
though
uh hey you can use it to build stuff if
you want
huh are you okay
we're back okay we're good
i got some meat uh if anybody wants to
sleep if you're if your brain juice is
low you can pick up this sleeping bag
here and you can start sleeping now but
it'll take your hunger so you got to
make sure you got like a
decent amount or else i think i'll wait
with that
and not do it right now
[Music]
i didn't notice how hungry i was i do
have one
uh chicken leg though oh
nuggets i'm messing up the planks
i think uh i ate some bad meat
didn't know i had such something so
useful the whole time
i can make a compass is that useful
i don't think so all right i mean we
haven't we have a map so it's not
[Music]
lit up are they always were they always
lit up no i put them there a moment ago
oh
nice why is the game audio getting
louder is that
is something i hear something too
i don't know i only hear the flies from
the poop hey yeah
let's pick that up
do you have any wood i can make chests
we can put some stuff away
i have a ton of i have logs yeah yeah
yeah
there you go thank you wow
i did a lot of chopping today
okay we haven't have enough to make one
now
chess okay let's put the chest open
pick up flowers where are flowers
uh there there are some flowers down
south
and okay east also
i'm gonna it's still not night right now
right it's still twilight
uh it's about it's about to turn tonight
[Music]
you guys ever have any wood you can add
it add uh planks to it and it'll like
make this big fire like this
oh i have planks i can make a i can make
a chest does anybody do we need another
chest
oh yeah the chest the chest thought
can i come meet you
[Music]
there's a table following me the table
where i took the flower from
a table
ugh
[Music]
oh
look at my table do you see my table as
well
oh it's all pretty this one's okay
he's gonna attack us in the night can we
like
actually if you make a hammer you might
be able to
a desk oh that's what the yellow ones i
was burning
burning myself alive i didn't realize oh
you're standing in the fire
yeah i didn't know that it's uh getting
nice and warm really close to the fire
with you then it's
burning did i have a job for you come
here okay
i'm really looking like johnny depp all
right take this
don't equip it yet but take it all right
okay don't equip it don't remember yeah
yeah
and now i want you to come over here
equip it and set these
these scraggly trees on fire oh but of
course
wait where'd it go
[Music]
oh i'm happy you finished that yes
that was not edible i got that
i'll please that's it yeah
is there anything i should be feeling oh
trees are on fire what a waste of wood
yeah you're telling me
you can catch frogs you know have you
have you tried that before i can show
you how
oh yes i did i got a truffle
so if you find a frog by a pond you just
put the trap down anywhere near the frog
and then you
you bake the frog into into walking into
the trap oh
i look perfect now you got it you're
fine
wow my ghost is so smart they killed it
killed my my frogs for me
oh yeah the ghost will attack your stuff
like
enemies enemies i love my ghosts my
ghost is amazing
nice nice hat cali
thank you i think so too looking good
where did i even get my ghost from i
don't know i don't i mean you don't have
the clothes right
what was the question here you don't you
don't have you play the same character
but you don't have the ghost right
oh yeah because uh if you there's like a
flower in my inventory and if i click on
it i can summon the ghost but i have i
just haven't done it yet i probably
should
oh wait hungry found a bunch of good
stuff
need one more flower to make a hat
yeah let's all get matching flower hats
there's a
perfume
[Music]
80 free but my hunger is still uh not
very
good looking i'm making crock pots now
so we can make more stuff
did you want me to show you how to catch
the froggies oh no
i i think i bought it
nice try a loser
i don't know why is all the audio
getting louder is this
is something happening am i dying what
uh
i'll give you a present it makes me
sleep i found a
mandrake oh yeah you can kill it right
yeah it'll make you sleep if you eat it
this will water is that that's the thing
i mean i kind of do need to sleep
here you go ah where's that
we need to kill frogs and we need stuff
to fill the crock-pot with
make meatballs some weapons oh i have uh
i have some mushrooms yeah yeah yeah any
vegetables or like carrots you find
i'm kidding i'm coming with carrots
i just need like a few more twigs and i
can make one i need three more times
does anybody have too much i have twins
just kissing you guys flick or control
click
on something uh you can have it and then
like oh
okay cool how big is this map
like this uh it's not yeah it's pretty
big gonna move your dog
in this side oh
[Music]
all right now if you fill the crock pot
uh usually like it's
as long as you don't put anything in
edible in there it should make
something up simpler
if you put too much monster me is it
chester
oh chester yeah yeah wait who found
you just do that's not mine is that good
what i don't know what's wrong you pick
up a bone
uh
i don't know who's the following emma do
you still need some twigs
i don't know i have a ton okay
what's a chester there's no oh
uh we can cook it there now okay yeah
yeah so if you put a bunch if you can
put like different vegetables and stuff
together
there's like different recipes it
doesn't tell you the recipe i'm dying
why are you dying i don't know
[Music]
it's okay you can you can you can
wait why am i oh i'm hungry what should
we do i'm very hungry as well
can i uh wait do we have anything
cooking okay i'll make something with
you come back
[Music]
okay
does that give you [\h__\h] more more hunger
oh maybe not
actually i think it i think he does what
i was looking at
what is that how do you make weapons
because i feel like if i had a weapon
then i could kill a bunch of things and
get us a bunch of meat actually there's
a spear right here on the floor i don't
know whose this is but you see this
spirit
i'm standing next to it you can pick it
up and you can use that you can equip it
you can attach them
cool okay let me see how we try and pick
it up who's who's the hungriest right
now what do you what are you guys
hungry levels 55
what's the one next to let's help i'm
stuck in the skeleton
[Music]
oh okay i make a uh i'm sleeping
need rocks to make the hammer does
anybody have rocks look good
i had so much good stuff but it does see
i see the rock
i see i'm gonna take your rocks i'm
feeling
refreshed i stopped to like really well
damn
[Music]
oh i'm super hungry let's see uh what
can i eat
we jumped over my trap here
cool oh seems nice
nice no piggy
thank you perfect i'll go kill some
things welcome
will they will they kill me for doing
that i wonder
um man i need to build it no don't
no leave me
wait so the stuff everything like
respawns every day
uh not every day there's like a cycle
some depending on what it is it might
take a few days to come back
yeah not every day
[Music]
since when are frogs so dangerous
yeah they take items from you too when
they attack you oh you're choking
you're kidding me i found the spider
nest um
ah the pig is so nice to try to kill the
spiders for me
uh he killed maybe one i got some silk
oh nice yeah
[Music]
i probably shouldn't try to kill the
spiders on my own right it's probably
gonna kill me
uh you don't have to kill them you can
you can make uh the flower traps
sorry i don't always have flowers you
can make the grass traps and then you
can
uh put them down on the ground and then
walk into the traps
and i'll just kill them oh i killed all
the spiders
you killed oh with your ghost with my
ghost and my pickaxe i got like a bunch
of
knees and spider webs and silk be
careful
because that that meat you have to you
can put like one in each recipe in the
crock pot otherwise it'll make you sick
okay hey uh amelia how does one make a
trap
catch the rabbit uh you need
uh grass and twigs and then you gotta go
next to the science machine in the base
got it okay i think that's maybe the
next thing about it
how do you catch a rabbit you just put
the jackpot on
yeah you gotta it's kind of hard to
catch one because like they're so
fast but what you can do is uh you want
to put the trap stand on the hole and
then put the trap like right on the hole
so then when they go back in and when
they come out
they they trigger the trap and they run
into it
they're really one
it's in big trouble because i'm super
hungry right now i'm trying to catch
these rabbits but
uh it's like dad watching rabbits is
more of like a long-term thing
like uh you can't catch them right away
you probably have to come back and
check on the trap like a day later
oh my dude it's fine i'll find other
things to kill
if you find um spiders you can kill
those you can kill
frogs the turkeys moles
there's like little mole wrap thingies
oh that mushroom is happy to see me
look at that he came right up there's so
many spiders
i'm gonna die oh boy can you eat spiders
i have spider meat yeah oh
but we have to cook it in the recipe
yeah
i'm going back now and we can cook some
stuff so we can all
eat let's have dinner tomorrow my ghost
keeps
like putting up a fight with these
spiders but it's like
killing everything legitimately wow
so strong i love michael
no i'm going to perish
i'm bringing home all the meat oh nice
you know
no but didn't die
[Music]
i'll make food now thank you chef
thank you let's go home i shouldn't eat
that right
well the mandrakes are really good they
like give you i didn't know they give
you full hp
yeah please stop me up completely
when this thing comes out of the crock
pot you can eat
make it up to you i'll actually kill a
bunch of things you'll see
okay you'll see
[Music]
me
thank you oh it's a teddy bear i was
wondering what that was
whoa that's right
i know my saturday's dropping
always picking a fight abigail
can we just parents live in happiness
together with these
i want to have the creatures way to like
unsummon the ghost because i i know
you have to summon it i don't know if
it'll ever go away though must be wait
[Music]
if you guys ever need more stories you
can pick up this phone and
this little chester guy this little
monster doggy
he'll follow you if you click on him he
has a storage
whoa
oh nice i got tools now baby
progress baby all right so if
uh i can give you guys some tasks if
you're like what should i do
what should i do you know i'll give you
some tests
uh your task is to go collect a bunch of
rocks and
there's a rock area if you go to the
east
and then you go south yeah
there's a whole rock area i don't know
if you can see it on the map
it's like that desert looks area you can
collect all those rocks oh yes this is
okay uh how do we boost our sanity again
fish right something about this
uh boosting sanity you have to sleep but
if you
are hungry then uh you'll wake up
immediately or
you can collect flowers picking bars
really happens with your sanity if you
find them ah
okay did they say there's a sleeping bag
it'll be in the chest
oh oh i'm sleeping once okay good well
uh is it when as soon as it reaches
morning you'll wake up so you just wanna
next time when you sleep you sleep in
the red time uh at the start to get as
much out of the sleeping bag as possible
we can make more those are really i mean
okay
does it look like it could be something
uh delicious
have you killed things uh take out the
if you guys collect any vegetables or
mushrooms or berries
those are things that you can put in a
crock pot or a mushroom what
yeah you just make it'll make like
meatballs if you have two meats in there
and those are really
healing
oh wait how do you put it oh i got this
i meant to put that in the crock pot not
my mouth
oh i think we might
be getting it back
somebody help me why is
[Music]
yes
north follow the path north and go into
the beefalos and like stuff
[Music]
berries
okay i'm still looking for flowers i
desperately need flowers
wolves ain't coming oh i don't know oh
flowers
[Music]
you'll be safe okay can we kill the
wolves yeah you can attack them
you have what you do you can make armor
or you can make grass armor too
oh they're they're coming
up okay oh god this is so
bad oh dear oh
run gonna hide it wait what is that
noise
oh the wolves oh they start attacking
you guys just run north
i made i made two fishing rods if
someone wants to have one i'll put
one on there here they're here
that's a wolf
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
thank you for protecting me
i had like two wolves running up to me
but my ghost protected me
and now i'll go fishing hey sorry callie
i saw it again
[Music]
are you still alive you know
oh it's the wolf
[Music]
should i can i fish anywhere or should i
go to fish somewhere where i see some
shadows
in the
[Music]
i'm coming back for my stuff are you
here
nice job kelly yeah that was interesting
you got food yeah so and when you make
the recipes in a crock pot you can only
put oh
no oh my god really not doing well oh
why is the earth shaking question
oh no
it's okay happens to the past ah only
fish and ponds okay wasn't that a pond
actually it means a really small one
really small okay okay one second i
gotta get the berries so i can make more
what was it crock pot
oh no there are wolves at the campsite
ah this is
watch out should i come to kill them
yes yes i'll use my
now i got the joke behind chester
finally
[Music]
[Laughter]
did you suggest that name to the game
there's free ghosts now what the hell
[Music]
can you cook never mind that's a stupid
question
you can put a stick but it'll it'll
change into something less
uh filling like only one stick you can
put oh
okay can someone light up the
the crackpot oh i think it just goes
automatically once you put enough stuff
in it
ah there we go oh who put in those
[Music]
carrots
yeah you're fine
i can make a shovel what should i make i
can make a pitchfork i can make a razor
oh
why would i want to save my face though
my face is perfect like this
that's a long shadow i think you can
shave your beard and like put it
up oh it's beautiful right now
yes please you know sure why do you keep
up oh wait i mean i need uh
uh i want skins too
hey why can't i go the server will drop
you like some
stuff you can put like different clothes
i'm talking about armor you want armor
no i want the skins but also armor and i
still don't understand how i can make it
back what exactly do i need now it
doesn't lock up
i don't know what is that okay we're
good the hand is trying to grab our fire
why is everything what is the
where is this game like what is the
story where's what's the lore
ah i don't know but actually i don't
know what it is
i don't know maybe chad can tell us
what's the lord and what is the lord
there is no lore
i wonder what we need the lord they say
is don't starve
now i can go get some jewelry
oh yeah we have a trap here all right
what we need we can uh we need to build
an alchemy machine but to build an
alchemy machine
we need electric dudettes you can get
those by like smashing
sometimes you might just find them but
you gotta like smash some stuff that you
find like that
there's like really weird gear stuff you
can you can make a refrigerator in this
game but
i don't remember how to get all the
materials for it
because your food your food has a
child's life
don't go back oh
i will not let you get away
[Music]
come on baby girl faster
stupid
the berries you stupid piece of [\h__\h] oh
strawberries i eat you with berries
that's how it's supposed to be
stop oh my god
is everyone i am
in rockland i'm in froglant oh
okay stay hydrated how do we stay
hydrated in this game
i got it did you also just get a super
chat saying stay
at the same time they're telling us to
stay hydrated how sweet of them
thank you hi thank you i need to drive
the rabbits away from where the holes
are
okay i'm making a bunch of food all
right have you got any food
i want to get another flint so i can get
a pickaxe
ah well i have some flavor if you need
something
uh i'm kind of far okay yes
usually you'll find them in the same
area where like you would find flowers
[Music]
oh a morsel what is this
oh my god oh my god
oh my god there's so much stuff at the
face
oh
so many frog legs oh my god
i got a gold nugget
that's a pond wait johnny eat can i rock
and eat at the same time
no that was good
oh i'm fishing for the first time in my
life
oh let's go back got two rabbits why are
you doing on food
murder i'm good
i have two gloves can i make something
now
abigail chill uh i don't know
we're making rabbits tonight baby
[Music]
i tossed my grass so i could carry the
useless glove
why can't i cook them i have this but
uh cook what i'm trying to cook the
rabbits that i killed but i only have
two yeah i have a
yeah i don't have anything to put in
there you need to fill the rest of the
slots it's gonna be four so if you have
like berries or carrots or mushrooms
one monster meat or one stick you can
put those in there
okay yeah let me see
i have more
morsels oh you killed one wait do i
look three oh you can put it in the
crock pot if you want it'll make
um tasty meatballs
i really love meatballs now hungry hey i
don't know how
how does it the work
yeah it says hook and then i click on it
one time or
oh uh yeah yeah you uh
put it in the pond and then minecraft i
got it
i never i never even fished in minecraft
i got a fresh water speech now i pick it
up
oh here i don't want to eat all these
meatballs myself
it has meatballs too oh okay me too
[Music]
it's okay living life on the edge
if we find any spider glands we can make
like this uh
potion there's a healing potion and we
need spider plants
sally do you need food my guy for now
i'm gonna wait till it gets real low and
then i'll eat my meatballs
yeah okay good idea i'm gonna touch some
more rabbit
that was fun you think just like peanut
butter
[Music]
brought some ice what can we do
make some piece of drinks i think you
can make
like a you can use it in recipes i know
you can put it in the crock pot
but i don't know i think you might be
able to make uh ice cream or like some
sort of drink with it too
you gotta have like the ice cream
yeah you can make cupcakes in this game
yeah you gotta like look up the rest you
gotta like
the rest of it i need to make something
wait a saddle does that mean you can
ride stuff you can like
uh i don't know maybe
now you can ride a boat it's
not with a saddle though you goober yeah
not with a saddle
oh my god that was that was
funny-looking
what what what what no you didn't look
at me oh i messed up
it's a gorilla i'm just eating okay
gotta try it you're cute i'm trying to
not dive okay
unlike you hey there's nothing wrong
with starving we all have flower crowns
i really want to grow the beard so i
really look like a real johnny depp
[Music]
you can also then you can shave the
beard and like turn it into a jacket or
something like a bed
[Music]
actually i'm gonna go catch some more
rabbits you guys talk about building the
boat while i go catch these rabbits
that's good i'm missing a bunch of
wood need planks oh
[Music]
okay
we need a bunch of wood to make boats so
as much wood as you can collect
you like chop the wood yeah um
yeah no that's my bag but
made a backpack finally 10 years later
congratulations just took me five
million years
bird trap who would ever make a bird
trap there's poor birds
oh you're asking how to get a chicken
that's how you get uh some chicken you
get a little uh
chicken legs from them no no no no no no
no
oh
how much wood do we need a bunch of wood
you can get
oh okay this one just [\h__\h] carry
now we probably need like uh
uh probably like 30 or 40.
oh my goodness if well if we all get
like 10
that's not that bad yeah yeah
hmm abigail
go with me abigail
i should probably store some more things
i still got all my silk and spider
glands
oh i can heal my mouth is that for the
heart or for the hunger
oh yeah yeah it's for uh healing it's
for we can make like a healing style for
anybody who's low hp
and you just it's really easy you just
need rocks and ash and i have some ash
so
oh
yeah you can get ash by burning down
like little bushes or grass or
twigs anything you put on the floor will
probably turn into ash
oh do i burn it down with my torch yeah
oh just gotta make sure fire travels
like between things you gotta make sure
you don't to burn down the forest or all
of our stuff for example
you got to do it far away
i was going to ask is there like a
certain way to cut trees fire doesn't
hurt me
no problem just hold space you can hold
space and it doesn't oh
you hold space yeah oh
i didn't know i kept clicking yeah
it's a lot it's a lot more comfy hello
no yeah i have vampire teeth
why does it take so long the fishing
stop
stop the burning oh yeah it takes a
while
murder damn there's two rabbits
i'm starting to be good at that ketchup
rabbits
oh you caught a few yep
i have a rabbit trap here
you kidding me
burning the tree thing didn't work ah
yeah you gotta you gotta burn like
little things like uh like
a grass bush or if you have twigs you
can
you can drop individual twigs uh i think
with
[Music]
i say okay i got the grass okay i don't
remember where i put my rabbit trap
oh no i think
you should you might be able to see it
on the map maybe oh
good good uh maybe i have it
did you find it oh no let me give it
back to you
that's why no
it's totally fine it's totally fine
you can have the meatballs that we that
we make with the
rabbit's like no that's not
oh
i was just like man i really lose stuff
so easy
gosh here i'm dropping it on the ground
no no no no it's only got
25 percent if you want to catch more go
for it i don't know
no i don't even know how to use it
really i'm a bad daddy i should wait
um
oh sorry oh you're good you're good do
your thing ina
weird thing i'm glad we have enough
stuff to put inside the pot
yeah i just put a lot of berries in
there i like pumpkins
simple and and i can do it
oh
[Music]
ah okay got it
whoa good night
whoa wow i'm like a professional
survivor damn
my what what other word i have no one
for you
doing so well i'm amazed with myself
i think this is because my mom was like
a survivor mom so
i think i learned it from him i have a
survival mom
really she taught me the ways yeah she
can do anything
with with no tools she survives in the
in the wilderness
isn't it cool yeah my mom is
survival mom
[Music]
mom get the camera mom look i have so
many friends
[Music]
or is it hunger i don't know it's the
third one four three two one
it's oh it's hunger oh dead
[Laughter]
i was trying to meet you all right
hey wrapped chewy
i thought you needed eggplant for that
ah all right yep
[Music]
[Laughter]
terrified by german fairy tales oh my
god look there
i have limits okay i want this pinecone
oh wait wait it's interesting that
things spoil in this game too
yeah i gotta cook my monster meat
goddammit i need some
some berries i have fairies now put some
i'll put
three berries in there okay okay
thank you yes
okay i'm gonna look for a suitable place
to put
i have water stuff i think this is
no this is not the ocean what we might
make another base
by the water because of that we're gonna
put the boat
wait do you have my wood i took it
okay it's mine it's very nice all right
let's leave it at the face
i gotta try it i'm gonna build it i
don't know what it does
oh pick up land with it
i probably want one meat in the pot if
someone wants to add
a berries you can make a crock pot uh
[Music]
i just need some stone and i can move
stuff over
oh i'm on my way to get some snow now
oh stop but yes don't you know are you
collecting some stones
oh yeah i have seven rocks oh can i have
some
yes i'm on my own okay
i need my potion again that's fine i'll
survive because i have my ghosts
yep
oh yeah i have i have a [\h__\h] ton of frog
legs i got 16 frog legs
if someone needs food i i got too much
oh you can make uh you can make frog
like sandwiches with those
oh hell no have you guys ever had
real [\h__\h] like before no no
from what i've heard that just tastes
like i tried it once but it was at like
a really
uh shady buffet and it tasted really
gross oh my god
yeah i'm not surprised have you guys had
snails
sure it was really frog like his nails
it was a frog legs it was a frog like
yeah
yeah i haven't i've had snails before
is it what's gonna call it escargot yes
oh fairy fancier
i prefer fried chicken but okay you go
with what you like
right can i kill this rock so what
exactly do we need to make a frog
sandwich i got to the frog
i just put one frog leg in there already
i put berries you can make it one time
[Music]
but it's fine um
does someone want um some meat
like actual cooked meat
is someone i'm okay for now but i
thought maybe later
you should say now melting ice oh no i'm
back
hey now go to my trap go to my trap the
meatballs are in the chest if someone
needs them
no no what is what is oh
eyes never mind i'm done my dad didn't
even make a sandwich then made
the same thing as before
no no darn it
was expected
so if i put four meats into the pot will
it still only make one meatballs for
everyone
uh yeah yeah so it's good to like uh
there's like a balance so if you put
like two meats and two vegetables it
should make meatballs but if you
put like too many vegetables and it'll
be like a vegetable based dish
you can use filler like uh monster meat
you can put one monster meat in but if
you put more than one it'll turn into
like monster lasagna and it'll take away
each
monster maya that's not yummy though
yeah
if you put a stick in there it'll make a
like a kebab or something kebab
unless it's fish then it makes fish
sticks
oh it's been so long let's just be
[Music]
um i'm confused because i definitely
killed three things today and i only
have
one morsel in my pocket
[Music]
anyway there are two things in the pot
so
we can i was gonna make a boat but we're
not really close to the water so if we
made a boat it'd be like a long journey
which
that's why you ate them
i bet you know what i bet i was trying
to put them into the pot and i ate them
god
bite me i don't see it
yeah yeah put them in
yeah like trying to make something oh it
started cooking okay okay yeah as long
as you don't put anything like weird in
there it should make like
some sort of recipe
[Music]
a lot today
cute noises everywhere
meatballs
uh let me know we have like stored
meatballs here too in the chest
hold on someone is at my is that my
abode i will be back in just a moment
don't die it's getting nice now
okay i should go back oh my god
won't be too bad oh thank god i'm too
far away from my face anyway
ah there is an ocean it's to the north
we'd have to i have to make a new base
up there
whoa
we have any more stone without all the
sun and lots more stone ponies
oh wow thank you this is one enough go
abigail
i choose you abigail your turn um
don't kill my ghost what i'm over here
oh yeah i i can't
i have no responsibility for what thank
you so
question when we make the meatballs does
it make one for everyone or is it just
one meatball
yeah it's just it's just one set of
meatballs it's like one
that's terrible that makes me sad we
should have enough for everyone
well there's some extra meatballs in the
chest so if people get hungry they got
food there
yeah okay well i'm gonna go catch some
more things and kill someone
okay i'm building another base up what
how is that can i help i don't know what
to do
yeah you can you can come with me to
help me make decisions about the boat
okay where are you just up i'm
up north yeah by the beefalo oh don't go
dabbing
i found the ancient ones um oh oh dear
bye bye abigail
you're not gonna survive guys or maybe
you are well let's try
hello people i love your dead staring
eyes
fine i picked the fight that was too
dangerous to me
yeah i got an interesting one i see you
i think
what the hell was all that that's not a
black rabbit
oh yeah oh nightmare
it turned into nightmare fuel thank you
do you have any wood ground
i have twigs
okay i go get wood i go get wood thank
you i need two so you just want
is there any way for me to get abigail
my best friend back
what happened to her oh yeah she got
killed by the ancient ones
while she
how do we make this my sanity higher
because i'm unable to tell rabbits now
oh um we gotta sleep uh you can make a
sleeping bag with grass
i think you just need grass okay cool
i'll do that
thunder survival at the bottom grass and
a rope which you see we're fine at the
science machine oh okay sure i can make
a rope already okay
well
pick a rope with grass i need a beard
god oh god
do the rabbits look normal to you gouda
it looks brown and fuzzy to me
a flower brown
when your saturday when your sanity gets
slow it starts to change how the
monsters look
[Music]
so saturday gets restored by
sleeping and picking flowers okay that's
a good idea i want to pick some flowers
my crown is
going too
i'm so hungry like uh outside of the
game like actually hungry i'm so hungry
let's go get some chicken yeah after
after the stream
[Music]
um
okay i'll leave it at the base okay
there we go
here you go thank you oh
the flowers are gone good night
good night
[Music]
hello i thought it would chop faster if
i helped i guess no
i don't know if it does maybe it does
kind of seem like it did
oh my axe is gone that was a funny noise
i was able to make a rope before
i could really use a healing potion i
got like one heart left
uh
right yeah i still have two spider
glands left yeah
and did you get ash pom-pom
yeah you want to share that sleeping bag
with me
oh i would love to but it's gone it's
one use
yes i'll make you another one i'll make
you another one
really wants it i'm sorry i wouldn't oh
that's okay i have a bunch of grass
actually i need two more grass
[Music]
whoever picked up the bone who was the
one who picked up the bone
you know i said i i
don't know okay he just appeared here
he's cute what's a moon rock i think i'm
gonna
thank you yeah i already have i already
have
a lobby yeah do you need that
i can make ash that would be
dope would you salute me
again i wonder why the table hasn't
tried to uh f-word with us yet
i think you have to like maybe it's
because kiara took the flower she has to
be near it
i want to step on the hands when you see
that look how peaceful cali looks
[Music]
protect the sleeping child oh no
i'm real hungry that's not great you're
losing uh
something yeah there's meatballs
meatballs in the chest meatballs in the
chest
uh i ate one so they might not be in
there okay
the table's
[Music]
is coming to you you always want to eat
the seeds
yeah i have the ash that you that you're
talking about
yes
yeah real hungry while sleeping yeah
like it's like a trade-off you get more
brain juice but less
uh hunger tasting breakfast
i do have frog legs
yeah you can put them in a crock pot and
you can put one stick frog leg and then
fillers like berries or carrots
i'm gonna draw some wood here a bunch of
frog legs at once
i'm getting more wood
thank you for the assistance
oh yeah uh we need gold to make the
little i have enough to make it but i
was just waiting to make it up at the
base up top because uh
[Music]
i'm making a new base up there um i'm
gonna make one right now if you want to
follow me
uh i'm gonna make it right now uh where
are you
north i'm going north follow the path
yeah
planting trees we did by the way
reached one and a half hour yeah
time flies probably been fun it has been
fun
we should do it again sometime yeah one
part two one part two is it if we
leave the server is it gonna stay like
that uh
it pauses as soon as i shut it down so
as soon as i exit the game everything
will be uh exactly as we left it
so we can go back to that stage that's
awesome yeah but i actually don't
remember
it should be fun
maybe should be fine it's better staying
like that
because i want my ghost back not gonna
say i'm good with this frog today
dance
oh boy
i survived 12 days what about you girls
i think you're probably the same eleven
yeah i don't think i died oh thirteen
oh i decided to start we all decided to
start yeah we all did huh
another extra time well we really didn't
do a bad job i mean
i would think i would have thought that
i would have done a much worse job but
i survived long enough yeah oh and by
the way uh if you guys ever want to
stream this game alone there's like
single player two
this is called don't starve and there's
like a lot more content in it and
there's like a different island and
different biomes you can explore just
like mine
very i like the art style of this game
too in the field it's very nice
[Music]
i'll definitely do that sounds good well
thanks for tuning in
everyone thanks for coming to hang out
with us we tried not to starve together
yeah thank you for watching thank you
thank you everyone
everyone have a nice night
you