[Music]
so
yes
[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
so
this is
[Music]
hmm
do
[Music]
hi
ask you girl how are you doing i'm doing
good thank you
[Laughter]
welcome back to the halloween house
welcome everyone today i'm gonna be um
i'm gonna be no i messed up the quote um
time to mix drinks and change lives
yeah that's a quote from a game that i'm
playing where you bartend in like a
cyberpunk story
yeah i'm into bartending these days um
change lives with my bartending um these
are all gonna be mocktails though i'm
not gonna poison them those of you
saying yeah she's gonna slip some
alcohol in there no
no
it's apple juice you don't do that when
your friends don't really wanna drink
okay when your friends when your friends
do want to drink and they're kind of
like oh it's nighty
amazing
yeah you put a little in but when your
friends are like nah callie we're not
drinking that okay
i'm very straight edge yes so i'm gonna
actually have to focus on something uh
like making the drinks delicious yes
which is a challenge for me you can't
hold me
we'll see don't you put any exes in the
chat if you put next in the chat i'm
having j-chad ban you i'm having j-chad
banu all right well whatever well you
already have your drink what did you
make yourself i did this like coca-cola
right this is not a long island iced tea
this is a long island nice tea
no alcohol just
um i'm lying mine has alcohol in it you
really can't make it you really cannot
make this drink without i mean i'm sure
you can but it just kind of i would say
it's an occasion to celebrate so
yeah
i would say so but i'm gonna focus on on
making you guys eat something nice and
uh in between making drinks you guys
we're gonna sing songs
[Music]
it's like a mix of karaoke night and
meat making drinks so with that being
said i'm going to now disappear to the
kitchen
and whose drinks gonna be first
we have to get out who gets the first
drink okay bye
oh
[Music]
she's lagging
she's lagging it's just like debuts
uh six six
oh
[Music]
hey
how is the audio guys how is it how is
the voices and how is the pgm
kelly's sofa why would we hear her
working hard i shouldn't be doubled
anymore
uh uh sounds good seems fine are you all
good nice pgm is doubling okay it should
be the extreme
it's good maybe while we're waiting uh
actually you guys can answer some
questions yeah
and i'm gonna
set up some it's okay if i show the
microphones or should i wait
cali oh go for it all right
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
thank you to kelly because she
commissioned all right
[Music]
thank you
yeah behind you guys
oh my god
that looks so nice
thank you
wow so
[Music]
that's cool thank you
it fits my golden accessories right now
oh yeah it does wow
is this should i flip it or is this good
this is good okay is it maybe a little
higher yeah okay would
we'll uh keep them on screen for now but
then we'll hide them after we shop
[Music]
that's so lovely
that's so cool
[Music]
they can come from anywhere and
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
it's so cool thank you
here is your drink i call it watson
concoct concoction just kidding ha ha
it's pink instead of blue
[Music]
yeah it's like you need a lot it's okay
i don't know it is good it's like a it's
like a little soda oh right you put
raspberries in there yeah yeah
[Music]
with this drink uh basically i combined
mango margarita mix with a little sweet
and sour uh syrup and then i mixed i
shook that together in a shaker poured
it out into the glass and then topped it
off with passion fruit fanta sounds like
for fresh
i'm gonna put some ice in there and some
raspberries
it's tasty oh you sound like a bartender
no and i'm an amateur you need a
bartender
i know
the microphones look really cool thank
you you're welcome i hope you guys get
to use them in the future
yeah please please do thank you so much
i'll jump in i'll go ahead and jump back
into this collab real quick so we can
sing a song
it's time to sing what do we start off
with guys
let's see again
[Music]
well
because the new microphones are so shiny
shiny and we're all smiling
[Applause]
i'm gonna
yeah i'm having some trouble entering
the room which is of course classic oh
yes let me try and get in again okay
okay that's all right a little splashy
i mean i can also live with just a gift
but still i'd prefer not yeah yeah we
could take time we're not uh
in a rush we're just chilling all right
let's see
is it gonna be archived yeah of course
yeah
uh oh
we have a guest
an audience member
[Applause]
[Music]
um
my
so
[Music]
sorry um
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey
[Applause]
[Laughter]
audience
behind us gonna be listening to us
should we put like a little bait i can
find one really quick yeah
transparent you can just find it
i think that's what's gonna come up
it'll work it'll work there we go oh
we should use
oh yeah yes is that okay
yeah that's a good one
that looks exactly like sheila that's
sad
100 accurate completely accurate wow
behind the window
flip it like upside down
from the ceiling yeah hang from the
ceiling perfect
perfect
all righty
incredible
okay
all right i could crop it behind the
window
yeah
cute
i'm so obvious
[Laughter]
let's sing shall we shiny smiley story
you better smile or i'll beat the [\h__\h]
out of you inside oh surprise
[Music]
yeah i traded some gushers for base tim
tams
and i think it popped in her mouth and
it was very surprising
i love giving people who have never
tasted gushers gut shoes because they're
like what is this you can tell them
first no [\h__\h] no
surprise
all right i have the
thingy up
okay are you guys ready i'm ready
it's okay
i'm just doing a audio test
[Music]
oh it's fine it's fine i'll just turn it
down just like that okay
i'm gobbling some sun's a bit there we
go that should be good
okay we're all ready ladies wait i'm
gonna pull up the licks because i only
know half of the song
you're good
look up shiny sponge story roomaji
i have yeah
i sent them to you i sent you the remote
little monty
you found them
okay you guys ready yeah
let us begin
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
ladies get me away
[Music]
is
[Applause]
up
[Music]
is
he
[Music]
[Applause]
i think it's a little bit laggy right
now because
yeah yeah a little bit i can't expect
cali you guys
are so intense my ears were like wow
[Music]
oh
if it's a high number
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you guys thanks for listening
i'm sorry to disappoint you but yes
[Music]
thank you i think it closed
i can work with that apple juice
[Music]
[Applause]
i think so too i don't know why we were
lagging during the song i guess we were
just too powerful for it oh my god
oh really i didn't know maybe
yeah maybe maybe it wasn't you don't
like the lime flavor oh
talk no we have a zip tie
i think she just doesn't want to
interrupt too much yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's just watching
maybe uh while we wait for a good ass
drink we could take questions or
something oh chad do you have questions
perhaps you're not sleepy uh
always
always what are you talking about
no we didn't practice oh yeah nope we
didn't that was our first time singing
together like all of us yeah i think so
ate the one red one though it was it was
funny
did you like milk a bunch of dressings
and make a drink yeah
have you ever seen somebody's done like
a giant ball when they like
push the buttons together
[Music]
but what is that
adorable
yes unbelievable i am in shock
[Music]
probably salty right there
always looking up it should be sorry i'm
looking i'm gonna look down my neck
heads from looking up and my eyes
[Music]
i need to push her i need to hold her
back so she stays up
is the microphone single
well i mean enos microphone seems to
have something going with the tentacles
so i don't think that one is single it's
looking like it's having a good time
what i mean look at it
maybe i should switch you guys
[Music]
okay
oh
what was the most interesting actually
an actual question thank you
what was the most interesting thing you
found out about each other meeting irl
was there anything that anybody thought
was interesting about one another
specifically
there was some one
girl is cute but like a different kind
of cute
gray
pink when i met her i will rat on that
you're
[Music]
that's true yeah it's so cute
yeah i can see it oh
i like fashion
it's hiding from me
didn't really feel that crazy because
it's like oh
it's like we've known each other for so
long it's like as if we saw each other
like on tuesday yeah yeah
it's tuesday oh
it's so sunny it's just
i guess it's also surprising sometimes
like good and i make eye contact when
we're
for some reason which is yeah it's
surprising i guess
i guess so
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait if you switch me and nina's faces
it would look like reality
i'm not gonna disappear for one second
one thing i know this i can't really
think of too much but uh i noticed ahmed
is literally immune to stress
she's like yeah offended
like she's always
like today today and also while we were
recording uh like free stuff
no matter how much like complicated
stuff there was and no matter how long
it took she was always staying so
grounded is that weird and chill and she
always seems like like even if after 10
hours it's like frustrating to me like
she still seems like so
like almost
unbothered by it and still motivated and
like she knows it's gonna work out so
she's gonna make it work out yeah um
[Music]
powerful
i mean i get frustrated when i'm around
other people
when i'm alone but when i'm around other
people i don't i don't want to get
frustrated that's right chad's like how
come you guys are how come you're not
being salty in the collabs and stuff
she's doing it together yeah she's
barely holding it
i think i have a drink
oh the drink is finished
it starts off kind of red right right oh
this is george
and then we've got registered
crosstalk now it's purple that's enough
color
i don't know if it's any good
it might taste like [\h__\h] catering
the blue one
oh does it taste good
can i have a seat
goomba thank you
how is it how is it it's like no no
it tastes like that it's frozen real
fruit
fruit enjoy george
george
it's got a lot of muddled fruit in there
though so it's like good for you you
know blueberries baby
i'm gonna pour out the rest of it
nice oh yeah
that means
another drink is done yeah so another
are we doing like one song for you
yeah
[Music]
it looks like it has an extra amount of
fruit yeah yeah
it looks like color too like the
[Music]
is jam just fruit soup oh base is liking
it
[Laughter]
heads
i'm making drinks and changing lives bae
yeah you understand that reference bae
bae understands that reference all right
would you like to describe that drink to
us
yeah the one that i get back
both yeah basically what i did was first
muddled a ton of fruits together
it was like blueberries raspberries
strawberries i muddled them together
then i put in some ice um you're
supposed to use a strainer but i was
like [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] so um
together and then i put in some sweet
and sour mix and then some powerade
and um for whatever reason actually no
like red like red coloring came from
anything except for the fruits huh so
like the fruit made it red at first even
though it was like sweet and sour
and like powerade the fruit made it red
and so i brought it i was like oh man i
could pour the blue in here but i want
it i want to make it like it kind of
looks like it could be george but then
we put some blue in there like it's the
real goomba and then we get like a mix
of like oh wow
and george which is which is
so much lower behind this
i try to put some thought into it
so yeah and then we just add you top it
off with more blue powerade afterwards
but this is like the cool frost power
it's not like the straight blue powerade
so it's like
it's like a little lighter than straight
blue powerade but you can make it more
intense if you want it
so yeah what are we going to sing can we
oh gekku
let's sing
um
[Music]
uh yeah i forgot that we were singing
that [\h__\h] oh it's somewhere i could
maybe there's an instrumental uh
somewhere on youtube i'm sure there is i
think that they're just
okay uh myth or treat i forgot we were
saying that
yeah because it's a spooky drink after
all
[Music]
another treat
there's a piano piano coming wait i have
it i just have to somehow okay yeah yeah
cool
i love playing oh just kidding wait i
can't i can't copy piece do you guys
wait for it maybe
yeah i got the link
except oh god can you send it in the
score
description
to maybe
[Music]
microphone covering giraffe oh no no i
think it's
a tent
oh no no no
and they say bottom left kiana
what
oh it's right there yeah
[Music]
yeah you don't know what you're talking
about big bullies
that actually kind of looks like it
could be i think that should be it's
like a kangaroo tail or something oh
cute
oh wait that's not good
i like that so what if in turn ina in
his tentacles were replaced with shark
tails
like not very tactile then you turn into
the kraken wait can we answer who has
the most drip award out of this oh i
think we know yeah
[Laughter]
when it's about drip well i mean there's
only one answer
what kind of drip though
is it like who's wearing the most ice or
like
who has the most drip the what's going
on what is it swag
what is that yeah it's obviously ena
yeah yeah you know what i'm saying
i know i look beautiful right now no
actually though you look adorable
yeah i'll give you a hug
[Music]
okay i can't get in a little bit
i can't get in you can't no oh
[Music]
oh yeah and they're both super chipped
underneath
[Music]
any technical difficulties
steam
[Music]
some of us will disappear but we'll be
back shortly
i'm just kidding
[Music]
just
try this one your head's looking pretty
big today
you're so big
just
you're welcome
i've been saying that girl is smart
since the beginning
yeah she's like right now
oh yes
your mind at all no
why don't you hesitate no i didn't
change my mind i'm just saying that i
learned more about you oh
yeah that you're super adorable and very
sorry
chill yeah you're very laid back oh yes
i entered
[Music]
oh
yeah
just chilling drinking waiting
we're almost done almost any more
questions chat
you gotta ask us some cute
got a couple more drankies to make a
couple more lives to change
will you change my life today
maybe it depends
this is nice waiting music though yeah
oh it's like elevator music yeah it is
[Music]
is
i'm sorry
[Music]
say how many myths does it take to
change your life
oh man we both got it
away zero oh okay okay we have okay we
have four oh my god we're in thanks will
be moving around a little bit
[Laughter]
two we figured out the answer to that
we figured out the answer what's for
dinner we haven't decided yeah yeah we
haven't decided yet we've been thinking
i haven't seen any weird sleep habits i
think because we've been sleeping in
different beds
yeah except i mean last last night no
the night before i slept in one bed with
but it was all normal did i so
because the air was so dry did i snore
because i never snore no molly i don't
know because i think i
oh yeah i didn't wake up before you and
you know you weren't snoring oh thank
god
thank god you just have to be on your
back to snore does not have anything to
do with the air dryness
i think but if you're sick then
if your nose is like well and my nose
was acting up but no no no no no no way
although i'm gonna dig
ammo did warn me that she
i haven't experienced it but she warned
me that she kicks
maybe you just want to wake up in a time
no because like whenever whenever i
sleep with someone in the same bed then
i really i go to the very very very edge
of the bed so even if you tried to kick
me she couldn't have
hit me
i was dodging while i was sleeping smart
yeah
is that a giraffe
yes
that's so fitting because you put a
gatorade in in her drink yeah exactly it
works it works out star i want some gar
all right i think uh everything is
uh hold on i'm just gonna hide this one
second
[Music]
what are these questions honestly who
has the best feet i don't know maybe
what no i do not i do not have the best
feet i bet gooda has the best feet yeah
how do i touch that
let me see
[Laughter]
with chipped nail polish
boy
i never claimed to have beautiful feet
what about enos
i remember one one not
no sleeping but i don't know today this
morning i found ame
sleeping in a funny way she had the
blanket
wrapped around the top of her head over
her eyes you realize that yeah it's a
survival tactic
well when it's really bright and you
want to go to sleep what you could do is
take the edge of the blanket and wrap it
around the top part of your head i was
thinking you didn't turn it sideways and
you could still breathe through your
mouth but your eyes are covered so i
sleep like that all the time oh that's
so smart i was thinking that might have
been a reason and then one more thing um
you you could never
never ever break uh safely and securely
break into where my limbs because
i
when i saw her there was a huge heavy
metal object lying next right next to
her i was like i'm like why is that here
and she was like to protect myself
[Laughter]
wow
i'm sleeping on the couch so you know i
i i i figured i'm probably the first
line of defense so i had a sex defense
you know ready to go sleeping right next
to me ready to defend all of these
mythical myth members the detective will
protect us even though we have mythical
superpowers
i got a big amount of guys
those british men
yeah that was a few things that i've
noticed
[Music]
now that everything's fixed we're gonna
have everything oh can we sing now
yes
yeah i have it ready
[Music]
but this one has actually lyrics
excitement
lyrics
you're a drop it low babies hiding
behind your screens it ain't a spooky
halloween without some mythical beings
it's halloween
hungry dinosaur just one tiny bite
please
all right singing songs that make you
peace
candy
[Music]
did you stop the pgm uh oh yeah
okay
[Music]
here we go
spooky spooky get ready for halloween
[Applause]
[Music]
i
[Applause]
[Music]
there's no bonds about it you'll scream
only show you on halloween are spooky
are terrified scarier sides
oh what a gotcha coin night
mythic witches with endless
hungry dinosaur just one tiny
the viewers with a song if you're brave
and sing along that's your wife i am a
pumpkin ding dong
in the graveyard
if you're looking let's go sing songs
that make you peace
why
give you shivers make you shout just
like that mommy
spooky ladies that is
[Music]
[Applause]
something something this chainsaw to
come in handy trick-or-treat but now
we're all out of candy
feeling something hold on what the [\h__\h]
how could i remember girl's lyrics and
not mine
oh my god there are lyrics for it on the
internet
feeling just a little sick i never would
have remembered that [\h__\h]
i should have write more lyrics about
pete drink it always
i always think i never write i always
thought to myself what remembering
lyrics isn't hard then i wrote more than
four songs
all right new drink at
there's only two left yes
should we get the dice roller to roll
the dice yeah come off the dice
all right pick another one guys
eight eight
[Music]
basically
in their food
[Laughter]
[Music]
you guys use the bgm a good volume chat
maybe i'll try
sorry i hurt your ears
[Music]
anyway yes
try convincing gooda not to drink red
bull for breakfast yeah what the hell
there's some breakfast
you had like what did you order oh now
you're glad you're
about your own mistakes first
breakfast is merely a concept okay
okay i told her it's science you're
breaking the fast
show something how did you eat something
drink some water
oh yeah yeah i ordered oh yeah i did
order a cupcake uh not for breakfast
though that was after my breakfast i had
a bagel so i'll put it down but
you guys you had carbs in the in the
physical form i have carbs in the liquid
for it yeah i guess it even doubt
amen's um
diet seems more or less healthy to me
who's the who's the healthiest at like
food wise who consumes the most healthy
food from top to bottom
who would be number two
you probably i mean but i i used
yesterday for dinner i ate waffles with
nutella so
i keep having to tell them like eat
fresh vegetables
no i don't love fresh fruit and
vegetables but i think like out besides
you we're all pretty unhealthy food
like my family's food so they're like
probably yeah it's healthy i'd imagine i
guess i like veggies yeah once you're on
europe what about all the cup noodles
huh
when you're on your
i took off the mushrooms but that
doesn't make me look healthy i know
mushrooms like taste buds
[Laughter]
there must be something that you don't
like then emma you might know tell me
what does she not take off of food if
there's something
[Music]
i feel like she's not really that picky
because she's like oh whatever
maybe green onions
no i like green onions peppers green
peppers
[Music]
it does have a weird texture i like the
shape though it's cute the shape is cute
yeah yeah yeah cute shape
huh
yeah because i had black olives on a
pizza and it fell on the floor and i
told her to eat it but she said
are you hearing this she said she said
i'll eat it tomorrow
why that made it worse
[Music]
no i cleaned it up though i made sure
that she wouldn't do that i know it's a
danger to her own house so
[Music]
out of these members and i asked it
because i know the answer is
although maybe uh that depends on the
scenario maybe
who is the cl
cleanly cleanly cleanliness or like um
no that's not quite the answer
i feel like i haven't seen too much
stuff from ina
like too much stuff
i will say i'm
everywhere
no it's okay i don't mind it it wasn't
so bad no but today and yesterday i
would like to defend myself yesterday
when we had dinner i brought all the
food to the table and then afterwards i
brought it all into the kitchen counter
right i brought all the plates that you
were that you stopped eating
[Music]
sometimes i tried to be a little bit of
a mama
[Music]
i don't know if you like it maybe it's
good
did somebody
[Music]
[Laughter]
margarita mix with sweet and sour
and then um
and then i put a bunch of different
fruits on it and then i shook the
uh the
sour with the pina colada mix and then i
topped it with coca-cola and put
color-wise
[Music]
i like to think dr oopsie isn't just a
soda it's got like a little special
flair to it oh my goodness
you really need to open up uh of the
drinks
you know i just hope you like it i do my
best mixing drinks change changing lives
changing lives mixing drinks
mixing mixing lives changing drinks
mixes
what are we singing next um speaking of
lives do you guys want to sing live
again yeah
[Music]
no no no we've been just listening to it
okay that's why i feel like you sang it
they were singing it a little bit that's
true
let me check okay
oh laugh again lyrics oh dear oh dear
i feel like i sang it in the card before
so i should be good
i even make sure they're right because
sometimes i can even do the wrap i think
i can't remember that you're gonna like
it
let's hit the ground before i have to
flash back to shiny gummy
the entry of a brand new story
[Music]
it does not bode well it's because
that's all
in my head
all right that's fine if you guys want
to wrap with me you can go down
here
my body batteries are
loose oh you can here you can use this
okay yeah you can use this one oh thank
you gozaimasu yes yes
you're worse than me
all right
nice am i really angry
give my body back give me my body back
body back body back body back
that's my new thing instead of gods
i know right i'm sorry
yes to this archive chat that's why
we're singing songs that we can archive
yes
it would be fun to do on our cup though
i know
one of these days
[Music]
here we go
beats by marie
sang by holo myth
this is a song of my first album
but it's still really fun to sing
chuckles oh more
[Music]
goodbye i can't promise it's a matter of
time before we're best friends it's not
the end i'm getting married now this is
every closed door it's just the intro of
a brand new story one wish that i can't
pretend i don't wanna see you come true
i know it wouldn't make a difference
but maybe it's deliverance but the pain
i know is coming on when my old cell's
finally gone it's not wrong to think
about it but i'll stop for the night
cause we're gonna last forever and this
sounds like we're right now
say
[Music]
um
where everybody's cherishing life in one
same space and it's embarrassing to say
because you're the one that i've chased
but seeing realities with making life
sweeter than the taste frank fatalities
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
see you again sometimes
a song in my heart
[Applause]
[Music]
you guys are great you guys could be
wrapped
yeah because that's not an easy song to
write especially in english if it isn't
like your like very first language too
it's really hard you know i i learned
your uh
very first most famous she special
i
practiced that one so hard and i must
say my wrap is on fire it's really great
i love it you are you are fantastic but
all of you ladies are on fire thank you
so much for singing my song you guys are
amazing
thank you you guys are so sweet and last
but not least speaking of tensho you're
in my last subject
oh yeah
[Applause]
that's right what do you like to drink
kiara no i see so far you've made a lot
of like berry based stuff yeah do you
have the possibility to make something
like citrusy oh like a grapefruit kind
of thing ah not grape
lemon and limestone lemon and the orange
lime
if you have something let me see what i
can do
wow i'm gonna get berries too but since
i want to have some variation here
[Music]
really
also covered it before like 3 40 yeah
we could both try to sing along
a little i think i think there is a
karaoke too
that's why i shouldn't put you on the
spot like that
hopefully the file that we got to play
oh
yeah it's a trade it's a trade
[Music]
wow
yeah there's like a certain way
[Music]
let me pause the other music
such a sweet song
[Music]
my
m
hey
[Music]
a
oh
[Music]
how
m
[Music]
me
[Applause]
so beautiful
[Music]
is
oh if you just write r.i.p or something
yeah yeah okay that's a a really
songs that i've listened to for so many
years i don't remember the name yeah for
example
love conqueror
is this okay
yeah yeah
hell yeah oh then i don't even have to
oh
all right we can we can do this one
right hell yeah
yeah baby
it's our channel
[Music]
[\h__\h] it
could you let go of your soul for me but
that's the key
[Music]
is
version ain't none that wasn't past me
gotta take a first class magically to
philosophy humans come out be a mess
acoustic absolutely
[Applause]
[Music]
is
bye
[Music]
human nature
[Applause]
[Music]
like
first first the lime comes at you and
the sparkling
but then there's like way
can you guess what it is
hey something iced tea
yeah there's a little bit of mango
oh so good that will that will heal my
throat that i just killed
exactly yeah but it's mostly got like
lemon lime stuff so of course
traditional stuff i love it
and then i actually use the first time
using traditional margarita mix tonight
so i use traditional margarita mix a
little bit of sweet and sour um some
mango and then i love it together and
then i topped it with um
a bubbly lime soda and then just a
little bit of the passion fruit fonza to
get like the gradient of like um
[Music]
yes of course it was my pleasure in fact
because we just uh made a drink for
kiara would you guys like to sing an
orange bird song yeah because i'd like
to sing
you know
tell me
hold on give me the video
all right let me see i gotta pull up
them lyrics too because i don't know
you guys don't know yes
yes we can do that
then we're only missing
i can do my cowboy one
hell bladder
yeah
return to the pastures
out there i love it though
[Music]
all right i'm ready
yes ladies let's go you know what we
should do
um like uh
uh you know that game where you have
something hot in your hand not really
but then
how about like we pass someone on the
shoulder and the next person strings
that part or something now we hear
yourself oh my god
oh my god
oh i'm sure
you heard me a
[Laughter]
might be nice it doesn't have to be
perfect you want to say the words i help
you
if you have a problem
everything and we
go
[Laughter]
we actually can go we're sitting in the
same order as it's on the screen so we
can go from left to right or so oh
you're first oh okay okay okay
all right let's go quick
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
i
good
[Music]
oh
i've been trying to find my destiny
[Music]
hey
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
is
i promise i will find
[Applause]
thanks for the hello
thank you for singing my songs
[Music]
and for everybody who wants to see the
famous kikkity kick again please watch
my birthday concert
[Applause]
yeah yeah oh there's no more drinks to
make i know right i was like oh i guess
we kind of finished up here
i don't know
we should get to an end anyway yeah
cause we gotta eat tender
let's do it
with ben
[Applause]
no bread you know it's a baby
[Music]
funny
um bales asked
i'm there
but no no i think am i telling baile
said chihuahua was dressing very fancy
yeah because yeah and then after them
oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
tiara and bear like dressed super nice
and the rest of us are just like like
hood rats
[Music]
yeah when she came in i was shook but
wow it's streaming in time
i don't know if anybody's up for it i'm
up for it to do like an unarchived
version but you guys don't have to join
but yeah good i'm gonna i know she wants
to do what i'll jump hey maybe you can
also sing with us if you're available
maybe
just open inside okay all right but for
now it's uh the last song for today for
right now yeah we've waited to do this
ah i can't believe thomas is
and we've all been waiting for you guys
it's finally come the time that we
they're all together
thousands maybe a thousand days not even
really done
eight hours
[Music]
fly dummies
we can't fly grocery stores and lyrics
journey
thank you very much you guys who have
been here to journey with us
[Music]
happy to have you guys take the journey
with us
we're celebrating two years soon soon
tomorrow fully enclaved
tomorrow
together everybody tomorrow
you know how do you feel about that
being has that that having become such a
meme i think it's so funny because i was
reacting to it it's funny because i was
very active in the march too
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay i got the lyrics on my i'm
yeah
oh boy
all right it just takes off immediately
okay here we go
[Music]
to finally defeat this journey
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
little
[Music]
the longer we wait the stronger it makes
success we fight every fade strength to
finally defeat this journey a thousand
years to meet
[Music]
witness to fire in our minds burning
inside rising again from the ashes every
bruising scratches makes us feel more
alive we never give up never keep it no
matter what's ahead instead we'll crush
your worries aside
and there's no world for us to touch or
to see
we'll make it ourselves and make
memories
there ain't a mystery our brains cannot
solve we just shine brighter go tighter
we fall
connecting songs across that wall
take off and fly the longer we wake the
stronger it makes us as we fight
everything
strength to finally defeat this journey
a thousand years to me
at the end of this world where's a
fighting chance
nothing's changing it's always the same
story staged with a different dance
seek out a happy end for me my friends
and those who love to stop to know
i wanna see your smile
[Music]
this journey a thousand years to me
let's try it can't be denied the wish in
my heart is you right here by my side
today is all that will need i won't wait
a thousand years
[Music]
wow
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for sticking with us through
this journey
yeah it's been a while it's not over yet
we still got lots more fun stuff to do
from here on out and it gets better and
better i know it
now one day we can all sing this on
stage yes yes
dance for you
yeah yeah i think i think we will
waiting for that moment subscribe
for more patience yes please just wait a
bit longer guys we'll see it i promise
we finally finally met
[Music]
no matter what it's going to be fun
um
[Music]
thank you very much
let's continue supporting home
bye-bye
[Applause]
[Music]
so
you