foreign
[Music]
thank you
laughs
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
laughs
[Music]
thank you thank you
oh
okay
[Music]
yeah
hi hello
[Music]
um
hello
come on
yay I'm in Japan
did my tweets My Stream starting tweet
go through oh my God it did go through
amazing Elon Musk amazing I can't
believe it whoa
yeah a nice good morning crack
our favorite Yellow Ostrich streamer
so
um maybe we should address the elephant
in the room already
I know
right here below me it says album
physical CD pre-order ending in six
hours 29 minutes and oh it's oh wait
it's not moving because I have to have
the window open nevermind one moment the
window there you go okay it's 22 minutes
oh my God the world is ending as you
heard in my voice pack my new voice pack
in case you didn't hear it yet and
there's a new voice pack out
[Music]
um on the whole life shop that you can
buy uh so since the world is ending
apparently in six hours 22 minutes and
five seconds
um you should get the album physical
release if you haven't yet that's
basically
um one of the reasons why I chose to
stream early in the day to remind
everybody who doesn't uh have a like a
reservation yet she
[Music]
um
and if it doesn't end after these six
hours
well then I guess
I guess then don't ever believe my
claims ever again
um but yeah
um
that was the the and you know like a
countdown like this is just so ominous
ominious I mean ominous
um so
no I'm not gonna be swimming for six
hours I don't I'm not no no this will be
a short stream uh maybe one maybe two
hours uh short because I originally I
was gonna stream like longer
because I had all day time but now I
don't have all day time anymore because
it's
crooked it's so
cool I should lower the AC is I I'm in a
big room all alone one second
[Music]
you know something's wrong when the wow
says it's cold
with AC
it wasn't even that uh low
[Music]
um
well I am inside right now yeah
I just wanted the Japanese looking
background because I I I you know I'm in
Japan
you were cold last year when you were in
a swimsuit
I said I was cold really are you sure
are you sure
well
so what was I saying oh yeah I have
something to do now and I wonder if I
should tell you
what what I have to do
[Laughter]
maybe I'll tell you
um it's a possible tangent for today
it's yeah
[Music]
um
yeah well so oh my God tangents for
today I want to tangent about well you
know there's not so much attention about
because I just arrived like three four
days ago probably four days at this
point
um but I wanna uh I need to I have to
talk about my flight
cause that was special for many reasons
and I need to talk about a little bit
maybe a little bit about bookable and uh
the collab that we did with Aki said by
yesterday
uh and meeting up with Moni my lyric
writer who wrote like every lyric in the
new songs
and uh yeah and then possibly the
retention about why
I am a little bit busy for the rest of
the day
uh yeah so but before we start let me
just ask you have you guys reserved your
physical CD of my album
have you I mean
yes yes yes yes no why not please do
please please please it's special like
it's the first time I'm ever releasing
like a physical piece of music that you
can physically touch and put in your
shelf
as a memoir
um
foreign
[Music]
Fried Chicken from kfp is the best
that's what it says behind me it's a
famous proverb in Japan
[Music]
I have to hope for a re-release sometime
can't get it right now oh no I don't
know about re-releasing it the chances
for that are
actually not that low maybe they did uh
mention that like if the sales are good
then it is possible to consider
even extension or a re-release I think I
think it was supposed to be a real
release I don't know
um
yeah oh YouTube kids organize a group
order
noise
[Music]
I'm not
jet lagged anymore
um the past two nights I slept while
having really bad nightmares but I slept
plenty I'm fine and I actually I slept
early and woke up earlier today too oh
yeah so everything is good yesterday I
even woke up at like what was it like 6
a.m right because I I went to bed like
at like 10 pm or so because I was so
tired
I'm so tired
I'm tired but yeah I'm currently
sleeping at normal
or like
I don't know good good hours Healthy
hours
sorry that you had nightmares yeah you
know my nightmare tonight was um
being a university student no
I mean that was part of the dream but
that was not the Nightmare part of the
tree
for some people it's certainly a
nightmare
well honestly for me it might be a
nightmare too thinking to go back to
school uh is quite a nightmare
no it was something else but this was
this was part of my dream I was like in
uh in University but I don't even I
don't even really
I can't even really imagine how it works
like I don't know if my dream was even
accurate if this is how well probably
not if this is how a university Works
probably not
um
I still have nightmares about being in
school and I've been out for a couple
years now yeah thankfully I don't
normally have this
kind of
dream about being in school
um
[Music]
still have nightmares about exams oh oh
I never
we never have nightmares about such
things
I have lots of other nightmares but not
that
University was fun for me I did
wait you sold homework oh wow is that
like legal actually
it's illegal right that must be illegal
that's certainly illegal right I only
hear about this stuff like maybe not
about homework like in in like Netflix
shows like you you hear about like
really smart guys that it was a show
like suits for example right who the guy
who makes money by writing other
people's tests
a real entrepreneur
I do something like that for real oh
[\h__\h] have you guys seen there's like
um there was a gathering in Harvard
they're getting more and more
um we have like two k like confirmed
kfps in Harvard and one takodati in
Harvard and they gathered
I mean
[Music]
um
my fans are smart very smart
I love
and I have to like retweet this kind of
stuff because I love spreading the image
I don't know like for someone like me
when like I I only heard about Harvard
and these like places and like shows
because I'm not even from America but
it's like fascinating to me that it's
like an actual real place and
and there's my hands there and they're
so smart a million times smarter than me
it's a real place
that is fascinating
[Music]
Harvard is in the UK
it's not in the UK
wait what
why so much
what's the time before are you for real
like read my God if you can read the
timer and you can read what's written
right next to it on the left side
yeah okay thank you don't confuse me
that's Oxford that's Cambridge Oxford
and Cambridge are UK and then Harvard
and what's the other one
um that were roaring from Gilmore Girls
went to that's also really famous the
the other one Yale yeah Yale is does is
Yale really that well known as like a
competitor to Harvard in in America like
if people think about uh you know
another harvard-like school do they
think of Yale yeah wow
yeah she was supposed to go to Harvard
her whole life her dream was to go to
Harvard but then
she ended up going to Yale and her like
everybody was like confused like what
the [\h__\h] her mom was like girl your
whole life you wanted to go to Harvard
now you're going to yeah are you sure
about this are you sure about it and
she's like yeah mom leave me alone I
want to go to Yale now okay it's my
decision hmm
by the way I'm using a like ashore now
it's been a while since I've last been
in the studio here
in the streaming rooms
like uh it used to be different mics
that they were using here but I like
that they're using a show now it's not
it's not the famous sure sm7b it's like
it looks like the smaller version the
smaller sure is it written here no it's
like a smaller smaller sure but it's
cute though it has a similar sound so I
like it I like sure sounds it's podcast
microphone
um it's a bit smaller I don't know which
one it is but sharp it's so funny to me
sure brought out a new microphone
you don't even understand how funny that
is
uh let me talk about it let me talk
about okay just it's just a short it's
just a short
jerk Okay so
sure as um there's a famous microphone
that maybe you noticed after you look at
it
um many many streamers and podcasters
and radio people they only use this one
I use it a lot of streamers use it
um mostly like overseas [\h__\h] Japanese
people may not use it so much
um yeah but there's this famous
microphone it's called sure
sm7b yeah and uh I've been using it and
generally like it's it may kind of be on
the quiet side but if you're using like
a Lego you know local mixer that has
like a preamp and they're like just go
away SLI for example then you it's fine
you know it it it pushes the gain
um but for some reason out of nowhere
after years of people buying and using
the Shure sm7b they brought out an
upgraded version
a louder version and it's called sure SM
seven
b b
foreign
[Music]
whoa audio engineer joke
but uh don't misunderstand it's not like
it's only 7db louder no um I think I
read it was
up to
was it 15 or 13
something like that more DB louder
it's not just 7 DB
you may not like uh
yeah 28 was it 28 okay
it's it has a like built-in preamp now
so if you if you don't have one yet then
you should get the updated version
upgraded version maybe
um but I don't think it's worth buying
for people who already have the old one
because then you also already have a
setup that makes it work properly like
in terms of like
volume so
so soyukoto
[Music]
yeah for people who don't know DB stands
for decibels when you you know the odd
like the amount of other you know like
like kilometers or whatever for
distances
it's the same thing you know kmdb those
are like you know you know yeah
okay okay okay audio jerk which is so
[Music]
oh
you hear my you hear my bottle
ASMR
[Music]
speaking of ASMR
I think it's the day after tomorrow
[Music]
I have collab with noido Senpai
my first ever ASMR
yeah we wanted to do it last time I was
here uh but she got sick right so we had
to move it and now I'm back again so
we're doing it the day after tomorrow I
think
it's just like a probably like an
introductionary
ASMR like I don't know how to do it so
just gonna like teach me Basics probably
but it's gonna be on her Channel
um
and um
probably like a lot of Japanese but in
the end it's like you know like making
sounds like
so it's more about the sounds
yeah
ASMR coaching not that I will start
doing ASMR after that regularly no not
at all
uh but you know I always wanted to I
always saw this as like an idea for uh
officer lab with someone who's good with
ASMR so
I just thought it's good to do it
at least once at some point
is
did you guys notice I stole Ina's chat
box again every time I'm overseas I have
Ina's chat box
you know lava's overseas when she's
using Ina's chat box
hey
yeah
there's a reason for it
yeah but you it's it fits the pink well
doesn't it
I think it does
yeah
oh yeah
[Music]
I'm I'm I'm already embarrassed now
thinking about doing ASMR but oh well
gonna have fun hopefully you're also
using a video
I don't know about that this is just one
that I picked out
I have a big library of audio stock
songs thingies
that I use it's just one of the ones
that I have in my drive
uh you know when I when I travel when I
set up the OBS every time from scratch
uh I I just choose one of the tracks I
use as a I use it quite a quite a lot
too
yeah
kick over key
[Music]
good coincidence I didn't know she's
using it hmm
thing
this is prime Kiana vacation BTM
accent change yeah
[Music]
I asked a certain link a a
um
possibly British staff
uh how to pronounce
in British accent uh
but it's hard to pronounce Kiki to keep
britishly
because there's not much that you can
play with there
um
[Music]
yes British stuff happens yes
why don't well you know it had to happen
at some point because we you know we we
keep on hiring like English speaking
staff for us so it's not a surprise that
you know it's on point someone British
but you know maybe we should have hired
this staff as a streamer
not as a staff because
you some people want to hear a British
accent right the people were always
waiting for a British accent within a
new gen
and we still are not providing it to you
it's Elementary in it
[Music]
stand that I still don't understand that
phrase what do you mean it's elementary
elementary are you going to elementary
school what you're too young too young
for all I've done
[Music]
anyway
um
it's simple oh yeah I forgot that's
that's what it meant six
six oh
[Music]
my God
stress
panic panic
panic panic panic
I just bought your city thank you
the world is ending
okay it's been half an hour let's get
into my real tangent shall we
[Music]
I will talk about
let's start from the very beginning
a very nice place to start
let's talk about my flight
to Japan why is it so special
I haven't tweeted about it yet but don't
worry the stream will be shorter than
six hours so I'll tweet about it after
the stream is done
um
how do I start this
how do I start this oh
um
so I normally fly premium economy
these days
these days as in since I joined the
whole life
uh but even premium economy even flying
with that it's a big Improvement but
even with that I am in pain when I fly
with premium economy
um especially like for some reason
normally I don't have pain in my legs
but when I fly I get like weird
pain in my legs only when I fly
or
wait I think I might get it also when do
I get it when I'm like on a training
Zone
I'm not sure but I definitely get it
when I fly
um and I've tried things like you know
like socks like the the special socks
um but it didn't really help yeah and
maybe the air pressure
yeah but I I don't hear about from many
other people that their legs
specifically hurt that much like
immediately the moment I'm like in the
plane like I'm not even sitting
uncomfortably but still hurts no
[Music]
no
um so it might be a pressure thing yeah
I tried the compression socks but it
doesn't work so uh when I was booking my
flight for this trip I booked premium
economy and the price was nice not so
nice actually expensive but uh worth it
at least for premium economy and then
when I was done booking My Flights
when I was booking by flight
I noticed something that I have never
seen before
[Music]
there was an option
to
bid
for an upgrade to business
to bid kind of like an auction
yeah a bit I was like what I've never
seen this before
[Music]
I I feel I never saw this before so I
was curious right I was curious
um and so I am I I tried I like I opened
that up and then it automatically
gosh I hate wearing pants why am I
wearing pants
it automatically showed me like you know
this like there's like a like a uh like
a like a bar where you can move the the
what's it called
[Music]
well anyway it gives you like a choice
you can you can choose how much you're
bidding uh and then like it
automatically was set to like something
like 2 000 or so two a slider yeah that
was a slider
um and it was like automatically set to
like 2 000 bucks or so for one flight
and I'm like hmm how low can I go so I
went to the very left of the bar the
slider and the lowest bid you could do
that that uh I could enter was like
815 Euro which is like really roughly
800 bucks as well uh US dollars
um
and I thought
[Music]
I in my brain since the the slider was
so big and you could bid so much and
there's not many seats in business
anyway I didn't think that my bid would
be accepted but I should give it a try
because you know 800 isn't so bad I
never flew business before my whole life
would be nice to at least once try it so
if it happens that's fine if it doesn't
happen that's fine I don't expect it to
be happening but if it if it happens
then maybe I should accept it and enjoy
it just for once in my life and treat
myself you know that's like my thought
process like I'm doing the lowest bit
possible
I I wouldn't get it right like it said
like um we will tell you we will notify
you if your bid has been accepted uh on
like the day before the flight and you
can silver track your bid until that
point
uh but uh after you've been accepted you
can't retract it
and yeah so I was like you know you know
you know for if it if it if it happens
and happens if it doesn't happen then
I'm probably relieved because I don't
wanna I still think it's expensive like
in total I know I think I already paid
like if you add premium economy
uh like the the main ticket price and
then the 800 bucks upgrade for one
flight uh I think it was still cheaper
than buying business on its own
I'm pretty sure
um pretty sure I think I even checked
the business prices out of curiosity but
it was too expensive
um yeah
800 yeah 800 bucks on top what did you
think of course not only 800 for whole
flights it's it's a direct flight it's
uh uh in a good Airline it's
you know long distance of course it's
not gonna be like super cheap yeah it's
still a lot yeah but I thought
I thought you know I want to try this
out I don't know it's super like I
wanted to try it out but I really didn't
think I I would be accepted for the
upgrade so I was like kind of relief
like the whole time I was like oh it's
not gonna happen anyway I'm I'm flying
premium economy and then
and then I get the email
yeah I went like YOLO then I get the
email
[Music]
your bid has been accepted
I'm like oh no
and I was actually like panicking like
oh no I no no no no
why don't you accept my [\h__\h] what do
you mean nobody bid more than me did
everybody just bit the minimum what the
[\h__\h] or did nobody bid at all no
but I was like well might as well enjoy
it that's okay that's okay I'll try it
out
the thing is I bid for both back and
forth and they like first they accept
like you know a day before the flight
they accepted so
um only the the two Japan bid has been
accepted for now and I was like I'm
gonna try it out and then I'm gonna
decide if I want to retract my bid for
the flight back but it's already so much
money and I recently almost went
bankrupt so uh I'm gonna cancel the
other vid that's for sure
um
remind me please remind me I shouldn't I
need to retract my bids
what did they accept it
um but yeah
um that was another story almost going
bankrupt um that was another fun story
in my Twitter space yesterday
um
so I was like okay well you know
it's I I normally I'm like
sometimes people are even surprised that
I'm still so careful with my money so I
thought for once
you know I can treat myself okay and and
and and for once not fly in pain maybe
you know
so I accepted it the way it is and I was
looking forward to it I was getting
excited I was like well well there's no
going back now so I'm gonna enjoy yeah
give me a treat yourself treat yourself
as they like to say in uh Parks and Rec
[Music]
nanto
um
[Music]
it sounds more expensive in Japanese
just because the yen is so weak man
um
why am I being tagged on the score
[Music]
okay
okay so I have photos oh let me tell you
like wow it it was really comfortable
so
I came to to the airport and first of
all I there was a special area to check
in
um where only people of business or
first class are allowed to check in okay
don't have to nowadays like a lot of
airports they like make you do
everything yourself like you have to
check in yourself maybe you even have to
check in your bags yourself
um but
um
I didn't have to do that I was checked
in properly which was good because I saw
like you know
um I originally for premium economy I
chose a seat
um when I when I booked the flight but
obviously since I got upgraded I lost
the seat right so I checked
um about this this this I find
kind of
how to say
well [\h__\h] up
um but if you you already paying so much
money for business class right and then
when you're choosing the seeds there are
still seats that you have to pay extra
for like there's
um Austrian Airlines
um constellation
layout of the business class seats are
not ideal
um there's uh not many like solo seats
and it's not ideal like compared to
other business classes also there's no
first class even by the way Austrian
Airlines doesn't even have a first class
wow which maybe at least that makes the
business class a little bit better maybe
they try to you know find like an
in-between I don't know
um but yeah they they charge extra if
you want to get a solo seat
um because probably because the solo see
it's because of the weird layout
kind of are huge
they're huge they're like they literally
are called Thrones
because they're huge I don't know who
designed this honestly it's kind of
stupid
[Music]
um
uh I don't know what plane modeling was
no idea
[Music]
um so I was like like when I was
choosing the seats
I saw that
uh almost all of the like uh double
seats were taken except for one row uh
like two of those like one one double
seat pair and all the Solo Seats were
uh like free still to take to choose but
they weren't free of charge of course
um so I was like you know the chances of
me when I just go to the air airport
without having chosen a seat yet without
checking in online yet the chances of
them giving me one of those Solo Seats
instead of the double seat that I have
to sit next to a stranger then I'm
pretty high at that rate because like
like they were like one two three four
five I think there were five solo seats
left
four of them Thrones and one not quite a
throne but like half of a throne
and we will see it later
um and then oh lean two normal seats
that are like a pair sitting next to
each other
so the chances were high of me getting a
solo suit especially driving solo you
know so I thought I'm not gonna check it
online I'm gonna let it happen I'm gonna
go there I'm gonna hope that they give
me a solo seed for free you know because
like they say I even like watched like
Airline reviews of this uh to make to
understand a bit more and they said like
if you if you if you're lucky and you
didn't choose your seat yet or whatever
and you go to the airport and you check
in they might give you the throne seats
for free because that's what they have
left over because it's the only seats
that you have to pay for extra so often
they're left over at the end it's Scott
giant strategy yeah
and we drink some water
oh
so
so that's what I did and I went to the
airport and I said it's my first time
flying business
and the lady was really nice and I asked
so about the scenes and she was like
yeah um so
I can I have um uh uh this uh SoMo seat
and it wasn't the throne basically there
were four Thrones and one half of a
throne and I got that one which is fine
in the end at least I got to sit alone I
had the window and the aisle both to
myself and
um it was nice so I even went to the
lodge before uh going to the airplane
and the lodge was fine they had some
pretty good looking food I only got
myself like a dessert and the dessert
was [\h__\h] but normal food looked really
good
and in the in the launch
uh like 90 of the people sitting in a
lodge were like men
in
80 suits
I was thinking damn ladies
ladies where you at where my business
lady is yeah why why no ladies and
flying business man that's sad but yeah
probably probably 90 of these people in
business didn't pay for a ticket like I
did but they got a free upgrade or
booked it with their miles
because they fly in business all the
time because of their companies that
support them so the real business lady
here is me because I paid for it
well yeah yeah
gotta put on some cool glasses some cool
shades to show how cool I am
but I I feel like I really stood out
like I was like
a small girl Solo Traveler
in like like almost pajamas and
everybody else was like you know looking
like old and serious and manly
[Music]
yeah okay and then
launch I went to the
to the like gate and there was a special
area
for us two there but well it was so
crowded but then yeah I get into the
airplane and I get to my seat and it was
in the last row of the business class
and which I I liked that in general
because
nobody can pick at what I'm doing for or
watching I don't like it like I some
when I'm sitting like in front of people
I peek at what they're watching
sometimes and just you know judging them
silently when you're in the very back
nobody can judge you silently like I do
so
so the business business
[Music]
this was my seat
okay this is like the basic form when
it's not like flat or whatever
but you see there's like a big
oh the soccer bag that's from me that's
like omiyage that's a souvenirs that I
brought again for I'm probably gonna
give it to the ID Girls
[Music]
yeah there's a lot of leg room going
into the left uh you'll see later I have
another picture but yeah there's like
this big story big
um like table right next to you the
fronts basically have that on both sides
the solo Thrones so this is only half of
the throne it's a single scene but yeah
and then if you uh if you on the seat
that's like not a throne not a solo but
like next to another person then it's
basically what I got
you uh yeah you only get like one of
these like side tables thingies
I like the aesthetic me too like I took
an extra picture of that
it's It Feels So Austrian like the the
pillow and the blanket they were so
fluffy and cute like with a kind of like
a austrianish design like a dandel
design I don't know it's kind of like
you know it gives me all certain Vibes
for sure the blanket was really like
um pretty heavy and big and comfortable
the pillow was Fluffy I brought my own
pillow I always bring my own pillow but
still
um it was like you know you can see the
size like here in comparison when it's
on the seat
[Music]
foreign
I want the blanket I kind of wanted to
blanket had a nice nice pattern so the
amenities that you get like you know
under the reading lamp there's like a
little bag of amenities The Melodies are
kind of [\h__\h] I've seen better amenities
even for premium economy and other
airlines
but it's fine
um there's like uh headphones in there
the headphones premium economy gets the
same headphones economy doesn't get
these headphones as far as I know
they're a little bit uh noise canceling
but not as good as mine
but they connect with the screen so I
had to use them
um oh yeah and then inside the side
table there's the the dining table that
you can take out which is
um a little bit more spacious than the
other classes uh then there was like a a
panel a touch panel for the seat where
you could like make it go flat or just
relaxing mode and there was a massage
option but the massage like it's not a
massage I think massage modes in most of
those so-called massage chairs unless
it's like a proper massager like a
proper one but most of them are so
useless like
it's like it's like barely touching you
it's just like really softly like giving
you the feeling that something is
happening but you're not quite sure
what's happening
no it's not vibrating it's just really
it was just really slowly
really slowly kind of like something was
moving but I was not being massaged no
it was so [\h__\h]
so weird
um
um but yeah there's a lot of storage
space
uh yeah it's good it's good it's good
and then
uh
before the takeoff
um a chef comes out there's a chef
dressed in Chef clothes
I don't think he's like cooking
everything there
but I mean what else would he be there
for maybe he's like
preparing some things but a lot of
things are probably like pre-prepared uh
prepared
um yeah but he was like wearing like a
chef hat and Chef clothes so Chef
is
[Music]
so he comes to you to each passenger in
the business class gives them a menu and
uh lets you like choose from the menu
what you want for other for the main
course so there was like
um a lunch
uh in the beginning of the flight and
the breakfast
at the end of the flight because the
arrival would be in the morning time in
Japan
yeah so when it's morning time when you
arrive they usually serve a breakfast
then even if it makes no sense
like in the time zone where you came
from yeah but they adjusted like that
um and then in between there's like some
some stuff you can get to of course like
snacks a few snacks
and so the Highlight was definitely the
first poof because there you could
actually like
put everything together like you can
make your whole menu yourself like this
this was really cool
um some things they brought out uh on
kind of like uh like uh like a rolling
tray and they bring you like all the
update like for example there's like
three starters but you can mix them and
make your own starter basically so and
also same for the dessert choices you
can you don't have to choose one dessert
you can choose all of them you can mix
them this and that that's really cool
um
foreign
drink and this and that only choose
water but you know and so here comes the
foof I was watching
uh Ariel the live action Mermaid movie
thingy by the way while eating and I
have to say
it was all right uh yeah it was fine
that's fine
um but yeah uh here is my starter and
there was like bread before that but I
didn't take a picture of that this is my
starter basically they had like a salad
bar they had other starters too uh like
salmon whatever but I put together I I
mixed two starters
to start our options so I got a salad
with some
seeds uh grenade Apple
and some ham and some Mountain
cheeseburger and this isn't that and a
nice dressing there are some choices of
dressings you
know this is the side the corner oh and
the table they when they like prepare
the table for you
um they put this like you know thing
over it there's a tablecloth they put a
tablecloth over it
[Music]
enjoy the salad
and then um next starter was a soup and
it said on the menu
uh caramelized green pea soup and I'm
not a huge fan of peas
because I like Black Eyed Peas but not
necessarily the green peas but that's a
soup it was incredible it's so green and
it was so good I legit want to learn how
to make it
the croutons were perfectly crunching I
haven't had like a good soup with proper
croutons in it for a while
um that was super green it tasted so
good well it tasted I never had a soup
like this before it tasted really good
really good stuff
then so for the main course I think they
were like three choices
think yeah free choices and
one of the choices I think this is
probably what they usually do one of the
choices is a typically Austrian Choice
like a schnitzel or a tavish bits and so
on and the other choices are more like
International there was one like
italian-ish choice and one fish choice I
think
um I went with the Austin Choice even
though
this dish has spinach and I
supposedly hate spinach but for some
reason
on this day I felt like trying things
that I don't like
yeah I felt open to trying things that I
don't like and so this is called tavish
bits it's a uh typically Austrian main
course dish with
um a piece of really soft beef that is
boiled endlessly of a long time to get
to make it really soft some potatoes
that were pretty good too
uh the sauce I don't know how to
describe the sauce it's also special
just for this the green looks disgusting
wait it's spinach
cream spinach at least honestly
I it was fine I kind of enjoyed it uh I
didn't eat all of the spinach but I hate
maybe like you know half
or almost half of it ah the sauce was
really good
um the meat was kind of bland but that's
just how this dish is because the meat
on its own is kind of bland you're
supposed to eat it living on the spinach
and the veggies and this and that
um
that texture looks off
to me it's at uh I think this is how
it's supposed to be I'm pretty sure
because like creamed spinach meat there
looks kind yeah that's how it's supposed
to look
trust me this is called toppage bits in
Austria
um
main course of this coverage bits
tougher speeds
[Music]
it's more tasty than it looks like
and it's boiled in soup so it looks
planned but it's not that tasteless okay
it's pretty good
yeah and I felt very proud of myself for
overcoming my hatred for spinach yeah
you should be proud of me too honestly
like my whole life I've been ignoring
spinach like whenever something had
spinach I said no
the only thing with spinach that I ate
in my life throughout my life happily
was um
which is like little dumplings where
spinach is in the dough but you don't
really taste it especially because
normally it's served with cheese sauce
I loved this as a child and I still
really like it today
but spinach on its own no no no no no no
no no
no
[Music]
so even though I knew I didn't like it I
ordered this one because it also sounded
like the best dish compared to the other
options honestly
um
so challenging
I wanted to know if maybe like
after living on this Earth for so many
years maybe now I like it
I wanted to see if maybe my taste buds
have changed
and
it was fine like I didn't think it was
really like my thing my new favorite
thing like super tasty but it was fine
yeah taste buds do change so I thought
I'll give it a try you know
I'll give it a try a little
bit and then dessert came as I said also
from a tray where you could choose from
there was like you could choose from
like a cut fruits and a warm dessert
that's also pretty typically Austrian
but not an apple strudel no it was a a
cream poodle
milk milk cream milk creams one of the
ones and with hot vanilla sauce of
course I was gonna go for that
thankfully they only served a small
piece I was worried that it would be too
much and then they gave me some fruit
too so here is the fruit that was pretty
good and Destroy though it was actually
too small I could have eaten another one
but this will be important later it was
so good I wanted more more and more I
haven't had this type of strudel in a
long time so it felt so nostalgic to me
[Music]
it was so nostalgic
cake
um and then after dinner you know I
didn't sleep so much in the night before
and I knew I would be arriving in the
morning so I wanted to sleep as much as
possible especially because that was for
me the biggest like Merit
Mary yeah plus two being in business
um this was the highlight sleeping and
okay I slept that I did hell yeah
do you want to see my POV speaking of
POV the sales of the physical CD are
ending in five and a half hours
so my POV
was like this okay I I took a night
photo so it like [\h__\h] up the the
screen there because you have to wait
for some time to shutter takes some time
but uh yeah this is
my POV
uh my legs my whole body went completely
straight you could be even bigger than
me and still be completely straight
there's like it goes quite deep into the
under the under the under the TV
and yeah I was wrapped in my blanket
blanket was really comfy and fake and uh
yeah and I could make it completely flat
and I was lying sideways and sideways
and it was really comfy well yeah I I
really I really enjoyed the seat belt
the seat belt is a really fake
um I it was it wasn't like uncomfortable
to have it on top it was really loose
really really loose that's where I'm
actually where my knees were where the
seat belt is is right under my knees not
my body okay
[Music]
that's where my knees were
I think yeah looks like a straight
jacket no
no turbulence at all it was really calm
flight really calm
so I was watching a little bit Parks and
Rec I don't know if you recognized it
but that was Parks and Rec uh before
going to sleep
and yeah really nice turning off the
lights they made the cabin dark and
people could sleep
[Music]
it's definitely spacious enough
and maybe it looks a little bit less
spacious uh on the picture but yeah the
whole thing like when you put push the
go flat button it's like slowly moves
the seat and makes it from this into
this uh yeah you you you go quite low to
the ground pretty close to the ground
actually
Max Camp I was so happy man and I fell
asleep pretty quickly it was Heavenly I
slept through Straight for five out wow
I was never so painless I mean my
shoulders still always hurt whenever
wherever I am doesn't matter but my legs
didn't hurt at all
[Music]
I was sleeping through comfortably
uh without disturbance for five hours
and I woke up because I had to go to
anal meeting and then
I already felt like you know I wanted to
go back to sleep but but you know and
then I I couldn't sleep anymore I
couldn't fall asleep anymore for some
reason but I slept until that point I
slept like I was in heaven
yeah it was so comfy
[Music]
my God
um
it's 800 bucks worth if it was only 800
bucks yeah but this was only on top of
the price that I already paid for
premium economy
so for that well my conclusion will come
later
um I saw one thing in the snack menu
that was so Austrian and spoke to me I
was like I have to get this even when
I'm not hungry I have to get this at
some point of this flight most things
were just like normal snacks like
chocolate or whatever but this thing
you want to know what business class
gets as an option in uh in Austria for
like a Austrian snack
[Music]
Germans will also understand uh
Americans and other countries may not
understand this but
a freaking liver car symbol
live a customer
you don't understand
the charm of this this is so popular
Austrian and German snack like when you
go to supermarket or whatever or to a
meat um thing uh on the counter you can
get like a fresh uh bread roll summer
with uh it's not spam it's lebakas
um you can get this fresh from the warm
counted libertas English
it's uh okay it directly translated it's
liver cheese
[Music]
traditionally served warm or cold in
finger fixed slices uh but this is this
was a free fingers fake they made it way
too big I don't know I was surprised
when I made it that thing it's not
supposed to be dead unbalanced compared
to the bread
it's usually like half of that
but yeah uh with the Crusty Brown ends
being the most prized chunks I wouldn't
say so libertez lit translate literally
it's liver cheese but that's not what it
is it's like a sausage like a sausage
that you can slice off and it's warm and
um
I went here the slides and you roll
traditionally comes from a baked crusty
loaf where the main ingredients are
typically some combination of finely
chopped pork bacon and beef sometimes
liver cancer contains horse meat lamb or
game as its main ingredient but it is
always labeled as such so this was like
an uh not the horse one I don't eat that
one that freaks me out I just eat a
normal one and and they come also in
variations of like cheese like uh
melting cheese inside or some other
variations this was a cheese variation
people love that [\h__\h] not my favorite
but yeah and then often you add some
stuff like pickles or uh
or I think Germans like to have it just
with like ketchup and mustard often but
I like to have either pickles or
pepperonis inside
they didn't have those extras they just
put in mustard and ketchup inside and
then I had a hot tea because I wanted to
fall back asleep but I didn't fall back
asleep yeah but do you understand now
what this is
[Music]
um
it's interesting I'd like I have to try
it you have to yes you have to
you have to but yeah the balance is a
bit off of this one I was genuinely
surprised like what the [\h__\h] this is too
thick but okay it was a bit too much
[Music]
um but it was good it was like and the
bread was also like
um normally I noticed this in like
economy and premium economy the bread
that they give you is
[\h__\h]
um but the business class spread was
really good fresh good bread they had
different choices too but normally um
this is served in you know like a roll a
white bread roll especially in Austria
it's a summer in Germany it's not a
seminal but something like this
um
foreign man
give us the proper bread
yeah business class have different bread
I didn't know you they actually had
proper bread back there in the front
come here
how dare you withhold that from me
but yeah so this was my experience the
food was great ah no wait wait wait
here comes the thing that confuses me I
experienced this a lot when flying
economy or premium economy but I didn't
think that this would happen in business
so I was a bit disappointed disappointed
it's a first world problem it's
absolutely not a real problem but I just
didn't think that this would happen in a
class where you pay thousands and
thousands of bucks to be in
basically few fueling the plane on your
own
because that's what I heard that like uh
without business in first class they
would not
like make the money back from how much
it costs to fly a plane but yeah
um what happened so uh breakfast time
[Music]
I don't understand why they don't just
do the same thing that they do for the
dinner for the lunch or so for the first
meal for the main meal they ask you what
you want and they reserve it for you
and that worked without any issues for
the breakfast there were two choices for
like you know the main part of the
breakfast
and what I wanted to choose
when they came to me in my last Road
there weren't even so many rows but it
was the last row when they came to me
they said they don't have it anymore
and I was like well I don't like the
other option which was porridge and I
don't like porridge and I I okay if I
was sitting in premium economy or
whatever but but I'm in business I'm
paying so much for this why don't you
have like enough options huh and even
the person that they served before me
was already getting like the leftover
option but she seem to be fine with it
but I didn't I don't like porridge
like it no yeah
[Music]
so I was like I didn't want to get angry
I just like I just looked with this like
really
disgusted face
at the ports that they put in front of
me and I was like like she's like sorry
we only have porridge left is this okay
and I'm like looking at it like
ah
[Music]
like I I I really didn't want this this
is not okay but I also didn't want to
make like a big deal out of it because
like what else would they have they have
nothing so
um but then turns out
the lady that was mainly serving me she
was not so good I have to say
um but like she was trying to offer me
other things then she was like
and then she takes away the porridge and
she's trying she comes back later
offering me
free main courses that I've never seen
before so I think uh and the way they
were served also I think they came from
a economy maybe
um but yeah she shows me these like
uh dinner looking main courses and I'm
like
again I just look at it really with this
disgusted face because the food looked
fine but I was in the mood for breakfast
and I'm not happy with this I want the
original I already forgot what it was
but I wanted the original choice and
this was not cool though and in my mind
I was thinking if the one thing I would
maybe consider is going back to this
because this is somewhat breakfasty it
was good I felt like eating more of it
but that was like freshly served like
hours ago I didn't think they would
still have it so I didn't say anything
but like I look at these three choices
again like that she's showing me and I'm
I'm like
[Music]
so she again is like
okay and she disappears again
um and then
uh and I think at the same time
um the Purser was standing next to her
who does with this really happy face and
they had this you know in in in in in
Airline Cruise the Purser is the scary
boss
who can be such an [\h__\h] to the rest
of the crew because the person has all
the power and there's so much like well
backhanded [\h__\h] going on between Airline
Crews like I know so many stories
because you know I was about to become
an airline crew a person and so I also
made a lot of research and like you need
to be scared of the person a person can
like end your life
make you lose your job uh you have to
you have to really suck up to the person
but this person looked like the nicest
person I have ever seen
um like it was a tall relatively old
looking Austrian man who had a huge
smile on his face the whole time he kind
of looked so naive to me like his smile
was like
she looked like I don't know like
he kind of like I don't know how to
describe it but he seemed like so happy
like he didn't really realize
like like he seemed like he knows that
nobody can touch him nobody can hurt him
because he has the power here so he's
just so happy like and um
he's like on a different level like he
has no worries no concerns he's just so
happy
and and yeah his his smile was nice I
have to say so he was standing next to
the lady who was serving me who was kind
of like meh
um uh and and he was like just giving
out bread and he was like offering me
bread and the moment when she was
showing me the choices of dishes that
they had and I'm I'm like and then he
sees it and he's like
oh oh oh oh [\h__\h] like I don't know what
he said anymore but he was like uh
immediately he was like I'll get you
something
um
and so uh what did he wasn't like
he offered me something
I don't remember I think he just off
Ayah I think he
um offered me like more cut fruit like
that that was part of the breakfast
anyway and I said well never just give
me more cut fruit so he was gonna bring
me more cut fruit and then he merely
disappears and he comes back uh bearing
a lot of fruit
cut fruit and fresh fruit like bananas
and so on and
but then I thought we were done but he
comes back again soon after
and without me asking he brings me a big
chunk way bigger than this one with
vanilla sauce of this strodol and I'm
like
sir
[Music]
read my mind I didn't even say that this
is kind of what I wanted I didn't think
you still had it
but like above the fruits like he
offered it kind of knowing that when I I
don't know how he even got the idea that
this is what I need I didn't know what I
needed I didn't know what I wanted all
the things that the lady was offering me
didn't speak to me like because they
were all like not breakfast looking
options then he offers me a fruit and
I'm like yeah you know what that's fine
because to me that's a breakfast I like
to eat how did he know I don't know but
then he comes back and he brings me
another thing that I didn't ask for but
he knew it
he maybe he sense that I'm the type of
person who likes to eat sweet breakfast
but then why would I turn down the
porridge right but but he knew it
she knew I would enjoy this as my
breakfast and I'm like
thank you so much this is how I
literally said to him I think you were
reading my mind because I was thinking
about this
so
he's a good person he's he's a wizard
yeah you know he's he's damn good at his
job then because he can literally read
my mind
man and that's what what made it all
fine again
because
that impressed me I'm I still do you get
what I'm trying to say like I know that
this is such a first world problem like
this is not a real problem
to not have this choice that you wanted
anymore like deal with it but the fact
that it's in the class where you pay
thousands and thousands of bucks
you would maybe expect to get what's
offered on the menu they could at least
like as I said like they asked with the
main course the first lunch
they could ask you about the breakfast
too what you want
and then sort it out beforehand not when
it happens because like this always
happens when you're in the and let me
tell you if you're flying if you don't
normally fly I would recommend you to
not choose a a seat in the very back of
the plane because especially in the
economy it happens so often that there
is one popular choice and one unpopular
choice and if you sit in the back at the
end the popular choice will not be left
over you will have to take what you can
get
this happens all the time so
I didn't think it would happen with
business but it happened
I know it happens all the time though in
other classes so now we know it happens
in business as well
yeah fighting for scraps in the back
rows all the time oh man
[Music]
um
you don't get off it on food on your
plants yeah that's because you only do
short shorts distance flights then yeah
I wonder if they started from the back
no they started from the front they
always do
yeah no normally they always start from
the front
yeah
easier access to stretch areas
yeah yeah there's other reasons why you
would want to be in the back of the
plane but generally if you don't wanna
like have this happen to you then don't
be in the front of the plane
yeah so my conclusion it's not about the
food is not influencing this at all
the flight was super comfortable really
but I still don't think it's worth the
money
if you get upgraded for free because of
your status because you have so many
miles or if you use your mouse instead
of real money then it's worth it
basically if you're not spending real
money
then it's worth it the little upgrades
it it was fine like paying 800 extra on
top of the normal ticket it was fine
doing it like once but I don't want to
do it again
foreign
if the company pays for it or or if you
uh have miles then yeah go for it that
then it will be amazing then it will be
silver or if you're like a double
millionaire at least
um
after taxes not before taxes
very important
this is the very important
if you're a millionaire if if you're a
millionaire after taxes
then do it
[Music]
not before taxes yeah so
that's that
was my flight I still enjoyed it you
know I didn't think like I wasted a lot
of money it was nice to experience it
once I got a good sleep but I will can't
I will cancel my bid for the flight back
and continue to collect miles in the
hopes that sometime I I don't even know
how I don't have a million miles at this
point no I do know I was just saying it
like this but I do know it's because
um I flew to Japan probably in total
over the course of My Life
um
several times a year
[Music]
probably I wish I still had my old
passport I lost my passport once so I
can't count it properly anymore but it's
I I probably
flew to Japan at least 50 times
in my life so Kiana
[Music]
um but
this year is a bit special as I'm mostly
flying with the same airline but for
example in uh in January February I flew
with a different Airline than I flew
with now and back in the day when I was
flying uh before whole life I also flew
with a different Airline each time
because uh then we're like back in the
day they were like no direct flights and
so I always always had to take a
connection and there was always a
different cheapest
Airline
like it would change each time
and so I could never really collect the
miles because some of them are connected
yeah some some of the airlines have like
you know like a thing but
yeah it never I never accumulated
anything
unfortunately it's really sad
now I think I'm accumulating a little
bit now
um
I think I did especially because like
for this flight I paid so I should be
getting a lot of miles for it right
I think so
um because it's an expensive expensive
one yeah
so yeah
[Music]
but next time I fly premium economy
again
so
[Music]
husina
are you getting one mile per mile I
don't I don't know how it works I
isn't it like one mile per Euro spent I
don't even know
how many months do I have now
I tried to add one of the flights that I
did in the summer
um to my miles thingy but I don't think
it worked out
I think it had something to do with
[Music]
um
with the fact that the company
booked it but I don't know okay so miles
and miles and more
does it say how many miles I have now
oh
I don't know is this a lot it says
is this two different things it says
award miles
uh eleven thousand something and Status
miles 14
000.
is this like do I add these together or
is the 11 000 part of the Fourteen
thousand
is this a lot can I get an upgrade
that's not that much that's a lot and
which one how much does an upgrade cost
went in let's go to count
[Music]
oh for this one
business class flight I got 8 500 miles
[Music]
oh compare that to
where's the difference between award
months and Status miles compare that to
my premium economy flight a while ago
that was it says word minus 2600 but
status miles 5006 is that how much I had
at that point no
but it's way less
if you just just fly premium economy
now it says status miles 14 I would say
that's my current miles right 14
000.
[Music]
how much does an upgrade cost I have to
look this up later I'm so curious I'm so
curious
statuses for status and why is it for
free fun
[Music]
oh
status so you can get the silver
oh maybe yeah something like that
frequent travel size kicks in at 45
cases
[Music]
and only like frequent flyer status
people get like free upgrades normally I
gotta keep on grinding gotta keep on
flying to Japan and the good thing is
I'm flying one more time to Japan this
year
so I'll keep on adding those miles on to
it don't worry don't you worry
um
as long as you enjoy the adventure all
that matters no yeah I I really I'm I'm
I really don't think like for such even
though that's a long flight it's still
it's not even a full day like
why spend
like I would prefer to spend more money
on the hotel than more money on a flight
because it's in the end it's still only
like whatever 10 to 15 hours and
spending like five thousand five
thousand seven thousand depends bucks on
on a
on 12 hours of comfort
just
if you spend that on your hotel you get
way more comfort for a way longer time
than that yeah
five hours left
[Music]
five more hours until I have a physical
City pre-order ends so link is in the
pinned comment and in the description if
you didn't get one yet please and
consider getting one this is the first
time I'm doing this and the sales are
important very important
um
[Music]
so okay
now
uh let's somebody was begging for a
couple tangent that's not so much Kobo
tangents yet
um me and Koba met two days in a row
and and we had so much fun together
we had so much fun together even though
it was on only a short time on each day
but like like a little bit more than two
hours probably
um how was the kid she was oh she was so
tired on both days she didn't sleep and
I was like I literally the night like I
was like about to fall asleep on the
night before uh we met when I looked at
my phone and I saw Kobo was gonna start
a karaoke stream after midnight
and I'm like girl we're we're meeting
[Music]
afterwards you're starting a stream at
midnight girl
I was like concerned about her but I
thought well I guess she must know what
she's doing
if she feels like she needs to do this
start her stream yeah she streams
apparently at night time a lot while
she's here
what's she doing
she's an adult not really not much of an
adult Behavior or visuals
[Music]
um
yeah but
I was hoping she'll be fine so we met
and
last time we met was like also in Japan
uh not so long ago but yeah I was so
happy to see her she was cute and
energetic as ever
[Music]
um but she quickly was less energetic
because she was like she was yawning all
the time she was tired and uh
yeah we were stretching together and
then I noticed she's like really really
stiff
I'm stiff too
not that flexible I was laughing at her
because she was really really stiff
could barely uh touch her toes when we
were like bending down
stretch show yeah
and then
um yeah I can't really say what we were
doing
hey but let's say after we were done
doing what we were doing where we had a
lot of fun and laughing and and giggling
and and
afterwards we had a little
um dinner lunch whatever and
um I found out she's necochita just like
me for real for real
and then she yeah that's when she told
me about you know her listening to my
album songs I was so surprised because
like what I understand maybe listening
to Pineapple but you listen to love Rush
too I was like damn she's actually like
following what I'm doing
um
and
yeah we were talking about this and that
and then
um we just had fun and together but I
said goodbye after that
and I think she had plans
in the evening to stream I think so
[Music]
um guess she loves you she does love me
I think so voice tweets were cute right
yeah they were my ideas and I don't have
iPhone only Iphone can do voice to it
can we make a voice to it of yours so we
made voice tweet I I usually I say I
want to do voice read but I never know
what to do so that was kind of like
weird
that was weird
the first one was weird the second one
was better because that came from an
interaction we were having right before
taking the voice screen I was like yo we
should make this The Voice tweet um
contents like uh yeah so the following
day we met again and we were having fun
again she was sleeping again this time I
was also sleeping
um but we were sleeping together and I
was like kind of like
[Music]
pushing her to do the thing that we were
supposed to be doing a really big I know
I know
um but at the end like she was like
fixing her makeup which wasn't much
makeup she was just putting on some lip
gloss I was watching her I was sitting
next to her
and I was like
[Music]
let me take that and she's like no I
know
she knew she but I'm like no no
don't ask me and so we were like already
fighting before the voice Street even
started and I was like I was
um like rapping you know how like like
when like people teach someone golf or
something that's how I was like behind
her with my arms around her and over her
arms she was
um trying to hold her lip gloss and I
was like
um
I was pulling and pulling and pulling
against her strength and it was like
quite a matchup
we had
uh
for a while the same amount of strength
but then eventually I gave in because I
thought you know what let's just
continue this during the space and not
the space The Voice tweet
um
no she has also noodle arms I mean well
I felt we were strong in that moment
[Laughter]
um so we were fighting and then uh she
already kind of knew what I was gonna do
but I was like trust me trust me trust
me
and so I we started the whole thing
again and I was like I finally got it
but we were wrestling so hard we fell on
the ground and then I got it and I did a
little dot on her cheek which looked
like a pimple
and then she's like what the [\h__\h] and
then she put one dot on me too but I was
like it doesn't even stand out because
my skin I wasn't wearing makeup and my
skin is just generally like pretty
reddish all over so it didn't stand out
at all because it was just lip gloss not
lipstick and so it's kind of like
like like a transparent pink color and
it just blended into my all of my
redness
yeah but then we we tried to get it off
of her cheek and and yeah it was a dirty
fun moment captured in a
legendary voice Suite I was hoping
because if you're just listening to The
Voice read you don't really know what's
going on but you want to know what's
going on I was hoping some people would
maybe try to animate it because there's
some people who do like especially with
my Kobo moments there's like animations
right maybe somebody can animate it is
[Music]
foreign
now you have a description of it
so maybe it's easy to make an animation
hello Ian Pretty repeat one day oh I
wonder if they would consider animating
a moment where there's also an ID member
involved
how did she get revenge on you well like
after after I made the dot on her she
just took it from me and then like this
but you're still wrestling and yeah
wrestling really really really
vigorously
uh uh how to say passionately
yeah like so much that we fell down
that's like the big Bonk sound I think
that you heard in the voice tweet when
we fell down
[Music]
I don't know how to describe it
oh well so that's that and oh what was
funny is like in the beginning when we
met on the second day uh
I knew that Kobo would be with Kyla and
Zeta before I would come but I didn't
think they would still be there so I was
not I was not prepared for it
and suddenly they're there when I'm
arriving and I was like no
don't look it's like especially for Zeta
it's the first time we're meeting
with me to see me without makeup as the
first impression
but I was wearing a mask so still still
okay
[Music]
were there and oh they were all so cute
wow
I don't know what I expected but
really cute
really really cute yeah
um
and uh so we went into the building that
we were gonna be in and Zeta and Kaila
like they were done for the day but they
still like walked a little bit with us
and so there was
uh ID staff the ID Girls me and my staff
uh
but we were like already speaking
English at that point but they were
still somehow a little bit conversing in
Indonesian I guess and then I was like
asking couple questions and she would
just naturally
magically returned them to me in
Indonesia and I was like couple I don't
understand what are you saying and then
that happened several times she kept on
repeating and kept on saying answers to
me in Indonesian and I'm like
I don't understand Indonesian speak
English to me yeah she was so it just
flew out of her mouth naturally
guess I gotta learn Indonesian for this
child
yeah it's hard to flip the switch Yeah
because like she was at the same time
still kind of conversing with Kyla and
Zeta so she was like in her brain she
was like still speaking Indonesian and
it also came out in Indonesian
[Music]
but I had one good like return phrase to
say to her that I learned uh by she
taught me this actually like when she
said something in Indonesian that I
didn't understand I said huh na Pine and
then she
she found dad was really funny too
because I had the perfect comeback huh
I think it means like like what what
what are you saying
it was perfect for the moment genius
[Music]
what are you doing
I guess it's not what you're saying but
what are you doing but it still worked
well for the moment
the comment section was shocked you know
that oh wasn't that uh in the voice
tweet though what do you mean somebody
clipped it did somebody clip The Voice
tweet the first one we did
yeah Kubo taught me that hmm
no no I learned it from kabulary yeah I
guess there's not much to go off and the
voice tweets were really good so thank
God I go up to YouTube somehow one way
or another
hmm I didn't know
our conversation made no sense anyway
like
it made no sense she talks about food
while I'm like I'm like saying why did
you stay up so long which is like hey I
want to eat food like what makes no
sense that's why I was like not buying
passion Indonesian
no it's fine it's fine I'm just cute I
love her I love it I gave her so many
hugs she's so small smaller small Kobo
we compared our arms
[Music]
we put our arms next to each other and
her arm is literally half the size of my
arm what that like the the thickness
I can put my my thumb and my uh index
finger around her arm and there's still
space there what the [\h__\h]
man
uh
it actually freaks me out and you still
lost the wrestling
it was it was a match okay
stop it don't mean
don't say that don't even mention that
don't talk about this this is a top
secret information
oh
but then I compared our feet too and our
feet are like the same like we put I
like she was sitting on the ground so I
sat on the ground and I put my feet
against her feet the feet are kind of
the same I was thinking that her feet
would be much smaller than mine but no
well I mean I don't know if we have the
same shoe size but it didn't look like
my feet were like much bigger at all hmm
song Bigfoot
nah I don't have big feet anyway so she
also doesn't have big feet
I wouldn't say she has regular no if you
look at her feet her feet are not
unbalanced to her body okay they're not
relatively big feet no that's not what
I'm saying either
maybe I just have small small feet
[Music]
um
I wonder if I can wear her shoes but I
don't think so like if I just look at
her feet they look smaller to me but
when I put our feet against a picture
that they were like same same-ish hmm
about them she's so freaking tiny ah
we wrestled and we we changed each other
and so much throughout the whole
meeting
yeah
what else happened I don't know
[Music]
I wonder what happened I'm meeting her
again tomorrow tomorrow is gonna be fun
you may get another voice tweet I don't
know tomorrow is going to be a long day
for me
so no no
no stream as you know from my shitty
schedule that I made
it
no
unrelated unrelated to whatever was
written there I don't know what you mean
it's just it's a coincidence
don't you point those things out no no
well it turns out I actually have a
recording today after the stream too
spontaneously
[Music]
um do you want to know about that
it's kind of connected with money
so
um
so I uh when I arrived it was like early
in the morning so and I slept so I
wasn't like that tired
um and I checked in relatively early
this time and so I had the whole day and
I I didn't want to waste it uh
because I don't have so many days this
time so I decided to hit up money
because I knew she was in Japan I didn't
know she like I wanted to meet her at
some point but we didn't decide yet on a
date but since I was free I hit her up I
was like money money do you have time to
meet me for the first time this world's
gonna be the first time we would ever
meet and I was I was looking forward to
that yeah she's my lyric writer she
wrote uh almost all of the lyrics in the
album
and she also like sings the demos that I
then sing uh so like my singing was
inspired a lot by her and like do you
and not
yeah and do YouTube I think and I'm in
pineapple and sleep talking yeah yeah
yeah yeah and then the other songs too
um yeah I really love the way she sings
She's a great singer she's really sweet
I love her and some
yeah she had time thankfully so uh my
plan was uh because she also never went
to one before apparently my plan was to
bring her to Japanese karaoke and casino
we're both like singings I thought we
can sing together and and she's gonna
like it and each together something and
I wanted to take pretty cool with her
yeah she has experience with a little
bit only one apparently but the pretty
good machines these days
so
[Music]
um
oh my God
decorations
[Music]
it seems so very different
nowadays it seems different compared to
back in the day I mean it still makes
you into an alien but I have I don't
know if I'm imagining this but I feel
like it makes me even more into an alien
than it did like years ago with the
older machines and then the decorations
and everything it's just kind of lame I
even saw an a I put a Cuda machine
what the [\h__\h]
hey
look you're going I didn't do it I
didn't test it but I'm assuming this is
how it works you go in it takes pictures
of you and then it turns you into like a
like a drawing like a cute drawing so
the purukura is not your face like not
your real picture but it turns you into
a cute drawing based on the picture you
took
yeah
I'm like what the [\h__\h]
no need for this
I don't want to look even more
unrealistic thank you although that
might actually end up looking better
than the alien they turned me into in
the normal political machine hmm well
well
stable diffusion can do the hand
yeah I don't know like uh whatever
I don't know if they have like their own
database or whatever I don't care I
didn't use it uh I hope it's not gonna
be like a common thing
but yeah I saw like the AI feature oh
well so we met and
um I was I was so shy I was like ah
because she's so pretty she's so pretty
she's so cute man you guys know you
probably saw her Twitter before right
it's just like an e-girl she looks like
an e-girl man she's so cute
um
yeah she's so cute she's so stylish too
foreign
[Music]
Vibes a little bit but she's so cute so
pretty and so sweet her voice wow
I already knew her voice was nice but
hearing an IRL like hits even harder her
voice is just so sweet sounding
she has
such a special talking voice and singing
voice hmm
yeah I'm not an eagle I'm a YouTuber
okay
[Music]
yeah so I was really shy
but we got along really well we talked a
lot and
that was chill we didn't only do karaoke
though so here here's the thing at some
point
this the day no not the day before this
is still the same day but it was a long
day uh in in the early hours of this day
you know I was uh with jenma and you
know when I meet Jen my IRL finally
again in a long time
um I froze so many topics on her I'm
like complaining about so many things at
her and she's like
and so there's like so much to catch up
on that's just so much easier to talk
about IRL and
uh that we talked about a lot and
I don't know why how when where I got
this idea again
but I was reminded of the fact that here
it comes
Eurovision song contest
auditions are still open I was just I
think recently out of Courage checking
if they're still open and I saw there
still open I thought they were already
closed at this point because I
didn't have the time throughout the
summer to bother with this
uh
and I thought it was open but
um the basically the German auditions
are still open
until
the 5th of October which is very soon
[Music]
and the Austrian ones are not open
auditions but I have a contact and so I
asked and it was still it's kind of late
too it closes earlier though than the
5th of October uh quite a bit earlier
but with this knowledge I was like well
wouldn't it be nice but no there's not
enough time I'm not I'm I'm not prepared
for this it won't work out again
um
because I can't I wouldn't even be able
to submit my album songs
because to see here it says August 29 no
yeah August
yeah
August August 29 was the release date
[Music]
you know what the cut off is of songs
you can send in
no matter what country you're applying
for it has to be a song that hasn't been
released before 1st of September
[Music]
that's like two days before uh or after
I released my album
song that meant none of a single one of
these I could send in
yeah also on the Freeman Zone but that's
no problem because last year we we just
shortened to you and sent in do you like
three minutes version
um
now I thought maybe if we cut it that
creates a new version of the song and
maybe they could consider it as a new
release afterwards after the
cut off but apparently not I mentioned
it to the Austrian person and they
didn't seem to see it that way so there
doesn't seem to be a thing
but this is what I was thinking about
on the day of my arrival and I was with
jenma I was talking with her about it
and
I
[Music]
didn't really think that anything would
be possible but
first I just I just I still wanted to
try so I still kind of like um wrote to
the Austrian
person in charge and like asked about
the you know if we cut it does it make a
new version can I still apply blah blah
blue so it was on my mind the whole day
right but then he said no it's too late
and I'm like okay
um
but then I made money later in the day
and we're sitting in karaoke and and
then I brought up
like you know oh hey after the album uh
I I hope we can put out a single I don't
know maybe January February or whatever
who knows just just casually talking
about this okay I'm related to sound of
Sound of Music uh Eurovision song
contest and then
and then she's like yeah yeah so I got
this and this so we were listening to
all these demo tapes
um and I'm like oh this is so good and
this is so good and I want this and this
and this and this but oh my God this is
when I said like I'm window shopping
right and yeah we were just listening to
all these demo tapes that they have
and their team
and then I was like
oh man you know
so actually I had this crazy idea
but like obviously it's like impossible
but like what do you think like because
like you guys are like pretty fast with
your work and you're kind of crazy and
and I know how much Kira especially
liked the idea because uh he's German
and my producer of
um do you and Sparks Etc and pineapple
is German and and and we really like the
idea of being a real visual song contest
last year and it didn't work out and
this and that but like he's like really
passionate about it and and I would
think the others would get it too even
though they're not from Europe but they
would understand and then like I I just
like throw it out there I just threw it
out there without any expectations I was
just like so you know like actually
Eurovision song contest I wanted to try
it last year but this year I'm again too
late so there's actually only so and so
many days left I think it was
[Music]
eight
eight days left until the deadline and
we have no songs because we can't use
the album songs I say that to money and
we're like yeah yeah too late
but what if not
so
start cooking we're like we're like
trying to make a plan how in these eight
days even though we're overseas
no usual recording environment
if we could do this
uh because we have demo tapes but uh
this one demo tape that we were gonna
choose is not even finished they still
would have to finish the whole song it
was like only like one until the first
chorus so like not even the half of the
song but they would have to finish the
instrumentals and everything and then I
have to relearn it and record it and
then it has to be mixed we're making a
full song in like seven eight days okay
so me and Moni were like this could work
so I uh I hit up Johnny
um who's like mixing a lot of uh vocals
for me or something and also is like
part of the team kiwa's Angels who are
making a lot of the songs you're seeing
Johnny on a lot of the credits here too
and I was like Johnny do you have time
to mix something between
the second to the fifth with deadline on
the fifth
and he was like yeah what do you need I
can do it
in theory he could mix a full song in
one day like if it needs to be done in
one day he can do it
yeah
his mixing is really good yeah I really
love his mixing and then the song that
we chose not not all the demo tapes are
by Kira you know a lot they work with a
lot of other producers too but this one
that we're gonna choose luckily luckily
I guess was by Kira so I hit up Kida and
I say sorry I'm so [\h__\h] late but
it's your vision
deadline time coming up do you wanna
lunch
[Music]
finish the song so we can send it in
because I can't use my album songs
do you want to give it a try the chances
of this being rejected are of course
High not only maybe because they don't
like the song but also because maybe
they don't see how
they can use a YouTuber there or they
don't just feel like trust in it but
this song is not wasted if it gets uh
rejected we can still release it later
as a single that is
the good side to this okay it's not a
waste we can still release it as a
single
so
but everybody money Johnny Johnny all of
them are insane like me it seems we are
currently in the works
uh in the really stressful works of
within a week creating a song from
almost scratch uh I have to record it
today I actually just this morning
listens to more or less the full song
there's still some like details missing
but most of the song is done I just
listened to it this morning because it
got finished
um I have to learn it after the stream
and then record it but we have the whole
rest of the day so it will be that job
and money is coming and gonna help me
record it uh she'll be here giving me
like instructions and whatever
and so that will be fun
and then we're gonna quickly mix it
we're sending it over to Johnny he will
mix it in a few days and then we're
sending it into the Eurovision song
contest Germany not Austria
unfortunately because Austria's deadline
is yesterday
I don't know why their deadline was just
a couple days earlier unfortunately
I thought I would have a chance because
Austria did crazy stuff before for like
surprising stuff on unexpected stuff
before uh with Conchita Wist
the only recent win for Austria and the
Eurovision Song Contest in the past 10
years was I think you guys even know
this person Conchita boost
if you remember sang as her Eurovision
song contest song
Rise Like a Phoenix
it would just be like the most perfect
follow-up ever for me as a phoenix and
again like a really strange character to
be on stage and perform a song it would
be Destiny but unfortunately Austria
um
is missing out on the opportunity they
should have scouted me anyway like
that's in their system anyway they Scout
people Astra system is scouting people
privately more or less while Germany and
some other countries there's like two
different ways I do it you know they do
all open auditions and then I think
there's like a like a elimination round
like they get like I don't know 10
people or so 10 artists and then I don't
I I'm not sure how the system is if like
uh the audience votes who will be the
German contestant or if it's like a
judge a jury
there's probably information about that
out there and I I'm not sure right now
um if it's an audience vote then we have
a chance but I first have to get chosen
to be one of the choices in the first
place so that's what I'm gonna do after
the stream and
I think
you're okay Americans maybe don't
understand so well but Eurovision Song
Contest in the end
um it's about making headlines you want
your country to stand out and even if
maybe for me it's not so much about
winning at all it's just about being
there and for the country it would be a
huge headline to have a YouTuber there
you know that's just what I'm thinking
like if you want your country to be the
number one topic of the Eurovision song
contest than having a YouTuber on stage
will definitely make that happen
everybody will talk about it some people
surely will make fun of it but it will
at least be a huge [\h__\h] top topic you
know good press bad press there's no bad
press there's only good press
this is my argument so yeah
so I'm gonna do my best but I don't have
high expectations my expectations are
honestly really low I don't think they
will go for it because I feel like
Austria might have gone for it because
they do crazy [\h__\h]
I don't know about Germany they once had
a contestant a few years ago who was
like a weeb teenager dressed in like
Harajuku fashion I think
but I think she sang a pretty normal
song
but her visuals were like a weeb
but that's maybe the craziest thing that
Germany did I don't know
[Music]
um
she tanked hard yeah I don't think she
did so well
um
generally I think Germany doesn't want
to go for crazy [\h__\h] they just want to
win
but yeah I don't know
I don't know if they would go for it
it's a risky thing I guess
um just place my order thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
yeah it's it's definitely an eye catcher
yeah recently Germany has been doing
really bad with their placement
so maybe that could motivate them to for
once try something new you know what I
mean something that stands out something
that's gonna make headlines something
that puts all the eyes on them
I mean if you think about it that way
I feel like you have to do it
yeah they did pretty bad last year and
in the years before too like I don't
think there has been any good
contestants since
[Music]
something like that her last name is so
complicated
[Music]
no I really liked her
but I don't think since her they had
anything big
[Music]
yeah now the thing is also the song that
we're currently making
since we are like lacking time we had to
choose from a couple of like demo tapes
that were available couldn't make a song
from like complete scratch
um and I don't know like no
um
I chose this
from three different demo tapes
and this song because I thought out of
these free ones it might do the best at
Eurovision but
I don't know if it's a winning song
honestly because it's still very k-poppy
but like badass K-pop
it's different from the K-pop I've done
so far
um it's pretty badass of a song a really
cool song
uh with like
[Music]
it's a girl crush like I would say like
maybe black pink which obviously
blackpink being popular overseas there's
a reason for it this speaks to a big
audience so we just gotta hope that
Eurovision judges and audience would
like this
[Music]
um
yeah I don't know it wouldn't be like my
my ideal first choice for Eurovision
song contest song
uh but my other new album songs wouldn't
have been either like I wouldn't have
relied on sleep talking I wouldn't have
relied on pineapple maybe the great
Wanderer love Rush no right to spend no
like you have to think hard about what
kind of song
because you only have one choice and one
song and like
yeah it's important the song is so
important it has to have
um a mainstream audience appeal
it has to be catchy and it has to be
impressive yeah but
I don't know we have this one song we're
going for it if they don't take it
that's fine whatever that's kind of what
I expected and then we'll just release
it as a single and try again next year
hopefully a little bit earlier yeah
[Music]
it's okay if it doesn't work out I am
expecting that but we're still gonna try
really hard to get it ready now
uh Eurovision Zone contest
so
[Music]
let me give you an idea of how big this
is uh almost 200 200 million people uh
watch the Eurovision song that's live
each year
[Music]
all right
so you understand why I have to try this
surely not everybody will be interested
in YouTubers but surely some might so
you know
look up what the [\h__\h] this is and become
new whole life and especially in Europe
I feel like you know Europe V tubing in
Europe there's still potential for a new
market and
France was thinking about sending a
French Hatsune Miku in 2007 oh really
interesting
[Music]
yeah
yeah I yeah I think this is
like I was always thinking I've been
thinking so much about how to get
another big boost another big hype wave
going in you know Japan youtubing viewer
numbers are are stable you know it's
always going to be popular in Japan but
overseas after Corona what are we gonna
do what would be another big thing
that's gonna bring another big wave and
I this is the one this is the biggest
thing I can think of or maybe the only
real thing that I can think of so I have
to I have to try it guys it doesn't
matter what you think about your Vision
Song Contest some people have like
thoughts about it uh doesn't matter
about winning whatever it's just like it
has to be it has to it's
tried at least
um yeah
one has to try it there's not like much
else like you know we we keep on like
going to Anime conventions on that but
in the end this is always like more or
less the same pool of people who already
probably mostly know about youtubing at
this point convention goers you know
it's a bubble yeah
we have to go outside of this bubble see
what else we can drag into the bubble
hmm foreign
s
but don't worry guys
um for people who are scared about the
bubble getting bigger chances are really
low that they're gonna go for it so
don't worry
yeah I I just I think for the sake of
whole life I want to do this because I
want home life to especially whole life
English to still grow
you know I want us to grow I want me to
grow but I want us to grow as a whole as
well
and this would be
possibly 200 million that's this would
be like the biggest exposure that we
would ever get
so I'm Dreaming right now I'm Dreaming
man I'm [\h__\h] dreaming
[Music]
yeah for real for real
you're crazy lovely but I love energy
and motivation thank you I know I know
I'm [\h__\h] crazy like
I thought of it earlier but this whole
summer like my mind was occupied with
other [\h__\h] and then I thought oh it's
probably too late anyway but then I
checked and then it's not too late but
not much time but guinea guinea is so
close enough time to make something
um
yeah so wish me luck me and money and
the others Johnny and Kira kiwawa's
angels
I'm gonna give it a try
[Music]
so
so yeah I met with Moni that was fun
and then immediately immediately after
this topic came up our Wheels started
turning in high speed all of our Wheels
wait let me um really quickly
check something
[Music]
so okay oh
oh okay
foreign
[Music]
but I have to practice the song so I
Gotta Give Myself time for that but
money is not coming yet but I need time
for practice you know
um but yeah okay I can still tell you a
little bit about the Aki collab
that's the only last thing I think that
I didn't tell you about yet
um
uh yeah so you guys if you follow me on
Twitter Etc you probably saw like uh me
replying to Aki Senpai months ago
uh you know I saw like she was making
Crepes and I was like oh
can I can I please too I love grams I
want them to collab and crap yes yes the
best idea ever
um and the thing is I don't know if I've
just left Japan or if I still was in
Japan but this was the end of my trip
but it was not possible to do it until
my next trip so I told her when I'm
coming to Japan again and uh we sat in
stone a date
um now at this time the plan was still
kind of that I was gonna be there alone
but I also noticed that normally she's
doing the collabs with two guests at a
time yeah
so I thought oh maybe it would be nice
to invite someone I guess you know I
like to hitorijime I like to have my
collab partner all to myself often but I
thought this would be fun with someone
else there too so I found you know
takamori would be a great couple to show
up and Cali had time
um coincidentally and she was looking
forward to it too so I invited Callie
and
this is
yeah gave me time to a little bit catch
up with Cali too because I didn't have
any other collab with her planned
um for this trip and you know I
think each time I'm in Japan there has
to be at least one Cali collab you know
yeah and she really liked the idea so
um yeah we we went to akizen by place
and Kelly brought a [\h__\h] ton of beer
uh to share with akistempai
[Music]
yeah and
um yeah we we entered and all cartoons
cartoons
so she has four cats and two of them are
like friendly cats that like to say hi
to guests the others are shy I ended up
meeting one of the shy ones too after a
while after things calmed down after the
Stream
but the fourth one I never saw okay
[Music]
yeah I don't know about this elusive cat
I was lucky to see the third one
I don't know it's really cute
really cute he kept walking in and out
and in and out and in and out I was like
girl stay
that was an Sr cat but I didn't meet the
SSR cat
so
uh the cats oh my God so fluffy So Soft
so big uh much bigger than Kelly's cats
yeah Wayne also huge cartoon But my cats
are like in between I would say and
these cards these good these cards were
pretty big
yeah chonkers so much to touch so much
to pet
I love it
and and then yeah we set up like move
and we actually had like quite a lot of
time to set up so we were chit chatting
a lot and we were drawing the the crabs
and she has like you know before the
crab stream apparently every guest that
shows up she asks them to draw on this
like big
uh what do you call Sketchbook uh and
she like gives you like a [\h__\h] ton of
nice pens and you then draw uh how you
imagine your crap and there's like a
choice of like there's a menu with
choices of toppings Etc yeah
and I looked through the other drawings
that others did and the reason why I was
teasing Anya on Twitter about her crap
is because you know everybody was
drawing like really colorful big crabs
really nicely and then Anya's
[Music]
stands out so much I don't know if in
their collab they showed it but they
must have I think that's what they do
they normally always show it
always shows it but onions
Anya's was just like
[Music]
um
it had no color it was really small it
was thin and you know I was just like
there were no colors it was yeah well
it was not really aesthetically pleasing
[Music]
um really unique yeah yeah I thought it
was really funny to me I'm sure it
tasted good but the art was so different
from everybody else's art
and yeah so yeah we looked through that
and then we drew it and the whole time
it was like screeching at the cats
because they were so cute and I could
stop touching them they were so so
freaking cute yeah
don't worry about Anya Dolly we're good
we're good we're good
yeah and I'm so excited for this because
you don't even understand how much I
love crabs
yeah I told I talked I told told
um I think this was on stream anyway I
told uh akisenpai about like the
Austrian crabs the palace
which I can make it's like uh like a
thicker thicker than the crab so it's
easier to make and you don't you just
make it in a normal frying pan yeah so
that's what I can make but I don't know
how to do the other thing
oh
um yeah she's so sweet she also created
us when she saw us with such a big happy
hug like wow she was like like coming
from like really far away and then she
like like
ran at us with big wide open arms and I
was like oh yeah
so happy to see her she's so sweet man
she immediately made me feel super
welcome yeah
so lovely big hug I gave her several big
hugs yeah
um so uh one thing I wanted to mention
that was really funny to me that uh
apparently even Aki Senpai is viewers
possibly don't know she said I can say
it but she never really directly said it
to her viewers
about these crep collabs
at some point Midway through you know I
had my the stream open on my phone
Midway through
I noticed that even though she was like
walking around
the whole room
like over far distances right well I
mean like relatively far like she was
not always in one space she was like one
time she was in front of the crap making
thing one time she was in front of the
fridge one time she was in front of her
laptop Etc but like she she's like
walking around this whole time and I'm
just like thinking to myself oh yeah she
when she's walking around she must be
like her model would like stop moving
right so I look at the my phone and I'm
like
she's moving even though she's pacing
around the whole room so I'm like I look
around like quietly this is the moment
like the others reacted to it I didn't
say anything why I'm looking around but
I'm looking around and I'm like where's
the camera why is it picking her up
sorry then then I don't see anything so
I look at her but did I did is she
wearing like in front of her face or
something no she's not I'm like
how do you think
I'm freaking out and they were like
what's wrong and I I I I wasn't I wasn't
sure like if it's okay to make this into
a topic so I just acted like nothing and
I'm just looking around because I'm
going crazy because the crap is so yummy
um so I waited until the end of the
stream to ask why how are you moving
there is literally no camera anywhere
actually
and then she she admits
that
she for these crab making collabs she
pre-recorded herself moving and is
looping it
on her obs
[Music]
I'm like what I didn't know
and she never apparently she never
mentioned it in her stream but if you
watch it then you probably notice a loop
maybe at some point maybe
I don't know did you guys notice it when
you were watching be honest
[Music]
never did no no no no there you go
yeah it actually like
seems to be quite believable
um
[Music]
last year
yeah yeah it's a shock now I'll be
questioning what's live and pre-recorded
I found it might be weird when like
there's a moment where uh me and Cali
are talking and she's not talking but
the her life today is moving and and the
mouth is moving and everything like that
wouldn't match but if you guys didn't
notice then surely it was like natural
enough to not seem like that
interesting huh
so
yeah
I will consider this as an option if I
ever need this in the future
wow almost as stuck as finding out about
the tales of talking yeah
[Music]
that's so funny sorry immersion broken
secret lore but I found that fascinating
because I had no idea what's going on
one more it was crazy thing I of course
had to uh recommend to Aki Senpai as I
recommend it to any cat owner these days
to and I recommended it to Cali too
that's why she got one uh I recommended
her to get like a cat toilet like an
automatic one like I have
um because she didn't have one but
the other like she had something for her
cats that I never saw before and I
didn't know this was a thing
[Music]
I noticed
in the room there was like this
big container modern looking container
[Music]
um maybe as big as a big suitcase
roughly
roughly just for your imagination and it
said that there was a writing on it
small writing that said something like
uh
air air dryer or something like that
and I'm like what is this for what is
this
yeah and I asked her and it turns out
it's poor or cats
hey
yeah it's
um yeah okay I I don't think this is a
necessary thing generally but there's
one usage that I would say makes sense
in some way uh this is for cats
she said the first reason she said is
like you know nuke like getting rid of
like uh all this like hair that's
falling out
um you put the cat in there and I was
like isn't it scared and she said no no
my cats are fine with entering I'm
surprised because I would feel like they
wouldn't want to be in there
um
um but we tested it out on one of her
cats because I wanted to see it and the
the one cat that I took a picture of it
went inside and then you turn it on and
then error error starts like
blowing at the cat
from several openings
and the cat was just chilling there the
cat was like cleaning itself
but I didn't see any hair really flying
around so I don't think it really works
well because once the cat went out and I
pet the cat again again I had a [\h__\h] ton
of hair on my hand this one was losing
so much hair
but the other usage that makes sense I
would say maybe also for small dogs
mostly
um because I don't think you really
watched you you shouldn't you don't need
to and you shouldn't really watch your
cats but I think Japanese people treat
their cats quite I hear from a lot of
Japanese people that they wash their
cats which is so unnecessary especially
if you don't take your cat outside
um cats are not like dogs cats clean
themselves they don't need to be cleaned
some people do though and so the theory
is that if you washed your cat you can
put it in this room and it gets dried
comfortably
uh quite
easily instead of having to put a hair
dryer against your cat which is really
loud and like they they wouldn't like
that very much the this like weird
container seems to
have at least that usage which makes
sense to me but makes more sense to me
with a dog than with a cat because like
generally I don't like most people
wouldn't wash their cats Maybe
that even if you take your cat outside
like you have to maybe wipe their paws
but that's like pretty much it
yeah I never no once my chunky wonky was
washed before when I was in Japan and my
roommate took care of my cat she told me
that chunkers had like an like something
happened like they
chunkers got oily or something by an
accident and then she showered chunkers
[Music]
um yeah so like maybe once that was once
in the whole life of chunky wonky
I never ever watched this movie and
she's still the softest cleanest
nicest untangled hair rest cat ever like
wow
it's not eel
shut up
she smells nice she smells like nothing
chunker smells a bit more like like a
cat that just cleaned herself but it's a
nice smell no this movie is really
really clean you don't wash your cattle
but anyway this machine fascinated me
yeah
it just looked so funny to me like the
cat just sitting in there I thought they
would get claustrophobic and panic
because of the airflow but no I don't
think it really helps with the hairs
though hmm
okay
did you ask her how expensive it was no
I didn't but it looks expensive and also
looks unnecessary for me at least
yeah you ordered my album thank you
oh you couldn't resist
[Music]
well it is already October 2nd anyway
at least here
um
so
[Music]
yes
foreign
[Music]
I think I guess washing your cat would
help if it's like shedding really really
really badly
then you can probably
then you could probably whip the bath
get rid of a lot of the shedding yeah
that's one reason I could see why you
would
wash your cat hmm
yeah yeah
okay guys
I think that's it for today uh you know
I'm busy you know why I'm busy
uh uh and I will now go maybe have some
lunch or something like that and then
practice and record the song yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
channel the day after tomorrow tomorrow
I have a collab on my Channel with the
ID girls and then that's it because then
I am busy doing you know the other thing
going to a wedding
so thank you guys you know what you're
gonna play yes I know
I won't tell you yet
we're playing a game though I brought my
switch and my
um capture card
no hand cam no because they told me I I
suggested handcam I wanted to do origami
uh folding stream I thought that would
be kind of cute and since we're in Japan
you know it matches the theme but they
said like hand cam streams are like what
they do for their members only streams
so they don't really want to do it
outside of them there's only streams
because it's their thing you know
yeah
[Music]
unfortunately at least for Jetta
they keep it for their special members
only streams so we're playing a game
that's fine too it's gonna be fun okay
wish me luck with all my things today
and tomorrow oh and please if you
haven't ordered my first ever album
point of view CD version yet then please
consider it it's pinned in the comments
it's in the description more links are
in the description
please
[Music]
know that
thank you guys in Germany
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]