[Music]
so
don't
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
so please be kind thank you
[Applause]
but
in fact
just a human
no no no no no no no no not man anymore
guru bad i am a duck priest nice to meet
you
[Music]
yeah second up is me i i i am the
first real real bird actually in hollow
life uh
[Music]
i am phoenix not chicken phoenix
[Applause]
look at look at my guarding phone
picture it looks like a phoenix doesn't
it
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
yes i'm rainy from hollow life indonesia
generation
it is i am fifao not turkey
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
and after that mummy joined me please
introduce yourself
hello i'm nanashi mummy from the second
generation of hello life
am an owl not a towel
yeah
it's not never happened i'm not a towel
ego
[Laughter]
m
[Music]
new member nice to meet you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
no no no no
okay
[Music]
beautiful
[Laughter]
so guys today we are here with these
horotoni members and by the way if if
you have not seen it yet
i requested for this sake of hurricanes
yeah thank you for putting it on the
screen i got it because i've just felt
like ah we were such a cute lovely group
we need something to connect one another
i mean
[Music]
is so cute
thank you
the steps on the bottom so cute right
it's so cute
i also think so
um
[Music]
very good
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
positive things
i think we should start with normal
normal mode but we can try other modes
too later okay okay and
just a reminder uh
the prompts please write in english
[Music]
normal turns on whatever let's just go
with the basics
okay okay
the right sentence
okay
let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
m
okay
[Music]
my
is
um
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
m
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
dancing dancing
dancing
[Music]
eat
foreign
[Music]
perfect
we need more more difficult prompts next
time
a lot of birds not a bird yeah many
birds that's okay that's no problem um
let's look at it together
okay okay okay
okay
let's go we start with hollow birds down
this is my chat's phone okay i can hear
it i can hear it
[Music]
[Applause]
i will never listen to chat again i'm
saving i saved it
let's go okay okay next one from molina
sorry i'm vlogging
[Applause]
actually before before the stream
started
me and elena told uh subaru simply and
the others that we're going to the
maldives to make them jealous
yeah and they were very excited to join
so what example i want to come too right
christina
[Music]
[Laughter]
everybody is
there even though the one that subado
drew one is missing so good job
you added me again
nope
[Applause]
you guys all know the mermaid loading
icon the membership
[Music]
i'm happy thank you i'm good i'm happy
thank you
mine's similar
oh missed me
where's it
[Laughter]
[Applause]
m
okay
[Music]
um
duck
[Music]
[Laughter]
everybody will
we
will eat duck
okay
m
[Music]
hey
oh
[Music]
hey
it
[Music]
hey
m
[Music]
so many people use horotoni so i always
have to draw draw five people
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
everybody will eat
[Laughter]
nice interpretation moment
it is a bird eat bird well done yeah
i like your
pac-man annoying
[Laughter]
oh
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
should we
play a different round a different mode
[Music]
what
hey
m
[Music]
foreign
okay
relationship
[Music]
okay
hi hi hi
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
e
hey
done
[Music]
very emotional
[Laughter]
yoshikai
[Music]
my
okay
[Music]
i will
m
[Music]
there
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay you're so difficult
here we go
[Music]
oh my god
let's take a look at
what what it turned out to be
thank you marshall
i was not sure what to draw
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
beautiful
it just looks like i'm sexually
harassing someone
why did you make them sweat
because the asmr was just too much to
handle
[Music]
[Laughter]
you need to put that up on the on my fan
art hashtag it's one thing yes oh yes
from that prop my my previous problem
because it failed
i'll save that one that one is precious
beautiful all right
[Music]
a mushroom
mushroom i
like the mario kart stream right now
i like
mushrooms
[Music]
sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god
this is this is abstract art yeah yeah
it's just
abstract abstract right here
you look at it and you think what do you
what do you see how does it feel yeah
depending on what you see you can learn
someone's personality
[Music]
arizona
uh
[Music]
oh
style but no way she can do that with a
mouse
oh
no
[Laughter]
[Applause]
is that a cherry tomato or a strawberry
moment i was going for it i was going
for strawberry
nice that was very stressful
do you want to go
one more one more one more yeah
um think about what you want to draw
okay
[Music]
um
what idea
um i can't tell you yet oh we did it
again or what yeah let's knock off again
one more round
um
[Music]
we can try animation animation
ready
[Music]
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
a b c d
hmm
[Music]
net
um
[Music]
this car
like classroom layness
names teacher
playing a teacher lesson
a good
[Music]
haha
um
[Music]
i will play hak pa
haktak
next week
we will collaborate fast probably
[Music]
okay
i'm looking forward to it thank you
and louis kolobu
[Music]
okay
a
hi
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
oh my dad
my
[Music]
sure
foreign
[Music]
hi
wow
nice wow
but everyone did their best i'm sure
power
okay let's take a look staggering with
mine
oh
[Laughter]
apparently in order to be a bird you
have to know the abc
yeah we all know do we mean
no abc
baby
abcd efg yeah yes okay
okay
i like i like the maybe someone can
recreate this and make it into a proper
fan art i want to see it
[Music]
chat
again yeah of course i'm always you know
what about you
hey are there
other three people other three people
[Laughter]
because of black hair
becomes
make use of it yeah yeah yeah
spicy
[Music]
[Laughter]
face scary face
when i panic
funny
just panic right
okay
yeah
yeah you want to portray yourself in a
cute way but no you're the one who
portrays yourself in the terrifying way
the most yes
toast is involved
[Music]
same same thinking
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i
[Music]
is simple art um with even less time i
drew a bit more complicated
and i added the earring
oh yeah
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay
okay what this turd duncan is turkey
duck and chicken what is
turducken with hawk and owl uh turd you
mean flamingo ow
[Laughter]
go
[Music]
animation
okay
uh
[Music]
kakuza
and don't
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
yo
um
[Music]
okay
yo
let's go
[Music]
i'm just
thinking
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah foreign
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
foreign
super
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
hey
okay
[Music]
foreign
is
[Laughter]
my dear leather phone
shitty say
i i don't know
what you say
[Music]
orange
me
[Music]
okay
hi
hey
aina
okay okay okay
let's go
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
and
foreign
[Music]
m
do
[Music]
eat eat human
and
put out
boom
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
someone's boom
[Music]
okay
a good good trike
good track
[Music]
nice
good taste
so someone's born
[Laughter]
my
[Music]
okay
interesting things going on
[Applause]
oh yeah
what's going on why is everyone drawing
such sensitive scenes huh
which one are we talking about what are
we talking about
[Music]
i think i think it's enough it's a lot
it's
all right okay let's take a look um oh
they were so happy did you get my idea
oh oh my god
cute stop oh you guys added oh
who's
oh my gosh
so scary
yeah
why is so angry
what station
[Music]
and then music was playing so i wanted
to start dancing dancing
emotions okay
okay okay
oh oh oh oh
wow
what's that even saying
this
is
i thought it was someone else
[Laughter]
like i got closer too yeah and the in
the end it turned into a little snake
[Music]
[Applause]
is like what
what what is that
but it's not it's
oh
[Music]
exploding
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh yeah your last night was very
important nina thank you for that oh
yeah you're welcome
oh my gosh next door nice next
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
eating louise
oh
[Laughter]
m
yes
i was hoping for that
thanks
[Music]
[Applause]
the best animation
[Music]
so moment
i want to try
uh wait uh do we still have oh do we
still have time can we do one more
animation one more yeah
okay um
you're right i'm hungry hungry okay
hungry
maybe afterwards you can have breakfast
mommy are you gonna go back to sleep
i'll do both or i'll just eat more of
you guys
okay
i'll give you some substitutes from kfp
okay that's okay
yeah
eat kfp
okay
[Music]
m
there
[Music]
that
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
though
okay
you can't
yes
[Music]
hotel
me
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
fernando clare
and korenando
[Music]
grenander
be
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
okay
no
[Music]
uh
swim sweets ah i say okay same sweet
seam suit
[Music]
okay
now
oops
[Music]
then
what is this
same suits
[Music]
foreign
ah
[Music]
okay
next
ah my
[Music]
it's mine
okay
[Music]
go
eat
[Music]
my
an eye
highlight
out out of highlight
okay
let's go
[Music]
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
foreign
[Music]
hello hello
hello
hi
hi hi hi
hello
thank you
all right all right this is last last
round let's see what masterpieces we
have created
yes please yes
okay
shopping for swimsuit
you turn into person she
[Music]
after eating the bikini top she becomes
a purse
[Applause]
dana try on some cute swimsuits but okay
this is fine
[Laughter]
[Music]
what situation is this oh um
[Applause]
[Music]
to read your mind
good job
[Music]
a little confused cooking oh yeah
cookies
[Applause]
i thought it was a mirror
[Laughter]
i don't understand the story
my implication was that uh simply comes
pushes away dana and wants the food for
herself
to get me to eat something suspicious
i hear rainer i killed it no i i
teleported
looks really nice though the way it goes
up it really it was supposed to be a
single hair but it's nice how it ended
up
[Music]
oh oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
stop getting bigger
surprises
dude
okay oh thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
it's tough out there that's why no we
have to we have to
be strong together
not eat each other's third wins
well the famous bird is is me because i
am a phoenix and and i will revive no
matter what
uh-huh
[Applause]
oh my gosh where do you revive
that that is a that's a different story
i cannot say that
but you know because the bird eat bird
world you know what we should collab
someday mina de corazo
super smash brothers
i want to punch punch birds
[Music]
oh
did you play super smash brothers before
i have but i'm not good at it uh we're
all kind of damn bad that's good because
we're not bad
and somebody will never play before um
in a different meaning too no
what's talking about what i don't know
what are we talking i don't know
yeah they're playing together yeah okay
yes
[Music]
we're the biggest
group of something i think in honolulu
maybe maybe we can do more stuff
together but getting all of us together
for this collab was already very
difficult
to tell
[Applause]
[Music]
you learned some good japanese there and
honestly yes thank you
i'm like so close to fluent now yes
you're getting closer you're getting
there fight those like close fights
yeah
that's simple enough i think we can
remember that our ending greeting will
be otsu
okay everybody thank you for watching
today
and in holo today we say
three
two
one
[Applause]
[Music]
what's up
quack
[Music]
you