[Music]
DET
A
[Music]
Kaki
Hololiving's high school
Yes Subaru Senpai, I heard that it was the 5th anniversary, so I
came to celebrate.
Congratulations. 5  A year is seriously a long time, especially in this world,
but I
really, really respect how you work hard every day as if you've just made your debut. I wish I could be as
energetic as Subaru-senpai every day.
Okay, I'll do my best too Subaru-senpai From now on, let's
do our best together as Holo-Holo and Hololive senpai and Holoto friends.
Please get along well, and above all,
do your best in the live from now on. I'll be watching you.
Fight!
Oh Hololive.  Congratulations
on your 5th
anniversary, Osaraba-chan. It looks like there will be a live show, so do your best. Let's play games together again. Bye. Happy 5th anniversary to Baiba-senpai. Masudegozaru
Congratulations on your well-being.Recently, we've been playing FF14 together behind the scenes,
and we've
been talking while watching us play Strokes, and I
think we've become much closer to each other.  Thank you for always taking care of me.
Suba-senpai's
cheerful demeanor and dancing are a
role model for me, so I
hope we can continue to do many things together.  I
'm looking forward to today's live show. I'm
rooting for you with Gozaru.
Please do your best. Subaru-
senpai can do it.
[Music]
Gozaru-
senpai, Subaru-senpai, Subaru-senpai, Ao,
thank you for your hard work, Hishio, and
Subaru.  It's the 5th
anniversary of your senior, right? Congratulations. No, you're
serious, you're serious, you're serious.
After this, it's
a live show. It's a live show, isn't it?  No, I'm really
looking forward to it, I'm
really looking forward to it, I'm really looking
forward to it, I'm really rooting for you, I'm really rooting for you, Suba-senpai, Suba-senpai, no,
I really respect
Suba-senpai.Subaru-senpai isn't just cute,
this is this.  It's hot, no, Maji Heart is
hot and cool, so I have a lot of
respect for him, so I have a
lot of respect for him.Here's my senpai, no, I really, really, really, really respect him.  You're so
cute today, too. You're so
cute today too. You're so cute, you're such a great senpai, you're such a wonderful senpai. I respect you so much, you're such a great senpai. You're so cute,
senpai, and I
'm really rooting for you.
Please do your best today,
Suba-chan.
Congratulations on your 5th anniversary live.
Wow, this day has finally come, the leader
is smiling, and I'm
sure Suba's friends on the other side of the screen feel the same way.  I'm
really looking forward to it because I'm sure Mr. Masu will be waving his penlight behind the screen as hard as all of his Suba friends today.I've
been waiting for the show since before the opening,
but what kind of live show
will there be this year?  Katsuba-chan's live show is the best every year,
so I'm already looking forward to it. Wow, I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward
to it. The 5th anniversary live begins.
[Music]
Subaru's 5th anniversary congratulations live begins.
Good luck Subaru live. Good
luck Subaru live. Good luck!
Subaru live. Good
luck!
[Music]
Kusa Subaru Live
Do your best, try your best, try your best, try your best
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
He
[Music]
Three
One Break out of your usual day and
go to a group of tough guys that will wake you up.  Let's
go to see the ceremony on a special day
[Music]
In the new season, where the greenery is soft, I stared at the
blue
light, my face, not seen by friends I didn't know, my
classmates,
even if they didn't live a normal life, or opposed it.  Nintan and  It's
too much,
even if it's every day, I can finally see you.I
can't help but feel like I'm at the statue.The
place we promised is the
place I dreamed of.A day that I can't forget is now
beginning.Today is a special day again.I've stepped out a little from my daily life, and look, I've
shuttered the place and let it be reflected.  A
smile that spills over no matter what happens
[Music]
Maybe all the people who just jumped on it are all together The waiting time, which is filled with irreplaceable moments, is also adorable
Where should we go next?
As I was walking, I realized that the time had passed, and the
sun had set, and the light decorating the rice cakes was
captivating my heart.I'm really glad I came here.I was waiting
in town, and since today was supposed to be a special day, I
jumped out and clicked the shutter.  I can't help
it, I'll always have memories Spring, summer, autumn, and winter I found them in this place, but they keep coming back and forth.When will I see you next?  Let
's go there, using the turning of the stick sword as a guide. It's a
special day.
[Music]
[Applause]
Your idol
[Music]
was there. I'm so happy. I'm waiting for you, and I'm
flapping my legs. I'm looking forward to going to sleep today.  I wasn't.
I'm nervous too. I can't afford
to waste every minute. Let's
get started. You, you, you, I'll be waiting for you. If you'd like,
come and join us. We'll go to a place where love gathers.  Welcome
to the top of the room If you come here,
let's dance.It does
n't matter whether it's a big box or small.
In that case,
open the barres [music] Your
idol
[music] He's
the one that I raised and he's so arrogant I have
to enjoy the moment with you and you.
Even if you're a shut-in, show me a different face than usual.  It doesn't matter if
everyone is pretending to be brothers
or pretending, it does
n't matter. I don't care. Even if your
world feels me, I wo
n't be scared if you're here.
[Music]
[Applause]
Look, look, something's about to begin,
but what a wonderful sight it is! I don't
care if it's big or small, I do
n't care if it's big or small. Your
tarum is so small that it could fly away if it blows right now.  you
push me
Then, if you're on my side, I'll
open up the barres for you. Your
idol will be
B. The
radio waves will taper and I'll be in awe.
[Music] I wonder
if there are sad things that you want to forget too. It's so dramatic that you shed tears even though it's a movie you don't know.  It's
because I
don't have enough of it. I can't reach my country. I keep thinking nonsense
. When the rain stops, my love and the side of my face
will belong to someone else. Even the lying
foundation is all for tonight.
Why in the world is this all going on? What's going on with this
unstable Katsuda? No matter
how far you go, I'm not joking.
Even when that time comes, there's no point in Tokyo. It's vague.
Just do what you want.
[Music] There's
no such thing as a weird hack, but there's
no such thing as a ploy to leave your disembodied emotions alone,
so why is it that you're already so stiff?  I've been
paying lip service to you all year round,
but I've got tears in my eyes, and now I can't hear you at all because of the music in my head.  Let me
go, but why in the world? My
anxiety won't go away. Even if you eat just one meal, it's
not a joke.
When the time comes, it won't matter.
I'll just do the truth.
[Music]
Now
[music]  It's
not okay, Tokyo Shabu Even if the time has come, it
won't matter, I won't use it. It's
only Lalis.
[Music]
Maji Love When the time comes, it won't matter. It's just going to
disappear, just stop me.
[Music]
Yes, so I
'm coming to Holo Lime. I hope you're all having fun today.
Thank you for coming to our Anniversary Live. I'm
really happy for you today.  I
hope everyone enjoys it, and the chirp that appears above this.It's Subaru's 5th anniversary, so please post it with
I would like to take a souvenir photo here. It's been a while since I last wore this
outfit. What kind of
pose should I do? The
signature I showed earlier is B's signature pose.
Please, everyone, please post this.
That's okay. And Sai
is B. Thank you to everyone who came. Thank you
very much. I was very happy.
Thank you.  So that's the
end of the idol-like part in the first half, and
something may change from here on out, so
please look forward to that as well.Then,
here's the next song.
[Music] Hooraho,
hora, hora, it's all over again, my favorite accident defense,
especially when I'm begging for it, hora, hora, it's all over again, like a pattern of scars on my face.Someday, I was the only one who dreamed of something like that,
but I'm tired of calling you only when I'm feeling lonely.
No, you're not interested in me at all. The only person you like is
yourself. You're not interested
in me after all. I'm tired of hearing that story. You're not interested in me in the first place, so you're cheating on me
again. My boy,
I'm too much of a mom.
Baby, hug me.
[Music]
Actually, I can't help it, I
can't help it. I won't fall over, if only I could dance just a little longer. I'm starting to melt. There's no
point in trying to appeal to me, and no one
will notice me, but even when I'm lonely.  When you
come to see me, you're
not interested in me at all. What's wrong with
me? Tell me. You're not interested
in me after all. You're always on your phone. You're not really interested in me in the first place.
Even if I make you expect a little, Ronri is the first one.
Baby, don't turn around
[Music] Let's
take Melty Walta Let's connect quickly and quickly Just
one last thing,
love me so much that I'm drowning You're not interested in me at all
You're the one who likes me After all, you're
not interested in me either.  I'm
tired of hearing it. You're not interested in me in the first place.
Even if you cheat like that again, I'm
ready.
Nore
[Music] I'm
happy.
[Music]
How about you?
[Music]  I
don't have much to laugh about in the morning when I'm dealing with an incident,
but I'm looking at you who pretends to be an anxious person
[Music] So I
cut it down to the right size.
[Music]
None I
broke it and died, but I feel like the knob is
turning.I want to get it back because it's so sticky.The
falling balaclaa is coming back home.Ara Ronde
Barreto is starting to face the Fai sweat incident.There's
nothing I can do about it, so I imitate the person whose day will come.
If you can simply believe it, I won't say it's not enough.What's wrong
with you?I
just eat and turn into a cow.I wake up and go back to sleep, and I'm
still alive.Even if I play
with my maximizer again and
break it.  Now I'm going to die,
but I feel like the knob is spinning, and I
want to get it back.
Maximizer Maximizer
Ah
[Music] Ah,
where are you and what are you doing now? I
'm in a place where this sky continues
[Music] I
lost what had filled my heart and
realized it for the first time. Please
support me so much.  I've
lost the things that made me smile so much. The
general is so huge that I
desperately try to reach out and struggle to get it back,
but it's like I'm slipping through the world of wind and I can't reach it.
My heart is squeezed by loneliness and despair, and I feel like I'm
about to die.
But your memorable smile
always cheers me up.
[Music]
[Applause]
Give me
[Applause] Let
's go back to those days once again.  I'm sure you'll
be fine. I'll always be
by your side, smiling. I'll be right next to you. Where are you and what are you doing right now? Are you
in this place where the sky continues? Will you continue to
smile like you always do? Right now, I
just wish for that
.  Music]
Continue
[Music]
[Music] Even though I was
chased after being thrown from my body, there's
only one left in the sun
Even when I don't like it, people take up space and
keep protecting it from being taken away.It's a filth.  Even the hands I've been holding without looking
dirty look dirty Before I can doubt my memories, my memories are doubting me. There's
no doubt that we'll come out. I'm always here, using the sound of the same child as my landmark,
so the reason for my waist is
heavy.  Meaning of Rere Sensei
As long as there are people who know this, there's nothing I can do about it, so I'll
take up space, and I can't fit two in the space I'm
in
Before you know it, it's just a plot
What you have to know is that between 1 and terrorism,
we'll meet for the first time. We'll use the same princess's flag
as a landmark, and don't forget. We'll call each other whenever. So we'll make
a promise when we'll fill in the piles of reasons together.  but  We're
like mirrors that can be passed over. We transfer our powers to each other. We
touch each other with our dirty hands and see the shape. We
're here. It's true that we're being touched. We're here
in our own private sun. Don't forget, call us anytime.
Because we have the same handle,
we must operate from the inside. When we make a sign of the cross for a reason, I will fulfill our
mission.
We will become one.
[Applause]
[Music]
So yes, Ehisa's song is Karma. What do you think? The cat
part was performed by the backing dancer Nee Takanari
Morimori,
but there was also Marshall
Maximizer and other things.  I think there was so much that I
forgot about it, but I
tried to pay a lot of attention to the production, so I'd really appreciate it if you could
pay attention to that as well.  I'm really
happy.
There are a lot of parts that I've
paid particular attention to after this one, so please look forward to the songs that come after this.
So it's
finally the second half of the live show, so this is the next song. Please listen to it.
Can you hear me?
[Music]
How much more should I avoid?
How much more should I cry? Stop, I
can't run anymore. The world I once dreamed of is closing. There's
no light on this crumbling road.  I
feel
like I've seen the hope of that time when it couldn't have been, and it's nostalgic,
my memories are just fun, and I was able to
move even though I was alive.I wish on the star that casts darkness, and I
run just one more time.
[Music]
From
With a scared and trembling voice, the sky is
dawning as I read my name.Even
after the distance to the line, I can't reach it.I'm
about to burst into frozen tears.Don't look down now, please
stop.  I know I
want to live in a future where it's gone,
remember it and believe in it strongly and strongly That's right,
Black Roshta The gentle
smell is painful, it's painful The words that I swallow,
Black Shooter, move, these
feet will
surpass the world
[Music]
[Applause] I
knew it from the beginning.
All the snow inside me won't run away as the days go by. There's only
one shooter. I do
n't care if you don't raise your voice. I'll watch you Blaklok Shooter. It's going to
start now.
[Music]
Story
When I feel like I'm about to forget, I'll sing this song.
[Music] The
canvas of the road I've painted, the overlapping scenery, I'll try to connect it
and repeat it again.  We'll
run through it as if it's vividly clouding us. Before we knew it, we'd shine brightly in our dreams, and we'd keep running, shoulder-to-shoulder. Your voice echoed brightly, illuminating you. Wherever can we fly?
[Applause]
[Music] I
want to walk with happy friends Every day I try to
grab hold of the limits that spread out in front of my eyes as my fingertips swell, and I look up at the night sky that looks like it's going to be sucked into me by putting everyone's hands on top of each other, and I'm
screaming now.  Yo,
Starry, my love, we'll always be by your side.A
voice full of laughter echoes in the distance.I'll
pull your arm, which is like a fragment of a wish, and where
will you stand and fly?
[Music]  Dakotono
also cast a spell and became 100 people,
and when I got over it, the kid who was about to make a big splash at the evil bull
burst out.
We've been waiting for this day too. I
haven't woken up yet,
and Stara, I can't stop.
I'll keep running until one second before the light disappears You're in the infinite universe
Hold tight to the voice that shines on you and shine
[Music]
te
Pare,
parepare, shine,
even without the voices calling each other.  I
ran to find Pare Pare Pare Pare Pare Pare I started every time
[Music] Date
[Music]
[Music] I
just kept talking to myself I
just wanted to start and ran I
stopped far away in the dark It was too
bright but
it was too fast I thought and
reached out to get closer  Our long-awaited thoughts have come together, and now we've
become us, and we're
shining brightly. Bringing our regrets and love with us, we're
flying away with a whisper of light.  I'm
relieved that I found you.From
now on, I'll fly away from here.  I can't count the
number of stories I've had,
but I don't feel like I can count the things that aren't there. Look,
right now, I call myself one too.
It's beautiful,
forgive me. The theory that we can meet each other flashes at night. The rain will clear up and I'll come back again.  A
pleasant visit is to be with you, it
's to be with you,
but even now, if you listen to it, I'll scream for you to go home. Is
n't it obvious
? I'm shining brightly. You're the one who fills my happiness. I'm
shining brightly. I love even the regrets.  Well, I'll
take you with me, Kazemu will fly away.It's just a simple thing.It's the
end of Nai's understanding.It's a
wonderful start to jump in with Nai-kun.From
here onwards, Our Fly Pare
Pare Awa Fly Pare
[Music]
Since I said yes to the parade, I played
Starlight, Our Bright
Parade, and Black Rock Shooter at Subaru with all the 2nd generation students.I
think it was quite a lot of content.  Thank you to all the
backup dancers who danced with us,
and to all the 2nd generation members.So,
with that said, here are some activities to
commemorate our 5th anniversary.Here, let's
take a look at them one by one.
First of all, here is the
Beats Tapestry. This is a
beaded tapestry made by Neshigure Uka-chan.
Please display it in your room together. It's
a little bit like clothes, too. It's a little
special, isn't it?  It's like a 5th anniversary dress.It
's cute.It
also has a Subaru duck on its face, and it looks
adorable with the flowers.Please
try displaying it together.And
then...
This is a Shiba jersey,
Subaru.Speaking of it, it's a jersey, but Subaru.Wear
this too.I don't
want to dance.I want to go to the studio or something, so
please come along and get it all ready.
Yes, I also recommend going to the gym.Yes,
and next,
this is Shima Cap.This is really good.I
actually wanted a Subaru, so I made this one,
but this one is written as Shiba.
Yes, it's a Subaru push, so
it's a cap that can be used while still appealing. It's black, so I definitely recommend it to you. If you're an actor, you can
wear it.
Next, let's talk
about these socks.  Well, this
is it.Subaru needs socks.I'm sorry.Subaru
wants socks, so I'll make them for you.Everyone
's cats are cute.You can wear Subaru Duck's
one-point socks to school or work.
Please go to the gym or reply if you like.Yes, and what the full set is, and it
is a reproduction festival and message.This
is a newly written postcard of Neshigure's mother.And,
this time, the quantity is not limited.
Thank you very much. It's not the original, so
please buy it at a different time.
Yes, and I have one more announcement.
After this, the PV of the new song will be released at 10 p.m.
[Music]
New songNew songNow let's move on to the last song.But the
last song is a new song.This song is
Subaru, who has been active for five years.  I
made this song thinking about all the fans and members who gave me this song, and I'm really happy to be able to celebrate our 5th anniversary with everyone like this.Thank
you for all your continued support.I want to express my gratitude and do my best to sing
this song.  I'm glad you think so  Please
listen to me, then let's go. Oh yeah,
then listen to me. Stella
Symphony.
In the sky that seems far away if you reach out your hands. The
[music] of shining hope. The
light stars
come together. The day when you meet a miracle, the day you seek it, floats around.
The heat that embraces the shining love is in the sky.
I was suddenly surrounded by the stars that were shining as they passed through the air.The
sky was
full of wishes and was filled with shining meanings, and I was surrounded by them.  I
pray that the stars will carry my love and that all of me will reach you. I'll cover the lid and stroke the stars. I'll be
gliding across the sky with you. My
dreams will be filled with stars.  The
stars were full and I was
illuminated by a certain miracle.
Even my tears ate time. If I
stretched out my hand, I could reach the sky.
Everyone's
light shines. We walked together. I can remember the love you gave me.
Embracing my destiny, I'll shine, so I'll reduce you,
so I'll glide across the sky.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much
[Music]
A
T
[Music]
I