he
[Music]
what sorry
HH uh uh uh uh there we go now you can
stream junky
wony yeah
make it
louder oh
you bye-bye
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah no
yeah he
[Music]
p
okay I should maybe
maybe smothie is still here next to me
sleeping or trying to sleep let's try to
not disturb her too
much k
key ah
[Music]
wait need to
check I I did I did some map before the
Stream
my
[Music]
okay I just realized how long this game
was it doesn't feel so long to me it
actually feels short maybe because I
like it so much it makes it like more
sad when it's over
ah there we go roaden are um telling me
what I wanted to
hear all right all right all right it is
one of the shorter ones is it though
like is it compared to other uh Zelda
games one of the shorter
ones that would be a little bit
unfortunate but I mean can't complain
when you're getting to two Zelda games
in one
[Music]
year hello
hello let's play the game until the end
today it seems pretty realistic
especially cuz we oh especially cuz we
didn't attempt to finish it last time
that gave us a a little bit more extra
time I'm sorry I'm picking hairs up off
of my
microphone suddenly intrusive
thoughts
um yeah today it has to be the last one
because the thumbnail the pattern has
changed and that is only acceptable if
it is the last part UNL your Oshi I am
not lemon
anymore it will end today this ends now
bit late don't worry you're not really
very late at all you just missed a lot
of purring from chunky wonky she's so
cute she goes
like when she's excited like she runs
towards what like her favorite spots
which is like if I'm walking into my
office then she will try to outrun me
and just leaps onto my office chair and
that when she lands on it she
immediately flops herself over uh into
the Nook of the chair basically and and
it's look
like but when she jumps she's like and
then she flap flops and
then she's so happy and she does the
same thing with the box that I have for
her um as a sleeping box on my bed when
she notices I'm going towards my bedroom
she follows me out runs me leaps onto
the bed throws herself into the box like
and
then expects belly rubs she's so
freaking cute I'm going to die but CH
chunky wonky very cute but also smoothie
very cute
today um sitting very close to
me wants always to be next to me while I
was doing um my Red Light lamp therapy I
was trying that out again we'll see this
is my second time I'm using it I'll try
to use it like every day or every second
day it's pretty chill relaxing it's like
some nice
warmth while I'm watching something on
my
iPad you've got free breads
what what do you
mean you mean my cats are my what
yeah
so didn't wake up too late today either
didn't take a nap just did
map and I I feel like today when I put
on my map I
finally got the pelvis
tracker into a position that feels
relatively secure so I think now it it
looks pretty good cuz last time when I
did some
moap like we had some chy told me there
was something weird and showed me and I
was like okay I'll redo it and I thought
maybe it's the pelvis tracker cuz that
probably that one always feels like the
more I dance and shake my hip because
the trackers I'm not wearing a full suit
as a reminder I'm I'm like wrapping
these um straps around me and I attached
the trackers onto the straps because
they're um what do you call that
material again the
velcro and so the one that wraps around
my hips slash belly or so you know is is
pretty big the strap and and I feel like
cuz it's supposed to go on the pelvis
right so it's like covering a little bit
of the hips a little bit of the belly
but like when I'm dancing it always
feels like it's moving around
yeah and I do think it has a little bit
of or a big impact on the map but it
looked good today it felt good
today
so
yeah see I need to Center myself the
hips don't lie the hips [\h__\h] everything
up
though a tournament what kind of
tournament congratul ations for the
participation you can do it you can do
it I believe in you
gamb
gamb you need to bolt it in place yeah
this whole time I've been thinking for a
whole year now oh I want to make myself
like a like a
leotard
because if it's a leotard and I feel
like things will move around less like a
velcro leotard or not the whole leotard
has to be velcro but the places where
the the things go um but I haven't
gotten to
it yeah but I want to DIY some stuff for
sure also the shoes like I always I have
um one tracker per foot and it goes
under the
shoe but that one also sometimes doesn't
feel too secure and I've tried things
like um first I had on top of the shoe
with uh um I wrapped um tape around the
whole
shoe with the tracker between the tape
and the
shoe um but that made a lot of noises
you may have heard it before when I was
doing 3d full body
map uh and you may have heard some like
tape
noises
like like that whenever I took a step I
think it was Audible
before yeah but that didn't even work so
well and it felt weird so yeah now I'm
just like trying to squeeze it
in as deep as I can into my shoe but
that also just doesn't feel so right I
need to sew one of those velcro pads
onto the top of the
shoe if it's sewn then that would be
good why do I have to do so many things
on my own
but yeah one of these days for now I
think I got it quite secure so we're
going to get the
next Mirage YouTube short probably
tomorrow are you excited are you excited
I'm excited they're looking good the
previews are looking good and looking
cute it's coming together
[Music]
so look forward to it let's
start question mark let
me sorry I was kind of stalling a little
bit I don't know why just felt like
it maybe because I don't want it to
end my beloved Zelda game please don't
end
SP on and on and on
this hello
controller are the batteries no are we
good okay
[Music]
there we go now I don't remember do I I
asked this before probably but do I
normally do full screen in this game
maybe I do do I no I don't I don't cuz I
show off the logo on the bottom left
[Music]
that's so fun I really hope echo of
wisdom zalas in the next smash BRS
because I love her design and Powers so
much
oh I can imagine her powers working in
Super Smash Bros what if
she she can definit she would like you
can definitely make a cppy
stuff but like you know how items fall
down in Super Smash Bros sometimes I
think you even get like boxes
like n she shouldn't be able to copy
everything because some things just
don't make sense I
guess but maybe maybe now when somebody
for example gets like a Pokeball item
picks it up throws it at her she should
be able to copy that Pokemon is that op
is that too
op copy the Pokemon and counter that or
um what else the the
hammer I guess that's that's to if she
can really copy everything her opponent
is already using
or yeah is it is it I don't know how
balanced is
[Music]
that would definitely have to test it
out let's leave it to
them okay it is time for The Legend of
Zelda echo of
wisdom oh
no can
no but yeah do you guys think there will
be a new Super Smash Brothers for the
second switch the switch
to you think
so like probably not right away
right how long did it take for I guess H
that was a the current one is
um uh what do you call it
again it's not actually made for the
switch it was um
uh wasn't it just um what's the [\h__\h]
word yeah a port was a port
right I mean would be such a waste if
they don't Port it to the switch too as
well but then again we want a new
[Music]
one it wasn't a port oh oh oh I see then
how how early in the lifetime of the
switch did it come
out I think speaking
of I don't think I did that much or took
that many screenshots
but oh yeah I guess I fought this thing
off screen which
is kind of crazy um it's like literally
a boss fight uh it's a boss that we
fought before but I think we fought the
ice vers no did we I don't know we
fought the water version or I don't know
but this was a different element version
of a boss we already fought before and
this I think uh a yeah I went into a
cave where there was this like
op Pig mob something funny happened
because um that mob is so [\h__\h] strong
actually and even this like pretty good
Force star red pig that I have could not
really it's originally four stars pretty
strong it couldn't do anything like it
was one hit for the blue one all the
time H but then I I somehow did
something funny so I brought out that um
ice spitting ice
blowing uh Echo right and the blue Pig
wanted to attack the ice
Echo but he like accidentally jumped
onto it but in his programmed AI mind he
was thinking all right I am in the best
position because I cannot get any closer
than this to the enemy so I will not
move anymore so he did not attempt to
jump down at all or move at all he kept
on swinging his big ass sword without
hitting anything because he's on top of
it but he thought he was hitting the my
ice Echo so oh stupid I kind of glitched
him into a situation
where I I don't have to do anything I
just have to wait for my Boomerang to
hit him often
enough which is is so good that that
happened because until that moment I was
like oh [\h__\h] this this guy is op my
Echoes are all too weak what am I going
to do then I was like okay let's freeze
him and then that
happened cuz he was probably one hited
my uh freezing Echo as well but yeah
that's how I killed him and as I said I
did that big boss fight too H that was a
goon side quest which is why I ended up
over
here here we
are am I am I too quiet
[Music]
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
okay all righty um what else did I do
yeah I told you I think in the previous
stream um off stream I got this lovely
Oh No I gave this away um I got these
two items to make this this item this
pendant and exchange I received
something this this the might Bell yeah
and this one I maybe I also got this off
screen not sure
anymore game kind of loud
[Music]
okay I turned it down a little bit maybe
still too loud how about
now how is
it let me take a bath cuz I'm
stinky seems good
okay uh so looking at our map it's been
a little while since I played I'm
confused we have two more two I mean
this one's really big but I guess it's
two more regions before we go to the
next region I want to go to
Dam cuz I have it uncovered over here
over here no is it this thing have it
uncovered but I haven't been there
yet um and then I want to do
this oopsie that's probably the side
quest for K's
brother what what is
this ah the [\h__\h] burning coal ah the
[\h__\h] side quest I I tried it but I
was like [\h__\h] this too
annoying uh I guess I'm going to finish
that really quickly with your
advice yeah we're first going to do the
small things and then we're going to go
to the next region which I don't know if
I should go first to the Eternal Forest
uh cuz I think there's some
optional stuff but then I think also the
main story leads you into the Eternal
Forest after you've done all the
dungeons
right yeah so I think we should go down
here
first sounds good oopsie uh what am I
doing I can't somehow my my fingers are
pressing all the wrong
buttons that's what I thought yeah a
certain someone just like goes
everywhere first before following the
story properly and
then sees everything too early and then
I can't watch those parts because
they're being uncovered too early and I
don't want to be spoilered
yeah anyway wait I was going to do this
Quest where is the
thing the sound is distracting me p p
where is the side quest
[Music]
guy flames of Fortune Flames why is it
two locations I think it starts up there
right
[Music]
okay uh so give me a new
ball of
coal have you guys done this side quest
I don't know how to solve this yet it
has to stay by like uh
hot the
sources but like a little bit outside of
it is fine for it but then ah see see
now it's like more and more losing ah is
that okay oh [\h__\h] there it goes hey I
think there's a specific route to take
use fire hint what do you mean hint
should I have one of my fire Echoes
follow me closely I I don't know how
closely I can force them to follow me
cuz they're slow most of
[Music]
them I just ran real fast
I don't even understand the route
yet should I go up up
here where are we going or I guess down
here jump no jump to the right
oops we carry it quickly over here and
then uh jump down
there and then where are we
[Music]
going no
sorry I'm stupid I don't know it's the
PS controller for the aceto Corsa that I
used the other day that's absolutely
confusing me and then over here as long
as it's as I'm carrying it closely to
the lava it will be fine question
mark all right let's let's
try I hate these can I let's should I
kill them first I wonder if they're
going to be an issue
otherwise where's my
ice where is he where is he where is
he oh yeah this this is the really
strong sword moblin he's crazy he's a
crazy boy okay how about this one
do some stuff do it do
it are you doing something there we go
oh oh good job this one's pretty
strong pretty flexible too flies around
wherever I need it oh I never got this
one
before you can have two yeah I guess so
thanks for reminding me cuz I do always
forget to do that but most of the time I
don't really need a second one
okay I I think we're
good let's
go
up and pick up the
thing H they might be in the way
but I don't know where that Ping P was
coming from I was looking for
it but I honestly don't know
okay they it shoots a little bit slow
but oh
well I always forget about the lock on
Mechanic it's so important to make your
Echo pay attention to what you want them
to find it's really
important yeah I know it's my bell but
I'm wondering where it's hidden cuz it
only rings when something's close by but
the funny thing is I've no noticed when
I was like out in the fields and it was
ringing and I was like where the [\h__\h]
what I've noticed that even if you're in
the Overworld it will ring
if the crystal is underground in a
[\h__\h]
cave that is a bit crazy to me because
I'm looking in the Overworld not knowing
that it can react to something that is
literally in a different
instance like you have to go through a
cave
that's really weird to me talk to me oh
you're scared
of got me now let me try again piece of
cake we'll see about
that you also can't remember why rings
but also could be reactive to the quest
if the reward is a crystal has it ever
been a crystal before a reward for a
quest
uh oops is it going to fall apart oh no
it
doesn't is this
fine is this going to be
okay what I don't know if it was
actually staying here that broke so
quickly what did
yeah it's really close to him but I
don't know I looked
around just can't find it but it's okay
we don't need every single one of them I
don't really care about getting every
single
one stay hot
how close do you want to
be stay stay stay and then and then and
then uh
down
what is that not the uh
oopsy is that not the best
path wait uh should I go up and down
but like if I walk down that'll be I
think too
long but you just had to reach the goal
fast oh no I think uh it needs to stay
some next to something hot but when uh
when I placed it in the lava that's when
it breaks as
well so
hey drop it near a fire
slug
okay oh yeah on fire again question mark
I'm not sure if it's
like losing heat constantly right now
but
um [\h__\h] is it going to break is it going
to break is it going to break is it
going to break is it going to let's
let's let's place it here for a little
bit
uh ow ow ow ow that's fine that's fine
um wait just uh
ow take care of you in different
ways get in get in there you little [\h__\h]
stay there get out of my
way okay ow
he really was not bothered by me moving
him thank you for your
cooperation um wait how do we get up oh
no we're going
down we have a a ping ping here as well
I don't know if I've checked out the
area properly here before but let's
focus on the quest first I suppose and
then what I just like fall down here
uhhuh can
I that seems kind of dangerous I feel
like this might not go so well but okay
it's as close as it can
be should I maybe spawn a he might um if
I spawn a fire mob like in an area he
might not react to my my
coal and there we go yay yeah yeah yeah
that was
easy cuz it was still very much on fire
that was enough
noise side quest complete what do I
get it was because of the
quest that makes sense because over here
it also is pinging
ah but I don't think I ever got a
crystal for a quest before so it's
like I think a lot of people might just
be looking around in the area for ages
without
[Music]
realizing
damn okay
um uh yeah sure let's do that next oh
God I don't know what the hell I'm doing
right now I'm
sorry I was trying to get to the map um
so what's my closest teleportation Point
can I just fall down from
here I don't think so cuz that's like so
high you die when
you try to jump down why don't I have a
single teleportation
Point O
see P has five buttons fusero
bamboozle I'll walk over from
here you die when you fall to your
death you die when you fall 5,000 m into
the
void see I don't I literally don't know
what I'm doing what am I
doing what am I doing
should I walk or should I get
my what's wrong with my what am I
pushing why am I pushing these
buttons I made also a lot of smoothies
by the way to get the the next level
smoothie achievement so to say which I
don't think it did anything what am I
looking for I think um what would be
nice is having the carrot anyway so no
you were supposed to switch to a carrot
don't you
[Music]
realize that's what I was trying to do
okay horsey
horse L don't know how to control this
game anymore I need your
help okay right button remember
Taki
no my horse was out of control oh it
respawns
yep right there good to
know what was I
[Music]
saying I don't know what I was just
saying um I was doing smoothie
stuff is that what I was saying I don't
know
anymore that's not a seahorse
K oops
misunderstanding
Yi okay I have arrived finally I have
avoided this place for as long as I
could oh why is there so many p
[Music]
ps and there is the warp point of course
of course of
course don't worry I wasn't going to
ignore it I was just looking
around why can't the bird not leave me
alone do something no do something do it
again even though the bird is already
escaping how about the
little
blobs good
[Music]
job there something up there o That's
Stone ah yeah that's
100% a I I never know what to call them
might Crystal was that what they were
actually
called there we
[Music]
GOI okay there's something else up
there I'm still hearing the pting pting
sound but I think it's maybe from the
cave over there inside the cave
possibly not sure if I want to go into
the cave oh actually never
[Music]
mind y another one I have gathered so
many off screen as well
oh there's still
[Music]
something maybe that one
is actually in the
cave or up there somewhere on the right
side oh it got louder so it could be in
the cave okay we'll check it out later
let's see what this is all
about
finally I've been waiting for you
welcome to my Top Secret Workshop T
studio all right before I forget here's
your
reward thanks actually I already have so
many of these because I just went to the
snowy
mountains anyo I work night and day
making an atim are here in my studio
guess you don't know the Jo yet of a
well all righty allow me to do to the
jazzling world of my Clockwork
Beauties here we go
a are works of pure art inspired by
moners i p my soul to each and everyone
my
artons they are so flashy they'll even
fight for you I'm sure you'll be great
with them I'm pretty sure anyway enough
of my hammering it's time to get
[Music]
hammering I'd like to any but any
struggling you see I'm an artistic run
so if I go to take a walk and clar my
head and I get costed by a crow can you
believe it at any rate I got be thinking
about making a real Jing or something
that can shoot up into the sky so let me
do the concept but I need more than just
one idea for my creative person and I
need inspiration if I if I saw something
fresh I could make a sh you
ultimate I'll find you something and you
sure a pie thans for the basis of this
new art piece let's see I'm thinking
about a creature with the big eye the
sword that always JPS around but that
won't be enough on the I need something
that would help me imagine the new
blasting upward in a lifting kind of
way looking for something that shoots
hard smoke out of its backside to blast
forward okay that that
really hard voice to create because
I'm twisting my
face uh I think so for a different side
quest I at least I'm pretty sure I have
the thing that shoots up into the
sky
uh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I I don't know what buttons I'm
pushing anymore today um so uh is this
last used okay how about last learned
maybe
closer this
thing but what was the other thing he
wanted something with an eye on the
ground
I mean there's a lot of eyes on the
ground big eye one one big eye this one
time oh he wants that
[Music]
first my it perfectly thanks for finding
it for me only think there
one what maybe he wanton that first what
let me look at the quest again cuz I'm
confused actually
wrong button
again that shoots Hot Smoke oh never
mind never mind never mind he didn't
want the fireworks yet I know they're
necessary later on I think I think I
must have shoot Hot Smoke blast
[Music]
forward moner shoot
smoke wait wait wait
wait um
I feel like we had something like that
in a dungeon but that wasn't anything I
could learn do I have a freeart but with
fire did I miss copying
something the
butterfly flying mushroom The
Moth why
is that what it does I don't remember
anymore it's been a while since I used
it okay it seems to
work I'm BR my inspiration
woohoo all right what is he making I
keep a hug eye top off of a glitchy
metallic
body finish the D at custom to make it
lunch in a really show
way
[Music]
no okay
Now That's What I Call snazzy Aon I dump
it to take that here all
yours okay and is that better than the
ones I already have yeah it's a fles can
launch High into this guy with a big
jump but yet when it jumps it BL away
any my mes so it's like a ground P but
like
reverse not the moment it lands but the
moment it jumps is when it's basically
ground pounds
everybody we'll see we'll
see you know you guys all mention CeCe
but what I'm thinking about is um ni
Joel he's so
cute was it Nel pretty sure it was Nel
right yeah n she's so cute
oh like her um the small little girl
that's her like scientist or what yeah
Haka said she is hak oh I need to
rewatch n so I love that anime so much
those two had like the best moments in
the
anime yeah she just wants to be a real
girl and hak it keeps on like messing
with her right making weird things out
of her making her arms into rockets and
stuff and then now was like no I just
want to be normal stop messing around
with me
right that was so
cute ah all these like core memories
of like the time when I was most into
anime is like coming back to me right
now yeah the cat was so
cute that's a really good one really
good anime I always liked nio like daily
life animes than on the most and that
one literally embodies it because it's
in the title everyday life
ni so it does it so well it's so
cute the opening music was also really
cute I know I remember that feeling that
was really good but I literally don't
remember the opening song anymore right
now but yeah he so
cute use that to wind him up it's a
precious window a Kinder so don't go
losing it these unusual Creations are
made by the automatone engineer damp if
one of them breaks you can visit him and
he'll fix it they break while holding
that button use R to select an automaton
oh the other direction Ah that's how you
separate them hold why to wind it up why
to wind it up mhm I need rubies to cover
the C of repairs but I fix it up good
are these even worth going out of my
way creating them
finally a ed for the other pet for
Realo anime what is that really the
title I've watched some anime that was
that had something something in the
title really I I hope so
H well let's try it out
first maybe that's why he had those
little enemies over there so I can test
it out on them but look at
that oh
cute and I can't ah
wa that was unexpected it does it once
and then it basically is done and I have
to wind it again I
see how would they break if I just use
them too often oh now it disappeared
because I went into the menu like
that
okay hold the wind wind longer if I wind
it longer it stays out longer or
what okay so he finally takes my
freaking monster
Stones ah let's go I love those things I
take monster stones for repairs R than
rupes if you're interested Ah that's the
only use for them for
repairs
o just talk to me if you need
repairs okay what about this Quest you
have oh wait you don't have another
[Music]
Quest what what's oh I have to read your
Journal I thought that was the I thought
the bubble was over
him explosions Galore concept A joval
explosive automaton that leaves
destruction in its weight good
stuff I know it will be
another but theide alone isn't enough as
usual I need the proper inspiration to
set me on fire hoping you'll help me
again for the basis of this new arm
piece a creature that spits stones out
of its mouth there won't be enough
though firework okay good
firework I have but stones out of its
mouth let's see it could be just um an
ooto oopsie but uh do we have like a
basic
octo that just spits normal Stones
probably
right
[Music]
um that one
is that what you want
oh good good
[Music]
good and then the fireworks that I
already have cuz I already did the side
quest
yippee I have oh we shouldn't do that in
the house oh no oh no turn it off turn
it off sorry it went off on its own I'm
sorry your house is going to be on
fire don't don't activate it in here
once you're done with it it might be
even crazier than what I
launched uh
uh-oh well surely his house has been for
a lot so it can take it right yeah his
fire is probably his fire is on the
house a lot mhm his house is probably on
fire a lot a talk to
rock oh cute
it's kind of cuter when it's out of
metal wait is
CeCe's skin not soft but out of metal if
I knock on her body will it make like
a no more like
[Music]
a like that kind of
sound is is it
it's very durable oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
interesting I never realized that her
skin might not be real real skin never
thought about that wait what
ah it's in
here okay here we go
do
something
who okay okay chill
oh wa okay smoothie is very disturbed by
this okay and then you fall
[Music]
asleep oh it also Finds Its Targets on
its own
nice
yo okay that's kind of
crazy oh I think I already pushed all
these Stones around thinking maybe
there's a item hidden underneath but
there
wasn't yeah that's pretty sick oh it
disappeared
okay I might use that one here and
there but how fast do they
break I
wonder summon two of the laser eyes to
start
blasting the hug
ability uh wait is there no more on in
the book oh there is
okay
uh huh sounds good let's do the Cho them
into if I can
[Music]
what do you
want a monster with a sword who fights
alongside
others oh wait this is side quest
related something in
kakariko
oopsie oh only one thing is what you
need
o uh if I do all of these side quests
from damp do you think we'll still get
finished
today maybe some of his side quests I've
already finished like the firework
one oh wait yeah there was the the the
fighter sword fighter guy in there in
kakaro that I didn't really do anything
with yet
huh mon one monster and one Quest Min
okay I haven't done it yet right hi
chicky
I do have a few items already okay
that's
good is it is that what those items are
are
about
wait these ones at the bottom ah this
one that sounded like something he might
use
okay um can I have this please
it's probably what I want to have it's
been a part of this do it's been a part
of this do ages real sharp too but I
don't touch it anymore it's too
dangerous perhaps if you ADV far enough
and the training I'll UST it to you okay
so what kind of training is
[Music]
this the slumberous path lays long
before you care to do some training and
aim higher for higher Heights of
unconsciousness I am ready
a here's our menu of dream options ah
[\h__\h] wait what do I have to do all of
them in order to get the
[Music]
sword takes some time to finish too long
for the stream
o okay I don't need every damp
[Music]
automaton I guess I chose the one that
is like the most
time
consuming ah half for the
sword go time on like six should I
try is it work two like am I not going
to lose too much time let's try one of
them and see how difficult they are
there's a fun outfit if you do all of
them oh
oh okay star no Echo and no items
allowed defeat your enemies using only
what's available in the in the dream
okay well I've never done any of these
so let's try at least one and see how it
[Music]
goes also giv items that reduce the
energy used for link from o okay okay
okay uh for this training all you have
is your Rod your experience and
inventory will be sealed off so be be
ready your gold time is 60
seconds
[Music]
okay uh wait can I how do I learn again
ah I don't know if I need the stone
though but that was a pretty quick
solution for that guy I don't think I
can do that with the bat though can I
wait there's hey how do I I don't know
the solutions H wait uh wait I can't
drop you um oh wait
ah how about uh oh God this doesn't fly
wait okay let me let me learn you um if
I if I drop you the problem is I won't I
won't [\h__\h] H [\h__\h] wait I have an idea
God what if I ow what if I lead you ow
oh wait um hi H [\h__\h] wait I I throw it
at you I forgot I can throw these things
can I redo this
ah this feel chaotic there little time
too big that's my first time okay okay
okay okay and now you can shoot the bat
and
perhaps uh uh uh where ow ow I'm not
going to make it a [\h__\h] I'm going to die
wait you didn't even kill the bat you're
so useless oh right because it's like
okay stay down stay down yeah yeah yeah
yeah cuz it flies up so high ah
[Music]
bind the plant bind well you think my
keys can do it per CH Perhaps
[Music]
Perhaps okay maybe I can do it but now
it's obviously too late we'll try it
again now I have a little bit more of a
plan of how to deal with this but it's
very strong what would I ideally do
can't even get up there um so I don't
know if this is the best thing to do but
what if I were to make myself
[Music]
well anyway what's the fire for anyway
pull a plant oh oh right I can just pull
it bad news you [\h__\h]
died we'll do it
again can I grab it from like one level
below it like on the step
what what do we start for what's the
best maybe as I did before the dropping
the guy I mean he could help me fight if
I kill him properly but I don't believe
in myself uh-oh being able to do
that uh uh wait
[Music]
um okay we're learning
that how did I kill the bat ah the
doctor
up I don't think I need to learn the
stone honestly unless maybe for
stairs you do that oh [\h__\h] I need to I
need to bind the bat to come down
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h] ah there we go it's down it's down
it's down shoot it shoot it shoot it
shoot it okay okay uh don't think I'll
need the
bat but I don't know
here you
go what
what
what come here come here come
here Target them a
[\h__\h] okay we did
it I forgot that I can even even though
I did it like 10 seconds before lock on
and then send
the send my lemon out there what did he
just give me I didn't look sorry I'm so
useless right
now well that's manageable I think maybe
if they don't get too crazy I could do
six of
these but they look kind of crazy
[Music]
you think they are sorted by
difficulty let's try Titan easy just use
that's what I thought like I know how to
fight the Titan at least it gives you 10
minutes let's
try so I do get to be Zelda H
link you do get Echo for some of them
okay okay
for this training your material
possessions will be available fight with
everything oh everything I have is
available not just specific
ones
oh I will I will probably I'll will
probably do everything wrong anyway cuz
I'm nervous now cuz of the timer the
timer for 10
minutes I mean but he wants it
under is it just as long as it's under 1
minute uh 10 minutes really really don't
that's going to be so
wait oopsie
[Music]
uh get out of there come
[Applause]
on wait I forgot how to turn into
link this is too easy is it
[Music]
not I literally didn't realize until
today
that you can do that too that you can
lock and then send your lemon I know you
can lock but I didn't know the lemon
goes that way
too the things you learn on the last day
of your game play huh all
right why is this so
easy sorry I don't know what I'm doing
Tak it on a little walk my beloved ball
oh hi smovie what are you doing you
chose the box to lie in it
okay holy [\h__\h] I did it in under a
minute wait is there more bosses that
I'm fighting more Titans
perhaps ah every
Titan it's not ending that's for
sure oh oh okay every B every boss
and then I don't know if 10 minutes is
enough are the first threee okay uh how
did we fight this one I was just
swimming and then I don't know I don't
remember I don't remember this one so
well but if I send out my sharks I mean
that should be helpful right and I was
using bombfish maybe here and there too
I don't know if I even had the shark
maybe I did
[Music]
well
great a [\h__\h] well maybe right now
there's no point but now it's a
point oh God the he's so D wait I should
put on the cloes to swim
faster
um dive faster does swimming help while
diving too I don't I don't know
maybe it does maybe it
doesn't anything else I could
help um
okay wait oh wait you still one oh
forgot I
forgot ow
wa
wa I'm still acting like a [\h__\h] idiot
but I'm doing pretty well for that all
things
considered
um what oh I can't shoot Arrow water
okay oh
[\h__\h]
um H what goes through water but also
through air don't
know let's just stay here for now and
survive oh
[Music]
here oh he's offering himself to me um
wait did I shoot right
now oh does it not get rid of the
bubbles though cuz I hit and it didn't
get rid of the
bubbles yo
Sharky I shall never doubt your
abilities ever again that was a big fast
hit that I really needed
okay third boss
then should be the last
apparently ah this one I was so bad at
this
one yeah sharks can one hit the
back the bubbles when he gets the right
angle I think at
least um
I don't
know whatever
although how how did I do this fight
again
sh I I'll need these statues right um
make him run against
them um
[Music]
uh well come out H there we
go he stopped right in front of
it trying to remember I crash place just
placed a
[Music]
couple get higher chances here here here
oh [\h__\h] the angle wasn't quite right it
was just too far okay okay here uh maybe
more like
here do it again please sir please all
right okay if you do it from there again
I would be really delighted oh oh that
could work yeah okay and
now do I okay I thought I had to pull
him out for a moment but okay just hit
his ass ah look at my energy it's empty
is any energy flying around or do I do I
have to I didn't see any flying
around I guess I'll drink uh that thank
[Music]
you pretty easy to protect yourself if
you just stand behind these
[Music]
statues is he going to end up coming out
of the same angle again just because I'm
standing here oh yeah uh oh oh oh Sor
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry we
know we know today is not my
day yeah Sile might have had some but oh
well ah am I fine I have the shoes on
right
so he flies now is he still going to do
the same kind of
[Music]
attack do these get destroyed by the
tornadoes because these are kind of
bigger than the small wind yeah small
wind storms that he had
okay but I'm still going to place them
because I think he still does the the
diving
um just don't know where he'll end up at
how about you try diving against this
one my
[Music]
friend oh well can I can I shoot him
from
[Music]
here oh
totally ah
wait should I just kill him with my
[Music]
arrows oh
[\h__\h] come here come here come here yeah
okay okay I got him I got
him took him a while to give me an
opportunity
again but it's okay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
chilling could try to shoot him a little
[Music]
bit I'm dancing like a
ballerina obviously not taking this
fight very seriously
[Music]
all right bring it on ah that might be
too far no it
wasn't
[Music]
yipp
okay nice boss rashes are fun to do
every once in a while so I didn't mind
that at
all 5 minutes yeah the first one I was
really fast cuz I still remembered that
one cuz I did the similar but different
element
version uh fairly
recently I mean that one is just the the
easiest in terms of mechanics
anyway the others are like what did I do
again to defeat this
boss
okay is that too slow for like is there
a secret
reward get milk
M ah you dreamed big in advance your
never Level Training is like the Wet
Stone of sleep it's promised I've got
something astounding for you in
recognition of your sleepy progress
oh
okay if you pass your trading just two
more times I'll have an astounding
reward for you wait so if I did better
would he have given me another thing or
is the heart
piece okay okay
[Music]
oh okay
um I wonder how you
solve this one should I try this
[Music]
one is
easy it's about completing a your quest
you did good okay okay okay
M fast time only gives extra ingredients
okay back into Dreamland
how you have to rely on your skills
alone you won't be able to use drinks or
items that restore your hearts okay but
how what is this about I I need to kill
all of the armadillos but
how what's What's Happening Here what oh
[\h__\h] does this open oh oh dear oh dear
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait
wait I keep the echo
oh he's a fast boy come on wait maybe I
should get
more like cheap but
fast enemies or my own armd I don't know
[Music]
wait can can I use
my ah wait uh
ah no let me wind it
[Music]
up yes
ah he fell down but oh he's still going
he's still
going shoot shoot
shoot
finished let's
go wow that was a lot faster than
necessary even though I was kind of
fumbling everything
[Music]
that is quite helpful for this
training let's do another one we might
be pretty fast in
these can we use the same automatone for
like everything to solve all these
problems like this an UNR hord of mods
if they give me time to unwind my or
wind up
my my explosion
massive destruction thing then I
[Music]
mean doesn't even have to be that but
yeah cuz maybe they don't see me yet
when I'm behind the stones so they'll
give me time right
right oh yeah they don't see me
yet just give me a moment here we
go don't get hit by The Spar though oh
yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
oh I can clear for these quite
easily I love Fireworks how
beautiful and speed like that makes you
quite the power Napper oh my naps are
usually very long I don't know how I
could nap so fast this time time
normally I nap longer really oh it's
almost as if he knew that I used an
automaton for
that you train big and advance to
another level training is like a
wetstone of sleep as promised uh here's
something astounding oh n first Mastery
is this what makes my energy go down
less equip it to slightly slow energy
loss when you're in sort by
yay I love that two more times all right
I think that will add up to six in total
anyway wait what are these
signs on on the top
right could it be that there is a reward
like special cuz these are the ones that
I did exceptionally fast I
think but is he not did he give me
something
[Music]
special without being Swept Away by the
current
am I in
the I want to know where can I apply the
same strategy again this one maybe
defeat your enemies using only what's
available in a dream this looks like
they will spawn me Behind the Walls
again so again I might have time to wind
it up but there's wind
H let's try although wait are they
giving me my echo for this
one oh [\h__\h]
oopsie um
then this might be but if I can just
drop them in the
hole then we might be
okay what what are the wind machines
for no T
Strat should I drop the wind machines
too I mean I guess they can Blow
Away wait do they scream are those the
screamers wait they don't even scream I
thought this would be more difficult
oh it's like I'm sort playing a sorting
game Mario party or something oh I see
um
[Music]
here dangerous can you come with
me uh
[Music]
oopsy y y I'm out of time I'm going to
run oh wait he fell down too wa there's
one
more I don't have much time come with
me was that the last one
yes yeah and this goes into the square
hole and this also this this shape goes
into the square hole this shape also
goes into the square hole
[Music]
this took you free tries you need to
cheese it like
me I don't even like cheese that much
but this kind of cheese I I like this
kind of
cheese okay floating on fire Sor no
Echo Fe all the
those allow fire fight for all enemies
oh another a enemy Rush m
[Music]
well honestly with that speed it feels
like I could do all of them this is not
taking up as much time as I
thought okay let's try this without
being Swept Away by the
current is this without
everything how can I cheese
this for you'll have to rely on your
skills alone you won't be able to use
the drinks or ah okay no drinks or items
what about swimming items do I get those
but my echo will be there
right um what if I just sent okay we get
these oh yeah
um what if I just send some
[Music]
flying
enemies uh [\h__\h] um sorry ah ah ah like
one of these
or that I don't even have to get into
the water right this one's kind of slow
like the attack speed use bats for this
one yeah how about the fire
Keys oh but the problem is come here
come here ke there you go he he gets it
he gets it
now oh [\h__\h] it spawn no ah ah [\h__\h] not
this is not that easy yeah yeah yeah
yeah you can do it you can do it can I
only spawn one okay but we got one down
ow do something quick okay it's on fire
um is there any more over there or is
that the end I I'm trying to see maybe
not oh I see I see it and the spiky boy
can you attack the spiky boy too
yeah oh who's
left
a hey if there's so much more on the
right side is there something oh yeah I
see something on the left side
[\h__\h] uh yeah damn might not be able to
make
[Music]
it okay we got the whole right side
yeah how do I get [\h__\h] I have to clear
the left side completely first otherwise
I'll have a hard
time come
on can I do it fast
please wait I can I didn't realize it's
eating me no wait if I can just turn
into link next time I'll just um shoot
with my arrow we'll be faster that way
yeah I knew there was one more over
there but I I was trying to see if there
was more when I was first on the left
side but the water was just so annoying
okay not first try but I can definitely
do
it this took you five
tries well I I will show you how it's
done but
[Music]
honestly um
okay no can I redo oh [\h__\h] I didn't have
these things on because I put them on
like after I started the
[Music]
mission ah
please please let me
up ah okay
[Music]
um no
no please please please please
oh okay
okay okay okay okay
okay can I get on some platform is m is
is it dead is my thing dead
no what why is it I'm trying to get to
the enemies
[Music]
the [\h__\h] water makes it so
annoying oh and like when when you try
to jump on the platforms but it keeps on
pushing you further
away
but somehow I still managed to do it
okay we good we
good I got the sword the katana get
to
wow you can't just give that to me that
easily it's an
heirloom bro if you pass your training
just two more times I'll have another
astounding reward astounding well that
honestly sounds tempting it's the outfit
right I want it I want it
I want it it's just wait two more we
have three more missions though H cross
over The Lava to defeat all the foes
okay just get some
ice um Echo out to
help should be easy outfit needs all
missions no problem this is not taking
as much time as I thought thought it
would take like an hour if I do all of
them that would be crazy but we're good
uh I
[Music]
wonder what would be
best I'm just going to
assist wait is my mob
[Music]
gone oh ah [\h__\h] do I have to fight that
stone in the ground too
uh oh no okay I think I can do it though
it's 2
minutes oh
sh we'll have to find a different
solution for
the The Rock in the water I don't know
how to kill
that in the water in the lava wait never
mind I'll just shoot it I'll shoot
anything but I can't if I'm out of that
energy I can't use it anymore I can't
get an item right ah sorry I can't even
speak anymore I don't know how to speak
uh okay I'm out and I don't think I'm
allowed to use smoothies right yeah um
okay uh the bomba boys the bomba boys
oops
no the bomba
boys yeah right yeah good that he's
right there drop it drop it on on him
drop it on him like it's hot not so far
bro bro bro bro bro bro
um Oh you mean do you mean should I try
my
firework for the back what shoot
[Music]
finally wait what's left what's left
[\h__\h] H what's what [\h__\h] sorry sorry
sorry sorry what's
left
[\h__\h] I don't even
know what's left what's
left there's a [\h__\h] bat on the top
left up there top right okay um
something that's fast I mean you're not
fast but you're very
precise let's try and another
B come on don't disappoint me go for
that go a it's right in front of you
okay
chaotic a time limit really makes me
panic but hey we first tried it
Yoo
next I am ready I was born ready as you
know next one is Ice start with no
Echoes and no items allowed oh not even
my icy shoes now my I think the those
items are always allowed just not
smoothies is what they mean so let's
already put on the right
shoes where are my shoes
did I not have those
[Music]
shoes wait didn't I have shoes to walk
on Ice nor like a normal
person or did I just watch that in Dum
tendel
videos oh
[\h__\h] I don't have that
item when you're mixing up things you
experienced and things you experienced
for watching a bot I wonder if you guys
have the same issue when you play the
same game as
[Music]
me and then you're not sure anymore you
get really confused about what you did
and what I did yeah
really uh okay well we'll have to do it
without then I mean it should be
manageable
H maybe I can just drop them again those
look very droppable to
me uh wait so what I don't have the
echo I don't oh but I could learn
[Music]
them can I read
[\h__\h] that was a a bad side ah
ah what am I
doing I'm supposed
to let me redo it let me redo it I want
to
redo how do I do
this wait okay they melt like I but do
they melt really
fast I think I I I
understand I'll just carry the fire in
front of me constantly and
hope that they can't get around
me try to always stay
frontal do I need to learn it or should
I just carry it around oh they really
melt it doesn't even see me
yet wait wait uh maybe I can learn it
though could help
me wait did the timer go on no
[Music]
right wait wait wait I didn't what I
didn't learn it I thought I did oh I
learned the I learned the fire
[Music]
fight each other
[\h__\h] so messed up oh okay I see it's a
good
distraction it's definitely a
distraction for
him okay they cancel each other
out umu
[Music]
how is this possible within the
[\h__\h] what okay
[Music]
what okay okay
um yeah I could I was thinking now too
like maybe I don't have to do everything
with the fire I could still try to go
back to my strategy of dropping them
while he's
distracted yeah maybe maybe just the
first one we fight with fire and then
every other one we distract with the icy
boy of our own and then try to get
behind them and drop
them the thing is
though oh okay I don't have I can't jump
high
enough don't don't you [\h__\h] me right
[Music]
nowm are you are you melting him okay
then let's learn him
too and then I'm not even should I bring
the fire I don't
know um no
uh so now I'm going to try to
um
[\h__\h]
sh there we go oh sh oh okay
[Music]
okay go for him go for him go for him
while I'm trying to clear the path a
little
bit
[\h__\h] I can't [\h__\h] move over
[Music]
here okay I don't think I can make it
though it's not enough
time or is this the last one is there
many
more you keep you'll keep on going
towards the goal
please wait sh sit
[Music]
sit attack attack attack okay
f with me no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
no no I hate this was that the last
[Music]
[Applause]
one this would be so much easier with
those
shoes where you don't slip on
eyes I could have grabbed it from R yeah
yeah
yeah was it the last it was not oh [\h__\h]
I could probably just
spawn but the moment they see the torch
I think they attack it as well don't
they so I would have to spawn it behind
them sometimes that's not possible
without them seeing
me when the Panic sets in yep nothing
else in my brain works anymore but for
real that that timer is a bit
[Music]
rough what I wonder why they want me to
learn the wooden boxes as well because
they're the same height as the ice
blocks but at least I guess you don't
um slip on
[Music]
them is the self mission I guess it
is well the first one kind of worked
like that
[Music]
so this this this has has to be fast I
should lock on why did I not remember to
just lock
on can you just box them in
ice
box
ice but then how am I going to reach
[Music]
them set box is on fire but that would
take too long yeah
[Music]
melt the second one
okay now torches can't be dropped on
them unless I I am on a higher place um
but I can't get up higher cuz I can't
jump so high and I can't spawn it over
them if they are that PA themselves from
my
experience uh anyway let's learn this is
this melting him
yeah I guess I'll learn that too
if this is a stealth Mission like
honestly they need to make the timer
longer because how am I supposed to
think about it cuz in stealth missions
you
think I can't think that
[Music]
fast
um well let's get him distracted anyway
[Music]
oh right
cuz yeah I was thinking but
I I can't come up with a better
way um but um ah no no no no no no no no
no
I want the outfit do something you
little
[\h__\h] no I hate
[Music]
them what I don't understand
um
[Music]
um come with me
[Applause]
[Music]
no the angle the angle man
getting there I'm what do you mean I can
grab it grab
what for the ice you no then I would
just grab the ice
block I can't sneak past I have to kill
every enemy
[Music]
yeah I was thinking just now I could
probably be faster if I just drop the
first one uh but if I drop him I won't
learn him maybe I don't want to learn
him maybe I'm fine about learning him
but oh well
[Music]
torch is all you
need but he attacked me last time I
spawned
the this next to him oh well never mind
now it's kind of working but he went
straight for attacking me last time
um if I stay calm and
collected
[Music]
okay and then wait wait wait this one
um grab this one from from from
where from where
never mind I'm
[Music]
okay how many
more wait um um
um oh
okay don't see me please don't see me
okay okay okay
what there's so many how do you do it
within the
[Music]
time maybe a second one oh oh no oh no
oh no I [\h__\h] up I [\h__\h]
up okay okay we we got to try again oh
oh yeah we got to try again the time
[Music]
is the last two
wait no now now it's wonderful they went
back and they're not paying attention so
now I can do this of
course but they were facing me
beforehand
um the table helps later on I guess on
the table I can
jump damn this one's
really stopping me in my
tracks would still be easier to have the
shoes for
the anti slippery on
eyes
[Music]
Okay the last ones I'm still not sure
how how I'm going to go about
those I'm going to
uh move
[Music]
on
[\h__\h] I'm wasting time because I didn't
get in the right
position it's over it's
over I already
like messed up in the
beginning [\h__\h] I right you're not
allowed accessories anyways uh well then
well
[Music]
then I don't think jumping cancels the
slipperiness does
[Music]
it [\h__\h] [\h__\h] come on I don't want to
waste too much
time supposed to finish this game today
[Music]
wait you're not melting him [\h__\h] get
closer get
closer should I
go let's
go okay okay okay okay
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait okay okay okay okay okay good
position okay okay okay okay
next next next
next okay okay wait I was just going to
drop that one
[Music]
right okay okay okay
okay uh should I use that right away
somehow for the next one the next one I
was still able to just melt normally I
don't know what I'm going to do at this
table yet um but I think after after the
next one maybe I mean yeah I can jump on
the blocks but for this next one I don't
know how that really helps
me you can walk over and
behind let's see let's see let's
see I see I see I see I
[Music]
see there we go
oh [\h__\h] that's fine as long as he's yep
he melted okay and now ah
ah I was so panicky I didn't quite
realize
yet um but [\h__\h] he's going to see me ah
not that I meant the other one's going
to see me but okay okay
um oh wait ah there's already a table
there but wait there's the other guy is
going to see me when I go around that
corner so I think how do I do this
what how do I do that without letting
the left one see
me I think I'm not going to make it in
time anymore anyway grab and
drop which one the top
[Music]
one that's difficult man
he I forgot well if that if I spawn it
right in front of their eyes the
fire are they going to destroy
it yeah
okay everything El I'm finding
yeah but like even if I jump like if I
want to you guys are saying bind onto
the top one and then drop him but like
i' have to get up on the table up on the
box Target him and then try on all that
slipperiness try to maneuver him into a
gap without falling
myself jump into the void with him H H
um all right
[Music]
I hate this game sometimes because
that's just not obviously not what I
want
to and that's when that really [\h__\h] you
up when you can't choose and there's the
game is not intelligently coded enough
the code is not intelligent enough to
understand that I'm obviously trying to
get the enemy first of first and
foremost not some random ice blocks on
the ground still doable there's 1
seconds left and he's about to drop
down and yeah
[Music]
well I don't know man I I I I
can't that
sucks y
oh yeah that one might be better without
locking on and just sending it
straight towards
[Music]
him if I stand straight in his Direction
then it shouldn't be an
issue I need to finish the next dungeon
to get the outfit
what I need to finish a lot of things
today this might be a little bit longer
than I thought it would be we'll see
we'll see I don't want to speed for the
game but I really don't quite 100% know
how much really it waits
me how many hours of game play really
await me
[Music]
um [\h__\h] I [\h__\h]
up he saw me maybe I should get uh maybe
I should push away the other block
that's right next to it not that one cuz
the chances of him seeing me are too
high
[Music]
all the others were so easy they made me
think I can do this and then this one's
really stopping me in my tracks
[Music]
man yeah this is by far the hardest
right this is
[Music]
crazy did I wait did I learn it yet
oh [\h__\h] come on that already ruined my
run
okay not going so smoothly right now
don't fall down okay
okay learn and then
[Music]
[Applause]
place I hate my life
[Music]
quick quick quick quick
quick
bro not enough time not enough
time not enough
time uh uh uh
uh
what why is that block there I guess it
will be gone when I melt stuff around it
because I got to take care of the lower
one
first I could the last two run away drop
them that was right what block his
vision yeah but then when I do want to
grab him the ice block will be in the
way so you can go go on his
[Music]
side okay so you're saying is he last
once I block his vision I go to the side
so that
I kill the one on the left first and
then I can go behind I guess I guess
that could
work if that's the
order jump first
what why
yeah oh
man if only there was a restart button
for this mode I agree cuz this really
sucks having to go back to the menu each
time
[Music]
okay kind of Speedy now very good good
speed
[Music]
faster okay okay okay
okay I think I saved the good amount of
time but now I'll [\h__\h] up again
[Music]
no
yes and now and now not uh jump up
push it it feels so weird when you are
running on the ice and just you're
trying to uh maneuver against
slipperiness and then suddenly you're on
a normal block but you're still trying
to maneuver against it and you're like
oh it's like when you're on a IRL when
you're on a on a like in the airport or
so you know when there's the escalators
that are not stairs they just go
straight and then I walk on them and I
walk walk walk and then I go on onto the
normal floor and I'm still like I feel
like I'm zooming right feels the same
way oh [\h__\h] um what's next wait wait
wait what's next uh the one down there
is taken care of now you guys are saying
I'm blocking his vision so I should be
able to walk around really wait
uh how am I block what I don't
understand
[Music]
I need a [\h__\h] moment I need a [\h__\h]
moment okay the closest one to me is
melting
okay how will I ah I could ah [\h__\h] I
should have learned the wooden box maybe
I could make myself a path to somewhat
smoothly stay on the same level and walk
over and then place the torch right next
to him while being blocked by the ice
block that's right in front of his face
so he won't see me
ah but what the torch I guess maybe it
melts everything
simultaneously but
then how am I going to take care of the
last
[Music]
one just fall you think that will work
smoothly I'll probably [\h__\h] everything
up again but definitely I know how to
take care of the next one but the last
one if those blocks
melt the one that he's standing on as
well that will get rid of my path to
walk around so that I can stealth the
last one as well you know what I
mean 45 seconds don't lock on for the
last one
no I mean I don't
know oh
[\h__\h] okay I'll wait for the current
one in the meantime I'll try to can I
learn the wooden blocks while I'm
standing on top of of them I hope so
then I make myself a path I walk over I
place a torch that melts
everything
around instead of waiting for that to
happen maybe I should just jump down try
to grab the last one and because that
might cost a lot of time with me
slippering around and failing at
grabbing him and falling down with
him h
after the first one grab the four one
and drop it then melt the top one that
order I could do it kind of s
wait I could kind of do it
simultaneously if I first make myself a
path jumping the far
one yeah yeah yeah I mean yeah
but can I drop him in like just by
running
downwards you
think wait oh God I don't want to [\h__\h]
this one up man I'm so sick of it
already if you melt the top
one you can go above and get on the
side of the that's what I was thinking
that's why I said I should do that one
first but at the same time if I melt the
top one it will melt the block that he's
standing on therefore getting rid of my
path to stealth around him unless
actually no no they seem to have quite a
tunnel
[Music]
vision 45 seconds in fear is enough but
uh okay can I a [\h__\h] I couldn't learn it
from the top [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] sh sh
Wait
what um
no that's okay I don't need the block I
can get back up by placing a wooden
[Music]
table and now and now and now and now
it doesn't even go straight
[Music]
man I was trying to lock because even
when I was looking straight at him my
lemon was so unprecise or like too
precise I [\h__\h]
guess so I was trying to go back to the
Locking but of course it locks on to
every I I know it does but I have to try
because even I was looking straight at
him it's hard to like look even more
straighter at
him oh I hated this I hated
[Music]
this
that's
painful so painful could it to a really
slow energy
loss so I'm guessing I can have both
activated
[Music]
now look at the last one
being easy again and they're fireing
nice attacks as you fight for all the
enemies I mean they look pretty strong
but why did somebody say I need to do
the last dungeon to do the last one or
is ah is the last one not showing yet on
the list and so this isn't the last one
I guess probably ah probably there's
going to be another boss boss Rush with
the remain bosses cuz we only had three
of them ah yeah yeah yeah that's what
it's going to be okay so I have
everything I'm
guessing I want to wind up my thing but
I feel like I won't have safety and time
cuz they already see
me and this one takes a lot of points
but he could be a distraction or he's
got the icy boys
too ah D I don't know what to do
I should have put on the items I don't
know what the best
um the best
choices fire yeah fire Wiz yeah could be
pretty good I'll have to like run around
dodging what's happening what's
happening what did he just do
[Music]
[\h__\h] yo yo you did that I wasn't even
paying attention where's the last
oh that's good cuz he was focusing on me
so he was turning his back to my Wiz
robe and I was just taking care of the
other enemies first trying to keep a
safe distance all right see how suddenly
that was easier compared to the mission
we had before that was the only
difficult
Mission
unbelievable yo good choice with the whz
robe yeah he's got pretty strong attacks
he he needs some time to charge it up
but that's okay with such a slow
Enemy No okay wait he didn't give me the
outfit yet huh he wants me to do the
last dungeon so let's do to the next
dungeon
um I kind of wanted to do CL this side
quest though I wonder if it's fast I
don't want to leave him hanging he needs
his
brother I can't leave him hanging it's
okay if today goes long I'll survive we
might just have to give up on Super
Chat I might let's see maybe I'll do a
super chat reading stream next
week
um it's kind of like the flame coal Rock
oh really just like keep it icy over
what but first I have to go into the
rift or no where's his house again
um what the hell where did I go where is
this
house oh down here
right yeah it doesn't even look so icy
that's why I'm like what this can't be
it it's all
[Music]
green it should be
snowy can't be next week why not yeah
um next week is Halloween ah [\h__\h]
I uh
whatever it's already fine over over
here
[Music]
con let me help you do you have a quest
yeah you
do you came to play
with have a little time to sh remember
something after we talked about Big
Brother the other day oh tell
us a long time ago big brother did Magic
change the weather for a day the magic
made so so he could fly off safely in
his hot everything wow okay that got
think would have an easier time coming
home if he Mountain was sunny again come
to PL to do the same
[Music]
magic oh my
God I bet that would make your brother
happy how does it work oh you need to
bring a snowball ah the C is like the
sun eh to specific spot on hiper
Mountain you have to carry the snowball
carefully so are you going to give it to
me that's so difficult con breaks it
every single time so could you show con
how to do the snowball magic might be
able to do it after seeing you do it
right thanks for coming with cond we're
finally at a special spot theic
snowballs cond told you about a rolling
around in this area ad those ah I knew
that platform was kind of
sus that's where I have to drop it off I
I knew that platform had something going
on you'll do this magic ride if you
place the snowball on top of the
pedestal mess up times but maybe you'll
figure it out Zelda please don't go how
to do it uh I'll try my best uh wait ah
so it doesn't matter where I start right
because there's so many dropping
down where are they
there okay one of
these I
mean
uh uh uh what if I wait where is the
platform this one Al I just should I
should just take the closest one I can
get okay I just take what I can just
take this
one oh
wait a sparkling one oh
[Music]
uh-oh is he going to spawn it for me
because I don't see any sparkling ones
[Music]
here wait where is he
again go
that one oh God does it
not wait wait wait wait
wait
wait I can't take
it oh there we
go e how am I going to bring it
there I'm obviously not that
[Music]
fast maybe not this path just because
like the thing is just because it's the
shortest doesn't mean it's the best I
have to go down
huh don't break oh God don't break oh
okay I it doesn't break just by touching
a wall that's
good
um
no no i f as long as it's like on the
side I'll it will be fine but I'm not
fine
can I jump up there oh yeah probably at
least up here let's let's test the
path I can jump up here to like wait a
moment but
then but then should I jump down here
too with the ball like go completely
even further
[Music]
back or try to jump from there to the
left is that even possible
test yes it is then go here then go here
that's safe as long as I have the ball
on my right side but I can't put it down
I guess I can put it down but I have to
be really fast to pick it up again wait
and then I'm here
[Music]
hey but then I'm just uh oh walking in a
circle you think I can make it up the
direct
path how ow
ow the short path
I
maybe I have an
idea
but what if I
place something
here that will always destroy the balls
is that
possible no but if I'm too far away will
it still stay
[Music]
there have a snowball on your left side
always on the the left side does this do
something not in this
case what if I place like this plant
here will it Bonk the balls
no all right you guys are seemingly
thinking it works without any extra prep
work even though the balls are falling
fall down so fast but okay on my left
side you
say uh no now it's behind me
again
ow how do I get it on my left
side oh there we go it's kind of on my
left side
[Music]
man Place block all right while you're
still connected to something you can
still
um summon things so I could summon like
anything like even one of these statues
right to break them
yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay well then
I knew I had to summon
something all right let's go
[Music]
buddy it's kind of so close to me I feel
uncomfortable
[Music]
um
ah ah
ah
ah so many
cats my ball is on top wait how do I get
it
again my ball okay
um
uh okay we're fine just got to wait that
one out and run run run run run run run
run
run and here it is my offering but will
it explode when I drop it no we're
good oh it doesn't even roll away I
thought it would roll away the moment
you drop it ah Hallelujah the cat saved
me
yippee heart
container no I think we got an extra
heart just
now could have forgot about the magic
for while but now we'll do it for Big
Brother every day make sure you two
three you can bet that cont will keep
doing his very best okay will we get to
see your brother
sometime does he have another
[Music]
Quest if I go to his house
again which was down
here that's all for now
oh
okay the brother was The Bu no did you
not listen last time revealed it wasn't
the brother it was just we thought so
but it's not true that is
slander uh oh yeah right we have what he
wants do we have the enemy as well he
wants the katana and an enemy
right what did he
want I was going to tell her don't don't
even say something like that that's a
spoiler I I was believing that wasn't
his brother nah it's not his
brother uh chop him
into a creature of a sword who fights in
groups and a super sharp weapon okay but
is it a specific
[Music]
moblin um because I got a couple of
moblins like maybe I only have one sword
moblin do I
the really strong
one
a that is the one he wants it's kind of
hard to get that one cuz he's hidden
away in a
[Music]
cave hey what I got I got the
sword ah are you ready to make it okay
you were just taking a look at my Katana
all right here you go I'm giving their
heirloom that I worked so hard for that
they only gave to me because they
respect me for the skills that I have to
a complete stranger that they don't even
know isn't that so
disrespectful and they're like using it
to craft something therefore kind of
destroying the real purpose and and and
beauty of it misusing
it that is so
disrespectful is it going to be a mob
carrying the katana that moin was
already so strong you're going to make
it even stronger you crazy crazy man is
he going to be dual
wielding Robo blin okay love the name
wow he's not even really dual wielding
he's just holding the chath is that what
you call it in his other hand he a
samurai moblin
nice can I already make the other f
things that you want to make performance
artist a cute fancy automatone that
plays a chipper Little tune and puts on
a show that's literally
CeCe that won't cut you you
a a jiggly monster with cute little eyes
I'm sure I have that and oh I have that
too oh wonderful we got that very early
on that item it yeah right
[Music]
jiggly
jiggly uh wait which one though I I feel
like I have a lot of jiggly
things what was the rest of what he was
asking for the The Prompt was jiggly
what what about
this
[Music]
no he probably just
means like a jelly right any of
them that's it okay wonderful
and then I talk to you to show you
my my climper
to yeah the music
[Music]
box
paron thank
you my favorite night outfit is also
jiggly is that what you're
saying it is indeed giz
more
cute it's pink and
glowing this cute one sings and dances
scattering groups of monsters with its
playful Antics uhhuh we'll have to test
that one
out can we make the last
one endless
stomach an Al who can gobble up any
monster any
time a creature that swallows things
with its M massive Jaws shark you
talking about a
shark or something else now maybe it's
also again a special enemy because I
needed a special enemy for the other one
too no not always I don't always need a
special
enemy that one was just a jiggly
little
goober special part can strengthen its
ability to ah okay okay I have that item
too nice
wonderful so I'll try with a
shark
G he like it it doesn't fit
oh what that's a big jaw like what do
you mean what else do I have that could
fit this
concept ah tick
plant right is this one okay you need a
higher level
one is it the problem that it's not high
level
enough a bigger
tickle do I have this
thing bio
bio yeah yeah yeah thank
God okay oh it's whole is going to look
like that item that we're giving him
[Music]
right let's
see we made them all and we did the
extra side quest for it too that took a
while but here we
go I can say I almost 100% did this game
with how much stuff I made wow wow is it
that looks like it's able to walk
around don't tell me it's able to walk
around cuz normally they never walk
around that would be a nice upgrade to
it actually it Chomps pretty mly
so he doesn't say anything about it
walking around let's
[Music]
see let's test it out sorry to
disappoint
y uh oops okay let's try hi
just a quick
mind okay it is not
walking I guess it's it just Chomps
Chomps even better but you didn't even
kill
it
HH what are you
doing how can you not win against these
little
jellies let's see this one in action ah
wait got to wind
it couldn't it for very long do
something wow he charges it for a long
time but he's got like a
360 uh range that's pretty good he's
cool and then now I have no enemies to
test it on but maybe down there
[Music]
oh it's so colorful it's RGB what are
you doing
though I'm I'm okay you're making music
now how is
it okay the notes have to hit the
enemies oh it's kind of broken
already you tell me I have to repair
this one
already it didn't do
anything it's not even a able to kill
those weak ass armadillos it [\h__\h]
[Music]
broke I'll repair it but I don't know if
I'll use that
again so
fragile what the hell it's cute at least
yeah it makes music and I have so many
of these monster stones that apparently
don't have any other use so might as
well repair
it oh [\h__\h]
oh I thought
BR I wanted to use the mon damn
it I literally used it once and it
didn't even efficiently do its job I
want a refund
actually oh well wait there's
more I thought we were
done get rich Quake concept the
sparkling gold automaton who really ra
in the
dough so you read my notes we finally
came up with an idea about how to turn
that meaning of a crow into anaton bring
me that I figured that crit would look
Dandy glittery gold so I need a real
special fleshy something do I have that
I think I made the guda who's got a real
shiny
thing is this is it the fan cuz we
haven't used the fan yet was it gold
though I don't remember it being gold oh
I guess it was was gold okay I think we
can make this one too so you just want a
normal Crow Crow still after all these
years I still don't really know how to
say that
word
um where is a dumbass
Crow guessing it's
Crow did I even ever learn it on let's
go low
cost there it is a keiss
wait were you not talking about that
Crow c is an old
[\h__\h] oh oh Crow
Crow that's a
bet
oh
um misunderstanding corner I mean they
look kind of sick
a wait I was so sure about this
one sorry my brain was
[Music]
offline it's a black flying
thing pretty close I would
say understandable that I would mistake
it
So when you say get rich quick are you
going to make something that gives me
money it
[Music]
better goie booty yeah I guess a
cockroach should fit the
same
description gold wow oh because the
crows when they attack things they
also uh scatter the money of everywhere
maybe this just scatters even more it
will attack enemies and sent the rupes
flying even better if you wind up the
Clockwork key you can hold the flashy
thing up and glide to fly well
okay so it's just a maybe a
more
um less destructible version of it I
hope it also gives more
money now you can steal money in the ex
wait are you saying my
if I summoned crows they weren't able to
do the same thing against my enemies so
[Music]
far
so
n well but I'm not really in need of
like is that worth wasting my time
[Music]
on go
no go for the there you
go okay I mean you did it one hit and
every once in a while I guess I could
bring you
out come here
[Music]
buddy oh if I do it in the monster can
am oh [\h__\h] no don't hurt my no look hurt
me hurt me
[Music]
instead why that took you a while
survival Instinct
to okay can you come down again so I can
wind you a bit more
[Music]
yeah let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go he's pretty strong
too so oh all right come on come on come
on buddy come on come on uhoh oh I can't
reach you thank god oh nice one
ow ow money over Health every
day don't get
destroyed hey what are you doing over
there oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah make the money rain oh no it
broke wait no it's not broken yet [\h__\h]
don't hurt it fly my little guy fly my
little guy to safety he I'll distract
him go go go for it hey what did you do
why did you and propably you going to
die okay they are not
very they are not as strong as I thought
they would be how about quick quick
quick go a well the problem is
really winding them up in a stressful
situation and I'm about to
[Music]
die I'm not I don't want to waste my
items but
okay all right here we go
wa wait did you see the wind gust of his
sword is that his
range is that his
range oh my
[Music]
God all right maybe that is a good use
of the heirloom no I still think it's
kind of [\h__\h] up but anyway
[Music]
um maybe just one of them is enough
right okay now
[Music]
uh wait am I able to no after the next
dungeon I can continue con the story
right not
now what about the little Rift over here
can I close it
now don't know how to get there really
except
walk fix the bird
no try going to it are you saying
[Music]
yeah some of them are a little bit
disappointing also because it just takes
so
long oh thank you what what wait
what ah I right there was this movie
that gives you winding
speed I was just about to say like the
one criticism I have is that it takes so
long to wind
them so like in a stressful situation
it's not really worth it if you can
prepare properly then yeah but even then
not all of them are that good like the
the RGB one is just
cute it looks like it's spotting a lot
of those musical notes but they weren't
going
anywhere when I was using
them okay in theory this exists but I
don't know if I want to really make too
much use of it
but it's good that we did
it I'm glad that we did
it was able to extend my game play a
little bit more make it
longer the Octo is the strongest Bunch
the
Octo yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I think that one I will still continue
to
use uh all right
um how from
here shall we walk
[Music]
from
uh spawn
[Music]
points maybe from
here small Rift what about the rift on
the mountain um
should I do it
now now I already teleported somewhere
else if we have some downtime let's do
it for now let's prioritize
the
dungeon how about that or the next
region first and
foremost
type ohy
we need to get
going let's
Dash to am I going the right way
uh no I'm not going the right way how do
I get up
[Music]
there I'll call you again horse
ow leave me
alone once I get to the top
no
what
[Music]
SAR
uh what's the official path
[Music]
uh is that the pap they're thinking you
would
take this okay I mean this seems to be
the first warping point of the region so
[Music]
no
quite huh that is the official pu
really well met Princess telda by order
of the king I'm on a mission to
investigate areas of roofs I was just a
little deeper in Fen white land's
forbidden place what forbidden place we
had electric monsters strange creatures
who called me a
bumpkin if you intend to visit the area
I suggest keeping your wits about ah
strange cre creatures calling you that
must be the people who live
here wait are they those are they who I
think they
are also is this a new enemy
[Music]
or
h no it was
not
what w
ah [\h__\h] octax or
what
who
pretty looks like it should be very
humid and very hot thank God I don't
feel it when I'm
here yeah that's what I
mean one of the Rifts looks pretty big
should we go and take a look at
it of course that's what I'm here
for what can lift these hey yo this
one's
big ah they killed frogs they had them
in wait the [\h__\h] they had the same
[\h__\h] frogs in the Mario RPG game that
I
played are you an
enemy no frog is never enemy he's just
minding his own business
singing but I need to learn you
green blue frog sorry drippy tune
Echo how will they become useful to us I
wonder well if if they really don't
attack and all they do is make
music what about these
things what speeda crab what are
[Music]
you as you can tell I have no patience
anymore to think about what enemy I
could best use it
for uh
countering
yep which I think at this point in the
game is understandable because there's
just an over stimulation an overload of
possible echo which makes it even
harder even though you should have
better ones that should make things
easier for you it's just harder
now why did the musal see a
I would roll with you with the laser you
really like the laser eyes
huh just the strongest ones the
strongest ones aren't always the best
choice but yeah
hello a cute you don't look like a dick
scroll but that get up you clearly an
out of towerer I'll answer your
questions if you have any de
scrubs we fo who keep up the latest
trends and we're cute too yeah you are
you know it basically we're the
best oh the scrub next to me went
underground guess You' have to yank them
out if you wanted to talk to them oh I
can do that where am I you're in foreign
Wetlands not an easy part of the world
to live in going to be tough on this
place or this place will gobble you up
any more questions all right have
fun won't he be mad that I do that to
him you plucked me what the [\h__\h] I guess
there's something you want to talk
about frog Monsters Electric monsters
Reon friends what do you want to know
about friend all these dark fors showed
up all of wetland so weird and purple
but you can get all this cotton candy
and it's so good what is he talking
about out cotton candy if you want to
try some drop by The Sweet Spot in nor
and fair and
wetlands all right why the [\h__\h] did you
disturb me just for that couldn't you
have asked the other one the same
question yep I don't know why the game
made me do that I didn't want to oh this
is cute wait where should I go
first this just good to go here
oh hello oh this this is this their City
their
Village I don't know who to talk to
First
oh that looks more like marshmallows
than cotton
[Music]
candy Le
are they is this bad for them by any
chance or it's made of I thought so I
had a
feeling spider webs I know I was worried
when the big patch of dark forn showed
up at the sweet spot but then the great
spider came out and started spinning its
webs oh is it an evil
spider you can say that again you can
say that
again they were eating spider webs
yeah what don't judge them I mean it's
not like they're humans so they would
eat normal things of course these
weirdos are going to eat weird
things I'm surprised they can talk their
mouths are so
sticky so please don't try that stuff no
not really into spiderwebs although I
wonder do spider webs like if if
somebody were
to make him into this kind of shape and
eat lots and lots and lots of it
does that have any kind of nutrition or
so in
[Music]
it don't judge them they're
weird judge them accordingly to their
level of weirdness like judge their act
you can judge their weirdness but don't
judge their actions because their
actions are just balanced out by their
own
weirdness protein yeah I was wondering
if there's something like that to it
say is it true you have a membership
card for a Sweet Spot what no well who
told you that that's so ridiculous I'm
actually laughing it's a little
suspicious how much you try to deny
it sus what is there to hide in the
first what
the sorry I got stuck I guess and the
game did not like
that I don't want anyone coming this way
while I'm paring
oh you got me I'm not working but don't
I deserve a
break can I move you too or only the
ones that are okay only the ones that
are in the ground
maybe I was the first SCB to eat cotton
candy really I kicked off the trend all
your trends that are just like
me I want cotton candy when it's so much
trouble to get a hold of I wish some of
the dark forns were growing closer
by these buddies are so cute I like this
place I like this
civilization oh you guys you guys you
Deco scrubs you should combine the
cotton candy with the butter it's going
to be so good actually is this a new
fruit
yep that looks like it could be a
smoothie
[Music]
fruit it's got to be
connected those PES are confused look I
know what you are you're a
[Music]
pumpkin
Bumpkin don't they call like people from
the
countryside pumpkins too like IRL
or yeah oh oh is a legit Bumpkin not
pumpkin Country
Bumpkin wait does that mean
something is it in any way connective
with pumpkin because pumpkins grow on
the countryside or
so or just bump can mean something
else no
oh an awkward person from the country
they're calling me
[Music]
awkward I'm the
princess oh wow
rude they're kind of kind of racist this
these little guys but
okay Ever Seen Rain before
Bumpkin here in Fire and wetlands I've
seen something way crazier than rain
that you probably haven't seen before
ever
snow here in Fire and wetlands we get
sunny days and we going rain what you
might call a mix but I noticed something
before the rain starts a monster makes a
sound I think that monster must be
causing the rain but what is
it I see the look in your eyes you want
to get to the bottom of it too okay f
I'll let you help I was having trouble
on my own anyway go find the monster
Bring It My Way Your Best Bets probably
to looking places where it's raining
I'll be waiting
here is that a side quest
H H is this a hot spring no oh it has
the same color but it's not hot
enough okay enough talking to the
NPCs we don't have endless amount of
time so he is this a smoothie
shop or just a general oh it's a big T
scrub there how I like to see you guys
all grown up huh are you a a grownup
then compared to the
others I'm a business SCB welcome to the
original smooy shop oh the
original this is a place where you can
craft your own freezing taste but
pleasing smoothies the process is simple
you pick two ingredients and blend them
together so come on now is this one
special in any
way I don't have any anything new I
don't know what I would make right
now honestly no
idea just a business scrub is he not a
DI scrub is he not related to them or or
just by doing business you grow up I
don't
understand H have you had s me from the
shop what do you mean talking about the
smie so fresh perfect for H meile
everyone else is on a cotton candy
bandwagon I don't care how un cool it
makes me I'll never stop buying
smoovies huh but it's not like they
behave weirdly by eating the spider webs
so it's not a big issue like compared to
him I don't see much difference in their
behavior but yeah I love smoothies too
and chunky wony I wish there were more
smoothies and more junky monkeys but
then I would be so
overwhelmed oh dear this is dangerous
right out
here uh wait should I go
up from
here for
story uh story time
yeah yes
now that has swallowed up a
lot there's a rift inside the
structure you wait here I'll go in and
see if I can make an
entrance make that entrance make it like
a
diva yeah I'll be able to do it
but you can't get in there if the door's
shut as we already
know hey what are you standing here for
we're not letting you into The Sweet
Spot
oo they're gatekeeping The Sweet
Spot that's so mean I want check it out
I want to try the cotton candy too
hey look at the blank expression the
tell tail sign of a bumpkin first time
in the city huh all right let's tell you
what one sweet is a place that serves
all you can eat Treats but it's members
only members only well okay I can get
into your sweet spot you won't get into
my members only stream tomorrow
[Music]
either yeah you have to subscribe to the
membership on YouTube if you want to
enter The Sweet Spot too but yeah we
don't
we do accept more but it's like really
[\h__\h] expensive it's like 500 bucks to
enter our membership because it's really
special you got that no card no going in
so get
scramming yeah how we going to get one
do we have to steal
one is it an actual
card guess we'll have to find one of
those membership
cards he yo voice
crap oh oh I see see I wonder if there's
an item to handle the stickiness of that
as
well interesting another little gimmick
frog more for ow more
frog frogy are you sitting on a strength
Crystal by any chance I guess not where
you going
wait where would I get the membership
though is that an enemy is That Bouncy
no it doesn't do
anything
sa oh frogy makes it
rain are you making it rain you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] he is making it rain what was the
request again I don't
remember bring them okay so I just
spawned in front of him I didn't even
notice because it's a pretty big range I
would expect the enemy that spawns rain
to just have a really small area of rain
above him maybe even a rain cloud that
would be like more noticeable for me
that was just such a smooth transition I
didn't even
realize and I also completely forgot to
about the side quest
already
yeah and thank you for the memberships
thank
you all right here we
go he's a
frog See's raining ah he's so cute
though you have to forgive him for
making it
rain look it's soned raining oh I wonder
if we're going to get into a situation
where there's a lot of fire and it would
be nice to have the Frog kind of a
cheese to have the Frog to make all the
fire go
out it's a huge discover May the biggest
ever I'm the genius who figured it out
oh genius that's got a nice ring to it I
could have done it without you but
here's a reward
anyway the Apple
really oh wait is electricity going to
come and play again in this dungeon or
no
anyway I'm wondering where how do I
proceed with the get to you need a
membersip part
great and
how how do I get the membership card do
I talk to these guys
again I'm pretty sure it's scrapped down
at heart L is a m and what about you
guys are you not members all like
Southwest of here it's where scraps go
if they you know sweet on each other
oh oh what is that where you guys go to
make more scrub
babies we have a specific area for
that south over here huh all right we're
going on a little
journey here we go thanks for the really
good
hint appreciate it
other sweet
[Music]
spot see that's what I expected with
that other flower I
said but
no what is this [\h__\h] Coppa door here
I'll put you into the water aren't you
happy about that I helped him oh and
[\h__\h] electric jelly no
[Music]
anything here I know you're an
enemy
[Music]
oh let's just make quick business with
these
things you think you can hurt me
you are very
wrong this one so if I spawn it it will
float on the water but also on the
ground oh wait I want the
money so behind on vods really on the
Zelda vs only
gambat
ketchup
[Music]
mayonnaise
mustard what
food has taken over my
[Music]
mind another one okay what what's a good
way to fight them though probably
fire but they're so
slow where did you go [\h__\h] Wiz robe I
am not locking on to the this one for no
[Music]
reason Mama Mia why
you there we go first
hit see like why am I even bothering
with using my echo at this
point oh my God
[Music]
piranas a yeah these are
piranas oh I saw in one of the survival
videos that I've been watching the guy
caught himself a piranna and ate
it pretty amazing
huh I never thought about eating a
pirania but I guess you can pretty much
eat most fish that
exist everything's
edible still on your survival kick not
really not So Much
Anymore oh that's a new bird I
think I don't really want it though do
you think I need to get it I don't
really want it oh my God there's so many
pink
enemies scream so much focus on the
other ones
first yeah big
hits yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and
then I don't know how we're going to
handle
that ey
laser
do it's just screaming does it even
attack I laser what are you doing where
did you
go what
I was giving you the benefit of the
doubt and I was going to say oh does the
screaming scare off Echoes by any chance
but
no ah it lurs Ah that's why they were
all getting
together it lurs other enemies in wa
what are
those um I would counter them with this
one but he doesn't move so that's kind
of annoying
[Music]
so here we
go oh damn they take a lot of hits all
right here we
go anyone else who wants some
[Music]
trouble I me oopsie sorry maybe I
shouldn't toss you like that if I don't
want to
break do they have turtle shells I don't
know what it is but they look kind of
op who wants to fight me oh [\h__\h] I'm
back in the city sorry sorry sorry sorry
wait wait wait oh new
spider wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
y okay at least it hit me instead of
my ah no no no my
octorok lifting him is not always the
best idea I thought he could like aim
for it when I lock on but
no he always overshoots it
what good job no
no
ah let's go let's go let's go
yeah I'll just distract him damn he's so
good so good this is the best thing
Humanity has ever created
very
[Music]
C is this helping
yeah no not the
stone
[\h__\h] it's a living
party he's the life of the party that's
for sure and he's also the death of the
party die
I hear
frog but it's okay I don't want frog to
die don't worry
frogs oh
[Music]
well I want to get up
there there we go
Stam I feel like I kind of uh
accidentally left the main path that I
should be taking but oh well
new stamp card do I get 50 coins or was
that just Mario Party eh
yeah
okay I found out by the way that you do
get an outfit for finishing all of the
stamps but it's kind of cute but it
doesn't do anything I
think
yay mhm
it's cute it's basically what he's
wearing with that stupid hat I love it
though it's
cute go stamp rally
Yoo I don't know if I'm going to finish
all the stamps I feel like I've missed
some early
ones are y wait do I get rid of the
spider webs of
fire can I tell
my what what are you doing why are you
falling you have wings you know what are
you doing is it ah is it the it's the a
that's why they put the Frog
here the rain automatically
deactivates my fire
Keys yeah it does how do I tell you to
put some fire on that spy web though can
you please just randomly fly into that
no
um will this work yeah it
works genius wa
[Music]
yippe yeah it makes a lot of sense but
I've never experienced that I think oh
crystals that's quite a good amount I
feel
like I need 20 I think for another
[Music]
upgrade okay going to try to go down
again or do I have to kind of go from a
different from
here so let me walk through the city
again Y and go left and then
down why
is on the mini map
why is that guy's
area like is it is it my P Pim I I never
noticed does my pal palim show me on the
mini
map oh wait that there's no path here is
it unless I
cheat does it show me on the mini map
precisely where I have to look and I've
never noticed so far or is it just that
one NPC in particular well we'll figure
it out eventually
[Music]
sorry I really don't like hurting these
frogs it pains
[Music]
me I know you don't believe it maybe
but I wonder if my fly leaf can also cut
the
spiderwebs Al this this spiderweb has
nothing behind it but this one has got a
treasure chest
[Music]
there was a heart on the map could be
the heart like yeah yeah I know that's
where I'm trying to go
to but I got
distracted apples interesting in the
beginning of the game they gave us a lot
of apples and now it kind of looped back
to electricity being the element of the
area why are you up there
buddy I don't know how I like that it
seems like they ran out of elements but
I really don't like the electricity
element
man are these new they don't look
new somehow I'm really good at dodging
them
loading up my hearts
[Music]
here oh what is
this let's check it
all how many years have you been fluenc
in English oh so
many too many learned it in in school
and I became fluent in school I would
say was definitely fluent during school
time
should I put my things on or is it not
worth what the [\h__\h] is that oh I knew it
have we not seen this type of enemy
before yet
surprisingly you speak
English man this whole time we've been
communicating in
English we haven't noticed because it
just
automatic happy birthday
GD you're lucky I saw that and you don't
have to wait a month for me to see
it happy birthday
M today so in Australian time so 27
well I hope it's going to be the best
day ever for
you ah he his
[Music]
backside one
hit what percentage of austrians are
florid English every like pretty much
everybody okay not everybody but
percentage is really high because
our and you ation is pretty good and we
learn it
early so you
know let me
Pro wait how do I get
through H I have an
idea oh I can't spawn it through him
though wait I'm going to die here how do
I how do I kill him a wait
wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait I oh he's so
heavy oh but I can turn him
around I guess this is how the game
tells you to do
that I was thinking I can lift him and
then get him over this little step but
yeah cool
local entertainment lacking we all yeah
that's I wouldn't say we all end up
watching American TV shows cuz um our
entertainment at least like gives us a
lot of translated dub shows I always
watched Charmed and scrubs and all those
shows dubbed
before I was like deep into the this
like kind of
culture of like whatever into internet
internet culture well even even
afterwards even after I got into
it but yeah and that was at a time where
I think my English was already pretty
good maybe during my first time when I
was watching charm no but when I was
watching scrubs I think my English was
was already pretty
good but my
first experience with scrubs was in
English like seeing it in English was my
first how to say encounter that's the
word I'm looking
for yeah now I wouldn't watch it in
German wait what did I say my first
encounter was in English I watch no no I
mean I mean my first encounter with it
was in German so I watched it in German
but nowadays I would always watch it in
English that's what I'm trying to say
y um how do I fight these or do I even
do I even want
to how about this what you don't Flo I
saw you oh oh is it just because it was
shallow
bro do something
job
[Music]
oh trying to aim
up but yeah we have like so many shows
translated to German and nowadays I
would feel like cringe watching shows in
their not
intended original
language if the show is originally in
German then okay but generally shows
that are originally in German aren't
even good
anyway but yeah so I wouldn't even say
that it's because we're getting forced
to
watch American
stuff wait what
wait what wait
what ah I see I
see wait uh need to copy from
[Music]
here bombfish where are you
but yeah I did end up in like English
speaking uh
[Music]
or English speaking
communities through being addicted to
the Internet so that surely helped me
with my
fluency yeah so the good education
combined with
the uh internet growing up with the
internet definitely led the way how come
I haven't found my way to the chest is
it impossible through this entrance it
was teased to me I saw it
I don't want to leave this cave yet if
I'm missing the
chest no it wasn't a dead end
but a dick spot
maybe but I don't know if I'm wasting my
time leaving or if I'm wasting my time
swimming
around this is a huge ass [\h__\h] cave
oh yeah music
also English music that's for sure so
translated
shows the the the TV shows oh what the
[\h__\h] are not really the things that help
but uh music yeah music probably helped
although I'm not sure if I could say
that music helped me learn Japanese like
Japanese
music he looks again I've said this
before I think but this enemy looks like
oh my God ah a he keeps on okay keep on
focusing on me then there we go looks
like from from from
um uh what's it
called star fo Advengers yeah yeah I'm
thinking of Starbuck Adventures but I
guess some people also were
thinking of
[Music]
Metroid all right let's blow this up
pour more air is wait is that the only
reason why I'm blowing that
up is that if you're having trouble
during the fight with this guy no
there's one bubble there anyway huh what
what's that
for now tell me that there's a digging
spot there's a
flower wait I'm just on top of
this are these flowers
burnable what's what's with the flowers
are these
removable why don't I have the chest yet
why is it burning still
[Music]
to go up go up where
go up where there's no more up what are
you talking
about it was already
up I'm it wasn't the chest it was a
heart piece yeah well how the [\h__\h]
that's what I was trying to get that's
why I swam
back you mean use a plat boom in here
you didn't specify at all where to use
it cuz it was
outside like what do you
mean swim all the way again
so I did
miss how to get there
bro oh the shitty
[Music]
cave it goes
up it goes
up it goes up I it was so dark I thought
it was the
end oh yeah
[Music]
oh
okay guess I don't even have to fight
him but I shall
anyway cuz I'm a
hero no enemies shall be kept
alive not under my watch and I finally
got the heart piece yeah should I just
teleport out of here what do you
think my teleportation points are very
far
so feel like both directions are the
same distance so I'm going to go this
way can I not
is the game calling me fat oh my
[Music]
God okay we made it I should have swam
back but even then I wouldn't have
recognized how to get up
there okay going to drink some water
hey to the
yo oopsie hello little hermit crab
mushroom hermit
[Music]
crab I hope at least now I'm going the
right way oh yeah the there is where the
heart lake is and there's a rift on
it oh come here come here let me stomp
you nothing beats a ground pound
oh it was not under my ground pound
platform how
sad uhhuh
fire and I of the elements makes even
the low most low cost and weakest
enemies somewhat
strong especially if you consider how
many I can summon like fire is just op
and hey we got a war point at the Heart
Lake I love your music so much oh that's
weird thank you I'm glad to hear that h
I shall make
more are you drowning or you ah you're
panicking cuz your your mating
partner got caught in the rift and your
mating ritual got interrupted is that
what it
is pleas that be right here but I've
been waiting and you're not here did you
feeling strange H did you stop liking
me oh dear
[Music]
The Mating ritual was not interrupted it
hasn't even
begun seems like something is bothering
us from should we try asking about the
membership now is not the time to ask
about membership cards you think he will
give a
[\h__\h] he first wants to make babies I've
never heard sounds like that
before oh let me tell you if we stay
here for too long after the rift is men
that we'll hear all kinds of sounds that
we haven't heard
before deu
scrubs most delightful
[Laughter]
sounds
spicy can I watch though I want to see
how they do
it do these also shoot little
balls D this is kind of I would think
some shiy would talk about perhaps
but
um do they shoot those too like the
octoo cuz I mean the their mouth is very
much shaped like it
would do they I don't even want to say
what I'm what to ask I can you read my
mind d they shoot nuts okay so my
question
is do they
no I'm just going to go into the rift
and then maybe we'll get to
see seems like you understood what I was
trying to say
anyway was it the hole e e you H my
darling could be in there
you know what I don't even have to ask I
can leave feel it my leafies out of the
way no don't are you going to no no
no wait if you enter the rift like that
are you
safe cuz we're entering like that all
the time that's a different way of
entering I is he actually fine
yeah let's leave it to
Shi I can sense my
friend they're trapped they're trapped
in five areas to be exact if we rescue
them all we can fix this
Rift
five oh is this the one that just jumped
in or the one from way
before what of course now the V scrubs
stop only you and Link are lucky enough
to move in here oh yeah cuz I was going
to question the logic right
[Music]
now what wait
so we're immune
somehow to all of
this oh okay not going to question it
not going to question it I thought that
the only reason we're able to move in
here is because of the way way we are
entering wait then does he even have to
wait wait okay logical
hole
if if we're fine
anyway then couldn't we just jump into
the Rifts we don't need to jump through
a hole because everybody else who ends
up in these Rifts they're not all
entering through the hole either there
are no holes usually so they're just
like being rifted in and then they end
up like that but this guy also ended up
like that even though he went through
our
hole so you know what I'm saying it
doesn't really have anything to do with
the hole as they just told us so why do
we have to open holes in the first
place if the others can get in without
holes then we should also be able to get
in without holes and we should be fine
because lemonade John just said that me
and Link are
immune because it's not that we didn't
we can move around because of the hole
as she just said yeah you get it you get
it so the whole hole making thing is a
plot
hole Yeah link also got sucked in
without a proper entrance point and he's
able to move around so why do we always
have to find specific points to open a
hole makes no sense I think I don't
think they have an explanation for that
that's kind of a hole in their
logic to a a road to properly go in and
out no but like we go out by closing the
Rifts so I guess okay maybe at
least without a hole let's say we don't
find the lemons and we want to go out
though then we're [\h__\h] if we don't
have a hole
but if we were to go in without the hole
and then collect all lemons it would
close the rift and we would leave anyway
I
think so yeah just for easy entering and
exiting I guess but I don't really think
that dat thought of this part in their
logic yeah yeah yeah whatever I should
not waste my time too much on these
Logistics
right uh so I can walk over it slowly
this I don't get to learn how to create
one of these though
right good oh my one hit wow that's
better than
my explosion
machine uh I
see as always my plat boom will be the
savior of the
day down down down
yeah happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you
happy ow what the
hell let me
pass
where that
P oh wait it's just too high I'm
slipping off it's not my perception it's
just too high guys actually surprisingly
too high
[Music]
wizzy quick quick quick
no assert dominance my
friend don't let him [\h__\h] you up oh okay
preparing the stage for me I appreciate
it oh there's more to burn there I wish
the Wiz rub could just burn
it why is this too
high
okay I've Got The High Ground
nowella is falling immediately yeah I
will say I
suppose falling for a hole
uh we'll be making sure that I land on
the
ground I
guess but okay we ah
sh we'll we'll take the
explanation that's not enough huh
to not enough time to let it do its
thing uh how about
okay I have an
idea I walk on the cloud even though it
will disappear after a while but I walk
on the cloud while
holding oh [\h__\h] the
fire wait I forgot I guess I can't
jump I need a little bit more fing time
a little bit more fing
time I mean I could I could try and hope
that my
bet there we go we'll fly where I wanted
to fly without knowing that that's where
I wanted to
fly right I just Ultra handed the
uh
candle oh my God sometimes you just
Poore where's the next PA oh left side
okay it's been a while since I used one
of these but they're always amazing ooh
is it swimmy
time you want to react this one or no
okay
kind of already have enough of diving
through caves for today so I hope this
is not
too
difficult Sharky
time what are you what are you doing
okay the only one that's left is also in
here let me get the
bomb what let me out why is my [\h__\h]
shark not being
useful now you're coming
over so
stupid took you a while needed a special
invitation I see oh wait I didn't
realize oh oh I see I know what they
want me to do
why is that not stopping the
flow was
it is it
from why wouldn't that stop the
flow is the flow created in perhaps just
by
um is this like a physics thing
or is it not even necessary I I would
think it's necessary to stop the flow
because I'm guessing my fish will float
away yeah maybe timing maybe the flow is
Unstoppable and all we got to think of
his
timing well okay this one will not slow
down this one no
wait
activate alter
hand oh yeah that was lucky I think
pretty lucky on the timing
[Music]
forgetting about moving things with
alter hand two times in a
row today's not my day
maybe maybe it's just not my
[Music]
day that is their mating ritual by the
way
so many different kinds of mating
rituals isn't it
[Music]
beautiful almost level
10 and more might
crystals how many do we
have
15 five more
maybe then we can max out
the bombs as well I think cuz I think
the bombs are the last thing that I
have thank
you
o spicy time everybody look
away where am
I you finally made it
you the F started spreading and then I
don't know what happened after that
are you shy you being shy what's
wrong I was waiting and you didn't show
I thought you weren't sweet on me
anymore oh sugar cane of course I'm
still sweet on
you you mean
it should we get out of here before it
gets too spicy M you're my favorite
scrub in the whole wine wetlands
you're making me feel out tinly oh oh
oh okay is that as far as it will it
will go while I'm
here well it seems like things are
resolved between those two we should get
out of
here do you two have a membership card
for The Sweet Spot before we go we leave
me alone once you give it to us I
swear I have a a I have a membership
card but I can't give it to you I'm
taking this one on a date to The Sweet
Spot well can you take me on a date can
I F whe it I'm a pro at third
Wheeling there a scrap named Blu who's
got one they live in the corner of the
sou they're sending me
around but why can't you take me with
you they got dark forns right next to
their home so they don't have much need
for it maybe if you ask nicely bloso
will give you their membership card
nah no
way what the waste of my
time not even that educational you're
not even teaching me how you do it how
are you going to do
it share with me your
ways that unmendable that
rhs all right um so I guess over
here no
problem I shall make my way
there quest to go to another quest to
solve the first
yeah I mean you know it's the main quest
so it can't be that easy that's
understandable what the hell is
this I love the music bo b Bo
so
perfect oh you're going to summon
everybody
oh all right we got that big
boy I don't know
[Music]
here so dark in
here but I like it it's glowy mushroom
caves a biomi that is very familiar to
me from other games
H they're wait they're bringing back all
the early things like the electricity
and the light thing that was a pretty
early gimmick as
well he really ran out of ideas a little
bit you're not dead yet what the
hell there's a heart container over
there oopsie do I have a smoothie for
lighting myself on fire
as I like to do every once in a while no
I do not I never have what I need in the
region where I'm going
to but
[Music]
okay think waa think
sometimes a good old bed will
do isn't that that's isn't that stone
sauce no oh
okay
oh I'm
what what what Oh I thought it was my
tile I thought for the first time ever
they freaking nerfed the tile and won't
let it go over there cuz that's not the
path they want you to take but
no I'm guessing that's not high enough
but ah
what it was
enough
[Music]
amazing okay before I exit for the door
over there let me
see what's over here
o speed and a very dark cave I want to
know where the spiders are so better to
take care of everything
ASAP
ow did you do your
job okay
okay I don't even want
[Music]
to what are you getting stuck
on oh oh nothing really just
invisible
problems oh
wait can I
get over uh probably not uh can I spawn
it inside yes okay cuz normally you can
spawn things through walls but this one
has holes in it therefore it
works and we get our chest money money
yeah they don't have much of value to
offer to me
anymore but okay
[Music]
is this really the final it was a great
game yeah I I think it will
be this we're on the way to the last
dungeon unless there's a final dungeon
which they probably I'm guessing there
will be oh it's a green
Lizzy
huh I see electricity is his thing
huh oh that's cool
don't know how often I will use you
honestly but sure I'm looking for the
ice
wizzy I have I I thought I had one
did I miss out on learning it that's
crazy all right fire will do hopefully
feel like ice kind of matches better
but he looks so
powerful oh
[\h__\h] ah okay whatever whatever whatever
whatever
[Music]
whatever I hate that they become
Invincible after each tiny hit man
you're wasting so much of my
energy oh my
[Music]
God all right we learned this
one was there a water
wizzy probably not right just an ice
one cuz I'm wondering how many did I
miss if I only have the fire one should
I have more
[Music]
there ice okay I would hope so we got a
another
froggy there're so adorable I love them
so
much I love
[Music]
them
but uh wait does Adele sing she sets
fire to the
rain that makes no sense
why are you so
stupid
oops I was about to sing a song because
of the rain you know why why are y'all
so
stupid and then I was about to
realize I was about to say like I must
be
mem remembering the lyrics wrong because
there's no way
she would sing that because you can't
set fire to
rain can you in this game I can't so I'm
guessing they want me to fire
these
uh
uh the
uh English words evade
me
these
these I wouldn't call it
torches but
sure I mean that's just an easy way
out
um okay I'm going to do it I'm going to
do it I'm going to do it I'm going to do
it
bye I I'm hoping that's what
they are asking me to
do there we
[Music]
go
yeah is that what makes him come out or
oh what makes me come
[Music]
in that that that's
where the guy is
right
[Music]
awesome I
no one
here is it I'm stealing this treasure is
your birthday too M happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday congratulations I hope you have
a lovely
birthday
uh is this
music doesn't quite fit this room but
I'm guessing it's a general theme
for several of these rooms in these area
this
area maybe even the
dungeon but this was not where the guy
was I another a mini dungeon H it it did
give me like oh dungeon vibes
why is the marker on the heart still uh
I guess it's still there because they
don't know that I'm already at the next
place and they don't show you where the
next place
is nothing means for cotton candy it's
not fair you got dark PHS growing right
where you live
BL yeah sure because that's a good thing
to happen
mhm yeah you get all the cotton candy
you want you Lo
out that's one I thought too H wait this
one with the flower head it looks like
that
Pokemon now it is kind of inconvenient
that most of my home is
gone so that's why I obviously don't
[\h__\h] like it but unlimited webs
unlimited internet yay elimin coton
candy I gu that's true so what's the
problem you even have a membership card
for The Sweet Spot you've totally got it
made they're so
brainwashed oh yeah GE
floor or in German we say G
floor not vile
plume now but I really like to have my
home back bruh priorities you know a
thing you guys don't understand
seemingly should we talk to them or we
just go
in M I have one but we can talk about it
later all right I'm going
[Music]
in th this very specific
spot
FL ke floors that's cute
so
far that was a fast attack I appreciate
that yeah but now you destroyed my paths
too but yeah I guess they were slow
paths can you all
right we're
good trampoline trampoline webs
what are they
bouncy no way if you're sticking to them
that hard how can you
bounce maybe electric would have been
better fire was plenty good I would
say oh hello little
thereare
[Music]
and don't have enough energy to turn
into link so I hope my R rope will do
everything I feel like all these plant
type
enemies even though there's
probably no particular Elemental
Advantage I still feel like I should
counter them with fire you know where
are you shooting what are you
doing this one this one thank
you we summoning instead of waiting ah
yeah I should do that all right let's
try to jump it's it's not trampolini at
all
um can you kill that
thing oh oh he went through the wall
good job
give him what you got come on I believe
in
you yeah that's what I'm talking about
no let me come back
up
[Music]
Wooh that's not the first time I think
that he hacked himself through the
walls you know when I showed you that
screenshot of me trying trying to find a
solution even though I could have sent
the ghost
through Wawa stupid sometimes wa stupid
all the
time but when Wawa stupid Wawa finds
different
way desperate times call for desperate
[Music]
measures you guys are so nice but you
have to admit even you guys make fun of
my stupidity often but when I say it
then it's
wrong I'm not allowed to call myself
stupid but you guys
[Music]
are I see how it
is
oh wait
what what cap do I take
do I have enough to get all the way
up can you not bother me right now oh I
knew it I knew you're going to grow
big uh wait if he's a body of water can
I place a bomb fish inside of him and
blow him up from the inside no that
would be so funny all right then from
the outside yeah yeah there we go
beautiful man they missed out on the
real really funny
[Music]
combination okay
wait this works I have enough if only I
could place them
correctly is this
a troll
moment or is there something behind this
block I doubt it
honestly nope that was a troll they're
like try to find the right way or
what by the way I'm like super unsure
about my schedule next week at least
anything
past
Halloween I don't know what to
do but also uh did you guys
see I think it was announced right
something for Halloween was
announced thought it was kind of funny
cuz you guys were asking about like VR
and stuff yesterday or like super chat
was asking about
it I was like you just wait you just
wait there is actually something being
planned but I'm not taking part in
it cuz it's like kind of late and I
don't I don't know I
thought
I I feel like VR always gives me
like this makes you feel like stressed
out and sick and
everything right I'm still missing one
where oh there's a whole right side over
there
[Music]
okay yeah and I thought H they probably
have plenty of participants cuz they're
asking all
branches
so it's not like they'll be
desperate when it comes to participants
is what I
[Music]
thought yeah they said oh anybody can
join
[Music]
MH but you complete Holo e
you Holo e doesn't exist it's just in
your
head it's not
real sorry we are stress here yeah it's
like it's way too heavy and I I the
vision is always blurry as [\h__\h] I never
get at right position I want that what
was it called
Big what's it called Big Vision big
something those goggles that are really
really small I want
those big
[Music]
screen I want them but I think those are
all custom made so uh I don't know if
you can freely order them now because
before there was like a an extremely
long waiting list or so or waiting
time I don't think they were taking any
more orders I don't
know yeah I could join for desktop but
then I don't know
I don't know I don't know cuz I wasn't
even sure what what I was when they were
like asking everybody are you going to
do you want to participate and I was
like I don't even know what I'm going to
do for Halloween yet like I don't want
to commit to something when I don't know
yet what I'll be up
to yeah yeah I've participated in plenty
of things recently that are past
midnight I think I'll take a little
break from
that especially if it's not like an Ian
focused thing or so where it really
seems like I should participate I don't
know yeah they got plenty of
participants I think probably
so
yeah you made the fors go away you you
bumpkin
you Mon oh wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait the others didn't call me a monster
because they were sexing it up they were
distracted but you guys should ask them
I saved their love
life I didn't get any complaints from
them bro don't be like this this Blossom
guy is also happy when will we get our
web go back to the main city don't you
have plenty of webs there I wanted more
me to you're horrible [\h__\h] you I'm going
to burn you
alive there's only one thing to
do
[Music]
get you're lucky it's not November
yet I would get rid of all of you no not
November me damn PR me those little
[\h__\h] we get now we're getting another
stealth Mission just like the beginning
of the game everything
looping yeah crack PL of SLE and scrubs
don't let cook from loose wait what what
about the what about the guy who's happy
because I got his house back
[Music]
hello about the people who I safe for
them to make love again you're going to
stand here in the clink until you show
your story what the me can we have a
trial and have them be you know
my my
my my Witnesses of Good
Deeds think about what you've done oh
one last thing I have to confiscate all
your
belong bro we're really back to the
beginning are you kidding me you were
giving me
something a [\h__\h] di stick
this this a joke is this a [\h__\h]
joke Cotton Candy
Stick anyway starving and I don't have
time to stand around talking to
Crooks cotton cand is calling my
name that's a cute
key I have a
d y me too me too I can still do that
are you kidding me wait it's so small
you're telling me I can't get it through
this hole oh I can
okay well
then it's so cute that is the cutest key
I've ever
seen I think the key goes through that
door uh yeah yeah
you didn't have to point that out for me
there was literally no other way to do
anything
so what is
this
oh do I go up or
down wait they have beds and I
didn't what what the
[\h__\h] all I had was a [\h__\h] rope
to what's he telling me
to bro they didn't even have the decency
to give me a stone
bed oh wait the Rope is maybe just to
okay well
anyway up or down let me go here
then had to tie me to the wall i f way
worse cuz I the moment I saw that I was
thinking of Game of
Thrones I can't believe it the game is
really looping us wait I have no way of
getting up there okay it's stealth for
real for real all right cuz in the
beginning of the game it was also
stealth for real for real until we came
back what if I do that does that not
make you think like what the
[\h__\h] yeah
I can't push you damn
[Music]
it I don't really know what my plan is
here
um what you can jump up there oh [\h__\h] I
can't you're smaller than me how are you
able to do that [\h__\h] going to jump back
oh you
are um
feel like I kind of ruined
[Music]
it you think I should try another room I
don't know I feel like I just started
wrong let's check out the other room
oh now that feels
like I got to go here maybe after I get
my own stick
back my magical
stick wait
[Music]
um he jumps over everything
so wait oh wait I forgot about this
[Music]
[Laughter]
my legs are a little bit longer than
yours buddy okay let's see I'm guessing
that is the front door and the moment I
walk out they see me and they're like
[\h__\h] you get back in there right I I I I
don't believe this exit no no no no no
no no but
I finally remembered that I can jump in
these cuz I for Gore and that was very
important to
remember
nice
nice just going to do the whole pack of
this one jug wait are you going
to turn around
okay
wonderful even got some money out of
that look
away oops uh-oh will I be too
slow no no no no
wait do they no weren't they like nicer
before and moved me back to so like
somewhere close by not into the cell oh
I guess I was only at the gudo
Village a man or the checkpoint is a
little bit later who
knows
he bro
I stopped early
enough that was
rigged I'm halfway excuse me I'm I I'm
certainly further than H don't stress me
out you're going to make me doubt if I
can finish it
today yeah I'll go slow no I I started
off way too far like I could
have made my way
there wait I'll wait for
him can lift boxes
[Music]
too I'm fine with my
jug wait I
guess if I get out but he sees me no no
no
no Over My Dead bu Over My Dead
bud at least I'm only reset to the
beginning of the room and not to the
cell huh well yeah that's a shortcut for
sure bro
[Music]
but yeah so he was able to see me when
he turned over and I was on the box dead
dangerous that doesn't work do I want to
try the n i I will just I'll just move
with my jug P to this guy
thumbnail is amazing well thank you I
didn't throw it but the artist certainly
did a good
job I got a bunch of
Zelda game related fan
art
wait for this game especially towards
the end thank you guys he's very
cute I'm scared
I'd rather stay in my jug although
oh oh they're doing a smart
[Music]
thing when they look up and down I can
pass like now uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh
no give me a checkpoint bro what no
checkpoint even now
distraction I yeah right distracting
them was also a
thing okay at least this part can be
skipped
[Music]
easily FAS faster faster FAS F okay
is H than Dark
Souls now I think Dark Souls would be
even more difficult for
me um well one thing that I think might
be smart is instead of walking although
then I don't
have okay I will risk it to try this out
for science
cuz yeah they turn really fast maybe you
could do it with the jug too
but I trust myself more by just running
really fast okay
right [\h__\h] was about to get me but I'm
not going to let him I am just not going
to let
him there are some interesting
cells can't move
it can't move these
though
okay is there anything there that's
worth going there I don't think so H
maybe this is the if I get caught in the
next part maybe this is the cell they're
going to put me in next
maybe huh
possibly hard
container it's I
see it's a little puzzle with objects
that are all different
heights cute the bed is the same as this
table is it not
that is hanging on a
red uh
[Music]
wait [\h__\h] now I can't get up
anymore I needed I needed to bring that
back
back wa is that really what's happening
though is that
really surely that's what's happening
right wait I I think
[Music]
um Al I don't know how necessary that is
ah how about how about okay how
about
um the last thing will be the tree on
the
bed oh I think I got it wow you got to
really use maybe almost all of them but
I don't think you have to use all of
them oh wait wait
wait well this is the first thing okay
okay okay okay uh I might need
everything I might
indeed maybe this can be here this can
be here
[Music]
[\h__\h] wait wait wait wa wait wait wait
wait
wait maybe I was right first putting it
here and putting another
object there
but this but then no but still not high
enough uh low enough for me to jump I
think surely that's correct
so I can jump from here to
here ah okay okay okay okay I think I
got it I wish I had another one of those
tables but maybe that's not what I
need how the [\h__\h] do I get that up there
there we go this is the
way no that tree is still too
high um
[Music]
ah like
this from here to here wow that was
surprisingly one of the perhaps most
challenging and interesting little
puzzles even though it's so simple that
they have in this game ah and that will
[Music]
a that room is telling us to do the same
thing here with all of these objects
which
is interesting
because some of these are Hearts to
bring
over oh you kidding me um maybe
can I grab it from
no probably grab the
bed but that one help me I'm going to
grab
the not
quite okay maybe
I'll bring this with no it won't fit
okay
okay uh
um
wow after all of that that I did in that
room I deserve another heart piece if I
do even more of
this okay stairs have been
made table is coming with
me
[Music]
yeah do I need the beds out here
hopefully not
oopsy I'm guessing this will be my
stepping
stone wait is that enough
already oh it might be enough so that's
a bit simpler for sure but bringing it
over is a little
bit thinking moment here we
go interesting interesting I think I
just skipped the actual puzz with what
you can't though cuz you can't use your
items yet what are you talking about
h no no no I don't think you can you
can't use your
Echo they're using it to eat cotton
candy that is not a Cotton Candy Stick I
can't stand to watch this Z what should
we
do what do you what do you mean like why
is this stick's purpose so important to
you thanks for their membership
Reno I'm HED stuff
y oh come on stop it no this is good he
seems distract oh why did you get his
attention you here to take this aren't
you
oh but now I get it it's not the normal
stick that I have oh we can exchange
it's my magic stick I didn't even
realize it's my magic
stick the rod is special it's not for
food tell one I thing was SC to give it
back don't accidentally eat the stick
too please okay a sec I'm just G to eat
the spider webs up of
it oh he's nice for
returning it to me you shouldn't return
these items to your prisoner should
you you don't know what power it gives
me you got your belongings back but the
tree Rod
is kind of sticky and slimy
and yeah not in its nicest
condition Bey nothing wasn't great
wasn't a great Condon are you sure I
think it would be great because like it
automatic te Al has this like twirly
thing where okay maybe maybe that sucks
I feel like it would be interesting to
twirl more up more volume but then with
your mouth it's probably hard to get the
cotton candy that gets stuck in between
huh catches it too well
yeah wait what
did they forget I'm a
prisoner I'm glad we got back but now I
feel
crazy oh wait now I think I understand
what you meant maybe did you not go into
that room to solve that puzzle for the
heart piece but first solved the so to
say smaller puzzle outside to get here
retrieve your stick and then go back to
get the heart container by just cheesing
it you
cheeser you absolute cheese
Lord
wow can't believe he cheesed it that
hard I didn't I didn't even think about
going into the next room yet because
once I see a heart piece I'm focused on
that did you even try to Solve the
Riddle or did you immediately feel like
uh I don't think I can solve
this did you did
you not even give it a try
but if you can do the one outside you
can also do the one
inside I believe in
you my
man time to burn all of these fake takus
and their whole city to the
ground I mean after what they've done to
[Music]
me I knew that was the
exit good that we didn't
try on to walk nice day
for yeah yeah surprise incoming
hang on you're the one we
arrested back to
yourself you little [\h__\h] don't you
realize I'm done being your
prisoner oh wait wait there was another
room
here I thought it was done I got my
things
uhhuh I see how it
is how about this kind of monster
wait are they all afraid of monsters I'm
eating jotto by the way
oh you
are don't mess with me cuz I have
control over all the
[Music]
monsters look at this look at straight
into its face let me feel your misery
you're terrorizing these poor de scrubs
yeah I'm also terrorizing these jotos
that I'm having for
dinner what do you mean you didn't think
of that solution
just
putting what
solution am I a
genius well you mean the solution of
just burning everybody to the
ground you still have to learn if you
want to become a hybrid Phoenix like me
oh no I'm not the hybrid though but you
know
have to think with
fire where there is a fire there is a
way M I have to eat more
part pigeon no no no no no fully fully
Phoenix surely there's more w Wait I
thought it was a Oh
no I thought it was
a oh
[\h__\h] now let me get
the thought it was a blue ruby but I
guess it's a violet one and that's why
it's worth it going
there can I blow up the stones sow
right good luck un lemoning our ooshi K
I'm already un
[Music]
lemon don't you see
was that a
50 it must have
been oh oh oh oh
oh I was out of air
[Music]
help oh
EV yum y
y uh
what that wasn't a platform to stand on
oh
oh okay no
problem I have other
things yeah Evan how you
doing how's it going
ah Pim Pim is that what I hear what a
beautiful
sound where is it why are you
hiding my precious why are you hiding my
precious oh I'm sure it's ped here
because that is a challenge although the
shark is not at all affected by it
interesting
um can I place the platform here and
then go under its cover yeah no
no
um we had a similar issue before but I
don't know if I can solve it the same
way
here that's just not stopping it that's
stopping the plat boom
but h
yeah I was thinking of latching onto the
shark but he doesn't go as far as I want
him to go will he
go will he
go oh but now he gets dragged down
because of
me a
[\h__\h]
huh surely there's a way how to solve
this I don't understand
I don't quite get
it what what even is
there
ah wait my plat boom goes even higher so
I just just I should just uh attach to
my plat
boom
aha no take me with you no ow where am
I okay a no where am
I it's too hot wa let take me with you
okay wait no it doesn't work
either I don't
understand wait genuinely I need the
solution please help
me
oh
oh oh
uh sit on top I saw you write that
comment before but I didn't quite really
understand
oh that's so logical
wait
wait you did it a different
way I'm sure yeah there must be more
than one
way I wonder what the other way
is we made it out
are you
free you little [\h__\h] why did you not
become my character witness why did you
just ignore
everything and let me suffer I could
have died in there they would have
probably let me die from
starvation you suck you deserve to be
burnt because of this these actions the
ignorance you're not willing to fight
for anything even though I saved your
ass this was the dick scrub that didn't
give a [\h__\h] about as being
abducted I came to thank you for getting
rid of the fors at my home now that
you're out I used to like that stuff but
I'm fed up of it I don't even want this
stupid membership card
anymore waa how do you get over your
addiction like that so much that you
like really rejecting it without going
to
like any kind of therapy or so how did
he do it how did he do it maybe absolute
desperation of losing your
house he found vtubers he did find the
vtuber
me can I has your
yeah okay I guess that's the least I can
do to make up for how I just let you get
abducted and almost
kill oh that's cute there a membership
wooden chopping board
cute after I'm done with it I will chop
it
up because of the disrespect you have
given to me I will disrespect you guys
[Music]
bag okay we got
it and now nobody cares about me not
being in prison anymore interesting
interesting cuz I'm one of the cool kids
now you got to respect me me and my
membership
card I'm honestly surprised that just
having a membership card is good enough
for these people cuz obviously I am
visually very different from them and
they the way they're like recognizing
that and calling me a bumpkin and
rejecting me I feel like they just
wouldn't let me in just because I'm not
one of them
and they're not even doubting like if
the if I got the membership card
legitimately how do you even get one in
the first place in a legitimate
way all of you are cool all of you
have
membership
uh
rights to enter The Sweet Spot
membership
streams it's like we told you Bumpkin
there's no going in to The Sweet Spot
unless you got
a what what the hell a membership card I
you got one why didn't you say
so we'll open the door for
you all right let me save your lives
guys cuz
those spider webs if you eat so many of
them right now you're still okay but I
think over time it will make everything
in your brain sticky it'll all stick
together you won't be able to fake
straight
anymore not
good is there no big spider who's eating
it it would kind of be even more like
interesting as a story if there was the
big spider like luring them in with the
spider webs and and then eating them and
they should be complaining about people
missing but nobody's complaining about
people missing so I guess that's not
happening thank
you yay my members are you new member
here oh [\h__\h] it's growing
uhoh look
the oh [\h__\h] it's growing even more
the they're spreading watch out
everyone what is it we spinning cotton
candy okay you might want to stop for a
second you're being so annoying why
don't you
just here we
[Music]
go well you'll get to meet the creator
of all these spider webs perhaps isn't
that exciting
oh no no not
good
karma just walk out the door honestly
and just ignore everything around you
again but sure I'll save
you
[Music]
uh
ow of course I'll save you
oh friend I disappeared in the horns on
the bright side there's probably plenty
of cotton candy in here is that all you
think about let monsters lose swollowing
up scrubs who knew that stuff was so
dangerous what if our friends are gone
for
good they'll come back if we meant the
rift
really but hang on does man Rift mean
getting rid of no don't think so
logically just let me do my thing me
what do you care about more your friends
are cotton
candy how dare are
you I think it's time to get
going yeah at least one of these scrubs
has the ability to think clearly right
now now and let me go in cotton candy
maybe you guys can have a spider farm
and then
organically you know make more cotton
candy I'm sure you guys could do that if
you really like it that much there's
always a way if there's a
will interesting how some of them have
more of
a
like sense sensical mind and some of
them don't some of them just can't be
saved or
helped but we'll force it onto
them we'll save them one way or another
but I got to say cotton candy without
any sugar just by spider we might be a
genius
invention maybe that's something for hat
to try again if she wants to make some
kind
of unique cooking stream that has never
been done
before maybe we should suggest this to
her she can
eat spiders and she can also eat sper
webs
right how do
you get so many spider Labs I guess
that's kind of
impossible at least not
ethically please stop cooking
okay thank you for 48 com of membership
Y
what
oopsie good job okay good I forgot you
were still
here oh well you going to set it on fire
for me thank you but actually maybe
focus on the enemies because you're too
stupid to aim high enough anyway
M there we
go oh there's a [\h__\h] frog Frogg you a
you little [\h__\h] where are
you I
choked ah I can't burn that up either no
where are you fry waa
must be over there in the
middle a there you are you found
yourself a nice little spot haven't
you but there's no Escape There's No
Escape no no no
no what the [\h__\h] is that
I've never seen that
[Music]
before
oopsie a Grime no no no gu Goose Spectre
Echo he look funny he was invincible
when he was
flattened what a
genius enemy
oh I'm in
pain okay it has stopped
raining it is time to set fire to the
rain and bring another Wiz robe
out wait do I have to set fire to all of
these probably right
[Music]
was there one over here
no okay maybe there's a fourth one
oh oopsie a no
ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow got an
egg uh okay that was four but that's
still not
enough I don't know if it's going to
make anything
happen but so far I wait there's not
even right there's I thought I was going
to look for the the souls again and
close the rift but no no no no this is
the dungeon
huh and sometimes it's just not very
clear what's going on did I need to
activate
those maybe if I activate all of them
this will turn off or they want me to
turn these
off what do you think y ow
turn these off all right I'm on
it oh they turn they turn on
again uh
how
fast one two oh it has it would have to
be literally instantly I don't think
I've a
wait is that the only way you can do it
I wonder the the
big gust Master like my Frost Master
woohoo
oh oh right okay the Frog would have
been another option huh didn't even
think about the Frog even though that's
like
the the echo of this region but wait so
was there nothing about
the um the Torches so
far maybe there there was a fifth one
that I didn't find that should have been
activated for an extra chest or
something is what I was thinking but
maybe not ow
ey laser over there that I don't think I
know
yet should I get
it
yes are you the one that makes the oh
yeah
wrong look at the other dark spider on
its back like a little baby that needs
to be flopped over to the other
side it's been a while since I've used
you but I can't think of anything else
right now even though there are a
million
options wait okay you're not you're not
really doing
anything okay but what about this
one
wizzy there we go oh
can it not be completely
killed only
deactivated
beos it
can but my wizzy gave up on
it oh with electricity that thing the
crystal activates
I see maybe I want all of them
activated in that case I could spawn a
couple or just one inside
here um but it will walk away that
little [\h__\h] don't do
that
um well uh well well well well well well
well it only has to be there for a sec
Split Second at the same time so if I
just spawn it like
so even for a moment it all free at the
same time or lit up it'll work no need
for extra work no extra platform oh
yo I can sense my friends deeper
Inn some deep [\h__\h] let's go save them
yeah that would have been too
easy oh
n that was a big flower flower
flower FL flow flow flow flower
flower
flower um where did it g
stop playing with my voice
[Music]
please what is
that
aha
egg it was a spider
egg how
terrifying can this actually like
attack or is it just for pretty nice
effects all right
disappears we even need to kill all of
these
[Music]
enemies
ow
[Music]
[Applause]
ow what I didn't even see the
hole do I want to be here this is not
really the way I wanted to enter this
Temple wasn't there a main
entrance my friends are definitely in
here I can sense them nearby but this
place is so huge Where Do We Begin I
guess right
here I thought I fell down well that's
weird I don't really can I even start
here I like the
music and FL flip him like a hamburger
at
kfp no don't end the pretty music that's
like the best music I've heard so far in
this game even though all of them were
great might be my
favorite okay
wait I guess the bottom part of this
room is not accessible right now
[Music]
oo do they again do they need to be lit
at the same
time cuz one of them cost
[Music]
three all if that's
possible wait no it's staying on isn't
it
oh maybe we're
[Music]
good not turning off right oh it is uh
but it stays on relatively
long nice
[Music]
uh wait how did I reach that one oh
[\h__\h] ah no no no I prepared it so
nicely uh wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I'll do it over again again it
worked oh it was in range I thought I
had to place it there now okay lucky cuz
I think the next ones were about to
diminish its beautiful light what about
the door to the left I definitely
entered for the wrong door did
I because now I have also again two
openings this feels like the kind of
room you walk into not out of you know
what I
mean sorry uh
[Music]
oh don't let them bully you just shoot
don't let them interrupt
you
no
quick quick
go why why why why why are you like this
[Music]
one more come on yeah just for good
measure okay hello good
[Music]
morning hey is this
room
um am I doing something
wrong wait I can I can move them but I
still can't learn them how do you
properly destroy them do I blow them
up how
[Music]
complicated do do I get a reward if I
kill everything in this in this
room like a chest a key secret
chest
[Music]
no well I guess it would show
if there was such a
[Music]
reward there's these little weird plants
again ah and wait that's not the the
boss key door right
[Music]
yeah wait H wait normally wait
ah is it so that normally you enter
through this door first and you're like
oh but lemon will then tell you like oh
we're in the dungeon but oh man we must
probably find a different way to get in
because it doesn't seem like there's any
way for us to get through here for now
so let's find a different entrance but I
found a different entrance first
[Music]
yeah that seems to be the
case okay well now I'm satisfied now
that I found the main
entrance and that now that I realized
that I was supposed to enter through the
other way eventually anyway I'm
satisfied
now now I shall go to the place where I
unlocked the
door I gamed too hard my
[Music]
my my intuition led me to the real
entrance okay we got the
map well the weird easy room Oh that's
oh that's that room we're already
connecting the dots
[Music]
Get
Wrecked oh you need you need two then
okay all
[Music]
right do I want to kill the spider you
think the spider deserves
death you guys like
spiders don't use bed oh that's why you
were saying
[Music]
that it's been a while since I've slept
on a
bed I don't mind them as long as they
don't kill you
[Music]
I wrote this in pre-chat but yesterday I
got real jump
scare I brought one of those I think it
was like a stink bug but it wasn't green
it was like just like brown gray color I
think I brought one indoors and then I I
didn't realize and I had it on my
arm and and the moment I saw it cuz I I
felt something tickling me I look down
like I literally screamed so
loud why would I do that why would I
bring that all the way down is that
beneficial to
me it was so scary but it was just a
little itty bitty bug then I brought it
outside I like yeated it the moment I
saw it I was like eated it but then I
picked it up and then I brought it
outside don't
wor he was not harmed honestly if I
would have left him somewhere my cats
would have attacked him and probably
really tortured him so I did a very good
thing oh the enemies are
coming ah [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
spider all right we get it we get it
stop stop trying to cause a
[Music]
[Applause]
drama that's a drama bird what do you
call a drama bird is there a word for
someone who like okay someone who likes
to cause drama is
a is
[Music]
a drama queen but is there another word
for it
perhaps hey
no no no no no no Nara doesn't like to
cause
drama what makes you say
that I mean she's a bit dramatic but I
don't think she likes to cause drama
she's dramatic when she's like suffering
like oh my God I'm going to die I'm
literally going to die but she doesn't
cause drama yeah
give her a
break is that where we came
from
or no it's
not oh no that other room it felt
like I didn't know what to
do uhhuh I see I had a feeling
well you clear the field for me and then
I decide what to do I haven't used my op
spider in a while where is
itle wall spider ceiling spider oh my
God has it no way it should be up higher
no was it this one no crawl TOA is
different right I've definitely used it
more than craw crawl
TOA uh my
eyes what the [\h__\h] dare you are I've
used you that much I didn't think I used
you that much but
okay wait the fire in the background
does that
affect
um anything go away
no it's not
[Music]
real bro
really yeah let me help you
[Music]
out what what's wrong with you
higher let me push
you now you can do it come on no don't
let him push you down again do it come
on don't let him interrupt
you oh there we
go really had to give him upes
[Music]
there cute
I I don't think of pulling them
ever you know when we first found this
Echo and everybody was like oh my God
that's like way too op oh we can use
this for everything but then you forget
about it it anyway and then you don't
end up using it that much
[Music]
anyway could we have really cheesed
everything with it I don't even think
so but what oh my this is enemy en enemy
speeda sorry I I I was riding your
screen because I
thought I thought you were friendly
speeda sorry that was maybe kind of
awkward didn't realize what I was doing
is this the
[Music]
room I don't know I am absolutely lost
in this dungeon so far but things
are kind of working out aha I see no
problem Oh but wait once
you can is this a dead end for
now yes uh I think it
is unless
I don't think I can
no speeda
up speed up
up where speed
[Music]
up I don't know about that one guys but
I can try
it I guess that's genius
that might just
work no not
every I thought I was stuck how else
would you do it if you don't have one of
these Speeders I wonder
[Music]
I came back to theuh now this looks to
me like there's speeda
connecting the entrances and
exits with
[Music]
strings
um wait what was the what was the point
of that room we didn't get any
treasure
well oh
[Music]
um Get
Wrecked trying to hide doors from wait
is EO gone now if I go back ohg God I
didn't learn
it it's gone no it's not gone reentered
itself you did it with different rocks
but the tiny ones
okay it's so dark again oh God should
I carry my little light here oh dear
hello I really like the Wiz rope don't
I nice
don't have a
key carry the fat
[\h__\h] walk on your fly on your own will
you
help no don't let him interrupt
you that's your big mistake always don't
you learn from your
mistakes keep on doing what you're doing
even if they bully you you know
this is a life
lesson don't let things like that
distract you when other people bully
you just keep on doing what you believe
in don't let it distract or interrupt
you
[Music]
turn your other cheek like
Jesus I don't know about Jesus I don't
know what he
did
[Music]
sure take out the Tor Tech Tor yeah when
they bully me I'd love to take out
detector
Rock bro you missed or did you you
didn't
miss
go good job so proud
of what is there is it still
alive I didn't even set that on fire
properly there we go oh the whole room
lit up I guess that was the last
one I didn't see those spikes here
before thank God I didn't accidentally
walk into them is there no key in this
room well I could go up ah into the room
with a chest or I go down
now what is this
sign it's here as well H
outside um uhhuh maybe I should go to
the chest first I don't know
oh wait there's a war Point what the
hell why mid boss mid boss close or
what why is it
[Music]
here yeah this didn't look like a mid
boss room I knew it
[Music]
Oh I thought when it moves down it would
hit it but I guess it
[Music]
won't can I
even do anything in this room right
now I think I feel like uh maybe
uh
eh I have an idea can my ghosts go
through if they can go through walls
they should be able to get through here
but what if somebody comes in here with
no ghosts are they just
[\h__\h] there you
go he's FR attack attack attack why
won't you
attack oh you're just
slow I
[Music]
could this is the easier side to enter
this room
from oh
really wait I didn't want to go there
let me go wait haven't I already cleared
that room that looked very familiar to
me
key key KY
key maybe the waro was there because
they realized oh I did clear that way
before cuz they realized
oh yeah this dungeon is like a spider
web
honestly and our players will rage if
they have to walk through everything
again okay then I now that I have the
key warp back down
[Music]
here um this way yeah
wait but there all the also the path
down here I don't know man let's see
where this
leads so many options
oh
egg
on yeah spider we
I guess we'll go
outside and maybe for going outside
we'll find another P
inside oh oh
oh wake up oh you don't want to wake
up is this some
I mean I can put anything on the buttons
[Music]
right do they want me to put
them on there
why don't they
activate ah those are the ones that need
to be hit at the same
time ah okay okay
okay keep on walking
[Music]
there we
go are they all going to activate
now they're all going to wake up now
aren't they no are you sure why
why it bothers
me they're not even attacking
me and I couldn't turn him around either
they were kind of
different another oh okay here is
surely maybe Outdoors is the the mid
boss
[Music]
I don't remember other dungeons having
so many safe points even when there's no
boss
[Music]
coming you know what let's use some of
the ones I've been learning
recently but in the end it's just all
back to Wiz Rob even the one time I'm
like oh let's do something else I just
automatically felt like oh wi where's
the way to
[Music]
go no he's letting himself get hit and
then distracted
again how about
Mo come on do
something yeah
come on why you so weak you're five
stars
bro come here I need energy hello how
low are you what's the point of you guys
flying around if I can't get
you all reliable wizzy not so reliable
after all
oh he dropped the monster Stone that's
rare okay I wonder if from the inside
you wouldn't have been able to enter the
outside through this
place
probably or it's more like
a Only One Direction kind of thing cuz
one door is locked from One
Direction on the
inside come on
[Music]
good night thank you
for watching for a little while are
these also same yeah okay wake
up wake
[Music]
up
why huh I mean I can do it differently
too but I was going to
like could do with ice blocks
again right cuz they slide in here
too yeah they
do
like but why are
those why are they
there I'm so good
I could have yeah even probably summoned
um the same thing but I just went with
ice blocks like in Good Old
Time
scared um what do we want how
about how do they even
fight like step by step they get closer
to you and then attack you with the
sword that's kind of that doesn't seem
very efficient does it
kind of want to try my T Rock again but
it'll take a while to l
no
[Music]
no let me get the
hearts no no no wait don't hit no wait
is he oh I see mut to electricity
because he's out of
met open
oh that's so why is he so strong
though oh sh he can't take damage from
them I love
it
incredible
woo I should probably sleep
again um
[Music]
now time to light up the room why am I
even in cat outfit I could at least wear
something that gives me something I
think
um that's the most helpful for now maybe
the spin
too oh yeah I wish these other outfits
also gave you a real
effect we wearing right now by the way
I'll
that
um what do we want
[Music]
I don't know maybe
that
okay what is this
room that scares
me I can't
[Music]
see Dam it
oh there so many spiders at least the
enemies can see right they can see what
I can't see so I'll just hope that they
take care of some of them are they not
willing to move from their spider
web as long as they have
one ow ow ow ow ow
ow
oopsie good choice wait that's is that
an exit
no gets rid of a path which isn't a real
path the illusion of a
path but there must be another
torch I
think take it
is it not going to do the thing again
where where the whole room lights up
when I have all torches or do I just not
have all torches
[Music]
yet let me see a torch
I'm over
[Music]
here there we go it another
torch ah another
torch that's got to be it is it
not maybe one in the beginning
no maybe this room just doesn't light up
maybe it's not always the case
I mean I can already leave ah never mind
in the darkest corner okay it has lit up
we
have so many paths that we can take that
leads up to a room where I've already
been to ah but the bottom part of that
room and that leads to another room that
I haven't been to oh this is really
spider web this might be the most
intricate even though it doesn't have so
many floors it just has so many
different kind of
[Music]
rooms a chest and a path
to that room I don't know there's so
many
choices and I don't like diving anymore
in this game leave me
[Music]
alone shark
oh there's didn't see the
[Music]
stone boulder can block wave
water feels like a
scam can it
of course it can no it
[Music]
can't no I die are you going to wake up
no I don't know I'm going to need air
yeah this is not the water dungeon give
me a
[Music]
break wait how
about I don't know do they want me to do
something like this no okay my shark is
really confused
too how do I get to the other side here
ah
wait I guess we probably the other airf
flow
[Music]
yeah W thinking too
complicated oh my poor
shark up you go come on go for
it and
then get some air there's a chest
let's add some
water I have tamy hord
today must be maybe because I ate CH
conned like two days in a
[Music]
row woo
this one's
yeah I got to go for the other
side
for wait what was the
was NY literally nothing blocks this
like water flow
right I mean like upwards I could use
the pl boom again
sideways maybe well no these don't work
in the
water I I don't know I don't
know I have to go
around oh wait then can I remove the
okay come here there we
go I feel like without that I wouldn't
have been able to pass would
I wooho
MH
mm cuz it was really difficult to remove
or was it no maybe it wasn't no it was
cuz two blocks tall
there okay are we good do I want to go
that way or is that where I came from a
that's the way back okay we don't want
to do
[Music]
that oh another dark
room really should have got some
smoothies that light up things but you
know how it
is you never
know what you're getting yourself into
on first try
[Music]
another one a
[\h__\h] please I hate darkg
rooms ah make Hyrule bright
again do they oh right they don't
stay maybe I got to do this at the end
when I'm like aware of every when I lit
up the room then I can like go around
faster doesn't the Phoenix glow in the
dark no where did you learn
that
MH come
on there we go okay the room is lit
[Music]
up wait just um
stay
here it's just free right that should be
doable
yeah
yippe I don't think I have enough trees
to have all three of them at the same
time right yeah but you got to be
fast like
stanic okay right room I've seen before
let's go to the
left I think I'm zooming for this
dungeon
mostly
uh what was that again that any me I
am oh when you kill them before
they hatch you get hearts or like maybe
something else too
but oh now we have more of these
platforms I see what you want from
me I already understand we need to make
it even with the
buttons so
that I can send something in the right
timing
again because if it's not even you won't
be able to walk across although maybe
actually I could probably like just drop
it
actually is that even
no all right what what am I even
thinking if it's just same Stone
wouldn't that make it even yeah oh yeah
but I'm going to uh I'm going to add to
it though so one small Stone would be
good where is the small Stone hello uh
cost
is a small Stone exactly the weight of
one
Zelda wouldn't I weigh the same as an
arous uh maybe the game thinks
so oh
uhuh all right I'll place an okay I'll
use the freaking armors
now
um will it not walk off the
edge I
hope wait it didn't even okay because
it's not
even good that also means he doesn't
walk off the edge
wonderful uh ah
[\h__\h] wait do we not need this stone at
all do we just need a small Stone
wa wait wait
wait oh [\h__\h] ah wait wait
wait do we not need any
stone no no no no I alone am not the
same wait it seems okay perhaps a small
Stone this is like math guys
ah
ah how about
[Music]
thisth one small Stone that's why they
had the small stones I kind of had a
feeling but I thought if we're going to
add many stones to it ah maybe just get
a big
one okay left side is chest let's go get
it we still didn't have a mid boss is it
just because of the rooms I'm choosing
maybe I could have already seen the mid
boss if I wanted to what is
this
[Music]
nothing I knew it I knew knew
it I knew it it doesn't show that it's a
door on the map but yeah I reminded me
of those kind of doors but it's more
noticeable maybe from the other side is
it don't know if it is but um this room
again okay so we got the whole second
floor
explored uh the whole third floor is
actually also EXP
explored ah but this part not yet so I
don't know I guess we can warp
there yeah we are getting map
[Music]
tomorrow here we go
is this the room yeah and I do have a
[Music]
key got it all figured out now but if I
hang on to it doesn't that
added I see that doesn't do anything
with the weight
interesting is that logical
is that
logical I think it's not that must be a
mid boss right yeah it's next it's on
the same floor even as the main
boss okay sleepy
time it's not right I know it thank you
for validating my
opinion my brains
what kind of mid boss will this
be I know you're
there I know you're
[Music]
there
no
[Music]
hello hello
hello is it is it on the ceiling there's
no ceiling is
there
um break
floor no
maybe it's a
[Music]
bug
M maybe maybe it doesn't come out until
I hide from
it
um am I too early do I do I need to
trigger something something that's lame
I want to do it now I've already been to
so many places okay which outsides have
I been for this outside I think I
have I guess somewhere outside it will
trigger it all let's go back here this
is like the kind of the beginning isn't
it ah it does show me here what outsides
I haven't been
for cuz they're grayed out oh no
actually yeah even inside okay all the
ones so okay
how about we try to exit through the
real entrance for
one the other mid boss room there's
another mid boss
[Music]
room try to enter for here cuz ah that
room doesn't even have any entrance
through the inside so we a try
let's see if I can get there there's
there's torches
[Music]
again do they need to be
activated oh
hello stop stop stop bullying me no let
me in was that the
room yes
[Music]
uh oh oh uhhuh
oh
uh let me just
swim can I manage to spawn one of
these up there
[Applause]
and will he stay oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
everything up ah quick quick quick quick
uh uh uh uh uh
uh no no no
Qui no no okay sorry smovie for waking
you up sorry please stay oh that uh I
guess it's probably fine if I
just oh
it's not as lenient over here maybe here
I do have to make a path
or well okay I have an
idea cuz look how lenient it is
here what about I mean if I literally
from here plant it on top it's got to
work
yeah yeah she's she L stayed the whole
time I thought she was in the box but
she's on the bed again she must have
changed her sleeping
position I got a
key which doors have I not opened yet
small
doors aren't doors also on the map cuz I
can't see any un opened doors
except the master
door oh fourth floor
oopsie oh yeah I guess so uh but there's
no teleportation
there unless
no
[Music]
o let me go here that feels kind of
short unless there was a hit hidden wall
there again that I was able to turn
around but I don't think that room was
connected to the other rooms at
all shortcut what shortcut do I have a
shortcut wait uh cuz I was just going to
go
[Music]
there
damn
who why is my is sort of
weak okay we're tiling
it we're tiling it over there okay is
that where I wanted to
go
no no it's not the that
one uh
Be Me Up
[Music]
Scotty
okay and you guys are talking about some
shortcuts the problem is I don't
remember that shortcut oh I I don't know
where to
enter so whatever
[Music]
oh oh this looks
like why does it look
like like uh it looks exactly like this
place but just not floating in the
air I'm probably he's going to move over
there after I'm done with him here and
then he's going to be in here or
so
okay surely that's a trick right ow let
me let me let
me let me get a hel out first of
all I should have maybe healed
what I can just attack
you get
[Music]
out I'm out of
energy come on one hits one hits or two
hits or three hits ah well now attack
that yeah yeah one more one more do it
faster he retracted you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
ra
Boomerang can I have two of them yeah
what he ate it and spit out energy
[Music]
come
on yeah I know where you going you
little [\h__\h] I have a shortcut I can just
teleport there so you won't miss me for
too
long we're going to
continue our grand
Vu um but first I take a nap
today might be the first time I'm using
these
categories to speed things up a little
bit
[Music]
but here I go here I have so many
DMS some of them I know are from
chy working on my YouTube channel
warts oh you got more heads now
congratulations ah my energy is still
gone how about I place some of you
[Music]
guys I can only place to I
guess
wait what am I
thinking they give
me bro they give me so time to unwind as
well all right let's go let's
party no no
no come on come here to
party yo yo yo yo what why frogs why
frog frog out of
nowhere let me out let me
out let me fix you
[Music]
[\h__\h] I I guess it's fun but it really
doesn't do as much
damage as you might
think but I just realized can we not uh
spawn these like endlessly actually
oh let him let him do his thing he takes
a little
while he just
ate oh wait I I forgot I have to launch
him let me just have fun with my no
don't break it okay whatever but I was
just thinking since this is not about
Echo would I be able to spawn millions
of these if I wanted
[Music]
to [\h__\h] frogs
man should I get a stronger enemy
out let's get the boomerang guy out do I
have to help cuz this is it doesn't
really seem like anything's
really happening
ow at least I wasn't eatting
uh
what I've lost
my patience
[Music]
take it pooped away what's
happening wait I'm what's happening with
[Music]
me the
rain you [\h__\h] frogs I gave you
I gave you
peace get that [\h__\h] frog out of my
face don't you dare get an another
frog out here
[Music]
oh is the bomb
persist oh there we go um like to have
more bombs but I don't want to waste
another
[Music]
movie let me
know I'm the princess of hyr you will
regret this
if you eat me one more [\h__\h] time I
will call the dentist and he will pull
out all of you beautiful little itty py
tee you won't like
that that's what I'm talking about come
on [\h__\h]
wait pleas
pleas I wonder if it saves the damage
like when it retracts does it like
recharge no not the [\h__\h] frogs again
oh but my fish still works I think
seemingly or is it just because he
didn't let it uh rain again yet
[Music]
it's it's the
fish fish is
good oh
[\h__\h] sorry this is taking too much
time [\h__\h] frog oh he ate it he ate
it no I'll be be it's going to I retract
[Music]
again what attacks right
away see
urchin I don't
know send out
electricity
okay now first I want to get rid of the
[\h__\h]
frog oh do you think when it's raining I
can do even more damage on the plant for
the electricity
[Music]
somehow maybe
not fuing
frog so I'm I'm so
another one
no I'm so close to I'm so close to
trying to recharge my energy with this
movie but I just can't be bothered with
it at least you're going to give me
energy right and if you spit that out
[Music]
yeah no not the [\h__\h] frog again
bro no bro bro bro what
[Music]
what's wrong with
him I can't
aim yeah I know the red
but he barely comes
out why is this fight so lame
[Music]
come
on
what took one more hit
really he gives us the master
key not going to comment on that fight I
will say I don't think that's entirely
on me
it's kind of an annoying
fight I wonder if it's it's not going to
be the same boss
right surely
[Music]
not mhm mhm how do I get to the boss
R these St
[Music]
no must be the main entrance no
no where's the main entrance was that
not
it
okay maybe this I don't know I missed
some stairs where I could have flipped
the
wall great that doesn't show on
the map where the walls are
flippable [\h__\h] do we know can you guys
tell me which floor if anybody
knows second
floor right
[Music]
side Maybe somewhere
here left
side might fall asleep soon oo you eepy
you
eie left side do have to go here or
maybe ah maybe
here those stairs I guess I've never
taken I love you a lot AR
why are you so cute than that's cute
things oh I didn't miss it I actually
already did it
[Music]
huh why does that
different no wait this opened up and I
never took those stairs I think cuz I
went somewhere else first
right or no no no no no no
or is this the right
path I think I saw that room before
[Music]
but I'm
confused was there a
secret here where does this lead i to
the boss room right
other stair will
[Music]
down that
one
okay no no no no no
[Music]
well there's no secret wall
here Mr stairs at the right of the
rotating wall
[Music]
room
what
what what
[Music]
these but I just walked through those
didn't I and that was the mid boss
room where the [\h__\h] am I
I
[Music]
no
ah very
confusing
dungeon very confusing
Vibes he e here we
go oh sleepy time me no go back to me o
electricity you you
spider not you spider oh oh
[\h__\h] can I lick that eyeball GMA oh it's
a
GMA aha
um so we need those jellies but do they
need to be AC at the same time like in
those rooms I'm guessing not right that
would be
crazy I will use my electricity
goar why
not first let's let's figure
out how this works
here should I let the baby GMA destroy
the do it do it no you stupid idiot now
now there's so many of these
[\h__\h] give
me yeah the ah
[\h__\h] okay ghost can you take care of the
small ones okay
one and and yeah wey you take care of
the oh My Ghost already dead [\h__\h]
[Music]
this music is
sick crazy ey
laser thank you for interrupting him I
don't know how you did that but good job
uh now it's my time I hope I have enough
energy yeah yeah okay reset
Spaghetti O nice nice good good
activation
nice how does he get it like he knows I
want might not have enough energy but
okay maybe he'll help me help me help me
help me help me help me help me help me
help me help me oh okay it was just
enough now I either charge up with a
smothie
or I don't know should I I guess so I'll
make more
smoothies after this dungeon
then don't turn around like that and now
we got those little [\h__\h]
again okay he's focusing on them
first oh you barely made it oh no oh no
oh
no last time something stopped that
laser which was really
nice uhoh uhoh P okay I I I'll get the
I'll get the laser away from
you but just hit hit
him oh I guess oh is is I I wasn't
paying attention so when he does the
laser you don't need to activate all the
electricity because his eye is open and
you can attack my mob can attack the eye
but otherwise is his eye always closed
so there's like two ways to do it to get
him
down I struggled way less with this one
like I basically didn't struggle at all
with this
one compared to the mid boss thank God
the mid bosses don't show up in the boss
rushes and that
one Katana challenge
huh well
sometimes things are easy and sometimes
things are hard wiser words have never
been spoken
[Music]
so that was supposedly the last
dungeon chat who people who finished the
game yeah how close am I to finishing in
terms of time what do you
think if I weren't to do a million side
things
now my friends shared some of their
power with
[Music]
[Applause]
me I feel like you can do even more
[Music]
now should I not do too many side things
but I want to do at least the last boss
rush to get the outfit cuz you know I'm
so close to it 1.5 to 2 hours
okay sounds
[Music]
good okay hour or two okay sounds
good Priestess no Priestess no maybe no
no
Priestess
Priestess your courage has freed this
land which was swallowed by
nothingness I am the
[Music]
goddess one of the three who created
your world you have demonstrated true
courage thus I grant my sanction unto
[Music]
you will she give us jetpacks oh she'll
give you something
better
Priestess we free have borne witness to
your true
nature now to open the path to Prime
energy go to the Ancient Forest guarded
by the sacred
tree there you may also encounter the
hero you
speak remember this your courage will
one day be your salvation
cool story
bro we have gotten all of the
sanctions my voice changed I'm sorry a
little bit of a voice crack now we go to
the Ancient Forest guarded by the sacred
tree and Link will be there too
right there's not really anything else
to do in the still world for now so
let's go back to your world zela and
wo hard
cont yeah I guess I'll go didn't miss
any treasure chests did I I think I
didn't so let's
go that's
SK stream heart container yeah stream
heart container instead of Mirage for a
little bit so that I can catch up with
the Milestones no no no no no do it
all at the same time hey yo do you guys
regret the way you treated me now
HH well that was
awful I've had of spiders and dark PHS
good friend and to all of it I'm just
glad everyone's back thank you for
serving
them what is it
I think I smell
something I smell it so it's light and
fresh and fluffy what you
that I know what it is I know exactly
what it is we were so hung up on cotton
candy we didn't see it under our snooze
this whole time the treat that tastes
great and puts a refreshing feeling in
your mouth you mean
Smo it all comes back to smoothies
yeah it wasn't fact in front of your
nose all this time yay smies we can't be
the last ones to try them we look like
pumpkins
pumpkins let's go let's
go I love smoothies
[Music]
too always chasing after the next thing
guess they didn't learn much from the
cotton candy incident no what are you
trying to say this movie is bad I've
been drinking on this whole time and you
haven't warned me at
all are you getting me addicted on those
smovies so that you can control me
[Music]
lemon surely the movies are fine
right wait so are they like a different
kind
of race or like are they I don't
understand
like they're kind of the same
right the small ones and the big
ones but I guess like the big one is
more of an advanced evolutionary
evolution
evolutionary
evolutionarily
Advanced oh they should be the same just
the other one is kind of a grownup sort
of
H so if they grow up they learn to
fly cute
I don't really understand scrubs or it's
like kind of a queen beefing where
they're the same but just like some of
them are special because they get
like treated and fed
differently and then they become
overpowered I don't really understand D
scrubs but as long as they're happy I
suppose it's fine well I'm glad we fixed
the far and wetlands Rift but uh yeah we
got a section from the gun F room
I did
it Z the Ancient Forest the godess
suspension I don't know where that is oh
don't worry I know where it is the black
part of my map maybe you thought nose no
I know where it is
from the
[\h__\h] long long long long have I awaited
this moment
[\h__\h]
money what the
heck are you
[Music]
[Applause]
okay another child
[\h__\h] it's a fake it's a
[\h__\h] it's a
[\h__\h] you can tell by the
cloes the goddesses have provided their
section so I should be able to approach
Prime
energy yes this identity should
[Music]
suffice she gets it lemon gets it thank
you for understanding who I am who the
real one is and who the [\h__\h] one
is oh nice brought me here this time
hopefully this is a safe
Zone wait let me drink a bit more my
throat is getting
tired [\h__\h]
let me help myself out a little bit I
mean so ridiculous
um uh yeah oh my God I
sounds um yeah
uh oh my god
um
Zelda oh Zelda you're awake
what the [\h__\h] just happened tell me all
about
it after you collapsed tree brought you
here to the castle we've been watching
over you waiting for you to wake
up but what has
happened huh I
see the godess is spoke of an ancient
forest with a sacred tree impa do you
know anything of
[Music]
this let go oh yes yes it must be the
Eternal Forest as for the sacred tree
well that must be the beautiful large
tree located
there so it's the forest Northwest of
here the tree and trees are Den to
navigating it will prove
[Music]
challenging oh my God no must have been
planning this from the start they waited
until you earned the right to seek the
Prime energy then created an echo of you
all according to their [\h__\h] K that's
why they imprisoned the goddesses in the
Rifts to lure Us in and that's their
plan if only I'd realize this sooner oh
man oh well this is rather discouraging
isn't it oh oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] Oh you mean this feeling
discovering those plans so late yeah I
feel very
discouraged null might end up obtaining
the Prime energy and become Metroid
Prime what a nice cooporation uh but
yeah maybe not because we don't do that
kind of stuff here that would be too fun
if that happens our best chance will be
to join forces with
link if only link existed
still we have to we have to erase him
completely and let Zelda take the power
forever this is our chance don't say we
have to combine our forces with link now
is finally the time to get Justice for
Zelda if we bring back link you know
who's going to be the protagonist of the
next Zelda game
again you know you know
it it's going to be Legend of Link all
over
again we had it in our hands it's going
to be so depressing for
Zelda how do you think she'll feel if
the next Zelda game is link
again poor girl she's been through so
much so much
gaslighting every single game comes out
called Legend of Zelda and she's sitting
in her princess room thinking all right
today's my time to shine oh this game
I'm also not doing anything well [\h__\h]
maybe next time next game comes out
Zelda's like all right this time for
sure for sure it's called Legend of Dela
after all I'll give my turn and again
she's done it so many
times she's SP through it again and
[Music]
again
no
okay thank you for the Super Chat
[Music]
the God is share that if you go to theal
Forest you may find our hero link tell
her as your father the truth is what
that I want you to remain here it pains
me to consider your stepping out into
danger once
[Music]
again but now I understand you are the
Priestess of wisdom as king I must ask
for your help please go to the Eternal
first find the hero and put an end to
n's nefarious plans please PR safe here
Hyrule Hu
[Music]
the Prime
energy Prime energy
[Music]
pre a Rel to see you safe I was so hard
when I heard you were attack I've been
waiting so nervously awaiting any news
from the King
you're not leaving again are you are
you of course we're leaving because all
of you guys are so useless that we have
to do
[Music]
everything Forest you say well then
allow me to ensure that the tural forest
is safe for passage if I leave
everything to you then I won't be worthy
of my office please anist was it not
what do you mean h I know you can get
there before
how are you blocking it are you blocking
it at
all what is she going to
do oh we're going have a chance to tell
right of the important part that no made
an echo of you
um and he's going there is he going to
meet fake Zelda [\h__\h] it
Zelda is he going to be deceived once
again
[Music]
no God please
no remember what clothes I'm wearing
bro I'm not wearing the clothes I'm
supposed to be wearing that's for
[Music]
sure going out in pajamas cuz I got no
time to
lose all right um ah [\h__\h] they dra me
away from the smoothie
place why is there no smoothie place in
Hyrule just going to go there to make
smoovies which feels right to do it
there you wor the cat
outfit are there cats in the forest if
not then there's no point wait before we
go in there I will go do the Boss Rush
yum yum y yep yep yep wait where is
moving oh right right
there
I'm look at them drinking I want to do
all the side cloes
SP what is your
side I can buy all the I
want are you listening to me I have no
choice I make you an ally in my
moneymaking mission now you know about
the AK a creature kept secret by dickle
scrubs no one's ever C it so there's big
money and offer if you do catching the
dickle snake is quick and easy path to
Fame and Fortune is it like a one of
those overpowered enemies not really
overpowered but it loves electric
apples that's my new record I need to go
on and oh I can give you some easy easy
easy easy easy right now I shall give
you I always got extra fruits with me
did you get the one no I didn't I I know
it exists though where is it is it isn't
it in the forest I don't know where it
is actually I've explored everything
except the forest so wait that was the
whole
Quest oh that was easy the
[Music]
[\h__\h] you don't need help from me to
actually find the snake
Okay it is in the forest okay in a small
Rift uhhuh e no you're telling me that
about the smaller than the mountains
yeah
okay I guess we could go
there right now it is
important
um what was it again
to charge
the ah is it just anything with salt or
is it salt with anything you know what I
mean
um can you combine salt with uh
honey cuz I feel like
generally though these ingredients are
to be combined with these fruits around
them not with each
other it a
try I have a feeling it will fail but
that
no the other way to find out would be
you telling me Oh smooy where you going
need to go
pee yeah that's what I
thought
di salt and egg
oh interesting like IRL I mean that's
kind of a thing
so does that
work please
oh
nice what does that
do uh wait which one is
it is it the golden smoothie at the
bottom this
one oh I thought it would give me energy
bro because I used
salt what
damn that sucks um no wait let me
check maybe I want to make a couple of
these
[Music]
yeah oh I can buy them without making
without using my own ingredients once I
made them once once I figured them out I
see I never tried that function before H
be that's so expensive though what 120
[Music]
rupees when I could make them so cheaply
with my ingredients I guess if you're
like out on ingredients and really need
that drink for some
reason I want to make more at
once give me the option to make more at
once please
[Music]
I will stop by
the uh place for upgrading myself
[Music]
again should I
make oh this could be nice actually to
make should I make like more like light
ups movies and stuff or will I not be
needing any more of that stuff
anyway least he brings me back to this
[Music]
menu sure I'll make one of
these yeah I guess there's a maximum of
how many smoothies I can carry that's
why they don't let you
make so many at once
[Music]
anyway damage reduction for 5
minutes yeah I'm at the end of the game
I should use up my golden
eggs eggs eggs eggs
[Music]
but
um I want a few
more that fill up
[Music]
energy sure I'll make one of
these maybe I'll wind something up while
I'm at it when I'm drinking that
[Music]
a blinking light on top of it so it's a
police
car
what what police cat police
car same
[Music]
thing he so cute he's so
extra all right maybe that's enough for
the final or one
more one more
[Music]
BBE there you go another one
okay I think that'll be enough to
survive I got fairies too after all that
I haven't used in a
while oh he actually told
me I guess now that I am full on this
movies oh yeah I am okay okay I'm
satisfied
[Music]
okay let's the where should we go first
anyway let's do this one first but like
how do I get
there quickly is that the best warping
point I'm sure there's more quests side
quests that I could
[Music]
do but I guess I'll focus on the main
quest now besides that Rift and the Boss
Rush
yeah and if I missed
anymore I shall witness them through
other
means oh
you what are you doing here here's a
stamp supposed to be here okay it's got
swallowed up huh don't
worry I'll get it for
[Music]
you is this even worth only if you want
all stamps I would
say I don't think there's any other
point in doing this Rift is
there but okay it's just free areas come
on we can do it
let's try to rush through it if I can oh
there we go is that ow yo you scared me
no you give me PTSD
[Music]
bro
no yeah yeah yeah yeah good job yo I
thought you would get hit again so proud
of you
yes yes
yes don't let them bully us I've had
enough of that thank you for watching
goodbye thank you thank
you I'm hoping that's all in that
direction
oh oh it's icy here
too wooho
[Music]
oops
oh they break each other what the
[Music]
hell who is
hiding my friends my lemon friends
you all will pay actually it's over
here it's in here it's in here Go Get It
Go Get It don't don't just look at
me okay if you really want to fight and
have fun I
guess I'll take care of this a different
way
[Music]
mhm and
now up
there always fun to ride these plates
hey what the hell happened here can i
sream o this must be really freaking ice
cold but
okay uh wait
what
oh the trees are going to stop
me what the that's what this damp
is I am an only mean
go go go go go I was hoping
no I was hoping that
would go
away the trees kind of did end up moving
the plat boom a little bit I just
notic damn
oh um it's more on the outside than it
shouldn't be in
issue how high can we
go all right that's fine I feel like I
went up here in an unconventional
way but we take
those want a pet lony we're going to get
that lony
[Music]
now I'm going to get
it I guess in the forest right you guys
set in the
[Music]
forest I got to go there anyway
so is he kind of hidden or are we going
to find him anyway maybe he's in like a
secret cave or
so more
lemons yeah I didn't expect the liony to
be in this game but turns out they're is
oh we filled up that little Gap
nice oh yeah even cheaper nice the
wheezys that I'm using all the time are
cheaper now and the really strong
moblin okay how many do we have oh so
many let's go let's go
I
suppose uh wait that Rift wasn't about
finding his brother at all wait is there
really no continuation to
that
maybe post game they show in the credit
scene or something how he finds his bro
maybe you got to go now no don't
leave but thank you for
watching it's been almost 7
hours you
guys are marathoning this with me let me
stamp
okay is that the last stamp sheet I
don't think I can finish it I feel
like I won't find them anymore and I'm
not going to go looking for
them um all right let's do the Boss Rush
or the first before Boss Rush let's go
where was it
[Music]
here can't finish
it that stamp was a JoJo POS aren't they
all JoJo poses
somehow every Dela find out is a
marathon
stream yeah but like I told you guys I
just don't really want to split these
kind of streams awkwardly with only one
hour remaining or
so and you know you
know it do be like
that
sometimes and there's no problem with it
I'm very really um fine the only problem
I have is my tummy
hord but besides that I'm fine I should
use bombs more often so can you upgrade
anything else now
no uh you want 25 crystals that's going
to be hard to get now I've been really
trying my best to get crystals
everywhere still cooking B I stepped
away for more tea what do you mean with
cooking what what was I cooking before
you stepped away
oopsie know what you
mean you've gotten all the upgrades but
what really I clicked it away but he
said something about 25 crystals
feel like that'll be hard to
get oh well oh cooking
[Music]
smoothies you just get a statue if you
find all of them a
statue oh no upgrade
anymore statue for
what St for what why am I going to put
that
have a proper house or
anything anyway yes I have returned
let's do
this I'm so ready you got a new dream
don't
you he got a bunch of them a wish rope
Gathering hey maybe here I can get my
icy
one
uh do I have to do all of these to get
the outfit I thought it was just one
more [\h__\h]
maybe they're not that
difficult you can speed for them fend
off an assault from
disguise okay here you
go I want the [\h__\h]
outfit you thank
you no you're going to miss the
finale oh no you'll have to rely on the
skills alone you won't be able to use
drinks or items
okay um
what's the best way to
kill uh flying enemies again I guess I
can just turn into link really quickly
but we'll we'll help each other out
we'll help
by maybe
[Music]
[Applause]
beos
[Music]
yeah shut the hell up
out ah ah ah
[Music]
ah okay okay easy
easy oh my beos is dead when did you
die do they recharge my energy when I'm
out of the dreams hopefully I didn't
realize if they did that before I think
they did
all right i' I never charged my ever
shots before
[Music]
right
cereal
um a shock in the dark no defeat all the
enemies under cover of Darkness
ah this would be good if you have a
lightups
movie but I mean at least the enemies
seem to line light up in this judging by
the
picture
o my skills alone you
say wait n
[Music]
uh
enemies
oh uh [\h__\h] I can't see them uh what do I
do no what am I even
shooting maybe I should light up the
room can I
[Music]
what's
happening are you why are you not awake
yet wake
up
uh-oh come here come
here how many more that was it that was
it yeah this one took a lot
what that was it oh smoy welcome back
doing a scr scrotch on the tree
yeah you going to lie down here again
baby girl she looks so soft you know
what it's winter time so they're going
to get even fluffier again as if you're
not already fluffy
enough you know you're fluffy enough
already oh there we
go yeah new heart
sick you going to get like Max Hearts
before the game ends
[Music]
oh I might have 100% at the hearts cuz I
can imagine getting two more heart
containers within the
finally uh start with no Echo and no
items allowed to feed your enemies using
only what's available in a dream in 2
minutes these are a little bit more
difficult
usually window coat
yeah at heart pieces eight
eight yeah but two hearts two full
Hearts
right wait what four two
yeah anyway uh wait can I still turn
into link I forgot is that a
thing no uh wait wait wait wait wait
wait uh
oh stop making me
fly
okay immediately have that one help us
does it attack at all I
wonder
[Music]
fuckes does it helps fly all right that
one
huh better than
nothing
ah
[Music]
ah come on
die I still got two minutes it's still
still doable I think oh no the fire
slugs I never know how to kill
[Music]
them no not the stone
that thing's still left wait there's a
what did it fall
[Music]
down oh my God there's a big
ass oh they're so strong ah
[Music]
I'm
dying oh
finally 40 seconds
left the ghoul Spectre at least is kind
of strong to P out the
fire uh with the with the flying can the
flying mushroom take out the slug
can you take out this
thing what the [\h__\h] will hurt
me
no rough rough I got hit too many times
in the beginning
especially just puts out its fire okay I
mean that's what I would want to do
right sounds good to me too bad there's
no uh holes to drop them into I can't
cheese it this time at
all if you get the DI I will eat
everything
else getting that one early on feels
difficult that one so
[Music]
strong maybe if
I focus on the Octor Rock maybe first
cuz that one could be very helpful
[Music]
I broke the stones before I learned
them
uh-oh I got
kids pick it up
[Music]
come on come on Takashi ki wait spawn
spawn what are you
shooting going to
die I don't even want to do this anymore
oh they both died
okay one heart two hearts in a
dream but these are pretty good fighters
let's go
up ignore the electric one for
now
and oh dear oh dear uh
[Music]
can I get only one of
them this is
rough
H all
right doable
doable can you do this you guys said he
will eat everything he
[Music]
better uh maybe shouldn't maybe I should
just be 1 2 3 four how many do I
have
four
no I'm running out of
time but he's kind of doing it po okay
then I can't do anything besides this
anyway besides throwing some rocks down
there
maybe why not throw some
rocks well he's trying his best
Miss is he is he doing it oh [\h__\h] now I
can't spawn the rock oh and he died oh
but I heard
something oh how did that thing
die those are not my
enemies wait I'm already over
time oh
[\h__\h] pull it I was just believing in oh
he can eat everything
[Music]
I was putting all my money on that
boy oh the DI I thought that I don't
know I thought that was the
de
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] all right okay
okay h
can I go straight up and ignore
everything
else feel like the slug will be in the
way oh
[Music]
no come on come with me come with me
come with me
Yahoo learn the
[\h__\h] get him get him get him get him get
him get him get him
[Music]
thanks for putting my fire
out are you doing it don't the [\h__\h]
door
[Music]
already okay he did
it yeah Nom n n n n good job here I'll
help
yeah n n n n
n so proud of
you can you reach him no
oh n n n n n oh
no let me help
you good
job [\h__\h]
no we still have time we still have time
uhoh that let just here really not they
really not working oh
[Music]
no here take care of them I'll throw
more rocks there we go there we go that
should be no issue anymore
right
right okay oh God 15 seconds
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I was going to throw rocks with the
Slime the slug mean 25 oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay wa if I'm really
fast wait which one which one should I
throw at this
lug what's the best
thing what do you mean I grabb this
slug ah into the air
[Music]
I'm just going to ooh this kind of
works
[Music]
please [\h__\h] I'm going to I'm going to
fail wait
hello no
no
a I had it almost had
[Music]
it
you oh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to do
better I don't know man it's
stressful very [\h__\h] stressful
[Music]
man that's going to be the end of me
so I'm sure those two seconds will count
in the end
possibly thank you I know I didn't
succeed that
[Music]
time tappy tappy to stock the SL I mean
I did didn't I
but then I need something to do big
damage so I was hoping for the plants to
do that but then everything was burning
again
[Music]
and leave me
alone leave me
[Music]
I hate you why did I commit to
this why did I commit to
[Music]
this plant does need fire enemies yeah
and what what what am I supposed to do
against this
[Music]
log
okay first step get rid of the big one
hello enemies here Focus
[Music]
did he die did my plant
die uh no no not that one I mean good
try I guess
but oh the bat is dead Yoo
[Music]
okay okay I just
checking I swear to
God I want to
help okay yeah I thought so I don't
[Music]
know I don't I want to help I want to
pick up the [\h__\h] Stone
how dare you how dare you hurt my
[Music]
plant
hello I guess there's no point in
letting you attack
[Music]
the it's so over like I don't
[\h__\h] I
don't it can't be eaten if it's electric
can it
well why now well it gets really [\h__\h]
up
anyway there not enough
[Music]
time what do I do I didn't learn any of
the other
[Music]
Wings can
you
eat I know you don't like to eat
[Music]
I know it's over time now
but is is way to
tight TR blowing at it you idiot please
no blowing at that okay
useless you're not
hired you are not tied
attack took you a
while why are you doing this because I
want the
outfit there's just like
two
painful challenges it's that one and the
ice one besides that everything's very
man
iable I didn't even know it was a link
outfit don't spoiler
me I didn't know I thought it would be
some kind of
like Asian outfit because of the katana
[Music]
shut up don't keep on
saying he's creeping me out now
[Applause]
[Music]
this one this one not not the fire slot
bro not not the are you dumb no you're
going to ruin the r okay now you're
focusing on it you're going to ruin in
my run but
sure probably dying so let me give you a
new
[Music]
one wait are we dead are we dead are we
dead yeah okay uh
[Music]
I'm going to [\h__\h] it up
again I what
[Music]
doing okay
okay he can't [\h__\h] reach it no please
go just be eaten just be eaten
[Music]
already get him
no okay he did it uh do I have to wait
for him to spit it
out
[\h__\h] do something do
[Music]
something is this not is this
not why
[Music]
can shove that golden egg into your ass
my skills
alone oh yeah yeah okay
[Music]
okay don't attack the fire one you
stupid
[\h__\h] the ice one
what am I actually
doing where am
I which one's mine I can't recognize
I can't recognize it anymore I think
only a fire one is oh
ah
huh yeah only the fire one is
alive there we go see there's really
just like two challenges that are really
a pain in the ass and everything else is
very
doable but the ones that are a pain in
the ass a really a pain in the
ass timer is just not enough
time I think only the boss boss Rush is
left there we
[Music]
go let's
go I don't think I get to keep the ice
Wiz it's okay I don't need
it oh
actually would be useful for this fight
maybe okay
we had an easy time with this before but
I don't know I don't remember how to
fight
[Music]
them but I mean an easy time in terms of
the timer for the Boss Rush being very
very uh
considerate
mindful I don't know
I don't have ice
wizard of course I'm going to finish it
today if I'm going to give up now that
would be so
dumb I don't remember what I used last
time whatever I used was pretty
efficient though I think
M we just go for the electric one
then oh dear oh dear oh dear oh dear ran
right into that
um
ow pry simple
[Music]
uh oh oh yeah I can I forgot I can uh
pull that thing out huh ah hit me
twice I want to try
that I don't think I ever did that
originally but yeah that's that's how
you can get him to break as well I
guess but he's traveling again woo
ow what the
hell f is annoyingly
long please don't hit me this
time
okay my R over is still
alive ow
[Music]
okay he's traveling
again I'm going over here no no here oh
yeah I think this is the second phas
beginning of it
right no it's going to hit me oh it
didn't hit me what the hell
amazing and now I got super strong bombs
I didn't always used to have
those it even took me a while until I
realized I should throw bombs I
[Music]
think is he going to go back to the same
place because in that second phase after
that he always goes there no oh I guess
he
doesn't are you going to do that forever
or
[Music]
felt close
again come on let's be friendly uhoh oh
uh wizzy are you dead here
pleas sa
sa oh should I
throw
ah okay it is pretty long what the hell
I did the previous Boss Rush all free
bosses in 5 minutes now this one is
taking over 3
minutes oh okay
[Music]
at least I kind of know what I'm
doing there we
go
okay thank
you 7 hours and we're still going going
hard oh this one I just had that one so
I surely should
remember I this was pretty easy this was
actually really easy I finished that BX
so
[Music]
fast okay I appreciate
that oh appreciate that even though I'm
locking onto these things but okay ah
nice okay when he does shoot the laser
we yeah okay okay he did it he did
it he understood his assignment even
though I'm pointing at something else
I'm so proud of
him
woo he went for the
[Music]
eye yummy
good
job oh he's stuck am I supposed to do
something when he's stuck was it just
giving me a big
[Music]
opening nice one more one more let me
try to there we go here it is ah you
almost had it buddy you almost had it
buddy go for it here it is oh good job
buddy even though he turned around you
reacted so fast reaction speed
op hey and off with
me my wizzy can't get enough he wants
more and you will give him more of this
satisfactory
feeling being a better player than me
honestly wizzy is like this is where he
really shines he thrives in this
[Music]
fight yeah you don't have to worry too
much about these teeny tiny
spiders don't
worry I think he's
dead there you
[Music]
go come on
wizzy the clock is
tiing no
oh no bro you're missing your Target now
there we go one more one more one
more bro you had it it was right
[Music]
there ah that one's hard okay I'll will
give you that one that was difficult
from where you were that is right in
front of you yeah no the other one no
the other ones are turning off funy I
only have four minutes left do something
[Music]
thank God I was hoping he would attack
fter when I bring him out again there
you go is this enough time for
the last boss wait which one is the last
boss that they're giving me or is it
only two cuz honestly it would be tight
if there's a third one and I haven't met
any new other
bus have I oh wait the order is off no
not this one fu I don't think I can do
this in it's a little bit more than for
[Music]
minut okay well it is what it
is well we begin with
[Music]
fire was that me or was that him can I
does it matter if I have attack do I
need the elemental
than well you don't need to shoot his
[Music]
ass I'm all of energy
[\h__\h]
that I don't want to use the full ones I
want to use a small one but I only made
full ones fire bat might be better
yeah
maybe fire keys my
beloved I think I used bats originally
[Music]
anyway only I could find
it
fast please stop doing a go go go Now's
the
Time well oh yep
maybe there we
go um wait what happens now do I just
[Music]
attack what did I do it ah did I pull
out this Helm or so I don't even I don't
remember what I did at that time when he
slammed
[Music]
down
go free free bombs are going to do the
trick for
sure oh he melted the floor too I I
didn't realize that the first time oops
see hello I'm trying to push this
button do
something stupid syy
b can you do something thank you
[Music]
charging oh no is something else better
than the ice bad a there we go they did
something okay we can do it we got
enough time I think okay
okay how about we hit him a little bit
okay get out of
[Music]
there actually let me let me let me
leave pleas thank you oh wait what oh
[Music]
stop I just brute forced
it oh my
God super syion so now we need both or
it looks like more ice than uh fire
[Music]
honestly oh yeah okay then he switches
it now it's ice
and now it's fire
bro switch is so
fast I can't even react that fast what
did I do when I
originally fought him
[Music]
oh now it's
fire
[Music]
ow now I'm starting to doubt if it's
enough
time can I also just shoot him
no
[Music]
no going to switch in a moment I'm
telling you a of course you miss of
course you're going to miss
oh um
[Music]
please
finally okay the other Boss Rush uh was
way more generous with time somehow the
bosses were
way
quicker than these
ones but at least we first tried it
one minute to
[Music]
spare oh what there's a third one of the
Scrolls that's crazy are you going to
give me my outfit
now
oh what I thought we were
done oh no there was this
one
no don't tell me it's
all of
[Music]
them
combined even though and this I'm in
[Music]
never happened never
happened at least we got the scroll
that's what I really wanted I didn't
care for anything else but the
[Music]
scroll what's the trick in here to move
on
forward U maybe it's the the tree stumps
I don't
know is it seems good so far I can get
lost in here too right
oh
Footprints Prince hey yo what the
[\h__\h] that was
easy I got to where I needed to go oh
righty my
man m
same bro
same why would oh why would you why
would I do such a thing yeah it was an
echo
yeah not
[Music]
me oh the hoop Prince lead me to the
liono
uhuh almost forgot about that
one the fraudulent princess gone wait
wait I'm recalling that last I saw she
was ex examining the stone monument h is
that the grave of
Link what will be the future grave of
the [\h__\h] it
princess I don't see a big sacred tree
here maybe it's
elsewhere
[Music]
M the path will open when the six
pedestals are oh okay to crony pedestal
demonstrate the power of Echo and proove
your
wisdom interesting
it's just one of
them so this one's
activated oh no these are the
six signs I
guess that's one of the pedestals I okay
okay why do I need
to what does it have to do with
showing my echo
wisdom see
okay can I even get lost in
here if I got to go all around
[Music]
anyway I ran to the uh exit
oopsie learn it
[Music]
oh
ball ay ancient orb
Echo learned
[Music]
it it's only
one ah I
see okay yeah H they want all of them at
once to I think you need a minimum of
five Echo then right cuz this one I
didn't spawn it so it's
free or do I not need a minimum at
all if I have have to spawn five more I
would
think you're not the liono what the hell
[\h__\h]
it quick quick shoot him now no now
yeah look at me sir look at me Focus
only on the pretty princess
is in front of you very good you did it
what a good piggy you are aren't you
good
piggy my math is Flawless why do you say
it like that did I do something wrong
you make me think I said something wrong
[Music]
stretch lately
no I feel very uncomfortable in my
[Music]
chair but not just because I've been
sitting for a long time it's also just
in
general my body is so messed up that I
just want to
die
uh have I walked around here yet hello
[Music]
oh hello oh you're sitting on the
pedestal but if you're protecting one
how come the other one the other enemy
wasn't prot protecting
one stretch a bit you should do yoga oh
no I mean maybe without all the yapping
yeah but that's just that's it yoga with
all without all the yapping just sounds
like normal stretching exercises
[Music]
uh uhhuh is that kind of indicative of
its POS like location at all if yes then
maybe one is
here where am I no I'm close to the exit
maybe up here then
or is that where the safe point is where
am I oh what was that ah this is NE
there we go could put an armadillo up
here too maybe maybe the goddesses won't
notice okay that feels like it's kind of
indicating the
[Music]
position are you looking for me
cousa so are my other balls going to
disappear if I spawn something new that
eats up those Echo
spaces wouldn't it have to be
[Music]
like
maybe
yeah wait are they going to disapp oh
wait oh there's one
here then I then I shouldn't no they
lost their cost yeah it will I
tried conflicting but I will try to not
spawn anything
then yeah see
it surprising I haven't oh look at that
look at the spear surprising I haven't
accidentally run into the
LL
coincidentally close
[Music]
one coming
back where is it
[Music]
there what
now do something something oh my God
it's a tri
voice
oh deforestation let's
[Music]
go my shoulders and I are off to secure
the path ahead of you um
okay no you can only those sanctioned by
the goddesses can go through
here good
argument so leave this to us and do
whatever else you can in the meantime to
help Zelda is very reliable and I'll be
with her too we'll handle
[Music]
this I need fro
candy and actually I kind of want to go
to idle
meeting spend 7 and a half hours
I go to a
me and then we go Li yeah hell
yeah see you in
the moment minute
[Music]
n
so I gave spoy a
hug she was looking so
fluffy
yeah
okay here we
[Music]
go let's go get that light fin know wait
I'm still down
[Music]
here I yeah but
first
uh where are the
footsteps I saw
some
that that
way
oh wait was that P always there
[Music]
how do
I I is he not here what do you mean on
the way but the hoofs point in that
[Music]
direction cuz otherwise isn't he walking
backwards uh uh
[Music]
okay
what that
way fly horsey
horse where are
you I'm sick of my old
horse I want new horse wait am I not
going back to
H is he going to be here now for
whatever
reason okay that scared me he recognizes
that I've been looking for him the game
recognizes is that way was going
like um I know he's very strong how we
going to fight
him maybe with Speedy
boys don't don't
how oh that's what you do you call in
smaller wolves W oh [\h__\h] he's so [\h__\h]
fast he's going to kill
[Music]
me oh never mind he wasn't as strong as
I thought he was
oopsie how strong his swings were I
thought he would have the kind of
HP that a
breath of the wild liner would have
thank you sorry I thought you were one
of the smaller ones and was wondering
why you weren't attacking but you're
just a nice little wolf
mommy yep who brings in her little
babies to attack for her I didn't
realize sorry for the
[Music]
misunderstanding all
righty so if you go here before the
story tells you to go
here you can't do this like ball game
yet
right and the right and the soldiers
will not be there either
right oh hello wow you looks so
OG I guess he always kind of looks like
this
H you have you you
you you
have you have returned quickly
Priestess so have you already obtained
the Prime energy
the person earlier was an echo of you
she managed to fool this old
tree I the de tree have long watched
over and protected this
Forest one so ancient as myself is not
easily deceived and yet my bark overgrew
my eyes it seems
however while she deceived me she won't
be able to deceive the Prime
energy enter and bear witness to Divine
judgment may you be strong of heart
Priestess of
wisdom what did the goddesses always say
to me courage blah blah blah I wonder if
this applies
now I a little bit ridiculous how
quickly he believed me I thought I would
have to like I guess this is the
proof
but nice of him I
guess ah [\h__\h] in
here how dare you how dare
you no oh will we see the Divine
judgment can you just like send the
solar beam onto her burn her into
crisp oh wow what's
up how you
[Music]
doing want some chuna cha saying that
because
of the potato video that I watched
chah I'm cha wait she's speaking so fast
long long ago before time ever was n
drifted into the vo of nothing this was
a pleasant place for know the vo needed
only
no all was well and it's in its right
order until the goddess K created the
world sealing away n's peaceful
voids n relentlessly toward the fabric
of the world but the goddess's servants
always repaired it
until now now no can return things to
how they were meant to be back to
nothingness it is time time to return
all to the void back to the state in
which n prospers
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
no Divine
judgment
no a [\h__\h]
what
me Link Link Link is it you link Link
Link Link Link hey hey link hey link hey
link
hey C goddesses how dare they insinuate
that I a perfect Echo do not have the
right oh I did receive one if I can GA a
daugh to everything is mine how the [\h__\h]
did that one get deceived what the [\h__\h]
one went to you and the last
one could it have gone on to
[Music]
him unfortunately I do not have time to
deal with you right
now I will take yours
last sorry mic test one two check one
two it was do you think she's going to
do uh oops um yeah I don't know uh I'm
honestly surprised so much for divine
judgment like what the
hell why does everybody get deceived so
easily especially when there's two delas
right in front of you goddesses what are
you doing think maybe give us a test
before you give us your
power I'm sensing something really
unpleasant from here
is this is this what it feels like to be
[Music]
afraid but everything will be fine as
long as I'm with you
[Music]
Zelda all right let's go we need to go
after the rest of the Prime
energy why can't they tell who's who she
got red
eyes and they could ask us questions
that only the real princess would know
maybe
oh not even only questions that only the
real princess would know I feel like the
personality would shine through in the
answers
anyway
oh is this a combination of
everything cuz I see
lava I sense no back when they attacked
you Zelda
and what the [\h__\h] is that on the
back I'm sensing that same presence now
I think the dark mass in the distance
maybe
[Music]
no the Prime energy must be up
ahead come on
Z
yeah
[Music]
okay oh wow oh it's
long it's long but it's mostly straight
up okay here we go
um is this a
dungeon and at the end of it is the
boss could it be considered a
dungeon check this area oh okay there's
one big island over here
ow
CH minute
oh okay he fell
down how are you not wanted by my Lio
how are you not two hit by my
liono disappointing
liono maybe I should make basashi out of
you of course Sashi
me maybe there's better use of you and
your
Hoops oh no
let's see where are we should I check
out this right part at
[Music]
all maybe it's just like whatever come
go up
here
uh there's no doors
no
no uh oh no keys No
Treasures right so far it feels like
like no
[Music]
treasure all leads to the end multiple
popet okay
so looking at every single Corner
probably no
point
[Music]
sh B
oh no not you
guys you give me PTSD now no no no no no
please please leave me alone please I
swear to God I swear to God I'm I'm
going to I'm going to [\h__\h]
more
um yeah save me how did you get how did
all right happy that you can just go
straight through that unbothered
how shall we get over there does this
work uh it's kind of
low do I have to go for the lava area
over
there seems like
it ow [\h__\h]
no why wouldn't you spawn me right there
no clouds may work ah yeah yeah yeah
yeah um it's been a
while oh
but wait wait wait wait
wait uh okay chill just relax oh
God [\h__\h] that's not going to work I was
trying to I should I make stairs that's
why I'm like standing here but it's not
building it on top of
it maybe
I can change it like here and then I can
afford using both the plat uh the
platum okay uh I'm taking the oh oh oh
wait I almost had it I almost had it
though I just needed more confid oh
confidence oh no oh no oh no that's so
annoying
really
[Music]
now they going to follow me
everywhere just take care of them
themselves
annoying but
whatever let's see I feel like we could
we could fly pretty far
[Music]
ah sh
sh I believe in it I know I can do
it
[\h__\h]
okay [\h__\h]
I was trying to get like really far with
it but maybe I'll just jump off like on
the carrots or whatever that
is yeah it was
fine oh no it's going to hit
me I
[Music]
will leave me
alone okay warpy points
[Music]
oh I mean look at that oh we're pretty
much we're right there it
seems where are they
yeah serves you right let's uh kill them
and then sleep in my bed so that I can
heal up before I walk into this fight
it's certainly going to be a fight I
assume all
right that progressed
quickly seems like not missing out on
anything so I'm okay with that
all right here you go I might switch to
different outfit I mean they're all not
the most useful but this might still
just help me the
most and I look
[Music]
cute here we
go Link Link do you think that's me cuz
that's not
me the Prime energy so you were the hero
after
all but I thought it was Legend
of it's link we finally found
[Music]
him well here you are I didn't have time
to deal with you
earlier but I suppose I'll make the time
now all of the Prime energy has gathered
here and a great null will consume
it you talk like an AI like you Nur
summer are you walk not like a
lady oh can you also summon all kinds of
[\h__\h] I
wonder I wonder if it mirrors like
everything I can summon she can summon
in this summon in this point of the game
and I assume she moves pretty fast so
[Music]
I don't know we'll see we'll
see oh nice already getting hits oh okay
you're summoning a
lot
perhaps I I have some ideas I have
several
ideas
um for now
[Music]
where' It Go
no wait I can I can move while I'm
winding it or was that a
bug let's get some distraction out
because I want to wind it properly come
on
um oh you're already doing it
yeah the wolves are really good for this
purpose okay can you bring out some
enemies cuz I I didn't want this for
nothing did I what what's going on she's
not doing anything a there we
go well those are strong though my
octorok isn't oh wait he killed one
actually he did
she's too high I know my octar can't get
her but I was hoping she would just
summon some enemies so that this winding
was worth
it let me
[Music]
just actually I get so much energy here
probably can I hit her yeah
wait
that's and especially with my my
[Music]
accessories I can probably totally
afford to stay as link the whole time
no where's oh my God the [\h__\h] SLO got
me free times thank you
Wolfie what what are
we oh we have he
Retro
Music it's eight
bit that's crazy 8bit music hey
[Music]
yo oh my god did you kill my
wolf I really need my wolf do not mess
with my
wolf oh my God they're so fast help help
[Music]
well oh she she Des summoned them oh
[\h__\h] no she knows I hate them
no sh
[Music]
sh no turn rly my God
okay good job I can get some hearts
here nice I like this fight so far it's
exciting always have to adapt to the
different enemies
[Music]
oh you already fell again falling from
your high horse
princess is her dress color change oh my
god oh those are some strong
boys I was going to heal
anyway yeah I guess I'll just drink one
of these
[Music]
nice nice yeah I think those
energy uh items are definitely worth it
actually never mind w w wof w w w I just
got to a leave
alone ah let me let me help let me help
a
oh God go away go
away that's big big spam
time he's a
Lio uh I mean I don't know he attacks so
slowly
you oh she already changed her
mind I love being ranged
attack it's so op
I could have stacked the another scroll
huh I guess so did I
even equip the last scroll the strongest
one I think I
did let's see if I nerfed
myself uh no I have the strongest one
on could definitely
oopsie turn this one on
link is the time to release you I don't
know if I want to release you you
know then all the attention will be on
you again Zelda just wants to be special
for once why does it always have to be
about
you what stacking them doesn't help your
thing they should say that
if that's the case cuz I feel like a lot
of people are going to
[Music]
try might not
but wouldn't you want to like stack it
if you get all of them it says nowhere
that that doesn't
help let's wear this actually cuz that
might also have a good effect on the
next fight which I wonder will we fight
you link just uh no
right do I turn into you to rescue you
of course I do oh my God the
irony let me out let me out finally
right well let's marry I guess let's
kiss
[Music]
link you're not hurt you're all
right I'm
glad so the hero of Legend and the
Priestess of wisdom are you too and the
Prime energy resides in you Zelda and
Link no observe the last one that little
[\h__\h] each part of the Prime energy is
incred poent so we have to take no
down we've all got to work together to
take back the Prime energy from
no's
being oh but link he unarm now let's
keep him that way don't give him
power no Zelda let's give link
[Music]
no
no no no h
no i' I've also been rying so much on
them how am going to do the last fight
bro if I no that
sucks that's so rude too I worked my ass
off to upgrade them and
[Music]
stuff cuz he didn't have the decency
even to give me his weapons in the
upgraded form uh already to begin with
because like he had them all fully
upgraded when he
died right and then they reverted to its
original unupgraded state
ridiculous I had to upgrade
them really no I don't want what am I
what did I make all the movies
for or can we share like I give you them
but I still keep them
too what what what did I make this movie
for
bro no I don't want link to save the day
you know I don't need him I could do
this alone he could just stand in the on
the side and be ready whenever his
Triforce part is
needed when you return his weapons you
won't be able able to use them anymore
[Music]
also I feel like once we go inside there
won't be any backing out are you ready
to head
[Music]
in well let me just save is there a save
point down
there guess I'll
die guess I'll die right guess I'll die
sorry link I just I'd rather die than
giving you back your
[Music]
things where's the safe point Thank
you
oops oh I guess I never mind that's not
how they use safe points in this game I
I made it this way why couldn't I make
it the other
way and they're even teasing me by
giving me so much energy to charge back
up are you really going to take that
from me I made so many Smo why can't we
share are you [\h__\h] kidding
me don't take this away from
me bro
oh yeah the night that's rearming no let
me keep
mine can we can can I have the arrows at
least you can just be the sword fighter
I
can
please you better be
good I'm a better fighter than you now
probably
suck
hang don't get to use them at the end
yay this link has done nothing in this
plot so far while let him yeah it what
no he should have let me because I have
done so much is why I should be ending
it so um okay I know you're not happy
with this but we're doing this now so
this is the inside of no the Prime
energy is just ahead
so please stop bitching around s the
link let's
go well what the [\h__\h] oh sorry I made
myself really loud this
sucks this [\h__\h] sucks I am so
mad I'm just his
[Music]
freaking little Backpacker again I'm
like his inventory is [\h__\h]
what what am I to you your heal slot
your inventory slot like all of
[Music]
them he doesn't even
talk how are we going to do teamwork if
you can't even talk buddy all right save
me I'm a princess in this dress show me
how you can do it at least you know how
to charge the arrows I will say I I
never did that ever I won't do anything
anymore now I'll just be the bait I
guess yeah I had the fine with that
mhm prove yourself then Pro prove
yourself worthy oh no how you going to
deal with that huh
huh now
okay pretty good now I'm just dancing
around buddy I'm so useless now because
of you why' you have to come
back a line yeah [\h__\h] him up [\h__\h] him up
[\h__\h] him
up H you're too scared to go for close
combat aren't you link you're not much
of of a hero after all guess I'll have
to
help our little damel in the
dress well but I took so much damage of
course you are fine you're always
fine but see who's really
hurt who really has to suffer me
why is it
DNA hello the DNA guess we better split
up yeah um forever
bye is going to be like a side by side
thing I don't want to work with you oh
you need my help oh you need my oh you
need my
help
[Music]
uh attack
get through you have to fly through you
[Music]
stupid sorry link please
wait no don't fly towards
me I'll get the
ghost I'll get the ghost
[Music]
uh if only I had my
arrows I don't hate him but he's
stealing
[Music]
Zelda's Spotlight her time to shine was
in this game and then you train all this
game to to develop your weapons and
stuff and then they [\h__\h] take it from
you so
rude all right let
me nice
AOE Lio Lio Lio Lio Lio over here Lio
[Music]
yeah I mean sure it's nice to fight
together but didn't they could have done
something like that my weapons are kind
of a special copied Echo
edition if you do something with copies
of people anyway and then we both get to
keep
them yeah cuz especially if if we
consider the fact that uh the argument
that the reason
why the weapons were back to its like
lowlevel State could be because they're
not the
OG then it would be okay if we both had
different sets of weapons I would
say but you
know I see I know I there's several ways
to do this but I'm going to do it the
fun way
[Music]
yeah yeah I guess one of the popular
criticisms in the beginning is that
oh Zelda game I thought this was a TA
game but now you're just um giving her
all the link Powers so she's basically
link uh what oh
[\h__\h] uh what
what
what spider I guess
[Music]
where could it
be
there but okay oh but I
can't wait wait no no wait wait for me
I'll come
back I'll
come uh oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] wait it's going to break it is it
not oh it didn't break it
[Music]
surprising oop
I know I can do this better uh let's
just
re evaluate the
situation why the [\h__\h] don't I use a
flying time I because I already have the
spider with me you know so I feel
like let's give it a
chance also we have the Tim as well
[Music]
quick wo
okay oh too late probably
fine
[\h__\h] now the tile doesn't even get
affected by the air flow so we can
summon it a little bit
earlier well what is that for you make
me think I can go up with that but no I
can't
just well I need that
though
oh
oh wait
our stance looks so funny Glide with
bird no
no why did I jump off cuz I was
scared no ow bu my head with
it no that way it's above
me wait no
wait maybe I'll spawn it while I'm going
up no
but wait
skills link there go what are you doing
huh can't even think on your own got to
do everything for
you what are we even what is this
do you need a platform buddy I don't
know I don't know what to do for you uh
cuz this is kind of ah wait you
can I don't
know
oh it doesn't go through
[Music]
though I can send you a ghost but
iies oh oh if I get closer oh I'm
smart aren't you smart
cookie knowing that you have to jump on
that
mhm I'm coming I'm
coming yay we're together again yeah
I'm more okay with this than the zala
that I'm playing is okay with this I'm
partially role playing
her absolute
disappointment in the way this is
going uh oh should I have
healed uh-oh
M doie doie heartbeat
sound here we
go is this the last
fight valid though right I would say so
too
like ah but it's maybe it's a segue you
know because the next game is going to
be about link again so we ended with
link being the hero after all because
yeah I thought this game would teach us
that women can also you know
but it's it's not teaching us that at
all
Nintendo you had one one chance to you
know send us a message here but in the
end the the princess needs help from the
hero the the boy after
H I thought we were going somewhere with
this are we
jumping okay we
are it has
claws
oh more
claws oh is BL BL
the Priestess we still into the hero I
see you tend to interfere how
fixing then again you've come here and
brought the Prime energy directly to me
I don't know what this voice is the
goddesses they have taken everything
from me now I will use their power to
take it all back my little whispery oh
there we go sorry something was uh weird
I guess this is my real
voice yeah I I look so
evil
and dark and fuzzy but this is my voice
yeah the god the goddess make it
scary more
scary the god the goddesses they have
taken everything from me now I will use
their power to take it back
so this is the Prime
energy I am overflowing with
[Music]
[Applause]
power the whole world shall become
Darkness once again
into the void you
shall
[Music]
go now is creating massive
Rifts the town's everyone's being pulled
in I can see it of my bird
[Music]
ey tentacles do we have tentacles now
what about the prime Divine judgment ah
what happened to
[Music]
that I understand it I understand all of
it uh but it went
away yet this insufficient I Hunger for
More I must have
[Music]
everything I must have all of the the
Prime
energy give it to
me
no Reve face reveal this is like what
what is that wait is that famous
YouTuber what was the famous YouTuber
called again I did the face reveal and
then yeah Dream It's kind of sim like
not similar in like looks but like dream
like this is all a dream kind of cuz
it's in a dream world and and then he's
like showing us him his real self and
then he gives us this look and then
everybody's like oh
okay that's youha okay was I supposed to
be impressed or
something well well well well I don't
know if the liono is going to do such a
good job here I I I'll send the wiiz Rob
no too bad I can't shoot my arrows
anymore my [\h__\h] smies are so useless
I can't [\h__\h] believe
it do you want me to pull your arm oh ow
ow ow oh okay I'm just the bait I'm just
the the doll to be
hit with all the damage and the damage
spawn I see how it is yeah yeah I'm
useless now this is a lame last fight I
don't even know how I can be a help
now okay I'll I'll spam a few whizzies
okay hope that
helps now what
now okay why was he hitting so
slowly oh WEA no thought he was running
into
that okay if I jump I can hold him
out
ah never mind I just got to lock on
don't have to
jump [\h__\h] got interrupt
it no no not you
don't hit me don't hit me don't hit me
in the back
[Music]
okay just let me take care why' you have
to ruin the moment again L I had it I
had it under
control I was pulling it did you [\h__\h]
see such
up feel py man
imagine this whole time they're just
having this fight screaming and yelling
at each other no no you want to steal I
could have done it alone no I'm the hero
I've been the hero for how many games
did you see that how many times I res
you need my help no I don't need your
help shut up just focus on the fight
you go
go kitchen or something I don't [\h__\h]
know man no I don't out in the kitchen
I'm to be here
[Music]
[Laughter]
all why is this not voiced guys I'm
trying my best to vo it
but what okay maybe that is what they
want us to do anyway like okay come on
ah he seems to be programmed to run for
it when
I cuz it's easier to cut it are we
supposed that what what is that on the
ground though e he's not really
programmed well for that
situation no don't have a solution for
everything do you pull it cut it I mean
pulling the
spaghetti do
it okay we're we're pretty smooth team
now but I still hate working with you
honestly no you do something he wants to
grab me
[Music]
oh now you now you need my no
no no I
don't it's it's good like teamwork fight
gimmick that's I I'll give that to
them not enough I must have
more I looks so pretty now
[Music]
no no one's trying to escape
hurry let's go let's go wait do I play
him now no way no way no way no way no
way no game what have you
done or am
I can use the piranna in this part oh
thanks for the hint oh okay now we are
playing Z up still maybe we switch back
and forth cuz it did feel
like hey stop my
lemons my
lemons haven't you guys taken enough
from me already the power to defend and
protect myself come
on now you're taking my
lemons why why are you dumb why you
going
something's wrong with my
fish something's going very wrong with
my fish what what is it doing that it's
malfunctioning okay I does it always go
upwards is that just what it does we
have to go under it
to wouldn't my Shark be
better oh God
[Music]
H I need uh I need air
what I haven't been looking at that
where do I need where do I get air um
well now I don't need these anymore do
I what did I collect these things for
what did I what I did what did I do what
did I do all the challenges were at the
end bro
[Music]
wait air where do where do I get air do
I get air for the no no no ah there's an
air bubble Ah that's the first time I
see one let me try the sharks or maybe
they can't stand against the current
actually huh they really might not or no
wait wait we're in we're I think
actually they're fine
oh my god
dude oh my oh what the
hell oh oh oh oh
oh come on yeah I finally got all the
tentacles
off so hard to keep up what if I don't
keep up do I just
get
oh I [\h__\h] did
itaz
amazing give those Scrolls to link I
will he will not even know that I have
them I will keep them secret for I will
burn them in
our uh fireplace at
home they will not not have ever
existed he doesn't deserve them he can
go through his own
challenges at the katana
guy all right we oh I got all the lemon
energy no he's so lemoning he's lemoning
stand back he's lemoning oh no
but you even got those weird
faces what the
hell
who
uh what
now same thing
again you thank
you Music epic oh it's going to be all
of the bosses now yeah
is that enough
cool
ni oh
youing you missed your
opportunity oh the balls the
balls okay I got one come on buddy Link
Link pay attention what are you hitting
thank
you yeah I think he only gives me one at
a time so
BL Rush is nothing now yeah not that
that part that part that
part he's so big so like stretching him
out is a bit difficult the room needs to
be
bigger
honestly do we not have light arrows
this
[Music]
time okay go go go sad turn him all the
way around for that cuz I couldn't
stretch him against the other wall what
do you expect me to do
game oh oh you got this you got his ass
let's
go you have lemon Arrow that's different
it's not really an arrow okay no not
link sorry
link what if I take him with my lemon
arm and oh wow wow wow wow wow wow
[Music]
and throw him into the boys linkink link
now
yeah no I know you can do it I just
don't like that you can do it because I
can do it just
[Music]
fine wa he's back he's back
again do
it why why you aiming so hard is it
because he was flying
oh wo wo wo W wo wo okay that was only
for a little
bit oh god oh wow it feels like kind of
spam
now okay
[Music]
nice okay's disappearing of course he is
uh-oh how did you not get there we
go Link Link Link don't you know you
have to press but butons to get uniced
earlier he doesn't know cuz he doesn't
have the same experience that we
do ow I ran for the heart might need to
heal soon well what do I have my energy
smovies
for for nothing that's right for
[Music]
nothing might as well thr all the
ultimate oh can I
uhuh I don't know I don't have time to
charge them I'll keep on getting
interrupted right where's my buzy
[Music]
no okay one arm easy no
no here it is here it is I it's on the
silver planet buddy what are you what
are you doing why you sabotaging a
uhoh why he always spawns in the way
that his arm is the furnest away from
me hello Link Link Link Link Link Link
not you're supposed to use your
sword very intentional huh okay
[Music]
I'll maybe it seems like we could still
do it without yeah
just uh eventually we'll have done
enough damage doesn't seem like you have
to pull it but it makes it
easier definitely here you should be
pulling it you should be oh
God
Jing oh there's a lot going
on now it's the time L now the time now
the time yeah thank
you even though oh while I'm pulling it
I am an
open an open book to be
stabbed in all directions but I'm doing
it for you
no Keep Me Back My
Sword I want to protect myself clink
clink clink
[Music]
clink spam oh let me go let me go let
me okay I prefer this right
now
guess the music is
amazing very emotional
[Music]
VI
me don't this this spam what is this
[Music]
yo I got another one for you bro
wasted Dodge Dodge Master prebound it
Takashi
Kiana Link Link Link Link Link Link Link
Link Link Link use your sword what did I
level it up
[Music]
for ha get wly
Link Link yeah yeah why do it why is it
not oh he needs to jump for a
damn what the [\h__\h] the
[Music]
spider holy mother of
spam how do you like to eat your spam
guys
in a
sandwich or I don't know what other the
best ways to eat it tell me tell me all
about it oh my God y oh my God how the
[\h__\h] do you not take a [\h__\h] ton of
damage in this
situation in this
battle
hello my lemon is rejecting me
[Music]
okay okay come on come
on no no
no what I don't know pull something else
I
[Music]
guess
be yeah I I saw it in the convenience
store and I never ended up buying it I
regret here here link I have it Link
Stop is he going to like not stop until
we cck his last arm because we keep on
failing at it
now he doesn't give me enough
time everybody likes spam be spam I if
that's so common have you guys eaten it
out of
Japan flame please I back
you there we
go next
p oh
oh ah you want me to pull the triers out
it's mine this one thing you shall not
take away from it spam spam spam
spam
[Music]
spam spam
spam
yay how you like that H how you like
[Music]
that was a very busy last boss
fight they were just
spamming lots of
spam very
hectic give me
nightmare fuel let's
[Music]
go main quest complete
lemon say something
[Music]
y
a
[Music]
yippi
zaa the Rifts will disappear here and
your world will return to a state of
Peace me and my friends came here to
heal an injured
world now that no isn't around creating
Rifts everything will be
okay with no gone there is no need for
us
anymore just like you because link is
back so this is where we par returning
to our useless selves our meaningless
lives but what's wrong
zela you liked it being the protagonist
huh but hell is back to normal me and my
friends have finished our work here and
you're done
too yeah it sucks doesn't
it but that's how it is it's the Legend
of
Link
[Music]
oh well
maybe we
can meet again for sure but we won't be
together for now
but I don't know you can become a lemon
how about that you already became one
just join
us
[Music]
no I guess you can't be a Lon after all
but Sal when I look at you I feel all
warm
inside I think I want to tell you about
this feeling it's like a aot lemonade
madebe with honey it's really good for
your fruit I love to drink it in summer
and winter yeah yeah yeah I'm
feeling thank you D I didn't understand
this feeling before but I do
[Music]
now I I have to go I have to squeeze
more lemons
[Music]
Zelda I'm grateful to have known
you thank
[Music]
you no
a oh
[Music]
man oh my
leg shouldn't have sat on my legs for n
hours they took away everything yeah
well they can't take away my cats
suit are we just not going to talk to
each other because I'm still a
protagonist I don't really talk either
and you don't talk so great what a great
[Music]
couple
H oh link finally you're back I really
hated that girl cuz I am uh misogynistic
piece of [\h__\h]
sorry finally I can make weapons for you
again my lady Zelda I'm so glad you're
back safe and sound and now we can ride
ponies every day again instead of
fighting
ponies oh my child's held on I'm sorry
for all the crazy [\h__\h] man not believing
that you are you when you were you and
stuff that was crazy also link I guess
it's back to the Legend of Zelda after
all which is
ironic it's misleading but it will
continue to be misleading you have your
job back I
guess I don't want my job
what what did he say but what what what
is he what are we supposed to think that
he just said oh because he spoke in the
first place they were like oh
but we don't get a we don't get a
dialogue
no couldn't have been so important then
oh
[Music]
no she still has her
stick that she got from lemon
[Music]
John so we fixed him we fixed him we did
so much for that boy boy and then we
even gave him back his power to
speak
um I mean at least this
Zelda doesn't share the memories of all
the other
zeldas if this was if all zeldas were
all the same Zelda then maybe they would
feel like oh man this was nice I wish I
could always be the protagonist I wish I
could go out and be the the hero and
fight um more often I'll not just be the
princess she can't think that because
like she it's not like she experienced
that much in her life anyway I guess so
this was just a nice little Adventure
but I'm sure when she's older she'll
look back on it and she'll be like man
that was
crazy I really enjoyed my time being a
hero
yeah well
I definitely enjoyed this it it uh felt
short I don't know if it really was that
much shorter than other Zelda games
besides breath of the wild and T of the
Kingdom um but I was blessed by another
Zelda game this year which I didn't
expect and so even if it's a bit on the
shorter side I shall not
complain short and sweet and Compact
and uh pretty well paced I
guess yeah I guess I guess it's well
paced is it well paced I don't
know story is cute I liked lemon
John um didn't like every side mascot in
every other every game so this is also
speaking of not just Zelda games so this
is not uh s not uh um can't just assume
that that was a a cute little travel
companion
mhm um I mean it was kind of rude each
time it flew away and came back and was
like oh oopsie I guess you can't fly
through
here well then I guess we'll have to
find another way that was rude um cute
cats and a chicken My Favorite
Things yeah
um cute Quest I was very motivated to do
like everything uh ran a little bit out
of time at the end I wonder how much I
missed but I think I did a lot like
maybe maybe I didn't 100% the game but
maybe I 80% of it I don't
know what do you
[Music]
reckon but the world was beautiful the
graphics were
beautiful
the okay it the game definitely had some
frustrating moments in terms terms of
like um having an endless amount of
Echoes that you have to scroll through
the Locking on uh to the enemies or to
whatever object was frustrating here and
there and I'm being
stolen my weapons at the end
rude yeah the winding stuff feels a
little bit unnecessary the aaton because
it takes so much time to wind them and
then they get destroyed pretty easily
they're interesting and fun though so I
I guess it's all right
um
uh con coni k what was that was was that
his name was so cute really liked his
story I wonder what the hell like was it
was there really no conclusion to
it yeah maybe it's a lot faster when you
wear the accessory and use the smoothies
perhaps R you stayed thank you good
night wa oh so okay I was thinking they
might show something in the credits okay
okay because that was one of the best
things about the game the best one of
the best story arcs story
Parts I would
say very a very very sweet character
very Charming these ones I really liked
too the
scrubs I mean the the whole spider web
story is it was a bit weird because some
of them got so to say corrupted but some
not so it's really not as much of a
corruption as we've maybe seen in other
places where it completely consumes them
it's just a little bit of an alcohol
addiction so to
say
comparable some can control them lves
more some
less some the crow damn crew some
enemies were bit annoying oh K's coming
[Music]
back and even though the snow didn't
melt didn't he saying something like oh
if the weather is better if the snow
melts but no Snow's still
there kindy oh I want to see their
reunion though show
me show me
[Music]
the
tree wish we could have talked more with
tree I wonder if there's any side stuff
that I missed that I could have done
before going to the last boss fight like
going out again and do more with the
tree or was that really all
fail S three times
wow well it was a long stream almost 9
hours now the horsey so I did get
spoilered somewhere along the lines but
about something that I thought was a
spoiler but we never got told this in
the game
so I think I can take this as perhaps
it's not true perhaps it's up to your
imagination about impa
something about Ina I will not repeat it
now I don't know I don't know if it's
um
officially confirmed or
anything about
perhaps somebody said impa's elda's
Mommy but maybe we'll find out now
what are you
doing
what heck no that's just a a game FY
what are you
doing we hung it up is Del Dead with the
cat's sleeping on the bed and that wand
is up there you tell
that now we're honoring it hanging it up
there the true bro the end
a I like how they made it very clear at
the end here who the real boss is not
Zelda not link it's the
cat
hey
yeah
mhm I
don't remember how I red other Zelda
games but I don't know um it was very
Charming but there were definitely some
mechanics and some fights that
were
[Music]
frustrating the story and the graphics
and the
music and the the aspect the gimmick
that you play with Zelda the gimmick of
like summoning things and then learning
and then summoning things that itself
didn't excite me too much in the
beginning
uh it was fun but it's not really how I
would have originally maybe
imagined a game where you played
Zelda but it definitely made for a very
interesting game where it helps a lot
with the puzzles The
Riddles you can do so many things with
it and they must have thought a lot a
lot about everything like okay let's
make this item but if we make this item
it can be used here and here and here
and here and here and here and here and
here and here will it not break the game
will it break the game how can we make
it so it doesn't break the game how that
can we make it so that it works with
other items Etc that must have been a
lot of uh brain Hort moments figuring
all that out 8 out of 10 7 out of 10 for
you
guys m
plat booms I love my plat
booms if there were magic spells she
could use herself instead of a sort the
link
form maybe for the
future yeah I don't know I'll say oh
what's happening
opening
trailer no okay
[Music]
does anybody remember my ratings for
other Zelda
games Game just got sleepy it closed its
eyes
yeah no no come on you you make don't
you don't you write down all kinds of
things that I
do would have been a nine out of 10 if
they didn't take the weapons from Zelda
at the end
yeah think you gave SK I gave skyboard
sword for the
7.5 yeah TK must have been a 9 or a 10 I
think I wanted to give it a 10 but I was
like hold up I can't be so nice I need
to think more
objectively but it must have been a
10 I loved it what that was 2023 it
feels like it was this
year is it already so long ago
well anyway in that case I'll give this
[Music]
game maybe should I should change the
score of skywood swur down to
seven and then this one
to
eight not 8.5 or any higher because
that is like Tok
territory in order to get there you know
that got to this doesn't mean that like
it's just ttk is just like that high up
there that good of a game that even
though like if TK didn't exist maybe
this would be a 9 out of 10 or 9.5 out
of 10 for me but ttk exists and
therefore we need to rate everything
else lower in general
we got a the the bar has been raced so
we have to lower the
scores it's not that great it was great
to me it was like
so memorable to me and it
was one of the best gaming experiences
I've had in my life so
yep yeah so I'll give this an eight out
of 10
too much
lemon no there's never too much lemon
the lemon was good I enjoyed the lemon
right lemon CH on my
shoulder it's 1 a.m.
now
um
tomorrow we're going to have a members
watch
along uh was it 3:00 p.m. or 400 p.m. um
or even later it was
later I don't know but yeah it's so late
man
bro but I guess I've I've done the thing
I came here for I've done my job my job
here is done oh we're reaching 9 hours
right now let's
go I can't be there once again oh
no oh no I was Tiding my room u u so
good
job ah wait yeah
tonight uh wait am I going back an hour
or yeah I'm going back an hour probably
cuz like our time difference to Japan
will be
bigger
yep so wait I'm losing an hour of sleep
or I'm gaining one I'm gaining one but
doesn't really matter I always sleep
however much I
want nice see I
see probably sometime around like 3:00
a.m. or so
right so I guess the some some time on
the schedule is wrong not the I also go
by like the original time for the for my
time zone but the American time might be
wrong and the jst might be wrong by 1
hour I guess more mon
became a bigger fan of hanuka wasn't
starting it let's go me too me too
definitely me too can't wait for the
iris short yeah oh hi smovie I think
tomorrow we can upload the iris short
yeah now don't feel so yeah it's just
midnight
basically
Mo she knows I'm
ending she's such a smart cat oh my God
God
crazy yeah um little reminder my um
merch my anniversary merch uh Link in
description is on sale right now if you
wanted to get it here a reminder because
in uh I don't know how many days maybe a
week or so they're going to be
[Music]
finished and I just wanted to let you
know and there is some your beat album
merchandise also in the shop so if
you're interested in
that but as I said
November might be some stuff you might
want to buy several
things
so be
careful
yeah Halloween merch I don't know I no I
don't think waa has Halloween merch
I don't think I am in any kind of
Halloween merch
no I think you're
good another 3D Live no Callie has one
on
uh Halloween
yeah K we house another one my uh I
think
um it has been at this
point communicated by several parties
and like evidences out there
um that we
do get kind of a compensation so to say
for the lack of lives in the past years
um I think it's myth and promise and
uh ID first
J
um so I've been aware of this for a
while now
mhm uh but we weren't really
supposed to
say it so until I guess when it happens
then it's
inevitable so that's why I wasn't really
talking about it
but yeah
um I'm I I I may or may not have been
working on something too but it may or
may not have also been gotten delayed uh
I'll talk about this one of those days
when
um in the
future um but yeah for now you're not
getting anything you were maybe going to
get something another one this year but
now you're not getting another one this
year that's okay uh but yeah W will get
another one too oh it's only for this
one year we'll get to and
then we will immediately join the new
rules that have started this year of
only one solo life per year which is the
birthday life um
yeah H that'll be like hitting us next
year yeah yeah yeah yeah but I
mean my extra slot will be now in 20 25
but it's supposed to be a 2024 extra
slot so yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah I'm glad yeah we're getting a at
least that anyway thank you thank you
thank you for watching today for nine
hours can you believe
it uh it feels weird to leave now but I
will take I leave in German we stay have
we doesn't I will rest my throat now and
think about if I eat more chili conar or
something
else thank you for spending your whole
day with me if you did if it was just a
few hours thank you too maybe you can
check out the Vault if you want to mhm
tomorrow Members Only
thank you lemon
Z oh no wait no I can't believe this is
over no I'm so sad it's
over ah yeah wait okay since the
realization hit let me just say um I
guess I'll be playing Diablo 4 next like
I want to focus on finishing the main
Arc and then play the DLC and the plan
is to play the DLC together with some
people
but until the DLC I'm going to like try
to get through the story alone however
long it may
take and then there's always the tales
of arise DLC that I still haven't
played and then I don't know if there's
something else releasing or something
that was on my list that I'm forgetting
I have Fallout always in between a
little bit here and
there where am at no I'm not really I
don't know not really
interested already got perm for Dia
Apple four or what yeah played it
before a the Witter r that was on my
list too yeah but I think with The
Witcher I'm just going to wait for when
it's relevant again through the show
getting its new season whenever that
will
be no not playing those games no no I
don't think think
so
yeah okay uh there we
go visions of M I don't think I'll
stream that no I don't think
[Music]
so it's getting new season yeah I don't
think it's cancelled what the hell never
heard of that don't think so in German
anyway we say up doesn't so see you
tomorrow thank
you
goodbye goodbye
game I'll miss
[Music]
you I'm
sad
man
no oopsie
[Music]
how many more years will I wait for the
next zeldo game I guess we just got to
play an older one here and
there yeah
[Music]
I was just looking at what the [\h__\h] FAA
is playing but even the thumbnail looks
scary so I'm not going to raid you into
[Music]
that what we're getting raided now I'm
ending
no well come with me guys let me show
you where we're taking
you 3 2 one