[Music]
pap
y
[Music]
K KY
K hello it's it's
pavi it is
pavi after one year of sorting out
issues between us we have spr sprinkling
no no we're like sprinkling the drama
you know people are like oh my god what
happened with them for a year why didn't
they play this last year something must
have happened you know yes yes we hated
each other for one year and now we love
each other again yes because it's uh
Halloween Halloween is like the day
where you know people who hate each
other love each other again exactly so
yeah you you you might have thought that
was Valentine's Day no it's Halloween
yeah yay and what better way to make up
other than play a certain game ride that
we've been um you know planning to play
yeah well I know thata played this game
on her own channel
a few times yeah project zero maiden of
the
blackwat I never played it before I know
it's like a game where cute you play
cute girl and you take photos of ghosts
right yes yes that's true that's true
but the difference is cuz um I played it
on my PC but you're playing with the
switch right so the switch one has
motion control so I'm really excited to
see how it's going to go yeah I think
it's it's a cool feature because taking
pictures so I just move it like the
camera I'm I like that idea in general
so I really can't imagine how it
works your s likeed or what I don't get
it we'll see we'll see also I guess
we'll see you told me the game is like
decently long and especially the
beginning is kind of long so this stream
might be like on the longer collab time
side right yeah yeah just head up you're
ready for it right you're ready of
course I am I'm ready to see you cry I
mean what be happy
with five promise is not scary it's not
scary oh okay well I I think yesterday I
have strengthened myself against horror
games so today I will be fine question
mark yeah course look at that it's like
pretty orange girl just like you in the
main character oh yeah yeah yeah what's
her
name oh what's her name
chat How Could You
Forget no there's too many girls I need
to keep TR oh okay Yuri all right I
wonder if the position where I have us
on OBS is acceptable should we like be
somewhere else wait um how is it looking
right now like I would I have us on the
left side but we can go somewhere else
too well we canjust
what I fought I fought from my from my
apartment not from the game no I'm not
going to lie like the this jump scares
me all the time like the the beginning
music wait it your heart is to weak the
memories are coming back okay new game
then let's get right into it set this so
you can see the ghost face no I don't
want to see the ghost face ah I can
already kind of see it here but maybe
like this is better yeah I think cuz
like I think viewers will will see it
darker anyway so maybe brighter better
okay
okay oh damn that face is scary though
work of fiction graphic IM
imagery it's not real the ghosts can't
hurt you Kiara they're not real L
lurking in the deep is the audio too
loud
maybe I'm not sure it's fine for me but
you know what about the Audio Oh Spirit
of the way in the vicinity of mountain
hikami people have been mysteriously
disappearing Without a Trace one such
girl is MI hinasaki she awakens to find
herself in an old half flooded
building wa
wa wa it's all right your fear will have
the same fate as her disappear oh okay
nice nice
one
me it's still the
flooding wobbly water no I know I hate
wobbly water what do you mean you hate
wobbly water don't you go take a bath
there's I I've experienced some crazy
wobbly water that is haunted you know
haunt wanted all right well if you have
experience you're going to be perfect oh
she's
cute yeah she is the girls here are like
really really like well designed uhhuh
and well rendered yeah as you can see no
you'll see later oh it's like she's in
the bathtub but it's the whole room oh
she's
wet the water look at the water she's
cold we need to hug her waa I know
bird
hug n we're fine just a slumber party am
I
right oh this is so
dark I know I feel like raising my
brightness what but my my controller is
vibrating according to the
heartbeat yeah doie doie doie doie yeah
doie
doie I can barely see anything and me
neither oh God somebody's coming
somebody's
coming
oh like honestly I I can barely see
anything either oh jeez I see that
though there's titty ghosts there's big
titty ghosts exactly this is what this
game is about they're wearing clothes
though oh
God I have to get out of here so
true use to look around okay now spooky
titty ghosts
oh there's an open
door okay let's go of may please move
out the direction you want to walk okay
slowly she needs a hug just not from
ghosts yeah let's not get too close to
them you got to Juke them Juke n they're
so slow oh Juke I learned that yesterday
juking very important you learned that
yesterday yeah very important what was
the context uh because I had to Juke a
huge giant chicken that was chasing me
oh oh you're playing that giant chicken
game okay okay okay chicken feet I need
to play that but yeah it now is the time
Halloween I guess
so okay so far so good I like it so good
yeah yeah yeah oo there's light at the
end of the B maybe there's a way out
that
way wow English repeating words uh-oh
uh-oh uhoh they're just swaying like
like like Tall Grass you know in The
Meadows hold z l to run okay run ah
anime girl running
oh oh
no it's not not a Fatal Frame game
without a traumatizing flashback uh is
this a flashback of her
life I I don't know I would be she
getting Visions I
guess okay not that way uh that L that L
wasn't that also for
running
okay I guess when you're like not
pressing walk at the same time
maybe okay if they get me will I become
like
them um only one way to find
out more fluing let's go n is what is
that doie doie doie doie doy doie doie
doie does the controller keep vibrating
yeah
[Music]
goes B bom who
is is this the maiden of the blackwat
turn
back wait where do I go though like the
ah it's open
now how old is this game I'm not sure
it's um it was actually I think
originally released for the is it we
guys I forgot we
uh do
iwi so this is a remaster four and five
so first second third was originally
made for the PlayStation and four and
five was for like the Nintendo uh
consoles oh that's nice of them to split
their children between the
big
consoles Nintendo and
Playstation oh like we're fully on the
water now I
know oh my God she's so cute she is she
is that's the thing that keeps me saying
like the main characters are actually
all
cute yeah no that seems to be
the the most enticing thing about this
game
series oh I mean I think you're not that
you know you're not wrong
oh no the black Waters oh no no oh no oh
no are getting on her
skirt is this the maiden holy holy moly
I think yeah I'm pretty sure maybe maybe
we can be
friends probably
could what what what do you
want okay so far I'm fine I'm fine it's
good that you're here yeah
yeah the ghost isn't scary they're hot
yeah a pretty nice looking
lady no man cuz I swear when I played
this game like Chad was like oh my God
the girls are hot like raining like
admit you have the hot for the ghost
girls and I'm like no I prefer my girls
she disappeared no one could hear her
cries for help as she was sealed into a
shrine in the mountain she gone oopsie
that mountain is where the events of
this story take place we follow the
fates of three
people yudi Ren and Miu Miu just
disappeared this is a terrifying tale of
the
supernatural let's
go wow project zero made another
[Music]
zero it wait did it just say project
zero thought it was Fatal Frame um it's
like a Regional Title difference so um
the USA yeah Europe is a project
[Music]
zero the original Japanese title is like
zero in like the
kanji but in America I guess like it
would be easier to Ste if they do Fatal
Frame I guess yeah yeah Shadow reading
among the residents of The Villages at
the foot of Mount hikami a certain
unique ability has been passed through
the ages this ability known as Shadow
reading enables the user to view Shadow
or trace of someone lost in inexplicable
circumstances this is not unlike the
psychometry psychometry practiced
elsewhere Yi kukata accompanies Hoka
kurawa a woman who possesses the shadow
raining ability to an abandoned Inn on
Mountain
hikami ah wait Hoka has a shadow raining
ability or
you uh I think oh okay seeing yudi could
in time become talented at Shadow
reading hea takes her along on this side
so we're me okay is he so called guy or
or lady I'm pretty sure a girl I think
the characters in this game are girls
everybody's a girl I like that let's
go it's just like a
sleepover a except you don't wake up
a I thought that I'd be scared of death
oh
English voice over English I can't even
cry
oh don't
jump maybe take a step back it's kind of
dangerous there what if you
slip I am alone no no we're here wait
and Wawa I am alone no we're not alone
no you can join
Pabi we can be a trio yes it's fine
right we can adopt one girl no
no it's a dream that's just her
fantasies her dreams what we're looking
for should be in here
okay this is an excellent chance for you
to take the
lead that voice though mhm it's
good nice this is a camera obscure it
will let you see the
Unseen she has like a beauty mark on
her
pretty we're all so pretty oh my God
this is your opportunity your first we
all come from the same beautiful
[Music]
mommy cuz we look similar I don't know
we look similar I I don't think so they
have different last names but maybe it
could be a plot twis secretly m Hot
Springs give it a try I love hot sprs
and Call's Hot Springs press X to end a
photo mode oh oh oh it's just like
camera just look through the viewfinder
there we go this is the this is the the
motion controls yeah the camera obscure
photographs the Nether world a whole
other
world oh nice photo ,800 points
[Music]
move for more
distance photograph both what both
circles s like yeah both
CES I think you can like rotate as well
uhuh if you aren't careful you might be
drawn into the ne world who ah like this
ah yeah like just like a camera or
something those two cires oh yeah yeah
that now free uh a
vertically
ah I can turn it like this okay oh there
is without motion
control okay oh that's pretty
handy you can lock on any Target with
what hold on lock on the target press R
to take for
okay
okay H I see I see I feel like I want a
reset button for my motion control to
say like this is the middle or so but it
doesn't seem to do that oh that's fine H
just to recalibrate or something I guess
yeah recalibration would be
nice you can also turn it off if you
want to I think like there's a button on
the right but wait it doesn't you want
to was making me do this the third time
am I doing it
wrong hold down there we
go okay your eyes were
closed
never oh like it's yeah like it's
locking I think um the game does a
pretty good job um with the tutorial so
I won't really teach you much before the
game teaches you to okay so
yeah okay nice we're becoming
professional photographer let's go I got
a postmortem photograph let's go
postmortem what we're looking for the
token what what we're looking for okay
well I'm looking for this this thing on
the photo but be sure to stay on your
guard come on yeah they're like sort of
like hints I guess okay Loosely speaking
uh plus to display the
map uhhuh yeah and then you can make the
map um what when you go like you know
it's like incomplete but then as you
walk like you complete the map sort of
oh
okay you can also press l and y to open
Snap mode at any time to capture snap
mode that's not working I don't think I
don't think I use that
okay oh welcome to snap mode here you
can freely position and manipulate
characters
ah yeah
sasao always need a mode like this they
have it
another no need for that okay search
theide the abandoned in let's go
wa yay o Missy Missy it's not just a
normal photograph it was taken to mourn
the dead is she following me sent us
here yeah yeah she is oh she's just
really slow it seems that this photo
came from somewhere around here and he
wants us to see she's really
quiet oh um can you turn her up in
settings wait where are settings I for I
don't know if there was set it setting
it's okay we have
subtitles
cute I like it
oh what were you scared I just turned
around oh no do you do you notice that
like glowing white thing it means
there's like something on the on that
side I don't see a glowing white thing
you can see ghosts better than
me no I'm not saying it's
ghosts
oh what why is she like
so no I'll let you explore it's fine a
tutorial area it's no big deal it's
F Peak o yeah who is
this looks kind of manly
yeah sorry this game is for girls
only no men allowed in this house
and you kind of excuse me are not
welcome you stick out like a sore fum
get out of here no no no no he's like n
he he doesn't understand
us uhoh that's so sad I
mean she like what's wrong with you girl
calm down don't be so
dramatic okay like goodbye no comment on
that really I guess no
comment
okay I can send something what is it
hold down that R to find a
trail this what you mean a shadow of oh
no no the token is showing you the way
showing me the way yeah this is um it's
really easy okay if you if you're lost
basically what to do you just hold that
that shadow okay following Shadow is
there more
yeah
okay they always say don't follow the
light but I guess we have to I guess we
need to in this game huh there's some
item to pick up but he went left didn't
he or is it an item to pick is it a Wii
U no
no a
book oh oh she oh you have to keep on
holding it
uh Mount hikami
downfall left in the hallway maybe
someone dropped it oh do you want to
read this oh sure a mount hikami has
long been considered Holy Ground for
centuries people have been drawn to the
many sacred shrs and places of worship
as well as the natural features such as
the twi Twilight Peak and the pool of
purification which have themselves been
treated with great
reverence next the mountain was also
popular with tourists and mountain
climbers for the beauty of its abundant
clear waters and ancient mysterious
forests worshippers and hikers alike
used to find rest at ichu Manor a hot
spring assort near the foot of the
mountain fruit Mansion now the in lies
desolate AO the void of visitors the
mountain never recovered from a
devastating Landslide it suffered many
years ago the shrine road to the summit
was cut off and the flow of the water
throughout the mountain was altered
forever changing the landscape oh oh
even more even more New Roads that were
under construction had to be abandoned
and ichu Manor was buried under a slew
of rock resulting in numerous fatalities
among those lost were the family of ichu
maners proprietor effectively putting an
end to the business oopsie Mount hikami
days as a tourist destination were no
more instead the mountain gain notor Tre
as the suicid spot oh
last perhaps because it was
traditionally a destination to which the
dying would venture the mountains the
mountain is now a place for those
wishing to end their own lives by
extension it has mountaines it has also
become a place for Thrill Seekers
interested in the
occult seems like we are The Thrill
Seekers
now so oh God
lady don't stand there scary wa where's
the here right mountain
is Mountain
isia oh obsc oh wait what was that a
shadow of the
past tutorial I gu in places where the
traces of the past are very strong you
may be able to view Echoes of the past
photographing them will earn your photo
points which can be used to upgrade the
cameras
ooh ooh I was too slow to take a picture
Yeah by a to
crawl oh let's go TI crawling let's go
you like these
angles we love these
angles I mean this room this room maybe
it appears we need a key try the camera
obscure sometimes when they like switch
to a different POV uhhuh um even though
they didn't move just because they
switched the camera angle their boobs
wobble a little
bit yo what I didn't even notice that we
have a very good observation
[Laughter]
H oh yo someone's oh sorry yeah someone
no I just read first okay uh when you
look around for the lens of the camera
obscura you may notice it reacting to
objects which are not normally visible
lock on and photograph them to expose
places or items they have a connection
with find the locations from the
photographs and you may discover some
Clues there as
well uh
okay uh
wait
oh locking and
popping yay your first psychic
photograph whoa what is this so that
means you have to find this
location ah maybe then there is the key
for the door that's the connection
probably okay there's a light coming out
of a closet and there's a doll on top of
a chest of drawers it looks like a wig
head yeah like a mannequin for a wig
find the place shown okay uh to view the
photograph again open the main menu and
go to tokens okay you go on ahead of me
and look for the key to the door wait
for you here you wait for
me spooky okay spooky
spooky yeah somebody said that they're
colorcoded oh my God I see feet feet why
are their
feet wait even when I'm crawling can I
take out the camera probably not right
yes you can and I'm maybe I'm pretty
sure because otherwise why would he
appear yeah right I should but it's only
the other way wait have to crawl the
other
way uh I think he's gone so I think um
yeah I think like first Fatal Frame
games people kind of learn the hard way
but you see um first game people are
always scared of the ghost but people
who have played Fatal Frame before when
they see something like that ghost they
was like oh my God camera I need picture
I need
picture oh the the sound of this it's so
scary to me the it is it is nice
atmosphere right it's so when you see a
ghost once and you don't get a picture
there's a chance he won't come
again yeah
um I mean it won't come again oh so
they're not really
mandatory uh but it's just like
Collectibles and and also um they give
points which is also for upgrading this
is the place though yep no that's the
place okay uh that R to pick
up why why is it so scary to pick the
the key
up
okay uhuh yeah now we got the key okay I
know I know we're going there thank
you
yeah go go
go
yes
so when I take a picture of him and I
then free to he disappear okay thank God
okay so these ghosts are not hostile
they're like for you to take pictures of
them they're just like sightings oh
that's so nice of them yeah so you kind
of have to like uh keep an eye on these
stuff and like that you were really fast
at turning around oh
yeah I I kind of knew there was
something good
coming I felt it hi I'm
backa hea's just like damn this girl's
taking so long I don't know why she
walks so
slowly oh yeah somebody said like the
characters are like Pavo Nashi coated
like the outfit color oh oh
true intimidating
her I want to
hug she keeps on walking
away wait wait no no no no she's just
going to follow
you Dam she doesn't want to be around
you she doesn't like me cuz she wanted
to play this game last
year oh somewhere in this room take a
look
around go go go ghost ghost
incoming um try searching when the
camera uh sometimes it's not always go
[Laughter]
sometimes the sound man the sound it's
cuz you were like holding the Locking
thing it zoomed on her face man recently
my my left boob always like pops
something and it hurts
way what is what what are you
saying my Boop way my Boop my left Boop
what does that does that have anything
to do with the camera of
skura no I'm just so confused like how
did we get here you know cuz like when I
laughed I I felt
it you make me laugh you're getting the
KO Techo jiggle
physics let's go jiggle
physics Urological physics you wish you
were Takashi Kiara
tutorial Phantom expose the cam obscur
will react to items that are normally
hidden from the eyes of the living you
can bring those items back to this world
by photographing the place they were
taken from with the correct angle and
position what what what does it mean way
it means uh you see that blue thing over
there but if you take off the camera
that's not actually real but if you
cannot take a picture of them properly
they will
materialize that's what it means okay so
I just take a picture like
this um I think that's what the game's
saying tilting while holding the yeah
until it's justang you know like that I
think oh you have to rotate it like a
certain way
oh oh now yes oh when it's red okay oh
oh there it is I manifested it secret
book oh oh yeah magic yeah like so
tilting uh I mean not tilting as in like
you know actually tilting the motion the
controls it adds flavor but like
obviously it makes the game more
difficult you know okay like when I
played uh because there's no motion
control I I already used the stick
that's why it was like easier for me oh
this what we came for we shouldn't stay
here any longer than we need to okay
let's go
home let's go let's head back before it
gets dark it's dark I mean it's already
dark what does she mean
definitely okay surely we be another
ghost on our way well I don't know the
game just Autos saved what does that
mean I don't know guys what does it mean
when the game Autos saves
chat
okay look look there's a ghost there's a
ghost really I don't
know was there a ghost maybe it's my
imagination I mean the door closed
that's I guess the ghost doing
psychometry allows you to see the
psychic impr as a shadow uh Shadow
should I look for the shadow
again never follow a shadow oh never
follow a sh wish you hadn't that seems
like an invitation
though there's no ghost behind me is
there I don't think
so all
[Music]
right way the ghost there should be a
ghost
somewhere Shadow her Shadow oh yeah the
shadow over there yeah yeah I I get
you paranoia kicking in oh n oh my God
swaying her hips like that slow motion
hip sway slow motion I know whoa n don't
look don't look I want to take a picture
I want to take a picture I want to take
a picture no hey he's look help me he's
just like bye girl it's all in my head
it's just in my
head and in my camera now it's in my
camera
let's hello to the little people in my
camera they're getting so
handy everybody wants a piece of Takashi
kaha go GH will try to attack will grab
you uh counter counter attack by
photographing oh yeah oh yeah oh oh
yeah does that hurt yeah I hope it hurts
you little the ghost recoiled when
you took a photograph of it maybe taking
more will exercise it for good yeah
everybody knows maybe just maybe
everybody knows taking photos is like
the best way of Defending
yourself I'm going to upload them onto
Twitter and Instagram and everywhere
else on Facebook yeah and people will
know how ugly you really
are photograph a ghost weak points uh
Circle to deal damage to them the Capt
are a rectangle the center of the screen
is your area of attack you cannot take
photos if you are out of film what okay
so okay okay before you
worry before you worry there's one film
that's actually like wait I don't know
if there's like the unlimited film but
like there's different types of films
and they both have different maybe like
strengths in like exercising ghosts so I
would suggest if you just if you're not
in combat just use the weakest fil film
and if you think you can manage to fight
a ghost with like a not so strong film
then you know just basically save up the
better films for like the strong oh how
do I switch it um I think the game will
tell you okay
uh press X
okay oh yeah right now you only have the
uh unlimited
film well is that good does it have to
be tilted is that a good thing what is
this it's an orb ah wait they want me to
have both on the
picture like this yeah that's
better it's
difficult is this also so difficult on
the uh on the uh version um I mean
I didn't have motion controls on so I
imagine it would be
easier what what is
happening what is
happening oh it's it's kind like reload
time there's a Reload time per film
oh okay hey oh yeah yeah more damage how
much HP does he have do I see that oh
he's gone it's
tutorial What Spirit fragments yeah uh
spirit fragments break off when a ghost
takes damage after a time they are reab
orbed photograph the fragments before
you mean the little orbs that were like
floating around yes okay uh okay Targets
in shut of chance when five or more
targets are in view taking a photograph
will knock back the ghosts uh the
capture area will go red during a
shutter chance ah so whenever it's red
it's like good to take the picture yes
okay keep adjusting your position so
that you have at least five targets
including ghosts and speed fragments in
view to trigger Str
[Music]
chance what if I want to go further
back you can but I don't think I can oh
oh maybe because it's tutorial I think
I'm already like at the wall oh
oh it's okay tutorial take your time no
come on take the picture okay oh
oh find ghosts indicated by the spirit
filament the red marks on the side of
the screen what you saw it just now
right no oh God K do you by any chance
have your um edges of the screen like
not properly displayed on your computer
he no my edges are
there wait what which Edge which Edge
of left and right Edge yeah well we'll
find it we'll find it when the capture
area flashes red as a uh ghost is
attacking you you can take a Fatal Frame
sh shot you need to capture the ghost
mid
attack okay apart from a knockback
effect Fatal Frame shots trigger fatal
time when you can take photos in close
succession without using film yes Fatal
Frame shots are very useful when Spirits
are too close to you to trigger shutter
chance uh-huh
yep so are you going to attack me there
we go yes and
then and then yeah and then so uh you
see when oh my god do you see that red
one okay good good good that's where the
ghosts are so when you see it there's a
ghost there okay no problem the camera
obscura only has an effect on ghosts
within a specific range ghosts are too
far that are too far away will not take
any damage oh
the bigger the target Circle the more
damage the camera will deal get closer
to ghost for more powerful shots
okay come here pretty goost a wait
uh no h uh uh no I wanted Reds
no no take the picture take the
picture I have to wait the film is like
reloading now oh okay good good good
good
uh oh W beautiful you're doing great
you're doing great oh thank you not as
great as you yeah he
did maybe you should try the switch
version with the motion controls I mean
I could yeah I think I would have to
play the game from the beginning oh
God okay we are absolutely traumatized
absolutely well he died
though
do that's what I wanted I'm sorry I
shouldn't have brought you here yeah
that's true yeah and you just left
me PTSD
[Music]
forever I hurts
alone no I'm not alone I have I have
waya aren't hugs a death flag in this
franchise though
what I mean not exactly I don't
know oh what is this no they're they're
just touchy it's all
[Music]
right you need a hug in a situation like
that yeah mental support just like what
I'm doing right now why does he have a
knife
he wants to cut the
fruit well done okay what fruit I only
see you
girl don't do it young boy don't do it
young
boy oh his face is
like
psycho Za Za Za Za Za Za
zawa wait nobody's even doing anything
it's like a
ritual yeah oh I don't see a cut yeah I
think it's just um for
show they drown
her he
missed is that you is that him oh no I
for oh my God I blocked this guy out of
my
memory there's a guy why is it not a
girl a guy I just
remembered I'm done playing this game oh
cute Hoka came by a little while ago
cute Hoka what did she want she found
the photo book isoka she did isoka yeah
here take a look look it's the book we
found
oh is there something
interesting is empty no he's like this
is
empty
puzzled he's
shook oh shook I see a baby on the top
left oh baby photo ritual
ritual ritual photo no it's a yearbook
it's a
yearbook spooky your book
Dame oh why learning about Shadow
reading from hisoka yudi used the
ability to retrieve an album of
postmortem photographs from a ruined Inn
on Mountain he also called PE postmortem
photographs the album was requested by a
certain Ren hjo as Ren awoke from a bad
dream he found himself tormented by
uncertainty was it really just a dream
or a suppressed childhood memory this
question has plagued him for some time
ooh
supressed oh y
oh there's other
difficulties oh yeah oh we'll stay with
normal yeah yeah yeah of course what did
you play it with uh normal normal I
think the first time it's just advisable
to play normal I guess okay and I got
some items too herbal medicine and
Sacred Water um I think I'm pretty sure
these are the items you uh got you know
you picked up oh okay yeah
okay next is second drop
find second chapter how is it so far
tutorial not scary not scary do you want
to read this oh yeah it has been several
days since the incident at the in Hoka
is out on a case a young girl comes to
the shop and finds a worried Yuri Yuri
is given a missing person's case
something Hoka forb
why why I'm going to do it anyway why is
it forbidden can't stop me oh what do I
do here ah and basically I wouldn't
really bother unless you need it it's
like a little item shop thing look at
the points that you got from like
photographing ghosts in general mhm I
wouldn't really bother cuz you got a lot
of that items anyways okay uh well then
uh normal let me go start ah start
episode
there you go
okay I think I actually I actually might
want to play this on the switch oh oh oh
like if I'm like you know if I can play
it till the end I want it maybe I'll
just like you know stream uh you know
try to finish everything as fast as
possible I didn't see any restrictions
about uh the ending honestly maybe it's
fine this one all right a few days have
passed since you his introduction to
Shadow reading at the abandoned Inn
since then Hoka has gone off somewhere
and hasn't returned yudi worries for
hisoka but isn't sure how or where to
start searching as she sits waiting at
the antique shop a girl named fuimo
shows up claiming to have enlisted Hoka
to help her find a missing
person well maybe the missing person is
Hoka huh what
maybe could
be oh there's Fatal Frame frame four on
the switch too did you play that one oh
which one Fatal Frame
4 uh no I did not I I know what it is oh
yeah sure I can play that one it's
harder than this one well way needs four
is a mask of the lunar eclipse right I
think maybe oh yeah yeah it seems
so oh nice anti shop
nice you like antiques way
me I like
antiques oh my God that tea that teacup
is so cute the one of the shelves oh
these are lot
o oh I'm I'm working in it is that me
what is
me
hello that hairstyle kind of looks like
the girl in that postmortem
photo honestly in this game everybody
looks like they're
related my name is fi
humo
fi she could help me find
someone
her you're looking for
someone she might have gone to the
mountain Mount hikami hikami hikami hiii
someone told hikami Tomy dowy friend
there why is there closeup on your boob
it's an Infamous suicide it's her arm
Kiara I don't know why Haruka would go
to a place
Haruka maybe that's cuz you pronounce
your name that way I love how they
pronounce Japanese names in English I
know wor that that was was that a joint
crack my
neck your neck I never like crack my
neck but for me it's my shoulders oh how
do you crack your shoulders come back I
don't know I would just like stretch
like and then it would just like click
and then like chat was like was that was
that oops you have to show me when you
visit me oh sure of course oh yeah we're
we're um I'm actually going to visit her
in case you guys don't know
yet sooner rather than later right yeah
sooner yes yes not that much time to go
cuz time is also passing so fast it's
it's November basically now is already
like literally tomorrow would Beth
November crazy way crazy but yeah way is
coming to see me in
Austria let's go let's go I'm excited it
won't be a long time but but we'll have
fun yeah let's make the most out of it
yeah Hoka left a few days ago and hasn't
been back maybe this is what she's been
working on okay she could have left me a
message but
okay he's a gu's room is upstairs maybe
she have some Clues okay let's let's yo
snooping into other people's room can
there be guests here too H guests
ghosts um I mean this house is not
haunted okay E I thought ghost could be
anywhere well I guess I mean if you
think about it that way then probably
but
also they're with us right now we have
to go up they're with us right
now uh yeah I think that's said oh yeah
I love this inside
Garden
no way what do you want to do in
Austria um I don't know what's what's
what's there to do like because no no no
cuz like like like you get it like maybe
like when I'm visiting there you know is
there going to be like some event or
something you know that I can enjoy
probably um I I have um maybe idea you
know you're coming like after Christmas
but maybe there's still um some
Christmas markets open I got to check
like win hopefully oh my God I see the
jiggle physics yeah you saw yeah yeah
yeah I saw hea gave me this room when I
moved in it used to be her bedroom it's
been a lot since I moved in but I still
haven't unpacked
anything oh just like me for
real what you you have unpacked
boxes oh I mean not at the moment but
just like you know it takes me a while
to unpack stuff me too me
too he so oh this is so
nice it is a really nice house though
honestly is that a door no okay okay oh
my God I hear something yeah some weird
like a TV or radio so grum
noise oh what's this room like a tea
room room's so neat though wa Japanese
style yeah traditional Japanese style so
nice with tatami mats on the
ground even the bed is kind of
interesting yeah has that Vibe looks
like it would not be soft which is good
for the back letter from fuyi an open
envelope has been left on a desk the
sender's name reads fui
heo
fuu the missing person reest maybe it
could provide some Clues as to where he
took got and for he went they want to re
this go go Dear Mr Cawa please find
heruka she went missing over a week ago
you do still take on missing person
cases don't you I've contacted the
police but they no help they say she was
probably Spirited Away the police that
what the heck W police oh guess she just
I know got snatched by
mean she just on you know what anyways
who says that what's next Haruka
wouldn't have gone anywhere without
telling me I'm certain something bad has
happened I can handle my own grief but I
can't send the thought of her suffering
somewhere what if she's waiting for me
to find her I'm worried sick what if
she's waiting for me to find her it's
like in this case maybe but generally
that sentence is like what it's so this
person is surely waiting for me but and
they're they're not you're just like
hoping like literally please come home
you know
why Haruka is still alive I know it but
something has to be done and quick
remember when you found that precious
picture of me and Haruka I was so happy
to have it now I need your help once
again okay I look got like what oh there
we go oh look pretty cute two school
girls with their uniforms they look
cheap
what what do you mean the uniforms look
cheap they look like
cosplay well maybe it's cosplay you
never know I mean why wasn't you wearing
uniform earlier May it's
cosplay they put it on for taking some P
probably I
know it's so looking shy and another
girl they look close that's how we
have we have to save her waam to look
yes let's go let's get her back to
Mountain he come again same
place uh I guess yeah cuz this mountain
has like Mount Hami all the events to
creepy events place where many come to
take their
lives I'm positive that for youi must
have come
here yeah we'll figure it out I mean
we'll find out sooner or later only when
the Sun goes down yeah cuz
obviously don't go in it's bright I know
why it's got to be
dark got to be dark you know that's when
it's the best time those cheap uniforms
perform well when wet yeah what yeah cuz
they get more sea frough and higher
quality uniforms right yeah cuz those
are thicker thicker material than the
cheap ones which is just like 5
mm what's 5 mm
wait five 5 mm I don't know maybe even
less maybe even less oh my God I should
be able to use this picture to
find to find her tray okay like this
game is called maiden of the black water
it's like water so you know it all
matches up yeah lots of
water it's so fast wait the trace is so
fast oh w w wo photo photo photo oh
maybe you can't I don't know I don't
have you have a camera why not why would
I come here without the camera cuz she's
stupid no well I guess that means that I
guess it means you don't have to care
about photographing ghosts right oh
that's great that means it's just going
to be a walking
simulator pool of purification
okay ooh again
water get purified
girl let's go oh wait I will I want to
um enjoy the scenery yeah yeah yeah uh
you Canad it's not bad there's a water
actually pretty enjoyable especially
like right now there's no threat right
cuz you don't have the
camera I saw her wait did you see it I
did I
did I want to look
here oh yeah so like um
oh oh the road has collap and some Stone
stairs are cut off it must have been the
landslide The Old Road seems to carry on
up the edge of the cliff okay just
flavor text so the thing is like um the
um the silhouette always tells you where
to go but uh that just means like but it
won't really like tell you to like oh go
pick up this item on the other place so
sometimes you can explore
too oh and not immediately follow them
mhm at least that's what I remember okay
yeah cuz I felt like I had to check that
out that was
important
mhm o oh this would be nice to like walk
through during the
daytime pretty so much
water why does she always why does she
have to go night time
yeah only show up at night time I guess
but we're looking for is it a or what
maybe the brochure
oh move move to break its hold on you
okay sometimes a ghost hand will appear
when you try to reach one object why
yeah go
away that rele set are the right moment
to dodge it if you do get it's pretty
fun okay I thought you know I was um
automatically shaking my controller
hoping that motion control would work
but it wasn't working it does not work
okay so we understand no yep no more
grabbing a tourist for sure I wonder if
F he dropped it has a map of the
mountain nice
oo and then so I guess this means if you
check the map it will be all unlocked
I'm not sure okay it looks nice so this
is the way from the pool of purification
to the unfathomable Forest got
it uh
open oopsy
uh
map oh no it's not unlocked H oh just
this one okay yeah oh but it shows me
I'm here oh that's cool though this it's
so big I think X
is what a treasure a treasure well let's
go no so we go up here to the shrine of
Dos
maybe ah the and unb Ah that's where you
have to go oh there so much stuff what's
at the
top Twilight twil Twilight Peak Peak
content oh it's like forbidden Valley
like why even bother going there you
know ephemeral station like okay let's
stay away from there there's a cable car
there is is it a cable car or like a
tram though I think like a tram it's
this cable
car okay
uh wait which way which way let's ask
the ghost thank
you zooming through the
forest let's get through
this oh
item oh something
on what what what's that
reaction no cuz uh that looked like the
camera to me oh never mind it's not a
camera let's go o purifying
Amber wow pretty Co that light the
fidant flame they dry you and remove the
taint of the black water
oh the wetness glass the lower right of
the screen will light up when you come
in contact with water ahuh I have to get
dry get Dr you become an easy target for
malevolent Spirits is that
so uh okay I'm not very wet
now yeah oh my God even though I walk
through a
waterfall
somebody was
screaming oh she miss never was there it
ghost I heard the screen but like I
didn't see
it did somebody jump from the
waterfall I I think so what is
this herbal medicine yay best item hey
but like there's I can't even use my
camera so like yeah so I mean no big
deal yeah damn you will notice anything
way now I'm like noticing only half of
the
ghosts which I think is better because
then I can't get scared if I don't
notice them yeah what is
this
ghosty okay ghosty
[Music]
ghosty so many
stairs so many
stairs oh another item yay what's this
oh it's another p flying Ember why does
she always pick it up so
slowly I know it's so
scary yeah it's always like I need to
get mentally ready for like whenever I
need to pick an item you know I I guess
I understand why because they sometimes
they ghost grab it so they want you to
have like this moment of can I pick it
up safely or
not yeah I guess so just just the deaths
wanting to mess with you
honestly you're only half wet so I think
you're okay
okay oh oh there's something in the
water yeah
B what is
it ooh the cam in the water it's broken
too bad can't take pictures
now there's no way I can use I got some
news for
you I got some news for you I can't
believe old cameras like this can be
fine after being in inside a deep water
for such a long time
to like well maybe it's just like you
know I'm made in
Germany yeah made in Germany old is not
effective at exercising ghosts and it
takes a long time to load great thanks n
no no it's better it's better than the
the unlimited F of trust doesn't sound
like it you got the stun lens a lens
that forcibly staggers to photograph
subject to use it equip it to your
camera obscura and press Y when you have
enough spirit Power it's done okay you
got the switch upgrade this allows you
to equip and take pictures with
different
lenses uhuh switch okay you can now use
that I don't want
to no wait don't I have to equip the
thing yeah put first but it like ah see
there's like control select film but oh
um remember yeah if um a good habit to
make is like if you're not fighting
somebody just make sure it's type seven
so you don't like seven is the unlimited
one okay
yep um well I don't see anything now
unless behind
me no I don't know there's nothing
here
maybe they just want me to uh oh okay
what oh what what where is it
where
okay yeah die second you can exit the
camera well you know if you need to
reposition
ever the red the red oh there
oh yeah yeah good picture good picture
let's take this one oh oh yeah oh when
you switch lens then it's like maybe I
can uh uh ignore
the the the the the the time between the
yeah yeah oh
ah yeah nice one nice one hey get
wrecked nice it's died wait there's
something here okay who are
you give me red give me like more red it
doesn't have anything any other orbs now
there are
orbs uh
ah
ah I nice go go go this looks
likea
what I've been carried here by the
current this meansa is on the mountain
too but I should focus on finding F he
first she can't have gone too far okay
it's over yay yay easy right nice
pictur wa can I put this on my on my
what on my what's it called my my my CV
or so now that I'm a
photographer professional Spirit
photographer
yeah I I I'm honestly I don't know if
you saw but like sometimes on Twitter I
upload oh hi oh I should have taking a
picture uh I upload all my food pictures
and like they're really good oo yeah
yeah I sometimes you know see like you
cook stuff and then you take pictures of
them yeah I I need to take more I need
to post more food pictures I have like a
ton but I never posted yeah but are they
cooked by you waya or are they just
ordered
food
sometimes only sometimes when does way
cook food when I was in Japan I cooked
food and nobody believed that I can cook
because I posted rice with tim tams oh
my God yeah I think I saw that but they
say I got to go right but I'm a jrpg
player so I know I got got to go left
first
let's go German
efficiency there must be something
here I mean there could be there's
nothing
okay okay there was nothing there no
loot okay why is this white thing
showing over um that means there's
something like an uh usually an item
that's what I thought okay that's what I
thought it was like leading me in this
ah there ah cuz I was okay it was right
there it's leading me in a circle yeah
sometimes it gets confusing when it's
like too close to you on new
film nice or is the same ah it's the
same but like more of it maybe mhm okay
that's good stocking up on
Films okay do you ever run out of films
way when you play this game no because I
have very good film management
skills okay nice Flex wait there's it's
showing me there
again oh
message there's a Tor note lying on the
ground it looks like f himos oh no
reading time wa I looked into Mami it's
always been a spiritual place not
spiritual as in holy but spiritual as in
filled with the spirits of the Dead
maybe that's why it's a suicide spot
heruka wouldn't go to die alone though
not without telling me I thought she was
going to say oh not without asking me to
go together the book said people get
Spirited Away to the mountain they get
called towards it and disappear alone I
read how we calls the people who are
perceptive anxious Meek and who lack
family my heart skipped a beat when I
read that doy doie doie doie it was
describing heruka perfectly she's so
kind and accepting she always opens up
to me me she's alert even when she seems
to be spacing out she knows what I'm
thinking maybe she was Spirited Away H
don't say that but where do people go in
they Spirited Away well there's only one
way to find out I mean what the more I
think about it the scarier it gets and
the more my heart starts
pounding okay doy DOI waku waku Spirited
Away oh oh we're going to the forest now
I felt like I was in the forest this
whole time but this is the fathomable
Forest
unfathomable by the way like um you saw
the vision of the ghost right um
sometimes or most of the time when that
happens you can pick up your camera and
take a picture real quick uh okay you
mean like when the the ghost was jumping
down the water fall ah oh that too but
uh remember the cut scene you saw the
girl go through the
fence oh
uhhuh yeah you can take a picture of
that okay
like okay like I'm I still as a new
player I need to like get a feeling for
everything that I can take pictures of
and also not just watch but like
act take it easy take it easy yeah but
like especially as oh sorry what the
girl that was falling jumping down the
waterfall that especially that that
happened so fast how how do you take a
picture so fast uh I mean I think that's
why
people no no no no go go go go go go go
what go Camera Obscura press
X there was someone by the shrine and
the other side of the river was I didn't
see what but um honestly it's not really
a big deal that's why this game has like
a replayability value um I think almost
nobody like can get 100% first try
especially like when they're playing
blind yeah so that's what you know blind
Joel I am playing very BL blind in
double meaning I am blind when I'm
playing this game not just because it's
the first time but also sorry it can be
overwhelming for
[Music]
real for now just I think it would help
you know how the ghost give points right
yeah so maybe right I don't know if
you're scared or not but some people are
scared of the ghost that's why they're
like ah you know but if you put your
mind into like being a hunter think of
them as money I need currency when you
see currency on the floor
no I did it I did it wa yes one more
once more no okay when you see currency
on the floor you pick it up as fast as
you can get items okay pick it
up another
note uh I need to sneeze you
read I don't know what to do now that
hca's gone missing I can do anything on
my own it's like I can't breathe
we've been close since we were children
no he no she's gone I realize how
important she is to me how
Irreplaceable oh huh I can't stop
thinking I could have done something
when she left that day maybe if I said
something I could have stopped her from
going the waiting is unbearable it
should have been I should have been the
one to disappear it should be me
dramatic if heruka comes back there's so
much I want to tell her I should tell
her how how I are they friends or
siblings I should tell how I really feel
before we end things before we you maybe
she's already known for a long time but
I'll tell her anyway I have to tell her
I think they're labu Lau yeah I think
they're like friends for you for you he
has been here I can use his note to pick
up her Trace again
okay oh I got it I got it
wa that's the spirit like you
immediately see the prompt and it's like
okay oh oh so good H I forgot how to
take a picture oh oh oh yes Fatal Frame
oh fatal Fatal Frame Fatal Frame oh
there's so many there's so
many ah a it's so
[Music]
wobbly what I do he's touting
me is he gone is he gone you
fight I want um
you you you can exit the camera by the
way to reposition if your position gets
bad and just run away for a while okay
oh well this is fine this is fine if you
need to if you need
to right I'm
dying no you're not see you still have
HP it's fine it's good it's all good I
accidentally opened the menu or what's
going
on I'm not done
ah
yo nice
pictur can I get a can I get a smile
please for the
[Music]
camera come on smile maybe a little wink
with your pretty
eyes yes go go oh you have so many faces
oh my God the three faces of whoever
this
is he's going to closer okay uh yeah
this one's good this is good oh
beautiful beautiful this one's going
into a
magazine go
away no he's so close go
away yes let's go that's the way but I
got to finish them yeah yeah you have to
okay what is this purple
thing it's a cute color come here I
challenge you to a photography battle
where let's
go go go go go this one's tough a toughy
a tough
cookie
away
away nice nice nice nice there we
go it's still not done now we're done
okay we're done yay nice Paparazzi
mentality let's go oh no Pokemon Snap I
think it's done this is Pokemon Snap all
of ghost here yeah but that's free roam
I guess right you can move and
reposition
yeah I like it so far it's kind of fun
it is I thought it would be more of it I
got to pick up the item fun yep you
should will I be a ghost again I'm ready
I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready yeah
ghost ghost ghost instead of being like
scary you'll be like oh I got a ghost
free money for
items okay just more that's the
secret there was another item over there
somewhere yeah okay ghost ghost ghost
ghost no ghosty ghost ghost no okay he
film they you fil oh 61 ooh 61 61 is a
better it's better okay
is it like the higher the number um I
can like remember that it's better yes
yes it
is but I think like uh it goes without
saying that the B the more powerful it
is the more scarce it will be oh yeah
okay are there like boss
ghosts um yes oh so I keep the powerful
ones for the boss ghosts mhm for me
personally uh the rule of thumb is just
to use
if I don't know I like using seven if I
can for like the stupid ghost and then
14 but then if I feel like oh my God
this is so tedious then I switched to 61
M I see okay that's why I like I'm I
think I'm just too um
stingy I can understand I would probably
do the same I'm such a I'm just a
hoarder oh a bottle of Sacred Water
Sacred
Water rest my health full heal B during
the battle or or just in the menu of
item menu anytime and you open the menu
so okay so the battle the the photo
battle stops for a moment yep okay I
feel like there's going to be a photo
chance anytime
soon
oh a I was like what is
that
little bit too late yeah it's okay it's
okay it was so far away I think like um
also like honestly I think the more you
like Miss photos like that the more you
be like oh next time I need to be fast
or something now I get it that this one
I did right before it felt like it's
just some random
cutscene yeah it's like that wait did we
just miss a few yeah I want to go here
yeah you can
it's just a Fatal Frame experience
honestly so if like if you're
overwhelmed don't worry like everybody
does get overwhelmed when they're like
first game okay okay More
film after this you'll be a Fatal Frame
Pro so true okay I don't want to go
straight to the doll thing I want to
pick up
items like these one
I would do that
too there we go another somebody has
like somebody has a hole in their
backpack oh no no I mean like cuz they
keep dropping all these items oh what is
that is that an item yeah it's an item
okay it's on the other side oh this one
I can pick
up yeah yeah got to be like so cautious
and looking around for a ghost all the
time all
right oh
yeah
and Nice Shot nice
shot good good what what what do I do go
away how do I stun again
there so if a Ghost Attacks you you have
to Fatal Frame her to make her get off
you she's on me again where is she oh
what's going on move
reposition okay a family picture
beautiful
nice go back to the river you came from
yeah go for S you stinky stinky
ghost was off that filth off of you my
goodness oh my goodness the cheap scho
unform cosplay uniform no so many
cosplayers M nice tilt yeah we like a
nice come on come on
okay good
shot good you like
that go back e wait are we done
yeah yeah go back to the
Netherlands to the Netherlands I don't
know the lands where you will never be
alive again I guess
so where's my where's my
trail your ghosty ghosty Trail
y oh well nice what these herbal
medicine more healing yep do I need
healing
um I don't know I'm usually very stingy
because like you can pause anytime
anyways okay wait but this is like I go
to the map like
this how do I go to like healing menu or
so uh I think it's like
items you know that menu that you did
earlier I don't know the controls of the
switch I hear the the Y okay oh my
health is at
half yeah
I want to
heal I want to heal let's go uh
completely and somehow
somehow oh that was only a little bit
okay okay I see I see ah I think that's
plenty okay now time for some action I
guess let's visit the shrine creepiest
Shrine I've ever
seen oh gosh I'm actually terrified of
like these dolls so this uh yeah this
this was scary to me that is
freaky more dolls freaky freaky
ningai
[Music]
hello not the best fre go not the best
all right it
counts yeah okay I got it down wait
let's
go okay she she opened the door I shall
open the door
oh yeah follow oh it doesn't look like
they went into the
shrine n okay oh but there's a note oh
but there's a random note sometime
somehow my
pH why is orange though usually it's
white right yeah more iive maybe give me
the
note ring let's go heruka and I have
been close since kindergarten o
childhood friend we sang a song together
at graduation it was called the song of
memories heruka and I looked at each
other when we sang together I'll never
forget that all right I think about
those times a lot lately they were the
best if I even hum That Tune I start to
tear up
a
oh that was not a picture opportunity it
seems oh was it wait no I couldn't like
disappeared I I don't know either I for
I don't
remember that was a memory maybe and
more so perhaps
uh okay so now now we actually walk in
now we go
outside I didn't get all of them
maybe I would have gotten more points if
I oh one more one more one more it's
loading too long yeah that that that's
that's
that's do all the films load so long do
I get like upgrades
ever um the stronger the film is the
faster it loads I'm pretty sure
okay the loading is so agonizing if you
miss something like that
I but better than nothing oh better than
nothing I sense something
that's why also like in combat uh you
shouldn't um you know it's like not
really advisable to spam it's like
better to like try to get like strong
shots okay so you can
combo did you know if you um score a
Fatal Frame you can get like free hits
without consuming film that's how you
conserve film what what does that mean
what what what okay so basically when a
Ghost Attacks you um and you get really
close to them and you take a picture you
get Fatal Frame and they get knocked
backed and then you can immediately take
shots after as long as they're in that
Fatal Frame um duration and the and the
shots that you take then do not consume
any
film so I didn't have that yet
H yeah the to the tutorial actually
taught you that but it's okay I didn't
do it yet though yeah but um I think
it's a little scary
because it's like you can can only do
fatal frames when the ghost is like
super about to attack
mhm it's like a Parry an immediate
counter I guess yeah just a picture when
they're
super
pro pushed woman birth yeah someone
pushed her
down okay that wasn't even
suicide damn it was murder it was murder
I thought she up she jumped cuz I missed
that girl as well oh I like it here I
can die alone here there's no one to
stop me I can take things slowly a
peaceful dignify death life is nothing
but misery and suffering I'm sick of it
o I'm starting to feel like I should
have put some kind of like disclaimer in
my chat like a trigger warning for
suicide I
probably this game yeah cuz like the
whole premise of the game is like this
mountain is where people like you
know oh guys it's just a game okay
oh there's someone there but it's just
her it's not a ghost it's just literally
her it's okay
it's okay then uh wow girl where is or
or is it she's not
reacting no maybe she just she just has
airpods
on she looks pretty to me yeah she's not
transparent slow
Pera she's here on the
mountain have you seen
her no but she's here okay I okay I have
to find her she got that
radar whoa
ooh a is like next to
her
or oh
what
why is this something that
happened already I wonder it's just a
vision skinny
diing not skinny dipping someone said it
in the chat they have cosplay on made a
promise oh okay it is a vision of the
past they were going to die together but
two survived okay
yeah
[Music]
oopsie yeah they are supposed to wow
this is
dark hey they want
to yeah why
didn't we see like a girl in uniform
maybe it's them true I'll go and look
for
heruka as she's fading I know I was like
[Laughter]
huh let's go back girl come on come on
come on girl let's go don't go near the
water it's not good for
you oh oh we you go should I write a
Trier warning in content warning in chat
like in oh yeah you can sewe the whole
games premise is sight not sightseeing
um
exploring searching in a mountain where
people uh often oh no no no in a
mountain that is a suicid
spot okay wait I need to and then fewer
discretion advised wow sounds like you
you wrote something like this
before so
professional did you send it
off yes I don't see
it a there it is okay
pin
comment
a pinned okay everybody is feeling
comfortable
now okay where are we going let's ask
our ghost
friend he's not
there he's gone my ghost friend is gone
wa ghost wait what do you mean I mean
the the white oh the oh the the guide oh
is he
gone gone they just want me to go on my
own okay oh I think you're kind of
supposed to lead her out of the mountain
mhm cuz we got to go we got to go all
the way here
so yeah yeah maybe you have to lead the
map because like the ghost is the spirit
he doesn't want to
leave true
true is this the right
[Music]
way uh
yeah yeah it is the right way we got to
go through this big
or can we go here probably not I think
that's uh severed Bridge though yeah
ruined Bridge it says you got to go a
detour through the lake the Minami Lake
okay oh something's going to happen
there ooh nice crawling in the
forest e my knees hurt from all the
[Music]
crouching oh what what what is this
thing I'm
sensing ooh I don't know no ghost
appearing now
what okay oh oh that just summoned
[Applause]
him he do something my God useless you
know what I would do use her as bait
yeah but I'm a terrible person I don't
yeah you know don't follow
me okay is he dead
oh
oh for for wait what what what is going
what no what what is this what no
no
what tell me before I die
way what's going on what's going on you
have
HP I can't run so well wait no I want to
get out off the camera okay good good I
want to heal I want to heal I want to
heal wait no it was
here my God what's happening suddenly so
so
chaotic yeah I know yeah it's children
children are chaotic they're also really
short so they got like you know the
mesent is different you
know you little you little
they're running they're running ah
ah go away from me go
[Laughter]
away this
is Musashi
Musashi okay calm down the kids are not
calm down they're not even trying to
attack me right now this was a good one
that was a good one yeah nice Duo fall
oh she's coming she is's coming she
wants a hug no Huggies for you social
distance
please and you whippers Snappers
cute no no no no no
please oh my God it just hit me that
people are saying y LS as in you little
oh
yeah you little get out of here
stop stop circling
me oh nice oh oh that's a good one
powerful
shot you little where who do I
shoot are you done they're done
okay she's run you can't catch me yes I
can oh oh oh
oh oh my God she's just like circling
you yeah
oh why why you got to make it so
complicated
[Music]
okay no more running I guess what the
hell was
that nice nice let's go so she went that
way right here to the right uh let me
check the
map we're supposed to go here but she
went she went yeah but she went there
girl not listening to me
girl
huh
okay good good good good good oh should
I heal
again nice you got plenty
okay oh you
here she loves you ghost it's locked you
can't go
in no heruka she's here no she's
not don't you
dare follow me is she follow
H yeah yeah she is okay let's go she
creeping me
out creepy girl heruka she's here
[Laughter]
and oh my God she's so
slow she's going to run away from me
again
anytime oh
yo that scared
me oh my God wait so that's the bridge
that's like broken y That's the ruin
Bridge so you have to turn left now turn
left and then right way knows how to
Direction yeah sheesh
sheesh uhoh oh well this bridge isn't
ruin there's an item there
though was going
get
there's something on the River Bank
though okay if they tell me like that
then I guess it's like from how I think
it's like very important
mhm ooh
Vision oh but also like you know um if
you're run you'll be less
scared yeah
yeah is that true I mean honestly yeah
cuz like you get through the areas
quicker right yeah but then maybe I miss
some ghost don't look at yourself in the
water that's
creepy that's
creepy no no can I take a picture oh oh
wa what kiss no bite no kissy drag into
the water Kissy Kissy oh oh so that's
how her uh the flow of the water brought
the camera all the way down
M well do we want to pick it up where
are you I you hey yo it started raining
oh that makes me wet makes you wet
exactly this was se's favorite it must
have been carried here by the river just
like the camera
obscura I hear someone singing or is it
me cuz I'm
scared no I don't think it's
you you got the evade upgrade this
allows you to detect Frets capable of
being
dodged eh okay I don't even know what
that
[Laughter]
is e my my wet uh thing is filling up no
yep because it's raining so you're
getting wetter by the second that's a
problem wait what was that was that wait
was that a ghost like that cuz it made
like ding yeah I didn't see
anything what did you see way oh just
like a ghost like far off in the
distance I don't even know if you can
take a picture or
[Music]
not should I dry
myself um I think there's no use because
the rain it's
raining the rain is
raining
yes oh okay this way oh even more water
let's go let's run even more
yeah M oh it's getting louder do to
singing I think it's
it's her she's it's
her no never
mind yeah it's her it's her
creepy creepy
girly
H going to use that on me or on
yourself oh no no for your head
no and ever
oh my god oh jeez do I have to fight her
now her ghost
immediately oh she gone though maybe
it's a
vision of um what you call she's already
behind me
wait look behind rate is pretty high
look behind
you
[Music]
no oh she
moves oh B wrong
button I I don't think I DOD
properly you uh you'll know when you
[Music]
do
okay it did and now I I did it yeah you
did it does there have to be a prompt
for it yes
okay oh that would be a good
picture oh oh oh oh oh oh oh all
right okay oo you got this you got this
I got it where is she there
she can teleport so nice I wish I could
do
[Music]
that why what are you trying to do for
you no this is not going to this is not
going to do
[Music]
anything this is not the solution Boi
don't drag me into death as well I want
to
live Yi it's okay it's
okay yes
what was that was was that a Dodge yeah
that's a Dodge I maybe I don't
remember it look like a Dodge for me oh
yeah
okay why is she not doing
anything aren't you glad she's not doing
anything yeah now she's going away from
me I can't even get
closer well you you can run I no it's up
there really I scared the ghost away
yeah what what is going
[Music]
on okay how many more do you want how is
this even possible like she's making the
ghost go out of bound it's so
insane I'm just looking like
what
oh she just not doing anything now it
was bit more it was more difficult
before maybe maybe I glitched her okay
there we
go there we go
nice stun locking the
ghost if you touch a weakened ghost it
triggers a fatal glance and you will see
its memories okay touch the defeated
ghost
run
[Music]
no touch for youi don't
touch blop blop blop
bloop oh vision of the past you found it
oh jeez what
is
that herself or someone
else I'm sure hold the knife is doing it
or ghost yeah it's the evil
knife he doesn't even want to do
it no no
no no no only she had a camera to take
pictures right now
wow oh wow it's not even that it's
voluntary the ghosts are making her do
it
yeah oh it's like a shrine that's so
messed
up she was like
brainwashed by goost yeah oh
dear who is she she looks kind of
touchable you seen too much
yeah I agree with that I saw too much
what do you mean you cannot
leave oh tutorial tainted Ghost Attacks
may leave you tainted by the blackw if
this happens your health will
continuously decrease oh yeah this is
kind of
annoying blah blah blah defeat all
present ghosts to remove it mhm
am I already do I already have am I
already tainted not yet right uh um I
mean but I do want to heal a little bit
okay yeah it's damage over
time
okay we have n no we have 11 11 oh
okay uh the purifying Embers when I'm
tainted okay okay it's going to be D
it's going to be D I
over strong film or maybe this one first
trust trust oh she's not doing
anything no I'm T am I tainted
now uh I'm not um do look like your HP
is the same
okay it looks lower to me the HP it
already went down because of that one
attack oh I mean like it's
what what did I take a Fatal Frame what
was that yes oh
oh so normally if you take a Fatal Frame
since the ghost is a recoil just take a
few free shots M
okay o okay okay come and
get so far so
good so far so good H I agree should I
wait for her to get closer I can't I'm
too scared n don't don't be scared those
are free
money okay that was bad oh wait fle Fram
fle Fram fle Fram yes try to get her in
every frame oh that wasn't okay okay
yeah see that's that you you just
comboed
nice that is the bread and butter of
Fatal Frame that's Shrine Maiden she's
the one that brought fi here the one who
made
her do it yes
oh I killed so this is like the boss
boss ghost yes boss ghost oh that was
fine the go the the kids were more
annoying yeah I guess so it's too
dangerous I can't stay here I have to go
back for now what do you mean for now I
do want to heal
though
uh
oh just the little
bit yeah no big deal oh I can't use the
the guide right
now so really yeah it's not working so
we got to go
where this way
maybe I
guess oh oh look is that where I came
from or where I got to go I well you can
you can see you can see like where it
heads off to like cuz there's like going
to be a prompt okay
true it says ah oh okay I have to go
back for now that that so they basically
moved me automatically to this place
yeah they forced you out okay thank you
for the shortcut oh there's another one
here gosh dang oh no H yeah I remember
this place
now yo Mory kayi and their viewers just
joined yo it's a raid
baby let's freaking go we're playing
spoopy game right now Fatal Frame where
there's cute girls and we take pictures
of ghosts to destroy them but viewer
discretion is advised because yeah not
so nice the
story where do I
go home that's where you go I'm
confused wait so this is this this the
right P oh yeah now I see a
lantern yes that this way
good oh be sure to check the seaweed
before you go the
seaweed the SE no no I mean like the
content warning the CW ah oh that's what
I'm talking to the viewers look oh
I oh oh oh oh scary I can't see the
bottom nobody could survive a drop from
this hide yeah so let's not
jump ah this way okay okay gosh it's so
dark
n
n a jump would be a shortcut though to
the
afterlife wa what is that
what do you mean the was falling
down uh I don't know it looks like cat
poop dead body oh dead
bodies plastic body wonderful they're
coming closer it's more Shrine
maidens ah yeah Shrine girl yeah
unbelievable
while searching for her friend fuino
ended up taking her own life no
having go
ahead wa
it wi I can't hear you oh sorry in
the same way not to mention the
mysterious Shrine Maiden s from the rain
Yuri managed to locate uh he took a
scammer obscura along with the charm
she's always like to wear for now she
must return to the Antique shop alone a
I failed my
mission but not really
be hey better than the
tutorial okay well that means you're
getting better oh I get more points for
using the type 61 film no no no I don't
know cuz I mean I got 10,000 points for
the 61 film huh um I think it's like the
one that you have so like the more items
you have in your inventory the better
the more points you will get a okay okay
hoarding has its merits
a okay that's uh we'll keep that in mind
thir
drop you want to at least try the guy I
think it would be good to like at least
yeah get the oh Ren Hojo the author who
sent Hoka to find the photographs takes
a closer look at the album one photo
catches his eye and he decides to
investigate further he goes to the end
with a camera obscura and ruie his
assistant R not R I stopped watch
reading that all right uh ikim what is
this ikim if I bring it wait otherwise I
would have none of this I would only
have did you use up all of them
no I can take more but it takes points
or is it it's buying what I used it all
I don't remember using it
all well you'll be fine
what no unless they only gave me like
five photography oh yeah this
picture h r Hojo the writer is haunted
by a recurring dream in which he kills a
young girl during a ritual a he receives
an album of postmortem photographs
located on his records by Hoka upon
viewing one of the photos Ren recognizes
the very scene from his dreams eager to
delve further into this puzzling mystery
Ren heads to the abandoned Inn in person
this time bringing along his assistant
ruie kagam kagia let's go he so we play
the guy now
yeah we play the guy now basically um
and I think the items are reset because
you're technically playing as a
different character they hold different
items oh okay okay that makes sense then
okay I am
relieved I want to play the girl behind
him she's
cute
cute and um I think cuz um they have
different
cameras um if you yeah it also has
different upgrades okay or like skills
basically he's so freaked out I know
he's like oh who is
this will you
die oh that seems like a marriage
proposal oh jeez together until death
Parts us
wait if dying with them then that means
they're still together after death
though that's beautiful isn't that
wonderful that you get nervous
around
yeah she's is she a girl I'm confused
there may be more of this stuff out
there I have um my assumption is that
it's a
boy E I think it's a tomboy
girl at this okay maybe not or a girly
boy tom boy girl or boy girl boy girly
boy I don't shouldn't
youca I don't think they specify I'm not
sure this could be your chance Shing
airs um just just pet girl off about
that place
okay we will never know he's gender
that's what I should take that shadow
reading Report with me too it may come
in handy Lou is always complaining about
me leaving things on a sofa okay we take
camera Ren Cera
obscura yeah it's different look at the
design too true you got the measure
upgrade this dis place the current heal
of a locked on enemy oh okay there's an
unfinished manuscript on the desk
it doesn't yet have a title it'll need
more materials to solidify the theme or
Memorial portraiture the act of
photographing dead bodies was a practice
in Western countries in the 19th century
a time when photography was still a rare
and expensive luxury next the bodies of
recently deceased family members and
loved ones were photographed in lifelike
poses as a solemn key sake of
remembrance while researching the
phenomenon I discovered that a similar
custom made its way to Japan as well is
this a thing is this a thing like people
putting like dead bodies in like poses
that are like as if they're alive and
then taking pictures as if they're alive
is that it's an actual thing it was real
I hope they don't do it anymore that's
really
creepy oh it's um Customs I think
known as
postmortem photographs a small number of
these photos still remain I have been
fortunate enough to obtain one such
photograph which I found to contain a
certain Beauty liking in its Western
counterparts huh F when photography
first arrived in Japan it was
accompanied by the prevalent
Superstition that photographs could
steal a person's soul really whether
anyone truly believed this or not it
surely gave postmortem photography a
special significance in Japan oh well if
you could steal if they think you could
steal a person's soul and then you take
a picture of a dead person so you
stealing the soul of the dead person
with that is that a good thing or a bad
thing I don't think it matters they're
dead if photos were taken with this
belief in mind then postmortem
photographs would not simply have been
taken as keepsakes or for morning
purposes rather the practice may have
carried a certain deeper spiritual
significance
damn
okay okay Noto they wanted to take
pictures of their dead uh friends or
family members whatever guess yeah
because they it's like spiritual
spiritual ritual baby
maybe maybe maybe
baby reply to the appraisal request for
this camera urges caution in using it oh
oh you want to read this to the camera
you left me to look at is a device known
as the camera obscura its purpose is to
capture images of the supernatural
things invisible to the naked eye hey
hey naked this cameras are incredibly
rare with an almost mythical status in
the Antiques Market a few have been
known to exist but this is the first
I've ever seen in compound lenses
immediately Yahoo auction I don't mean
to frighten you but rumor holds that to
own a camera obscura is to invite
Misfortune they say everyone who has
owned one has either died lost their
mind or gone missing oh jeez cameras
themselves have outlived many owners gee
good to know thanks for sending me this
I don't mean to frighten you oh really
oh we passed that I guess well some
official AOS who seek them out the
stories of previous owners meeting with
such Misfortune has had an impact on
their value as antiques my camera obscur
was left to a local family after its
previous owner passed away they
graciously gave it to me jeez it's kind
of like you know one of those like
cursed VHS tapes and you're like oh send
it to the next person I believe yours is
still usable but please do exercise
caution in doing so sincerely Hoka
Kurosawa the Onan oh PS the cover on
your camera obscura is broken but it
seems originally had a box shape I doubt
you'd sell it to me but I would like to
borrow it for a while if you don't mind
I am happy to compensate please think it
over okay I I left the shadow rating
report on the sofa should should take it
with me okay so he SOA gave me that
camera that's how the characters can uh
you know connect however you it may have
some information I could use who knows
when I might need it it looks like a
report written by uni it seems to be
about
ALB found item report I'm just the
report girl now client is Ren Hojo um
report by yudi kukata which is the other
character verified byoka kurawa the
other char
details of request find items pertaining
to post photography on Mount
hikami obtain them if possible perform
Shadow reading using a postm morm
photograph found on Mount hikami as a
token located album of postmortem
photographs in ichu Manor took custody
of the object wow good job Yi you did so
many things well documented yeah oh oh
it's moving on its own ghost oh really
oh it's kind of like a Ouija board o
yeah where did I put that book about
Mountain hikami has really been tidying
up again it might be on one of the
shelves oh could it be the one that
sparkling oo oh oh I think that's
it the M
Slayer I don't think this story has
anything to do oh sorry sorry I don't
think this story you never know okay the
maiden like oh wow you want to read this
for once okay the nen Slayer Mount has
long been steeped in Legends revolving
around suicide and ghosts rever rever as
a sacred place since time IM Memorial it
was once the worshipping ground and home
of many Shrine
maidens that kind of Maiden okay once
there was a man who fell in love with a
maiden and came to the mountain in order
to court her however she remained loyal
to her duties and refused his advances
enraged the man killed her and threw her
into the river great what the Great
great several days later he returned
with a torch and blade and proceeded to
brutally butcher all the shrine maidens
on the mountain tossing them into the
river as he
went hello okay chill the Waters of the
mountain flowed red with blood carrying
the slaughtered corpses of the maidens
all the way down to the pool of
purification it is said that the eyes of
each of the shrine maidens had been
gooed out no no this is I guess when we
saw the scene of all the shrine maidens
falling down at the end oh they have no
eyes right yeah that's that was the dead
bodies just before killing the first
maiden and tossing her into the river
the Man's eyes met with those of his
victim something in her eyes led him to
murder the others or so the legend goes
with all the maidens dead he killed
himself by cutting his own throat oh my
gosh this is such a wild story what is
this the ghost of shrine Maiden still
drenched in those blooded Waters have
appeared on the mountain ever since it
is said that those who meet their eyes
are led to their deaths they followed
the woman into the water and drown
themselves yeah we've seen these cases
could have seen it coming they only
Legend the story is believed to be based
on an actual incident local records show
that the bodies of several Shrine
maidens were discovered long ago and
that all rituals and rights ceased to be
performed from that day
on okay not a it must Journal yeah looks
nice feel bad reading it but oh what
another read okay your turn gosh Mr hoo
can't clean up after himself for someone
who's lived alone for so long he's
incapable of housework he can't cook and
he's bad at tidying up more like his
caretaker than his assistant okay he
loses things all the time and whenever
he doesn't have a book he needs he blows
up he usually ends up asking Miss kurawa
for for help one time when I was trying
to sort all his books there was one I
couldn't find anywhere it's like it just
disappeared okay that's sus Miss
kurasawa found it with her Shadow
reading she went into this his room on
her own and then came back out a little
while later with the missing book a she
just smiled and said something about
making the Invincible invisible visible
what is this Shadow reading business
anyway we did that right in the first
chapter that reminds me of that one time
I was tidying up and I came across
something i' never seen before it was
like Mr not Mr Miss Kur said the in The
Invisible became visible it was kept
inside an old box I don't even know what
it was I put it aside the sword out
later on but when I went to take a
proper look it had vanished it must have
gone invinci invisible again in
inet we should hurry oh who's saying
that yeah let's go oh she talked through
the wall to me yeah open the door and
talk to me directly uh it's almost
Sunset then why not go after
Sunrise there's they won't show up if
it's bright not to go up Mount Hami
after
dust if you climb the mountain in the
Twilight hours it'll show you a
different form it's true form
form only those who wish to die come
here at that time but we don't have that
wish we don't want to die right we want
to live yeah but we need to investigate
I think that's the where the ALB was
found this must be ichiru Manor ichiru
Manor Manor use the camera obscure of
course easy should we're a pro so easy
nothing easier than that this type of
camera allows you to take multiple
photos at once shut multi shatter uh use
the multishot function to take four
photos at once dealing more damage to
the ghosts that you photograph
taking multiple photos at once also
helps you get Fatal Frame shots after
Multi Shot the camera s will take longer
than usual to reload the film oh okay
so mhm yeah keep in mind that multi
shots quickly use up a lot of film also
standard camera obscure lenses do not
work with r camera obscure okay it's
just a special variation okay let's take
a cutie picture your film your film your
film do you only have one film
oh we can take this
one nice
waa oh I like this
oh oh okay yes
M
[Music]
well oh it charges so
long so it takes four
pictures yep okay is the camera working
yeah it was working like yeah is that a
good thing we should is that a good do
you prefer this one waya over the other
one the camera I think um it's
interesting I think it's because of I'm
more familiar with previous games I like
this one cuz it's like a new addition
sort of a new
mechanic
okay where we go the proprietor's family
lived here but it doesn't look like
anyone massive land that her voice L
just overlapped I know hey it looks like
too fast in the old building she has so
many things to say sure that
way oh this is the place we visited
before yeah but wasn't it like uh filled
with water last
time uh no it's it's the one with the oh
I mean yeah some parts of
it okay that r hi yay we missed him I
wonder if
it look yeah probably
go run
dude nothing here this time run run run
water keeping an eye open
oh I got it Yay good job yay go away now
already took a picture of you you want
another one no okay
no but if I take a picture like that it
was only one not like a oh no uh I think
uh easy way to is that if you photo and
then there's like the name of the ghost
then they're not a hostile
one the hatch on the duct has shut
itself it must have been the wind must
have been the wind y must have been the
W I take it so
fast you didn't get the girl though I
don't
think well better than nothing oh well
it's
fine
good girl I want to pick up this
item y y y yeah yeah
nice gosh when your own partner keeps on
scaring you
man no nice oh oh
hands hands waiting in the dark yeah
it's like a like a concert like a tin
anago you know yeah hey another one oh
it doesn't count anymore yeah they're
just like waving they're chilling they
don't even go away oh there we
go wait there's an item there
[Music]
yay what was that
check I saw a prompt but was gone right
away okay to the item we go to the item
we go go go oh I don't I don't even want
to look
there yep
no I'm pretty sure it's this item okay
sometimes it gets kind of confusing so
don't worry about it oh ah not the best
ah did that count wait it's an actual
fighting it's hostile ghost okay okay oh
oh
hi
yeah oh oh
God yes okay you dodged it I did
okay okay I'll get out of the
way here let's try it
again all right oh what is
this oo
o o
o go away what was his name Ren or what
uh uh do do where's where is it where is
it ah
ah it was right there oh no it's
cornering
me got to wait for my film you'll be
fine oh why are you why girl what I triy
to take pictures of the ghost you
idiot no wait but will will her Circle
be counted though it might really is
that a good thing I don't know yeah cuz
like more chance of shutter chance right
there we go
yay
dodged I don't really want her own the
picture though
what don't go into the
wall okay this is a
terrible hey she's attacking my friend
my family no
no okay that's a nice Fatal Frame shot
though
I dodged
nice let's go you got this you got this
this lady is
so
obnoxious
oh is
[Music]
was can I even take normal pict without
the
shutter um you can but it's just
generally maybe lower
damage also if you're a little bit
impatient you can change films oh true I
could take the stronger one
oh let's take one of
these yo come on
[Music]
lady it didn't work why
not oh she's she is in the walls
clipping well she's a ghost after
all get out of the
wall
like wait I keep pressing that ah cuz I
dodged and then I press
the it's okay it's okay you got this you
got this let's do it this
way
well no no yeah yes picture I can't I I
can't take the picture why
not what why is not working it should be
why
well guess I'll
[Music]
die change my film
okay
charging no it's not
working is it
[Music]
glitch
uh what is going on I'm pressing for the
button maybe I don't know maybe oh my
God the wall glitch or so no no no it
shouldn't matter it shouldn't matter
but
H maybe I I think you don't have the
thing equipped look look the lens you
don't have the lens equipped do you not
have the lens equipped a when did I
unequip it what you I think you mashed
something oh must have
oh
yeah that was a Fatal
Frame
yay but with the this kind of lens for
the Fatal Frame you can't follow it up
with more you um you're you you should
be able
to how much longer do does this lady
want to live I'm switching film
now press down you you unequipped the
film again okay what
how and no I want to take a picture
now she's
[Music]
moring holy this ghost wants to
stay forever and play with me
didn't it say something about showing us
the health bar
now uh I don't see the health I think if
you lock on is it if you lock on I'm
locked
on oh no
no she
di she died second time y might need
some
upgrades yeah upgrades would be nice on
this camera cuz that was endless
yay where were we supposed to go this
way go go
go now let's go to the left now we took
care of
her right side okay okay are we going to
see the same things as youy I'm not I'm
not interested in particular with this
Crouch
animation yeah his crouching animation
is not as Charming found
thatb yeah he lik in the charm
Department makes it out with his um
quadruple shots I think oh hi how you
doing man shrouded in darkness all right
now go back to the light go die camera
is reacting to something maybe I can see
something for the
viewfinder uhhuh oh yeah right like a
many festing items again
yeah oh man wait how does it work just
taking a picture right uh you have to
tilt it also like a certain angle ah
you're
right oh ah there it was I
think
no what's the angle oh
oh
no I forgot how it looks I feel like I
see it it looks red I see it more
now a lock a
locking is it there yet no you need to
lock on and then you need to um tilt
there we go we have it ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding yay we did
it crumpled old note has materialized
this must be what the camera was
reacting to mhm whose note is it messy
notes how long has it been since I lost
everything the mountain swallowed up
half my in all I have left is that old
album of postm and photographs the one
left by my father I don't even know who
these photos are off but it's the Last
Vestige of family I have
oh how long have I spent here wallowing
in the darkness it doesn't matter I I'll
burn it all and then there will only be
me I think I'll end it up in the
observation room on the roof the sunset
is lovely up there gee thanks for the
heads up I guess we're going there up to
the roof using this note as a token I
might find a choice that will lead me to
some information information about the
photograph uh you again I already took a
picture of you that didn't even count me
man yeah sad he's talking to me it's all
because of that piure I
guess
ooh
spooky
ghost I didn't even keep the door open
for my
sister I just let it fall on her head F
she's a grownup she can't open and close
her own
doors more like a teenager
I guess would you consider a teenager a
grownup no
no that's why they're called
teenager
hello what is that what is that did I
take a picture what is this oh it's
coming CL we're fighting oh we're
fighting okay okay hi hi hi hi let's
take strong
film come
on yeah yeah eat
this want some more I am professional
photographer yummy I can take your
yearbook picture I can take your wedding
photography I can
take I can take your life once
again host morm photography service by
Tak and cabonia win let's go with
competitive rides we will take your
pictures we have competitors who else is
taking these
pictures well there's multiple
characters in the game right there's
like the girl and the other girl but we
all work together somehow same company
oh true we're like a team or something
truly pictures to die for she wants me
she wants me
oh ah ah ah upsirt shot
up scared
shot yo now like after this I might want
to like rewatch my fat frame gameplay I
was like yeah my first time playing like
how did I react I know I screamed a lot
though I'm very like vocal yeah I'm so
like jumpy if I you
[Music]
know I'm sure you did great but you
shouldn't re-watch it you should replay
it on the switch it's it's currently I
think like 30% off or so oh for real mhm
yeah I
could but also there's the other game
the fourth game yeah yeah yeah right I
wonder that does that have motion
controls too oh should
be
beautiful and all of you yeah I want all
of you
[Music]
w ooh BL
so sorry I'm sorry I think they're I
think they're dead now good okay there
is
safe let's continue oh hello ghosty
ghost oh oh
no and that didn't count I got his b the
stories after the land man you need her
his face man I thought it was a real
person
to death there why would real people go
to this place I mean I guess we're real
people but
also tell me about I want that item
though I can't have I guess we're going
to have to do a little bit of a
detour s they say that if you look up at
the third floor verand you see someone
looking back down not really I'm
sorry he's like stop telling me the
scary stories I'm already plenty scared
okay
like shut
up but maybe it's a hand maybe somebody
will look
back it's going to be a photo a
photograph free photo yeah free photo
means free money aren't you
excited of
course I'm just like better points for
upgrades well when can I get them so far
I didn't buy any upgrades
uh I'm not sure can you access it to the
menu yet hey could I do it in the middle
here oh let's see R
camera enhancements look at enhancements
in use in use in use H yeah oh ah here
up there oh oh you can't oh there it
is that
is ooh many options what's important you
think um in my opinion I forgot slows
the enemy down while taking I think
snapshot could be important but also
let's see output what's output oh no no
output is probably third or last Brant
increas Dam load loader is a short time
between taking pictures loading speed is
good sensor um sensor personality I
personal personally I don't really care
that much because I I'm always hungry
for the you know close-ups yeah I think
I would go for snapshot and loader for
now sure like uh yeah slowing the enemy
down and then uh shortening the time but
for now definitely the
loader yes it would help yeah because
the whole um four shots thing slows him
down a lot right yeah and also I don't
want the damage I'll I'll take one of
the damage
outputs I mean
um not good it's honestly it's up to you
but for me I just think you'll get more
like stronger films
anyways okay maybe we can save for more
loader upgrades yes okay but also yeah I
think loader is most important for this
guy okay yeah true and also be careful
because uh there's two cameras right you
will need to up uh points to upgrade the
other camera too oh do they share points
you mean those two characters
or Y little
where
why I forgot if um the points are shared
but you know I'm a hoarder so I always
like you know
yeah oh oh right here
something what is this a film let's
go Ty 14
film yay I feel like I'm going in the
circle wa now oh no ah for the door he
just went through that door yeah
okay it's locked but the camera is
reacting to the door a spiritual keyo
jeez who oh what what was that or uh
psychic
photograph wait yo your film girl
no
uh like
this yes yeah okay ooh o that thing that
the door the little the little door
there's something going through
it yeah there's something in the photo
remember this one that like where we
were like oh must have been the wind
yeah yeah yeah M shows ducked with its
hatch open
mhm might be showing me the location of
the key to this door oh
really yes wait where where where
where just got to go down to the first
floor again right yeah that's where it
was
oh what was the pick up a note we love
notes a note hello messy note M yay the
inkeeper note mhm even before the
landslide there always strange going on
around here some years ago two girls
went missing on a college field trip the
police were stumped a few days later one
of the girls turned up again seemingly
out of her
mind there were lots of theories but
most people believe they were simply
Spirited Away that girl came back each
year to look for her friend like some
sort of pilgrimage Hess people have gone
missing here over the years we're all
used to it by now leau my father was
Spirited Away too as the folklorist kg
water next oh kg watery thanks it next
it'll be my turn I I bet I'll vanish
with the rest of them I doubt anyone
will think to come looking for me Al
negative I
know everybody's just getting Spirited
Away is that their nice way of saying
they're getting dragged into suicide by
ghosts I think so I mean they don't
really know what actually happened to
them right right M the these people that
keep saying Spirited Away true
yeah
oh more items
there slowly as possible pick it up yeah
yeah let's go where is the path
downwards
again you'll find it this is maze I mean
is there a
map uh it uh
map there we go through this room and
this room and this room and then there
okay
so through this so I was already on the
right side but then I got
confused yep ah is it
here
no no no no again for the
the no
here wait what did you eat
today what did I eat today I ate fried
rice I ate Indonesian fried rice and
then I also ate instant
noodles he in
Mia uh
yes yummy yummy yummy nice hey um is me
going the one I sent you last time the
one without the soup is it spicy for
you wait I ate one IND mirr recently but
I don't know which one it
was I don't know well was it spicy if
it's not spicy that means you're fine
okay the one I ate was not spicy but I
don't know if it's the right one cuz I
got so many recently from other ID Girls
when I met them in
Japan
so well it should be fine if you don't
think it's spicy m i I may have just not
added the spice packet oh I think that's
also an
option that is it is truly the best gift
though I mean like people are crazy
about indomi just be uh you know it's
like you and your
s but I did find I did find find the one
India package in my superm market oh
really yeah but it seems like a really
basic one uh no that's the one cuz it's
like the one for um overseas consumption
it's healthier that's why it sucks okay
where do I go
here where do you go the map is I one
more Flo floor down okay yeah well but
you know wa know what they say if it's
spicy sip some
tea yeah of course wow I'm surprised you
remember of course I love it I love the
song thank you
to be followed now let's go I can't get
the hatch to the duct open it's being sh
held shut by a powerful force camera is
reacting to it okay sink shots taking
photos identical to the psychic
photographs taken with the camera
obscuring can break seals blocking your
axes okay we're going to
vent I got to play amongus
again okay
so what do I have to look at the again
Bas um yeah yes oh oh well now I saw it
uh
I'm now wait H like
this oh I'm not
sure W that's not identical that doesn't
feel that's not
identical I feel like I took a better
picture here but you know if the game
accepts that then we take it we take it
we'll take it we'll take it oh we can't
vent cuz it's blocked off I guess but
we're taking a key or so yeah
yay okay on yellow keychain yeah yeah
yeah I know we got to go up again thank
you what what is this
feeling what where are they
where I guess they just show themselves
too close too close too close for
comfort my
friend social
distancing don't go away
now they're just like
nuh-uh oh so
many yeah oh oh oh I'm getting cornered
again oh my oh it's charging so long
it's charging so long oh I switched to
sword charges again
wait wait wait wait wait wait I got to
stay committed to my
film okay I'm ready now try to attack me
come
on oh my
god oh yeah Fatal Frame Wow Let's go
that's the bread and butter or Fatal
Frame you just dealed massive damage I
better go back those extra three shots
they were free by the way oh cuz it was
a Fatal Frame
was it more than was it that many I
didn't count oh no ah
wait
no not her not
her
oh you're going to attack me but not her
she's too young to
die are you old enough to
die I guess so compared to
her I guess I would sacrifice
myself for my young
sister I guess oh there he goes he's
vanished
so the the path back up didn't I come
from
here no I guess not
okay run run what's his name again uh
Dan Dan his name is thenen and her name
really oh damn you
remember of course got the big memory
slot I did touch a ghost yeah what the
man wrong side wrong
side I got it what oh it's an attacking
ghost oh I didn't
realize wrong side wrong side wrong side
it turns so slowly okay he just a out
there
wait okay so
yes this will be the
shot come
on oh he falls down
[Music]
again must have ah must have been an
acrobat let's
go he's aggressive very
aggressive you could say he roped us
into this situation yes fiddle frame
you're so good let's freaking go I was
waiting we want some more I'm I'm not
ready yes now now I'm ready
now uh not quite a Fatal
[Music]
Frame oh his knees are his weak points
too ah no I'm not ready for
that okay oh he's got like shards glass
shards I guess cuz you know he threw the
glass
[Music]
friend title call now we can end the
game oh oh
oh okay ah that would have been
good oh oh don't be stumbling he
stumbling and
tumbling
[Music]
B oh my
God okay I'm I'm using the strong film
now again it's all right you can do it
come on come
on oh come on attack me attack me I know
you want want it you want revenge on the
world I shall be your
target no oh okay I'll just they didn't
hear you you normally didn't oh oh
oh
what no
no that was supposed to be a good
shot
N I think it's like he charges but you
don't uh have his face in your uh
viewfinder
a yeah
it's okay no problem no problem we
can oh he's coming no I will not let you
no
no nice
Dodge no he's going for her
again we're so different she's like no
she's going for her again and I'm just
like yes she's com for her is that good
yeah cuz it's like free Fatal Frame what
are these shutter chances again what
does that do um shter chance is when uh
you capture five or more uh
[Music]
entities in a camera you're he's coming
me what what do I do what do I
do you just
shoot I need healing I need healing this
yeah you to do um little bit of these
medicine that's a lot of medicine yeah I
got
plenty no stop
it no okay his face like I try to shoot
when he gets close
but go away go
it's okay it's okay yes he's going away
good how much
longer I don't
know oh oh careful
careful I no
this are alive longer than the boss
fights
okay that's why um I think you are
pretty I think you are really good at
taking um fatal frames off this boss
yeah so oh is this supposed to be a boss
yeah he's got a death cut scene oh yo
run up to him and touch oh oh maybe you
can't never mind oh that's why he was
more difficult okay I thought it was
just a random one no he's not he's the
one who's been leaving the notes ah so
that makes sense we didn't even go up to
the roof well he left a note there you
go this place has gone from a tourist
Hot Spot into a s hot spot but I suppose
that was always the case this mountain
and death go together side by side
a mikori Miki
M was once known as The Grove of shrine
maidens a sacred grove where the
mountains maidens oversaw the deaths of
pilgrims easing their past to the other
side I like that I envy it I wish
someone would be there to see me off
okay okay was that the man who wrote
this note yeah maybe I'll find something
upstairs what we do keep on going up
okay are you all right yes I'm
fine I hear I hear
stuff but is there I heard the scream
that was surely a ghost maybe outside
the window that I should have
captured Maybe H anyway I need another
one of these Mama
Mia Mama Mia oh yeah I was supposed to
unlock the door right
yep
okay where's this door I lost my sense
of direction I got to check the map the
map's your friend don't worry turn
around go through the room there
okay okay okay okay
okay let's go let's go we can do it we
can do it let's
[Music]
go yay I want to learn that song but you
have a you have a Korean part in it
Korean Indonesian
part maybe you should make a full
English version a
[Music]
i
hi Spirit photograph woman who was
hanged a very
descriptive that means you learn
Indonesian you know tonj that's just the
first but tonj is not even in the lyrics
I guess so I mean just a little more
push I guess but it is a cool a really
cool like sounding like it s it's flows
so well the Indonesian part mhm even
though like the whole first part is like
English when I hear the Indonesian part
I'm like oh this this is like a nice
Rhythm nice flow
a yay I do like that makes me
happy we got a mirror Stone what was
that again mirror stone is if you die
revive oh okay nice there's another door
above the stairs on the side
[Music]
okay
the
sunset
beautiful there we go man transfixed by
the
sunset oh yep I don't see it man I just
don't see it oh the way he jumped he's
just
like okay let's read the note is that
candy yeah I was like what's that I'm
hungry I think
the sunset beckons it's calling me into
the water this is the right thing to do
did you jump into the water not oh
man what if he missed it would have been
so
sad
scar that's not really how am I supposed
to capture that I can't see the
face um I also I'm sure I also missed
that part M maybe the first time you see
it you have to be inside the room you
have to like run or like run and then
instantly you
know I would guess was it a high oh was
it a high cool cuz it's so short the
sunset beckons that's five and then what
575 I guess so you
beu even in
englishy beautiful you know I didn't
even know how many words it has to be by
by
heart I wouldn't remember
oh there's
oh huh it suddenly gave me this like
message the whole room is chart I was
taking a picture that man might have
left something behind if he did like
like there was a fire I was
supposed
picture oh that's annoying though oh so
apparently it's only um New Game Plus
because it's impossible to get in first
playthrough wait what happens in New
Game Plus is there like a the upgrade
that lets you photograph just the
freaking ghost feet or
[Music]
whatever what what's here oh the timing
is
different something's
here oh yeah ah like this okay
Expos I have
Focus was that
it no that's oh there's one lens that
can SL SL time oh
oh
interesting
interesting I want to watch a YouTube
video or something to see how it works
if there's some a video of that oh
I wasn't focused even though I was
holding it
down there we go okay is cuz I
constantly hold it
down that's read reading time reading
time yay uh-oh yay
omnus ominus ominus
ominos so something's going to
happen o what her walking o
o do is just you know
[Music]
checking H oh it was a stone maybe not a
candy I don't know
you got to aim and time it right so I
guess through the window like and then
look up or whatever not sure
no the
uh what the
um let's go let what do you mean
let's go I mean let's go to
her something there oh no
great pho
oh it works let freaking go face is
literally CED
[Music]
face W whoa whoo whoo whoo whoo whoo
whoo no uh you ain't touching my
sis
uhoh let me go to strong film no hey
take take no this this is oh God n she's
just stretching ah
[Music]
[Applause]
ah oh beautiful beautiful
nice okay
good come at me come at
me she just I'm out of
here no no no no she she walking on air
yeah I guess cuz she's a ghost oh she's
hanging in the
air yeah just hanging
out no no
what didn't get her face it's okay it's
okay we got this we got this we got this
it's another boss fight I guess sort of
yeah the real one this the real no hey
why not work working do I have the wrong
lens oh I might have did I which one is
the this one no yeah yeah if it lights
up it's right I might have had the wrong
one again then it's confusing me
here now okay yeah yes yes yes go go go
that's a great one let's go
uh wait I want to use this one strong
one oh she's coming oh is she not no yo
lens Ste your lens oh what the why
is
Twitch no Fatal
Frame
creepy go good good good good good nice
nice nice nice nice do well
timed
yay okay okay
okay oh she's she's swinging and
Swinging Swing Swing Swing Swing Swing
like a little bit of just
swaying yeah the the diagonal it's so
worthy shot it wants the the top the top
part too here you
yeah yeah yeah let
go all right all right good one that's
good that's good that's
great I'm ready Wooh I'm ready for
another
one yeah uh well I'll I'll talk later
but basic I mean I guess now I guess
yeah talk now but basically you keep
getting the Fatal Frame cuz you already
know the timing right and there's also a
sound Cube so I guess so each ghost have
different timings and different angles
like style of attacking right that's how
you like that's how you have to adapt
and eventually you'll be able to like
constantly hit shots yeah is that how it
turned out for you you always fa
framing um I don't know but at least I
try to get red mhm she's not attacking
come on do I do I have to get closer to
like bait her to motivate her uh yeah
you could try to bait her I don't get
the full
frames yeah that's the thing cuz like um
if you uh kind of waste it on a regular
shot on when she attacks you'll still be
loading and it's like uhoh oh yeah
okay all right that's good that's
[Music]
good one more one more come
on you can
[Music]
try
come on I'm not scared the days of laa
being scared of horror games are
over
yay thanks to
way n
you're she's just
wiggling wiggle she's excited oo oh my
goodness like a she's like seaweed you
know like
algae oh yeah oh that was just one more
shot okay y I saved her you please saved
did you did
it with the power of Photography did you
remember anything I
know
girl let's go home that was scary if we
didn't interfere she the ghost would
have influenced them to jump but oh I'm
done
[Music]
I'm not listening to you oh wait oh hell
no another fight face
two it's a different different ghost oh
yeah I'm going to go to the cheap one
again for a little bit to understand
her her
patterns yeah that works that
work here take this
just a little little pre photo just
testing just testing go go go yes yes
that's good you got it nice just testing
if my ISO is like properly
set is going to be grainy or not no
maybe I need to use the
hey maybe I need to use the flash or
maybe I should use my soft box many
options for
what about the natural light yeah
usually you always want to go for
natural light I oh dancing oh
jeez it's the maiden she's
dancing is she laughing though you hear
her yeah she's happy finle frame oopsie
I I I went out of it
oopsie but see you got her attack
pattern down so kind of that's good a
oh jeez what I'm dying he heal up
heal up he up I'm dying let's go I'll
join the afterlife let's
go no no afterlife for you
oopsy okay part
two
[Music]
oh she's she's uh when she attacks like
this she gets close so
fast yeah so it's like you know
difficult to get her face
mhm I like her headdress it's really
pretty it is the
ornamento oh o o yes yes you get it you
get it nice good two fatal frames in a
row that's the spirit I mean like yeah
that's the spirit also W baby a
triple yes you're getting it that's
great yeah yeah yeah yeah she's waiting
for my shutter to charge the moment it's
charged she's like going at
it wa Pro Gamer oh shoot she
died was that you're really good at um
yeah yeah see once you got everything
down a fights become like significantly
easier right yeah thank you
way I don't get to touch any ghosts this
time woman dress um if there's
no the album of postmodem photographs
was assembled by a folklorist who lived
in the mountain his name was Ki watery
he became fascinated by the custom and
moved to mount hikami to study how it
spread through Japan my father seemed to
take an interest in these photos as well
strange foreign Customs always
fascinated him while he was running the
Inn he helped watai collect post motum
photographs from the nearby town on
Mount hikami water itself was de deified
it seems like watery wanted to get a
deeper understanding of this unique
Outlook so he set up a house in the
forest to experience it firsthand oh he
was greatly aided by my father who had
already set up the in by that point he
remodeled it from an old unused Shrine
and I think he thought the extra
religious heft would help attract more
visitors
jeez seven pages one day the folklorist
went missing several people formed the
search party but they were unable to
find a trace even the road to his house
seemed to have been lost to the woods a
my father scoured the mountain too but
all he found was that photo album he was
soaking wet when he got back I remember
he was acting strangely his eyes had
this curious glint almost act like he'd
been possessed by something creepy the
next thing I knew my father went missing
as well I'd forgotten about the photos
until I found them in the old building
after the landslide but now I understand
why my father left what that I doo these
photos are too
beautiful K folklorist who lived on
Mountain hikami hisa probably has some
books about him we should get back
really needs to rest okay I think so the
photo album left behind by The inke
Keeper was put together by a f who lived
on M nikami as R and Ru explored the in
and Tra the spirit of its owner a ghost
tried to lure do to Suicide then through
the pouring rain an OM ominous Shrine
Maiden appeared R and left the mountain
with more questions than when they
started do I get a
shortcut oh I do srank srank srank is
that let's
go you were you were doing so great at
that uh boss fight yay thank you see she
she learned from zero to consistently
fatal framing in just one stream this is
your first Fatal Frame game right yeah I
had no idea what to expect but with
motion controls too yeah maybe we can do
just one more
chapter okay what's the next one good
question hopefully we go back to the
girl but probably
not maybe maybe probably not Shadow
reading INE Yi y k with Miss Yuli
recalls what she witnessed on the
mountain fuyi taking her own life while
entranced by a malevolent Spirit and the
bodies of Dead shrine maidens washed up
at the pool of purification these
disquieting images leave yudy with no
doubt that mountain hikami houses some
kind of horrifying secret Yi takes the
camera obscura that she found on the
mountain and begin searching for a token
that will lead her to
Hoka wow can we find her again by the
time we we find her maybe maybe she'll
die or she'll be dead I mean get outfit
change outfit change oh is there any
outfits at my disposal we can check
[Music]
o bodies yeah yeah that's what I'm
saying something like that before who
what is this radio a phone I'll see what
I can find
tomor so I think interlude is probably
like shorter than the other chapters I
guess oh okay wait people want me to
check if I can change out this I don't
see anything here
items no you guys just want to see
the immersion breaking
outfits stop it inversion breaking
outfits yeah so uh you can pretty much
unlock costumes uh but yeah in this game
there's certain requirements and I think
there's you know I saw that there's uh
they have cuz it's also a KO techmo game
they had like Risa outfits from at R
yeah it's actually still available in
the shop for free in the Nintendo store
oh okay okay okay but I didn't get it
cuz I don't know if I can show it
really oh wait the dark standing what
looks like a body of water the other
photos are no good they're all black as
if they were exposed to strong light
this doesn't tell me anything maybe
there are more clues in's
room okay we're just going to search
people's room sneaky
nyyy saky NY sneaking through their
rooms like I don't give a sneaky
sneaky sneaky sneaky sneaky sneak was
her room on the same floor I think so um
yeah her room is on the same floor the
Japanese looking
room
yeah
ah he's
a does that mean she's
dead no right I think it's just like a
vision or something I'm not sure she's
pretty she's so C she like to sit at her
desk to relax the Japanese self the room
helped her
distress I can understand stand that I
can see that that's
nice look so nice oh the drawer is
locked camera will SC for some
lockpicking oh or that too spiritual
lockpicking oh wait I have to oh that's
it under the bed
ah what a good uh good place to hide the
key nice under the bed secret secret
this
oh I just check this room used to be a
study and the bed was in another room he
move the bed in here so I could take her
room is says that she prefers cozy
quarters I hope she's not just doing it
for my sake mhm wait this is under my
bed then cuz she moved the bed I guess
so I don't I don't even ah the store
room so that was a picture of a vision
of where their bed originally was
it was a vision of where the things are
mhm oh forgive me oh my God forgive
me what are we forgiving you are
forgiven nah she's like forgive me for
intruding she's more polite than us we
just don't say anything are you sure
that's it is not forgive me for trying
to kill
you what what she going to kill the door
then who was
inside I don't know can you not
check sneaky
sneaky ooh TV we can watch
TV oh this is not the storage room right
so where is the storage
room it's probably the
exit I don't know maybe the door the
girl was
entering wa or maybe this one I don't
know honestly oh this is the one oh yeah
oh yeah yeah I can sense it ooh the
pickup prom is
here a small key small small key under
why this key be in the store room though
cuz uh they said that she moved her bed
from like one room to another we don't
need to read
this
yeah status of like people isn't Miku
the person we played the very first time
remember the one in the super prologue
did we remember the one the super
tutorial the very first woke up in the
water was that Miku that was was that
mik or me
me okay so this is someone
else search aband attempted shadow times
but traces were too weak to follow
supect subject is alive but a newer or
stronger token is required it may be
that the subject does not want to be
found oh oh cute warm and lonely
expression she looks like she might fade
away at any moment
now we have to do something oh even more
Tumi
K family physician I got it mixed up cuz
they got the same uh last
name tendency to blame herself or strive
of her half sister bear self inflicted
wounds strict family maybe the cause
will ask doctor for care after subject
is found search abandoned matter has
been turned over to the police have been
asked to drop the investigation
oh
pretty she's still missing but her
family has giving up the search a case
closed case closed what do you mean Case
Closed oh
y emotionally
unstable excuse me after family loss an
accident stopped going to school a few
days ago neighbors say she left home as
normal claimed to see things others
can't now recovered taking into
custody wait I thought I'm I'm I I not
yi yi is the
Onan oh who am I right now me me I'm me
Y no I
am what you are y yeah no you guys are
making me so confused so is this about
me no no Yi is the Onan another uni
second
uni must the
isao really yeah so is this about this
note safely in my C safely my C so this
is written by he probably believe
close
oh that's me that's you that's you my
God I wonder how much I've changed since
then I still have a hard time looking at
mirrors what okay after so confused dude
it's 12:00 p.m. come me some slack you
even played the game still confused uh I
know it's like the I don't know it's
like the guy messed up with
everything yeah I don't know why we had
to deal with that
just want to play uni all the
time no one else I
still yes your
room yeah I'm trying to like remember oh
it's 12:00 a.m. see I can't even like
tell the time
right yeah so like we see we we in this
stream we play as Miu we play as Yuri we
play as Hoka we play as Ren we played
like four characters
mhm all right we're back back in the
right
room so now we can open
this you don't play ASA you're right
you're right see another subject I don't
even understand
anymore client subject used to be Cafe
Cafe regulars group Suicide was reported
at the time of
disappearance
okay oh yeah
yeah this and me
hinaki
that's that is the
me the person we saw
there what a pose W
cute cette tape from an answering
machine o can we listen to it uh missing
person we're getting so many missing
person files what the hell
K it's so hard to keep up with my brain
at the moment
I never seen this guy before I don't
like
him what do you mean what did he
do he looks
chaty there was a journal tucked away in
the drawer looks like some notes related
to cents and more notes met with a
potential client doesn't know whether
subject is alive or dead says she may
have wanded off somewhere maybe waiting
for help doesn't want to leave home in
case subject comes back on her own I
tripped up said something I shouldn't
have I asked what she'd do when we find
her she laughed and said when she gets
back there are things I want to tell her
her smile looked forc she looked worn
down by it all I should mind my own
business I'm worried about leaving Yuli
alone but this one is urgent no time to
lose I have to go okay and then she
left okay may be able to track her down
if I use this Photograph as a token
okay
okay well weren't we all ready looking
for her but we needed a stronger token
this is
it yo guys I legit don't understand what
she's
saying like it's not your fault but I
just I feel like information's just like
going through my brain yeah I get that a
lot and like you know when went on the
left
ear but wait where do I go
now I got the
token I go to my room maybe yeah
I'm so careful when opening even the the
door to my own room it's it's you know
she's just
[Music]
delicate what now I want to listen to
the tape that we got in the tape
recorder
but make your bed I can't let's leave
okay leave for the I want to sleep on
the
bed soon way soon and what time have you
been sleeping
lately 12 12 oh that's
early yeah 12 is my
bedtime like my Max bedtime or actually
I've been sleeping at last time 8:00
p.m. and maybe
11 what I'm not lying the days I don't
the days I don't stream I slept at 8 and
then sometimes 11: what how long do you
sleep normal I wake up sometimes at 8:00
a.m. or 9 if I can afford sleeping in
oh okay so you just you you sleep early
you wake up relatively early like a
normal time yes so normal the normalist
pile in Holo
live oh using the cam SC you found a
number of missing person Case Files
she's now more more determined than ever
to head back to the mountain and find
hisa okay she's so
determined yay oh I see that was just
yeah really just finding more stuff wait
c x is costumes look oh
X
Punk oh I have to pay for it oh pay with
points n
man I mean I'm I'm interested in Punk
Ensemble or the cuty golf and Ensemble
oh cuty golf sounds tempting too you
think you guys think it's worth it we
could always like farm for
points I mean yeah there doesn't seem to
be a preview what the
hell all right I'll get i'll get this
one bet it'll be looking good oh cute
that's good though that's freaking good
let's
go yo pretty you want to see the others
no cuz they cost
money e yeah the guy is whatever it's
just me and me yeah and L oh me and he
has a what about me what kind of outfit
does me have I don't know going to we're
not even going to play it anytime soon
right but she has the white version of
the cute she has a wi version how what
how you you don't want to get the
matching one well when am I going to see
her wearing it I don't know well next
next chapter I guess maybe she's not
dead 10,000
points I want to I want to I want to buy
uh these are the same points that I use
for my camera upgrades right yes it
is no I have to get camera upgrades
man I mean honestly yeah I have a rule
for myself I have a rule for myself that
my first playthrough I have to use the
original outfits oh okay that's just to
like get Max immersion you know that
kind of thing it's just a me thing do
you think we should play the fourth drop
no no I want to sleep yeah that's
understandable that's fine I think it's
a good timing we did a lot of drop I
don't know why they're called
drops drops like like water droplets M
oh okay okay maybe cuz it's black water
I'm not sure either okay well I do think
like possibly I could even continue
without you cuz I'm not that scared but
honestly I think so oh well I I hear
the yeah the
BL uh so I don't know if I'll continue
this as a as a
playr in the future cuz I have a lot of
other games going
on um but maybe actually maybe you can
you can go to sleep if you want and I'll
try the fourth drop alone cuz my stream
is so short yo oh my god well well can I
watch I might I probably like okay I
want to watch sleeping I'll watch I'll
watch yeah I mean I can literally say
stay but like not say anything
how however you
want all right and then I'll just you
know like basically um be like yo guys
I'm going to head out or something like
that you know okay okay that's fine I'll
I'll prove how how much you've taught me
and how I can handle this alone okay
let's freaking go make me transparent or
something okay I need to restart this
anyway cuz the sound is
like popping again restarting theame
capture so thank you way for helping me
I hope you sleep
well thank you for inviting me finally
we did it but I hope I hope we can
collab again before the year ends oh of
course of
course unless we hate each other too
much yeah I guess so well we'll see what
the future holds we don't know yet but
maybe we'll make up again so you know oh
yeah and I can't promise that I I'll
play much more of this game but if you
want to see more of this game guys waya
played it on her channel so check out
her
archive yay I guess so he how long
ago I don't
remember uh pretty much a long time ago
it's kind of when I was still using the
heart rate monitor a lot I forgot
oh I pretty much a long time ago but
yeah thanks Kiara I'm going to head out
stream's not going to end
so watch her play more Sama
Sama you guys
byebye
byee she's going to be a ghost now
oh there she goes yeah I know we could
have just ended it there but I feel like
um it's kind of short right it's 4 it's
not even 8:00 p.m. here so we can keep
on going if you guys
want I don't want you guys to feel like
stream so short might as well do another
one I guess right seems like I can do it
alone ah
wa way going to start her bedtime
routine now I
guess you can do it yay I believe in
myself so let's see if we had been
searching for a friend a girl called
Haruka M you find a photo of Haruka so
we're going to track it let's go let's
go I trust you I'm still going to watch
while my bedtime routine you
right yo I want to I want raina's
bedtime routine to be uh documented what
is raina's bedtime
routine mine is watching Netflix for a
few hours actually that's a it's not
even that long I I fall asleep so
quickly these days so my bedtime Netflix
time is not that long
okay after finding a missing person's
file she recalls what F said when they
passed the shrine of dolls Haruka she's
here with this in mind yudi heads to the
shrine of dolls hoping that if she finds
Huka she may just learn of hisoka's
whereabouts
too true true
true
yeah I just watched a little bit to
unwind and like calm down and I've
noticed you know that uh for Family Feud
where I was struggling to fall asleep at
[Music]
night I was struggling to fall asleep
and so when I was complaining to you
guys in the pre- chat I ended up after
that I ended up just turning on Seinfeld
quietly and cuddling with smoothie which
is like how I always fall asleep these
days so it actually worked I thought I
thought I want to fall asleep without
the TV on Cu uh you know I'll be fine
I'm I'm tired but it didn't work so then
I turn on the TV and cuddle smoothie and
suddenly I fall asleep
instantly H it's the magical recipe like
my brain is used to it now so I need
it isn't this outfit
cute the the Wobble though her booby
wobble
oh what I feel something
ah okay we're back to the normal camera
that doesn't have the quick shot there
right
[Music]
so shutter
chance he's also a stutter chance where
is
he what what's
where I'm
blind what I don't
ah let's get a Fatal Frame if I
[Music]
can come on attack
me okay I'll wait for you do
it so
close uncomfortably close
what of you you're lame you're so
lame I just take normal pictures of you
then
okay ah ah ah ah
Dodge wait wait wait wait why couldn't I
take a picture is my lens not
on was it not on did I switch it again
why do I I don't I don't think I'm
really touching that area but
CH
[Music]
chance is he dead I think he's
dead okay
nice oh wait I should get upgrades I
wanted to get upgrades uh
camera
enhancements ah we got the loader
upgrade for the other
dude oh oh wait are these different
absorption increasing spirit Power
absorbed damage loading I feel like
absorption might be
different which one should I get what do
you think shared points but different
upgrades
yeah that's
weird loader and output yeah let's take
loader for
sure I could get no not not another
another different
one output increases I will do that
yeah okay now we have invested our money
wisely
check beautiful clear water flows down
the bare surface of the rock here it is
clear yeah otherwise it's in other
places it's
red how is everybody's Halloween going
so far
nice reaction
wa behind the waterfall
oh she's not
real toiling away at work a it's my
dad's birthday so we went out for dinner
oh
ni don't celebrate it here yeah we don't
really celebrate it here either like as
a child definitely something we tried to
you know make use off a little bit to
get free
snacks but it's not as big as in
America I awoke to the sound of water
should I press on or go back this is the
point of no return if I want to see for
you here
again I wouldn't say it was a point of
no return you're still like on the
mountain I knew something was there but
like what I couldn't and then it
was
ah all these jumping
people there's so ah here the
item the fast ones that jump I I
rarely get
them but I guess that's where the
upgrades to slow down comes
in
I don't know when I would be getting
that buy bags of candy and give them out
to my neighbors oh that is
sweet are you going to check them before
for safety you mean like how I checked
the S before giving it to the bride just
to make sure that it's
not
poisonous uh did I tell that story
members
only or in real in a real stream members
only streams are just your
imagination oh it was members only
that's okay we can reference
it
nice okay so in the beginning I missed
so many but now it's really not that bad
I should not be taking these with the
good film though
oh guys did you see I tweeted out the
one
sponsored the one sponsored stream that
was not on the schedule cuz I was
waiting but I really wanted to put out
the
schedule yeah so this week's sponsored
stream on Sunday is Mai Mai chocolate
but the one on thur day is uh a game
Star Ocean the like it's like a master I
think of an old
one yeah from Square Enix I was really
happy to get another
jrpg
uh um yo what for real yeah another jrpg
sponsorship it seems like I'm the go-to
girl yeah Second Story I I never played
a Star Ocean game before so I'm curious
you
I also know nothing about
it I just watch the
trailer that was
it but I think it's a good series people
say good things about it maybe it's a
little bit underrated I don't
know it's basically Tails but in space
aha the Star Ocean death Ed deaths for
the first tales off game what what a
connection I came here because of the
sunset it was so beautiful it made me
want to cry it was the same as the
sunset I saw when I
survived the sun seemed to sink into the
mountain I had to come and see it
melting away into the Waters of the
mountain seems natural it seems right I
feel like the others are telling me to
the ones who didn't survive the sunset
is drawing closer or maybe I'm drawn to
it
I want a throat candy because even
though I didn't scream or talk so much
my throat
hurts
H straining my throat on
Halloween so it's coming out
like now or
what leave me alone
what is she
saying shut the
chance I I forgot completely the the
difference of like shutter chance and
the normal
photo yeah yeah fatal frames
baby let's use a stronger
one look there go I just it just feels
effective so I keep on doing
it let me
go let me they keep on they so close
they're so
close no let me
go there's bloody hands on my
screen
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
okay okay okay
oh dying oh
okay damn I never saw that before the
bloody hands oh wait am I
um is that the T the taint the am I
tainted I don't
know faster reload definitely yeah I
feel it and the the damage damage um
that was faster than other
fights yeah it's not draining so I guess
it's
fine
okay
okay no pictures
okay uh there's a shrine Road wiped out
by the landslide and the pathways up
there
yeah
no
no not so close to the cliff
please where is
she where is
she in the stone she's in the
Stone come
out W she come out
oh
what I should be using my weak ones
again she's still there I just can't
what
what oh oh oh is she
behind no she's just inside okay
nice pictures of a rock there there she
is I was waiting for
[Music]
you what oh I wanted to make use of the
faat frame more but like I literally
don't know where the she is all
this
time oh just went through me h ah ah sh
CH sh the CH
yes
oh wow that's what I call a Fatal Frame
like literally it's just
falling dead now she
dead that was a nice
shot do we go up here okay
a fork in the road yeah
yeah I remember this place so we'll go
this
way oh item again why do film I
think one year anniversary for four
blood thank
you man for blood will forever be in our
hearts as a one of everybody's
favorites of my
[Music]
covers
I'm alive still
breathing yes I am this I am I am
alive photo up anybody that's what I
thought that's what I
thought harda peering into the
river
girl you got to walk around this bridge
is
broken oh another raid wait o
wait we are playing Fatal Frame kiaha is
playing a scary scary spooky friller
horror game that's right I know I know
unbelievable something unexpected 2 Days
in a even this is something you will
only get for
Halloween a frog Meer nice I love
frogs I love
frogs I don't know why they make us go
through this whole area again kind of
lame I wish they just would give us a
shortcut but okay this way I can get
some items I guess oh what's this
oh
memories ah is it a video someone took
on a video camera recorder this is the
Hanging Tree I
guess certainly looks like
it this is where people do it what what
is
that
[Music]
what the
hell
freak need to be more
[Applause]
confident okay what what is
this thing
oh here he
comes I messed
[Applause]
up doy do oh shutter chance
nice the maiden slay the maiden Slayer
but he didn't even slay a maiden in that
moment oh cuz like that was a dude that
he
killed seems he just want to kill
anybody all right here he comes here he
comes or does he no thought he was
getting ready
oh
n
[Applause]
uh-oh here was always thinking that I
was always
already
uh locked on I guess I can ah do it
without wait I'm dying wait I'm
dying what was I
dying since when was my health so
[Music]
low okay okay let's go serious time now
what the is
this
I'm so scared of circles circles terrify
me ah
you know uh I was watching AA a
while ago play some weird game when you
draw
circles you're trying to get the perfect
circle that's all there is to it the
whole game is just you trying to draw a
perfect
circle perfectly
balanced
come
[Applause]
on N my sh
chance should I get the stronger film 59
oh I do have I do have different ones
M okay but I'm waiting for the right
moment he's just
lurking ah n it disappeared in that
I hate
[Music]
[Applause]
that
okay
attack me try
me he juked us extinguish the torch
makes
[Applause]
invisible I was taking a
picture ah
ah
okay I I don't even feel like I need to
focus on him I'm I'm used to doing it
without the
focus and that must have hit hard I
think so
goodbye run run
run should I heal one more
time this dude's
[Applause]
strong it's so close and yet get
invisible
oh yeah okay I I it seems like I need to
do one of these shutter chance things
otherwise I won't be able to see
him oh that was a f frame oh
okay kind of hard to read this
guy okay he died I think is that his
death
qu
exercised can you call it
exorcism is an
exorcism I guess is it I guess
so
I just
pooped all right
following waa what is that it's like
elves wandering through the
forest but it's Shrine
maidens yeah I see it thank
you I took it with the strong
film h
another lore moment about takanashi Kiwa
in case you didn't know it yet I've used
to be a shrine Maiden in Japan is a side
job
yeah pretty cool
huh
no that was really interesting the most
difficult part about it was every
morning putting on the the outfit cuz
like all my colleagues were like really
fast and really good at it and I was
like they T they showed me once and then
I felt like cuz I didn't really know
anybody there then I felt like I
couldn't really ask anybody for help it
was like super shy and intimidated so I
was always like struggling with it and
taking ages to put it on while everybody
else just took like 2 minutes and then
left and I I for me it takes like 30
minutes to go out for this kill
right oh he is guing out the eyes
Gucci super shy super shy but wait a
minute while I put on my work uniform
hey he's still he still there take
another picture
[Music]
but no
but but it was
nice once I finally had the outfit
on P he didn't see the sunset only I
could see it that's why I have to go
alone the light of the Setting Sun lives
on in the mountain I wish for you he
could have seen it you ever get good at
it
no I I say I still suck at it if I would
try but I haven't tried like I would say
generally like the Miko Shrine maiden
outfit but also other Japanese
traditional clothes
generally they all work kind of similar
in how you put it
on so once you have the gist of it down
for one of
them let
go then the others shouldn't be much of
an issue except for like kimon no like
you can't really
compare like a really proper kimono to
Yukata Shrine maid in hakama hakama
hakama is
easier than
[Music]
kimono need
help for
Kimo
something
something is that sound Q not like a
sign of something weird close
[Music]
by
hanuka heading into the grounds yeah
yeah thank
you I was wearing hakama pants for
kendle they're really confy yeah I think
so too I think they
are quite comfortable to wear check
dolls of various sizes have been placed
around the shrine white faces with faint
Smiles gaze out from the dirty kimonos
and black
hair
but what are those dolls called I would
say they're just general dolls I don't
know if
they have a particular name
oopsie release h
what the is
that it's just another
doll yeah just a doll life-size doll I
don't want to go inside
here wait to come back to
me e that's creepy as e what if
they come to Al
come
on that's what I
mean it's
saved but why did it
save don't don't touch my leg don't
touch me don't touch
me
I
well we'll be needing that
uh This Way well I can't see so well
it's really
dark what oh nothing okay that was just
my my my
Trace okay for here okay okay healing
you think there's a boss upcoming right
away no I guess I could heal a little
bit uh wait what where's
[Music]
my no it's supposed to be this
dark it's for the
immersion if I raise it it's just going
to look
gray there's a doll the stairs yep I can
see that I mean in theory it's a pretty
doll but like in this
environment ooh water oh wait I can't go
for the doll nice
block later I might be able to pass who
knows oh more dolls let's
go somebody likes to collect
them two
items
a
present
H oh oh it's really present Crush lens a
lens that deals more damage to targets
based on its level to use it equip it to
your camera obscure and press why when
you have enough spirit
Power a so it's like different
from
H why like with the shutter
one
H I was looking up like literally away
from the screen stop it just thinking
doing a little
think give me this piece of paper
man ever since we survived I felt like
every day could be my last I feel closer
to F he than ever it's nice sharing
secrets of her sharing my guilt we often
talk about the past I remember remember
a lot of things from back then like how
her face was the first picture I drew in
kindergarten we split the sheet of paper
and Drew each other I remember growing
taller than her and how she stayed at my
house while hers was being renovated we
often talk about that kind of stuff most
of all I remember singing the song of
memories at kindergarten
graduation graduation I look over at fi
and she was already looking at me waving
whenever I hear that song it makes me
want to go back there to that time my
whole life has been flashing before my
eyes of all the moments that's the one I
want to keep on living over and over
forever what where's Haruka oh behind
there was that Haruka yeah there's
something under the doll display
oh a candle
oh but that's not what we
mean
o stairs below the do display how might
have gone down there the wooden great w
buds there must be a way to open it burn
it with the
candle is that not why it's
there
what oh she's
so oh you found me
cute oh
dear you can't die either
huh I mean I don't know if I could I
didn't try you want to go down
there I know you want to die
no before you do how about a game what
don't play with this crazy
girl this is you mm- doesn't look like
me it's an effigy what does that mean I
don't understand
English find me if you
can no not the kids
[Music]
again camera is reacting to
something
oil
another doll perhaps no what the is
that something in the photo a person
hanging from a
tree
M okay yeah yeah but that's outside then
right or do I look for a
[Music]
window do I leave this place again so
fleeing T you're just standing right now
there we go wait it's a it's a here the
path is open do I go
there
but I don't know if it's time for that
my my my thingy doesn't work right now I
can't let the game tell me where to go
sadly I'll open this
oh don't think we've entered here before
nice nice
film a model of a person usually made to
be destroyed
ah kind of like a voodoo doll but not
really cuz you're not supposed to
destroy voodo dolls you're just hurting
them but why made to be destroyed why
why would you destroy it just out of
Rage I can see water for a hole in the
passageway floor some of the dolls are
missing from the Shelf they must have
been washed away do it
oh oh
YouTube Oh
spooky
spooky oh we're back YouTube spook
YouTube doing us a little
spook
spooky should I read this
again what I it's not over here when the
mountain of flowing Waters have long
been whatever life Springs from the
water then returns to it all of the
bones in the cave beneath the shrine had
been laid into the waters this was
probably considered to be a way of
returning life to the water the shrine
was built upon the pure water river with
a walkway Crossing it I have found
numerous dolls at the bottom of the
river and downstream these dolls were
likely placed on the water as a form of
memorial for those they
depicted
n h are you two being funky
again not everybody maybe now we're back
again okay the oh yeah YouTube is being
haunted stay with me guys
don't let the ghosts take over you you
have your own
will oh which way do I
[Music]
go
oh wait but like why would it where
would this tree
be there's so many doors now so many
paths okay this one's this one's
powerfully shut closed
huh was I supposed to photograph
that
photograph wait so is the door open
now
no I have a map but like Does it show
the
tree h no
H this one opens
okay
H give me give me give me give me give
me give me give me give me give me give
me I think a doll just fell over
again no
no I guess I'll walk over to look at
this in the middle oh oh oh yeah yeah
what is this mastman is it the guy I was
fighting
no okay that's it
here
still
Clos am I here too early I feel like so
far the game was so linear that it
wasn't possible for me to go anywhere
where I'm not supposed to
go yet but I feel like I came for there
like this seems like
logic logic to go here need to go into
the water can
I Tippy tappy Tippy tappy Tippy tappy
ah
blind I'm going to get
wet oh wet marker not going up
though
interesting I guess I didn't get
wet oh
hello
oh we
fight no
okay a haunted
[Music]
doll got some medicine it's exactly what
I
need wa yeah oh yeah should
I you guys just keep on telling them I'm
too lazy to put a comment or
so the other
side
a wa is still there you'll do
it wait door
door okay oh oh that's creepy that's
creepy I can see a large door through a
crack in the
door but then if we pin that then our
thing has to
go did you ride it oh she
did our viewer
discretion oh well oh well it's probably
not much
longer
pin I Am A Brave
Bird why why is this doll there just to
haunt me later on
seems like these are one hit
wonders the door and then here is
nothing
else
nothing I updated
it okay here no
where I don't see
you I don't see
you wait is that a
door it is a door but wait wait maybe
there's an item over there at the end of
the room
here update the updated message
what what
[Music]
it's fine the way it
is damn
it oh I
D don't
move don't move freaky
doll okay
okay is there another door no okay so
it but
there's there's something there for me
to pick up
right oh
open every time everything is so
ominous the Heart Light Shadows
yeah and if I would have played this
yesterday it maybe would have freaked me
out really
bad anyway I think that was some nice
film oh now it's okay so this whole time
I was going the right way obviously oh
oh there's many hanging bodies not just
one and it's kind of neighor like
uh uh
uh what what is there
well foggy mhm
Franky ew something's
there I can't see
it must be right
there if it keeps on moving like
that what I don't get it
to look
up I don't want
[Music]
to now it's up now it's
gone do you want a
[Music]
picture what
a
what just a charging sound just a
charging
sound okay sometimes these items are
just
like what the
hell n
whatever
keep your camera ready
guys
proceed Haruka didn't come this way her
Trace led me inside the building oh do I
have a trace right now no
no
but oh okay this is where it
end hey but yeah wait I was supposed to
see something hanging on a tree right so
yeah but like I'm I'm seeing things but
like not the right thing
and do I have
[Music]
to
what under I see
anything but here it makes the woo sound
I had the FG yeah yeah that's what I'm
looking
for
maybe there's nothing I can focus on
F
AF I find the right
angle okay oh
wait what was it in the
records uh
this
one
okay yeah I mean that's not so far off
of what I was doing it's definitely
like what what what was that ah is it
this one
[Music]
no it can't
be it's this one is this one for
sure I had it for a moment
[Music]
but can I crouch to take the picture
from a lower
angle this one that keeps turning it
turns to
me this one doesn't turn to me there's a
different one turning to
me
wait are you maybe
no what is it wait it might be turning
to
me
holy
[Laughter]
terrifying absolutely
terrifying sounded like something fell
into the
bushes oh over there oh it's my
Effigy whatever that
means so-called
Effigy not I think it was made to look
like me it doesn't look like me at all
it doesn't even have a proper face
ohoh oh ah the kids ah
ah oh
[Music]
you want to play with the epig or
what you can have it I don't want
it oh so fast can I get a
oh no no no
no can I get a can I get a can I get a A
can I get
[Music]
a okay wao can I get to a faster turn
thingy let me get stronger thingy
film oh nice got chance nice
nice got as many as possible on
[Music]
there ah oh you little bu
I thought I W that's a lot I
thought I already exercised you
guys oh they dying I think the other one
is still alive yeah she's cute really
wonder what happened with
her what's the purple thing nice shutter
attack me
H she Jed
me there's not many
like like things to capture
so
oh
what it's some kind of a Fatal Frame she
wasn't attacking me but ah she was
hurting herself oh oh okay okay she's
she's freaking out I'm freaking out
we're all freaking out n that's that's
how you that's what you do you act like
you're you act like you're falling down
need help okay I try to help you and
then you do this to
me uhhuh we got to go back to the shrine
wherever that
was
okay oh
hi I go this way I still have
no no
Trace is that a meme call an ambulance
but not for me
yeah oh
hi me what where is that
from do I have to go down wait where
would I go down I have to go down right
I don't want to go into the
water uh
path
what can I go through
there
no I'm
lost
uh the door I came out
of the red ones are closed aren't
they the blue one is the one I just came
from maybe I took the wrong
entrance a spirit guide
offline oh no it's the right one
it oh okay that was the outside wait
then I go left here
ah that must be
it
maybe oh yeah this room just a wait what
is where where where are we
going oh no that might
be
connected I didn't enter this room
before huh did
I there's something there there's
something there there it's
confusing you see the white things well
wait maybe there's two things one is
here
what an old
document having sat abandoned for many
years the shrine of dolls has now
undergone significant reconstruction in
the past local Legends tell that the
shrine used so-called Effigies as
offerings these effes are likely the old
dos that were found inside
uhuh the road to the shrine was improved
and so the number of visitors gradually
increased there was no end to the
visitors bringing their own dolls to add
to those left outside assuming this
practice to be harmless no effort has
been made to prevent it as we were
repairing the old dolls we learned that
each of them is engraved with a name we
also found tiny teeth bones and small
bundles of hair tucked away inside were
these mere keepsakes or perhaps
something
more yeah the erors are
confusing when you get too close to them
they're like wopop the purpose of the
shrine has since become clear it appears
these dolls were believed to contain the
Souls of deceased children and were
likely offered to the shrine as some
kind of ritual we also learned of a cave
below the shrine h no as the womb Cavern
it housed several human remains perhaps
initially it was not please don't tell
me I have to go there it was not dolls
offered up at The Shrine but people it
seems the cavern may be where the bodies
were disposed we are considering
renovating the cabin into storage space
placing the bones into dolls of their
own and holding a joint memorial service
for them
all what you want to put the dead bodies
like basically the all the bones into
dolls instead oh there's eyes
e uh
Shrine one
is Ghost marriage okay a lot of
games uh my fear is that these games are
based on actual rituals that took place
on the mountain mountain in my dreams my
the games go on until the children
disappear into the Mist I wonder what
would happen if they took me with
them let's hope we will not find
out oh this one's supposed oh later
maybe in that
case we got to
go around here well wonder about this
door I never tried opening
it
this
one it
opens don't get scared guys don't get
scared it's nothing it's just a
doll
Shake It Up sh Shake it up Shake it
up Shake it up Shake Shake Shake it
off Shake it
off Shake it off that's it that's all
this room is
[Music]
okay that's what people
say that's what people
[Music]
say Dancing On My
Own be
say mhm I know people say
mhm but I keep
moving Don't Stop Don't Stop
gring do I really have to go down there
is this what what's
happening no it's possible which means
they want me to do it but no I have to
go back to this rain maybe
later I have to go back to the how do I
go back maybe I have to go outside but
this door is
closed
H right this
door for here but wait how do I enter
that
one did
I did I go through here is this how I
came here cuz now it seems like the only
path
a
what is
this I
can't oh we are fighting okay okay we're
fighting I get it okay we're
fighting
Bo let's use a strong
one
[Music]
a FAL frame FAL frame FAL frame FAL
frame what up like
that what the
hell go away from
me suddenly showing up like that is not
cool oh
FAL frame no oh it's when he drowns he's
like playing playing a game with me of
drowning I will not reach out my hand
for you to save you no I will
not you want to drown again
huh oh yeah okay he wants that's a
yes that's a yes
guys replaying oh he likes to replay it
a
lot
shot the
chance
hey how much more do you want
huh where is he going to show up behind
me oh
yeah I want to try
something oh I still got it I still got
it I still got it
all
right oh he's
dead now he's dead for
real not listening to your
screams is this the right
way is this the way do you know that way
ohop so weird that they just fall
down must must have been an
earthquake sa water should I
heal
uh not so bad but I I I'll heal maybe a
little
bit the pickup
animation it's really just so that
there's a chance that I could get
grabbed and that I I could catch it in a
moment
yeah okay for the first
time but it's just so dramatic each
time special
film when you
both what kind of situation is this
compared to when you both try to take
something from a shelf at the
supermarket and then you touch and then
it's like
a oopsie I guess we wanted to ride the
same thing uh kind of moment kind of
romantic what the
what too close I can't
see nice nice yeah Blaster Blaster
up
M what is what is
this what are
you yeah oh she's posing so nicely for
me
woohoo
hey try it again P for me
you're so photogenic after all ah that
wasn't get out of here get out of
here I shot too
early
yeah is there like a way to look at all
these pictures by the way or are they
just like you can't look at them are
they discarded or are they safe
somewhere
oh oh oh with me
no
no get back stay
back who are you going to
call
n no no no no
no yeah yeah we've seen that
before how much more do you want huh
you're using up so much of on my
fil what was the other lens I got the
crush L what do that do
again I don't
remember don't I have to like this now I
have the crush Dan on more
damage okay let's try
a did did did it work I think so cuz now
it's grade
out
where yeah it's great out now it
did let's use one of the 61 types cuz I
have so
many ah too early
wait
dead
[Music]
ooh oh oh Shadow chance beautiful Shadow
chance that was it right
no where is
she should be dead now okay nice
finisher
okay I was about to leave this place I
think but I don't
know what is
this no no no tou I don't want to touch
your hand I don't want to start a
supermarket
romance oh mirror Stone
oh okay let's go this way I
guess no that
restore lens a lens that restores your
health based on how much damage is dealt
to the Target oh so life eating HP
eating restoring like a Pokemon to use
it equip you okay how do I even know
which one is which they like in the
bottom left menu you guys aren't seeing
it when I I guess cuz I'm covering it
but
I don't understand which one is
which yeah life Le that's life steal
that's what I was trying to
say please tell me I went the right
way
yes oh yeah oh yeah this is the place
are you ready guys whatever happens it's
okay I'll give you all a hug
afterwards
saving how can you still alive from a
ghost right I guess it doesn't work no
in this game it
works so I'm
here nothing's
happening I go to this place yeah the
girl was sitting in the middle of the
doll this place I should try placing a
doll here ni here we can play
together stay until you feel like dying
I'm never giving up she doesn't know I'm
a phoenix are we
fighting okay are we staying in this
small
[Music]
room oh okay she's like one of
these yeah one of the kids they
just oh she even has her minions she has
minions ah
ah get out of here get out of
here I feel like
this no out
no she's
[Applause]
[Music]
difficult oh what was that damn it damn
it the other chance I missed my sh
chance give it to me again
please
both ideally both
yeah interesting it's the first that
they're doing something with minions I
like
[Music]
it no no no no no no no no no she Hur
me let's heal a little
[Applause]
[Music]
we got it okay
okay okay
okay
o well that's my Effigy don't don't
don't break it is it like a shield for
[Music]
her yeah I got it I got it we a strong
one of the
61 I'm like I sound like a photography
geek
now I got the perfect picture with the
with the 6 type 61 film yeah the other
day yeah it was
amazing all is this like a guess who's
who kind of
thing ah
oh no no hold no yeah it was uh two
eff I do take pictures often
[Music]
yeah I excel at selfie
photography
[Music]
shitaka okay I need the weak
one
oh what what who whoa whoa what are you
doing another
one
ah oh beautiful
beautiful get off of
me supposed to be one
hit
[Music]
okay how many more she's spamming
them wa Who whoo wao good timing good
timing unfortunately I had to weak film
cuz I don't want to waste it on the on
the cheap cheap ones oh here we go a
[Music]
on yes now no no no no no not quite not
quite oh not quiet not
quiet do it again please I'm ready
[Music]
now oh which one do I focus
on there's something coming from the
left I hear it
oh it's gone now it will come
back
[Music]
oh t a
t i light the camera like it keeps on
resetting okay okay
[Music]
I have to use the expensive one I can't
keep on
Switching
yo
[Music]
oh
whatever can't wait for
it
[Music]
wide lens
angle
oh and not now
really that was not the
timing what was that who who ah please
let me let me take a picture let me
take she died anyway let's
go she didn't say
cheese didn't get so many fatal frames
but it's
okay it was a difficult timing for
her we're putting it back again on the
display last time we placed it the girl
appeared are you sure sure about
this just break it just destroy it the
wooden lad is blocking the Hidden
Staircase has opened uh where what head
underground
okay what wooden
lce a wait key you think that's what it
is to womb C oh out here it's like right
here anyway okay good thank you
no h the
womb entering the womb I'm tired by the
[Music]
way what the
hell crazy
oh thanks for the advice I'm trying my
best Oh wrong
type do I need
healing a little bit
oopsie would you want to continue this
game after Halloween uh well if I run
out of games maybe yeah but like
generally I
have oh yeah there it is ah it
didn't work no
no damn it both times
missed funny if I run out of uh
games
oh sure but currently we have so
many
a also I'm I'm I got to play Tales of
arise soon the DLC which is not
sponsored anymore like me playing it it
was just sponsored for me introducing it
but I obviously want to play
it surprise
surprise ghost hand yet I know when I
read chat when I'm like not 100% focused
turn around it's a dead and okay
someone's floating there cool
cool
this oh it's like sealed maybe to keep
something
out KN is broken got to burn it in these
times just burn it a black box sits in a
hollow along the passage Ro what the
what the
hell a seals to keep the freshness
in is this the right path or this is
where I came from no it's the right one
cuz there's a new
item but yeah it's not it's not that
scary
like so I feel like I can handle it
alone in the future too and it's kind of
funny so I wouldn't mind playing it more
just uh it's just a m matter of uh the
other things I got going on so if we
ever have a gap I think like this kind
of game is doesn't matter if we play it
with like a six month Gap in
between there we
go before The
Relic no Huka you don't have to do that
I would advise to refrain from that
are we done
girl I wasted the the this thing
because of you but does that mean she's
in that box where the hand is hanging
out please say
no that's her sweater
no
[Music]
a unboxing
video unboxing
haruk is it is it is it Haruka
yeah
Haruka worst unboxing
ever
har that
[Music]
beautiful become mea
Hara nice dark
humor uh I feel
secure I'm not
scared nice
lips
weard does is he holding a mirror he's
absorbing her
soul does she have a
mustache lady
stash look like she had a lady stash for
a
moment
no yeah that's terrifying cuz like
it's like you're being buried alive no
well drowned I guess cuz here comes the
water and the realization only kicks in
the moment when it's just too
late oh no she's
not she being controlled by a ghost or
something oh she not alive no no no
no no I don't believe it I don't believe
it stay with
me
no oh
how is she
alive I don't believe it okay we
fight
[Music]
oh a
oh how was that not a Fatal Frame ah is
that the timing when I should take the
[Music]
picture no leave
me got it got it got it got it got it
got it got got it got it okay uh we need
uh healing
ABA Abba
shot but due to International copyright
laws it's not oopsie ah n no I
don't want to what's happening I don't
want to watch a
scene that's by accident I thought that
I'd be scared of death no no no
no Panic press but I can't even cry how
long is
this
no I can't cancel it I'm pressing all
the
buttons I am
alone in the
end I am
alone what you
got I will end it all hostage by cut
scene see now
oops this is what I wanted to do maybe
another
one cuz this seems like
a important battle let's take no am I
want some
[Music]
[Applause]
distance oh
no
okay let's use this strong
one
honestly I really don't understand the
focus feature much I feel like I like
this more cuz then I get more of the
circles but maybe during a Fatal Frame
will it tell
me it's kind of
close it's hard to tell if I do it like
that oh oh yeah yeah yeah nice TR to
dance I'm kind of stuck
here e she's wriggling
[Music]
it helps to fail frame
really for me it's now more difficult
cuz I'm used to doing it like this if
you lock you guarantee a shot so if you
don't then you get more
[Music]
damage and but I got plenty of fatal
frames without blocking
on
[Music]
ah there it
is oh that's
it my my film must have been too
powerful okay I'll take it a win is a
win me
I'm Yuri I'm
Yuri who is you sent here to come and
look for
you so quiet can you walk come on let's
get out of
here all
right how is she
alive guess she wasn't drowned for that
long check uh okay
no okay it's under water somewhere
inside this one too I guess we not we're
not checking I mean we opened the one
from her and she was still alive we
don't want to test if the others are
still alive maybe no no no don't don't
give them a chance
no check her pulse
check this
way follow me Hada
too dark for me to enjoy the crowd
shot this
way where are we
going guess she was outside asked you to
come find
me was it fui
yeah yes it was she kept on talking
about you man I want to see her guess
she was right saying that you're in here
I need to
apologize it's too late to
apologize it's too
late we're going out
right at least for
now she's probably dead what she is
right what did we see did we see her die
anti- wetness thingy nah no
need yeah we did oh we saw her cutting
her throat I
guess e I'm so L I'm I'm making these
like BL sounds
Yi forgive me it's okay she's dead she
might attack us though that won't be
nice
ghost lady why did I Wrong
room wrong room or is it wait
what no not wrong room wait what no
that's going down
again well or do I go through there to
get to the big doll room again I'm so
confused down down down by the river is
this where I came from
no okay I mean in some way in some way
it
is this is the right way I
hope go St not or I mean I guess I mean
I don't see him but I guess it's that
way
then I don't see the
GS
wrong wrong way where I was going or
wrong way where this is telling me to
focus
on but what if I turn
around no it tells me to look
here
okay yeah a lot of backtracking I guess
here that's the door sometimes the doors
look like the same as the
walls I told you we' be together
too wrong
way no
way I can't use it I can't use it it's
not
working it was it
wrong
oh now it
works or does it just show me where she
is
oh sorry I'm lost
my small
room am I not going here I guess Ah
that's why all the hanging dolls were
maybe now I can go there though don't
you think they want me to go here I
don't really
know I could go for the
water is that the it's one exit
maybe yeah since I haven't gone there
yet just like logically thinking and
from the POV of the
game it was blocked off four but the map
looks like it still continues there
little uh wait wasn't it the other way
the other
side wait
door
and check the map again does this path
work here here here here here
yeah well I guess that's a happy thing
that she's still alive I'm just I didn't
want to believe it cuz that didn't
seem wait wait wait
uh oh I missed it cuz I was
switching for the films Mama
Mia scaring the out of me what
where is this uh
what
should
here and
then
[Music]
here yes we're outside let's see if it's
the right outside if that's where they
wanted me to go if not then I'm
sorry but you know there was this path
here but it did say I don't think they
went here
proceed I found how we need to get off
this mountain
do you mean not in that direction n
maybe another time you have to go
here cuz it does say proceed so it feels
like sometime that you you will be able
to proceed through here N I have to go
for this maze
again I guess yeah just goes up
higher let's see does this path work
even
can I go through
here
yeah I wish I had a mini
map oh but that door is
closed that
door that door wouldn't work would
it
uh that's not not a door is this a
door is this a door that I just didn't
try
yet this Temple needs to be
replanted it's
amazing an amazing maze I I never tried
opening this
one cuz that's why it was grayed out but
what is this just a tiny storage room
Workshop
closet oh there's something in there
though
hey I just came back here for
completionist but I can't open
it what this room is
useless this room is
[Laughter]
useless
who so this one is still closed
mhm okay oh my God if only moving around
wasn't such a pain in the
ass
um have to go outside no all for the
stairs the stairs these stairs
here are they like going through the
water was that what those
were oh I've taken a picture of the
draw St let's go down to the
water which water the good
[Music]
water this one
uh wait is this the the womb the womb um
path
uh
no is that
[Music]
uh you guys have any direction sense
going on right now it's just a Flo of
okay good good y that's also what I
thought going back all the way is pretty
annoying I must
say I wish that wasn't
necessary
can't rush through the water
either all
right and then for here
no no no ideally not cuz that's kind of
but what's this this
[Music]
room what was that
again a the bus fight
room
yeah that's the boss fight
room so we go here and then down
here and the double doors the dumble
doors hey I thought we go right
now we go
straight take a ride that's what I
thought taking a
ride yeah right right okay you say take
the dumble
doors why why why sorry oh she's talking
that's a good
sign oh
loading should I get
myself
dry does this mean I'm I also have the
taint or am I just
wet and wet
your okay way says so way is still
watching way is watching above us
protecting us so sorry so so sorry it's
okay uh uh just cornering me
[Music]
ah no run run run to this side so I can
fight her
better her
again we've had this fight before Oh no
I no
no Fatal Frame at least I got a Fatal
Frame out of
that she got uncomfortably close to me
but where
she okay I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready
I'm ready
anytime Dance For
Me dance for me the shrine Maiden
Dance show show show
show and I show you a different dance I
can show you the pineapple
Dance I'm going one two it's just
menacingly
slowly coming
closer N I wasn't Fade All why you don't
Fade
All I'm going
[Music]
two me I'm taking
pict yes
no oh my God I miss it oh you're
approaching
me I want that
pineapple give
me
okay maybe we should keep it Square cuz
when she comes closer to me feel like
square is actually
better no I missed it
again ah ah okay thank you for holding
my hand and like teaching me how to
Fatal Frame you just like literally
holding my hand to make me do it ah
there we go this was my own Fatal Frame
yeah
H this one came from
me oh she did they die like so weirdly
like you think you're not done yet and
then suddenly they're like well I guess
I'll
die guess I'll
die not worth it
anymore I shall he heal one more time
holy I'm healing so much in this
level the death so long you can touch
him oh I see during that time I should
be touching
them I
see I forgot some I thought she's just
going to follow me on her own what do I
does she need a special invitation or
what there she
is she needed a special
invitation
I can hear a
song what's that song yeah tell me about
it after I pick up the
item
hey there she
goes once
again doing stupid
ooh I must kill them all every
Shrine maid and I can't stand their eyes
I must goou them out they have seen too
much
okay wait she went that
way
um this
okay maybe maybe I saw the all the
directions are confusing
me
okay who you here she's she's not there
oh is this where we uh come to see
me
um is it leading us to that
Lake H wrong way
what
yeah we
did um girl time to
go I guess not time to
fight
oh yeah crushed it I think I thought I
did maybe I
didn't what was that time
oopsy he I'm
bloody no I did use the crush but I
missed no is there more than
one okay I'll just do normal ones
then
am I tainted or something no why am
I suddenly
bloody no no why you
teleport no no no no no what I'm not how
was that a Fatal
Frame I only got her
knife
okay if you if you're happy with that
then I'm happy
with okay already a fail frame when she
holds it up like that okay good to
know so that would be one oh yeah yeah
yeah
okay
sweet a sh now she
teleported oh no yeah now I got it yeah
yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
nice no come
on
[Music]
okay if it's Fatal
Frame in this
version but the game is called project
zero in in the European
version but they use the word Fatal
Frame all the time why did they not just
keep it Fatal
Frame also what's it called in Japanese
F fur or something else come on all
these
questions and no
answers just zero
this Fatal Frame no I mean like the shot
that you take like me I my guy just
did that's
zero yeah you know what I mean I don't
mean the game I mean this Fatal Frame
that I'm like doing to do big
damage zero what you doing there
got a mechanic girl I saw the
settings it was drawing me in wait dud
dud is here a part of it as if I were
melting the
gang well what's important is that
you're back mhm don't go there ever
again Miracle you're not hurt mhm truly
a
miracle
let
no where is fui I don't
know is she
here this girl needs
therapy I hear a
song that
song Haruka please just try and get some
rest for now
okay right
[Music]
thank you you're
welcome
damn well certainly a traumatizing
experience being put in a box like that
almost drowning to
death
is that her
song this just my room right nobody's in
here
okay what the that creeped me out
whoa thought was a dead body he must be
having a terrible nightmare it wasn't my
room it was indeed his
room
now I see his
dream this is the girl that we fought I
think did I did I kill her no I killed
her don't don't look at
me at least the
ghost
wake up huh Ren it's
time for
what Super Chat the reading time we'll
leave
now you should get some
rest I
know good
night I guess
so
super chatting time super chatting time
super chatting super chatting super
chatting time super chatting super
chatting superat
reading
shiny that's a a big bathtub for a
Japanese
house hair
extensions
no no I'm being put in the
box it is
shot I've
noticed hey I changed my
clothes she's
wet chapter done
when a dream it was just like the memory
I saw when I touched sha in the cave I
need to know more maybe if I ask her
[Music]
okay wait is she downstairs or upstairs
upstairs right is
she it's not in here
right
no then I think she's
downstairs
so wish
wait yeah in the storage
room next to the couch
[Music]
room where is which one is which is this
a
room bathroom oh the bathroom first time
I found that
oh ooh o she gone she
gone nah I'm done rescuing all these
girls I'm done I'm not running after
them that's why this game is ending
here I I should put
them in in in in handcuffs honestly I
know
but like what choice do I
have I want to box
H I'm alone but she's looking cute in
the outfit I don't know why we switched
back again
but what what what what what what
what is is the video going backwards or
do she walk backwards cuz she's like
needs to be exercised
oh it's her
ghost I see Yi finds the missing Haruka
in a relic in a cave beneath the shrine
of dolls she takes the girl back to the
shop Huka is in no state to talk and
can't explain what happened to her that
night Huka is visited by fuu's ghost
which takes her back to the
mountain
again only be oh man I took too many
healing portions and stuff again but
damn it was
difficult it was pretty difficult
[Music]
man it is the fifth the last one or is
there more not that I'm playing more
but B is pretty good there's 14 okay
yeah I thought it was it has to be
longer
someday maybe we'll play more of this
cuz it's not as scary as anticipated so
reason
manageable no why
not why not check costumes no I need the
points for upgrades did you see how much
I was
[Music]
struggling with the
fights the cute girls helped for sure
the cute girls helped yeah a great
choice for a Halloween game now let's go
to my
room oh
oh
I let's put my stuff back where it
belongs I'm ghost maybe I'll stay like
this I'll stay
ghost it's part of my
costume let me close this do I have to
save it it's saved right each chapter so
closing that great work today thank you
I'm done with Halloween
yay I graduate from
Halloween for now for
2023 no more
please for now until
I survived I played two horror games
yay that was totally fine the chicken
feet game was
terrifying so today wasn't so bad maybe
I wonder if uh if I would have been more
scared today if I would have not played
chicken feet
yesterday maybe it made me
stronger who
knows but I'm going to put on some
spoopy
music didn't I download new spooky
tracks was were those spooky tracks or
were those just normal tracks let me
here that was normal that was normal but
this one
H this was kind of
yeah our spoopy
[Music]
one
mhm
nice chicken be definitely a scary one
this one more atmospheric yeah yeah so
one was more jump scares chicken feed
was more jump
scares and like the terror of being
chased
[Music]
endlessly
but there were some jump scares too in
the Fatal frames just uh after a while
you're like ready for it you expect you
know where when to expect them it's easy
to read I guess like oh I feel like now
now there's a one upcoming that I should
take a picture of
yeah oh
the lineup for who's doing which game
has
arrived
okay I am one of the
two
uh contestants or whatever candidates
contestants yeah for Minecraft for the
hollow
up the one where you use a trident to go
up up up I have not practiced this yet
at all so tomorrow I think is a
Minecraft stream is it
tomorrow then that's my practice
chance is it tomorrow I got to check my
schedule it is
okay uh and then I don't know if you're
curious do you want to hear the whole
lineup for team
white in case you want to hear the whole
thing
I'll give you the Deets so it's me and
Lal Senpai but like we're not competing
against each other we're just two of
the competitors from our
team so I guess if I fail maybe if roko
Senpai does well then I don't maybe my
mistakes get uh fixed I don't know now
but I'll try my best it when I saw it
like uh being introduced it didn't look
like too crazy
diffult I'll practice
though and then there's escort the
princess I didn't sign up for that one
cuz it's it's it's very long and so many
different things you got to do um this
one's a azuki s by kada S by Ida and
M one of them would be the princess and
then three others would be the
knights it's a lot I didn't want to do
that and then there's the Four Seasons
relay race I signed up for it but I
didn't get chosen I was put elsewhere
this one's auki s Senai Cho Senai no
Senai Ila M Kaa
Nissa and then Holo member hunting is
also a game where I if I understand
correctly like there will be like a
prompt look for this H member and then
you run around and find um I guess
something like that
mhm and this one's I am a senpai no
Senpai me Kyla narissa and
[Music]
raden so m is an escort the princess
alone as English speaker I hope she'll
be diob
but she will be
fine yeah they're probably practice
together like them as a team
so generally I think it shouldn't be too
difficult cuz when you know like what am
is and N am is not in our team I
guess I don't think am is in the white
[Music]
team I yeah Hollow up even has uh
checkpoints the the one with the Trident
who what was that even has checkpoints
so even if I die
once I can go to the
checkpoint It's pretty
dope different group yeah so yeah I'm in
in the those two I'm in the H member
hunting and then H
up H member hunting is a big team H up
is a small small small basically solo
team
excited to see the Trident one yeah I
can practice Trident
skills I got to practice so tomorrow I
don't know how long the stream will be
but I'll do my best to
practice at least the I wonder if we can
practice the hunting one while
because tomorrow will be the white team
practice and I don't know who we would
be
hunting not many people to
[Music]
hunt we'll see how it works I'm not very
informed at the
[Music]
moment
uh one side note I'm not sure if I can
really say this but it's so soon so I
feel like I should say
something or should I I think I
should
and but I might check I might better
check if I'm allowed to
[Music]
say I'll
check okay okay uh
we we got to read Super Chat that's I
guess a little bit from this stream um
don't worry I'll be working on the Polar
W as soon as I
[Music]
can
um but for now we'll just read the ones
from
today
[Music]
yay well
wasn't that just a a Risa
thing I think it was just a Risa thing
with the super chats now you wer now now
you ask me after I already received the
super chats oh can you really receive
super chats oh now you ask
me wait uh
fatal
oh it says
okay super chat's
okay ads okay super chat's
okay a she give me a heart
attack damn that's big spook biggest
spook of the
century
yeah Risa was special one can I since
it's Halloween can I snack a little bit
on my on on on a chocolate because I'm
hungry not even asking for your
permission
really happy Halloween happy Halloween I
got some Mado basically the European
Pokey
save some chocolate for the sponsor
stream oh I didn't receive
any it's not like they send us
chocolate so I was thinking maybe I go
buy some but it's not about eating the
chocolate in the
Stream I think you could compare it to
didn't Ena do um a sponsor stream about
that drink
and then she was like watching some like
video of the
factory
mhm it's going to be like that I
think cuz they said there'll be a video
prepared as
well
but um Maj chocolate is so big that I
could probably find it in an Asian
supermarket
here
probably if I wanted to but like there's
not
really doesn't seem like they want me to
eat
it
oh
chat not on
screen like what am I going to do like
what how do I even prove that it's major
chocolate I would have to turn on the
hand cam like but that's like what what
what am I going to do show off the
chocolate be like look this is Major
chocolate and take a bite and be like M
so
good
they didn't ask for that
so maybe not
necessary there's no need for pictures
they probably provide me with pictures
anyway I do
wonder what the goal is I wonder if they
want to start selling major chocolate
overseas
why are
they or is it for promotion to
foreigners who want to go to
Japan to let them know hey M Chocolate
number
one cuz there's so much tourism again
now promotion
menion you have it in major grocery
stores in the US oh oh
really I think I can only find it in
Asian supermarkets
here but if that's the case then it
makes more
[Music]
sense no
wow even in gas
stations
damn e
the Hello Panda little cookie things
those those I actually um ate them a few
times already in the
past and wait are there
[Music]
oh are those magic magic
chocol well there's the famous basic one
we'll be talking about this on Su anyway
but there's a famous basic one The Kino
and all those are
from ah wait I was thinking about a
different Panda
snack wait I didn't mean that one I
meant a different
one the Almond ones I think I had those
before pretty sure those are decent cuz
the almonds are PR
big old the nut not
chocolates but is that is the
one ah crun cranky is not M cranky is
LTE oh that's the Korean Chocolate
Company I do like
cranky need to understand which one from
which company but mes mes um existence
is huge in
Japan we'll see we'll see how it goes
what I'll be
[Music]
promoting you can represent whole life
for Ian Branch about major chocolate
sponsorship
though
yeah that's what I'm
doing should be a fun stream will make
yeah I don't I
don't you know sometimes I feel bad when
it's like these collaboration
um uh uh
sponsorships
because um like sometimes you know I
have them with Ena too right and then I
feel like oh wouldn't it be better if
it's on their Channel cuz they have
better CCV don't you want bigger bigger
views on your sponsor thing
well for some reason they choose me I
don't get it and you know I feel so much
pressure for
that I want to cuz it's a sponsorship I
wanted to have more views but if I can't
provide it like man why not why not why
not stream it on Ena or Moon mate
Channel whoever's like involved in it I
don't get
it it makes me feel even more
pressured
oh H what reason is
it why do they know do they
know like generally I just feel like as
as the company wouldn't it make more
sense but okay I can still be part of it
even if it's on a different Channel
or maybe they thought they want to they
want M just to be like my my
sidekick and want me to do like the main
talking cuz I have good talking
skills and thus it must be on my channel
cuz I'll be the main talker
probably probably it's like
that she's my side
BB
W
chocolate
yeah I'll take it I'm getting paid I'll
take
it I'll do what you
want but hope they don't regret
it read Super Chat um but let me also
put the schedule on the screen cuz it's
new
did you see the new did you see the new
art it's so
pretty I said you know I know it's
already like now November but um I I
felt like you know cuz the October one
was like spooky I felt like I missed out
on doing a um an Autumn style uh
illustration cuz right before the spooky
it was still like summer I
think so I thought maybe November can
still be forgiven cuz
nowadays the um snow is mostly falling
in like January February anyway so so
November is still fine right can still
be an Autumn
month had snow here yesterday oh well
sometimes it comes early for like one
day but then you don't get snow again
for another two or three months no
that's how it's often in Austria one
early snowfall and then two months
nothing that's how it's
here
yeah you're burning in heat in South
America well that sounds
typical I choose wild for sponsorship
any day thank you nice Autumn Vibes
right it's so pretty like the
colors so pretty so the full version
will be up for members tomorrow I hope
everybody ended up being able to get the
the previous one there were so many
issues I was so
confused people kept on saying oh it's
still not working what so I hope
everybody got it link still works okay
just like apparently there was one post
the new one where I said here's the link
or go to the main post the actual link
didn't work but the one that I replaced
in the main post apparently worked
right sorry I am so confused I'm having
problems
still might be my phone yeah try
downloading downloading it on the
computer I think it's a phone
issue yeah just because a raar
file I mean if you're still missing
it I think if you go to the KY Discord
and you say I'm a member I think they
will check if it's
true and
then we might be able to distribute it
to you I don't
know
if you give
proof they don't share they don't do
that you don't do you're not allowed oh
okay oh
well if there's anyone here who still
doesn't have it and want me to help them
uh I've tried already many times so it's
a little bit annoying to me that still
not
working but please just open your if you
see a laptop or something go on the
original post cuz that link should
work I know that's to
do yeah just unzip it just unzip
it it worked for others so it should
work somehow otherwise skill issue
maybe okay I'll I'll try I think the
reason why it all went wrong is because
I did it when I wasn't at home so I
didn't do it the usual
way this time I'll do it the usual way
so hopefully it will be smooth
sailing but yeah full schedule tomorrow
I'll be starting 1 hour earlier than
today but um it's
okay it's okay because Japanese prime
time actually all the time the times are
all over the place every day it's a
different
time
check Twitter I already said on stream
and on Twitter what the stream is on
thurs
day it's super chaotic
yeah I'm kind of concerned about the
first day stream
cuz again for sponsorship streams I feel
extra
pressured to have good views
cuz I want them to get their money's
worth but it's at 7 a.m. and 2 is 2 a.m.
EST PST might be fine but I feel like I
have accumulated a lot of EST
viewers so on a weekday
even um the time's like for
everybody I don't know
if that one's going to go well I don't
know if my audience is going to be
there they chose the time yeah they gave
me like some
choices but they were all like morning
time for
me I don't I don't remember but maybe I
could have started an hour earlier or so
but like personally I don't want to I
don't want to stream at 6:00
a.m.
oh well it is what it is we'll see how
it goes for now let's focus on Minecraft
tomorrow typing with one
hand Super Chat
reading it's working time but try to
watch it on mobile yeah please even even
if you just put it put the phone on the
side and not actually listening please
try to tune in that would be
cool even if you can't watch it have it
open in a tab or something and don't
even look at it if you don't if you
can't but um just keep it open
somewhere
not supposed to say that why not why
not it's only if you can't otherwise
watch
it I drew you for the last day of hober
pum maker oh it's the last true it's the
last day of whole
October well will it pop up on my
Twitter oh no the first thing that pops
up is gum Mia's art of my tgw outfit
looks good
good let me retweet
that where is the pump maker
art pump
maker oh cute ah the final them is your
ooshi I see what you did there
just look for
feet thank you looks cute look
[Music]
cute didn't you draw like some kind of
like collage before of me and all kinds
of cute poses can you do that again for
um my upcoming
3D like birthday whatever end of the
year stream thingy I want to see those
again those were so cute the way you
draw my butt and the legs is so
cute what's the sponsorship stream oh uh
Star Ocean R uh no something something R
it's so long I
forgot yay thank
you those are so
cute I really like that
collage Second Story art
yeah okay let's go Jacob 47 not out Jim
Tracy used to have nightmares watching
my friend play this game when I was
younger e really but I did still enjoy
when she explained the story and the
lore to me
oh nice thank you sush than
[Laughter]
oh
uhhuh uh-huh
I just saw a clip of you meeting Final
Fantasy 7 16 Sid congratulations on
being the newest member of nyn cuz
you're definitely bye bye
bye sky D candy stamp one thing that's
really neat about this game was that
when it originally launched on the Wii U
there yeah yeah I read this this while
Raina was talking I read the Super Chat
that's
cool costumes for the girl for s and
Zelda
nice I am
a Anon M Brandon
po who he's dead who's dead morally
immoral T all alone kiaha will have to
fight ghosts of nothing but a camera
will she make it or will the forest
forever have another W Forest have
another victim
I made it hey I'm reading today's stream
cuz I'm caught
up duh what else is there to
read
du oh
Sid
a h Sid Sid lives in me okay I'm s
now James Jackson thank you thank you
soon yay
love Rush please stream love Rush Give
Love to Love Rush g d morally immoral D
Brandon
sa is this all see I
think because of the Polaroids
thing I have accidentally drained
everybody's Pockets so the other streams
don't get many super chats so I'm done
[Laughter]
earlier
oopsy wait did I read
allo
artist d I'm also not much of horror
game about you playing maen of black one
don't don't I'm not no stop it got me to
play mask of the lunar eclipse while I
listening to the stream is that the
previous one or
so thank you and zly thank you
[Music]
I now I have to
refresh yeah I think the next Polaroid
uh action will be um oh it's not
refreshing will be uh for Christmas I
guess and then maybe Valentine's for
like special ones I feel like that's
already like so little time in between
each one I don't want to do too
many
so after Valentine's we might have a
break where I don't do any special
ones so we can um
chill and I might do
like the normal the normal menu
again for one time between Valentine's
and my birthday or so who
knows I'll save up for Valentine's one
good idea also now I don't know should I
always do the special one's 50% off like
I don't
know I don't want to charge you guys too
much you know I feel bad but I also
can't charge too little because then it
will be too many as we have
[Laughter]
seen
uh it did seem to result in more
yeah so I think yeah but then but then
will you even if the if the special ones
are always 50% off then will does it
even make sense to sell the normal menu
at
100% again ever does that
even make
sense you know I'll maybe I'll just I
still s a
red okay for now I'll keep it the next
one the the the Christmas one because
it's Christmas I'll keep it at 50%
probably because you'll probably have
other stuff to buy like merchandise and
and uh presents for your family and
yourself and all that Christmas is the
time where you lose all your
money
so Valentine's could be 100 e
why maybe we'll see on that fluctuating
Market these
Polaroids might have have to consider
how much longer it takes me to sign them
when there's so many orders because I
made them too cheap you
know red is a must Wonder okay okay okay
you seem to like this uh
logic okay okay wait my my super chats
are not really refreshing properly all I
see is siton ELC weabo and spice
waterfall for uh extra blue ones was
that all I feel like I saw a few more
[Music]
maybe maybe it's fine did I miss
anyone oh another there is another red
one what the hell it doesn't show like
it's not
updating James MC thank you for the red
super chat never underestimated chickens
yeah
I this this Halloween one wasn't even so
long since the last one so I didn't
think I really didn't think there would
be so many what the
hell I really underestimated it I truly
did thank you guys for being so
supportive
honestly it's definitely helping me um
get back the the basically the money I
spend on the motion capture suit to be
honest with you H oh but speaking of
that um think of the fact that my next
single is already finished and it will
have to have a 3D music video whether I
get into your vision or
not
um and that would be pretty close to
sleeptalking and the suit still not
being there and me running out of time
and all that I think I might just try to
quickly prepare um a 2d music video not
not this like I want a few more
illustrations though not just one I'll
see what I can do I might just settle
for 2D now and and then put all my power
into the next 3D music
video what's happening with the suit
well it's complicated like originally I
was going to buy
it uh on my own and then they were like
we were dating and then they were like
okay last thing we need from you is a
vat number that number and I was like I
don't have that and it's like an
annoying process to make it so I said
cuz at that point I was already like
going back and forth like so much and
wasting time that I
said I don't know can I have my company
order it for me uh they were like yeah
sure and
so yeah I don't know they seem to need
it I don't know why it's so necessary
but they can't do it without
[Music]
apparently so then I gave it to my
company to handle uh and and JMA was
handling the com the the um
communication
and um they
did like all the procedures like oh for
the order and um then I got the
the the quotation and this and that and
then at the very end where it's already
like closing in suddenly they're like oh
and last thing we need is uh the vi
number from
kiata and I'm like
huh what what do you mean we wasted 2
months communicating in the end you're
still going to ask for the V8 number huh
I I don't have one the entire Point yeah
for asking my company to do it there was
because I thought thought that was how I
don't have to give you that or they have
one so I asked cuz I feel like I saw
previously that they the all life has a
VI number I thought I saw it in some
document and so I was like wait why
can't we use covers and then gentleman
says we don't have one and I'm like what
I thought we have one and also it was
the point of asking you to handle
it so that's why currently it looks like
even though we have everything ready the
only thing is missing is the V number so
it's like what the yeah it's an
it's not a tax number it's an individual
number that you have to apply for that
normally you only really have if you
have like a business in
Europe I
think so you see there like so much time
being wasted and it's not looking good
anymore I'm not optimistic anymore that
I'm getting it but when I should be
getting it cuz kind of said if I want uh
a 3D MV uh at the end of November then
the latest I should give him the most
capture from my side is early November
and well now it's becoming early
November so I can't I have to create a
backup so I have to put that aside now
because I thought in the end soon after
I'm making a 3D MV for uh the other song
the new single anyway it's really sad
for me because I have a choreo for sleep
talking and I had this I thought it was
perfect for a 3D music video but
now it's like
getting too late
anyway and I don't need this stress
anymore you
know so I'll try to do something with 2D
something interesting I'll I'll find
myself an artist who can work
fast uh give me like three four five
illustrations
hopefully
yeah
it's okay it's just really disappointing
cuz like I was I kind of ordered it
because of sleep
talking and then for future projects too
but like the reason why I really needed
it was sleep
[Music]
talking but it is what it is
so I don't know how that's going
to turn out but
yeah I can't not I already said many
times that there's a reason why I need
this to be out at the end of November
and if it's not out at the end of
November it makes no
sense I need MV for it at the end of
November otherwise it's not fulfilling
his purpose that's all I'll
say
what no no no no no you have to apply
for it like my my tax lady did it for me
before for some other weird
reason
um uh and then we got rid of it cuz I
didn't need it
anymore but it's stupid it's just stupid
overall I don't understand why I need it
I'm just give it to me without the vat
number
so uh are we done with super chats wait
there's one more motion D is there any
plans to release the K inal version of
oh no normally with the singles it
always release them automatically
[Music]
right I had no plan for
it do you guys want
it wait why are they not on the album oh
speaking of the album
ah yeah more bad things but I won't
bother you with this
because you guys will be mad if I tell
you
this not at me but at other people in
charge so let's not talk about
it ah no I must know I'm mad
now we're always mad no be happy be
happy if you're happy any you know clap
your hands if happy and you know I CL
your
[Music]
hand anyway uh wait now now it refreshed
properly Lord EV D M
D no no Resident Evil sit on
Dan uh Dusty oh my piggy turned into a
red with the tip what will that count
for the
Polaroid just asking for next time well
this time I it only needed to be
pinkies so I don't know
what what do you mean
Dusty
you sent a
red oh well if you sent a red of course
that's also fine minimum was pinky but
if you sent a red
okay I appreciate the extra
donation there's a new aoe2 patch and
DLC
what like just now like today or
yesterday or
so what
it doesn't say update for me oh but it
says Ah new new DC available now the
mountain Royals Mountain
Royals who are the mountain
Royals two new remarkable civilizations
the mountain Roy I'm a mountain Royal
I'm an
Austrian but who are
they
uh
uh who I can't find it I can't they just
say Mountain Royals it doesn't say
home the Georgians and the
Armenians that's not
Austrian Georgians and the
Armenians and the Persia
rework and a new campaign for return of
room do I or you have to pay for this I
think do you 1,800
Yen well well well for now I don't need
it
okay watching Georgia not Coca-Cola
Georgia what I know I wouldn't think of
something like that
what
I don't know what Coca-Cola Georgia is
is that where the headquarters of
Coca-Cola
are Austra was part of the hre during
the time period AOE to coverage yeah
yeah I know I know I know I know there
couldn't be like a Austria I
know but I we we were Mountain Royal
don't you have yeah well I'm not going
to sign them
today I don't I don't
know soon TM I keep on reminding me
though I'll do my
best come to Georgia the
state
translution go yeah did you just come in
here did you just arrive did you miss
the whole stream cuz I'm ending now I
already read super chats and I already
played the game with and without waya I
even extended it after way left by
playing on my own oh now I'm going for
signing stream next week no I noticed
that I get really like focused on the
signing also with the real life Polar
rights that I have to sign so I feel bad
for not being able to talk much it's not
even like a drawing stream it's even
worse so I feel bad I I think it's good
in the future I think I might unless
it's really a small amount I might
always uh sign it off
stream cuz I don't want it to be so
boring anyway I'm just wasting your time
then we don't need that and and off
stream I'll be faster because I can
focus more and I don't have to worry
about entertaining you you know
then it's better to just give you
freehanded tangents cuz I got my hands
off of the
Polaroids and my
brain so now I'm going to go wow early
end at 9900 p.m. and I cooked
yesterday
Wow Let's go so I'm going to make myself
a little snack with bread and salami and
tomato and
cheese yeah 6 hours of horror game
baby hope you enjoyed it guys hope
you're satisfied with your wa wa scream
Cravings it was actually kind of funny
today like the I I like the game I like
fail frame like some parts like the
moving is slow and that annoys me a bit
but uh it's funny I kind of like it yeah
it it has a charm and it's very original
like taking photos of ghosts with the
Japanese lore and all that stuff I like
it yeah I'll make myself a brle Yi yeah
yeah also my mom really wants to call me
since yesterday so I got to talk to
her H
chill I don't like horror much either
but you like so passionate
about hating on me playing horror games
I'm okay you know I'm okay I survived it
I'm
fine I'm okay oh hi
Aura wasn't even that bad was funny
makes funny
clips yeah I wasn't dying I'm okay
especially today was
nothing t with uh waya too
so I think you have to look at it from a
different
POV look at it
positively something like Outlast no
thank you but this is
fine this is fine so in German we say do
in have a nice day or Halloween oh I
can't believe it's Halloween oh my
God ah
[Music]
see you there at Minecraft white team
practice did you see all the collapse
that's happening my I almost only
collapsed it just happened
naturally I didn't even
try bye-bye bye-bye
an
an happy Halloween this is Halloween
this is
[Music]
Halloween