[Music]
so
wait i don't hear myself
[Music]
oh there we go
my chickens
how have you been
good evening
[Music]
did you hear her i i heard her
what's up what's up junkies
[Music]
how's it going how's it going guys
it's been a couple days
although i have provided you guys with
lots of content even though even when i
was gone right
it wasn't it wasn't too lonely
[Music]
cats are very happy that i'm back
you guys
are hopefully happy as well
[Music]
i will this will be a short stream first
of all very short stream i'll i might
want to keep it around one hour to one
and a half hours because
uh i just want to quickly say hello and
i don't want to tell everything from my
vacation yet i will show you some photos
and tell you some things
but i don't want to say everything
uh we gotta keep some things you know
gonna keep some things for the long long
jrpg streams
so we'll just look for some
pictures and i'll explain you some
things but maybe i'll go more into
detail
in the tales of our ice cream i'm not
sure i don't even know if i can hold
back on telling
the all the stories now
but
oh there's definitely one thing that i
should start with
[Applause]
[Music]
we got the screen down here
is the btm too loud
by the way
yeah yeah yeah about the day that
where i said that it already started off
badly
i will definitely tell you that so it's
a little loud it's perfect perfect maybe
a bit it's a tiny bit okay
oh there we go
okay okay
okay
wow
it feels like it's been a while also i'm
not sitting on it yet
but
my
aeron
herman miller iron chair has arrived and
i didn't film it yet because i wanted to
sit on it live on stream for the first
time
so that you guys get the first reaction
it's it's it arrives like pre-built so
um like i can literally just take a sale
it now but i i held back
to have the first reaction on stream
[Music]
tony i'm surprised because it looks um
so much
smaller than the chat that i'm currently
in
um the channel i'm currently in is just
one of those generic
gamer gamer girl jazz
oh well i mean it doesn't really look
like a gamer guild chair if you look
behind me but
trust me that's a
an optical illusion
yes
actually this is a pretty big gamer
wheelchair i bought it because i wanted
a cute chair
but after after a while
i've realized
it's it's not only about the looks
[Laughter]
uh comfort in a job like this
where you stream or when you're in your
chair all day comfort comes first i
suppose
but i also i didn't honestly in the
beginning i didn't when i started doing
this the streaming job
i didn't realize that
uh
[Music]
a gamer chair
is not really
the best
choice i didn't i thought i thought that
those were the best choices
i didn't realize that
it's
um
it it would have such a
bad impact on my posture i mean that's
partially on me though i would i would
definitely say a big a big portion of
that is on me
that um
the gamer chair didn't work on me at all
i wouldn't say that it's such a like
useless chair it's it's in general it's
a super comfy chair
but
uh
yeah
um i didn't i i didn't realize that
you're not like
that
it's not the best choice you know i
thought i thought those were good chairs
i mean they're they're pricey too
they look fancy and they look i mean
they're called gamer chairs and i'm
literally gaming as my job so my brain
was like
this is what i need
this is what i need and it has so many
options to like make it even more comfy
like the leg rest and stuff which i have
never used literally but
but still
like you would think that
you know
you know this is made to be comfy so
it's good for your body for being on it
for a long time
yeah so now i got now i got a proper
chair i suppose it's an office chair
just buying officers are you listening i
did it's right next to me i just i'm
just not sitting on it yet
is that the first thing that we should
do
should i sit in the chair
should i sit in my herman miller chair
so
oh
[Music]
i i'm a bit worried about the size
because
i was kind of
in between two sizes
um
but
i went with s size
and i hope it's fine but but m's the
range of the m size
was just so
wide
that i thought
[Music]
like on the spec on the on the on the
lower higher high lower higher spectrum
on one side the spectrum was just too
big
from the m size and and i read that it's
really really important
um to get the right size for yourself a
fitting size when it comes to this chair
specifically
yeah
but
so originally okay so this doesn't even
have anything to do with the location
but that's okay let me start by saying
um
[Music]
so
uh originally i was looking for this
chair that i ever run everyone
herman miller jack and i couldn't find
any distributor in my country
that
uh yeah would sell it to a singular
person
oh the other time
she must hide
yeah
but but but then i gave up then i gave
up but then later on a friend sent me
this url for some reason we were i guess
we were talking about chairs or so
but i was sent the url and i think it's
a yeah it was a german german germany
distributor so it came from germany
um
and i guess i just didn't really look in
german i don't know
i don't know it was a kind of weird
website it has all kinds of like chairs
but it's not like
it has all kind of office chairs yeah
and um
then it had listed the the old herman
miller errand chair and the new
herman miller errand chair because it
got at some point it got revamped i
suppose
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it got revamped
you guys know that like a couple years
ago or so
yeah there's a new version but but it's
like the old one is still like
superb
still superb
um
[Music]
at first i chose the new version because
i think it was because
because of the song was it because
yeah yeah yeah cause i looked at the old
version and
no wait the other way around no i looked
i looked at the old version and the new
version and the old version had my size
but the new version didn't so i was like
oh
oh well i guess i'm gonna go with the
old version it still seems superb
according to the description it's
still amazing so what the hell i'm gonna
go the old version so i ordered it but
i got an email immediately from the
customer service
telling me that they do have
the new version in my size in stock
and if i would like to buy it it's just
it costs a little bit more like 200
bucks more or something like that
i was like okay
okay
why the hell not
so now i have the
the new version
some parts i think that the back part
the thing that holds the whole chair
together in the back that one was
updated or so
it got sent over and uh it arrived like
during my vacation but thankfully there
was someone here to
uh accept it
yeah so shall we sit on it just let it
go
[Music]
let's get it over here get out of here i
want i i've heard so many good things
about this chair if i'm not gonna get
like a super amazing feeling sitting on
this chair i'm gonna be so
disappointed i'm gonna be so
disappointed if this doesn't do wonders
for my body then i'm gonna be so
disappointed
all right all right all right let's
move move get out of the way get
out the way
huge ass chat okay it's super super
scratched i'm gonna keep that old gamer
chair maybe as a scratching pole for my
cats now let me get the other one here
oh it moves so nicely
okay
okay okay so it's behind me
it's it's super small it feels so small
okay
i'm going to sit down i'm nervous
i'm nervous okay sitting down in three
two
one
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
yeah
interesting
i mean i can still do adjustments right
i don't know like where would i adjust
it though but apparently that's
important too are you healthier yeah my
back is suddenly healed
let's go
no my back broke let's go
no
didn't break it didn't break but yeah it
does feel
like because there's less space to sit
in i suppose
also
and
i have less space to up my posture
i i probably couldn't even do my crazy
sitting poses on can i
can i put my
i mean i can i can do like some kind of
i can sit on my i can sit on my foot
on this chair as well
yeah somehow i can but
but it does feel
already like it's improving i gotta
without my without a headrest by the way
that's also why it looks smaller
it forces proper potion i'm not sure if
i'm in proper poster right now i mean
i'm leaning back
um but i'm supposed to be leaning back
with this one maybe
it's comfortable
it feels it feels comfortable
[Music]
i think it feels comfortable
i don't know how it will be in a long
time i think that's what really counts
[Music]
she said that her back problems
literally disappeared thanks to it so
yeah
review after two weeks all right let's
do that ask me ask me kfb sticky notes
write it down ask me how it feels in two
weeks i mean i probably
might be talking about it anyway
if i if i don't talk about it ask me in
two weeks how how how it changed
yes
okay
one thing that i hope uh
i'll fix through this
is leaning back at leaning forward too
much that was one of my big problems
poster problems
um like with a really hunched back i
would lean forward a lot especially with
my with my head
very much
uh like
but not in the right position
like and it would be very like i don't
know i can't even show you
need to become 3d first
no my small 3d model no that was
hunchback because i don't know because
of the the thingies but not i was i was
standing straight okay but the the what
you call those things the things that
you put on on your waist and uh your
your
legs and all that
yeah
that now that was
the senses yeah yeah yeah especially the
the waist sensor it was not like
uh skin tight
like it was moving around a lot when i
was moving and jumping
that's why my poster was so weird okay
yeah um everyone's poster was kind of
weird every now and then it's not only
my post okay
just wait until you see me in probably
okay then you can judge then you can
judge my
my post junk and then i'll accept that
judgment but for now you don't get to
judge me by free senses free
trackers don't tell you
especially on the chibi model okay
okay
now let's show you a little bit of my
vacation
uh oh but wait i have to start by
talking well
i don't have a photo of this so let me
get like ah
[Music]
uh
what exactly am i looking for
[Music]
um
i don't know maybe
maybe not
[Music]
okay
we have to go first to the very very
very beginning
no
we have to go all the way back
i got something in my throat that's
poking me
i need to drink water
[Music]
so first of all
um the vacation
goal
destination
was uh inside of my own country
so
eh
[Laughter]
[Music]
we didn't get hit by a truck we did not
get invited for frankfurt
um
[Music]
i did a vacation in australia yes
and um
we went by car the my best friend
my best friend went with me i basically
invited her to an all-inclusive
literally all-inclusive
um
vacation
yes
and and she she was the chosen one
because she's my bff and because she can
drive a car
and because she had time at the right
time when i needed it a bit loud okay
really
[Music]
okay so uh
however um the car that we drove with is
not her car
it
it's her mother's car and it's a car
that's super super super old
[Music]
and
i don't know any numbers i don't
remember any numbers but it's been in
usage for many many years and it has
many many many kilometers on it
and it looks and feels old
i've been in the car a couple times i've
been in a in a horrible trip before with
that car um
through winter
uh driving ten hours in the snowstorm in
that car was not comfortable let me tell
you that
it was not a car like that on the
picture
no no no it looks more like a box car
like the one that you will see in in
japan
um
[Music]
yeah so
it's being old plays a big role
so my friend arrived
when was that monday morning monday
monday i think it was like 10 a.m yeah i
got up early for this
and uh
she was like i'm here let's go then i
went down with my luggage i went down
several times like five times
and um
and we started driving and
very soon after driving while we're
still in the same city
um in a very busy city
uh
my my friend by the way she got her
license somewhat recently but she claims
to be a good driver and i don't want to
say anything i think
i mean i can't judge by
i personally i don't i probably don't
have the right to judge
she's probably an okay driver
she's gonna be mad at me if i say
anything else
she's a she's a good driver today she
did a great job
and um yeah but she's but she got her
license recently okay so it's a lot of
first-time experiences here but we were
driving on this busy road
[Music]
our vacation literally just started
literally just started and then we
um
uh
i think
we wanted to
i think it was a four-lane road or so or
even a six lane i don't know
and she wanted to
turn
uh oh yeah she oh yeah that's that was
she wanted to um go go left
um
but while we were going left
even though i think
the navigation also told us to go left
the the signs on the on the ground
it showed it as a iron branch dresser
one-way road to the other up to the
opposite direction so we were about to
drive
in a in a one-way road right even though
i've seen cars go that go the opposite
direction from what's written on the
ground on that lane many times i've seen
it many times
that cars go the other way on that road
i don't know maybe it's written
incorrectly on the ground is that even a
thing but even before we enter before we
try to enter that road
uh another car went into that road right
in front of us but
but because my friend is very very um
new with her license she didn't want to
up
you know she wanted to be she wanted to
be careful understandable
so she kind of while she was in the
curve and about to go left
we kind of stopped and uh while we were
like
panicking about what to do she she tried
to go around instead of going left she
wanted to go into the other lane and do
a turnaround you know and while doing
that
her uh van lift lamp or something like
that some some kind of bing bing bing in
her car started uh blinking
uh something that blinks when something
is wrong with the car
some kind of light i don't know
about cars
but it turned on randomly ah i think it
was something
something about the motor
i think
and maybe
i don't know some light that is kind of
you know it normally shouldn't light up
and it was in the middle of that
maneuver so it was obviously
a crazy no well actually while that
happened or like a second after that was
blinking up
the motor in the middle of a
busy four or six lane road in the middle
of the traffic while turning around
while trying to do a panic turn around
in the other direction because we wanted
to go left but we couldn't is when the
car broke down
um
and um
people were looking at us from outside
and my friend was panicking i was like
yeah why this must be so uncomfortable
for her we literally just started and
the car died down but it's such a
old car and i was like yo does
that does that happen a lot with this
car and she was like no this is like
this is like the first time i drive this
car and that happens and and the car
also has recently went into maintenance
and came back from maintenance and was
supposedly healthy
they fixed some things on the car that
were unrelated to this issue
but it was supposedly fine you know
we started driving to a vacation and
just the day before she was already she
was using the car as well yet and the
day before everything was fine and all
the days before everyone was fine
so anyway
we broke down in the middle of that busy
crossroads
people were looking at us she was trying
to get the car to work again but it
didn't work for a while we were we were
in the middle of that road for it felt
like an eternity
and
but we kind of stopped in a lucky
position actually we didn't even
obstruct the rest of the traffic
actually that was quite lucky we stopped
in a in the best possible spots that you
could stop in in that horrible situation
position whenever
yeah
so at some point she got it to work
again so we continued driving
um
and after a little while we got on the
highway
and we were on the highway for five
minutes and that light started blinking
again
and my friend obviously didn't want her
car to break down in the middle of the
highway or later on when we're way
further away from the city where we
started off at
so she went to the side uh to the like
the highway side thingy that way you
stopped the place you know
[Music]
it broke down
and we went to the what hard shoulder
shoulder lane interesting
interesting
so my friend was um
a little bit stressed out and i was
still laughing i was still laughing
still i was i still thought this is
funny
um
so
we called her mom and we called uh
her mom was like super apologetic she
was like oh my god so sorry oh my god
yeah
but her mom wasn't in the city either on
that day she was somewhere else for some
reason so she couldn't help
um
only on the phone and then we called you
know some kind of service that helps
check the car and maybe totals it if
something's really wrong
so they
they came after while we chilled on the
highway
we're chilled on the highway it was a
nice sunny day so everything was cool i
was still laughing and uh then they came
and they the guy looked at the car
and um
we were kind of already starting to hope
to get a different car from that service
because my friend was very nervous about
the
functionality of this old car at that
point yeah
and we were pretty worried uh
so we were kind of hoping for a new car
because that service you if you have a
membership there apparently you can get
a car for like up to four days which is
absolutely perfect because we were gone
for four days
so
it would be a new car a comfortable new
car
uh-huh yeah so
yeah uh the guy checked out the car but
he couldn't find anything specific that
was wrong with it
and he says he doesn't know if this is
like a one-time thing it was a two-time
thing that's for sure
it happened two times
right it didn't break down at that
moment but she just went to the shoulder
lane or whatever very quickly so that's
why it didn't happen who knows what
would have happened later but yeah so
they were like nope
nothing specific wrong you can probably
drive back into the city on your own we
don't have to tell you or pull you
so
we
drove back and went to the office of the
branch of that um
[Music]
company
in the hopes of getting a new car
uh
however that whole thing was also
stressful that's that's when it started
to get stressful for me because it was
getting later and later and we we at
that point when we left the highway
we were already like an hour late
and
it took us a long time
we had a lot of delay because of this
and i had a massage coming up later that
evening and at the hotel
and it was by the way uh
i won't say how long to drive i won't
say that yeah i will not say that but it
was a decent amount of drive so yeah we
had some delay we went back we went to
the company and we asked
yo
can we get a different car my her mom is
insured
in this has an insurance at this place
so she she's like
uh like they have this thing called
shoots brief or something like that i
don't i don't know about these things
but like somehow she's like in like she
can somehow use the membership from her
mom but when it comes to renting a car
from them she would have
had her mom with her
she was she would have been allowed to
use it but she wouldn't be allowed to
rent it in the first but she couldn't
pick it up the mom would have to be
there
and
but mother was far far away so she
couldn't help so we were already
stressed out we're losing time and time
and
then my friend spontaneously decided to
make her own membership to get that
extra car because we didn't want
to use the old car anymore
so she made a membership that also took
time
and we paid for it and then she uh we
got the car and we inspected the car and
we switched over the car
and then we finally left off again
and we left the old car there
so that later her mom could pick it up
so
oh by the way the drive from the highway
to that company was totally fine the car
was fun nothing happened anymore
yeah i am
yo well where's the chicken now that's
great
you guys have a vacation too huh
[Music]
okay
and after that everything was smooth we
drove pretty quickly like she she she
tried her best my best friend tried her
best to make up for the time loss i did
not get the massage i had to move it we
came we arrived much much later
many hours later and therefore
the first day we want to arrive around
check-in time we wanted to arrive at
like i don't know 3 p.m or so at the
latest
but we arrived so much later we arrived
at like i think 7 00 p.m that's like a
four-hour delay even though she made
like the navigation said like we needed
someone so much time but she made up a
lot like she she really
zoomed through the highway thank you
while still protecting
all the laws so don't do it's all good
no don't don't call the police okay
don't call the police but she was speed
yes she was zooming
thankfully so we still kind of arrived
somewhat early but it was late we missed
we missed not only my massage but i
could move that so it's all good not
like uh in greece where i lost a lot of
money because i broke my neck
and they were like oh do you want to
move your massage down to later and i'm
like i have my flight later
please just give me back my money and uh
no we can't do that
how about you just i don't know take the
massage now yo i'm crying here obviously
you see that i have a broken
neck no i'm not crying for no reason i'm
telling you i can't think the massage
will make things worse
no we can't
[Music]
anyway that was grease that was grease
um
but yeah i was able to move the massage
but we also missed strudel toolside
there was a
every day between a certain time
you were able to get to get free free
free straddles um
like apple strudel or top film store
or
bearing store all kinds of stores
like uh wait you know what's totally
what's totally in uh
english
what's totally in english
you guys know what apple strudel is
stolen
[Music]
okay good then we understand one another
basically the reservation i made
included breakfast and then
from 3 p.m
to 5 p.m
daily strudel time it was literally a
college total outside stroller time
they had like sweet stroodles and and
not savory strudels
yes yes all kinds of strudels and every
day the strollers were different but
every day they had they did have an
apple store every day but they also had
other specialist roodles every day so
that's from like three p.m to
um
uh
5 p.m and then it also had dinner in
five course dinner included every night
and some other cool stuff so
we finally arrived
in the hotel late but still
it's all good uh i think the pictures
that i'm gonna show you guys now are not
really sorted
i don't even know what color i think a
good picture comes first
yes
there it
is
uh
big look it's a heart the blankets are
shaped into a heart
i got i got us a sweet
a sweet it was actually pretty big
and uh uh
there was a couch there and if you see
on the on the table on the right side uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait
wait let me
[Music]
there's a box there they had um they had
a google hook
a welcome complimentary whole google
hoop
it's a cake it's a it's um it's a pound
cake
[Music]
yeah it's a welcome welcome google hope
that was made in the hotel a fresh one a
fresh freshly baked google hoof we call
a cake here google
[Laughter]
google
yeah hoop
i was in the room and some fruit and all
that and uh yeah we had a balcony too a
pretty big balcony and the view
from the balcony was amazing
uh
i might be able to show you in a
different picture but the pictures are
all aligned so randomly so this is going
to be fun
um
i'm just gonna you know what i have i've
wrote everything down what we did on day
one day two day three day four
but uh i think i'll go through that in
the tales of our ice stream i'll just
tell you whatever i see in the picture
is that okay
but i'll tell you that after we arrived
we didn't really do much we just had
dinner
it was really good
it was a five-course
meal i think well next picture is i
think some yes
it's it's just one of the uh starters
for uh the five-course dinner this one
was
on this plate it was like normally
normally they had like proper starters
but on this day they had a mix of
different starters
like small small little pieces of all
kinds of starters on one plate which i
thought the idea of that was cool
oh that was the following
i think she did a piece no is that
it's a weird peace sign though
is that really
no you know what that's not that's not
my friend doing a peace sign those are
straws
those are straws from my drink that i
had i think it had double straws
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah this is just stars i think pretty
sure
anyway i have to say those those little
balls the those were rice balls but not
like in the mochi kind of way
more like a normal rice but you saw the
rice inside those one yummy used and the
the one on the very left is not a cake
even though it looks like a cake the
cake is a lie
and it was actually
like a cheesy thing
i mean it has berries on it which really
really bamboozles you but it is a lie
it's not sweet like it's not really
sweet at all
and the the thing in the middle was like
a
pork i think with pork with some radish
and some
the the white cream underneath was like
a fish
thingy
uh i didn't really like those but but oh
that's this was like a kind of unlucky
one the others the other things were
mostly really really really good and we
had a choice like we didn't have just
one five course menu but every day we
had three three different five course
menus that we can choose from and we can
also mix and match like we if you if we
didn't like one starter from one uh
specific course but we wanted to rest
and we could use a starter from a
different course that was really cool um
[Music]
it was usually like just normal european
food or also a lot of specifically
australian dishes yes yes
uh
this is one of the desserts
and there's a story behind the desserts
this one was so good
[Music]
um
this was really good oh man the ice
cream was a hazelnut ice cream
yeah
the texture of that thing looks so cute
doesn't it it was a cream inside
yeah it was really yummy that was a
dessert i love the desserts
yeah they make they made it they made a
joke about uv they made a uvue joke
like i ate one i was like holy this
is so good
and the waitress was really really nice
and um we kind of we saw her every day
we saw the waitress around dinner time
and we also saw her every day at
breakfast time they have like double
shifts it's crazy it's insane
um but uh apparently they they live
close so it's okay i guess they have
short shifts but because they have short
shifts they have to probably do like a
four hour shift in the morning and the
four hour shift in the evening that
sounds horrible
and but yeah it is what it is
so
we kind of like had some good vibes
going you know me and the waitress
and and i honestly i didn't intend to
say anything with it but after the
five-course
meal where uh
i think
nah no no that was the second day okay
after after i finished eating my dessert
i she was about to take our plates and i
was like yo
this was south okay no this was
literally me okay this it was so so so
good it was really really good i loved
it like i honestly told her i looked
into her eyes with this passion in my
eyes i really just wanted to convey that
it was really good
so she read my mind i didn't
even know i was thinking that but she
knew i was thinking it so she was like
you want another one
and i was like
i didn't think of that
i didn't even think of that possibility
but you know what yes i do
yes i know if that's possible
if you can get me another one yeah hell
yeah
so she brought me a second serving of
that and then she she brought it back
and she was like she was making a joke
about um the the kitchen chef lost
another finger for this and i was like
hey what do you mean and i looked at the
desert and a few seconds later later i
understood
desert this dessert a few seconds later
i understood uh-huh that's what you mean
funny she's funny and she raised my mind
what a angel i love her i love
her i just i honestly didn't think of
getting a second serving i really just
wanted to convey that was really good i
wanted her to tell the kitchen that i
was happy with it
she was so sweet oh man she had a really
german accent by the way because she was
german she's so sweet she's so cute
yeah we got i got a second one
[Music]
oh
okay so actually
this hotel
supposedly
was
saying they have an onsen
[Music]
so i was very very curious about that
and
um it had it had this uh wait let me
let's look at what they say here what
you're supposed to do
the onsen ritual basically oh it says it
in english too that's perfect so cleanse
yourself at the onsen wash plats with
our wild spa peeling soap to prepare
your body for the onsen bath so that's
the first point
you you clean you cleanse yourself
before going to an onsen in japan but
you don't put a freaking peeling on
yourself that's that's not really part
but i guess they just wanted to you know
bring in their peelings and all that and
because they have a huge spa and and so
many selections of peelings and so
i i like this i like this addition
[Music]
reflect
go to the onsen pool full of peace and
mindfulness and notice how the
beneficial peeling lingers that's why
they kind of make it about the feeling
it's not about the feeling yo but okay
yeah you but you are supposed to like in
an onsen you are supposed to like
reflect and just be calm and think about
yourself and think about things just you
know go into yourself and just
you know
think about things
so i think that was that's pretty
correct
um
that's the main point one there
[Music]
step is dive in immerse yourself step by
step into an onsen pool and feel the hot
water on your freshly cleansed skin
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay
and then rest sweet switch oh there's a
typo there what oh no that was like a
stone plate and they have a typhoon oh
the didn't check this
switch off in the relaxation room and
let the you had one you had one job you
had just one job to not mess up this one
single stone plates
printing fire no okay it's okay
uh switch up in a relaxation room and
let the onsen ritual take effect on you
yes yes there was a huge relaxation room
um
it's it doesn't look like what you would
usually see in a japanese onsen but it's
very nice it has a european taste to it
and it was very comfy and calm and
nobody was talking there only um uh
whispering was allowed but basically no
one talked and there was a there was
also some snacks there and tea and all
that so it was cool
uh i know
eating meat
[Music]
i didn't even read that part so
um and that was
oopsie oh i moved i moved uh
i moved i moved this okay
and
next
to the sign
was this
which
looks pretty accurate to me
like just simple stones to sit on
sitting sitting on something while
showering yourself that's very accurate
[Music]
and it had some stuff to wash your hair
and your body and it had the peeling of
course as well yeah yeah but uh it was
missing you know those buckets that you
pour over yourself i suppose but not
really important to me personally
yeah
um
but if you look
look at the picture you notice the thing
it's
very visible right
[Music]
the thing is this onsen uh
understandable to me because it's in
europe and personally for me also better
uh but you're not supposed to take off
your clothes for this onsen
for this bath
by the way it is not the pool that you
see right there on in the back i thought
that first because it's right next to it
logical thinking but it's not that but
in the beginning we thought so logically
because it's right there we thought that
that's their onsen so
after washing us
we went into that pool
but it was like
not hot at all
so we were so confused
we were like that's not an onsen what
the actual also this is this is
just a normal pool
[Music]
we're very confused we were very
confused then but we enjoyed it anyway i
was like oh of course there's no proper
onsen outside of japan what did i expect
so we chilled a little bit in that pool
and then we noticed something
around the corner actually from here it
would be left and
there was another pool outside
it was smaller
and it had way more
uh
um
heat
clouds
coming off of it so i was like
maybe that's it
steam yes
[Music]
so
we we went over to that smaller pool and
we were like this must be the onsen
i don't have a picture of that on
honestly
at the moment at least yeah
but uh um
we went in there and it was hot as
yay
i think it was like 46 degrees
uh i know
that's
it was very very hot it was outside
uh and and uh it was mixed
that's another thing i i don't think
that's a thing in japan
unless if it's a if it's one of the
rare onsens where you actually should
wear clothes in japan those are very
rare but they do exist then those i
guess there are mixed gender um
onsens but usually no they're always
like divided but here i guess it makes
sense because you wear your swimsuit so
that it's also mixed so that's okay but
it's just different
um
celsius celsius
[Music]
um yeah so we ended it was hot but
the biggest thing i guess which bothered
me the most is
it was basically just a heated up pool
the water was just pool water
[Music]
um
so
it we were wearing clothes it was mixed
and
[Music]
i was actually really hoping for proper
onsen water because i don't know it was
in the middle of some mountains so maybe
they have a
super special
um source of getting like some special
water why the hell not
yeah it's like a jacuzzi
no but it was very hot and um
it was nice we went there in quite a few
times uh it was funny people like coming
into that onsen and they were like
that's hot
i liked seeing their reactions
yeah
um
[Music]
i was just like
i i wasn't sure if you were really like
supposed to call this an onsen if it's
it just has hot pool water
i guess i don't know what what is the
official description of an onsen let me
look it up
well okay
maybe they just maybe they looked at the
wikipedia
article and they say they saw that onsen
means hot water and they thought that
that's it that's all it needs
but um but it says wait in english
[Music]
and our the country's hot springs at the
bathing facilities and traditional ends
around them out as a volcanically active
country japan has thousands of
unsustainable
answers come in many types of shapes
including outdoor and indoors
[Music]
it doesn't say anything anything about
what kind of ah
onsens by definition use naturally
naturally hot water from
geothermally heated springs so
by definition this is not an onsen
[Music]
i guess they just wanted to be fancy but
it kind of i think it's okay
for it like
for the fact that it's in europe oh this
card is here what do you say about that
ocean
[Music]
discord can't find it what did this
court say
oh there it is
welcome oh thank you discord yo thank
you i'm back it's a nonsense
nonsense onsen nonsense onset
nonsense onsen nonsense
i like that
um the rest at the the the hotel
actually had a uh has a very new
japanese restaurant restaurant as well
um
which is right next to this onsen
so it kind of makes sense yeah we didn't
try the japanese restaurant though
because
i didn't believe in it being authentic
i didn't trust in it
but yeah it's interesting how this hotel
while being so very australian
uh has these little parts that are
trying to be japanese very interesting i
did enjoy the onsen so i will not
complain about it i just have to say
it's inaccurate
okay
continuing oh this was just a
um
a building
that is was part of the hotel that i
thought is cute and i wanted to show you
uh
it's just one of the all of the
buildings looked like this
[Music]
they
and the entrance looked like this
isn't cute this is like the typical
australian
style of
[Music]
i love this kind of
australian countryside
um houses they look so cute and on the
way to the hotel we saw so many of those
and
i was like one day i kind of want to
live
in a place like this it's really
charming yeah looks so cozy i think back
in the day when i was younger when i was
a child or a teenager i didn't really
think of them as charming that much but
nowadays i i look at this and i just
feel like it's so charming
yeah that was the entrance um and
seeing the pictures are aligned so
randomly this was just a small picture
of our dinner table there were several
rooms
of uh where we could have dinner i
thought that was really cool like
um each room gets assigned to a certain
dinner room and every dinner room has a
different look to it
we were actually
in in the least fancy one i suppose but
that was kind of randomly assigned
but even though it was the least fancy
you can't really see it on this picture
but it it was very very
woody
very wooden um i don't know what type of
wood that is but it was
it was like the whole the whole room
the whole hall of it
was in with this wood and it was so
pretty it was so beautiful you can't
really see it on this picture but when
you walked into the room you could
really literally smell it
you could smell it yeah like a rustic
style it was really nice even though it
was the least fancy the others were like
more fancy there were some dark red
rooms and some uh more like a um
hunting style room very interesting
[Music]
oh
no this was not the minecraft tweet no
no that was just me on the road looking
at trees and my first thought was
minecraft
so stupid
yeah
yeah anyway we had some nice dinners
here and i'm in the end i was glad that
i was assigned to this room even though
it was release fancy because i had the
best waitress she was so cute
i love that waitress i love it
yeah hi chunkers
hi baby
[Music]
all right
all right all right um next door is a
food picture
just so i didn't even like this but it
looked fancy
[Music]
you guys would probably like it
it was like the things the light things
on the side like um
the white
like like white pinkish looking things
on the side there's like three of those
cubes right
that was fish
and then there was some
yellow colored uh uh
car fuel
the white broccoli
flat flower
no that's not a dead flower i don't know
what that is that was some kind of like
vegetable thingy nose i don't know
cauliflower yeah yeah hey
what are you doing
and then in the middle i don't remember
what that was um that was like all kind
of stuff mixed
it was a fancy food started but i didn't
like it
unfortunately but that's just me being
very picky
this was another dessert that was on the
second day the dessert from the second
day
it was so good it was a passion for
passion fruit
and
little
cake with uh chocolate ice cream and um
i think it was mango mango stuff around
it oh so good the desserts were so good
every day oh chunkis wants cuddles she's
like she's she jumped up on the on the
extra chair next to me
huh should i keep that chair here for
you chunkers is that gonna be your chair
now
is that your chair now
that's okay i'll keep it there for you
yeah oh she's she's getting pets now i
don't have to bow down to give her baths
this is perfect
i can just oh oh i even hear her purring
i can just uh put my hand to the left
and then i can pet her perfect and i can
i can still move in front of the camera
too
perfect
so anyway
this was the second day and it was
another amazing dessert so
um
at the end of me eating the dessert the
cute waitress came uh by again and she
was about to pick up the plate and i
looked at her and she looked at me
and i think she already knew what was
coming but i said this was really really
really really good
and i kind of gave her a really strong
look
[Music]
and she understood she was like you want
another one
and i'm like eh again really can i
really
[Music]
oh she's a mind
reader she's perfect
she got me those she got me no second
servings
honestly i have to say on the second day
um the menu was not really my thing
so i i didn't really eat much of my five
course dinner so
it was really a blessing
to get another dessert yeah
[Music]
yes on the third day by the way
yesterday the dinner from yesterday it
was so good i i loved every every part
of the uh five course menu but because i
loved it so much and it was very very
depthic uh very um
filling um
i i the dessert was really good but that
she offered me a second one but i was
like i was like no actually today i
can't
you'll see it later you'll see it later
so
in obs
uh
when you put in like image like photo
albums it only takes up to
like 10 pictures or so that's so lame
okay let me do it manually then here uh
it will be big but whatever
there we go
so ah that was what this is just give
you like an image of what the
massage just looked like
i'm not on the table but
uh
yeah
massage my mind
so i had a massage every day
except for the first day so i moved the
massage from the first day
to the day of departure
yeah
originally i wouldn't have had a massage
on the day of the departure but we moved
it over they were so kind they were so
kind to move it from day of arrival to
day of departure i every day i had a
massage and let me tell ya on the first
day
of this this one where the picture was
taken
i got a massage that was a like a hot
stone massage but not only with like the
typical hot stones but also with
bag cristale um
mountain crystals
and they were also like
warmed up and put on my body so it was a
mixture of like
meow
meow yawning and yeah it was a mix of of
of uh normal heart stones that you
should usually use and yeah
and yeah it was a one hour massage and
this was the one that i also um invited
my
bff to she got it in a different room
uh
yeah and we both got that massage was it
good ah
wait wait was that really chocolate was
that smoothie
oh whoo
um
uh
i have to say i have better hearthstone
massages i think i think in japan i have
better a better one
[Music]
yamaha
it was good it was relaxing and at the
end of the massage i was like i just
want to lay down here and then sleep i
don't want to leave right now i can't
i'm too tired it really it was relaxing
but it was not the best hostile massage
yes
japanese massages are like so good
they're next level
they they really know what they're doing
[Music]
in
still it was it was good so
and then the second day i had a
it was called wild duft massager it was
a one hour oil massage and then that was
like with with forest scents because it
was in between the forest and the
mountains
um forest and so when i walked in i was
able to choose one of the forest scents
that i liked and i guess
uh
they used an oil that used that forest
and
i have to say
this massage was the worst album free
and
the technique
that the massage therapist used
was
considering
the price of this hotel and the spa and
the level of
everyone everything around me it was not
not that good it was not that impressive
yeah
like the therapist he was really really
good
and
like nice
and the way he talked he sounded like he
knows what he's doing he knew a lot
about like
things that are wrong
uh with bodies
but yeah it was not that good so i
wasn't that happy about it to be honest
[Music]
today on the day of the departure i got
my third massage
and it was um it was an anti-stress
massage that was the one i was supposed
to get on the first day because i wanted
to get rid of the stress i got that on
the last day and it was
it was the best massage that one was
really good
i went in there with
not many uh expect expectations because
the first two massage were just like
average but the third massage was really
good
[Music]
and the the special thing about this
massage was that like after with oil
after uh massaging upper body and legs
um
she put like a
mud pad
actually not mud i suppose more more
m-o-o-l what's that in english
um
some kind of some kind of muddy pad hot
hot mud head
on my back and left there left it there
for like 20 minutes while she was
massaging my feet swamp swoop
[Music]
swallow
clay
something like that swamp fat
[Music]
put it on my back i got that before
during like a physiotherapy
that was prescribed to me
before getting a massage they put that
on my back as well so i really i suppose
this is really really
good for your buck
that they would even use it in a medical
sense
tells me that it's a good thing um
yeah so that was nice i was so relaxed
after that
but
i
how come i was so relaxed after that
massage but later on on the same day
today i wrote on twitter i am
dead but i already don't know i wrote it
in the pre-chat here only i suppose how
come how could that have happened
let me tell you the car ride was fine
nothing happened on the car ride it was
before that
so
i because the day the first day because
we lost so much time i actually extended
our
stay today
by not extending by a night but by
extending the usage of the spa
and by that we got another strudel
we got access to the strudel of that day
as well
and we got um
we had the opportunity to use some more
of the like activities that are included
in the whole package for that day as
well so that means like for example we
did on the
second
day no on the yeah on one of the days we
did yoga because that was included and
we did yoga for beginners i will talk
about that maybe during test overrides
but yeah we did that and then for the
last day i looked at the list of
activities they have that we could still
make use of and it one thing that that
was available
it said
um what are you doing
baby yes yes just lie down let me pet
you while i'm talking
um
uh
it said
mobility and stretch
four
um people of all like difficulties
difficulty levels
so supposedly for beginners as well
said mobility and stretch
and that to me sounded like basically
a stretching session sounded good to me
you know
sounded simple
so i was like yo let's do this before we
uh get into a car and
go home
so
um
it
let me tell you there was definitely
stretching
but it was
it was more like a
workout
and i was i was dying during this
workout it was a one hour workout it was
a legit workout
it was a legit workout
um
it was so embarrassing i
like um i think i was the only one in
the class that um had to stop uh every
once in a while like i lost i lost um
power in my arms i just couldn't hold my
strength i lost strength i couldn't hold
myself up anymore at some point um
everyone in the room thankfully kind of
seemed like the type of person who is
not someone who goes daily to a fintech
fitness center so i was definitely not
the only one
in that regard but i was definitely the
one with the least muscles in her arms
as i could barely hold myself up for
some time but yo it was really really
like there were a lot of um
a lot of uh exercises where we would
hold ourselves up with our arms and then
like raise our legs like kind of there
were some like like poses that were
similar to yoga
um
but more intense than that but i just
couldn't hold myself up anymore because
it was focusing on the arms for way too
long i don't even i don't even i don't
even think um
i did that badly
i think i held up
quite well considering that this was my
first workout in
two years or something like that
yeah i know
[Music]
i died so many times but it's okay
because i'm a phoenix
it's okay
it was
i i i was really dead after that i could
like barely stand up and and move my leg
and my arms
but i at least felt like i did something
for my body
yeah what are you doing what are you
doing what are you doing baby
maybe don't do stupid things here no no
don't play around there
no i don't know if it's safe for cats
okay
i don't know if it's safe for cats be
careful
time to not work out for two years again
but hey
in this wellness vacation i did yoga one
time and i did a freaking proper workout
one time in those three it was only
three days
uh for
three and a half days
so considering that
i think you have to praise me guys
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
that's the first time in a million years
that i've moved my body
and the the lady the instructor the
trainer she said something that
really made a lot of sense to me but i
don't know how to explain it in english
i can only really say it in german so
help me out here german translators
she said that
um
in between our
uh via disorder there are van type
and in between those bunsen
there is a bunch of pluses kind like a
liquid
in between the spine is some stuff and
and in between that stuff is some is
some liquid right
[Music]
and
you need to
um um every day you need to mobilize
your body your shoulders and your spine
in order to get that liquid spinal fluid
i suppose to get that running
to get it like in there you know in
proper liquid shape
uh fluid and and and if you don't do
that then your bonsai then
the
things in between the spine
bones
will be very sad
and
like
you know
they won't feel well and then your whole
back doesn't feel well she kind of like
said it like that and it made a lot of
sense to me i was like yo that's
probably my issue that's probably why my
spine and my body and everything hurts
so much because i don't mobilize my arms
and my shoulders and all that and that
liquid it just doesn't the fluid it's
not it's not happening so
my my bad time they're unhappy
it makes so much sense
[Music]
discs and yeah discs the discs my discs
are out of shape or dead or
damaged i don't know
probably most likely
the way she said that it made so much
sense so we definitely mobilized my body
during that workout yeah
anyway moving
on i i tangent so much oh my god i
wanted this to be a short it's gonna end
in three minutes let's end this in three
minutes
uh uh picture
this was some of the strudels
[Music]
so every day between 3 00 p.m and 5 p.m
there were it was struggle time in the
back you have an app still with vanilla
sauce and in the front you have a like a
what was that some kind of like dark
berry i guess it was blackberry or
coriander or something like that
i think it was heidelberg
um
yeah a struggle with vanilla sauce that
was one of those special ones and today
today it was um
uh
um
[Music]
uh
was the special one from today and and
today we actually ate with vanilla ice
cream we didn't know on this day that
they serve it with vanilla ice cream as
well
what's so good mm-hmm
[Music]
it's now
that made us very happy because that was
basically our lunch
we ate breakfast
i was i was living pretty healthy these
days uh i have to say every day i
uh woke up at 10 am to get breakfast
and yeah
that's much earlier than usually
[Music]
i didn't even netflix that for that long
yeah
it was pretty pretty healthy i have to
say
yeah
and uh yeah so for lunch we had strudels
and then we had dinner later on so it
was it was really nice we didn't have to
buy extra food at all we had breakfast
we had lunch and we had
tonight yeah um this was a random
uh starter does that look familiar to
you
does that look familiar
[Music]
no i did not cook for them this was
actually uh yesterday part of the five
course
meal it was before the soup
and after
it was like salad then it was like uh
i guess yeah cold starter and then it
was a warm started and it was a soup and
then
it was
the main dish and then the dessert yeah
i think that was usually how it was
and this was a really small serving
normally this fills up so much
that's why uh i didn't uh order a second
dessert on that day
because this okay is the case but i made
it in my stream before it's not macaroni
no no no watch my cookie theme then you
will know
yeah but it's it's uh it was really good
it was way better than the ones that i
made
[Music]
um
and on that same day the dessert i was i
switched it midway for i was like i was
looking at the people who were eating
next to us i was like yo that actually
looks
pretty good damn good let me ask my
favorite waitress if i can change my
dessert my dessert uh last minute it was
not last minute it was pretty early so
it was all good and i was able to change
and i got this
[Music]
so what is this
so this was a banana toffee
toffee thingy you know what i mean
inside there was like a
soft fresh cut bananas and then banana
chips and it was like some cookie
crumble
and chocolate cr
pieces and all that
and yeah
and it was not a pudding it was not a
pudding
banana toffee
um
is that a name in english as well
hello baby oy nice jump but not bad no
feed pie yes yes like that but there was
not much pie there
but yes that's what it was called
banoffee pie
[Music]
it was really good but it was it was so
sweet
mr
[Music]
very very good you guys want to see a
video
oh wait i have one more picture of the
room um
yes i have another picture let me show
you here
you don't have to check in the windows i
already checked manager already checked
and i already uh uh mosaiced something
so
don't even think about it you don't have
to look too close into the windows i
already checked
but this was uh
the other side of the
room where you would see like how it
looks like
it's a very natural style very
wooden uh style
[Music]
it was very comfy yeah the bathroom was
nice too but i don't have a picture of
the bathroom and the balcony the balcony
had great view because
um like all the buildings were like
facing
and surrounding
a pot yes meow i know
facing and surrounding a pond and a pool
in the middle which you will see now
uh before i show you the video i'll show
you just no i'll just try the videos
it's easy to comprehend
uh it's this one right
now this one is also checked for my
manager so don't get too crazy about it
okay
uh let's stop this uh audio for a moment
this will
calm down my cat is zooming
okay calm down it's gonna be big i think
there we go oh it's a proper size
so wait conduct it's too fast let's do
it slow let let me slow it down for you
guys speed fifty percent how about that
it's
this what this was filmed
while i was in the pool
my bff standing right behind me
turning around while i was turning
around so this was the pool that you saw
that's right next to that um the onsen
washing place the shower place this was
the pool that you saw from that view
okay
and now i give you a
uh view um
oh slow slow it was actually pretty cold
outside and on that day it was raining
as well we were in there while it was
raining softly
and um it was the pool was uh this pool
was while not being as hot as the onsen
it was still fairly warm so it was
comfortable to be in the water although
yes meow stop zooming
while uh when you get like out of the
water it's cold then you
we what we usually did was get into this
pool first then get out of the water
freeze but quickly
go over to
over there well we walked over there
quickly because over there now in the
middle in the middle you see some uh
steam coming up over there is uh the the
onsen
the onsen pool is right over there so we
quickly run over
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah the mountain view yeah yeah it
was very cloudy though very uh nearby
league and
do you know this
do you know this uh
that there is actually a lake
so the whole the whole
hotel
in the middle of the the whole like area
was a pond and in the pond in the middle
of the pond was a pool which we we were
in but during the summer time you can
also easily go and chill in in the
natural pond
wait it's not a natural one i think but
um it's natural water it's like normal
water not pool water that's what i'm
trying to say
so and then here is just one of the many
many many saunas on the on this this
building that's the sauna oh that's
mountains
there were many many saunas there
mountains mountains actually this area
is very popular for skiing
er ski
actually right next to this hotel is a
skiing place
so um in the winter time this completely
completely transforms into a winter ski
hotel
and uh
you actually get uh free
tickets to use the
uh the the elevator thingy you know that
goes up the mountain and it's right next
to the hotel
it's really nice because you can go like
skiing and then you come back to the
hotel which is right next to the
mountains and right inside the mouse
mountains and then you go into the sauna
and the only said
imagine that yes yes
so and then we turn around
we go back down again
and
there's i don't know what that building
is but yeah you see here the the lake
pretty lake
beautiful beautiful inna and what you
see now
[Music]
is the main building
our room was in that building um
like in the middle part of it actually
um
uh actually that that's not the main it
connects here to the main building you
see how it connects
yes
and
that's kind of like where the reception
and the lobby and all this and
restaurants are also somewhere in there
that that's where the restaurant is in
the front i think one of the restaurants
and
more rooms lots of rooms
there were also not only suites but like
um like two
two floor of family suites that had like
way too much space so i didn't go for
that one but they have a really nice
view as well and they're really huge
yeah
and
yes yes we turn around
you see some other different looking
buildings ah but if you i think that
little space between the
the
um trees up there
i think that's one of the places where
you can
ski down but that's not very high that's
i think behind that was actually
mountains too but it's just covered up
by the clouds completely i don't know
but there was way higher mountains
around here as well
and
yeah i stopped filming somewhere there
yes yes yes yes
nice
kanji beautiful isn't it and that's
that's where you would see on the very
right side you see uh the place where
you would wash
your body
you're not supposed to take that shower
naked you're supposed to watch yourself
while being in the swimsuit so it
doesn't matter if they see you yeah
oh and oh actually right next to it
uh that the place with the chairs that's
the japanese restaurant that they have
there so no suzuka
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah and there was actually one more
pool that was pretty far away from all
of that um that was pretty high
uh
uh high up
like this was like on ground level but
if you go like up to the highest level
there was um
more saunas and there was a sports pool
and we went to that on the first day
and
and the sports pool is a bit more cold
it's still like low-key heated so it's
not ice cold even in the winter
but it's not warm
and it's pretty long and it has a great
view and um i wanted to show you this
because i was excited about it
the person that you just saw that was
not uh one of us but uh okay this was
really short let me show you again
see like you start inside and then you
go outside and there's like automatic
doors in the water
in the water mitaka
and mountains all around
wow
cool isn't it i was so fascinated by
that
it's actually probably not even that
special i got i got some like hotel ads
uh later uh on that day and it showed me
like a hotel uh in in the same country
there was also a wellness hotel that had
the same kind of pool with the same kind
of automatic doors
anyway
yeah door in the water
pretty cool i would say
yeah so
let me let me show you this beautiful
picture
wow my camera phone camera takes good
pictures decent pictures
[Music]
nice we had um
kind of bad luck with the weather but it
didn't really matter because this was
more of a staycation anyway
we we
my friend
actually got me to make use of the
saunas yeah
i'll talk more about that uh i think
during tales of our eyes about my sauna
experiences because i'm not the type of
person who likes going into saunas or
any place where people who don't know
each other are naked together
i usually don't like that the lake is so
nice isn't it like i want to go back
here in the summertime but
i think it's probably good that we went
during this time because
it was already crowded during this time
i can't imagine how crowded the hotel is
during winter and summer time because
those definitely are the most most
crowded seasons for this hotel in the
summer time you have this great lake and
all those pools but in the wintertime
you have the snow all around and you can
go skiing and then come back here to
relax
so
it is a very popular hotel
um i can recommend it though so let me
tell you my final thoughts before we end
this stream here because i need i don't
want to immediately ruin my my sleep
schedule which i probably will i can't
really escape from that i suppose but um
i don't want to i don't want this to be
too long by the way tomorrow def loop
changed to
minecraft with welcoming senpai
yes
really spontaneous uh but i thought def
loop i should probably hold back on it
until i get my ps5 and then it will run
perfectly smoothly on ps5 i didn't want
it to be like a failure scuff experience
i hope that's okay
um everyone's playing minecraft right
now and everyone's like chilling there
and vibing so i kind of wanted to join
in on that so
me and wata myself are doing a proper
collab i i give her a tour and then we
work a little bit on phoenix then i
think uh
oops
[Music]
so i still have a lot to talk about this
trip but i'll keep those stories
until
when i need them
i wrote everything down
yeah
uh yeah there's some things i need to
fix in phoenix apparently so
it's good that i'll get to it i suppose
i've heard yes i know about zombies i
don't know how the hell that happened
but hopefully i'm not too late if i fix
it tomorrow cause i'm not gonna do it
now i just got back from my vacation
apparently it's only three zombies and i
hope that's true
i hope i hope that's true
uh anyway so
the vacation
was very good it was too short
[Music]
for me
i was able to relax but i was not able
to completely shut off
every day
i
every day i was bombarded with um
important things
on our discord
uh often also specifically for me
and it was just like
impossible to get my mind off of it
every morning i woke up and i opened my
my discord it was like thousands of
messages
thousands of tags
and
while it was all exciting things that i
was happy to see
it was still like yeah i knew that i
couldn't really take a break
and
yeah so that's kind of unfortunate
um
it wasn't really an option to just
completely turn everything off
eva
but
yeah i tried my best
to relax i had a great time i had a
comfy time
and
um i got a lot of massages i got a lot
of good food and i did a lot of exercise
besides those the exercise that i told
you about i also did swim every day in
the pool
and uh
yeah
it was nice i had some good sleep
um i had some social interaction
and with people like mostly my best
friend but that's at least something
like for
for the longest time i haven't been
doing anything besides streaming
so that's very good too
[Music]
there
um
i don't know if there will ever be a day
where
until you know it's over i don't think
there will ever be a day of complete
serenity and calmness
yeah but it's fine it's fine i had a
great time and honestly i mean i love
whole life and i love my job so
i mostly like i'm fine with like dealing
dealing with it every day the reason why
i went to this vacation was basically i
wanted to like do something about my
burnout and
uh asking myself the question did it
help or not
i think it helped
i think
yeah
i don't know
i don't think that a three-day vacation
can heal a burnout
so it's more like what i'll do from now
on
and um i think it is still important to
take many vacations from now on as well
in the future
so i'll take another one in winter time
maybe a whole week that then
[Music]
and
um by doing yoga uh in this vacation
i kind of feel like
it took my maybe it took my my my
my fright my fear right my fear of um
doing it like more often from now on so
i think i'm motivated to do that uh
on on
i forgot the word
uh
regular on a regular basis
and
um i want to move my body more so i will
do that and also i also talked with my
bff we talked about doctors and stuff
and um she also has to go to some
doctors uh soon so she said she'll drag
me along
and uh yeah so i'll also i'll take
better care of my body hopefully i'm
still very busy and it won't all happen
at once but
i'll try to do it step by step and try
to improve my my lifestyle and um yeah
my weekly schedules by
implementing things that are important
[Music]
and at least now we got the new chair so
that's already a good step in the right
direction yay
yay so thank you guys for giving me a
chance to take a small break
um
i i hope i hope it was uh i hope i hope
you guys didn't um
um forget about me or lose interest in
me
while i was gone i hope your passion has
found a new fire on your flame
[Music]
we will have a great rest of the week
it's packed anyway even though i was
vacation week tomorrow minecraft and
then we also have a diggy kami digikami
online convention we have a collab with
amen
we played tens of horizons yeah it's
gonna be a fun end of the week and next
week is gonna be fun too so my fireball
is stronger than ever really
that's what i like to hear a new spark
would you say a new spark has ignited in
your heart
that would be great i would appreciate
that
[Music]
yeah but i still i still want to
maintain
um
a big percentage of the amount of
streams and the length of my streams
so
we'll see how it goes
[Applause]
[Music]
a new spot caused by hinotoni has
challenged my yo what's going on
[Music]
but you guys gonna take care of your own
health too all right
are you listening
to me
your health also important not only mine
take care of your own health as well
yeah
so
me honestly
i ha i have to ruin my sleep schedule
again and anyway because next week is
ttrpg
and by the latest at that point it will
be ruined so
there is uh
no no choice dude i have to ruin it
again it was nice while it lasted
if ttrpg ever ends i think we have a
chance
i think we have a chance in having a
healthy sleep schedule for now it's okay
it's okay it's okay
but the days felt so long
during this vacation it felt really long
getting up at 10 a.m was already like
a big thing
and i felt i didn't i didn't take naps
i was awake for the whole day
no
noise
making use of the full day while still
being very relaxed and doing relaxing
stuff
yeah
all right so uh if you're curious
we're not sponsored but the hotel's name
i don't know
it was probably in one of the pictures
i don't know if i really want to like i
don't want to you know what i don't want
to advertise but it's a it's a great
hotel
i know
[Music]
it's very close to the border of germany
by the way so if you live in germany
especially if you live like in in
like um
bayern you should you should uh
easily get to this place
it has this this hotel
you know how i got to that hotel in the
first place i googled uh
austrian uh wellness hotel and
this was
one of the
ones that was pushed into my face
immediately
and the strongest because they pay i
think they pay a lot for advertising
because they're everywhere they showed
up everywhere even after i already
booked i saw them in all websites that i
you know like apps that i use like as
advertisement they're literally
everywhere they really really really
push it into your face so you might even
just stumble across it
i think if you google
uh uh australian
wellness to tell you you're probably
gonna find it it really stands out in
the pictures as well and and it it
focuses on like natural nature and and
um you know or organic stuff and as well
so
yeah that's what it advertises a lot too
oh actually you know what if you look up
wellness to tell australia onsen
then you're probably gonna find it
what's the first one really
oh there it is oh there you go i don't
even have to say the name
yeah yeah if you ever come to my country
and you feel like you want to take or
especially in the winter time if you
ever want to take a vacation it will be
packed it will probably be packed but
it's a great hotel the service was nice
if you want to take a vacation where you
can also ski right next to the hotel
why the hell not
tell them kiala sent you no don't i
don't know i'll shut up now
maybe next time i'll get a room for free
just kidding
yes
english of course i'm sure they speak
english i didn't speak english down but
i'm sure they do
[Music]
okay
i'll just i'll just tangent endlessly if
i continue now
and
thank you guys for watching i'll see you
tomorrow in the collab with vata man
i'll probably be speaking a lot of
japanese tomorrow but i'll try to
squeeze in a english every now and then
because it will it will be um not a one
hour collab it will be a bit longer than
that i'm sure
since she'll help me with some phoenix
and things so i don't wanna
ignore you guys for too long yeah
maybe i can get a lot of my senpai to
speak some english with me
[Music]
i'll make a thumbnail out now and
then can we could honestly just do her
point of view only that would probably
suffice but i'm gonna do a point of view
on my channel as well because
just because i haven't been around the
past few days so yeah
um
yes yes yes yes yes so
thank you for watching
thank you very much i'm i'm glad to be
back and i'm looking forward to sleeping
in my bed tonight with my cats
and in german we stay
i'll finish in
i'll have to find time to read super
chats another time
i'm sorry i want to take it easy today
because i just came back
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
i appreciate you guys thank you love you
thank you very much
[Music]
thank you
goodbye
[Music]
yum
you