foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
thank you foreign
you took every opportunity to just fly
in there I expected me I respect
[Music]
[Applause]
by the way
the teacher is sick today but that's all
right because it's always yeah
[Music]
no no free days we have to learn by the
way stop poking me I can't poke you back
feel issue wait I wanna I wanna uh what
are you padding okay hold on a minute
okay okay it looks different on my
screen
in front of her and you were touching
something else like oh my goodness I'm
brushing her
okay okay
wait back it up what
I'm doing well
well just don't just don't ruin my
extensions
yes wait what you didn't know that I
have look at my hair how do you think my
hair is this long without extensions it
looks so perfect
actually well no not anymore actually
because I ripped them out last night out
of craziness why I had a men hit no
but I do have these songs I do have
spots where the extensions were
connected and they were tied too tightly
so I snipped my own hair off in order to
cut the extensions out but they're not
bald spots yeah I was not yet no they're
just shorter they're Parts where my hair
is shorter than the rest of my hair
I had a crazy moment because it hurt so
bad and it's so hot in Japan and my
extensions were Rat's Nest
I took fate into my own hands and I tore
them out and I feel good
I feel great actually I feel great yeah
so this is all natural Mori hair now
well I'm not bald from here not bald
no
no some of you guys were suggesting I
was bald let's not run away from what
you guys were suggesting here that I'm
bald which I'm not as you can see
is that why you're wearing the mask
there oh my God
it's okay Callie with all the work that
you do and all the stress it's natural
to start building yeah
all right excuse me thanks for coming to
the stream everyone
um everybody have a great day bye
everybody
[Music]
I'm joking yeah
okay let's introduce ourselves my name
is Maury callathe from hololive English
I am a Shinigami nice to meet you or
nice to see you again
[Music]
all right who's this who's this person
oh
uh ha this is this yes hi this is a
takamashikiara and the Phoenix Phoenix
from hololive English Ohio goldaimasu
um yeah today I am wearing a pink you
could thank you does it look good
[Music]
maybe someone who has a nipple on their
foreign no don't teach them that don't
teach them that word
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay hello I am Amelia Watson from Hello
Life English Mist 2 and I am Tensai
nice to meet you
[Music]
wow incredible
English myth
um I like cookies oh yeah
what is the tattoo moment over there
[Applause]
[Music]
oh sorry sorry you know sorry about that
hello I'm girl it's very nice to meet
you have I met you before
I have a gun
I'm so excited to learn English today
wow this is not in Japan
okay
[Music]
put him up Kelly hmm do you wanna
explain also in Japanese and English
what we're doing in both languages
my Japanese is not as good as Kiara's so
I have I have a rule sheet on the screen
for the games I'm we're playing three
we're playing three games today you guys
three English games
three types of games yup yeah mitsudes
[Music]
simple simple English games that I think
you guys will enjoy okay sensei Sensei
yes yes
your ego will be very good very good
English I'm ready okay
uh everybody this is listening practice
okay
[Music]
that's a different tour
story I thought you kicked the kicked
the bird no
am I
[Laughter]
but you know I was I was an English
teacher a long time ago
[Music]
yeah and the sun teacher but also also
English teacher so so I know I know good
English teaching ways so that's what
we're gonna do okay okay
leave it to me leave it to me is
okay and while you're at it if you want
to learn more English okay look below
guys
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
no no no no
okay all right let's listen let's learn
let's look away from Maury's mistake and
let's learn today the first game that we
have today and if you win if you win by
the way you can get points playing these
games and if you win you get a trophy
special trophy
yeah it's a special trophy so get ready
it's special so here's the rules here
are the rules of the game the first game
we're playing first games rules this
game is called guess what
[Music]
guess what the main player has a card on
their forehead okay you cannot see the
cards so no stream sniping ladies okay
you can't stripe this okay you can't
sniper okay okay no striping no stream
sniping okay we can't look at the screen
um everyone else can but the person who
has the card on their forehead can't
look okay okay it's like in the office
exactly yep so every other player has to
give a one-word hint to help them guess
what the card says okay
all right because who who gives the last
whoever gives the last hint before the
main player correctly guesses their word
wins one point
okay but there are no go words that you
can't give as hints okay yeah so for
example maybe I want I have blueberry on
someone's forehead but the no-go word is
blue so you can't use blue or Berry
oh okay okay
aside
[Laughter]
anyways
um if you're lost you'll understand it
when we do it okay sometimes you need an
example okay you just need an example
okay so let's start with a with an
example word okay so this doesn't count
this next word
so the person we're gonna start with is
gura for this the example okay
all right I don't don't look girl
I'm not looking I promise okay so here
is the secret word you guys all the
other ladies you guys look
this is the word on girl's head
is it cute
yeah it's pretty cute aha okay
okay so these are yeah maybe a little
bit but I'll let it slide so these are
the words you can't use you can't give
these hints it's spelled wrong no it's
not yeah yeah it is no it's not yes
it was an English teacher by the way
all right I don't like this particular
thing maybe that's a hint yet okay but I
don't
foreign
[Music]
yeah
oh wait you know I should add some like
sound effects to Discord like the people
next idea would you like to assist me
with that Nina I shall I think I should
have it so let me let me look for it
while you guys do the practice round
okay assistant okay Kiara is the first
one to give a hint give a hint
ask me what you are wait do I ask a
question does she just give me anything
she just gives you a hint that's it give
me a head then
you green
oh okay how about something just one
word green something that could I be
more it doesn't like it must be a
vegetable
s to go past my lips in a very long time
so don't worry okay well I'm a big
veggie fan that's what I'm talking about
deny for me okay yes green
Amelia what's the next step
oh
wait what'd you say hey
watermelon
[Music]
paint hit is it is the Discord cutting
me out yes it sounds like tits yeah
I hear the pit
okay
yes okay okay okay okay green has pit
hmm
uh avocado correct so Amelia
yay
Uma gets a point
except you don't because sorry
to burst your bubbles it's not a real
point though all right you don't like
avocado no
tastes like nothing
let's go
it's like anything
yeah basically like vegetable butter
okay already half an hour in let's get
going all right okay
all right now I've got the next uh the
first real word and we're gonna start
off with Kiara okay oh okay so let me
put the secret word on your head it's
not on my side of clothes
all right
so you can't look at the Stream
here is the word
and ladies these are the words you can't
use oh okay okay all right are we ready
to start giving you a question yeah can
you only say one word at a time one word
at a time
oh okay yes all right can I ask all
right uh go ahead I'm in give a hint
[Music]
what am I uh heart
heart feet heart okay
[Music]
yeah okay
can I ask you too by the way no I am the
I am the Puppet Master
puppet master I put all of this together
I get to watch you guys I get to watch
you guys go through trials and prove
your English proficiency
okay what am I
um
uh
I'm
um
something good please
big
heart big the [\h__\h]
next be next all right let's go oh man
your turn
remember more than one oh okay yeah
we're going we're going all the way
remember
yes member ah wait feet heart uh
no what what was the one the good I said
big big feet hard big member can I go
can I go
[Music]
go Ena
oh wait wait pink okay okay I was gonna
say it
all right there should be a five second
limit but alrighty okay you know I got
it
maybe half point I don't know it looks
like kind of in the middle okay fine
I'll take the boy I'll take the point
oh it's very close there you go
yay wait so are you gonna add the five
second rule or yes yes we will add a
five second countdown on the Mori side
alrighty nice well done Kiara for your
guess so the person who uh manages to
make the person realize what we're
talking about is the one who gets the
point exactly exactly
it's a thin line that you have to walk
right you want to give the best hint to
like make them realize it but not too
much to give the others an advantage if
they don't figure it out with your hints
yeah it's a hard game okay all right
turn
Amelia Watson are you ready to rumble
I'm ready I'm not looking already all
right okay
okay
here is your word
ladies one moment I'm getting the no go
words
why did you say big did you say big yeah
and you were connecting it with Ina's
hint I guess okay
I guess it makes sense that's not
English shut up
yes it is oh
that's probably a big hit
all right first off
Kiara go
um
well you don't have this in your words
re-zero
okay okay
[\h__\h] you that's technically two words
right because it's technically written
as the one thing
two yeah one all right go Ena your turn
ah
[Music]
somebody
slime
okay okay
four three two one gura can I guess wait
oh you wanna guess go for it
I don't know okay never mind if you
think you know it I don't know I'm not
sure okay okay
[Music]
hmm
Komar
m a
yes C what are you Australian Comer
I fell into a
comarin
coma yeah
as a reincarnation or something
um
what a Japanese word on there
why
[Music]
[Applause]
okay everyone knows everyone
knows what that is
fine fine we'll use okay close your eyes
you know
okay we'll use I guess this will work
okay
here's the next one
[Music]
or I'll take it away wait wait I did
play it we were just uh busy talking
over it I think oh okay
all right
next
nope you guys don't understand all right
the point isn't for the secret word to
be English the point is that they use
words simple English words
okay you know what you know what we can
do we could use completely boring words
Chet do you want to use a word like
apple you guys
okay uninteresting words
Sensei is the word on the right person
yes now begin Kiara
okay
um
flat
okay okay
four three
two one wait will I always go first
just a disadvantage
oh my [\h__\h]
I'm gonna left my extensions in so I
could pull them out right now
Amelia go
okay
um
um English
okay okay okay okay okay four
three
two
one gura
office oh
five four three
two
one Kiara
ah
um
[Music]
[Applause]
pants pants
pants Oh wait can I guess can I guess
yes yes please Chad okay
one point for Kiara
yeah
threw me off let's go
manipulating but then office I was like
wait no one oh let me fix my [\h__\h] really
quick hold on
my neck is popping off hold on a second
I have to fix my head
my neck I look like a snake Okay we're
fine anyway ping pong that was correct
all right point for koala well you made
a good point Kiara so this time when you
do the hints we're gonna start from Ina
okay okay so all right secret word now
on the head of garden Shark Girl Idol of
Ian it's not boobs
your eyes cover your eyes all right
close them close them good yes good
all right now here's the word
now do not do not wait give anything to
discern
no no tunes no sounds no songs I don't
even know it's music
okay not necessarily but you could
discern
all right is it a fart all right no it
is not a [\h__\h] fart noise okay go all
right Inna let's start I'm gonna I'm
gonna strangle everyone here
[Music]
uh I'm sorry I can't I can't seem to
read the word
oh my God
I'm gonna [\h__\h] lose it
I'm gonna lose it okay my word is
name okay nice nice That's a good hint
five
four name three name two now my one
okay Amelia your turn
uh above
[Music]
oh oh look mookie mookie man
okay five
four
three
two one
boo-boo
Kiara your turn
[Music]
my time yeah yes celebrity okay
a celebrity
is it He-Man
that's not a real person
four three it's John Cena
oh
that's correct you got it
John Cena
I don't even really know
that well that's pretty good not bad
for me yes has your gangamari face
changed because I don't think I've seen
this before
3D it's quite something yeah oh yeah
that's pretty good let's go thank you
congrats very well done
all right we've got we've got one more
round to do through you guys so here we
go okay yeah okay all right now the next
secret word is Kiara you better be
closing your eyes oh oh yeah oops okay
okay I'm close my eyes no looking at the
Stream
no okay okay ladies here's the next word
now here are the words you can't use
all right
here we go
ready Amelia start
[Music]
does it have to be in English yes
but what if it's like a like a nickname
or something
no
no I know you're trying to do it I'm not
gonna allow it okay uh viewers okay
anyways okay
all right
five
two
one you know okay
um
listeners
[Laughter]
okay
we have a hunch sorry two one
uh
uh somebody
[Music]
uh
oh
Fuji
Fuji okay
okay I'm very
um you you pushed in a very different
direction but I'm gonna guess now with
that hoping that's right no sunkis
Brothers
listeners viewers Fuji and brothers
huh
three two no idea one you know damn it
that was pretty good though
Super Chat
nice
[Music]
sorry
listeners two one uh-oh
[Music]
Mario oh what what
oh my God okay I get it it's like a
different different look at the topic I
get it uh-huh I technically
okay
she said she was the number one English
speakers somehow
view viewers listeners Fuji
[Music]
no all right try try Universal Studio
okay y'all made your turn
fan base
oh that's one word right yeah yeah
[Music]
Holo live
can I give up
uh yeah you can pass you can give up no
one gets the point though okay what the
[\h__\h] is that give me the point yeah
Bros
[Laughter]
you did your best sorry Mustang sorry I
mean technically no suggies are part of
JP Bros so
no problem I mean just get off your back
you couldn't get a point that time
anyway so
all right now next up Amelia close your
eyes you better not be looking or I'll
strangle you okay I'm glad I minimize
the tab okay awesome I believe in you
here we go here is the word and here are
the no go words that you cannot use with
this word and don't make a comment about
it being English or not shut up
oh
we have something to say I'm just I'm
just trying to cover the bases for what
people might say
okay
interesting all right now let's begin
with gura this time
shall we
start
[Music]
um
Dev
[Music]
that's smart
that's a good one
alrighty okay three
two
one Inna
[Music]
um
can it be names
that's not fun I mean I mean I'm sorry
I didn't even hear what you said you
didn't hear it no okay
okay uh you know
[Music]
oh maybe she doesn't know
I probably wouldn't really know what you
mean with that either
what do you mean you know maybe she
doesn't know
I know maybe she doesn't know
can't assume your turn Kiara
Obsession ooh
okay
three
two I'm confused but I know that that
word alone is not enough but it's a good
base word for the others okay have fun
all right girl what's your what's your
hint
simulator
oh
[Music]
Hollow Earth
think about all the words you have so
far what are the previous words
session
[Music]
um
um stalker oh
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is a rough one okay all right let's
go go okay I'm gonna remember the last
word I said
Obsession my next word is love
ah
[Music]
um
you're getting there you can get in
there maybe a bit warm all right girl
let's go
[Music]
um
nice
developer knife Obsession huh no no she
said that first I don't know why they're
confused with developer
oh
it doesn't know oh you didn't mean death
and that I mean that could also make
sense though you say knife or death
knife
how about Ina
[Music]
you know he's gone oh okay she's back
she's back
oh
you know I think I might maybe not
working bro
oh yeah
don't think too hard about it for the
sake of fairness for the sake of
fairness don't think too hard
but but we can at least give a hint
maybe that shoot that is a Japanese word
right yeah I mean I did freak out about
that in the beginning
[Music]
maybe I don't know it if you know what
you know you know it
um you definitely do
okay sorry I'm back you're good keep
pooping no problem where are we at
[Music]
um
baby okay what was good sorry I didn't
hear nice
knife hmm
maybe this will lead you in the right
direction
um
[Music]
okay okay I mean I said no Japanese
words but it's fine oh really you're
sorry I mean my word can be Japanese
videos can't that's okay okay it doesn't
matter
it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
it doesn't matter it's English right we
use it I mean technically
well
Kiara you want to give another hand yes
maybe I'll get on the next one okay you
remember my love and my obsession now
here comes boyfriend
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
is hurting herself in confusion all over
the place
right knife
um
would you like to pass Amelia Watson
all right I'll pass up guys let's move
on the answer is yandere
answer is Yonder yeah you know you know
I must be getting the the Japanese words
to guess like first place
now that you mentioned probably probably
not new
my brain just wasn't in that area of
like oh you know I thought that it would
kind of lead you into the thinking maybe
it's the other you know I would have
thought if you guys said like archetype
or Trope or something like that but
that's okay
simple English I guess I I would not
that's not even
gonna be Larry sorry
you know what that's what we're gonna do
be from the other girls here not mine
yeah you know what let's do something
boring let's do a boring word you know
what okay all right
all right yeah close your eyes close
your eyes
all right closed it here we go
it's kind of cool the audience can play
too if you guys don't watch the stream
yeah yeah you should test your English
close your eyes yeah that's your English
okay all right it's this [\h__\h] boring
one so here we go little palette
cleanser
all right we start this time from Kiara
all right Kiara I don't I don't think
you would have to put those I thought it
was like uh self-explanatory that you're
not allowed to use the words that are
the words well I'm just making sure
covering my
I think I think I think this is related
neverlands
like Netherlands yeah like the country
yeah I think it's related Netherlands
okay interesting okay two one Amelia go
uh farming
Farm
okay
three
two one girl wait wait wait wait I think
I know what it is but I don't know what
it's called
yes
[Music]
yes what's it called though well as long
as you don't know you can't get the
point
I can't
I'm not getting point I'm giving the
point okay enough to produce is that
thing what what what does it produce
oh
yeah that's correct point for Amelia can
I get half a point yeah
just kidding just kidding just kidding
God damn okay no your egg was very
Joseph
[Music]
well you're doing your best and
as long as you try your best okay this
is the last one for gura
all right get ready girl here's another
[\h__\h] boring one here here we go ain't
no boring
all right now here are the words that
you can't use
oh
everything else is fine
okay
everything else is good to go everything
okay everything
good luck all right
I start
um
[Music]
good oh
three two one
curd
is he
c-u-r-d curd ah kurd okay oh honest
words you can't hear the beginning
all right two one Kiara
substitute
substitute yeah two substitute
substitute yeah
a food that is occurred that is
substitute used in as a substitution
what yeah tofu
[Music]
winner winner chicken dinner wow
nice that's pretty good that was a hard
word I think I think I understand why
I'm so good at this because English is
not my first language I I can simplify
the meaning of words yeah
your teeth makes me die
[Laughter]
[Music]
and that gives me a point yes
you're powerful congratulations is the
best English speaker yeah low-key though
actually
so far so good now we were gonna play
Hangman but we don't have enough time so
we're gonna play a funner game we're
gonna play more fun games all right now
you just have to you just have to trust
me okay because it's gonna take a little
explaining
oh
okay
now before you look at what whatever
that says here are the rules okay the
rules are important because this next
game
[Music]
is called great minds sorry great minds
think alike
all right here's how you play a prompt
is given to the group for example name a
food almost everyone hates it's Family
Feud basically uh each girl comes up
with an answer and messages Mori in
secret on Discord the goal is to have an
answer that overlaps with another person
in the group but not too many okay
so
if you answer the same as one other girl
you each get two points
for example Kiara and gurase durian
right and then
say other answers right because you guys
overlapped you get two points okay
imagine though Ina also says durian
right that's three of you guys saying
durian so you each just get one point
but if AMA says durian as well nobody
gets any points because you all thought
of the same thing
so you have to find the good balance
exactly
so you have to be careful but also
having no overlap is also no point
exactly
you have to try and overlap with one
person
[Music]
um
Joseph
candy is does it huh does he I think she
just put that in there oh maybe it is
I thought that was flavor
just Chiara flavor
alrighty ladies so let's start with an
example one name a hollow life member
that's blue and you guys have to DM me
okay so say Okay into my DMs okay and
give me your answers here we go now okay
yes
sliding
all right I'm Gonna Change uh the music
to a little more like thinking music
I just had a thought oh you can change
it thought
if I haven't put it in yet
all right let's see what we got
all right
it looks like the answers they're in
yes the answers are coming coming in all
right
now I've got to do more ding dong
foreign
that was a beautiful ping pong Jesus
Christ girl
what is she right nothing don't worry
about it all right here everybody's time
to look at your answers ready Kiara says
yeah
almost said okay
oh no we're not gonna match
[Laughter]
no points for anyone I
was getting good
yeah
well sometimes you gotta work with that
reverse psychology you see
yeah
she's in the room and we forgot about
her no no she was my first choice but I
was like what if everyone puts it yeah I
was like don't overthink it I guess
exactly you can't over you can't
overthink it all right now for the real
game that's okay because that was just a
test okay now we get to the real game
okay so let's see what prompt do I wanna
do
because I have a bunch of different ones
here let me see okay here's a good one
um
and by the way they don't have to be
word for word the same
for example like if you say Name an
activity you like to do and like you say
like
what the [\h__\h] was that noise that was
water pouring okay all right that's not
what I meant to say say um for example
going to theme parks and somebody else
says uh going to Disney or something
like that then that's I would count that
as the same it's fine you mean didn't he
right not yeah sorry
yeah all right the first prompt is
name a food that goes with peanut butter
name a food that go with peanut butter
yep that's right
that go with peanut butter what would it
be
give me your peanut butter go with Foods
Let It Go oh God wait
I'm getting hungry now uh oh I wanna
apples and peanut butter mmm and then I
won and then I won toast with peanut
butter I think I'm giving you guys a
bunch of answers you can use them or not
it's not that's not the point of the
game Sorry
just going a little I mean personally I
would say nothing oh [\h__\h] unpopular
opinion
it's not like peanut butter
okay
what
why what did I do
yeah you would help my answer
oh now we know now we know well it's
fine because I already put in the
answers I already put in the answers so
it's fine Kiara said jelly
Thomas said banana
said
oh that was girls answering it says
Apple curses jelly yeah
and Kiara
[Applause]
congrats good powerful all right the
score the score is going high five bro I
use my head oh nice
very nice nice one team well done all
right now for the next prompt hmm what
do I want the next prompt to be
let's get a little crazy
let's get a little a little nutty name
something people do to their armpits
they themselves or yeah like what do you
do like to your like just what do you do
to your I can only think of two things
yeah and then write it down
and one thing is unhinged and not
something I do
no no they may not it's just something
people do or I mean I guess you could do
I don't know it doesn't need to be
something that you do personally
let's be normal okay at least one person
two things but none of them are unhinged
Kiara
wait we can both wait no it's that I
wouldn't do it but people maybe want to
do it not saying that is my answer but
you know
two things that I thought of
okay
still waiting on two answers
is going nuts
you know it's pretty hot in the summer
huh
wink wink I see
okay I think I get it
I can spell
you do sweat
Jesus
okay all right you know what here we go
here are the answers Kiara says shave a
fairly hinged answer yes Amelia says
deodorize
reasonable
deodorize accident two different ways no
wait hold on I spelled it two different
ways
which one is it girl says sniff
which is the answer I expected from girl
so it looks like Amelia and Ina you
should get two points yay
oh wow we're really catching up here
it's getting close
not for you Kiara you gotta watch out
here they come yeah here they come all
right let's see let's get a little more
let's get a little more abstract
name something you think you go does
every day
oh
what do you think your girl does every
day
come on somebody work with me here
please what are you trying to bring
um
yeah okay I can't I'm not allowed to I
think but but I think you understand
I'll write it in German no secret DMS by
the way
that would be impressed if you know it
in German
oh my God
this is German by the way
what's German
where is the German
I send it to Cali because I'm not
interested wait why did you send
something in German
why not all right let's use it it's both
all right I think
okay
there are two answers that are very
close to each other so I might give I
think I'll give it to you but okay okay
Kiara says
run
email
I mean yeah yeah
I mean yeah I mean it's true Ina says
sleep
I hope that he sleeps every day
creating dreams and gura says Sports
I'm gonna go ahead and give it to Kiara
and gura because it's pretty close
pretty close uh it's it's I I I'm just a
sport
I don't he does though every day he goes
jogging every morning I know it we know
it from holotalk yes
yup I watched whole tank I know thank
you you're welcome you're welcome all
right nice well done ladies now we're
gonna get even more abstract
um let's see oh
it is indeed uh German and you know what
it's German for it's for sport sport
surprising huh I believe it yeah
wow
foreign
name something that runs
something that runs yes
name something that runs other than feet
and here they come and all right there's
Chad all right yep
all right cool
did you Cali
I'll go with the first word that came up
in my mind but I doubt that anyone else
is going for it
I I wrote down the first thing that came
from I see no regrets as you should
that's a good way to play the game
because you don't doubt yourself too
much
you don't doubt yourself too much
all right I'm gonna take a risk What's
it gonna be give us
we'll see all right I am going with
German engineering
[Laughter]
so Kiara says
machine I'm a machine
gun right I mean I think
yeah probably unless it's free
it's a machine
okay it's fridge a machine
it works with everything
let's decide after everybody's answers
because we don't want everything to be
looking right okay okay think about it
dictionary says machine is an apparatus
using or applying mechanical Power and
having several parts each with definite
functioning together performing a
particular task Bridge is a machined
that is a fridge all right
all right you're walking on thin ice
Kiara but I'll allow it this time no
more generic answers like that all right
paper water runs water doesn't work
running yes and then gurus said fridge
too so I guess the three of you get a
point
except except for Ina
no everybody gets one
yeah yeah because if everybody it's all
four and no one gets one point exactly
yeah so
um
[Music]
Point all righty already has too many I
don't think machines
no the first time that you were on my
side first oil
here let me change this font because why
do my fives look weird
I don't why do some fonts just choose
not to have certain numbers I don't get
it all right
all right well nice job team now we've
got a couple more a couple more what do
you mean get ready we're getting
penalized
what what should I be penalized what do
you mean
Madden's run
run cow make it awake
I mean to me
ah Kiara Kiara Kiara you're on thin ice
my German brain I can't help it all
right I'm just gonna I'm gonna allow it
just this once but you gotta be careful
give you a little slap on the wrist you
know like a teacher puts the ruler down
like on your desk it slams it down and
then look on your head and stuff that's
me
I'm sweating yeah same and my um I'm
blind right now hold on
oh no
what blinded you sometimes if you
if you have contacts
they go to the back of your head like
they go to like wear your brain what
yeah no that is not good should I call
an ambulance Oh no I got it it came out
it's very normal
it's very normal that's not good for you
it's not normal yeah it is
sometimes he just gets lost I gotta help
him find his way
all right now the next word is
name a word that rhymes with honey and
don't be weird
I don't know how I could be weird about
that why oh whatever
honey it doesn't matter
okay I got mine already okay
are we done oh Sunny Rhymes Oh you mean
because of hi honey
Maybe
yup you got it yep
yep really scarred
let's see what girl I had to say
hi I'm honey honey
I sounded like an old woman there
we're starting I can't believe that you
don't know what I'm talking about Kiara
because it's something we've talked
about oh I think maybe now yes I get
all right oh this is an interesting one
up
all right here we go it means nobody
else baked it
maybe maybe it could be a wide me a
broad meaning right yeah
[Music]
true
all right Kiara says bunny
honey bunny oh that's cute that's a cute
name I want someone to call to call me
honey bunny
well honey you're funny
my day is made I feel like I can live
this old filthy world
oh I said chubby which I I think he's
kind of close yummy oh I should have
said tummy the tummy that's the second
word I had in mind you know says sunny
that's
the challenge of the game
you know
no pointers for anyone all right here's
another one how about this name
something you see outside that would
make you want to stay inside
and vaguely overlapping answers are okay
so you know
name something
word yeah
just no sentences
a very reasonable answer okay
you better hope not everybody says the
same one I I doubt everybody says it but
I hope somebody
oh my God
it smells like someone will have the
opposite
answer to mine oh
I love how all of gurr's answers are
just in all caps at me
like is there a reason is there a reason
she is the furthest away from you she's
trying to you know make it yeah all
right funny fridge understandable have a
good day Kiara says rain
yes I was also thinking son though but
rain is maybe even more you know you go
outside and you see rain and I think
most people say [\h__\h] that
understandable well not if you're
worried Uma says heat rays
well I was hoping you know it's a bit
it's a little general so maybe somebody
else has something heat related I said
you can't do that I said you can't do
the Happy Kid in general but okay all
right you know what I don't think I
think that that's pretty specific
personally yeah but now we have a
problem because son
right
I think I would count because in the end
they're saying it's too hot yeah yeah
um
count it I love how like Amanda are in
sync here and then Kiara and gura are in
sync with all these other answers
organisms
all you guys
like people or something right or like a
bear or like
something
yeah even a cat
are you saying that if you go outside
and you see your fellow gen mates you
would want to go back inside probably
I respect that
means
girl you won't see me outside because
I'm not outside so does it really count
she's a boy exactly what if you see okay
I'm knock on the window and say come
inside exactly
I'm in
you won't be outside in that Japanese
Heat Wave no
[Music]
man okay oh true well some of us wait
I'm not a living organism
but oh I get the point oh I'm not I'm
I'm a dead person
I mean you know what that makes my head
hurt let's move on to the next question
there's two more two more questions that
I have here well there's a lot more but
I'm only gonna pick two okay let's see
Bring It On Let's sink
good luck
name an event where it would be a bad
idea to laugh and this is like this is
like a thing like a thing that you go
out to or something like that like I'm
gonna give an example you guys now okay
okay actually never mind never mind I'm
not gonna give an example you can't use
just an event where it would be a bad
idea to laugh
a chat again some good examples
not that you should copy chat no I
already sent it
immediately I'm trying not to be very
general here I'm trying to think of
um
oh I have another idea but I can't I'm
staying
I mean you could if you want to but you
can also keep it I'll keep mine yes okay
how loud are we laughing here
I know so that people will see you doing
it
um
[Music]
all I can think of many now
um
somebody think they're broken nobody's
gonna think of mine but I sent it
anyways
um it doesn't want to sync up Mommy
wants to be special she wants to be
unique I just I can't think of anything
else
contrarian wait can I change something
else okay I don't think yeah you can
change it mine
that's not a bad idea but you know
preferably not to laugh in this
situation okay understandable
uh-huh very understandable all right um
gotcha
alrighty
now let's see what you guys said
Kiara said
funeral yes I said it before the spam
went for it she just went and went for
it says
Library
I mean okay that's a good one very good
one I mean is the library an event I
don't know I guess spam was Shannon
reading club like their book club or
something like that yeah I'd accept it
yeah sometimes when there's like a like
an event stuff it's okay
nice yeah in court maybe one of those
like funny you know funny judges and
stuff they make jokes funny
because if you're like you know giving a
testimony or something like I wish I
didn't do it I solemnly swear
challenge
[Applause]
do you even want to match
I thought that maybe
have fiancee brainwave and
are you thinking of cocky not Skye
what the oh the comedy show with the
with the dudes who are not supposed to
laugh for 24 or 48 hours
I was just thinking in general that do
not laugh challenge oh okay well um try
not to laugh yeah funny meme for my
YouTube like this stream ends if I laugh
um
says
funeral
yesterday
I think I I am I I need to propose to
you or something because like this is
too much oh my goodness
because I thought that's the one you
meant Kelly like you didn't want to
start typing yeah no come on man
come on that's not what I said
[Music]
ah
all right well there's one
there's one more question and this could
turn the tides of everything because
this next one is worth double points
[Music]
it's worth double points and this one is
a tribute to our JP Bros
a Japanese word used Often by Foreign
anime fans
oh wait what
a Japanese
yeah yeah like weeds girl like weebs
okay
you could have just said weebs all right
well I'm just trying to be nice okay
okay
is that a bad word
no I mean
a word I know that it'll trigger chat so
I didn't want to say it
but okay it's fine it doesn't matter
because now you're giving me your great
answers
oh well
[\h__\h] my life
what no one saw anything why not it
doesn't matter nobody saw anything
I saw it but I will not and it changed
my answer okay
[\h__\h] all right
it's okay accidents well it should
happen it doesn't matter
well wait what was it I wasn't looking
you shouldn't be looking just follow
your heart follow your heart listen to
your heart
all right you know what
all right let's all right here are the
answers
um
[Music]
uh American artists like I don't know
Gwen Stefani for example they probably
also use that word I like Japanese
Kawaii fashion oh Avril Lavigne Avril
Lavigne definitely used it mean no
psycho Arigato yeah yeah
you go
let's go
um
okay well Uma says daijobu
this is
yeah is that not too advanced
no no
I've got so many like people who just
start studying Japanese they will use
them
foreign
now I'm about to tear both of you Kiara
and gira's heads off because I think you
guys are cheating I think you guys are
colluding with each other
I think you're colluding how can you get
this many the same
we just we've been connecting
it's kind of sweet all right let's go
wow powerful
well even though you take a picture of
my Discord DMS and you'll see the kids
yeah on the list yes all right I don't
know it's fine it's fine I I I believe I
believe you I believe you
don't worry well communication happens
via line actually just kidding oh my God
[Music]
penalty penalty penalty all right here's
your trophy wait this is like a joke
Cali I was just kidding on Twitter that
I am you know the best English speaker
well I don't know but you got it so
congrats yeah
this is from a different stream so just
ignore it it says no let me see um
there you go
even though some questions did not have
English in them but it doesn't matter
it's fine Comics
I hereby a word the ego Jose trophy to
takanashi Kiara
thank you I would like to thank all all
of the uh people in the chat I would
like to thank my Sensei my trustworthy
Sensei who has been teaching me the ego
and I would like to ask uh my my gen
mates to also continue supporting my
journey to becoming more more ego Jose
and thank you for giving me all the sync
points
yeah
hey Google
thank you for that and all of this to
celebrate something really special
that's going on you guys can you guess
what it is
what would it be perhaps the a book a
special book
s
an open Eagle chosen whoa that's right
hello live english's first English
conversation textbook by YouTuber agency
hololive production wow
[Applause]
let's go English conversation textbook
and we all we all performed in it
together we have some long conversations
so yeah
physical copies that come with the CDs
with our you know and hear our voices
our conversations
does actually not come with the voices
so maybe get the uh the the physical one
yes that one actually has the voices if
you want to hear us of course it was a
lot of fun to record yeah I thought it
was I thought so too it was a good time
when when this was first announced I saw
like some English-speaking fans being
like yeah this is this was for Japanese
fans to study English I guess I'm
passing but I just want people to
understand this is basically a huge
collaboration voice pack okay only in
English and we're laughing like this
whole you know Adventure where we talk
to each other it's a really really long
voice pack the longest voice pack any of
us has recorded probably it's an e-book
yeah
yeah like a drama City exactly that's
basically drama City with text yeah true
true yeah perfect for everybody everyone
can enjoy
cute art too cute art yeah super
adorable artists so so cute the artists
that day I can't wait for you guys to
see it it's really cool
[Music]
I remember
oh and the TBR is super cute too you can
already kind of see it in the example
page but thanks adorable
um
we've of course already seen all of it
so we can just tell you how cute it is
but you have to take our word for it and
purchase
purchase it see for yourself okay how to
buy nna
where can I buy it Amazon or Amazon
yeah I'm pretty sure they still have
copies in America right do they oh I
mean there might be some Japanese like
bookstores that might carry it I'm not
100 sure though Amazon
yes but again
misunderstanding the fit the only the
physical version has the audio okay guys
um
remember remember
books on Amazon Japan I just add this to
my to my color and just buy it along
with them oh yeah
[Music]
accomplished
this was a fun collab thank you Kelly
for sending it up
everything no problem I tried to think
of some games that would be cool and fun
for us to play together but that others
would understand I guess a little bit JP
Bros if they knew the context so I think
it was interesting but very nice plus I
always love spending time with you guys
I want to play these games again yeah
that was a lot of fun yeah think of all
the prompts you could come up with I bet
you could come up with some really good
prompts Kiara I feel like you'd think of
some funny ones maybe we could also do
it as some off collab in the future and
put actual pieces of paper on their
foreheads
that's a good idea I like that
well everybody I hope you guys take care
of yourselves
um and keep enjoying English and Holo
live and all the things that make you
happy in life happy summer everybody
[Music]
well that's okay everybody I'm just
gonna tell you about it I'm just gonna
tell you to go over there and I'm gonna
put the link in there so you have to you
have to go
yeah you have to go hold on a sec I'm
gonna I'm it yes I'm in this episode of
Watson News
live news
let's freaking go Watson weekly here we
go I'm putting it in the in putting it
in a chat hold on it's going I already
posted it five times in the chat okay
well I can hand this so I'm gonna chat
camera
I am I'm I'm it I'm chatting spam chat
spam on the news
bye everybody
peace
[Music]
foreign