[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
sorry i cannot move
properly
i hope that's okay for you guys
a girl you stream with that setup oh my
god you sound like gooda
that's exactly what guru told me hey but
my setup was fine then what the hell
that's my travel setup
i don't know maybe it's the hotel wi-fi
um
having some issues
trying to make myself move
sorry about that
i don't like it but
i
i guess the urge to
talk to you guys was
stronger
now
maybe i'll figure it out until tomorrow
but
hello
hello yes so um
the reason i'm alone
is because
uh we kind of
the girls kind of separated for
a few days
for a while
until we meet up again
[Music]
with kelly
yeah
and then and then we'll be
probably doing enough collabs again
um
yeah but now it's
just me
yes
alone
and i wanted to
share some
things or some some of my notes because
my note
pad is filling up and
i need to let it out
oh yeah i guess fauna talked about it
yeah fana actually was there yesterday i
was waiting for her to say it
herself
oh she said you're working hard yes i
was very much working hard
[Music]
i think i'll start from the beginning
though i have so much to talk about
uh when i say the beginning i mean the
beginning
yeah i'm in america
in america
it's um
in theory it's not my first time
but
it's um
kind of i would say i would say it's my
first time i feel like the last time was
not not really you can't really count
the last time that was long long long
ago
and did you like the grand canyon did
you get bamboozled i actually did not go
there it was just a [\h__\h] post i have a
few more photos like that
the only real place i went to was
walmart
yeah um
how do you feel about time difference oh
it didn't really affect me at all i feel
like
um
uh yeah i'm like
used to it already um
it wasn't really a problem
no
walmart is the grand canyon
did you see glow canyon or gran i guess
grant i think that's why people say
grand canyon
why did you guys separate
because
do we have to stick together 24 7.
it was just kind of planned like that
because cali is still
not here
she comes later
let me first of all explain
how
i mean
regular kfp viewers
should know
but i've seen some people you know
complain about
why you're not even why are you not off
collabing even more and all that and
these people don't seem to understand
the reason why
where we got together in the first place
was not to off collab
but
because i needed to do something and so
let me explain
originally i was
um
looking for studios to record in in
europe
but
basically it was a long long long search
and eventually i had to give up on it
because
it was just not realistic uh the pricing
was not realistic for something that i
have to cover
um
[Music]
so then
yeah after asking like feels like every
single studio in europe
uh i gave up on it and
i guess ame offered
to
have me
use her
suit that she has been using before in
her streams
at her place that i will eventually get
as well
but just not in time for my birthday
concert
and
i really really really really am so
in my mind set on having a 3d birthday
and i just don't want to give up on that
um
however that suit
uh i don't know if you've seen like alma
play around with it like for normal
streams it's fun and nice
and to me already impressive
but i tested it out
and
recently
at ama's place and it's just not good
enough for like you know free
concert
um that's
yeah for that it's just not good enough
not not the best
capturing
unfortunately because it just works
differently but then
i you know i was like whatever like at
that point i i guess i kind of like
underestimated how bad the suit was
for that purpose but i just really
wanted it to be 3d and and
it felt like i had no other choice so
i was like whatever it's better than
nothing
so
i said okay i'm going to ahmed
and then
i guess uh
[Music]
inna caught wind of it i don't remember
like how maybe we told her
um but eno caught wind of it and then
ina was like hey you know what i i kind
of wanted to like
go
travel anyway
so
could i join
yeah
and then yeah we were like hey why the
hell not
would be nice to meet you now
so then yeah
you know
uh decided to join and then
uh
yeah for a while we were just planning
to do it
with a three
and
a
little bit later
gonna caught wind of it
and then and then she was also like hey
hey i want to join too
so
it's like more and more
everybody wanted to join in and it just
you know
became turned into something bigger and
because it turned into something bigger
that's why we actually also didn't
um sleep over at ama's place we booked
a separate place
so because like we would have been too
many people you know
yeah
um but for the recording
during the day we went to amma's place
so anyway
the dates kind of like
of me recording
turned out to be so close to
when cali is coming
to
the land of the free
so
when i heard that i was like
i guess i could stay longer
because the others were also like hey
let's stay longer
and hang out with kelly
and i was like okay i guess i can extend
my stay a little bit
yeah so
[Music]
uh
that is how it all
ended up lining up
the original reason was just because
i wanted to record something in 3d
and
yeah i was going to go to ahmed and then
people the other girls they kept on you
know
wanting to join so
yeah
um that's why i want to say to everybody
who's complaining that we didn't off
collab more
there will be more but you guys are not
not everybody but the ones who are
complaining are freaking spoiled
we had work to do
and
the the priority was getting my [\h__\h]
done because we had
very very very um
how to say
a lot of time pressure okay
let me drink water
yeah a lot of time pressure and a lot of
problems
um
i originally
uh planned three days
of actual recording
spreading it out you know because it
takes time
uh
but it was good that i planned it for
three days because we ended up only
effectively recording
on one day which was yesterday
which was
quite the grind incredible
uh incredibly exhausting
i don't understand how this is even
possible to do live
because i mean i guess if there's like a
if it's like a properly
set up studio by professionals
with professional people
uh
controlling it
[\h__\h] alleys hotel noises are noisy
then uh yeah then it might be easier but
you know
uh and i don't want to like even like
criticize or complain or anything
because
uh it was like
mostly ame and ina setting up everything
and them being able to do that
to this
point
is absolutely incredible
amazing now
wow
there the amount of brain work that it
took
the amount of brain cells and effort
that it took
holy [\h__\h]
no
but it's
supposedly done
i can't
do
any more than this
um
it's out of my hands now
and i'm just
hoping
for the best
yeah
all i can do is
hope now
yeah um
although
i still have some some things to
do but
the basic
capturing has been
done
and
i hope for the best um i i worked so
hard like no joke
like i learned
you will see
how many it is
but i learned so many choreographies
in
a week
when i was
sick
during it
um
not only did i learn choreos but i also
recorded
all kinds of [\h__\h] during that one week
and still try to stream
on the side
so it was so much work
and uh
yeah and
then the problem was
you know having to stuff all of that
into one day
[Music]
i was dying it was so hot
i was sweating i was drenched
and my feet hurt so much partially
because the floor was not made for
dancing
so
now it's really really tough conditions
um
i'm really exhausting you know i don't i
don't have the stamina anymore either so
partially that's the reason too that i
was so exhausted but no um
it was tough
um
but
what i've seen so far it looks good
so i have
i have hopes
yeah
are you telling me you're getting old
kiana i'm not telling you i'm getting
old i'm telling you i am old
uh
good job powering fruit thank you very
much
thank you thanks for the hard work thank
you i
i'm worried though and there might be
we'll try like there might be like some
some
how to say like twitching in my limbs
here and there but i'm hoping to kind of
save it with
angles whatsoever
uh
yeah so
don't look too close
just ignore if you see some stuff please
just ignore it and
act as if you haven't seen it
yeah some sometimes it was really
difficult but
we tried our best to optimize
everything or like i'm it am i mostly
try to optimize everything
i am
in eternal depth to amit
she's really really really amazing so
impressive
yeah what would like we basically built
a mocap studio
with
the brains of
a couple of
normal girls
although i mean ame has like good a good
technical
understanding in general right so
yeah that's i guess a good base but
still like that was a new territory
anyway and she had to look up a million
things and and
trial and error a million things
troubleshoot a million things
yeah it was all not that easy
so
um
i'm really curious i have
no idea what's it going to look like
i mean i have a rough i i i i have hopes
of what it would look like
but i don't want to get my hopes too
high
um
i'm worried i'm worried but it'll be
good
um
now let me tell you let me start my
tangents shall we
oh also one more one more thing i wanted
to say
kind of annoyed me
uh
this is just a handful of people but i'm
gonna say it anyway
um
[Music]
complaints about
not announcing
of collabs
beforehand
i must completely throw into the trash
can do not understand
something called
security
if
we would have like announced this
beforehand
there you know people would try to like
you know try to find our flights
and our location
and stuff like that
and i mean i might be
not so not as
scared about stuff like that as others
but it's important also to respect uh
the other
girls wishes okay
and
some people underestimate
or don't understand
how much
the security is important
for us
and how necessary it is
um
also
like you know the first
the the other days like the the super
smash brothers for example that one at
least we tried to announce
uh as early as possible as we knew that
we're doing it that we have time for it
um but the first one the pop-tart one
was spontaneous because
well
it was also supposed to be a surprise
that something's happening
yeah
it was supposed to be a surprise
that's just how surprises work you know
it's one reason it was a surprise the
other reason it's necessary for our
safety
so yeah i know most of you guys
understand it um but i saw a lot of
people like angry that they missed it
and they had to watch the vlog
excuse us
we couldn't do it any earlier
we're traveling and
and uh you know setting up [\h__\h] and
doing private [\h__\h]
buying [\h__\h]
settling in
checking in
you know so spoiled really so freaking
spoiled guys
oh my god i had to watch the vod
so what
normally i stream from a european time
zone and other people have to watch the
vlog
now well how the tables turn
come on
it will be like that sometimes okay
yeah
anyway
yeah excuse me for streaming at 10 am at
2 am for some time zone
2 a.m it's a good time to be awake
other people you know when i stream in
in europe you know my my korean or
japanese fans
they
watch me at 4 5 am
and they're not complaining
so spoiled
spoiled for the children
unbelievable
okay so let me give you some tangent i
want to tell you
did i i don't know if like roughly
mention it
in the pop-tart stream maybe not
probably not did i
about my arrival
at the airport
did i say something because that was
that freaked me out
oh man
so
okay i didn't okay then that's good so i
i'm i'm trying to speak carefully i
don't want to say anything
dangerous but okay so i arrived
and
i go to
passport control
and
um
so i said hello
this is me
i would like to enter america
and
guy asks
what
my purpose is
of coming to america
so i say
well
meeting friends
i guess
and then he asks what kind of friends
and i say
uh
[Music]
work colleagues
and then
that's where he starts digging deeper
and deeper and i get more nervous and
nervous
yes uh he asks okay what what work
and i say um
i'm a voice actress
and he says oh like what for anime
and i said uh
[Music]
interesting that you say that i guess it
could be something like that
[Music]
i didn't want to straight out say like
me tubing because
that's
like first of all you probably wouldn't
understand second of all
do i really have to say it so detailed
and also i was embarrassed
so anyway
then i confirm i guess it's something
like anime
and then
uh
he's like oh
what are you like are you like a
streamer and then i'm like what
yes a question mike
and then he says
oh twitch is it twitch and i'm like by
the way the whole time he says it all
with a serious face
no smiles whatsoever
and yeah
he asked if it's twitch and i said no
it's some
youtube
no he didn't see any equipment no no i
don't know how he he seemed to not
really understand because then then he
says like well he asks more like what
what is that like what what is that
anime voice acting thingy so he gets me
to say
it's called v tubing and then he was
like what's that
like he seemed to not know but maybe he
was acting i don't know because he's
they got really fast to assuming the
whole thing like anime
and streaming but then he asks if it's
twitch
so
maybe he thought like i don't know i was
some one of the youtubers on twitch i
don't know but but yeah then he's like
oh what's what's be too big and i say
like he didn't even hear it clearly so i
say it again v2 being but i'm saying
like i tried to say quietly because
there's someone right next to me doing
passport control as well and
and then he's like okay so what's the
youtube channel and i'm like really
intimidated at this point like i don't
wanna lie
i don't wanna make up something i feel
like
here i cannot i'm not allowed to lie i
have a duty to be honest i think
so i i didn't see the option or
i don't think i have a choice i don't
think i was
allowed to say i don't want to tell you
even with an nda or so
i don't think i'm it's a it's an it's a
an officer
i think i have to say
so
i'm really [\h__\h] nervous at this point
i'm i'm like
my youtube channel uh can i um can i
write it down
because i don't want to say it out loud
because you know the person next
standing right next to me
it's a stranger
so
he's like yeah yeah okay
so write it down on my
phone and show it to him
and he types it into
his
browser thing whatever i didn't yeah he
looked it up and he looks at it for a
second and he's like oh okay
so are you
are you gonna
like you know it keeps on taking and
thinking are you gonna be streaming and
i'm like yeah i guess probably perhaps
and then
he asked like how do you get paid and i
say well i'm with this japanese company
and they pay me
and he i think he was trying to figure
out if i was getting paid directly in
america
if it would be considered work you know
why you tell him because he made me
[\h__\h] nervous and i don't think i want
i don't i don't want to lie i'm an
honest person
but then you know i explained to him
that youtube
pays
the company like they sent the money to
the company and the company sends it to
me so it's not directly
and then he's like ah okay okay
cool
um
yeah
uh
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah then he asks
oh yeah
he did oh my god yeah he didn't ask that
holy [\h__\h] i'm looking at my notes
he asked like what would i do like uh
what what am i what else am i doing on
in my trip
if i'm going to ax
huh
and i'm like no
i'm not going to ax
[Laughter]
no no no i'm leaving before that
yeah um
that was funny
and then the
now this freaked me out too
you can tell them in the air next time
they leave you can't do anything but i'm
worried that you know like
you think some susan won't let me into
the country
and also i mean he hasn't i i'm assuming
that these officers have a duty as well
to shut their damn mouths
about what they
hear what information they get
when working right i'm pretty sure they
have something like that
like the like doctors
i would assume so confidentiality yeah
confident obviously they have to
um
yeah so
um and then
at some point he seems satisfied
with
uh he seemed to feel like
i am safe
a safe person
so he um
says all right you can go
and when i
wha the moment i'm about to walk away
he's like your secret's safe with me
because like he noticed that this whole
thing
is like you know
it's
not something i tell everybody
and i'm like oh oh
thank you
and then
while i'm walking further away
the lady from the passport control desk
right next to him yells out
laughingly
jokingly ha ha but i heard everything
[Music]
and i'm like
oh no
and walk away
uh
no they were all they were nice and all
um
but i don't know what to think about all
of that
what these these tsa officers what does
tsa mean
something security
what
they were just yeah yeah i think they
were having fun teasing me like at the
end yeah yeah the ending was definitely
just teasing
ah
transportation security agency
oh man after that i was walking away and
freaking out like what the hell was that
conversation just now and i did tell i
did tell genma and she was like ah okay
interesting
she wasn't mad or anything it was all
good it's all okay
it was just um
so freaking awkward you know i was
really intimidated
but i guess it's good you guys take it
very seriously with
security
in america
yeah
very very deep digging
no no no it's not customs it's where you
give them your passport control and then
there's that they decide whether or not
you're
allowed in um
no that's not customs
customs is like where you go through
with your suitcase
uh
at least like in other countries that's
how it was you go through with your
suitcase and if you're getting picked to
check
in inside then you're getting picked
some places i guess in japan for example
they always check your suitcase in tokyo
yeah it's a different thing
i think that normal is whatever it
doesn't matter in the answer they're i'm
pretty sure they have something like
confidentiality
protocol
or something like that i would hope so
yeah
oh yeah wait no
oh wait it's loading
my bag no i forgot one one important
detail
um
you know when they were teasing me at
the end and joking
jokingly saying um
[Music]
your secret's safe with me you know what
i said
as a joke because i'm funny i said
subscribe
and he was like nah
not gonna do that
so hey he's not gonna subscribe he's i
don't think i don't think he cares about
any of that information
i just wanted to be like a cringy
youtuber i was trying to clear up this
really embarrassing
situation
[Laughter]
uh let's just try and
you know
hit that bell subscribe exactly and want
to just make a joke
hit that
bell notification bell leave a comment
subscribe
ah
you can make super chatter oh that would
be funny
you can't subscribe because he's already
subscribed no come on
comment for the algorithm
here's your throat with peace sign
wasn't saying it now my hands are full
unfortunately
yeah so that's uh that was a great start
to
that
put you for all that travel didn't even
bother subscribing right
so disrespectful
i would have imagined i would have hoped
for him to at least subscribe after
after asking me as if i was in a quiz
show
oh man
i was so nervous
i always get so nervous in these kind of
situations
even though i didn't do anything wrong
like
whenever i walk by a police station
i also get really nervous
even even though i'm not doing anything
i'm just walking by
right
not the only one
this whole story worries me it worries
me too
it worries me very much too
well wow
what else what else oh and then you know
after
i left that
um
after i went like outside i went to it
went to the
airport idle meeting room
and
i was gonna do my makeup you know i was
opening my suitcase you know and then um
a middle-aged american lady she sounded
american
walked in
and
she said
you're wearing i like your outfit or
something like that i like your outfit
that you're wearing
so nicely she said that so nicely and
i'm like
thank you
and at that moment i was like
wow
these people this is the first person
the first person basically after that
officer that i talked to in america
and she's nice
she's nice
for no reason
and i wasn't even dressed that cutely
i was wearing
airport fashion
which means
low effort
but
in my in my world airport fashion is low
effort but still
cute enough
to
not look
disgusting when i meet
the girls
but low effort and comfy but still cute
because i won in the first the first
meeting when i'm meeting the girls i
want to look cute
yeah but i wasn't even dressed that cute
no but that was
nice and then i met gooda later
in the
accommodation
and
she also said that to me
she also said oh i like your outfit i'm
like what
this is just my traveling outfit thank
you
nani oh no
i was already shut up get out of here
what about the confidentiality
[\h__\h] that you
you signed hopefully
um
i will report you to your supervisor
all right so
um
yeah the first one i met was gula
and then
ina joined a bit later that's how uh
white oh
that's that's
what am i saying
second one was inna and then we collabed
but yeah i i the moment i met them i ran
at them both of them
gave them a huge hug and you know when i
give when i give these girls hooks i i
go like
swoosh i sway from side to side really
aggressively you know what i mean can
you imagine like a run at them like
swoosh and then give them a strong big
hug and then i sway from side to side i
make them sway with me
and uh
and they usually i squeal
so
you shake them no i swayed them
like a baby
yeah i have a good technique
i did that with all of them
except for um i was like so excited that
i had to do it twice
twice in a row
nervous job nervous
yeah i was i was nervous yeah
now i i kept on jumping around
after seeing gouda
i was like oh my god oh my god you're so
cute jump jump jump jump oh my god oh my
god oh my god and i
ran around in the room
i was like so
bouncy and nervous and wow excited
yeah and then actually it was um
right before
and when i arrived at the commendation
it was right before
gura
was going to stream
so
i was
actually
chilling
next to
the whole time but i didn't want to
disturb so i didn't say anything but i
was trying my best to stay quiet
i was watching her
and obviously
making her feel awkward
probably
uh yeah at the
that stream where she um showed the the
concert
thingy
that was i was sitting next to her hmm
no no i was not staring at her at all i
i felt like that would make her more
nervous so i just stared at the screen
but then the during the pop-tart stream
they were staring at me so that made me
nervous
i it was not payback or anything i i
didn't look at gooda at all
during her stream i was just looking at
the screen and looking at the comments
to hold up i didn't even have audio
i was just imagining i was watching the
whole concert muted
yeah i'm in a coma hello
it was very embarrassing to um be looked
at during the pop-tart thing oh yeah
yeah yeah so um
one more thing
one more thing from from
airplane
you guys probably
don't really relate to this but i was
really excited about it
just a random
small thing so one night when i was in
the plane when i like sat down
i
soon after i heard like a
small
meow
behind me
and i was like
what was that
was this was someone playing something
from their speakers on their phone
and then the whole flight over i didn't
hear that anymore
until the very end when we landed
i heard an hour meow and instantly
instantly i turn around i'm like oh
cause like my my things activate my
neurons activate
and i look around really excitedly
hopefully like what was that
and actually
the
uh the couple sitting right behind me
the whole
flight
through
we were traveling with a cat
so they're like oh yeah yeah we have a
cat
and i'm like oh my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god so cute what that
so i actually started a conversation i
was like oh what you're traveling long
distance if you can't like i could never
do that with mine i was i'm so worried
about mine yeah but yours was so quiet
and didn't meow at all only in the
beginning and in the end once oh my god
so brave how old is your cat and all
that i
made a conversation and then they opened
the the thing
the bag and showed me
and it was a cute orange
orange cat like garfield
yeah
very cute must be very used to the
carrier i thought so too but it didn't
like i asked if like they do it all the
time but
didn't seem so
i guess it wasn't the first time at
least
so cute
yeah
so brave but it was more of an older cat
i guess they're more chill about it
seems weird sometimes you have to when
you move some people move from
continents to continent and you don't
want to leave your pets behind i
wouldn't want to leave my pets behind
i'm just looking at some
just looking at some
messages
yeah
i wouldn't want to leave them either
yeah me neither i mean i had to because
i didn't also didn't want to risk them
being
hurt or die because sometimes
cats or pets i guess
die when putting when put into a lot of
stress and
put through a long distance flight like
that
so yeah
yeah
oh by the way for good as
a concert thingy
i performed
i guess
together with her i mean i didn't
perform you know i don't wanna
i i don't i don't think i
want or need to
act as if that was me that wasn't me
didn't i couldn't record anything
uh
in 3d at home unless it was vr chat so i
just want to make that clear
it wasn't me okay but it still turned
out super super super cute and fun i
loved the dancing yeah
i got the song choice i was so happy
about it
uh because
it's an artist from hello project
kusumi koharu i think a lot of people
know it like for the memes
uh
nika
but uh the original is by like from an
idol from hello project which was my
favorite idol agency
um so i was really surprised like i was
like hey you want to do this song and
i'm like um hell yeah excuse me i can
already sing it i don't even need to
practice this
yeah
so that was
a great song choice
the thing is she sent me her
like
recording data song recording data
um to like sing along and i was
listening to it i'm like girl you're
missing the important line of bololo
so i was like maybe she'll record it
afterwards so just in case
i recorded it
and then
turned out turns out she didn't record
it
and they left mine in and then i was the
only one saying it
wasn't your choice to be small yeah so
the reason i
i know it fit really well but i didn't
do it for
you know the fact that it fits well with
the song i did it because i didn't want
to
um
you know
show
my
3d
too much in or at all
in other places
than my channel before i was able to
properly
reveal it for like on my own channel by
myself
because besides link your wish
i didn't really have had to have a
chance yet to
you know make full use of my 3d
and
yeah just for the sake of i guess like
exclusive exclusivity exclusivity
that's a word
and
i just didn't
feel like
that was the place
but then i saw that all the others were
like full 3d and like full like full
size so that i was like kind of low-key
regretting my choice
um
because they looked so cute and so
pretty
but yeah then i guess it really fit the
song really well too because it was
dorky yeah
yeah yeah
yeah
yeah and i uh i also don't understand
like
some people's disappointment in that
because like
if you
like if you look at the dance moves that
small kibaba did
they were really good but i don't think
it was like i think
that just doesn't
that's not how i move
i'm sorry but if you watched my vr
stream so far i feel like you you won't
know that's not really that doesn't
really look like me so why did you get
deceived why did you get bamboozled huh
not my problem
but it was hecking cute
i love it still it was so funny
love those
those step step step step
leg up like i don't know what you call
that
that move
it was really funny
i'm glad we did that
no
[Music]
no no no no
i'm not saying it was like bad i just
feel like my personality
uh
would make me move
a bit differently if i did the same
dance
no it's not it wasn't an idol step
different people different movements
yeah
um
and even even if it wasn't me then i
feel like still
like there's no need to
complain about it like
it's better than getting nothing at all
right seeing
cute kiwami move cutely
is
a blessing that should be appreciated
oh yeah yeah
and soon enough don't worry
i worked my ass off
to record
my own proper
3d concert
with my own movements
i worked so hard guys
and i have really sore muscles from it
um
but yeah it will be
i guess i i guess i'll say it maybe i
should have done a proper announcement
to hype it up maybe i will still do it
but yes
on the 6th of july
on my birthday
i will be doing
a 3d concert yeah it's pre-recorded
because well
it kind of has to be
for technical
reasons literally impossible
with the setup that we had looking at
all the technical difficulties that we
had even pre-recording it
not really impossible to do it live
but yeah uh you can imagine you traveled
back in time and were watching
while i was recording it then it could
be live you could imagine it was live
you should you should
doesn't change the fact how hard i
worked on it and how hard am i also
worked on it
doesn't change anything
i wanna dance yeah
yeah yeah
i'm really glad i can finally show off
the dancing
um
i feel like i can do even better with a
bit more practice time and
when i'm not having
a heat stroke and
when
the floor is made for dancing
then
i feel like i can do even better i just
want to say
that
don't be disappointed i hope you guys
are not going to be disappointed i'm
already so worried
oh he's so worried
[Music]
thank you
how do you know how do you know you will
love it
how do you know
but it's good that you guys are so
positive
i mean although it puts a lot of
pressure on me
yeah well as i said it's out of my hands
now so
um
so yeah then we did a pop-tart stream
and then we slept soon after because it
was already late and
um had to wake up early
so
so that was monday
and then
the thing is
now he starts
the pro the story of the problems the
endless problems
the equipment that we wanted to use was
supposed to arrive on monday and then it
didn't arrive so
um
we were hoping for it to arrive
on tuesday as early as possible so we
can already like set it up and then
start recording if everything goes well
so
um
on tuesday
uh
me
ahmed
we're waiting the whole time
hours and hours for that for that
equipment but it just didn't come
it took ages
and then at some point really late in
the day it finally came and throughout
the whole time i was you know trying to
make use of the time by by practicing
yeah so i was practicing while waiting
and chilling with the girls
waiting waiting waiting
and finally it arrives but guess what
of course something important was
missing
of course
i think i think we started to already
like uh
set it up
yeah yeah we did we did we started to
set it up and then we noticed
something's missing
we can't
do it without that
so basically i lost the whole complete
day
to record
and uh
yeah
it was already late so anyway i think we
streamed we streamed on that day right
we did uh
super smash brothers
um
and then i was like okay well two days
two days is still enough to record all
of that
two days is more than enough i can do it
so let's hope that tomorrow
we have all the equipment necessary and
everything works fine
so
the next day
we set out to get
the equipment that was missing
which was
a lot of equipment actually so it took
us quite a while we had to go to
different stores
um
and then finally
we had it all together finally thank god
thank god it was at least something that
you can
[Music]
normally buy at least
yeah
so we brought it
over and we set it up
and you would think you would you would
hope that everything would work right
away but no
ame and ina
where the whole
day
oh like 10 hours
without a break and me i was like taking
part in it like i was you know always
the test object it was like let's try
this let's try this oh i guess that's
not working
recalibrate etc
um
so yeah i couldn't help much because
that was a test object
but the idea is that they were like
without a break for 10 hours
constantly using their brain power
when for example inna was already like
super tired
and yeah am i also didn't get much sleep
because i guess she
was also
when we were gone like
working on stuff trying to set up stuff
and all that
trying to get stuff to work
yeah
yeah uh and then it was really really
really late
and
at some point
you know
we got it to work somehow like we
recorded something but that ended up
being um
useless
data
uh it was not optimized yet the whole
setup
i think that i tweeted out about you
know how that i was able to get
something done but i wasn't really yeah
so you know i thought oh at least two
songs hell yeah i got two songs done i
guess i just have to do
no i don't want to spoil how many songs
it is i guess i just have to do so and
so many songs tomorrow i guess that's
not ideal but i can manage but then yeah
it turns out it wasn't usable
um it was too scuffed
and yeah but we were all so [\h__\h]
tired holy [\h__\h]
next day day number three
i was
i i one thing i have to say though
throughout all of this
i met ina
where
like the whole time so
what's the right word
they weren't getting getting frustrated
or anything
maybe because they didn't have quite the
same feeling of pressure and stress that
i had you know because i came all the
way from europe
um and i only have this one chance to
record it
this one opportunity
this one trip
these few days
and
if it doesn't work out then it was all
like
i mean i met the girls yeah but like the
trip in itself the original reason was
wasted and i wouldn't be able to do my
concert and i would have been like i was
after
after like
let's say eight hours or seven hours of
testing
i was really getting worried that
it wasn't gonna work out and
it wasn't gonna happen
[Music]
ever
and i was getting really worried it was
partially not being tired and being
hungry but also the stress and the
pressure but while i was starting to get
like
really really worried and
um sad
the others were still like super super
motivated
okay no maybe not super motivated but
they were like
still
so committed to it and they wouldn't
stop
they would just not stop
amazing
i'm so so so so so thankful for their
hard work
i mean like we're not professionals you
know in that field we have no prior
experience with that
and
yet
we ended up on the third
and last
possible day to record
we ended up
figuring it out relatively early
partially because i think over the night
ami was still doing some testing
yeah so
um
i arrived on the third day and i was
like if it doesn't happen today then
it's not gonna happen
it has to work today
oh and by the way that's why on um on
wednesday
we didn't end up streaming i'm sorry we
actually wanted we had ideas
but um
[Music]
we couldn't
couldn't stream because you know
priorities we had to get that [\h__\h] done
and we were hoping until the last hour
that it would work and we could at least
record some songs we did but they were
used less in the end so
sorry my throat is getting dry
air is so dry here man
i feel like
only in the room though probably
um
yeah yeah yeah you know i i like to
do love collabs when we meet because i
feel like it's a special
opportunity and leaving something like a
stream behind
would be something nice to look back on
um
so i usually like i i push i push for it
and let's stream every day
and even if it's just for an hour let's
stream so that the viewers get something
and we have something to look back upon
you know make memories it's fun it's
special
um but in this case with i had we had to
prioritize our work
so anyway on the third day
um we actually finally got everything to
work relatively early
thank god but i had to do everything
every song
and ideally i wanted to do double takes
because
um
even though it was good enough to
have some good recordings there were
there would still be like every now and
then some scuffness some
some limbs like twitching and all that
that
would be hard to use
um so i wanted to do double takes but
in that one day it was impossible
i
mostly just had yeah one take for
everything and it still took 10 hours
uh and in between i
did like mc parts and there will be some
like
collins and stuff
so i had to record that too
all all in one day
[Music]
10 hours of endless dancing i was so
[\h__\h] dead
[Music]
yeah oh on the on the
last day
as you may have heard fauna joined us
um
it was like you know
you may have been hearing that i'm not
mentioning certain names on certain days
it's because
you know for example on the last day
inna wasn't there
um
[Music]
she left
early
and yeah on the second
day or third day depending on how you
see it
um good ah was doing other stuff too
[Music]
so it's not like they didn't help
because they were lazy or whatever they
just weren't there
um uh but yeah the last day uh it was
ame gura fona and me
and yeah the the fact that fawna would
come was also kind of like unexpected to
me
uh and i was like
she was really cute then i was nervous
but when i saw her i was like [\h__\h] sorry
i didn't do my makeup um
i'm usually
cuter i wish i would have done my makeup
now i'm sorry fauna
but she was so sweet and she seemed very
excited to
um meet
me yeah she said that like no i i warned
her i said you know it's gonna be kind
of boring for you i think because
we're gonna just be recording all day so
there's not much to do for you i think
but she was like yeah it's okay and just
you know
[Music]
oh this is the only chance to meet you
who knows you know when when that chance
would come again
[Laughter]
this is my it's my invitation to follow
oh
no
no it's only funny not happy
to meet you
[Music]
she was really sweet and yeah we had
some good talks
good talks good talks um
it was great yeah i'm really happy she
was there um
because uh
i it's it's true i don't know when else
when whenever the next chance would be i
don't see it happening anytime soon
even
i don't know even within the year i
don't see
me
coming to
america again
so yeah
but who knows i mean maybe i will maybe
plans change but still
gotta take the opportunity
yeah
yeah was happy happy happy and then she
ended up you know helping a little bit
too
uh but good good also helped a lot and
but there was actually not that much
need to help on that day because things
went more or less
somewhat smoothly
but still like it takes a lot of time
anyway because like in between we had to
recalibrate a lot
sometimes some songs i would like
um yeah need a lot of calibrating in
between and then there were some
problems because certain moves just
weren't captured
well enough because the moves were too
fast or the arms were like i don't know
covering parts or whatever
it was cussing but i felt like we
learned a lot
and
yeah ame was also really really inspired
to improve the whole setup for future
uses
and
yeah
it was really really really really
insightful
insightful is that a word
yeah
really great quality
in
theory
i mean the
the
um aggressive rough dancing that i was
doing
ruined some of it because of the scuff
that it creates
but just normal movements
looked so beautiful and smooth
that it really looks like
you know
the stuff that the japanese girls record
in the japanese studio if not partially
in some way
even better
but no no now i'm just gonna get your
hopes up which i don't want to do
but
i have to admit it looked
pretty damn good like it looked really
smooth
in some ways it depends on like where i
would look at it depending on which
program but
um
we will see we will see
we will see
yeah my choreos are really complicated
so
i'm worried about that but yeah
we'll see i'm looking forward to it i
hope you guys will look forward to it
two and now uh my fruit is getting
really dry i still have some stories and
all that but
i think uh i think um
i'll keep that for another time
i don't know if i'll stream the next few
days
if i get this
um coma
fixed if i get out of my coma i might
stream again
i still uh didn't eat dinner so i'm
gonna do that now
and yeah
i'm gonna do some
sightseeing i think
in next couple days with
uh other
uh people that are not a
whole life
or another person
yes
kind of make use of
the
chance
to meet the one person that i know
yeah and then we'll reunite with the
others
again
no
i will not say who but no it's not
that person
unfortunately
maybe another time
no no no no no no no
inna did you get some sleep
please tell me you did
oh man i was so worried about inna
you know on that day where
we were like setting up everything for
10 hours and it just wouldn't work
you know ina actually she said she
wanted to get some work done she was she
was planning to get work done because we
were expecting for it to you know work
on the second day
um
however
you know helped the whole day
and didn't get any work done and
therefore also didn't get any sleep and
i really really really really appreciate
that you know that she sacrificed
her whole day
precious time and her precious sleep
for me
thank you so much aina i won't forget it
i won't forget it
i think she already fell asleep while
writing that comment
oh there she is
was happier everything worked in the end
yeah
i mean
whatever we recorded on that day wasn't
usable but the next day was really
smooth
yeah next thing i wasn't
quite there but uh
you know i will have you know
things were pretty smooth on the next
day thanks to your hard work on the
previous day
[Music]
a big big big thank you soon
i wouldn't have
been able to do it ami said so too that
you know having inna there was so so so
so helpful
really excited for the result
of our hard work it's something that we
created together we can say that i think
um i gotta put your name in the credits
it was a big effort from all of us
so with that being said
i think it's time for me to leave and
eat and then sleep
[Music]
thanks guys for listening and for
watching and
yeah see you guys soon keep an eye out
for
uh off collab streams on other girls
channels next week i don't know if one
will be on my channel i don't know
there'll definitely be one on kelly's
channel at least one
yeah thank you thank you thank you for
listening thank you soon
thank you
yeah
have a nice evening day night whatever
and uh
yeah
i'm gonna try to
see some more
of america
this weekend
more than i did last time i was in
america because i didn't really see
anything
and then i'll make some memories to
report back to you guys all right
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
thank you thank you
good night
[Music]
oh my god i'm so hungry oh god
you