foreign
[Music]
key
and
um
what no it's not there's a reason I went
for kikiriki and not cock-a-doodle-doo
Kitty key the German version it it's
kind of yeah I I'm spelling it a little
bit differently but it's definitely how
we would say it in German oh I see I see
you know that roosters tilt their heads
to block their ears to stop them from
going Deaf from themselves because it
was so loud yeah did you know you know
that did you know that
thanks for the lore
it's kind of crazy it's really crazy
actually
we're back we are we're Baldur's back
baby
[Music]
's gate yeah
chat is the sound okay maybe the other
chats can answer it too also
I don't know why that is oh really uh
maybe it's because I'm like constantly
lighting up
lower my or high because like my wrapper
hat
wait I'm lining up for you
I mean you're permanently lit up
actually yeah oh yeah you're permanently
not let me turn up here oh that's weird
voice
what what about
there we go this should be good
according to the Discord my buzzing is
like so loud I'm so sorry if it bothers
anyone not that that is the music's also
in the background from the
[Music]
it doesn't go dark it just completely is
not there
no it's there but it just it's just
permanently dark oh okay I'll give you a
bright PNG yeah give me a bright PNG
yeah yeah let's see how about how about
these it's from my thumbnails
I'm the Yellow Ostrich streamer
tanakisha Curry
yellow I want this okay context I got a
super chat a while ago that was like
probably just a parody but they called
me a yellow ostrich streamer tanaki
shakaria and it just cracks me up all
the time
yeah yeah
honestly I thought that was hilarious uh
it was great that's my favorite thing
where's Cali's clothes don't worry about
it
I finally understand Cali thanks to me
using Carla in my private playthrough
that you your thing your class or
whatever is like stronger when you're
naked
yeah that's right that's the thing well
see here's the thing is that like this I
mean clothing I could at least put on
clothing that isn't armor and that would
be fine I just think it's easier to cut
to the chase than just be naked I
understand show your strength assert
your dominance yep
Marion
[Music]
I've changed my mind and we're breaking
up
it's just a vampire
but he likes you
the nipples
I'm popping off but maybe answers
he's so naked he is naked
so naked naked little guy
oh we just had this conversation he just
confessed to me he's a vampire and I'm
very confused I thought we already went
through that and I will not stand the uh
evil leave no you can't banish him
can we permanently remove him from the
party not just kidding I'm right why do
you hate a Starion
I don't hate I just pretend
just straight back in the city it's all
rather tedious he's a magistrate oh my
God just straight I don't know I'm
waiting for what that means
neither do I actually that sounds like
adult speak yeah right
big words that adults use we can
convince
all right cool I get it moonrise Towers
uh well I don't need you in my party oh
game quiet okay
doesn't look right to you guys
um anyway
so today's uh leader we have decided
generally will be people but maybe if we
go to the tea house then the leader
there will be Kelly because she's the
only one who hasn't really seen the tea
house yet and it would be nice to have
some innocent mind going through it I'm
far behind
oh we need to get the lady that's the
first thing we should do yes
yes yes
let's yeah I want to do that let's leave
the camp I love Carla
best oh best wife Carla oh where are we
yeah I meet you guys at blighted Village
okay
oh yeah
um what's the quickest what's the
quickest teleportation Point beep boom
bladed Village oh yeah I'm I'm so sorry
that was so silly of me
uh yeah but still I I can't go to this
area anymore so uh I see yeah oh you can
no return yeah I'm past that point is it
is it like like every act you can after
after a part in act two you can't go
back here and after act three you can't
go back anywhere except for the new
areas
so wait there's something I want to get
from the blighted village while we're
here
do you know how to get it
yes
um
[Music]
they were they were very very bloody
oh yeah I stepped in a puddle
hold on a minute the blind the village
is so much more than it is
for life
oh Authority
um
fisticuffs get her baby
I'm not seeing that what's going on
happening
yeah I also don't see the role for
whatever reason
mind your manners of course we will nice
worry about no reason signs inspired it
was I don't it's in one of the houses
right yeah yeah I think it's is it in
the basement of The Alchemist building
yeah
yeah yes I think
we need it though
we need it you want it I I want it so
bad
okay
okay shut because I remember when I
found that I wanted Marissa to get what
did you find my double stream do you
like Universal no
it was something I told you that we
needed this house it's the other house
it's the one it's this house
the the board the the it's it's in the
the bottom the bottom uh it's in the
underdark yeah The Bard sword I know
yeah I know where it is
I found it yay
alcohol I lose give me all the booze all
right where did they go down there oh
okay okay I don't know where it is down
here I just know it's here okay go
explore okay
be careful
a little potion of sleep yum yum
[Music]
Evelyn
I totally didn't know that there was a
lever there I didn't know that at all
I know
you guys go into a different room we
went into the down in the house
I'm blind we've abandoned I did Calliope
Mori
tastes fine I see the hatch now I just I
don't have eyeballs
where'd they disappear to I mean
where is everybody
I I get you
this is poison that sounds fun it does
hmm
where is this book did pass the
perception check no you think it's in
this room because there's other rooms
the one that I just opened the oh the
door to oh probably
well let's follow the the more
interesting stuff is like probably
deeper yeah you gotta performance that
sounds yeah sounds accurate
feel free to open all the caskets good
I need nothing in there I need my book
oh wait are you looking for the
ah
surprise indeed
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
yeah I want it I missed it in my run so
I need it please help me live my dreams
and fully now you are surprised how do I
play this oh yeah I am
[Laughter]
Margaret
I think this is how I play it and then
what do I do
it's been so long I'm just a
refresherence just a little refresher
course
can we welcome the Bell I'm ready got
him all right well you guys got it all
taken care of I guess
yes
books she should talk to them do that
thing over there never so you already
know it I I missed this in my run
through I didn't even come here oh you
didn't get the book okay we need the
book and the book key so the book key is
also somewhere yeah the book here is the
the gem right
yeah I know where both are
um what's your name Mirror Mirror I'm a
mement race what the what are these
answers
oh
good luck
wow has Disney tried to sue
what oh my God I mean this looks
literally like Snow White yeah
like I wonder why they invented that
yeah let me in
oh it's because girl I am a Barbie
[Laughter]
okay
I wonder what that is oh my God what's
that looks like a trap do you need me to
disarm it knock it I think it looks in
there oh wow okay wait let me see if I
can uh I found a bunch of Scrolls may I
take them of course yeah hell yeah take
everything that looks interesting I have
no thieves so I can't lock pick this
people attacked the door
yeah
yay
oh we're in this room now
where are we
[Laughter]
[Music]
do I have a weapon
no thank you Kelly we need you yeah
you're holding a sec please not ranged
attention Callie I've got gloves for you
oh
thanks in my inventory if you find the
blue gloves the bracers of the fence
those are for you oh thank you let me
equip them really quick yeah
we are uh Mario
see
Grace
I can't uh I can't take it from you
actually here I think you got to give
them to me oh okay yeah all your stuff
is blacked outfit is stealing illegal
now wait it also has bludgeons
thank you
she got it
okay
[Music]
it's the only thing I can do
novel Keyhole it's an important thing
we need a big tank a big tanky brute
this is my book
you try to examine the book but the
longer you step
oh I love playing with controller I can
just spin in circles
I love this book oh
you feel better the second the book is
that oh you dropped
your boss yeah that's why you drop it I
didn't have an option to stop
what where'd the book go what did you do
the Trap
uh oh it's just not he's got a little
it's in my inventory that's fine okay
Apple
look at it
it is
a little fire breath gargoyle dude I
don't need to be in turn based mode for
this
okay and is the gym guys is the gem down
here to unlock it too no I will see I
know it okay oh
my nose
it goes pretty deep we have to go pretty
deep for them yeah if you want to like
be fast and we could get out out of here
first and yeah then we have to jump into
the into the whole of the other building
I think I don't mind oh well the well
isn't that bad oh yeah there's several
places to get whatever in there it's all
connected yes
I think that was the key to the cell
that
Molly we don't need it yeah yeah yeah
yeah I can break any any left through
the hatch
be open
oh you guys are still down there again
oh
right here
let's go through the well the well is
fun
okay
yeah I will even break the the lock on
balder's gate
on the Baldur's Gate
what does the gate
go yeah I don't what what is Baldur's I
guess well we we sing the song of
bolderon who founded Baldur's Gate you
know remarkable
I just want to open this chest really
quick
you guys can do
your things
Ally being a little bit aggressive over
there vibrations
you got it just just definitely grabbing
some things wait
I'll find them sorry
[Laughter]
Rod next one well all right I have no
eyeballs
to go
I trust you baby
oh there's a spider web that's not
creepy or anything
it caught ladies
I'm stuck can I rescue oh me looks like
it yeah
[Music]
oh no
let's party let's ride along oh you guys
already started oh
where's the bathroom behind us oh we're
behind us
oh
now I know where we are okay oh they're
behind
are those little alligator dudes no
they're spiders
it looks like alligators from far away
they they do you're so right
yeah nice
um I don't think I have any ranged
attacks
oh music changed
[Music]
I'm just gonna
I'm just gonna sing a song
good luck
nice one puppy
oh there's another one far away that's
coming up oh blue one
um yeah
[Music]
you are
in the web still
Chomp jump try jumping or so yeah you'll
be unstuck after this turn
I think oh well good luck
wait I'm still stuck in the web you guys
need to get me out
[Music]
that's pretty rough helping
okay well
I guess I'll just keep I'll keep playing
music yeah
no it's cool I'll get the spider yeah
we'll chill can you chill yeah
who damage please don't don't try it
I'll I'll come over here
but I have I don't have no more action
left I have to help you you can wear
them this way I
do I not have I bet I don't have any
arrows oh it hurts all right let me
throw something damn teleport probably
next turn again
oh that's not for sure I could never
mind
as long as you have the bow you're fine
oh
okay I kind of have my friend here
oh I'm not left
okay get out of here
go kill that spider biboo
got it yeah beat em up
Eric Gonzalez
yeah steals lunch money
yeah yeah doing it let's go I'm gonna
fly out of the web
my voice is so husky because it's really
early in the morning
come here for
if it makes you feel any better I just
woke up too
where's my other spider yeah where is
this oh it's up there
and I guess
yes they can just range attack it I
suppose or he could just come down here
stopping that's what I was thinking too
a little
little baby little baby baby dude
[Music]
[Applause]
something tells me we're not supposed to
cross that bibu is that correct
yeah that is correct okay the correct
way okay you trolled me away I knew that
the poison-filled tunnel was
yes all right you're right oh you're
going that way
I don't know where I'm going I haven't
been here
in here anyways you're naturally
progressing correctly oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah let's go away
way this is in fact the way do we go
across this final oh there's a giant
spider I really want to find the big
spider yeah together okay don't do
anything yet don't do anything I see I
see the dark amethyst that we need okay
yeah this is something I can see it okay
like this
it's prone baby
it did Big damage oh
oh she coming
I want she coming
wow it's kind of awesome that was one
third of the house yeah we could
continue that whenever she's on the web
if anybody has something with fire just
shoot the web with the fire oh cool okay
[Music]
she's currently considered I don't think
she's on the web right now huh no no
she's on the she's on she's offline yeah
oh okay
okay I killed most of the babies
yeah
we feel very strong 50 that's nothing
I gotta rely on the
wow
wow what's going on today
we're on easy mode
yeah yes oh okay okay makes sense yes
they're a real opponent oh
as we should be honestly
okay
oh
come here
go up to this little spider
[Music]
oh kill the spider
okay I'll try if it lets me not enough
movement all right I guess
oh you guys are blocked oh
that's not incredible
are we vlogging this thing
yeah I can't see past nourishes She's
Too Tall I'm too short story
just jump over me
yeah Point Blank never said all right
come and hit me I can't
Howard
whoa
gotta get rid of the smaller ones too I
just drew
you guys got the big one handled though
yeah okay
yeah I'll Frozen you know what to do
wrong Maybe
should have gone on the web more than on
the yeah spider maybe it's okay
and this is
I hope this one oh you inspired did you
inspire me yeah I got some bardic roll
here
because you inspire me every day so
you stop now does it go away I don't
know how it or Smash and juice it or am
I using it
oh now I'm using it
it hit
Mutual inspiration not the discharge
you're running when it flew away right
now baby spiders
it's okay I can take a little bit of
pain
a little bit I have the bathroom a lot
very much
it's so big
so Bieber can we still multi-class uh
yes you well you have to turn it back to
normal I think but if we turn it to Easy
Does It undo the multi-classing
no because I still have my cleric stuff
okay then maybe next time we're at Camp
it doesn't have to be right away it
doesn't matter but um I might want to
swap to wizard oh now I can move away
I want to be strong nice cloud of
daggers
man just making making me excited to
play on my own at some point because I
just got it on PS5 baby yeah let's go
and popcorn and playing Baldur's Gate
alone
no I agree this is this robe
it's a different game is this rope that
the spider dropped good oh are we not
done yet no no we still have two spiders
yeah
yeah where are they oh that might be
good for people oh
maybe maybe maybe
okay
he's stronger without armor no
hmm oh wait Kelly just doesn't like to
wear clothes just like me for real for
real oh hello
it never ends
come on spider find five more
business armor okay okay
shut up
without clothes though yeah excuse me
sorry I mean like well your character
gave that same rope to Carla and she
just doesn't look good in it
I get it
oh I killed that one yeah
I believe in you guys
time to throw
yeah you get it yeah yeah half is not
interrupted
it's not that bad okay sometimes it gets
a little frustrating
there we go
all right rope for somebody in this big
spider
I fell
oh God okay it's okay it's okay I've
only got eight health left
is that so far fall oh at least you got
the thing
I'm about to I'm trying to pick it up
but it's it's tiny there we go
dark amethyst acquired
I'll just take it from that okay how do
I get back to you guys
it was over here where I am there's a
little climbing thing
okay so I have to go back to short rest
and climb up okay yes I see it yeah we
should probably short rest
save the game
better than nothing
oh now I'm not basking in in the the
weird God's love anymore
oh wow what a shame I know I mean I
still have it so whenever I thought it
was a permanent blush no it is but uh
it's you you have to meet certain
standards to reach it you know what I
mean
so it's a it's la vietara's love pain is
the path to Clarity when you have 30 hit
points or less you get a two percent
bonus two attack rolls and wisdom saving
throws for three turns
that's
pretty cool yeah have you not been
engaging in the sadism enough these days
it seems not
so do we wanna like explore this place
even more
let's go get Carla
okay should we go back to blighted
Village yeah
yeah
let's do it
yeah I know how to tell
if I got it waypoints hello
I'm ready let's go yes she's ready
Freddy let's get it ladies
we gotta meet the hot lady the hot lady
literally and figuratively yeah
she sets my soul on fire mine too man
he's great she's powerful I have a Siri
in this round so you can have a cereal
um yeah
I will steal him from you by the end of
this run it will be mine
all right good luck I mean you can have
him but
I just don't think he's feeling it pick
someone else
that's right over here if we jump
yeah this was a bit of a hard one I
remember a bridge
that you had to jump yeah I don't think
I walked over a piece of uh tree A Long
Tree yeah I did too I think I think we
can just go the other way
um
it's up by the Risen Road
oh yeah it's up over here
yeah and then we go up I believe
we'll find it eventually
we gotta get our okay well
yeah it was blowing off my weights to
you girls because I'm my inventory was
too excuse me
Boo has a conversation to do I have a
all right I'm on the way get in bee boo
oh this one
oh I guess we go down here and then I
don't know how you guys climbed all the
way over there but we'll find it
find the way jump
yeah maybe I can jump vendor at some
point that would be cool
look at this guy balding
I'm watching you she looks a little bit
like Nam
a little bit oh my god
oh yeah is it
okay
[Music]
it even made me like one piece who had
nothing to do with one piece until now
why can't I jump please just let me jump
game I'm begging you
I don't know how you guys got over there
we went down again over by the the cave
for the owl bear yes I'm in front of the
cave and then we just walked over we
didn't have to jump
you can walk over the water oh I guess
you can just walk through the freaking
one
don't overcome underestimated very smart
just not the brightest
it's all right absolutely okay let's go
a brother
I'm a true
sir oh my God
I'm special
well
the last one I think I consumed so
and Theresa got one so Kelly and people
should get one I want to eat a worm yeah
she's going to rip down the old world
order they don't know we killed all the
goblins
oh yeah
[Music]
um
like you has been chosen by the absolute
absolutely you speak with her voice
the truth wow so I can make them do
whatever I want um
You Will Rule it flashes back to Baby
who's like half this person's son
that's comedic
I'm sorry true soul I
finally repeat learn more if I knew it
seems the absolute still has a great
deal to teach me
um good job guys just just time to leave
just tell him to leave we killed the owl
oh yeah I did continue
we won't take any more of your time May
the absolute guide us okay bye bye yeah
[Music]
just wanted to get you out of there to
loot his body yeah
um
no you can have it Bieber
wait there's one on him where where'd
you put that robe I wanted to see it
oh the Rope it's uh it's in my first row
oh I can't take it I'm sorted by way
transported to me I will take the weight
off your shoulders
if you want it sure I want it I gave it
to you thank you
oh a very cute little robe
oh
much taller than you
can I wear this
yes you can that reminds me of your RPG
outfit yeah
what which one oh the one I'm wearing
now true yeah oh it's
yeah
nice
okay okay boo
Carla okay we go this way
lead the way
wait we don't need to go this whole one
let me think
um I don't think we've been to the Risen
road yet but the Risen Road I remember
being able to get to Carlock from here
um
I think it's up I'm pretty sure it's up
yeah it's up more we need to go north
we're going south
[Music]
I don't remember anyway this place is
too large
a big big
the other side oh yeah I remember
jumping over this uh
no wait not this bridge there was
jumping over a bridge okay I guess I'm
doing this
I don't really care but apparently I'm
talking to dead bore but not really are
you gonna heal him examining it I'm back
at the blighted Village I've walked back
over and I presume we go north from
there yeah we go out the other side and
then go north
a vampire's been eating yeah oh my
husband eating
yeah okay
this is North oh I follow I follow
Marissa
I could be wrong
I'm saving oh oh no oh no oh no
where am I that it's quick saving
in trouble
it's okay I come help to smash please
Cali's ready to smash
I wait for you guys smash
yeah with big fist
[Music]
and Meaty thigh I like that
fist meets the eye
oh
yeah I got you hold on a sec I'll see I
need to watch this yeah ah improvised
melee I might not make the jump you know
so just in case okay let me use my mouse
let me just use my mouse bagel
group pickpocket no do not pickpocket
throw
go on
oh wow that was pretty bloody
boo come back
is that really okay welcome back bagel
[Music]
getting thrown by catlins The Dream It's
a lot of blood your back is broken but
what can you do
oh give him a fight
oh what happened to the doggle
right
now I smashed them
it's not my turn
ER
how do you say it in English
definitely kill them very quickly
um
nice yeah
like some some very fruity Jam yeah
that's a lot
it's a lot of fruit chunks in there yeah
I guess they like it chunky yeah and
there we go
pretty rough
oh yeah
you're standing in between the three oh
um
I thought Inna was in the chat
[Laughter]
because hyena sounds like hyena
you made me scroll up in the chat guys
where is she
inadoko
[Music]
Cali punch him smash him kick him yeah I
did again
damn it
oh okay oh boy oh boy oh he's flipping I
need a glitch yeah
all right
nice dummy
bonus action huh
oh friends destroyed now we're good nice
I'm just gonna electrocute us like that
bee boo I killed them very cool
this will not be the first the first
time I electrocute you don't worry uh
I'll look forward to the next time
okay
oh come on kids wait food wait let's
take this food because um yes we need
camp supplies hey yes we do desperately
we need to loot Goblin all this stuff
now we're trying to load some food too
here and there
oh yeah nice idea grab all that all
those goodies
more European find Red Apple milk
I like I like your um
I like you
for rotten food
did you find her yeah she's down here I
haven't interacted I'm waiting for you
guys
oh down down down down there yeah she's
literally down by the river I'm gonna
talk to Carla okay
see the one who who wrote the lyrics to
that no that's Daisy
okay
okay does not look okay
too
she's on fire just like me
yeah Sparks like the flame yay she's
starting a fight every day
oh the
the last her Flames always make my
OBS lag so much is yours lagging too
girl yeah
[Music]
she's so cool so weird
lights up yeah I love her too
Lloyd please tell me I found you before
those so-called paladins of tear did
does she not remember me only
meme Hatter in my team she loves me
what why good great
glad I don't don't hurt me carlak
oh please hurt me Carla please hurt me
then your last envisions of demonic
she's so beautiful through a landscape
of fire Jesus so hot I know right
what do you mean
ready
I relate to her on another level mm-hmm
my my Burning Angel
ice cream I love her and Lover's wearing
more please
I think all three of us swear quite a
big except for being together
I'm your girlfriend now
hey you already have all right
no I'm joking I'm not gonna date
she's all yours Kiana I know you love
Carl Lang a little
bit all right I see how it is
everybody's turned their back on me just
because Darion decided that he wanted a
little poke even though it's not like no
no no no
everybody deserves some love
me her personal attack even ogres
I mean
you're pretty hot so especially ogres
but now I'm free congratulations Carla
goon off to goon to hunt me down that's
huge believe me when I tell you I'm not
going the latest yeah
um
yes yes yes
she's great yeah we can work on evicting
this parasite and take faerun by the
short hairs sound good
um absolutely my favorite companion I
think oh yeah
if it wouldn't Scorch your skin off
we already have a Berserker Barbarian
though yeah don't roll for the party
I'm sorry
have fun at the camp Queen
ette oh we we have to do the fun stuff
without you though there's no room
yeah sorry we're a full team you're
gonna have to deal with that where did
that oh boy hold still uh wait never
mind I can't do it why can't I use my
spell should we go beat up the dudes
yeah let's go beat up the dudes yeah
this guy suck Marissa needs healing at
some point too yeah
I've got potions
um I I was trying to use my spell but I
found out one of the things I had
applied wouldn't let me do my healing
word so ah
[Music]
yeah yeah okay
of course thank you
guys
that's a dude's head cool
okay
[Music]
gonna loot it oh I just want to kill him
yeah we're going to I mean
understandable for sure oh wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
uh Kiana you want you want to talk to
someone who will sell you things yeah
pass this door there's a person you can
buy and sell things from we'll have to
kill them in the fight to come but if
you want a quick sell off some stuff you
could before the fight starts
okay that's that's
thumb wait where is she she's selling
uh
oh maybe out out here out here
maybe I thought I thought they were
inside no maybe not sorry
try try talking outside she's cute oh
yeah she sells stuff here you can go
first Kiara okay
here
going oh she's going inside to her sales
table or what
oh well you guys are doing that I need
to how do I turn off nudity again I
turned it back on for my
well as you turn it on there is
something um why do you think she turned
it on me for my private personal run
okay I think I turned it off because
private moments has nothing to do with
that yum
yeah private moments is like blocking
the scene okay can see it how do I uh
what's the quick way of doing this again
is there a quick way to sell stuff
I'll just double click okay
just quickly double check and make sure
nudity off yeah not that I would turn it
on because I don't care about those
things but let me see it's not about
caring about those things
it's about the immersion in real life
people are naked he wants she wants the
authentic experience I don't want I
don't want little Leafs covering my my
nip knobs I know what they look like
already you know all right
let's get you yeah yeah you understand
yeah all right whatever you say
almost done you're cool take your time
[Music]
um
yeah
next one okay I'll probably sell a
couple things no don't do it yet you're
gonna have to just wait two seconds
people
okay
we just wait for Cali I'm I'm ready
so I don't make you sure I'm gonna go on
this side
is that okay oh yeah you got a plan
don't you I do have a plan
freaking go or I can throw the goblin
Scimitar so hold on
thanks let's do this
poison resistance could use that all
right um you know I guess that's
probably probably about it
oh I have a soul coin these coins
are they good for carlak I don't
remember I thought I remember her
talking about them and I was like oh
I've never used this once oh no yes you
need them for her I think you can you
can slot it in her body and it makes her
stronger oh like a slot machine yeah we
also need to save the infernal iron so
if you see that don't sell it
okay cool let me see let me just grab a
dagger really quick so I can throw it uh
oh yeah good idea
hate having to do math right
hold on
they shouldn't they should really make
this a little easier to figure out but
that's okay
I'm almost done guys sorry what eight
plus two is eight eight plus six it's
14.
you got it all right let's do it all
right kill him okay hold on I'm gonna
enter turn base
and then I'll kill her
yeah
okay
don't make noise so wet
oh I didn't make him wet it's okay he's
wet no it's fine okay
now go ahead can everyone end their turn
please
oh
turn ended
oh rattle them
environmental turn
okay oh okay there we go
foreign
[Music]
just murder exactly as planned
see
I don't want to go down
I'm blocking it you can't
oh wait no oh yeah he can't climb up the
stairs
then take these
nice nice
we still have some more right yeah but
they wanted to fight Mario babe
I can't blame them really
yeah who wouldn't want to fight Mario
fish
hey
it's interesting I guess I should go
down though because they're all like
yeah out of my view
theme
hey let you down
[Music]
oh we're gonna kill the poor oh she's
invisible
[Music]
oh she did she turn invisible yeah
but she's still there you could like if
you have some AOE or something like
something like cloud of daggers you
could place it there and hope that it
hits her
I'll randomly shoot he's right there
boom nope nope
oh burning hands scroll Grease
[Music]
set all this stuff
turn off your electric water thank you
give me all your
I need to find this book oh Kelly do you
want a sword
of Justice
that sounds kind of neat would that be
good for me that might be I gave it to
you
loot content I found a fan fiction a fan
fiction
a pleasurable deal this is an excerpt
from the play a pleasurable deal of
banned in no fewer than four cities for
its lewd content it's scandalous nature
led to a number of widely distributed
and illicit printings
yeah
okay
narrator come here fearful curtail now
lost to time in grief this man will sunk
to death Sublime a gift he saw to win
his lady's heart our Campion smiled for
now the game did start enter Robert male
teethley crying Carlisle stage right
flash of smoke
weep not young man dough free your wife
has fled and comfort found in comrades
arms and bed she licks her lips and
cries his name oh my and now seek you to
be the apple of her eye
yes stranger no such things I ask
Carlisle I watch you from the shadows
and I see your shame and grief for
Nature's Melody you seek to win your
lady and her bed to have your name upon
her lips instead Robert you know my
curse my pain my grief my woe Carlisle
of you I know you seek a larger hoe to
plow a Fair Maid and sell sower seed to
grow but lag do ya Mighty horn at best
with which to guide a maids to be bad
and fast
book I found in this game
wow I respect it
um I'm downstairs thank you for that oh
he's never had it
cool
I should have sent it to someone
what
a severed head I was thinking of putting
it in someone's inventory
now what did you do
cucumber you are cucumber I'm humbered
now
I I put armor on you I put armor on you
more you'll pay I need you downstairs
yeah sure what's up please come
downstairs and help me knock down a door
with your power if you tell me where
downstairs is I'll definitely there's
there is that hat the hits right here in
the house oh a hatch
I can't I can't yell I can't yell things
at the door to make it break
sadly the door does not have feelings
I can't burn a wooden door it's okay
we've got Kalia Mori open
look at that
[Applause]
oh yeah yeah there's a trap there's a
trap there's a trap
don't be like we shall disarm it my NPCs
okay
okay someone come sit on the other chair
on the other side oh okay I see disarmed
okay moriope you're gonna go loot in
that room
all right I'll play what I find I guess
but
be careful
it's dark
oh there's a marble plate maybe I can
get around it jump
jump all right
just a moment
let's go
to be wary
there's 203 gold yes which I'll take and
we can split loot everything
all right hold on there's a great ax
great sword Give Me Everything
and sell all these
on this arm
pleasurable deal hey they really like
this book here
this is what it is
another one
the other pleasurable deal there's more
[Music]
which one ones with Cali let's see this
one's just hold on oh oh this is kind of
good stuff yeah no there's really good
stuff in this room make sure you take
all of it don't miss anything
I have a pleasurable deal
it's that book right there
it's just a regular pleasurable deal
[Music]
you can see him
just wanted the sequel really it's more
gold
let's say it was illegal because it's
too lewd yeah yeah it's been enforcing
Kiana will you grab the the Quarter
Staff behind where you just came from oh
yeah it's on the weapons in the middle
table
the Quarter Staff mm-hmm looking great
thank you
okay get out of there
before I lock you in Cut and Run
the where's that girl this great accent
what did you just say Kelly
it's great ax no no before that
you say Cut and Run
Cut and Run what does that mean
it means get the it means get the out of
there
thank you retreat
see I wonder Sword of Justice or great
acts both are really nice but I think
I'll go Sword of Justice for now
oh I picked up the necromancy book
um good loot guys good loot do I can I
play the amethyst or do I have to give
it
do I have to give it to a Starion
to do it
are you gonna give to a Syrian the book
oh
oh you see anything about it can you
summon
small animal
oh maybe
listen to the book do it I can summon
the perfect thing a rat
why would you want us
and then and then interact with this
whole
uh oh I don't see the whole I
oh I haven't perceived it I think
do I need to perceive it I think so you
feel changed battered for having opened
it
suddenly because I can't walk around
there oh here let me get out of your way
no I'm not perceiving it ah wait the
borough hole yeah okay okay
I could understand
I'm not sure if the red can go there
I can't if people can't fit no one can
yeah I can click on it with the Mouse
um
you would need you might need to Wild
shape or Mist form yeah oh or can you
guys enjoy your familiar
I don't think they can controlling the
Familia but
[Music]
um
um is there something we can can we
remove something
no it doesn't it doesn't
I don't think it wants to go there
that's weird it just says can't get here
oh you need to be a druid oh
[Music]
I see
rest
in shape shift into like a tinier Mouse
oh it's just another entrance to the
locked room oh Okay click and dragged oh
what
what what
you gotta figure out how to click and
drag to move boxes look I mean yeah yeah
yep guys I might have to use our
inspiration
if we have any because I'm I'm I'm
reading a book wait what are you doing
oh my God
I got it I just keep rolling above 20s
because I have some things I'm just
reading the books
which book add an economically written
I am oh did you put the stone in yeah
you look very concerned
too much
what profane knowledge is now seared
inside you you won't let me in you never
have no are you guys seeing it
you've seen too much I'm seeing nurses
cutscenya oh yeah
hello it's okay I've seen it before I've
got the Forbidden Knowledge now
I don't know what that does to me but I
have Forbidden Knowledge yeah
yes
I am shielding are you in jail okay
the necromancy of Fate yeah
cool I don't know it's just as long as
you're smart it's good
oh I'm not smart yeah
[Laughter]
you're smart just uh not in the game I
am
[Music]
yeah
we all leave without you
in the house waiting for you hi hi hello
and a cute new little rat friend
sitting around
oh have uh any of you gone to the gith
Yankee uh crash
no nope
crashed did they crash the crash crash
it's called a crush
in case you didn't know
what is going on I don't know
I don't want a hyena here
yeah I don't want those either
let's just leave it here I wonder if we
keep walking down the Risen Road what
we'll find
hmm oh wait there's a there's a
teleporter here
nice Discovery Bijou welcome to the
discovery
what the hell is this
yeah I've never been up here before so I
don't know what this is
spooky
well there's some pretty good stuff we
can get if we
move on a bit from
here
okay I don't know where it is though
exploring exploring this whole area
there's so much fun stuff you know
what's this something is over there
you and me
you know sorry people you lead I'm being
a little nasty
yeah be bullied everybody
okay calm your feetsies
we follow people
Mario pad like simple commands follow
people what's up here
or I'll be understand
I understand follow
there's more death thing yeah there's
lots of dead things everywhere I don't
like that
ew they're feasting
can we kill them I don't have
that's all right that's okay how hard
could they be yeah yeah it's mine
probably easy we've got more open
the feast is over
the feast is over coming inside us you
fools I mean we are on easy mode so oh
Dad could it be
what are these things anyway
so numbed what's that mean not a clue
couldn't tell you
oh
I think these guys can speak English
to like understand the threats I say at
them oh yeah you're gonna insult them
yeah yeah I'm a Bard tell them their
mothers never loved them
well my first Miss of the day
they're like hyena people oh no it's
weird
who learned to walk on two feet okay and
they look like hyenas
please Mario pay smash don't play Red
you got it
you know that that's what moyopay is
here to do
bonus action
what's this
yeah how do you like that nice
noise hey
wow
goodbye to the rat
I was sure he was gonna last longer than
all of us
gone
yeah
wow
nice one rude
getting out of here
good luck
okay I can thank you
oh I can prank it
oh
come on come on
just myself
nice shooting ticks
oh my gosh what
[Music]
that was a critical Miss
it's pretty cool
protect Kiara
thank you welcome I had a bonus action
um
oh I probably should have given it to
narissa because your health is lower
it's okay for me yeah no it's okay I've
got it I've got a thing so
yeah rattle them
yeah
what's going on
I don't know what's happening actually
a murder I'm getting clawed
[Music]
why
nice
so
we need a little red stuff I've missed
70 chance
oh that's rough
seven years oh boy
I don't know what true strength does
nice
[Music]
should we do a long rest or oh we should
I guess yeah we should have long rest
of these people an open letter
to peacocks
being oppressed
you gotta go Savor any kind Furious
this is a leather oh there's a city over
here
oh there is a thing should we ask before
we go in there though uh absolutely
absolutely we're going to Camp okay okay
[Music]
walk deep yeah Alex here Kyla
all right Carla I took care of those
paladins for you
okay girls we want to have uh
conversations together right not two
separate ones yeah
um I always take care of my people Carla
glad to be counted amongst oh she likes
me I love Carla I've been there to watch
this she's so good she's the best but
I'm just happy they're off my tail
oh
[Music]
anytime soon so I'll just make the most
the most of the extra heat just don't
get too close until I found a way to
calm it down
we can't give her a hug yet
um
certainly can't do other things too
you know so back off well
don't worry about it it's a bit early in
the game too young to understand
meanwhile I'll need to find someone who
can tune up my engines sooner rather
than later oh you mean hand-holding yeah
yeah why did you have to say it on
stream oh sorry
he might be able to stabilize things if
I can find him
um
okay we moved there they're not there
anymore hopefully oh they're not no we
saved them and they left to Boulder's
Gate remember
of good oh but yeah they did leave but
she needs a teeth uh yeah but he's on
the way to Baldur's Gate
oh oh sorry Carlock I guess
oops
is dead I'm not about to consume it
she's trying she's trying to raise up a
Syrian again oh she's trying
dude
even though he loves Mario Fame
he does
That's What I Call edging
you can you think that's a threat
let me give you the book why can't I I
ca how do I give him the does he have to
he I bet I can't I bet he has to be in
the party no it's too
much uh what yeah if I read the book it
can't be
you can't read the book
no I can't read the book I don't think
anymore take it from my inventory oh my
God
oh my God
did you learn a spell from them no I
didn't get anything I don't know what it
was supposed to do
I passed all of the checks so apparently
I got the knowledge but I don't know
what the knowledge is it's late
at the book until later okay I'm gonna
I'm gonna send it
I don't need it on me right wait I'm
gonna read the book oh okay take the
book read it yeah see it doesn't open
for anyone except for the person who
read it oh
my book
look at Carlock dancing I love when she
drops
she drops it
oh hold on yeah yeah hold on Bust A Move
yeah some head spinnies oh
yeah I remember if you okay
oh shaking you for good after the Mind
flare ship he's crazy enough of me can
you
Carlock
advocates diaboli
think of a furnace
why am I making the choices
or no okay it's a suggestion sorry
it's just suggestions who's making the
choice yeah oh it's me
and you've got hello
be back here will he join us
isn't he still mad at me
no he's probably forgiven yeah
porn horn blazes with flame bloodied
great ax held high he chases the fiend
ignited you know Will's pretty cool she
is yeah I really like well more devil
inside
he's like I don't really have him in my
parties
he's the only one who liked me in my
solo playthrough I know I don't like 100
and I didn't even have them on my team
barely and I was like what
think I am how can you struggle with
making these NPCs like you like I feel
like everybody's lusting
is hard
[Music]
yeah she's a victim
you're not being tricked will not be
tricked
I may be an effective Soldier but I
never wanted to serve Zario legged it
away from it the first chance I got and
yet you served
ah
Stand Down
stop it
Devils cannot be trusted oh come on will
um
so stubborn will would you listen to
sense
it doesn't have to end
bad for either we could be friends you
can use this right have you considered
yeah Buddies
my man's were you not paying attention
he just doesn't want to believe it
come on man
that's okay
we forgive you even though you didn't
forgive Bijou for looting your dead
friends but okay we forgive you maybe
he'll join us after this thankfully but
truce
a little baby begging face
stab him right through the chest pranked
but luck won't be on our side forever
yes you have my blade Your Leader
willing of course
join us
okay
um the more of the merrier as they say
no dies no
um
I was the rampaging Beast I see the good
in you karlak I promise not to lose
sight of it even when the girls burn
hottest
wow the famous blade where'd you come
from
are you seeing Shadow heart because I'm
seeing nothing
um
that's crazy right she has a little
thing above her head
listen
s even more glad he decided to stick
around me too it takes a pretty slick
movement yeah and he came out of nowhere
yeah I'm just glad he's not mad at me
anymore right thank God keeping an eye
on him if he turns on you again he's
dead yeah
see you've got a little butt chin here
but do I
do what let's see your character has a
butt chin
[Music]
someone who can admit
somebody's behind
plus big behind
you'll see
next time you zoom in I didn't see you
next time maybe yeah you'll see that you
have a butt chin oh I think will wants
to talk will wants to talk let's go
listen to his conversation
I'm sorry to say
and I've played my part all too poorly
poor guy
sheesh
[Music]
I forgot what outfit you were wearing
one night soon
lots of hot looking ladies
everybody looks real good you too thanks
I know maybe the most good looking is
yeah
possibly
do you like them well tell us about
yourself
you want to talk more sleep
house what's going on house and we okay
yeah I forgot he was here now let me
have a little conversation with him
yes
if you have anything he wants to say oh
God there's literally so much stuff
just a couple what is this
um
has had a lover before
really the option
those who remained are Shadow cursed if
you don't die of their hands then you'd
be beautiful moriope we have together
your face is so beautiful it's hard for
me to look at it for too long it's hard
for anyone to resist especially
yeah I'm just as tight I don't know what
else to say part once was part once
ladies that's how it is after
afterwards
hideous but fascinating like nothing
else in nature I'm glad to say yes
hideous but fascinating
praise
[Music]
who are we talking about
Francesca
The Grove needs to move beyond the
mistakes of the past what it needs is an
unknown quantity an outsider who can
invest your father you can get your reps
in ladies I chose Francesca do you guys
want to know a fun fact that I learned
about housing
he's one of the only companions that you
can date one person also date housing at
the same time yep oh so he's into
polygamy yeah
I believe it
um what about the secret passage in the
underdark tell us how to go there
because we definitely need to go there
there's stuff we want there
is
n't like it's not for the content
for guys right it's the content
obviously
to do what I can to stop story's gotta
entertain somehow right
underdark is fun I feel like that's just
the better way to go years ago
to prevent him from unleashing Darkness
across the region before he was defeated
perhaps I can lift this curse just as
you find a cure for your infection
okay Allison I'm kind of done talking to
you because we just really talk a lot
more open just doesn't like the clock
bro what's good
Molly smash Molly no talk
yeah
another player is choosing camp supplies
leave it to you
I made dinner
hope it tastes good I want it I made
tonkatsu last night
[Music]
Yeah by myself
wow was it good it could be a Austrian
schnitzel but I realized I'll I can just
make it into tonkatsu because it's like
pretty similar I love making tonkatsu
with curry too oh yeah yeah delicioso
hungry
our bodies wait before we go we have to
go home
oh and uh
I'll check on him crazy guys
steal it from him you're gonna steal the
poor dog's balls
[Music]
yeah each time
that's not something you see every day
oh that doesn't seem right we'll try
again really quickly come on this time
it works
thank you
yes it must hurt oh I got it why are you
stealing the ball from him he's just a
little guy
are you okay
he needs attention of course approved
yeah that's sweet baby Chihuahua yeah
you'll have the ball in your inventory
if you throw it somewhere he'll bring it
back that's so cute
let's see now that you can pet the dog
why are there two Gales I don't know I
think he's glitch yeah so the way closer
to him oh no he goes
it is
[Music]
again cute okay girl Gail needs a
probably a magic item oh somebody talked
to him already yeah I gave him a magic
item oh that's so sweet of you I know I
gave him one I was wearing so now I need
to find a different one but I you know
in this camp for whatever reason I can
never find the Traveler's chest
I feel crazy oh it's over here oh yeah
okay it's just by Shadow heart
he's not glitch to talk to him oh so he
just has another dude version of him
don't question it
is normal
yes because you went in it I can't
it belongs to only one
[Music]
only one
no we don't share they're pretty
how do I know which one's mine the what
everyone lets you open it I guess
Travelers chess traveler's chest
I feel like there's a bunches
oh this is mine yeah it must be mine
because it's got a severed head
nice if I put that in someone else's
chest now good luck
yeah
why is not the orange one
well I'll put it in your inventory then
added armor I'll just sell that
I'll store my gold
all right what's next I'm good to go
let's keep exploring up north because
there's stuff happening up North and
then the tea house is down Way Way South
yeah I'm interested in up north because
I haven't been there before yeah okay
okay have I been there
have you been to the Crush
the crush I don't think so
then you haven't been up north
okay are you still in the camp no I left
I am I'm coming out right now
where did everyone go oh somebody has a
pink chest
did everyone leave no yes
we just stop stop running
wait
she's just coming to me for some reason
really far away from everyone
yeah I'm just waiting by narissa thank
you please hold my hand I was alone I
was so scared okay what was that all
right lead the way
oh the burning Village
oh why is everything on fire I don't
know I wonder what could be up here to
cause everything to be on fire like this
hey what's happening is it like a raid
Maybe
the village is being raided Maybe by God
well I did not see this yet I'm in a
conversation oh okay
what is this
please just leave me that's no good
all right oh okay all right guess what
once we're doing what they want us to do
okay might as well
I think if it wouldn't it be red then
it's fine
[Music]
they're goblins is probably fun but what
are they doing
I'm sorry I'm in a conversation
uh strength push I don't ask questions
[Laughter]
a little bonus yeah
good enough yeah big muscle
um
there you go
go go
cute my work here is done
[Music]
nice bathtub
it's this place
it feels wrong to loot things
sometimes I mean they're not using it
anymore it's on fire might as well with
the goblins
potato porridge
well we could also go in where I opened
up the door if you guys want yeah I
think yeah here is a dead end it must be
a reason why you opened the door yeah
you gotta go in
comfortable
[Music]
yeah I mean it is a burning building
your wine give me that I'ma save the ham
I'm Gonna Save the food do it get the
food
oh
yeah save the kitchen stuff I saved the
sausage oh one thing that I wish
you could do in this game is cook right
yeah like I know you technically are
when you're camping but like it's not
the same
just not the same as being able to make
a recipe you know
Apple
pineapple we need to cook
did you girls go to the second one hear
me please
so that way we have food for our camp
seems like there might be somebody
behind this door oh boy oh I'm in a I'm
in a I'm in a I'm in a scene
yeah I mean I just opened a door and it
exploded oh I mean mode
I don't think so
there's an extra step yeah okay
who are you talking to I don't know what
they're trying to say no
but I'm saving a guy
[Music]
no I'm trapped I've just run out of the
building
um there's like a person underneath
I'm gonna oh he just kind of roasted it
foreign
does he follow you now oh he has one HP
uh-oh except I'm like not in the same
area as this guy and he's dead
yeah
why did he die
um well hold him and get out of there
yeah we completed
the clothes let's go
let's go yeah it was there a quest that
we could have gotten with that guy yeah
oh well wait wait for me I'm getting I'm
loading all the food in here feeling it
sounds good
it's pretty rough buddy I gotta save the
food yeah that is super rough actually
that didn't go as planned maybe not but
that's okay
a lot of burning things in here
yeah
okay I saved the food I'm coming okay
Empire
Mill what the are you doing up
there
eh
is that will who's that guy yeah he
looks like will Riot can you talk to him
recruit paddle
table
yeah that's not will just to look like
can I go here
the council Floric needs help too how do
I get there
oh there's like so many people up there
well go help them you know what I
realized is that I bet we could have
saved that dude if we had video use the
water yeah
[Music]
well I was too busy looting the food
yeah that's all right yeah that's your
priorities I didn't I didn't even mean
to talk to that guy
okay
I see a bunch of people here
they need help do you need help
people hi hi maybe spread some water
wherever necessary I gotta open the door
I guess yeah maybe there are still
people to help
oh wait hold on
hold on yeah
yeah there you go are you guys spreading
more fire oh what is going on
okay proper fangs must wait she says
you got them out on the outside
we gotta cut and run
and run cotton run
no water
oh there's water barrels yeah
maybe a short rest
yeah maybe
oh Callie what's damn hit you hard huh
counselor yeah a little bit you're right
it takes more than me a fire to break me
Eva Eva
yeah
everyone's using this game
drow have taken Grand Duke older
ravengers if my eyes and ears can be
believed oh Gauntlet report to the man
and send for reinforcements we must find
the Duke the Duke on your command
counselor was you so sweaty count the
dead I mean yeah we were just in a
burning building
be surprised if we weren't
ask us again for your Aid
please rescue Raven Guard from his drow
captors
the council will reward you for your
effort more European wants to smash
oh let's do
hold on a sec uh why entrust this to me
who is the Duke Raven guard
um
I'll I'll travel West and rescue Duke
ravengard
his generosity command understood the
towers with care yeah the land itself
has been swallowed in Shadows and join
you when I can who are you West left
all right yeah oh well I guess I got
inspiration reward oh
rewind I can't read
reward rescue the Duke we learned that
the Grand Duke was captured by drone
taken Westward
only choose one
route whatever it's the same thing
um
really there's like a tried I don't
really know what would be good is there
both
there's a bow I heard there's a bow yes
we can do that
I accepted it
can I has Bo
o I don't know
did they just give it to us already even
though we haven't completed the quest
good to be in your inventory yes it is
not I took it already Okay I think I
think this is the one yeah
the jolt shooter what does it do
electric blood when the wheel that deals
damage using this weapon they gain two
lightning charges
Leo
yeah
no more goblins yeah
yeah now shall we immediately uh look
West
I guess we shouldn't say that yeah we
should keep going west for now yeah okay
party members in a conversation they are
not I want to put short dress guys oh
yeah I'm trying to get short rest it
says a party member is in a conversation
and cannot rest right now oh
so odd
please let us rest
oh yeah it says it for me too like can
everyone try the short rest oh oh
[Music]
maybe now
um well there's a person over here so
maybe if we talk to them it'll get us
out of our predicament oh yeah
[Music]
do you see that shadow in the background
yeah Shadow yeah it's a looks like a
dragon
what
[Music]
above oh her hair is popping off kill
you wow what could they want just escape
the tragedy do not you ought to do the
same I doubt I think that look on Google
we could just fight them
no
no at least this is a different group
just
just to stay alive
there's plenty of us around she's cute
yeah
you want to join me instead what
goodbye
have a nice day that's it well should we
go try to get down there and see what
those guys want oh there we go ah yay
Arrow of Darkness it looks like there's
a path down here yeah I just oh boy oh
well they all kind of like Get Yankee
no
no oh
[Music]
oh
um it's dark in time I think you should
run okay never mind oh wow
what the hell is going on
there's a dragon
Daenerys Targaryen please calm down
we merely sought to no excuses question
kill then move on find the weapon find
the weapons fail her
wow what a very good Yankee in response
suicide
why am I talking well why is she stupid
uh we should save before we talk to them
by the way
um whenever we see them again
they're around here somewhere if we keep
moving
I just don't remember don't worry
yes
hey I think I'm experiencing a problem
Oh wait am I walking right into your job
okay
do your best
these creatures are
creatures
forgiveness
as for you
tell me the dragon's kind of big can I
run you yeah a little
tell him people I should raise um
persuasion I don't know you look I'm
tiny I'm almost no authorized at all no
uh I'm gonna add guidance
can I add friends oh wait so I add
guidance to friends is two dice better I
don't know
oh two dice is nice
I love just looking at more of these abs
Springs
thank God
I raised him up
much as I want to see the dice rolls
not a thing until wow really nice all
right can we kill them sucking ass
take hold not your own but that of the
artifact you can
[Music]
Shadow Hearts thing possibly
notifying does not want to part from you
it does not want to fall into the death
Raiders hands
and I will leave your blood beneath your
skin don't let him know we have him
um
[Music]
sure I'll help if I can't should I say
that yeah be like I'll help if I can
obedience is your only hope
now stand still oh he's gonna Frisk yeah
what is he was doing Ninjutsu wait wait
wait uh
steal your mind
steal my mind
give me guidance
please pass me boo yeah
my mind is stealed you cannot get past
my mind
Frisk no Jutsu
Naruto
[Music]
yeah look my head empty
is you know what save the day there you
go uh can I detect his thoughts try it
[Music]
oh I have minus one intelligence maybe
not oh good luck
ah
no thoughts
sure yeah one time one more time
I prefer we not die yeah
let's go
this one was
he
um
first one why not don't be too hasty I I
just read your mind unlikely
but it costs me nothing to
your sorry life
very wellistic yes from the ship that
crashed on this wretched World
definitely not us we did not Crush not
us if you
refuse it the reward will be great
now go
no you didn't it has so much health
oh really it's like over two okay look
there's a path
we have four again might as well use it
if you fail things sorry I don't know I
was going up there
oh I just follow you guys
follow
it
I hear kitty cat yeah she thinks I'm
done streaming because I haven't been
talking no no
I'm still streaming
people look over here there's a gate
there's a gate is it balder's gate I
must be it's the first gate we've seen
gotta be
oh no this is for the act two no this
leads to the Yankee threat dancing
but we can come here later but can we do
everything yeah not yet so but this I
wanted us to get the quest so we can
come back here
okay
okay yeah there's a good weapon in there
we we less less we lose it
okay
interesting
well we're to next lady might as well go
south
oh Tea House Tea House okay we're going
this house the underdark thing right
yeah yeah there's a really good weapon
staff for me there I heard yeah
I want to keep a lookout for it and we
gotta keep a lookout
that should be easy
[Music]
well
Which Way Tea House Tea House
flight a village everyone teleport again
okay
quick
um
there we go this way by the river
by the river
[Music]
if you right click on things you can
move it to Camp yeah send to camp and
it'll be in your storage box thing yeah
if one more person in chat tells me to
put clothes on I'm gonna take these
clothes off no
no thank you nice
okay
um
so tea house is down here Molly you take
the lead over here once we get there I
will do oh who's that over there dad I
baited you I'm not gonna take the
clothes off over there
they did reveal how many thirsty strange
people are in my chat but what's going
on
talk to them
hello Mario bedes Moshi Moshi
ah
be nice to The Hags
she's on
[Music]
something yeah she seems nice
how about you all just calm down this
has nothing to do with me goodbye lower
your weapons she's just an old woman
full
she's with the hag don't bloody stand
their gaping scared her what going for
the same outcome
I mean I've seen this somewhere before
we have to protect her yeah it will
smash and Destroy I'll play music
The Natural understanding
that's all that she is nice imagine
being so rude to hurt an old woman
he's got like blood all over her get her
granny gown what happened it sounded
like a heated argument oh nice thanks
are paid in Gold I like that option oh
yeah that's not lethal
you forgot about it again
[Music]
with her
wow she seems like such a nice lady
she's evil isn't she
no
why would she be even look at her at her
she looks so nice she stole that little
girl and the dudes were going to go
protect the kid
all right well can we loot him at least
see what they got if they've got one
don't get mad I mean it I'm only leaving
this note so you don't panic and do
something stupid I'm going to the hag
come on man so rude I owe it to Conor to
make things right you know he'd do the
same for me I'll be back soon so not a
word to ma'am all right she has enough
on her plate
and then yeah
something I didn't mean to oh
I don't think I can roll a 20. I rolled
a 20. oh there you go you rolled a 20.
let's have a bite to eat oh wow what the
is this like some Hansel and Gretel
ious
no it looks so pretty I don't want to
walk around here anymore
[Music]
okay oh yucky putrid bog we're in the
Bog bog beats what's going on
more poisoned apples
what is going on what is that who's this
little dude I'm not sure but I don't
want to know
girlington with a piece of gold hi
hi
diminutive creatures oh they look sick
gangster what's going on a funny
creature known
is that supposed to scare me buddy boy
pretending to be
breath and say bye
okay we had a little conversation there
yeah that was a conversation
yeah
food for bog hey
seems like there's so much to look
around here yeah it's a pretty big area
[Music]
nothing in the wooden crates
what are these stairs up here oh stairs
a frog
hold on a sec let's go down here first
before going up there there's a dude
there's a duder there's a guy wait wait
I'm talking to I'm talking to a frog I
think the frog doesn't really matter
until later no
what's wrong I don't know he's crazy
what are you croaking on about
he's stinky
spine
he hasn't taken a shower
something wrong with the Frog wrong
oh that all sounds bad
follow Cali Girls look at that where
look at that behind right
oh okay bye frog okay okay all right all
right okay
oh who's this
we'll kill it
a quick wit is rare indeed it was
actually pretty slow it took me about a
minute to answer same thing
whatever you say
what's wrong with her
why you take it it's a bargain it's a
bargain Lady of the house a more
innocent name than some I could we're
here for tea but it is what she is
wait what did I miss since the first
Darkness
and their knowledge is matched not much
it's just stinky not to ask a little
sneaky man
if you're full enough to pay their price
I look so at home here this just looks
like where I belong
it's your
uh what price is that
and the hardest to do without quit
speaking in riddles bro
who out him
I guess that she's a witch
who is it you're hunting this is like a
blade my friend
okay don't tell me I guess that throat
I would not put you in danger good yeah
that's not what this is about is it
Barbarian I like danger the truth no
yeah
yeah F1 but moriopa is gonna try I
believe in Mario babe
come on 2 20. plus four wait wait yeah
this is what I excel at I'm made to
intimidate
yeah yeah a little bit
big dummy now tell me what's going on
oh don't help him bring him back to
Baldur's Gate alive
absolutely not don't help him
we shared a a special moment we have
never met anyone named a Starion ever
he's no vampire we've met you can give
up your hunts hysterians under my
protection
some people were recently attacked in
the night
spawn
in the case of battle one of them stole
away with our children
oh we've been searching for the medicine
it what children believe this Astorian
knows exactly what happened that night
and where to find our little ones
don't hand them over
the children make him talk
so I ask again
is he known to you Daniel we've never
met asterian oh we've never met
there is no we've never met it's I'm
protecting him or I know him just leave
just leave just leave
just leave
no leave no oh I'm kind of curious
actually
don't give him he's not the type to come
quickly
quietly never I'd never tell you where
it is so help him
some people are saying they killed him
in pretty good loot apparently
ah I'm not going to help you find him
yeah
we kill him
you'll never heard a Starion I mean not
that I like him or anything you know we
did share a moment oh yeah sure
ooh so what happens with my Lightning
Charge
plus one attackers
consumed the next time you tell damage
what you gonna do what are you gonna do
when we go for him yeah
yeah you got nothing on me okay now you
do never mind good job good job what if
you go up to him in a starians in your
party I did that and I was like I
literally was like hey he's right here
on this there and was like what the
and
fight and I was like sorry it was a joke
a Starion sorry about them it's just a
joke
[Music]
it was very funny
pretty good gandrell's aspiration
there's a brand new bow for you if you
want here I'll pick up the stuff
that one wasn't was that one good one
good for me you didn't
yeah well good we can leave him here
like that I mean if you keep hitting him
they'll die eventually but
you want you want the bow qo do I wanna
I mean you already have a pretty nice
one right
happy with
I love a crossbow
um
or maybe should we kill him
yeah beat his ass
you dead now yeah now he's and now he's
dead
like Andrew sorry
go trap this arm kit that's exactly what
we need well let's see
um now that we got that guy maybe let's
go to the house yay
but I don't think we should jump in yeah
I think we should go into the house
first Maybe
babe don't drink from the well what the
no
stinky I'll never do that I guess we
could just go in the front yeah
we're gonna help the lady we need we
want to be rewarded I just don't trust
her though she's gonna hurt us nice no
hurry up it has bad feelings Spider
Sense
I don't know why you would have a bad
feeling oh my God look at that she looks
like Fiona
the green dress
oh she's pregnant
you look really dirty now take a bath
for a girl
I won't say it again this is messed up
poor girl I have some bad news for her I
killed you before
ask me all your guests so poorly I have
some bad news for her
be nice I'm scared what's going on
nothing or true side no
no I
nothing I mistook you for someone else
you
this is messed up
and he actually killed your brothers
pretty insane but yeah she did it she
did that Bros you guys are crazy
grow up not very convincing and I used
can I try one more time no three or four
we have four
go for it
oh up man are we gonna have a big
fight now
uh
one more time one more time please
we've got so much information
however if we don't get it this time
then
it's a critical failure critical
I mean I suppose that's what we deserve
your brothers damn they got us
anyway
she's just a drama queen
oh
whoa anyways at last sometime in the
cage should do her wow you're not mad
about what I just said
I was just a jerk
[Music]
transformation just like oh man my God
you're so right using Cali's
looking good
images
[Music]
oh I don't want a fighter
what I mean why not she should be easy
no the good thing is she gets invisible
I think it's better if we don't manage
to kill her right away anyway
okay I don't even see her anymore so
actually I don't know where these shoes
oh
no that was just amazing hand
a solo run right
yeah so that's what I'm saying oh
really yeah yeah what should we do I
don't know oh we can kill the red caps
that are that are attacking us
yeah okay and then we follow Where She
Went basically well she's still here
just invisible no
yeah for now she's she's running away
though oh okay
ah where are the red caps I don't know
bring him in what if we all just came
inside and closed the door do you think
they can open the doors
I think they can maybe they're too
stupid to open doors yeah
[Music]
Epic
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
says
[Music]
There Was His Hands kind of close to my
butt
right where it should be
yeah yeah copy copy oh yeah I don't know
why I went the other way maybe I can
maybe I can distract oh ah there she
goes okay she went through the
the fireplace run away
[Music]
yummy yummy
she's gone now let's focus on the red
cats okay
I come back and help
me
[Music]
you guys ain't
grumble
yeah
yeah nice one
you stood there like a statue oh
no
oh I'm dead right down and I get up
again yeah we're gonna break me down
nice
night we got this get up Wawa
stop come on somebody
that was a stick Burn yeah for real
oh
wow Larissa couldn't you have used that
magic hand to give me a hand
a teacher
I'm back up again
at all mommy mommy
oh what was that maybe I've given you
safety whoa
so safe
yeah with my Shields
yeah two left wait there was more
yeah I think they're on their way oh
yeah they're about to enter
your name
oh yeah play us a tune oh we'll battle
music yeah a little a little music to
jam to you know a jig I can't
why can't I hmm
oh
why can't I hmm what are you trying to
do
nice
nice okay one left I'm Gonna Save My
ranged weapons I wonder that's okay okay
I'm always like throw daggers on spares
I think
if you have some
oil
or bagel nice try
when in doubt
get him I wonder what happened to my bow
and arrow I need to do my bow and arrow
back
okay
I think I can throw some I can't throw
anything but why I think I need to be
enraged
um
see
yeah get mad
I probably could have been a bit further
away
you got one Health left
whatever
cool
wow
that's pretty rough I'm not doing so
well I'll give him a little tap I love
that
come on I guess
oh well
so there it's done for and she ran away
yeah
[Music]
okay we fall I'm gonna steal this stuff
I guess yeah
oh yeah
for me and Callie yeah
the chest I'm gonna open it open I took
it
see
lotion of Greater healing I steal
because I don't give a I don't give a
yeah yeah I steal everything yeah
everything
yeah she sucks there's also so much
bread
buttered
bumps
we do like buttered buns in this
household yeah
[Music]
yeah I love buttered bread sounds good
right about now cucumbers and what do
you call the
schnitzel
not the long stringy
chives with chives
chives isn't that the best thing I love
chives so simple right I literally never
understood putting butter on bread I
think it's weird
is so weird to me yeah that I wouldn't
do either
we're missing you
there you are
because butter is like a salty thing I
associate like bread with like jam and
stuff so oh I could still work with the
butter and there's unsalted butter I do
like garlic bread though oh yes
oh thanks
I look like that could be related to you
actually
yeah you're prettier
oh thanks tell me where the girl is
knowing what I think so I don't think we
care about the girl
she's gonna eat us or I'll make you try
oh we'd like to see you try
I don't care we're gonna go in and do it
oh there's a lot of funky things here
is that a headless person oh
it's pretty wacky wait what did I
perceive I personally I'm gonna talk to
this guy over here
for some reason it made me talk to the
tree so I'm in a cut scene sorry oh yeah
yeah glad to people through okay hold on
can I leave
uh
it's Wolves
and we have some other stuff
everybody's suffering yeah
yeah if you had to cry
cry that's too bad she's got quite a few
prisoners okay I'm gonna leave so Cali
can do this but I want to talk to Lauren
oh
this guy
what's wrong with him what's his problem
s
he does look like Legolas
yeah yeah he's a Legolas gone Gollum
mm-hmm
no no
can't stop can't then don't stop don't
stop just go your own way
poor guy give him a hug
no
why are you so much
he's gonna have a heart attack
I'm gonna die
mile as he twitches and whimper
it's to him you realize there's magic oh
my eyes are so wide and kind
whatever you're seeing it isn't real
no lies moriope would never lie to you
talking like this
others this is nonsense
oh I mean his stuff together always say
and it's not separated I think it's
it's uh
God everyone looks like you do elf it's
shocking I know
um
this guy must have been inside like a
lot of Mind flayer
he's so mean
he thinks we're out there any way you
can get him to not be uh later but we
have to continue uh so why don't you
look at this door Mario Fame
all right gnarled door
open sesame
[Music]
oils nice ass he pulled through
thanks this is pretty good we could just
stay here and look at this phone yeah
honestly honestly
time to chat and I'm here to kill them
you have like good leg muscles too
mm-hmm very nice
shrouded in the glow of the Divine
weapons brandished they charge into the
hex layer Leroy James
that's a blockade for each you're mine
for 30 more years
petal
nice leg the hag will be the least your
problems if you don't open up
barbarianism Roar do it
do it yeah
Roar
little ogre Roar
S
I wish that other guy would shut up
through the door hence formed shimmering
with a jerk you're pulled from the
vision
you feel the presence within shrink
terrified oh somebody did the door open
oh
open
this should be easy to find her from
here right
can you get in Kiara is talking to the
door
you see the gallery
you don't you just just walk through you
don't need to you don't need to talk to
it
there you go nice onward
let's do it
let's go run it laze
I'm the battle some randos yeah
non-lethal attack random people fight
they have to die
yeah
[Music]
can I read They're possessed but
okay I probably gotta go anyway
oh I can read nice incredible nice but
there was something in the way
apparently I don't know if this is true
but they are saying pickpocket the masks
and save them
yeah I picked up some masks no
pickpocket The Masks like take the masks
from them via pickpocketing
apparently apparently save them as in
rescue them yeah I think I don't know
oh it sounds not possible I guess we can
turn on non-lethal
it's it's an insta kill when you steal
the mask but we're gonna kill him anyway
never mind then yeah let's kill him
oh cool okay fair and square
sounds good to me
[Music]
oh she really doesn't want to oh
I feel kind of bad murdering all these
people yeah same hello
it's kind of complicated to not kill
them
[Music]
we'll go ahead and kill him yeah
yeah no one will know it's all happening
down here in the cave yeah no one needs
to know
our little secret our little murder
Secret
murder Secret
s
shall we Ollie
are you scared only a little bit right
I'm immobile because I'm frightened
oh wait you're not wearing any boots
yeah I would say yeah Reckless attack go
for it
that's the end of you and then
another frenzy strike on you nice
that was pretty sick
ah there we go whoops
they're knocked out I should just kill
him um
or just just take the masks uh you know
gotta go
yeah good idea
I could have looted
no nice
yeah yeah
everybody's in such good shape in this
game yeah
I love it
everyone's fit now he's going down so
annoying right he's archers man
something from below he's not very smart
is he
yeah oh yeah
oh nice I'm not sure I think we can wear
the masks
that seems not great yeah
I mean yeah weren't they being mind
controlled yeah you've got a good point
yeah yeah maybe I mean
do they carry anything besides the masks
a little bit but nothing really garbage
I take slime bomb
[Music]
let's see there must be another one over
here
you find something this is a waterfall
we can jump through it okay clean
totally did not I thought that we could
not go through there yeah we have to
jump I see
oh my gosh I did not uh
Lisa's Place yeah
um I would not short rest until we get
all the way down
uh yeah joining Field hold on my game is
glitched oh no are you okay
oh I'm fine
joining failed cannot join the party huh
that's really weird very out of the game
no it's just every time I say except it
like glitches out
I have to restart my game okay good
thing I just saved yeah
gotta restart the game no problem
that was super weird very super weird
very odd
oh God
some glitches here and there we can take
it I mean for the most part it's really
not that bad but yeah usually you still
run into them as you do with anything
play game
[Music]
good job
all right I'm pulling it back up and
then I'll invite you guys back yeah
okay
[Music]
please sing it for me Callie
down down down by the river why do I
still have a morning voice
hydrating properly are you drinking
water streaming like every day throat
yeah it's crazy
yeah yeah does it hurt when you talk
it doesn't hurt but it does feel like a
bit of a struggle to speak sometimes
yeah well while we're doing this I'm
gonna quick run and take an idol meeting
so I'll be right back okay I'll grab
your snacks ladies
grab your snacks
we'll feed and then I'll invite the
ladies hmm
mommy is not done streaming
[Music]
invites a game
game
by the game
Marissa
I invited everyone thank you
this movie yes
back in the game
yeah
working now
where are we okay here
look at that
oh narissa only has 21 HP
oh that's not great maybe a short rest
wait no wait don't don't short dress
until we get down there yeah but I can
throw them maybe she can drink a potion
of healing oh
she's so much better we have no short
rest left oh we don't yeah no oh
maybe big rest
we might want a big rest before we do
this oh yay
I'm fine with that but let me see
actually I've returned
welcome back thank you oh
we have to leave the the tea house
though because
yeah really yeah oh yeah cause the map
is red yeah okay
we can always come back though right
yeah yeah
nothing bad will happen surely
just potion of animal speaking yay I
wish that was real no I know right
right I wish
look
let's get out of here
we can see for your fancy magic lady
please
oh he's still talking yeah
Legends say he is still talking to this
day to this day
oh we can rest up here yeah
alrighty ladies to the camp we go yeah
[Music]
yay
oh will wants to talk I wanted to chat
someone want to talk to him
I'll talk
okay
he sees the burning see look you have a
butt chins rest
but I need some Botox Charming
thank you
older Raven guards been taken who sold
the forever I don't know
oh that's the guy who who the who were
supposed to rescue yeah from the fiery
building
yeah oh okay the one that died no they
they said he was kidnapped and that we
needed to get him back remember
okay and then he got the bow
then he lives
oh
um
what do we say
and the choice is clear we should rescue
Duke Raven guard that means a lot but
what about Raven crafts
don't save me Raven craft around
my father
no this is no drow plot these absolute
Nutters these true songs
he could leave Boulder's Gate to ruin
all the more reason to find him
he got him
but the future it was kind of cute
yeah
you should keep secrets like this for me
will no hmm and you're right yeah
yeah
[Music]
damn wanted you to know the blade not
the shadow he left behind
deep okay
we'll do it for you we'll see you guys
okay what else nobody else wants to talk
I think oh I'm talking to a Syrian again
yeah
yeah he's asking he's asking I told him
someone was looking for him
uh
but yeah why
sent him why else tell me about this
Hunter he always sounds so offended
whenever he talks I know
something ferocious surely
Camp
um
okay what are those vagabonds why would
they I suppose I shouldn't be surprised
what do you know about the children
asterian yeah what do you know about the
kids man
example of me to show what happens to
runaways well maybe he thinks death is
too good for me I mean true
um we just have to be vigilant keep our
wits about us
and kill any Monster Hunters on site
I do
I love Monster Hunter
I'm not good at it though
she just called me beautiful what
leave
[Music]
I'm gonna kill you you are my enemy
narissa and shambles
all right you got your friend zoned I
hate you every time lord
[Laughter]
oh what the oh no oh it's coming
I remember this part yeah same oh
if even why hot
well
I've been naughty and you know what
happens when you're naughty God's damn
it
anyone but her
aren't you a luscious thing now
I'm just getting comfy
[Music]
I'm Will's Patron the fount of his power
will has a patreon I guess
I think
oh
whoa she's in control
but carlock's still breathing I've taken
more pleasant shits than you miss all
day this can be buried after that's lady
up mizora don't even mention zarya
Devils only
she's a tiefling not a monster oh
precious that vocal delivery is really
good but his face does not match
targets shall be limited to The Infernal
the Demonic the heartless and the
soulless
carlak meets the criteria by virtue of
having no heart
[Music]
will
the last
last at all
you better not lay your damn finger on
Carlo don't you worry yeah oh they all
approved
sticks nice
must still pay his price
to which
is
[Music]
not well
so gaining their essence
light the wheel
I mean is there any way to attack her in
the camp no come on game
oh he just got horns that's not bad yeah
he's still looking great he got horny
bonked yeah
that's
a bit like that what the hell suits him
yeah I promise yeah you're looking good
the price paid
no the terms get used to the new form
Pat
There's No Going Back
some magic even I can't then why would
you do it wow
um
I have a swimsuit with a cut like her
dress
yeah
wow take pictures for me
send pics
I think I know which one you're talking
about don't make me jealous like this I
have two that have a cut like that
actually
don't do this to me good yeah
oh so many people want to talk ah what
do we listen to First
[Music]
oh yeah do it bro
when
very presumptuous
once off hey don't do it look something
don't do it for the content
[Laughter]
[Music]
and now my game is glitch
nope I guess that's what I deserve of
course
if joining failed cannot join the party
is full no companions can be dismissed I
mean the game disagrees trying to
protect my viewers I'm gonna commit
seppuku
continue continue
all right well hold on a second uh we
might need to
eh the screen says black oh no am I
gonna get jump scared with something
lewd
[Music]
this glitch is really bad
like before like last time yeah it's the
same thing if we have I swear to God if
we have to redo everything we can just
get past the text too yeah yeah
this is really annoying
I don't know why
what's your screen look like
oh my God it's kind of weird oh hold on
a second uh
it says it just
it's like how do I describe can't join
party full
party can I say it no problem and then
it flashes again all right well now we
wait to be invited again
so
we shall save more often now if this
happens again well we I mean look all we
did was reload go to Camp do that scene
and then you know so we we really
haven't lost that much progress but
still yeah well here's the thing I can
switch to mouse and keyboard that's fine
but I'm gonna have to relearn the game
I mean that's what people are saying but
I don't know
so easy
yeah there's not much
yeah a little point-and-click yeah it's
just point and click
no party like a memorial party because
the Maury party is full and no
companions
but your mouth
hmm oh very odd well maybe if I stop
using a controller it'll work all right
let me get you guys back in the game
yeah
we'll redo the will scene well we'll
have to re-talk to will first and then
we'll have to do that again
no
I refuse
horny horny girls
it's for the content here I can't
believe I can't believe Cali is so horny
I didn't know this it's like a Content
are you talking about it Kelly you're
just so crazy I didn't expect that from
you
nerissa you're the one that had nudity
turned off on the game whereas I kept it
on let's not go there I know I had it on
what do you mean
let's not go there
oh yeah there's one leader of the the
horny Patrol here and let me tell you
it's not me bless you
no I just turned to nudity
let's see how do I go how do we go to
the camp Oh we gotta get out of here uh
yeah read the lifted Powers okay let me
switch back over to game shall we
expect again bless you thank you
um
go away yeah we're going okay chill dude
all right let's see map
map ping is it map salute you cannot
fast travel from this area oh we gotta
leave it I guess yeah yeah we have to
walk out again
hey you guys talked will I'm just gonna
tell Starion again about the guy same
text Skip through unsettling places
are you guys at the camp yeah
I have no clue where it is
please hold on camera
oh this is so weird to control
how do I Zoom around do I how do you Pan
the cake oh there we go you can rotate
it like that
maybe was it back up here
interesting
you know you don't have to it's it's
okay I'll feel oh there it is got it
there's the door
oh yeah I I know no one left behind
submit me you did it all right
hey thanks
hey hey
go
enjoying the camera will be a little
it'll be a learning process but we'll
figure it out
your cookies if you are a little stinky
no I I took a shower today
[Music]
yeah after she's done talking to carlak
we can just go sleep redo that cutscene
yeah end the day
[Music]
what does that remind me of oh there we
go huh
well there we're ready for sleeping yeah
ready for sleep before the sleepies and
the day let's end the day what does that
remind me of
um
we talked about this before
oh is it me again okay
uh get out of my camp
I'm trying to say the same things again
yeah yeah
we can't hurt
he's going wild I'll be getting crazy
oh that's it right yeah and then oh
um I don't know what else to tell you
bro I I'm gonna I'm I'm I'm I can't live
any longer
I'm talking to Will
okay good everybody has nice
conversations
it's rough buddy
well I mean
Mario videos wins by virtue of being you
know big and buff I understand I get it
I can't blame him he wants to put his
hands on the market Wants What It Wants
You Know can't blame him
I mean I guess I'll come find you after
everyone is asleep I guess
I guess
do it
we're all uh doing our best here
image but narissa was trying to do was
very homie like Anyway this whole time
she's trying to steal your man like what
the hell
I'm getting Shadows
she's a drama queen
she's always hurting
I'm gonna go Snoop on you guys this
conversation I can't to the terms or
circumstances of The Pact
I can tell you most all else but The
Pact
wow is that supposed to be Shadow art
yes
it was my proudest deed
it was worth the sacrifice well I can
give you one back
is my solemn word yeah I get you
something are you okay
what's on your mind
think of it as
as long as I pay there will be here
should I ever stop baby oh that's the
kitty cat Battlefield
I watched Garfield today
it was cute
fluffy
we're gonna get another Mario face scene
I don't know if I want that to be honest
I mean you don't have to watch are they
still making up
but the artifacts
I'm listening I'm snooping somebody
else's relationship let me take it back
the best I can do is to stay close
it's real Snoopy eventually I'll need to
take she complained about Garfield not
showing his balls
I don't know what that said okay dad
said you complained it and show his
balls cats balls all right aesthetically
pleasing you are that is the strangest
thing I've ever heard someone say like
when when they do like uh drawings of
cats and they include the little cat
butt and a little cat you know yeah
Garfield didn't have that and there were
so many shots of his like back where you
could only see his his big chunky
stomach and not not the balls though it
was like something's missing
man
why can't we go to sleep
what stop canceling someone keeps
canceling
[Laughter]
oh
goodness gracious
Chihuahua hey this is a great this is a
great time to go ahead and let you guys
know that it's time to look at a
cutscene
[Music]
maybe I have a big announcement you guys
something brand new screen now so great
news everybody
oh it's over oh wow anyway I mean why
didn't you make your announcement anyway
I mean no no go ahead
yeah yeah it's the Vine
what vinyl
let's go
um yeah I asked I asked ahead of time
the ladies said that I could oh yeah it
is showing her
oopsies
um it was it was secretly secretly shown
there just kidding huh it's not a secret
because you guys definitely saw it right
um oh God the bgm is so loud sorry
nothing I asked I asked the others
permission to be allowed the show
because I have to because in about in
about seven minutes
my my brand new Ep jigo 6 the EP is
being released in a big old record look
at this it's vinyl
Bingo vinyl record this is the shill
hours by the way everybody's gonna show
some stuff hopefully everybody's
yeah check it out you guys in about
seven minutes correct so be sure that
you check the link there's gonna be a
big old big old Link in the description
check it okay make sure that you click
make sure you yeah you grab it before
it's gone because I don't know if we'll
restock this bad boy so you wanna you
wanna get it quick you guys you'll want
to get it quick congratulations on the
final Cali
thank you you guys I appreciate it yeah
it's the Mori store thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
it's the morning for you guys Maury
store has really fast shipping by the
way don't restart you have a more store
yeah there's a universal Universal made
it uh it's a Maury store it ships very
fast to us
um
I'm not sure I I think it does
does it ship to Europe because I know I
have EU Beats I don't know it I don't
know if it ships fast but to Europe but
oh it's a US base it depends I think it
depends on the country but oh yeah it
does ship to Europe but um it's it
probably won't be fast it works here
yeah that's fun worldwide you should I
know but I never wanna I know there's
gonna be one person who's like those are
shipped to my country
sorry I messed up I made a mistake
anyway you guys can get it and I have a
couple more images to Joe sorry for
people that aren't on my stream that
can't see yeah be sorry go to Cali go to
Kelly's to check if you if you want to
see pictures of it you want to click the
link in the description it'll take you
to where it's going to be sold
um but yeah it kind of looks like this
and then uh there's some of urana's art
that's also going to be included it says
sample on it because no no thieves No
Stealing No Stealing yeah no thievery no
thievery but yeah
yeah then you can be a thief and then
you can feel it and that's totally cool
totally cool no problem no problem
um let me get the link I don't know if
if the if they're gonna paste the link
in there hold on a second I'm gonna put
the link in the description myself
because I am my own master
and I can I can do my own
yeah I sure can so yeah that was what I
wanted to
um promote for today and um yeah
the description is now updated so grab
your coffee yes
[Music]
just kidding uh but it is really cool it
makes a nice decoration piece you can
frame it you can play it on your
phonograph
Etc so please check it out
um who's next on the the show yeah it
sounds like we're in
the game afterwards we're not by the way
yeah we're gonna keep playing it's just
it's chilling yeah very very specific
timing no skip ad yeah the very sorry
could not change it
but uh yeah Kiara's next yeah I recently
released an album it's still open for
pre-order uh link is also in the
description if you want to get a
physical version and oh surprise
actually today I released the Korean
version of do you it was so good yeah
because it was actually one year
anniversary of do you so I thought let's
make a Korean version because it already
sounds like K-pop let's go yeah so album
and uh Korean version of do you and
pineapple MV is still out there to be
streamed yoroshiku please please take a
look at it and yeah keep on streaming
the album so because it's my first one
so I hope it can do well
everybody is great yes there's something
for everybody all the songs yeah it's my
first my first have a physical like
music thing because all my singles
before are like online only digital only
and this one you can actually get as a
physical thing yeah so very special
yeah yeah that's it stream point of view
point of view
anything else ah
um let's see oh uh this Friday or
Saturday depending on what time zone
you're in uh but Saturday for uh c
um I'm going to be appearing at Thai
comic oh yeah uh yeah it'll be my first
panel ever so I'm kind of really nice
for it but um I'm calling my mom so she
can you know coach me and teach speaking
Thai better so I can I can talk to
everyone I'm really nervous but I'm
excited uh lots of please
[Music]
cool that's so cool that you so quickly
get a con appearance that nice nice nice
I hope you get to speak sometime let's
go
Flex those skills yes gotta Flex
I apart from my streaming schedule I
don't have anything I have a collab with
bibu next week I think on Tuesday
Yeah Tuesday Tuesday me and Boo-Boo are
doing a chat where we're going to talk
about the first night that we spent
together
give us the details we will so please be
sure to be their typical uh time at 8pm
C team
on my channel so look at look at
Marissa's song covers yeah yeah check
out my song covers so I can release
another one
yeah that's all from me
being busy with putting out things so
support that yes please yeah everybody's
working hard to give you guys cool stuff
so yeah yeah
thanks for for supporting us
again I'm talking to everybody I'm just
seeing what they have to say this
morning it's so funny
oh man let me fix my little sensor image
I'll just keep it right in front of me
it's nice weather at your calling
it's nice weather we're having today
oh wow well telling me his life story
there you go you can have will yeah I
guess I'll go for will or Gail what
Everyone likes me more
he's horny just like you what
is he yeah I mean horny as and he's got
horns now oh oh I see yeah
yeah you make a really good point
I heard you were making fun of me in
your stream in your member stream Kiara
unbelievable
[Laughter]
information anyway I don't know it's
bad I've just heard it oh courtly Dan
he's gonna
go yeah
what's up lizelle give it some time
sorry that no one's talking to you are
you lonely
[Laughter]
did you hear about it or are you a
member
I I can't be a member anymore
oh yeah right I don't think we can we
can each other it's a shame it doesn't
let us I mean you can handle the private
account
um
the farmer's dearest fruit naturally he
was no apple no Peach who are they
can learn a lot from fairy tales
why is he acting like this
I mean the dude just got transformed
like yeah I feel a little bad for him
yeah
and given the circumstance
I do it again
price to pay for
is he okay sickness cough
um sorry little guy I had but one road I
could travel
for now you have a dozen the hundred
a thousand to choose from
a road that leads to it yeah this really
wants to make me this makes me want to
play more on my own I know right I know
right let's see all what happens to all
the characters exactly
yeah it's such a different game playing
with everybody it is
in the river of blood finally someone
approved of something I did
it's a lot like that
can't please everyone can't please
I mean I feel these ridges snaking down
you're just too sexy to mention a few
bucks
I'm sorry you were just born that way
man
what do you see oh
dude
quite the handsome devil it's because
you know the heart looking
oh she's trying to raise them up
maybe even a beast hungry okay but will
do you understand that she is also
tiefling now yeah like
I'm a monster and I'm like hello
there's so many there's so many he
approves every time I talk to him
nice
yes
gotta get my approval up even though we
can't check because we can't put them on
our team
yeah for real
I found him in the fields flanked by a
goblets you just gotta believe his
mother's corpse you know what if the
approval only goes to moriope
she just blessed
with some kind of special Magic
[Laughter]
I don't know is friendships
angry at myself too true so long for me
to see the coasts I don't understand why
there's two of Gail
don't question it I I am questioning it
don't question it and it's nice to meet
someone it's just a thing that he does
he just does that sometimes confidence
in the
as my Ally
yeah I heard this before Mr Nice Guy
countless nights
if you want to play the hero and be the
nice character in the game will is
perfect
yeah he loves you when you're nice
laughs
she could clone yourself wouldn't you
what a good argument I mean yeah but
what would you do with the clone of
yourself if you had one make it do your
chores what if it had a mind of its own
and it may just also want itself you
want to make out with yourself Kiana
what kind of she's standing here with
nothing but the clothes
I mean you know yourself best don't you
I'm sorry one of my jailbirds just said
something funny and I need to repeat it
to you guys but they said you should
have turned a Starion into the Monster
Hunter and gone the full yandere round
yeah
that would be pretty funny actually he
almost turned him in
yeah maybe next playthrough yeah next in
Another Universe I'm sure no I refuse I
would never
it's okay I'm I'm too attached that's
right I'm too attached to every single
one of our one of our things what are
the companions I'm too attached to all
of them I don't want anything that to
happen to them we should go we should
leave the kids let's leave let's go kill
the hag let's get out of here yeah
the long rest leave Camp there we go
back down gotta learn how to play again
yeah let's go
foreign
[Laughter]
waterfall
be careful
is this a bug where you don't see them
oh okay yeah I had that bug before that
can't be good do you see the fumes girls
no no but I see the flowers
okay that's nice actions helpful
jump
uh we should save after we get down here
we can uh throw things onto the noxious
fumes thingies
I I just figured out how to jump
okay thanks
wherever you want to go
okay obviously they will just find their
way
I'm gonna learn how to use the camera
you're like a little baby bird yeah the
camera took some getting used to but now
I would not change my form of gameplay
for anything oh what's this at least I
figured it out eventually yeah so we can
like throw something on it that's
normally we should we have a like a
graphic glitch right now I think
normally we should be seeing like fumes
yeah
wait wait wait wait wait wait don't go
away
for everybody
short Rush before we go in didn't we
just do a long short short rest and then
heal or uh save save
enough all right now let me figure out
how to speak again okay you quit Escape
how do I do a quick save Escape
F5 yeah okay
yeah if you want to see like items press
alt and you see what's lying around
without
hold yeah alt currently you don't
there's nothing really around okay got
it I'll remember that
all right onward let's get it
yes let's find stuff leave me here
you want me to kill you maybe
do we care about her and
I mean it would be cool to save a life
but I mean we don't have to
[Music]
oh yeah
oh I see the head see where the wind
takes up
hello hag
hello I'm gonna attack her
wait you could really use it
real fast oh you're in a cutscene oh oh
I'm sorry I thought I thought it dragged
everywhere no no we're in it we're not
wearing it
mean
[Music]
I'd like to see you try maybe you're
alive and alive
I don't think that'll work
you can shoot several people
I killed your brothers why do you care
about me
shut up she doesn't care about you
yeah but she says just get out of here
please like she has any kind of concern
for me shut the up
she does
oh that was like half my house yeah
good luck girl remember you have potions
so mean even though I killed the fan uh
I guess I guess I'll save her there you
go
which one's real
I swear I had a bunch of them
maybe I don't I guess we'll Frenzy
someone want to attack one of them
I already did I got rid of another one
[Music]
gross okay I won't do that spell yet
then the shame
end turn is that the real one
okay
yes
um what a coward making clones
yeah I can't believe
what a cute birdie is that yours Kiara
yeah I brought a raven tea party yeah
oh my God it's like you like me or
something and there's a murder
right
a group of is there always it only crows
is there a difference between there's a
frozen a group of ravens the murder of
crows is yeah it's an unkindness of
ravens
[Music]
group of animal names so funny I wish I
knew
see I wish they weren't invisible no
wait it's the one
okay actual the wet one I can beat up
the one that's not what you can beat
them so the one that one that is wet I
should not beat up yeah the one that is
okay okay yeah let's see where is the
other one
oh yeah right uh-huh foreign
yeah the one that's on level one versus
the one that's on level five yeah yeah
oops that's not what I meant to do but
all right oh God actually I didn't need
to do that either
oh
[Music]
I made our decision easier yeah we made
a decision so let's keep going
[Music]
happens to the best of us
it's fine it's fine it's fine
brain empty
the bow there he
she's really not that helpful anyway
yeah
um inventory okay there we go inventory
and then my I have a yeah cause like
when you save her she's like super
ungrateful apparently okay I mean
validly yeah
I mean well yeah because we did kill her
family so yeah yeah
here by her own
her own choice so she didn't really want
to be safe saved
yeah so you kind of interfered and then
you know she doesn't need to be great
why would she thank you for something
she didn't ask for
it doesn't happen
oh you're right
I'll use an action equip
ment they need help not letting me
oh no oh
just kidding I don't have any more I get
it and turn
this is terrible
oh
good much
he's annoying I'm just better with
weapon you know
um
hope your soul is in good hands
oh
yeah no nothing yeah
go Raven go
rage charge
yeah tell her
oh let's go we're doing it guys
figuring it out it's all coming together
oh man I need to get on the high high
ground
yeah um
yeah me and your Raven are beating her
up it's sick let's go my Raven didn't do
no he's trying his best just pick
her eyes out should be as he is
good luck
I mean bro
if you hated that made her really upset
yeah you're bleeding look at that oh
oops
she's wet right now yeah guys did just
realize the girl that we killed there
was a child inside of her body it's fine
baby death Ah that's no good
well I'll keep that in mind for my
personal playthrough I guess
please kind of forgot about that
I find him to return
double kill then you wouldn't be begging
then you wouldn't be begging for your
life right
so how about we be civilized about this
hmm
I have something you want
um what are you gonna do Mario babe
continue I want to hear what they have
I can give you power anything you want
you want to be stronger tougher smarter
done
let me go ability score plus one that's
pretty cool I mean that's kind of cool
we can just beat her up again if she
comes back to life
give me power the more the better the
more the Power of Choice
it's sad you have to eat it yeah it's
her scalp yeah
I mean
yeah before I changed my mind if I ever
see you again you'll be fertilizing this
swamp again
glad that we have an understanding peace
it gives you great power yes
maybe strength min max the strength I
think
yay um the marina necklace yeah maybe
it'll be useful someday
[Music]
yeah
yay
scalp a small price to pay yeah maybe
someone's scalp what are you gonna what
are you gonna go for
strength so I can smash more
big smashing I don't know what these are
all these potions potions take them
free potion what's that what's the
mushrooms I don't know take it
make everything
it teleports you if you go there all
right then shall we get out let's go you
guys not everything right yep yeah okay
let's go
okay that was interesting wow where
could we be
I wonder
yeah another day in the Bog
yay
oh coffin that's her her guy yeah this
is her husband Marina's
can someone talk to the dead
um yeah uh maybe you gave me a thing
that helps me talk to the dead right
yeah you have what you should talk to
the dead necklace
having a new skill bar yeah it says rare
speak with the Dead
um in my skill oh yeah there it is
let's go hold on let me scroll
hold on let me turn turn it around I bet
I can oh yeah narissa also has the
ability now because she read the book
that gives her the speaker
Target Undead
but he is dead
did you get the the one it's called
bitter I do have bitter divorce can you
use
I don't know how to use it pass spell
oops okay
must be playable I wonder
no I don't think did I eat it I don't
think I think it's because
dad that you can't continue yeah
probably that's rough fine that's rough
buddy
I mean I understand though it makes
sense but
[Music]
I have her necklace should I leave it
with him no just wear it and there's
something we can sell it doesn't work on
all the day if I wear it maybe even
somehow no the guy is Undead not dead so
apparently he's a zombie and that's why
we can't talk to him
uh okay I see well
that's that I guess what do we do next
guys
ladies I'll leave it up to you good
question something short you're dark
oh I guess we could go to the underdog
didn't we go there last time yeah but we
didn't finish yeah we entered briefly
yeah we could yeah head down
definitely want to get some health back
maybe a short rest cell unite yeah sell
sell night
s
fellow night
um how do I quick travel
um
and then click solo Knight Outpost okay
don't go so fast Cali is not even here
oh I'm just gonna grab a weapon and then
I'll be back
okay
it's a barred sword
the one that's right by the entrance
just don't get into trouble I'll try
uh
[Music]
um oh thank God
everything grand for us I'm gonna get it
yeah we killed that dude too the
Minotaur I'm not gonna go in I'm just
gonna what he has nothing just kidding
she got it
yay Bard sword
all right am I solo play for what came
to the underdark from a different place
and I I wasn't able to enter where we're
standing in right now I just explored
everything outside
well I think the South idea from here
you need to collect like three pieces or
something oh
Apple I think okay
there's a staff of the Moon made and
what's that oh fancy
all right
I think beautiful good place where we
could go here in the underdark okay take
us okay lead the way the Mushroom City
I love oh that's the mycelium it's not
what it's called but I like those oh my
God the chicken
whoa earthquake we just gotta get down I
don't know where the weight is let me
equip my crossbow really quick
oh wait the shaking isn't that a sign of
the that monster oh yeah oh yeah
was it oh
let's get out of here let's keep walking
no let's keep moving
okay okay
through here
I don't know what I'm seeing yeah no
wait oh she's just talking to me
oh that's still your mind
there's a voice talking to you
okay he's done coming now we can go
big deal they're coming who cares I
ain't afraid of no ghosts
it's like I have three Olympic pasta in
the pasta just remember we all share the
illicit powers are those oh what's this
oh
a wooden chair nice stuff
whoa Olympic Powers I haven't actually
used these yet
um concentrated blast yeah I haven't
used these yet either yeah
there's a Minotaur up there I've used
one
oh I just used one yeah remember we all
share them but are they all combined we
all share them yeah
okay well good thing I didn't use more
oh I just used one I'm gonna use one as
well huh
yeah
uh click click click on your inventory
and then you you see the little things
in the Middle top of the page that opens
up click on the one that says a lipid
powers
I thought yeah we we had three
but we can find more there's a lot of
them in the game
we're all gonna share mm-hmm yeah help
check which one do I pick
they're not shared yes they are
they absolutely are shared I mean we
don't all get the same but we we
collectively all have the same amount of
brain worms there's Minotaur up there
bookie
I don't know where it is okay I saw it
said three and I popped one thing and
then I heard people say I used one and
now there's only one left
careful all right eat The Witcher I know
I already ate the hair guys look at my
inventory
wait I eat it look look up here
it has been consumed
there's bad guys
[Music]
well you did your best
um
[Music]
what well that's okay we can do a ranged
attack that should be fun I'm just
kidding it was not fun difficult
position to start in yeah me too
oh oh well we'll get through it
where is the second one
we'll find it
oh I'm surprised I hit I only had 55
percentage
we'll be fine we won't die oh maybe we
will but it'll be six
oh he doesn't have that much health this
will be fine
[Music]
oh yeah
that's awful oh God
[Music]
Force tunnel
I want to try and use that
okay
yeah back up okay wait I'm gonna put
something
here don't walk past it
oh okay
nice
[Music]
that's so broken I love it so much
yeah no he's super dead we just got the
other one
yep just one more left
nice
cool
oh
yeah
did he get hit by the clown daggers yeah
I think so
whatever
okay nice one ladies good teamwork
here's a question of something I haven't
figured out how do I turn off that
how do I turn it off
[Music]
you decide concentration
I borrow somewhere
[Music]
somewhat sounds fun concentrating on it
you want it I have the answer I don't
know someone who does that what was it
bludgeoning thank you yeah
vulnerability to bludgeoning damage if
someone wants it
you can just take it from my inventory
sharing your inventory
yeah well I mean it's all our inventors
the party's inventory
how about disarming first I disarmed one
if you would just wait can I take this
hat in your inventory Cali chicken okay
I'll take it if you want something just
fast you can probably whoa what happened
there
they just disappeared critical failure
of disarming oh the Trap yeah where am I
Theresa walked through it
did you just I broke it I broke the
chest
guys why didn't you crawl up
the roomba's going crazy downstairs yeah
I know I can't get down yeah you can
there's a thing over here a mushroom
jump on the mushroom yeah like Mario
yeah there's stuff up here though if you
want to look cool goodies yeah oh
goodies I know this place love goodies
it's looting time
[Music]
oh everything's
everything's everything is locked yeah
[Music]
yeah I can attack it
back
spoils are there for the taking
Alchemist fire
that's it
the Ring of Fire
you girls being aggressive
oh my God yeah we're little Luke goblins
oh my God
I can't believe I can't set wood on fire
I know
[Music]
what if we just break it salutenberg
that
without disarming it oh it's got a trap
oh I got got you got you I didn't see it
had a trap on it
I just disarmed it okay yeah there you
go
okay where I disarmed it but now we need
a key
ah Classics
[Music]
around here
lock picker do your thing
do your thing oh there's skulls in here
nice rolls
such a ring of fire you're worm today I
like that song so I don't blame you yes
Johnny Johnny good man
break it
oh it's pretty sturdy
lock pick
oh this should totally be possible okay
yeah there you go yeah open sesame
oh we opened it
lots of goodies
Arrow of darkness and arrow of ill Mater
yeah broken I already looted everything
here okay
it's like we got all the goodies
all right let's go down
to uh mushroom land
I like mushrooms I'm happy to go to the
mushrooms I don't like to eat them but I
like to look at them
I would agree with that they're
responsible yeah aesthetically mushrooms
are great eating not so much unless it's
a Milky reason like accessories or so it
means sauce
a mushroom sauce I think I can still I
can still eat but just mushrooms that
are not mushroom pasta sauce that's what
I want for a day oh that sounds good
don't make me hungry
I'm gonna make you hungry unless you're
gonna feed me ah there's the people wait
wait who's
yeah you talk to them yeah okay hello
careful mushroom people
listen
swallowed by a cause turbulent
ation wow they look cool yeah it looks
thick are these little mushroom
villagers yeah mushroom people cool
oh he's got a funny face
they all look so shiny beautiful a
single Melody rises above the others
Ross world
[Music]
the sovereign
threatening
um
your best
I I'm Adventure
yeah there you go Welcome to the fungals
look at that booty nice
[Laughter]
booty yeah
it's not quite good enough
true intent
yeah mushrooms
all right good welcoming
yay
well do you want to live in a mycinoid
company Music Company
yeah you'd have to live here Underground
that reminds me of that's the that's the
sovereign
shiny like you
close but follow one person
yeah
who wants to lead the way I want to
follow
[Music]
oh is this a shot
oh blurg what a name
in my chat is saying Cali taking a
compliment is she feeling okay
I'm trying to learn
trying to learn my face yeah that's a
big old hand in your face
with you like us
does he have a worm I don't think it's a
true soul I wonder
um
he's a fun guy
to improve conditions
curious to find the surface dweller here
what has brought you down so deep
wanna chill looking for sure I'm I'm
lost
could I ask what you were searching for
to begin with
mushrooms uh
affected by an illicit tadpole
it's a miracle you're still intact you
must be worried sick but have no fear I
have a friend who may be able to escape
it is
a pole inside her head but she hasn't
turned we're special
is this the one that is he the one
oh
he's the last one yeah let's have him
take out our tadpoles ah try
um help open your mind
he seems friendly yeah he seems like a
nice guy use our lipid Powers it's kind
of sad yeah totally let's do it uh okay
[Music]
okay all right let him in let's see if
it's that easy
the twin word it feels
ew
transformation
is nice yeah
with some form of State
wait is this the one you can beep no
oh okay it's bad what a shame
uh can you tell
your house
and even without the shield the
extraction would involve severe cranial
trauma
Ukrainian
that doesn't
house I have healing magic disrespect
but one can only heal so much man
[Applause]
but not to worry
should you transform oh well I don't
want to transform that's the whole point
damn
I never set foot on one mice
they were they were warships during the
greatest eras of the illicit Empire
plane from their decks his design was
lost
the gift Rebellion
[Music]
interesting oh that's why they were
dragons or something
okay thank you I guess of course
I'm sorry I cannot assist you in its
well Big Ups anyway
yeah no idea an idea
notes
or substances substances
uh uh what are we talking about what
kind of alchemy
from
what a silly word right
I like that
sounds like sphincter
[Music]
bones
why you sound so surprised I just ruined
it you ruined it no I don't like it
anymore most of these
according to plant confused
that approach them
the tongue is
self-explanatory we have to eat a tongue
you
um other mushrooms okay lovely so where
do I find these mushrooms the underdark
of course although they are quite rare
and their Discovery perilous
I imagine Lenoir would have them in her
possession she served mistra as a cleric
oh
ah
all right where's she live she lives the
Southwest when I last saw although her
Tower does have a tendency to move weird
it's a line interesting
Lenore has always been a lonely sort
nature was her only companion
[Music]
um
to join the society but who asked you
her experiments he knows a lot right
yeah
okay
um all
I'll come back when I find
I find I like this too
yeah that was nice oh can we steal from
them no no no don't you dare don't don't
steal don't steal
not gonna steal but does somebody need
to sell some stuff oh yeah let me no I
like to be blue is very full on her
inventory yeah
I think after we're done like like we
can explore the city a little bit more
and then we could end it yeah it seemed
like a good a good place
[Music]
oh Cali's talking
I mean I thought this was the shopkeeper
but he's like going through a bunch of
weird stuff right now so I don't know
yeah he first wants to talk
um
shopkeepers always so talkative why are
they so okay
but I can I can sell him stuff
yeah
if possible
okay do you have anything interesting to
trade
all right let me make it quick oh I have
a lot of swords
no you can keep them to throw tea I know
which is why I kind of don't want to get
rich what about uh sell all jewelry that
isn't useful right yeah yeah jewelry and
all items
you could tell a lot of your greatswords
and stuff can I throw the great sword
yeah
yeah I might want to hold on to it then
you want to know a fun trick
yeah do we still have the girl we killed
junk no menthara I don't think so yeah
oh okay because you can do his math you
can collect dead bodies and keep them in
your inventory and then you can eat dead
bodies for big damage because they will
that's pretty awesome what the heck
what about yes we don't need the masks
anymore right now
no okay away with you that would be
pretty cool I do like that that is
deadly
yeah I enjoy that
um I'll sell all these poison apples in
my own playthrough I've been collecting
dead bodies
and keeping them at my Camp so I can
look at them and remember my spoils
oh pretty base
wow
when the wearer gains lightning charges
they also gain three temporary hit
points one of you guys might want that
um oh does lighting charges help because
I'm lightning
I think so you should grab that I also
have a weapon that gives me Lightning
charges automatically
so oh nice now you could really use that
so maybe you should buy that after I'm
done in here oh something he's selling I
have lightning yeah on my shoes actually
yeah he's selling something called the
lifebringer it's like a tiara looking
thing oh wow Tiara fully hour
Tiara for Liara
and then I have to do math oh gosh okay
oh no you
can you get to balance it oh I see
there we go wow that's so nice I didn't
notice that okay
all right I'm done
go ahead
and do it
do your shop stuff
lurg
s
what a silly name dude
what a silly little guy I'm just such a
silly little guy indeed
wow I can't look at what's in the chest
without like opening it and stealing
right
no you will you will make everyone here
fight you don't do it I'm great
it's not great let me save really quick
I'm not gonna do it of course yeah yeah
of course of course you're just thinking
about it every once in a while no it's
good because honestly here I kept
accidentally clicking on the barrel
stock and they will all attack you if
you do that because they think you're
trying to steal
um not pleasant
what the
oh
the Mind flare can remove your tadpole
if you talk to them
yeah but why would I want to do that
what why didn't you just say
okay
okay really quickly to that is not true
really yeah no they're lying don't
listen to him
oh the head could have removed it though
if you would have not tried to kill her
really yeah
she she just this is your eye powers
from it
yeah which is why I kind of don't want
to give it up yeah yeah but she would
kiss your eye and it would give you a
special skill too that you can only get
from the hag had you not intimidated her
right away
true I guess yeah
well sometimes we just got to be true to
the characters we play you could have
looked even cooler okay
the trader has no more no more money
okay uh wait oh no more money okay
although your weight looks fine there's
I know but I have an Ingot I wanted to
sell there's another Trader down here
oh
they're both Merchants interesting
this lady yeah let him dry
[Music]
um
okay
can I talk to you yeah that's his name
Bello he's cute
cutie
hello little buddy
that if you can talk to animals wait I
have animals oh yeah
are you guys killing people what are you
doing
oh
yeah
the lightning thing
yeah I guess I'll buy it um
oh the hag can double your inventory
space that's wacky
yeah sounds tough though and complicated
I think so
should I wear it guys we'll see
yeah where what
the Tijuana yeah Tiara for Liara yeah
see how it looks on you
um
this one
oh did you grab it uh
uh grabbing now
okay I own it yeah yeah that should be
useful for your lightning stuff
yay
we all right now he also got some money
back good for him
now
are we all done trading yeah I'm done
let's I'm done explore should we talk to
the guy first who wanted us to talk to
him yeah oh I think he's up here in this
way
you go up these uh mushrooms here
mm-hmm
[Music]
there's a guy like this hello
what you doing
why don't you ask him
sovereign
[Music]
broke up
right this is how I killed those chicks
in my anniversary video
yeah that was wrong yeah that was crazy
Kelly you saw it
I mean yeah
of course
Ron you turn them into raw chicken
measures your worth survival in the wild
we gotta beep up some people
[Music]
um
uh
uh sure why not yeah we can help yeah
I'm choking on a cloud of
oh
drugs and poison
nice
shrimp powder mushroom does
your girl's so pretty
you think so yeah I like your buns I
like her eyes I could stare into them
forever just like yours
oh yeah
we will await word
a circle
um what are you doing
our enemies
don't do it don't do it don't do it oh I
wanna how do I do that I want to learn
oh all right at least he was honest
at least he's honest
he's real for that okay
bye bye
um but you know if there is a mushroom
you might want to kill I can lead you to
one
we want to kill a mushroom yeah a
mushroom guy
okay you mean the
wait he's not here looking one uh yeah
the fat one
um ah that one what
come we bring him with us
oh he's talking to me
sovereign
[Music]
he's cute
he's cute not cute
because I want to give him a big hug
yeah it reveals the other one the other
one's beautiful this one's cute no no
the other one's cuter
better be nice to him narissa no he's
not cute he's an ugly bastard
what's wrong with you why is so much
anger
is there something you want to admit to
us no he's gross maybe a secret
projecting
what I don't know she's really
protesting quite a bit
do you have a problem with me see he
wants to join us
okay then he can join you but he's not
joining me
yes join yeah you can let him let him
join you yes he will be my new pet yes
your new pet
cute
and
I don't think he's cute Solitude there's
peace why do you think he's cute are you
okay because because round animals is a
big teddy bear friend shaped yeah
lovable
I mean yeah but he looks he looks sticky
and slimy
yeah he looks like the mushroom in your
fridge that you've left in for too long
slime is fun though yeah but not not
rotting slime he looks like he'd smell
bad
rotting yes
when have you ever seen a slimy mushroom
and been like that looks tasty I should
eat that
oh I don't like slimy mushrooms yeah
because I don't like any mushrooms you
are a nice new friend yeah yeah as long
as we stay in here
yum
yeah we just can't leave the on the dark
then he's gone yeah yeah okay but we're
staying here so all is good yep
what else is there to explore I don't
know much more because this is where I
ended my solo play for there's just a
little oh it's just a village basically
there's not really much here though to
be honest
should we like end it then for today
yeah sure
[Music]
never-ending content also I might I
might not like stream every time that we
play by the way I'm thinking that's okay
I woke up so early and was like yeah
yeah if you were on the early turn it's
recommended to not stream yeah
definitely
but it was nice to hear your sleepy
voice yeah yeah
[Music]
I need to go
eat like some mushroom pasta get
something in my throat that isn't just
water yeah but wake up it's still not
awoken what that was that was fun you
guys yeah for our stream very effective
today efficient I mean yeah
again yeah check out the description
Link in the description and in the chat
grab the new EP it's for sale and we
probably won't restock it so go grab it
um yeah that's all I have to say thanks
for coming today yeah
a date for the next collab but it will
probably be a an a morning time again
like yeah first time Monday morning okay
so I might not stream that one oh okay
let's discuss after this three months if
we can find a date that works for us
yeah okay sounds good let's do it thank
you guys thank you for watching
thanks for watching everybody and for
supporting us we'll keep doing our best
still lots of fun things happening
see you soon see you soon everybody
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]