[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
wasn't that a cool ass starting screen
oh my God
wow
thank you
[Music]
they both made one so uh they're now
combined forever to be used in my
uh all of my all of my upcoming GTA
streams
really cool
I think
I saw like Kyle carrot already made one
at the time when uh
uh before I started I saw it and I
didn't understand it but now I
understand it after playing once um
okay uh
I have one
um
I have one confession to make
I forgot to make my own radio but I do
have some
um super cool driving audio stock songs
on my VLC
that that I have to
um switch to every time we drive if we
have a longer drive you know
I forgot
for next time for sure for real for real
though
believe me
trust me
um but I have my basic I don't know
maybe it's just putting it in one folder
if it was that easy then I could do it
right now but uh somebody sent me a
guide but I couldn't look at it yet
uh yeah you can do it now it's just
copying really
oh it is then I can just put my audio
stock things in but they're like things
that are meant to be looped uh um can I
have one radio station for each song and
then it keeps on looping that
no no
uh
crap why Crackle
what
why Crackle
make crackle or game Crackle
what about now
what about now what about now what about
[Music]
it's okay
yeah but if I can't Loop it then that
kind of sucks and I'll have to do some
background work to Loop these audio
stock songs myself
um
and then throw them in just looping in
them like a couple times and saving it
as that file
okay oh well okay
um
yeah I know in VLC I can Loop but every
time I want to play a music I have to
tap out for a moment
which is uh annoying but it's okay we
can do that today whenever we feel a
little bit
um
a little bit bored
I'm changing a CD exactly
having a CD in the car
uh but yeah besides that uh I think we
can get right into it but let me let me
let me try to wait that was the wrong
thing
[Music]
oh
where does it start
like last time I pulled it up a little
bit because of the subtitles being too
low and being covered by the jet box
oh wait it's still not quite it's still
not quite ah
for sure
huh
here but then yeah there's some space
over there
honestly maybe we should play without
the screen to like generally this game
get rid of this get rid of this we know
what we're playing also the title should
be a tale of
kitties and bowling
I think that fits more so in hindsight I
regret that title
titties and uh swing it just doesn't
quite match you know
but I I I I'll take it as a mission and
we'll check out the
the swing
hopefully
yeah
and we're in chat chat chats here
where do you want to go where was space
uh
I mean I don't know
let's see
oh wait I'll be in the way of the
subtitles won't die
um
maybe maybe a little bit smaller like
this
oh
[Music]
when I get in the way of the game you
know I don't wanna I don't wanna
it would be so funny if I just pull
through and stream the whole time like
this
[Music]
come on
let's be left side today
yeah
small small small small
wow wipes small small voila why hmm
on small bird no
or else
I'll stream like this
uh why is it so funny to me
oh we're playing GTA IV today I mean we
can go big or go big or go home
I hope you can see everything well
uh because that's what this is about
right I'm streaming game you should be
able to see everything well
okay
um for real for real now
I really like the small one though okay
this is still pretty small it's like
it's like we find a good middle ground
right
okay
[Music]
Boop
why do I keep on doing that recently
why so fast
they should learn from my loading screen
where are we right last time we were
worried about where we're gonna
continue yeah they probably um yeah set
me back to that that's no problem that's
fine
you can see the mini map oh [\h__\h] okay so
right side best side
I mean I could also put myself on the
top right
hmm
okay how about this
yeah of course I know that would be the
best
but that would imply that I am not a
phoenix but a bat and we don't want to
confuse people
us
what's up oh maybe I should eat
something wait I was just at home why
don't I just sleep we've never slept
before let me try that
got the way he runs is so funny to me it
sound okay
everybody
sleep on this [\h__\h] bed
that's that he wait does that heal me
yeah okay
sprinting to sleep oh
are you sure yeah
[Music]
wow that was so refreshing honestly
maybe maybe it's better sleep than I'm
getting these days I had like so many uh
nightmares
I don't really remember all of them in
detail but I remember something like
people
AKA part of my family and also just
randos
coming to my apartment and like trying
to kick me out
and it felt really threatening
and then I I was like basically kicked
out and I was like trying to escape and
they were chasing me through the city
and uh
I was like really scared and I didn't
even have proper like I think I was in
pajamas running for the city and I had
nothing and nowhere to go and they
didn't even let me take my things like I
had nothing no money and nothing
yeah it was really scary and I tried to
make my way back to my apartment
while they were chasing me
um
scary scary [\h__\h]
ah what is this it's your iPod your
trunk was open
um this one's nice nice oh but police uh
oh more police is there really so much
police driving around
in New York City
at all times
yeah whoa
oh why that's not one move
what if I change my mind now what if I'm
like okay
I don't need the car
I would let you out but I need to First
Escape Ultra oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
excuse me
get out get out get out
thanks bye-bye oh that was fast this is
how you get yourself a car yeah nice
muscle car
or is it
this game is confusing my muscle car
senses
no something's wrong with it it's not
quiet but you know because it's old cars
it's confusing me
this is also low right I was wondering
because it doesn't look it doesn't look
so low to me
it's called a land yacht
really there's really anybody saying it
that way
what a [\h__\h] sake
okay I think now we're heading to the f
where we stop
sorry where we stopped last time oh sure
miss the little guy on the map what
nice Dodge
[\h__\h] traffic man
oh roller coaster
whoa I mean I think I've drove in by the
roller coaster before but now it looks
really
nice to me
of Aya the fun fair
okay
this is does this have like this kind of
gate because this is like rich people
area what is it for
like only rich people allowed past this
point but they're not even properly
checking
oh gated community
[Music]
well I don't know why they feel so
special I live in a goaded community
that's way cooler
yeah
okay
or do I I'm honestly I don't know I
wouldn't really say I live in the Golden
Community
farmland
[Laughter]
oh
hello hello so this I've seen before
should I skip it or should we no let's
watch it so we get back into the groove
I guess and I eat cherry tomato
no no thank you you're welcome
um
sit down
thank you you want some tea before the
stream I did recordings a little bit
Mikhail doesn't let me use this anymore
and I went for a short swim again
like immigrants
I know what you're thinking it is a bit
funny coming from him
I'm going swimming almost daily yo
he did not used to be like this wet
poultry When We Were Young I'm not wet
anymore
beautiful
he was happy
he made me happy
but um then something changed years ago
I never quite knew what it was
so many years I wondered what it was
come on YOLO
what was wrong with me
that I did not see it in him
or I changed him
life is complicated I
I never thought I'd live like this no
when the war came I did bad things and
after the war I thought nothing of doing
bad things
killed people smuggled people smuggling
people is not not so bad right isn't it
and you're helping them
after you walk into a village
and you see I'm thinking of smuggling
them out of a like a dangerous territory
each with their throats cut well I
guessed you they asked for a lot of
money huh you realize that the creature
that could do this doesn't have a soul
God is very maybe we're thinking of
different people I'm not thinking of
like him selling humans
I was thinking of
when someone really needs to get out of
an area where they normally can't get
out of I tell you one thing can you
ignore me
stupid [\h__\h]
baby but they always say smuggle can you
smuggle me out I need to get out of here
what did you want
I want you to teach
to teach to listen to you want him to
get us the money [\h__\h] the money Mikhail
please calm down we're already in a lot
of trouble I don't know if I can smooth
things over with Patrick [\h__\h] you who
are you my dad
get out
yeah I mean refugees
that's what I mean okay we're talking
about different things well then if he
did human trafficking then that's
[\h__\h] bad [\h__\h] him owns a garage and
Chase point
I want you to pick up a truck and take
it to him
call me when you get to the truck it's
in shotler on Montauk Avenue go
get out of here
okay
now we're back where we were at last
time go to the old factory and find the
truck why is the color suddenly so [\h__\h]
honestly is this like
what
I don't understand is it a bug because
it's still daytime
what is the color suddenly it becomes so
is it the style stylistic choice
is that thing moving
I assume yes
yeah Twilight Princess filter yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I just recently just a couple days ago
watched a video about Twilight Princess
like the whole
development process
I forgot what the point of the video was
though I think the point was saying how
Twilight Princess
[\h__\h]
saved or was supposed to say
Nintendo I don't know I don't know I
don't know
but I don't even know anymore
you decide to
do
[Applause]
you saw that too wow we all get the same
things recommended it's actually insane
do you guys also like I've been like
um
practicing one specific vocalo song and
I looked up a certain Cava once
as reference because I thought it was
really good
and I watched it once and then YouTube
keeps on recommending me the same thing
every time I go on my YouTube front page
and I appreciated it the past days
because I needed to find it again anyway
to practice more
but how does YouTube know that I do want
to see it again and again
and what if I don't want to see it again
again why do you keep on recommending
because I guess every time I click on it
every time it shows up I
must be it so guys so if you say one of
my songs on your main recommended page
click on it and then if you see it next
time you load the main page click on it
again
and if you say it again click on it
again please then you're telling YouTube
it works like I just experienced it
myself you're telling YouTube that you
want to see more of this and other
people will be showing the same thing
that's what I do already thank you
you're doing it the right way
and you're doing it the wrong way if
you're not you're not in my songs on
your main page every time you load it up
Mr faustin I have the truck driving
private what am I delivering what
happened
explosive what the [\h__\h] if I don't drive
carefully could I blow up myself oh dear
I wonder how sensitive it is
I love the ping pong
how long is the drive
okay that's a good drive here let's
listen to some musical
foreign
[Music]
are you hearing it
I put in my favorite uh mixtape
oh [\h__\h] it's loud
where the [\h__\h] am I okay
Bob right
ah found a good one
audio stuff
okay
oh yeah okay okay it's not the best Loop
this one
it's so loud I cannot hear it
the flashing light on the back of the
truck indicates its conditions
highest beat building
that sounds like it's about to this
it's on the table but it doesn't mean
that it's about to go off okay okay go
go okay
[Music]
feels very intimidating though
it's like telling me I'm about to go off
oh maybe we should
be more careful for this ride
specifically
test it you know what you want to but
actually I do
follow me
how do I make myself blow up the best
way
try me shoot me shoot me that'll make me
blow up baby
that didn't do anything to my truck
[Applause]
that would be too bad
oh no
oh yes
the sound the sound that I want to hear
so badly
get down
[Music]
beautiful
cool
oops
retract
but this music doesn't
mean this one should look better maybe
[Music]
okay let's do it again we just wanted to
see what happens once right I'm not the
only one right oh oh blow this time
we're blue
Alpha what a nice car and I'm already
losing the top man
okay nice
yeah this blue is nice
but on a car like this
it really doesn't hurt to go for a
really flashy colors you could go for a
really bright blue too neon blue
[Music]
on a car like this it would look good
welcome membership thank you for the
gift
how much does car like this cost guys
10K 200k
50k 100K 100 200 okay I think it's 100
to 200.
get out of the way
[Music]
um
okay we're back at the truck and this
time we're gonna be extra careful
[Music]
my first trip to the U.S east Coast an
accurate simulation
if only I had a license yes but thank
God I don't
[Music]
it has motorized spoilers that's only on
high-end cars
motorized spoilers
what the [\h__\h] does that mean
turn right
never notice it actually says it in
voice charge over
wow
I never noticed that before
[Music]
oh it's only some of the cars that's
what I thought
oh it's my car but repaired
turn left
I don't I don't speak miles that's the
problem
but even if you set it in meters I think
I wouldn't know for sure
I can guess how much one meter is
but like bigger distances I'm like um
hard to imagine you know
so every time I cook something
and it says cut the
cut the carrot or the potato in
one centimeter five centimeter three
centimeter thick slices or whatever
um I was wondering
is this is
kind of unsure but just going with my
guts
what the [\h__\h] guys why is there in such
a huge traffic jam
all
there we go why is everybody going to
the right side
when the left side is too much also what
are they doing
if Peyton's box
okay let's not let's do it properly this
time I guess I guess you have to wait
until it goes down and then you drive in
[Music]
that last time that was so mean when I
tried to pay it and and then my father
did but then they get angry at me
I was not fair Romance
my man no it's Roman we should go
wrong and not nervous enough about
driving a truck
he's out of control anyway I'm sorry but
if I get drunk with you and then drive
this thing I'll definitely blow myself
up he's making a decision for me and
okay cool cool at least I'm not getting
minus friendship points right this is
just like a little chit chat for me to
enjoy
little boys
oh my God this is
[Applause]
like a purpose that during this Mission
traffic is like extra bad
you were trying you know yes
oh [\h__\h]
yeah
that's all good
is that traffic light really red
I can't see I wonder if they're just
messing with me
[Music]
you can lower traffic dancing office
for real
but that's like lowering the difficulty
of the game you guys for real subscribe
come on I know it's red but
come on
here we go
nice almost there maybe yeah
park the truck inside the garage
[Music]
Roger
immediately yours
[Music]
do I get out
trigger the bomb ah wait while I'm
inside oh my God
oh
why are we blowing them up anyway holy
[\h__\h]
I hope there was no camera that saw this
sheesh
no security cameras hopefully
get out of the area okay
should I take a car
[Music]
can I run faster than this car yeah come
on come on
why I didn't do anything why isn't
somebody asking me this
[Music]
okay Fountain I did it I did it let's go
I'm blown the place up but don't pull
that [\h__\h] on me again maybe I don't want
to drive around my city
understandable I felt nothing scares you
man [\h__\h] hasn't anyone got any balls
how you speak to me
[Laughter]
well maybe we should go get drunk with
Roman now
[Music]
oh oh oh this is asking for it
are we gonna survive this
oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
wow what do you mean not good enough
that's good enough for what
yeah I'm going I'm doing all the stunts
today well if you're not getting a new
mission right away then I want to know
where the swing is
where is the swing
oh I didn't I thought I was just
watching it I didn't know I had to do
something
[Music]
where's the swing
near Hospital
[Music]
s
show me
[Music]
bottom right
like here bottom right
[Music]
there's the airport
project
[Music]
okay let's go there
I'll check it out I want to know what
this swing is all about
[Music]
oh wow I came back for the same
Nico it's Roman I was talking to Bruce
monkeys
anyway he's got some work and we are in
need of money
[Music]
together
was that okay
okay
I guess now it doesn't matter if I drive
back
I felt a little bit uncertain about it
can Roman wait for me I need to check
out the swing
or should I go bowling right away
fine okay good
as long as I don't choose something else
over him I suppose
we're almost the perfect run
nothing this time
you guys are taking all my money
not cool
[Music]
you know recently even though it's like
still really [\h__\h] hot in Austria
I'm not suffering as much
in my
[Music]
mind I actually
I think
I think I finally figured out something
oh
[Music]
if I finally figured out how the cooling
system actually works in my apartment
hahaha
but
it's it's still not perfect like air
conditioning or anything like that
like not like super chill
but
I've gotten it to uh
a distance
livable temperature okay
wow
you're gonna make fun of me again aren't
you maybe I shouldn't tell you okay
[Music]
you're gonna face
again
[Music]
now I have to reconsider dead
but I think personally that I was just
doing The Logical things
[Music]
is this the swing
swing
let me do the swing first
[Music]
wait what
is that supposed to be a swing
nah
different swing
chill music chill
I passed the other line okay you guys
have to give me clear instructions
foreign
the swing near the car wash where's the
car wash this was bowling
this is pay and spray
well it's not on my map is it
the car was
you drive into you need a car for the
swing okay
okay
a bit more up
man
don't [\h__\h] the police I've learned my
lesson
there
uh
does it look like an actual children's
swing
right okay thank you
[Music]
in here
that's not a swing though
left
here left
[Laughter]
should I change to a different car
because this car maybe is kind of lame
let's do it was a fancy car
this car is okay okay
[Music]
left right left right left right
it's like I'm playing like um
like uh I'm like one of those like
audience plays Pokemon twitch streams
be a swing here no I see a swing
how are we gonna do this I just
okay
I'm gonna just drive in Reverse towards
it
hold from which side is that important
could I enter from the other side
ah
[\h__\h]
give me a moment please
what kind of messed up here
with me
I wish I could use Auto hand
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'm stuck
um
maybe if I re-enter it's like restarting
a PC
is this normal is this how it's supposed
to be this um back wheel
okay yeah I think I'm for real stuck
in your car man don't beat me
you can have my other car
I want to try to push the other call
away
[Music]
okay
we're making space
for on the bus
now oh it's still bugging out that car
is still bugging out
gonna have two star cards
probably
oh [\h__\h] this is difficult can I enter
from the other the other is it important
that I enter from this side
oh look uh
there's nothing to see here uh foreign
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
I don't think I can go up the stairs
with this car
it's a low rider oh [\h__\h] it's low as
[\h__\h]
nah
fancy car doesn't always do the trick I
I want your car
stay very calm buddy this one should be
fine
will you let me do it though cause look
he's still there
you can have the other fancy Low Rider
car
us
I'll take you and be on the swing
we need momentum
or do I need momentum [\h__\h] where exactly
which one am I going for
holy [\h__\h]
other people even find out about this ah
I wanna go down
you don't need momentum okay
the [\h__\h]
um I only need momentum to go up
oh
ah I made that one
[Laughter]
[Music]
make way please
oh come on come on
[Applause]
foreign
because it's inverted
hey need a new car
the new cars oh here I'll even drive it
into the scrap and all the parts
place because it's [\h__\h] up
oh can I go go upwards normally
and then turn around
oh nobody told me that
okay
um a car that doesn't look like it's too
low
did they clean up that other car yet
yeah okay okay
this one was more gravy but police oh
I want that one
ah
in town of esos you are worse
why are they all driving low riders
okay I'm gonna take
this one so I I saved him from his
suffering because they're all stuck here
oh my God
hey
guys
[Music]
[Applause]
get there
wait let me just remember where where
the swing is
ah okay
[Music]
um escape and then I'll be back at the
swing
oh no
[Music]
today is not her day
I lost my check what I mean my
checkpoint
and write a Dr what was Dr again doctor
[Music]
hey why did I lose it but it was like
like here maybe
I'll find it again now that I know what
it looks like I'll find it but this is
the wrong car again
so want to switch cards
face power
[Music]
oh bye why does this car move like [\h__\h]
it's like it's buttered in oil
[Music]
hey man it's me what that's good you
miss me huh
yeah I will go but can you wait for me
he will drink wait for me for one hour
okay one hour
one hour in game is that less than in
real life
[Music]
I don't have time for that
uh
cancel plans so this way we don't have
the Mindless friendship right because
they're not drunkenness we'll have to
wait something is happening all right
Nico we shall do this another time later
on yeah
how understanding and kind of him
[Music]
am I going the right way right
ah it's there yay my memory
thanks for the memory this time it's
actually great yay
I remembered the exact location
and all the cars are gone it's cleaned
up nicely
here we go
this is how easy it can be but uh so
what
I don't know what exactly to do you say
middle but um what the what popcorn
is that what's
um we wanted to see although the car
I'm still making popcorn
not quite even more okay we try again
hmm
[Music]
um
new car new car
now reverse it same car
it can launch the car
but in this current state of the car I
feel like it's gonna blow me the [\h__\h] up
reverse interest okay
oh
the lights are around it's showtime baby
wait what I was unexpected
that wasn't even the middle
wow
oh this one same car
please your car looks perfect for my
experiments
that is but a fraction of its power
I want to see yeah
the real power oh God there's so many
people there now
[Music]
they're in the danger zone
construct me on the number Island
cool wait oh [\h__\h]
um
no
[Music]
no why was I indecisive
this is my mistake
oh
God damn it uh
oh oh
okay sorry this side is now unusable
what about a motorbike can you do this
on the motorbike
I wanna oh let's just do it
yes
I got into the bike
I don't
know right
[Music]
what me
me
this is fun
go on I want to go on broken
broken
yes that's broken
okay one more
um
okay
okay I understand
oh those bikes are really fun it's fun
to do it with bikes isn't it is that
that's not a low rider is it
I need your car
I think it should work with your car
police didn't see that whoa
[Music]
oh no
let's go
[Applause]
oh
isn't that like in JT JT GTA 5 too uh
like I'll just I can just hide like
somewhere
and they won't fight me if I'm like
under the radar
JT
can I hide and I don't know a place like
this
and they they can't find me here can
they
I can't
you sure
I don't hear any sirens
or is the engine different here
I have to leave the circle
really what about the last time where
where it just suddenly disappeared
oh my God
well they certainly don't really seem to
have an idea where I am
but I guess the circle will never go
away
um I think they're coming
and I have barely have HB Mamma Mia
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay can we really
save ourselves from this situation
[Music]
is because it's covering the whole mat
ah never mind there's
there's an opening
[Music]
there's an open again yeah
you gotta believe handbrake
[Music]
give me
oh
nice Mommy
[Music]
what if I start the mission the Dr
mission where exactly is he I think that
would work
repaint your car
uh I don't know where
I'll be fine it'll be fine
Escape via the highway oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
no
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
otherwise I wouldn't be playing with the
swings right right makes sense
okay
can I see the I see the end of the
circle and the streets are very empty
well I see a police car though
oh wait if I'm like in between oh [\h__\h]
oh no oh what is this
[Applause]
welp
um
we'll play with the swings another time
I'll I'll continue the missions now
uh Dimitri oh Brucey uh let's go Bruce
that was epic though
epic fail LOL
o
car would we like to go with
the first yeah that's what I'm going for
no
saw that police officer in the last
second oh my God
I'm gonna take this one
I'm so sorry please please please
please please please thank you
so nice of you
to donate to the Wawa charity let me put
on some music
stupid
[Music]
foreign
do you like it it's smooth I've got all
kinds of different museums today
[Music]
they're just not in the actual radio
[\h__\h]
no no no
I'm sorry I was looking
[Music]
a nice car
I like the color oh [\h__\h]
mmm
[Music]
oh
so about
now we're almost there I can't talk
about it now
next time
I was gonna see
but wait if I start the mission if I
start to mention
[Music]
Ed trying to pull the break the break yo
I really want to try again
how can you be
not understanding Excellence happened
okay this is perfect
oh thank God
wait music
hello hello
I said hello
[\h__\h] what'd you do that for is
your boss around yeah he's around Brucie
some [\h__\h] Pollock [\h__\h] for you
pleasure to meet you too he's not a
pollock the gentleman
sorry Nikki man that is me sweet
oh [\h__\h] him I'm big but I'm also fast
wake up boy oh I'm sorry can you show me
that again
no thank you I bet 450 oh man
yeah yeah yeah I hence four
man well Ramen said maybe
we need some money real bad [\h__\h] my bad
yeah of course love that guy love him I
mean I am no chubby Chase but if I was
in a queer guy oh
okay all right now Nikki listen up I
know you guys need money yeah saying a
nice job not exactly mom and pop [\h__\h] no
problem as long as the pay is good
sometimes people [\h__\h] other people over
okay and the people that [\h__\h] other
people need to get [\h__\h] with
especially people that go into hiding
before they can get on the stand and put
a lot of guys inside for a lot of time
uh-huh
how do I find him man you're cold you
didn't even blink I love that I [\h__\h]
love that you gotta see
us to get on the computer give me a call
there is
there is not really
all right Brucie I'll give you a call I
Co man I
I very much understood that more than
the Jamaican accent
get a cop car okay
okay
sure no problem
um well nothing here inside
um
let's see
the luck your Chosen One
I see one
lucky Chosen One congratulations on it's
two of them
is it always two
oh
get in
[Laughter]
here is Daniel better way to get a
police car
so actually a miracle that didn't kill
me
oh God
two stars for getting a cop car I just I
was just looking for just for a job I'm
job hunting
since I've been small I wanted to become
a cop to protect
everybody around me
I just want to help people
so I want to become up
stay on the download yes yeah
I'm here I have a computer
[\h__\h] run man no
no cats don't wanna mess with someone
packing 24 inch guns like mine baby yeah
I'll track down this Rivas
call me when it's done bro
they have a computer in there oh okay I
guess
press e One Stop
so access to a computer
police database to find out where the
Lyle Rivas lives
uh police records a name
uh oh
a lot Lyle Rivas
whoa
should I press stop no I just got a
little smirk
ah lion what are you smirking for huh
Hangouts broker wanted for drug
trafficking okay locate this bastard
how do I know where he is
what
what's a broker
we have the location right
okay
no I don't mean like I I just want to
know how do they know where they are
yeah that's open
how do they add is it like a foot
um
a GP the tracker
do they have some foot tracker going on
my HP is kind of [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh that's his address oh
does he have house arrest
yeah [\h__\h] should I do this with like
current age space
no I shouldn't
um
a pizzeria can I eat food in there oh
wait maybe there is actually
um
find the food stand can you not go to
actual restaurants in this game
food stand ah
face officer now I I got priorities
hot dog when are all these bottles on
the ground doing there huh
oh [\h__\h] yeah that's good
a dog get that out
I might need another hot dog
no I'm good I'm good I'm probably fine
[Laughter]
can I get three seconds
all right from which side do I enter
you know how to say sorry I'm here
okay
this I got the message from Brucie for
you Brucie I thought he was [\h__\h]
joking [\h__\h]
the way he moves
like um
it's like uh out of the
Lord of the Rings game I don't know he
reminded me of smurgle
yeah did it give you
give you God I'm not the only one
oh
oh with the police dog
foreign
that must be him right that's him that's
him should I shoot
[Music]
we want we want him alive or dead
wonderful
you're speaking my language
[Music]
ah I got him I got him
oh yeah
oh
does it always blow up so nicely
look at him
while Rivas resting oh oh I should get
out of here oh God I should get out of
here oh God don't worry about the rivers
anymore
oh [\h__\h] I get the money oh [\h__\h] you're
all about the cabin I mean
[Music]
a little bit of a situation okay
are we at the airport right now oh my
God
maybe I should just escape the the city
or the country
[Applause]
oh okay good good good good
good good good good good good good good
stay stay down lower okay nicer
what did Bruce say
I was not able to focus on what he said
but I'll just go
Um back to him
that was a Kill it's a huge explosion yo
here's some more smooth music guys
ice cold
bro come to see me at my crib in bowabo
stay Alpha B is that Brucey
no well I I'm on my way
come see me at the Depot is this new
ah we need to talk I'll be on the five
light Island Boardwalk see your friend
Dimitri okay
okay
man I'm so popular Dimitri is new right
but can he wait
I hope he can
show up in a cop car to Dimitri oh wait
book him
ice cold [\h__\h] like you should
look into doing some vigilante work for
money bro cops are Outsourcing that [\h__\h]
to private contractors check it out next
time you have a police computer be
EP
thanks for the advice Brucey boy
couldn't have waited to tell me that in
person ah
why everybody got the same car hmm
boring look at the car that I have
Vehicles
yeah I'll pick you up with the police
car
wait if this if I
um okay no problem I'll be there in an
hour
pick you up for what
[Music]
where he at
oh [\h__\h]
if you quickly honk the horns
she just needs a ride super close button
ah here okay
police over
were you going to jail
better because that's the only route
that I know
this music is really chill right
really nice suitable for some children
it's not too overpowering
but it's there
to care for us
smooth and chill
are perfect for our car dates
yeah I think driving distance
so far you guys said it's close he was
close but fight for life what's up Jacob
yeah
I'm saying no I don't know what you're
saying make you think that things matter
when all that matters is that the sun
come up and we have a good time and
laugh and thinks it I hope so man I do
your opinion on equal even for a shatter
yeah
what what is he saying I'm short
he's talking about Positive Vibes right
just trying to share positive vibes
oh God that was close wow
very suspicious police car driving
around here kind of about to blow up
oh God
[Music]
we don't want to get in trouble while
our friend is in our car right
okay we did it
hey I'm not gonna join you for bowling
or anything though I hope that's okay
yo thanks for the lift my brother [\h__\h]
boxing what does that mean
what does that mean I do not understand
car lingo
I want to get a different car
well Jacob like this yay
oh
fill in the car oh
are you saying the smoke came from him
oh
[Music]
wow wow
why is the solution always to shoot huh
I'll just I'll just continue my my
travels
timing it was safe at first
stay calm Lala
just gotta stay calm
sorry everybody's in the way right now
okay okay okay maybe we can stay around
here for a little bit
and there we go
I'm a pro at this now
I can escape them without
panicking
in just a few moments
[Music]
so I'm being caught by cops more than
GTA 5 but it always ends like it always
has a better link ending than GTA 5
don't you think
whenever cops are
in GTA 5. it was quite a struggle I
think
[Music]
too easy in this game
I remember the chase on the ocean guys
oh is that cutie
I'm working out
hey Brucey let go one second
why didn't you tell me it was Nico what
God like women Chinese Japanese tattoos
yeah
General
are you all right you seem a little
tense sorry I'm I'm just juicing makes
me love
pent up juicing yeah bull shark
testosterone Amigo ordered online from
Chile makes you feel really
well and be careful man I heard that
stuff does funny things to your balls
hey do I look like I got funny balls to
you no show me I haven't considered it
you sent me a message
help I'm losing the plot here pause
shitty man
what we look good with that thing that
thing A lot of people are very grateful
now listen this guy Lyle had a car with
stealing what he left it in an Alleyway
off of Yorktown Avenue in Steinway well
he won't need it anymore this time no
problem yeah of course and the risks nah
okay uh I'll just go take care of it
then yeah
hi can it really be so easy
I didn't really talk to the lady I wanna
talk to the lady
go to Yorktown Avenue
same
music made that so much stranger really
I actually thought it's landed in so
nicely I didn't even realize it was my
own bgm
music made in a porno no I didn't
what
happened
whenever we get a long ride I might
consider
telling you about my temperature problem
[Music]
foreign
are we ever going to the other Islands
[Music]
come monkey wow you want to know uh just
to make fun of me afterwards
walk around and get the car
let's close the door
otherwise it's an invitation for someone
to steal my stolen car
what ah there
that car that car worth stealing
um
not really but okay
this is a really normal car
no risks Bruce maybe this juicing is
[\h__\h] with your head he's trying to
take Laos why
you got a problem with that
ain't your car no I thought it was
oopsie I'm so sorry get the car back to
Bruce's lock up okay uh how do I get out
of here
okay and left them there we go
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa why do they all
have guns ready
[Music]
nice nice turns nice turn yeah
okay this is good Street
oh [\h__\h]
oh no
[Applause]
they got me they got me
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
hmm
[Music]
I like this alley I like his Road his
tunnel
oh I've been through this one actually a
million times now that I realized
just from the other side no
what
maybe not
wow can I lose them
oh God
[Music]
also am I not supposed to like not break
the car too much when I like do this for
a mission
pretty sure that was uh
thing yeah
[Music]
oh man
I ain't got time for this [\h__\h] either
man
oh [\h__\h]
almost peed in my Santa's panties
wait wait
is there a mission like paused for now
yeah I think so because the the people
stopped following me didn't they
are they gonna show up
where are they now
[Applause]
cancel the chase with another Chase yeah
will they
will they find me
and I'm almost at the go
it doesn't matter at this point
I hope they accept the card the way it
is
[Music]
oh wait are they not is that a like a
way of skipping the chase
by having the cops instead chase you
is that a strategy
here's the car for Brucey I hope you
were expecting a fixer-upper the only
thing you respect when you're working
for Brucie is a whole lot of [\h__\h]
thanks
I've been enjoying working with Russia
I have no problem with him
um
the car is in your lock-up it was not so
easy people were waiting for me nice man
if I've known to be like that I'd have
Gotta Get It people don't [\h__\h] with
Brucey though you made it man you got
the Mad ran a harvey driving skills
spinning once crazy original Styles you
know well Crews will hang all right all
right thanks homie and thanks though man
all right then bye bye
okay so we go to Dimitri finally I've
been keeping him waiting I'm so sorry
Demetria
my man my man can I use your vehicle a
moment
just a moment
Bobcat imagine he owns the cat called
Bob
and the car called bobcat
perfect fit a match made in heaven
[Applause]
what what I'm not paying to fix the car
right am I
[Music]
Bob is a good name for a cat though
no cats that are called Bob I mean not
personally but I think I've seen
cats called Bob
on the internet
I had a bobcat about a cat named Bob or
Bobcat because apparently Bobcat is a
thing too
I saw like videos
from like neighborhood cameras
in America Maybe
we're like a kid a kid was terrified by
a bobcat and was trying to get into the
neighbor's house
yeah what the [\h__\h] why are you guys
being chased by Bobcats what's going on
over there we don't have bobcats in
Austria
damn that's crazy
[Music]
we don't do that here
sit down
wait let me stop my music
I wonder when that Tab out does it stop
the cutscenes I think it's stopping the
cutscenes
it's a problem no no it didn't [\h__\h]
maybe what do you think oh did it
Mr fauster it did kind of did
but loading back in took a second
you're given the choice
kill your best friend or die what do you
do
and there is no way out not now not
after you catervix son
you don't have any family you could run
wherever you go people will find you if
they want to badly enough
and for this they want blood
you have so much history
sure
well I killed the boy so they want me to
no
I told him you were a Hired Gun
and they said as long as you were the
one to kill him
you'd be spared right okay
so that's the way it is yes that's the
way it is
he'll be leaving his house in a little
while and heading for the club
do what you have to do
you know if there's one thing I've
learned
it's that we must obey the rules of the
game
we can pick the game Nico Bellic
but we cannot change the rules
deep [\h__\h] bro see you later
hopefully avidazen yeah
yeah let's go to Fashions Club
I saw we're killing faustin
It's that car
did I leave that here
oh man a man no Dimitri is
nicer
what's these cars
stranded cars
which one should I take it's so dark
it's hard to tell which is a nice car
but I don't see any police cars
so actually I want to take a bike
anyway
so I'm sure they don't mind
and I'm basically doing less damage
me really
should I get myself a scooter instead of
a car
no but I think generally I don't think I
would do that before getting a car
no half-ass thing I need if I get
something I get a proper car
so I can put things in the car
but I still can't really imagine myself
driving a car
me and my bug
Blossom is inside Panasonic all right
Nico there can be no mistakes with this
Mikhail is a dangerous man I've left
some protection for you around the side
of the club oh thank you you mean uh
like armor
oh
around the side of the club okay
oh in here
nice thanks I was actually thinking
about that a moment ago before I got the
message
all right going in baby
going in
this is gonna be difficult
Nico Bellic
see
you and Dimitri are taking over now
this is not about taking over yes
practice on yourself
push things to fall you would be dead if
it wasn't for me
that is what Dimitri wanted when you
killed Vlad
Dimitri
my brother
hmm
you see this you got matching tattoos
this is what you says we are brothers
for life cute
and now he betrays me
you didn't give him a choice
you should have been calm
no one not Dimitri not anyone tells me
to come
you think Dimitri would have survived
prison without me
he'd just be some prison Queen had I not
been there meet for some Gin monkey
I can see that
I'm not dead yet
some are still loyal to me
that
can I shoot no oh we're doing office
wait I can't flip my weapons can I
remembered it oh God
[Music]
come on God
ah there it is
trying to kill him or this game
ah Boston where's Boston
where
so the red
it's still there isn't it
still at the top
okay I probably have to redo this
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I have to go outside
okay
maybe it was not letting me change
weapons because I was like still in like
a fighting position but I I left it but
I guess it was kind of slow
[Music]
rented the guns from the beginning okay
uh
[Music]
that's a nice car
I mean not really but I feel like it's
[Music]
how do I how do I make that stop
making stuff
[Music]
huh
this is ways
you're chasing me but not really okay
there we go there was no Circle
I'm here again
so ready weapons and also
uh
Go app instead of going out
got it
let's go
don't worry we'll get in fine
it's a pleasure
weapon ready
but I don't know where the I'll probably
be like confused
[Music]
just guys
I see again
from the back
[Laughter]
hey I was I was I was going I was trying
to be aggressive way but okay
to take cover hmm
cute
you don't mean crouching
but Q doesn't do anything for me
ah when I'm on the wall okay
um
[Music]
[Applause]
oh what am I doing at least for the
first moment
uh uh we can go kind of aggressive
[Applause]
[Music]
maybe I should use like my micro SMG or
something like that
because it worked it worked
it's good right
enjoy yourself
what's that
okay okay
okay
um
wait I only have these two oh please
okay
but I have at least a lot of munition
we didn't see nothing
excellent
am I taking cover I don't know what I'm
doing
I got where I am foreign
[Music]
you're surrounded now
yeah face me Cowboy I'm scared
okay okay
take your time okay we're going up right
is there anyone even left
where is this
that doesn't look like the way up
where did he go thanks for the
memberships
hi guys you're not getting away from me
nothing to move for [\h__\h]
me neither
it's a bug
out away oh come on what I don't know
where exactly he went
huh
I'm like so disoriented
in moments like these
stupid [\h__\h] red era on the map uh I
have a row I saw that I know it means go
up but like where
yeah the camera is really weird when I
take cover
it's kind of annoying
[Music]
adorable that one stairs up deadly let
outside so I don't know
isn't that my car buddy
foreign
my dead bodies
my dead body is probably inside too
red double doors out didn't I go for a
double Norm but it's like eh
do I have to go outside once in order to
get up Nico
Nico belly that was the right way
Oh I thought I shouldn't go outside
my God
I would have some Buck on [\h__\h] take this
away from me I made you what you are
Nicole
well I want to kill this one first
is over I must rule
come on
that's so funny it's party man
okay
let's go
[Music]
what
[\h__\h]
we're loading in the worst moments
oh oh oh
that is barely a cover
hard
okay
not the other way
oh my God what I've only done
none of you will survive
how are you not dead is he dead yeah
he's dead okay nice
always those dramatic rooftop fights man
fasting is dead he's dead for real for
real
oh my God
well me would have killed him probably
he was dead before he fell I think
hey sorry for traumatizing everybody
here I'm so sorry I didn't I didn't mean
to do that
I I'm just trying to do my thing
but if he fell down from down from up
there
would his body be
here
or did they already clean it up
oh wait maybe here
anyway my car this is my car no one
inside
yeah that looks like my car
it despawns oh no I would have liked to
dance on his dead body
just to prove a point
I wanted one now
game no tell me yet what to do
should I call Roman maybe talk about
stuff
yeah we should hell yeah we eat together
I come get your next hour we haven't
I'm waiting for
you
and I am actually really close
I have to tell him about what I did like
that was really cool you know
out of a movie
straight out of the movie
[Music]
but we're not going bowling or are we
Ramen move your fancy shirt come on come
on in let's waste no time Nika good to
see you let's go
where to
walk
and sometimes I cannot
oh what is this
clucking wow
talking Bell it's kind of far but with
me really I can't go out for some fried
chicken correct it has been the [\h__\h]
nightmare but that's not the point no no
no the Bellic concerts are here in a
land of opportunity and we are making
trouble for any fools who get in our way
if you say so I do say so man I do I
just did it's good to have you here
whatever [\h__\h] we get into man it's good
thanks
Miss home you've been there a long time
sure
I miss things about home but I I think
things are ruined now yes I know what
you mean I missed the good times we had
these children when our fathers were too
drunk to beat us when there was food and
the Sun was shining but now now I live
here and life is good there ain't no sun
in New York it is sure this crazy but
it's home and
home and a taste for fine women wine and
song is that how you see yourself women
familiar the raged cousin this place has
made you sick [\h__\h] you I'm an individual
my friend one of a kind or to put it
another way a freak
[Music]
let's go
clocking Bell wow look at those crazy
chickens on the windows they're
suffering kfb's doing so much better
American fast food Majestic we could
have the exact same I won't get the
scene inside and that's
good
huh oh but that car is nice
that's their home
come on
[Music]
stupid [\h__\h]
it worked
nice
[Music]
my car this Bond so this is compensation
yeah
okay we have a long ride relatively long
ride let me tell you
so when it was winter time
I
um set
the heating
to the maximum yeah
it was like you know there's not like a
proper
you know
like I wanted to be so and so many
degrees setting
but there's like a one two five
oh where are the other really rich of
them oh no oh
cool
uh
so I I I I saw okay five makes the floor
the warmest okay
so I set it on five sometimes in the
winter sometimes less than five but yeah
I I I know that the floor because it was
floor heating
was warmer at five than it was at three
you know
so in the summer time I tried to you
switch between Heating and Cooling
so I just always had it on five
but then the other day I experimented
and I set it to one and I noticed the
floor got ice cold
I'll catch you around then B call me if
you want to hang out again
isn't that interesting
why is it the opposite for cooling and
come on nobody nobody
really like
oh that is completely my fault of course
I would assume that if A5 is the most
for heating then five would also be the
most for cooling don't you think
right and then the other thing that
confuses me is because they told me that
um the heating comes from the floor but
the cooling comes from the ceiling
but that was wrong because
now that I finally figured out how it
works
the floor gets ice cold
so
it doesn't come from the ceiling it
comes from the floor
weird stuff so yeah recently it's been
way more manageable in my apartment
like proper air conditioning but it's
been way more manageable like really so
much better I I'm saved my summer is not
killing me anymore
[Music]
it's not quite my fault right it's just
logic in my head is logic
oh
Dimitri you got my money I
have Warehouse
thank you and you know I I just kind of
knew already like I know heating works
well with this kind of system but you
can't expect too much from the cooling
so I just thought okay that's the way it
is you know
it's just really bad cooling
I just have to accept it
I only pissed off one he's dead but it's
not going to be bad
I'm not afraid of him yeah
a warehouse
he'll join me Milan okay
see
two is a little bit safer safer than one
I think
Jacob join the party it's the party
it's a date and a party
[Music]
I'm so relieved about the cooling
honestly
it's been killing me like sleeping at
night was really rough but these days
like it's not the it's not the heat
anymore that's like making problems when
I sleep and I try to sleep
right now I'm feeling a little bit
um
too warm though like in my office like
it got it's currently it's a little bit
hotter than I would like it to be but
but it's fun it's manageable
[Music]
and recently I've been sleeping only
with like the
um blanket cover
but yesterday and so on I was able to
sleep with blanket
and with proper blanket and it feels
just better don't you agree
I know like my mom and my brother for
example they prefer to sleep with a like
just a linen
but I don't like it I prefer to have
something a little bit more heavy and
cozy on my body glad you can make it you
know yes you got the money
sure yeah but I just wanted to say how
grateful me and my bosses are for what
you did
this feels suspicious yes
and I just wanted to check something
with you
ayushi
don't walk in don't walk in well at
least I'm not alone thank God you are
Nico Bellic correct what is this and you
used to work the coast in the
Mediterranean smuggling people into it
what you're talking about but you're
following me now
and left a lot of bad debt you left a
good friend of mine out of pocket oh no
big time
hello Nico did he know that forever or
just recently found out about it
gorzo money
I don't know I didn't rob you
really
oh [\h__\h] we busted the mile off the coast
swim for my life
I don't know what happened I nearly
drowned my heart was bleeding I did my
best I didn't [\h__\h] up
there he is there he is let's go
my man
I'm not alone I'm not alone
[Music]
oh my God
International
news
gotta get that one
ah different gun may be better maybe
just normal gun to get the shakes
think he's dead
any guns that one did you get that one
okay
whoa I'm switching hey but this one's on
zero
reload
oh no no no okay the right number okay
there's something there's a Mexican in
there but I actually don't even need it
I'm surprised if I was running out in
the open
yeah
who's next
I got him
is that a Molotov cocktail
wait
how do I throw that
oh that's it
there there go go for it
oh no poor guy
I don't got a lot I'm looking good
something's on top of us
and wait let me pick up
oh
wait there's police [\h__\h] wait wait where
do I go where do I go where do I go
where do I go
not that way up there
probably up there right right
am I doing it right
huh or the other outside where it came
from because on the underside is police
but the era was showing up but like okay
that's why it's up
don't die my man
[Music]
okay my health ain't looking so good now
wait that's close that's
a [\h__\h]
I thought it would be open okay I guess
we gotta run past the police or we jump
over the buildings
we can try then
maybe there's an opening where we can
jump over the building
what's my my current home
jumping not a good idea fight the police
okay
[Music]
well there's not many people left I
think at this point so that's good
is my friend still alive
okay time to go buddy
[Music]
I don't see them should we just walk
foreign
[Applause]
can we go now
okay I think he's following me now
uh Jacob
[Music]
he'll spawn in the car
are you sure about that
because it just said when I left the
building before it just said you left
Jacob behind and that's not good
uh
don't lose
Drive closer to the door
you say as if that's so easy when
there's a million police cars there
um
take the car to the door
he was just getting in
so close but we had so far
oof my weapons are got all my weapons oh
my God all my weapons are gone
because I got arrested
even though I reloaded
all right remember Russian and seriously
next video I only pissed off one he's
dead I'm going to meet Dmitry to collect
on the heat
I'm not afraid of him yeah but I can't
see okay
a warehouse
around above
what a homie
but yeah we gotta load something because
that's that's not cool
um
well I only have that apparently I don't
know where that will bring me
[Music]
um
do I always just uh spawn there when I
load the safe
that's after the previous mission
you can found immature see if you have
spoken to petrovich yet wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
oh
Dimitri what's going on right now tell
me Dimitri you got my money okay okay
meet me at the warehouse okay
come along
now there comes the call from my homie
right
there it is all right my brother me and
I'm Russian and seriously the next video
I only pissed off one he's dead I'm
going to meet Dmitry to collect on the
heat
I'm not afraid of him yeah well I can't
see
them
a warehouse or no honey I know what they
want you see around the bar
okay next we get a car
um
any car is fine
[Music]
no
get out of there
turtleneck guy
now thank you and maybe
we go here first
I'm already still wearing armor but I
guess
why not get more
and I don't think I necessarily need
ammo
well you guys are saying got ammo maybe
a stronger weapon
[Music]
nocturnal like shaming I I don't think
they're like uh are cool I do wear a lot
of turtlenecks in the winter
I love turtlenecks
just making fun of him I want to be
badass you know I'm not trying to be
badass
yeah I've been picking up like so much
[\h__\h] from the enemies anyway after you
kill one or two so I'm wondering if it
is really necessary
I think I'll just buy our armor
wait is that ah
I drove to the wrong thing
no we're not doing that
we'll make it work but can I save
D oh wait I can't
okay we better not get caught by the
cops then
short base huh
small small tattoo neck
hi
why is that always so funny
[Music]
clean shots
watching your back nice come on Nico
moving okay
okay
someone in there right
hello
I'll show myself so they show themselves
so stay in firing balls
okay I gotta go there
I will use it on the police if I have to
oh my oh my oh my oh my oh my oh my God
wait I don't like the displacement
there we go
better
I want another SMG
waiting for you waiting for you
he's so tiny his head is so tiny
small small
oh got him got him got him even from
that distance okay I think I can enter
the room
okay they're going through the door okay
where the police would be
but the police is like there immediately
should I still clean a little bit more
oh
okay I can't see
uh okay
okay
on that one
then not dead
okay okay my armor is gone I wish I
could pick up another armor
um
but I can get the healing I think
okay he's following me
can we do it now
how far can I throw this thing
[Music]
bro
okay let's go
outside
[Music]
where do I go this way
when I don't want to be greeted by a
wall of police again
but I feel like I'm going the same
direction where that happened didn't am
I not
oh no no maybe not
[Music]
smoke recovery
yeah second try second try it was much
better oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh New York traffic only two sides for
all of that holy [\h__\h] we're losing him
which is a good thing in this contest
thanks Jacob man
without him
I would have actually without him I may
not have failed to first try because I
would have gotten into the cars
if I could have killed them all then and
there those children come on one at a
time one one o'clock I feel basket say
it Refinery is then mom take the rest of
them all let's keep it down until then
[\h__\h] Dimitri they've been killed
faster then he's selling yeah I wonder
if he knew
that would mean that
like it was kind of like all planned out
to take Dimitri
um
thousand I mean to make to kill
Palestine first to get him out of the
way but so that he can then take care of
me or something like that I don't know
[Music]
or did he just find out about it after I
killed faustin hmm oh yeah you think
they knew it when they first met me
and so they first just used me
as long as they can and then when it
comes to paying me they're like um
actually well actually
gonna pay you if anything you're
supposed
hey thanks for your help Jacob one love
my brother
yeah I've been done dirty they used me
they used me
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
you can call Remington for me okay yes
we'll do
you should probably know
One Love
be in the alleyway off of Hopper Street
what are you doing why are you
Whispering I'll be there soon
okay we're going to Ramen now maybe we
should be whispering too
secretive
are those dudes close by
did they take him
what's going on
Roman what do you know you're not you're
not
you're not selling me to them are you
not acting nice to me just to sell me
out to them
right
oh man be a good boy
think of all the times we went bowling
AKA once what did we wait nevermind I
only went bowling with that lady I think
but surely in the past and in our home
country we went bowling
they were
bowling
for real for real
we'll go bowling real time
big time
[Music]
balling and bowling whatever you want
for you
I reserved my time just for you
[Music]
oh
no you didn't hit me oh no you didn't
[Music]
hmm
Roman
Roman where are you in here I'm stuck
[\h__\h] man
it still doesn't explain why we why he
had to whisper I got scared people
started calling the house oh he pulled
himself there on purpose he's got the
big problem Dimitri was not a man of his
word he's only dead more or less yeah
everything was fine
now this thank you thanks a lot it's
rainy
David
it's done it's done yes but there's a
bigger problem
what
that guy I owed money to bulgarin yes
the guy in Europe who lives by the
internet yeah he's here now
I'm sorry
I've ruined your life
no don't be like that we can find a way
out of this bunch of idiot rush I will
kill every one of them no that's exactly
what you won't do no we have to don't
have time for Revenge we can't afford it
what can we afford ah
we can lay low
and start over
sure but that wouldn't be interesting
for the game let's go back to the
apartment
we could just Bowl all day we can pick
up our stuff and then get out of here
shall we they won't try to find us in
the bowling alley
right
[Music]
so that's only a legit strategy but
again that's not super interesting for
the game
unless well I mean we're talking about
bowling here
hey beautiful
um listen me and Nico are in a bit of
trouble um need to get out of broker a
few days
broker any of your cousins have a place
we can use that alone
[Music]
beautiful and kind
maybe things are not so bad this I did
not expect I was thinking about getting
out of the cab business
last night I had a dream really yes you
and I are the place of our own place
where people come to eat and relax
classy place none of these fast food
Diner [\h__\h] we're on the real
restaurant it's a place to see you know
I can't see myself what's the problem
with fast food donors in the dream
they're Charming in their own way just
like Mallory
dream Mallory and me are married
everything is perfect thank you
fresh beginning all I know is we have to
get this far from Dimitri and Bulgarian
as we can we will
but they have left something important
at the apartment something I must show
you cousin
who's that right now
game switch to Arc two now whoa
yeah yeah I saw you guys saying in the
chat that like this is where it gets
dark like with two two missions to build
ourselves
what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] it's [\h__\h] burning fire today
I've got to get something leave it
because this place is gone unbelievable
man
if if I was in the game you know
nothing nobody I worked my way up from
the [\h__\h] dirt
poor Roman wait did he lose all his
belongings now
they stream sparked for too long it's on
fire
oh no nothing left not my home not my
business nothing they took it all I'm
sorry Roman I'm really sorry but we have
to go we'll meet Mallory and Bohan still
have her and you for all the good you've
done me
maybe we should go back to our own
country
maybe we would be better off
Jesus do you know how long until I took
it set up here you don't because it was
easy for you you had it all from day one
it took me months to get some cash
together finally I bought the cab and
then another then I got the people I
slept under my desk at that place for
over a year then I got the apartment the
apartment you thought was so shitty but
it doesn't matter and now it's gone
along with everything else I said I was
sorry
I've had my computer smashed I've been
beaten up I was kidnapped and then shot
in the stomach
sounded my business things have been
going so great maybe Roman has been
suffering more than me you remember that
time back home I found it raised to the
ground just a pile of rub
everything smash
except for that one bottle of vodka yeah
we sat down and finished it off there in
bed wait wait I don't want to talk about
back home we're here in America now and
I should be thinking about my life here
my life which is ruined just drive shut
up and drive shut up and drive drive
no what do you mean Rihanna song
I haven't been crying since my allergies
allergies
[Music]
really really
yeah trying to impress Michelle or
something they're coming to your cousins
are you there
cheer up Roman great see you in the
bedroom
now I have nothing to buy it with I I
have nothing
[Music]
come on
Roman pull yourself together
for medical attitude come on
at least they want me dead and not you
I do not think it will be much
difference to them one dead Bellic will
give them a little bit
[Music]
we are in this situation okay
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
is that police
oh no okay okay this is an actual Road
oh
can I take a boat or something
over the over the ocean is that an ocean
I mean there's an ocean right
oh nice nice nice curve beautiful curve
okay wow the curve master
[Music]
ah please do not Bridge off to Highway
be careful if I see a little traffic jam
that means you know what
and
yeah yeah if we get over the bridge
we're good
nice graphic glitch
and automatically I think back on track
or no
police
oh no
oh no okay okay okay
[Music]
the circle keeps on following me
over there
somewhere
wherever the circle
[Music]
shitty ass cops
surely that's what I need
[\h__\h]
yes I did it oh God oh God
they set our car on fire now
I didn't even see what happened
Roman is our next car
[Music]
Sparks oh God get get away get away
could blow up again
of course this looks like a stable car
an upgrade this is an upgrade is it
now hopefully without further incidents
we're going to our destination
[Music]
absolute upgrade oh really you guys know
your stuff about cars did you read what
was Roman trying to get from the house
um
no I know he was trying to get
is it important
they're right oh
maybe we can make a ring
the one ring
maybe we can make one
you know those ring candies I'm sure she
would understand
like hey yo this is all I got cause you
know my house got blown up
yeah
boyfriend and he was gonna propose to me
and his house got blown up I would be
very understanding about it
and I would be very happy if it was a
candy ring instead I'd have no problem
with that
[Music]
no not for real though like what
obviously
there's anyway more important things in
that moment your house got blown up so
what's fun come on we've already lost
everything
no I'm serious what the [\h__\h] why do you
guys not believe me that's like a
obvious
obvious thing
[Music]
you guys don't believe me what the [\h__\h]
you guys don't know me
materials lady
materialistic lady
here we are the beginning of our new
lives
again
believe me
you
home
oh
not so bad yeah I mean it looks the same
it will be impressing women with a
wonderful hot tub but uh this looks okay
it looks exactly the same how did we get
our furniture over here what's wrong
what's wrong what's wrong oh the kitchen
looks freaking nice so the kitchen is a
huge airport what's wrong with you
15 minutes ago you're recurring in fear
because you did it I remember the old
kitchen now you know everything is [\h__\h]
and we're going to be killed and you're
all cheerful I don't get it I guess I'm
an optimist an idiot not in Optimist I
was part of Brooklyn anyway I'm glad you
turned up and made some Russians do they
mean Brooklyn I don't get it thanks Nico
thanks a bunch is that better Fair
version of Brooklyn because they don't
say New York either God you're okay yeah
okay okay both of you we're [\h__\h] I
thought it was flying from Brooklyn no
I'm from up here Nico I know a bunch of
people who might be able to help out why
don't you come and meet me at the
community center later on
I gotta go to work bye Papi
and have a shower you smell a little uh
I love the way she talks
did you get Poppy Joan yes we start
again
sure
I'm going out
oh
lowest point doesn't sell lowest point
oh that sounds so bad
it could be worse and it's only up from
here according to the game
oh that's fine wait did I lose all my
money you guys say I lost everything I
didn't lose my money
I got 8 000
that's oh freaking lot
Brucey and B I've been in touch with
real man get here soon bro we need the
three most dangerous blinging hardcore
[\h__\h] in the whole of Liberty
City to be rolling in the same room
together for real
what
[Music]
free motion
oh
just an invitation to like talk to chat
at least he's still we still have
friends we still got people on our side
when Maddie who the [\h__\h] is Manny Manny
is closed so let's go to Manny and oh
yeah we did kind of like change areas
what's this area like in New York what's
this area called
the Bronx whoa that sounds so cool I
mean I've heard about Bronx before and I
don't really know
what kind of place it is
but I've heard about it
Bronx I'm from the Bronx yeah
sounds really cool
not the nicest area oh okay okay yeah I
think I've heard those things
this is the one that you get a really
nice shot of them it's gonna be
beautiful
I know but we want to make sure that we
see them okay we want to see you just
film it man yeah we'll just keep looking
at me something music video or what oh
why all these old ladies turn this way
please turn the spot yeah six
good good right over here we need them
in some hotter clothing good good
perfect look man you look good no not at
all it's very manly kind of dance okay
so here we go then yeah dance it's the
streets man but people gotta understand
the struggles for real oh yeah for real
I'm getting it I gotta understand the
struggles yeah
I don't hate Nico
this is my boyfriend's cousin the guy I
was telling you about Nico how's my
little man doing anyway for a guy who
just lost his home and this business now
has a price on his hand pretty good
my love is optimism so Nico this is
Manny we grew up together hey yeah yeah
yeah what's up man streets man all right
this is the guy I told you about who
beat up all those Thugs and broke us
yeah great listen would you uh give us a
little space copyrighted but I don't
care yeah great so uh so you know
streets take no prisoners right but you
know kids need hope you know what I'm
saying yeah well you know sometimes you
gotta break some omelets to make some
eggs you know what I'm saying okay no
you gotta bring some eggs to make some
omelets you don't understand we're gonna
clean them up you know simple things
don't KFC and you will understand
we're just talking
sorry
okay everyone that'll be all for today
that was great and thank you very much
that'll be all for today thanks a lot
what are you doing what do you sing We
got to get some of the Steelers off the
streets man you know and I want them to
know it was me man fine just don't put
the camera at me when you're doing it
well it's my testimony man look brother
will you help please look I got money I
got I got money
in which case you've got help
just don't even
money right so you can fix the camera
they're gonna know what's me
okay okay
the dealers off the streets we're gonna
clean these streets hell yeah get on the
vehicle with Manny oh okay okay okay
I was uh
that was a
interesting what's the word for Tenkai
last I heard these dealers was up on
Grand Boulevard let's go take a look man
development yeah
interesting quick and fast
development we've got a new friend
so you and Mallory is tight huh she and
your cousin is together now I love that
girl man I love her man
your cousin burn not me messing with her
head you're gonna propose right she's
gonna make an honest moment of all right
I think that's as much of a decision of
Mallards as it is Romans I don't know if
he's grown up or not to make a good
husband it's up to you anyway I didn't
know you were Mallory was that close
[\h__\h] man the dealer in this drug wagon
are up there pull up behind him we wait
they're my people all right sure
they got a nice car I like it
[Music]
yeah thanks for fixing my parking
baby we got to follow into them other
leeches man damn life out of these
streets
I spoke the dealer nice
I can't move
what
last time I spoke to someone it didn't
mean that I failed
follow don't mean get all up on this
[\h__\h] it's over okay guys tonight man on
your head and B get out of here
would have been mine up
man
Mission failed Mission mailed let me do
it again
let me do it again
huh
[Music]
thank you
I don't think we had to be so sweet so
careful
oh
thank you again
Manny Manny
last I heard these dealers was up on
Grand Boulevard let's go to take a look
man
all right all right this time second
time always best time second time is the
time man I like it you're about to make
money but you want to make a difference
too man Best of Both Worlds man I myself
that way man an entrepreneur who's gonna
clean this [\h__\h] up money and respect
philanthropicalism
the dealer in this drug wagon are up
there pull up behind and we wait
I feel kind of like super behind
you guys are still talking about the
fishes
looking the damn life out of these
streets
oh
okay
me I'm just after the month no amount of
scrubbing is gonna get this town clean
well that's seen of it at least yeah I'm
an entrepreneur man you gotta have some
money if it is
the kids have to look up to me man to
know that the clean bathroom this boy's
got personal space issues man stay back
why the police not angry at the dealer
for bunking the police when I always I
just I just scratched the police car and
immediately we need to find them I
immediately get in trouble
sure but I don't think you hear me it's
for the kids man believe that
they only dislike men
I don't know man I I I feel like
they got some
very personal problems with me then huh
only someone who's been impressed
against that close to a man hold on man
guess we're back to Corona times now
taking my sweet damn time
see that's why I need a [\h__\h]
helicopter
I'm gonna see you man
invisible princess started to annoy me
it takes so much time uh where are we
going uh
you better be reaching your goals soon
or else
okay Wawa cannot be patient for so long
sneaky driving ain't my thing
I want this to be done quickly
you know these streets is mine man I can
feel them flowing through my veins you
sound like you got something else in
your veins and I didn't touch that [\h__\h]
we've been talking to man I'm clean man
Serene [\h__\h] Serene oh I'm sorry you
ever thought about doing something
you might be able to get a series of the
back of mine you know we go
Justice bro that's good
just wait till you see your face on the
screen man maybe you change your mind
then yeah I always wanted to be a
well-known idiot people say to me Manny
why you do this why you want to clean up
the street so you gas something man stay
away from his ass he will tell them to
get famous I'm just European okay I know
because I help people man I'm on love
okay for these streets
and
[\h__\h] idiot
[Music]
gay or european
[Applause]
big question
[Music]
now [\h__\h] way after all this time
[Laughter]
[Music]
now the kid dies tonight man on your
head and B get out of here
for [\h__\h] sake
what the [\h__\h]
I don't know if I want to do that again
hmm
Fair try is the job one more time
need a car if we're gonna clean these
streets
I'm just doing on my fan
Kinda hot whoa
been in my room
okay guys this is taking so much time
this was up on Grand Boulevard let's go
to take a look man
let me see it if I have
a tangent
um I'm bored of you man let's listen to
some music no no no music
music for kfp is a tangent just one
second I'll drive up to the dudes and
then I'll check my phone
okay so you guys don't get bored at me
neither
that car looked like a looked like a
dealer's car
the dealer in his drug wagging her up
there pull up behind him we wait
[Music]
baby we got to follow into them other
leeches man they be sucking the damn
life out of these streets
uh
what are these
[Music]
what are these These are not my Tantrums
are they
um
[Music]
no you guys give me something to talk
about it's two car lengths right uh
that's how far you stay behind the woman
when you're harassing her
yes
I can't find any more tangents
photograph oh did you see the Hologram
USANA construction hologram yeah
oh my God they cut I did a really laugh
because they asked for it
and they cut so much of it so it didn't
really seem that crazy I guess
and then the part where it's like what
did I say ha ha ha
[Music]
the gospel of the streets [\h__\h] how about
that for title huh yeah gospel man I
wish I had a damn pen man [\h__\h] man they
gave me some like actually
it wasn't as a reference they gave me
somebody who was imitating
the laptop
scene
I was imitating someone who was
imitating someone
and probably that was maybe an imitation
of something else as well
yeah so I was like watching that video
like several times to get right
awkward though because it's in Japanese
but they made me do it in English
[Music]
honestly I thought after the hotel
Grande View
that they'll let us speak Japanese in
the Holograms but I thought it was only
a debut holographing where we have to
speak our own language
it turns out
they're always making us continuously
speak
English or Indonesian
you like me speaking English
I don't know it's just kind of weird to
be mixed in the middle of Japanese
chit chat some random English and
Indonesian
kind of froze me off
it's like Tekken verse
is that how they do that in Tekken
foreign
Japanese
when in their debut if you mean for one
line maybe for one line
kind of an exception
but generally it seems like they keep on
making us speak our own language but the
English isn't even my my own language
I would be German but okay
I'm gonna add some Japanese lands in the
previous episode I want to speak
Japanese
[Music]
but okay
whatever
it was uh only someone who's been
impressed to get that close to a man
hold off man it was a fun episode anyway
[Music]
I wanna get in trouble
so yeah that's another Holocaust
recently there was the the summer theme
song one where all the members from the
theme song were participating and this
one is the usaken one
apparently I tried to kill
yourself bye take over and become the
CEO
stew
okay yeah make me the villain okay looks
like he's about to stop yo you best pull
up behind them man I'm a villain
follow him into that warehouse and get
rid of the dealers
okay I have a feeling that we were
actually like super [\h__\h] closer I
would go I thought you were going to
clean up the streets the message is
what's important man it don't matter who
gives it I for one ain't in this [\h__\h]
for the ego trip you taking my money
aren't you be my voice I'm gonna go back
and get Jay
oh wow okay you're leaving me behind
sure
no problem door is locked
okay now
where could we enter from
maybe here
me for free
no
wait should I shoot the lock
okay
shoot the door that just seems like such
an Unga Bunga solution you know
where is the lock
here I don't know yeah
oh my God
big welcoming
oh my God oh my God
bless me
shotgun in the back
what
I'm happy with the one I have right now
looking for a nice party yeah
[Music]
[\h__\h] off
that's nice I was waiting for that one
I'm not now this guy
you surrounded devil 360 Degrees okay
seems pretty dead now
someone's still alive
hello
they said let's move Shores I guess but
ah
bless him
hey it's safe black take cover
[Music]
they could have shot me all this time
when I was walking around openly
oh hi
what
taking cover in this game is kind of
awkward
whoa but that's cool you can kind of
break the the wall
City I guess
all right
hmm
I have cleaned up the streets
at the warehouse
yay
some Street Warrior stands outside the
site of another Gangland Massacre strike
oh cut what okay what oh could you walk
out of there just one more time we need
to get the shot
yeah where exactly is this gonna be on
on YouTube if you like I don't mind
doing that again and again until I get
it right
Unico Nico hey they look good huh was it
a good mixture of that sadness and
resolve you looked great
narcissist
where are you going narcissistic more
senseless death than the police aren't
even here yet help has only one name on
the streets of South Bowen many Escuela
that's right follow me or be prepared
street life ain't pretty
oh [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] was that a thousand
bucks for that hmm okay but we got
Maddie as a friend
we've got a friend in him
but let's go back to the real stuff
the real important stuff I mean Manny is
still there though but
we were told to go to Bobo
let's go to boappos
um
yeah I was thinking should I um let you
listen to the crazy laugh
without editing I might do that
afterwards
stop juicing when you get implants how
tell you homie my balls are golden okay
I want to talk to you about Roman he's
got a problem he's gambling like an
animal online to do clubs everywhere you
need to control your cousin bro Romans
are grown up
Michelle Brucie he's getting involved
twice about deal with it and I want
dangerous [\h__\h] okay
thanks for the heads up
okay uh what
sorry I'm going first
but I'm paying
of course I am
Law Abiding Citizen
wow a great example of how you should
live life
that is pretty
nice Diamond City Lights a little bit
[Music]
according this emotions
mm-hmm
[Music]
oh
what
[\h__\h] Dimitri
did not find your body with the others
in the warehouse oh two bags look better
and I'm very disappointed
why did you turn on me you think I could
survive
like this by aligning myself with a
bottom feeder like you you who have so
many enemies
you robbed full Garden you killed
Mikhail you know no more of loyalty deny
you know why I killed faustin it was not
my choice
a hiding place you have in this city see
you soon thank you Dimitri
I was gonna say uh
singing gonna say diamonds such a
[\h__\h] good song and it reminded me of
my album that I'm working on all the
lyrics are done like there were already
as you may know from me telling you
like two songs completely completed like
I I already recorded it it already got
mixed like they're done but I was
waiting on recording some songs
that didn't have lyrics finished yet but
now they're finished
and I really like them
well there's good variety of like Happy
song and maybe sad song and so on so I
think you guys gonna enjoy it wanna
pre-order hey man hey guys don't worry I
got you on my list
Jessie
hey hit me
what hit me come on now my lyric is
money did a great job
there you go you want to go on a date
come on really reliable
okay who is she that's the thing it's a
guy [\h__\h] you no
killed Lyle Rivas owes me a lot of money
and the dick won't pay instead he said
he's gonna have me kill that [\h__\h] hi
yeah foreign
this guy isn't hiding but he's a serious
serious car count oh so you think of me
no but the guy knows me and I don't
think anyone would date that that's love
so I'm just doing your profile all right
let me see
I am a vulnerable guy who needs to be
held by big strong arms you've got to be
kidding me I knew he should have made
him a giver another taker shut up now
listen Nikki
I need you
and I will pay heavily this guy to be
vulnerable Nicole okay
nothing to be shamed off cousin you're a
dick everybody likes a good hug don't
they neck
[Laughter]
you're a vulnerable slapping proud of it
let's go I'm proud of you too
I'm going to an internet cafe to fix
this [\h__\h] profile I guess
everybody
[Music]
yo
they're all English by the way all the
songs are English done a single Japanese
song this time
oh
[Music]
English
oh no German no
well English I think you guys will also
have fun singing along yeah
I believe it recently all my songs have
been English
all English
actually my like a German song you know
what I've been thinking like instead of
going for German songs I do want to do
like a German cover
of
some like Vocaloid or anime songs
and kind of make that my thing
I want to try writing the German lyrics
by myself I'm at the internet cafe what
now
go to it bro cool thing to be my thing
French Tom as his screen name you heard
animal man eat him alive okay
can I like chit chat with him
French Thomas cousin is good to see you
again yeah good to see you it's Nico by
the way I'm going to my spot oh no
there's someone behind me then I don't
like that I don't want to be
I want any money but anybody to be
checking over my shoulder let's go take
this one that one's well hidden
hmm
okay French Tom
uh
where is it here love meat Maybe
what how do I what
did I check the emails okay
[Music]
um
how you doing
hey I broke my own setup records today
two thousand
files I should reply to Roman's email
okay
message sent
and I'll reply to this one too
I guess I'll reply to this one
it's my mommy
[Applause]
he's living American Dream mostly in his
head like all dreams
oh no the whole sadness
like good job Brucey I'm so proud of you
hey that's not what I was gonna say
delete that [\h__\h]
oh
oh there's the sweet saver oh sabertitty
it's down some alien shot with some
whacked out dealers Roman told me he was
good for this [\h__\h] he told me you were
[\h__\h] Alpha and going to [\h__\h] rule
the world and you could handle yourself
I believe this [\h__\h] you're the [\h__\h]
man do this for Bruce Lee oh I want to
but can I keep the car
hmm
apply this email and get the right for
me how do I reply it doesn't say reply
can't do it now oh man sad
so what's this about how do I write to
the French Tom
um
that's me right
hump police Rupert Troy harder French
Tom
no big Willy very honest very honest
okay
ah
uh sweetie I'll tell you all about me
when and if we go on a date if I reply
to you you're going to love what you see
trust me chances are though you're a fat
desperate old guy who can only afford to
eat at Burger Shop guess what if that's
you French Tom is going to say bon
voyage I like money and I like to find
muscles okay we're not taking him to the
burger place then that's fine
like celebrities being fabulous getting
pampered singing along to burlesque
musicals in rustov I've heard a lot
about people talking about this whole
work thing it really doesn't sound like
my saying I'm not going to lie I want a
free ride I figure that going out with
you is probably going to be hard work so
why don't you pay me a salary to do it
oh you want a sugar daddy
people who are Financial challenge be
members of the fat Liberation movement
or as statically inferior that's poor
people fat people and ugly people in
American you get the picture if you want
to get with me you better have the looks
and the dollars to back it up wow
the [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
time to date him
yes time to log off because that's
almost already too much of the internet
for one day
I love sometimes friendship will check
love meat and email his reply okay
is it time yet
now
I really have to go somewhere else and
then come back to here
I should read my own profile ah next
time okay when I come back
I hope they don't
um uh get rid of it
um
okay I'm going to Manny now unless
something interrupts me
wait
let's do some music
not that one though because that one
doesn't look properly
[Music]
we're getting in the mood for our days
wait where's my map
[Music]
what's going on is this a bug
ah there it is
having a game past eight hours of
in-game time
I am right I'm hoping that
to the many quest in the meantime
whatever that is
Manny
[\h__\h] weirdo
not worth my time to be honest but if we
have to squeeze it in between something
else then okay
[Music]
he's your cousin we should play each
other inside
uh all right man let's play darts I pick
you up in next hour
yeah but no
never time okay
starts who hit starts me because
for him sorry
you guys told me about the fact that you
can cancel it and carry no consequences
like this
are you a good cousin here I guess not
but um I don't even have cousins that I
really am in contact with
so that makes me not a good cousin I
guess
the one cousin that I am like really
aware of and that I met before
I think he's like maybe one or two years
older than me
and
the one memory I have
of him is when I was in uh
uh what's before Junior High School like
an elementary school
it's Elementary in it
when I was in elementary school I was
collecting the little
like some kind of Mouse mascot little uh
like paper blocks and all that
and he was his side of the family was
off a little bit better financially and
he was a
single child No No Sisters no brothers
well I did have quite a few
so I couldn't afford as many of those
papers
little blocks
yeah but they were like the hit they
were the the thing in school everybody
was collecting them mostly girls but I
guess some boys do because he was a boy
and um I didn't have so many but I was
doing my best to collect them and then
making myself a respectful respectable
collection and had it in this big folder
uh however yeah because he had like he
was he was getting quite spoiled from
his mommy
down
so like I I went
uh
to their house once and I saw his room
and he had like a million
things
his room was full of that [\h__\h] and I was
like can you give me some but he
wouldn't really share with me
and so I was [\h__\h] jealous that he got
everything
and then later on afterwards I think
and my my little collection was stolen
School
so then I add them more and I think I
asked him if he could share some with me
one more shotgun but he was being really
really stinky stingy about it
yeah
you're so mean oh I can only remember
you'll continue to make the community a
better place hey man yo for a cop you
ain't so bad man you don't give it up
the streets
officer McCree This is Nico right here
this is my man Nico oh good to meet you
I'm sure he's grown up before a decent
man bye now
look Manny I gotta go all right keep
doing what you're doing thank you
officer just what I remember from
childhood yeah you know it was a real
thing for me you know
and I don't I don't remember
no I don't I haven't met him since then
since
um
the community to make things better I
mean where I'm from out here man police
is a dirty word Manny I got things to do
you off yo man my mind
the mother I was one of them
like charity work [\h__\h] man I'm the voice
of the streets man yo if I'm gonna make
some money that's the way shit's gonna
be all right I'm just saying whatever
man [\h__\h] punk I'm your long lost
cousin
give me these little papers I need you
to get somebody and now move down
whatever
promise Miss McCready I was gonna get
this place cleaned up and I will okay
how many a bunch man a bunch they're
hanging out and making bad [\h__\h] happen
all over South Bohan man they're over on
Windmill Street right now all right what
did they do man they disrespected the
clothes of the streets man the streets
man they owe you man yeah
over here man I'm on you yo that's what
I'm saying man Street we got codes man
you know what I'm saying we live by
these codes you know
flush
yeah so
I will only talk to my cousin if he
delivers 500 little papers to me
otherwise we ain't talking ever again
no many no many how many years have
passed
just kidding
it's not that serious
and there's not even like a particular
reason why
I haven't met him since it's just like I
don't know our whole like family tree
it's just like
we don't really like mingle much you
know what I mean
like me my mom my brother my half-sister
yeah we meet but then you know
it's just like other we don't really
mingle except for my
except for my half sister like she
mingles with her part of the family
oh yeah
the other way around not much
[Music]
because I've done this from the car
um wow probably
ah [\h__\h]
yeah branches of family tree
there's still someone there that do I
have to kill him
okay
time to go
oh he's they're just driving around the
block
okay okay okay I thought they were
already like over the [\h__\h] mountains
[Music]
you can run but you can't hide
[Applause]
done done baby
[Music]
oh 1100
yeah stop running guys Manny I got rid
of your street problem now help me out
with my financial one yeah it's all
business with you kid yeah that's okay
money's what makes these streets big man
I'll call you when I get more work stay
safe stay real thanks
that was fun a quick little walk in the
park time to go back to the internet
cafe
I don't know if they replied but by the
time I'll be there hopefully they did
my chat sometimes even though I'm not
tapping out it Scrolls up my chat
and I have to scroll down again but for
that I have to tap out
spooky
also the mini map keeps on disappearing
[Music]
that
um
it was taxi for faster
I suppose you didn't watch my GTA 5
player through huh
taxi ain't my thing
I drive with my own feet
in my hands
yeah
you might have some work for you
Elizabeth
board side
another another person who wants me to
do their [\h__\h]
[Music]
anymore where is she
on this island [\h__\h] hell I'm going is
there no way
internet in the Bronx
can I not check it out in the Bronx
[\h__\h] no
Bronx only has dial up
what the [\h__\h]
they don't use the internet maybe maybe
not back then but now they definitely do
sure I'm sure did
uh do we have to pay in this one too
okay
thank you oh there's almost five bucks
a bit cheaper
I thought it was 10 bucks again
a complicated series of carrier pigeons
ah I see I see
[Music]
oh
birds are always the popular choice
to do anything in life understandable
I get it I would prefer to communicate
through chickens too
[Music]
we're so popular yeah don't do anything
in this world
honestly we should overtake the humans
should we not
I think we can do it
oh [\h__\h]
we deserve it
some respect man
[Music]
we don't want to be served crumbs no
more no no we want some freaking proper
deep dish pizza or something
no more stupid crumbs bread crumbs for
the birds
proper food please
uprising
probably shouldn't go in here with guns
out in the open
my place is taken what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
deep dish in your city with one state
the thing I was just you know
thinking of
let me look at my profile
oh my job is sugar daddy perfect and I
am athletic am I really that athletic
though
I'm a vulnerable guy who needs to be
held by big strong arms I'm a man in
need but wait
if I'm the sugar daddy and I'm athletic
shouldn't I be the one with the big
strong arms
oh well I am a man in need of looking
after I want to be told that I am the
only guy in the world I've got a
shitload of cash and I want to spend it
on the first guy I meet hey man I've got
so much lettuce I could open the salad
bar it's all you can eat when you're
rolling with me that's how I roll
need to have big arms Define delts lats
and triceps some must money dollar bills
baby all that [\h__\h] men who let me pay
the check bling bodies hell yeah don't
mind people who use the bull shark
testosterone as long as they don't have
funny balls
a reference to certain someone weird
balls dislikes weird balls people who
take money and go into hiding and think
they ain't ever going to be found jokes
hot women titties all that straight [\h__\h]
America's Next Top Hooker if they did
that show with rent boys maybe I'd watch
it
should I date myself
yes
anyway
can we we're not gonna reply it let's
see maybe would it go here
did he not reply
foreign
what happens if you write to the others
think yourself
you can see the car oh
but it didn't say I can't oh wait now I
can do it maybe
done deal it will show me where it is
right
shuttler
[Music]
uh
this one
yeah okay
okay I was not so far but I'll take a
new car mine is like falling apart again
um
oh [\h__\h] there's a police over there
um they probably wouldn't even see but
still
oh wait wait
now time to take the bike
no no
bike a little bit more convenient
[Music]
nice break
I like the sound
and beat and be back
B for bike
sit strong working
[Music]
oh
there's someone there though
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
do I have to fight him
[\h__\h] manage to do business when you open
his crew
what
go friend
I broke the game
I played the game
I crashed
crash
dead headshot
was too good apparently for my own good
[Laughter]
oh no
how unfortunate man
Phoenix so strong I couldn't held back
my power
one shot 40 90. it is a 40 80 maybe the
49 he could have handled it no but I
this is not my my my fault right it's a
game's fault right you guys keep on
saying that the game is not so well
optimized for you PC
I don't care how to play GTA 5. I
already played it and finished it on my
channel last year
went through the whole game
there's a playlist on my channel if
you're interested
GTA 5 playlist if you want to watch the
Bots there they were a lot of fun
stream starting now we're just getting
started
where are we
welcome everybody today we're playing
GTA 4 again thank you for coming today
just made it in time wonderful oh I am
at home then we shall
sleep actually because why not
then we actually might be uh already
getting our reply
um
from our
upcoming lover
have you been having nightmares recently
oh yes so oh yes I've had a nightmare
you know
I wanted to tell you guys about that so
sad
Nico have you heard from your boyfriend
yet check your mail again thank you
don't I have another one
hmm
ah I still vexed about that dog heart
Dimitri you got them rude driving skills
to get I and I away from there keep your
head down and keep in touch easy
uh okay is he telling me to just be
careful and drive
how are you handling the heat well
actually yeah I gotta tell you guys
something
I think I figured out how the heat thing
the cooling thing works in my
apartment yeah I'm embarrassed to tell
you guys though
[Music]
I was tired of him as soon as I saw him
okay
going in foreign
I'll take this one
excuse me
it's called Golden whales
that one too that we're matching yeah
we're twinsies
oh we got a yeah the E is so close okay
I'll go to the e
come on quickly
and there was police around I didn't see
Wendy's for real to you
[Music]
and I already checked out the swing set
you it was quite the beginning so you're
welcome to check that out in the bar too
I did
um
this car ain't so bad though what's that
in the trunk is that is that subwoofers
oh [\h__\h] did you take that to the MTV
show where they pimp your ride
because damn that's a [\h__\h] disco
that's the way you want it Amigo then
that's what you're gonna get and let's
show you my [\h__\h] punk
oh we learned tonight
he's with me
Liz This is Nico romance cousin and Nico
this is Elizabeth she's an old friend
she'll get you some work okay thank you
so tough guy you know about this
business
I know about protection
what do you need
I need someone no one knows
to oversee a deal I'm not sure about
easy I think it'll be a bit more taxing
than hanging with Manny on the streets
not sure for one I won't have to listen
to him talk
[Music]
yeah let's roast them more and more and
more hey Nico this is Patrick [\h__\h]
mcquiri all right so
[\h__\h] is shopping but I've never trusted
the people he's buying off and I can't
in good Consciousness help him unless
he's got some extra insurance you and
that's why you're the best darling ah
maybe all right tough guy let's do this
sure
will you call Michelle again she really
likes you yeah yeah when I swear it's
okay
is that have a nice day
packing where are we going I got this
meeting over on toilet Street there's a
rifle up on the roof of the place next
door you need to go up there and make
sure nothing goes wrong rifle in the
room me and my boys show up in a bruful
you're my guardian angel you don't trust
these guys you're trying to deal with
your teeth
think about you and I'm lucky with my
feelings
Buena suerte
okay
uh-huh okay
Angel today I am angle
a cute angle
nice orange car this the ruins is so
rare here
and like
okay
[Music]
yo wait can I keep it because I I I
don't I didn't have a sniper rifle until
now it was actually kind of nice to have
oh sick
vantage point
where am I shooting
sniping baby
with the sniper rifle okay
that's not Packy or the associated
the fancy jacket guys okay okay
every day I spend to burn your house
down
yeah actually we did
[Music]
okay what
I wish I could read lips
I know what's going on should I shoot
randomly
just the trash cans wouldn't that be fun
oh
[\h__\h]
did I get him yeah
can I get him can I get him
ah did I get him
no this one though
there's like sand inside or something
why
should I aim higher I don't know I have
this feeling that like maybe I should
aim lower on purpose that's what I've
been doing oh that worked out actually
[Music]
sorry I didn't see him
I am sorry but your friend Patrick's
luck ran out
Anna
does that mean pig sounds like it
[\h__\h]
oh I felt like I was doing well so much
for being Garden angle I wasn't stable I
guess
okay oh I got the gun already
uh where's the building okay
maybe I'll just walk
oh
uh man
wasn't it in GTA 5 so that if you put uh
like run around of your gun
uh
kind of a problem
but I haven't been noticing that in this
game
Walk of Shame yeah in the rain
right now more realistic and GTA V also
my butt is starting to hurt from all
this sitting
man
maybe I'll do Super Chat reading while
standing
do I get a second one
me just completely ignoring the dead guy
on the ground
there was blood so I'm assuming he's
dead second sniper rifle
oh ah you get more ammo
oh yeah standing desk oh [\h__\h] my butt um
do not
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know that's not what I meant
sorry
oh my butt hurts
come on
now
anybody here
[Music]
right in his weird ass balls one more to
be rabbit secure
okay
I was good that I checked
checking again okay
is that friend of her take down the last
bit before he makes the getaway oh
it's safer I think
ah I think we did that
it took too long to start his car
yes yay
those dealers double crossed your boy
but I managed to keep him alive that's
good ending the good timeline
yeah Rocky let's pack up okay and go
home
there's a dead guy still here maybe I
should call an ambulance for him oh he's
gone
he's gone
where are we going now
ah she's close so I guess we go there
again
one more one more and then we check the
emails Maybe
oh what's with all these cars here
the body wouldn't care or not notice so
quickly
yeah it was like plenty and Far Away
what are these
stop
I know I uh I can just go in here
quick quick get up get up this place is
assisted
wait wait where are we where am I oh
there did I just glitch through the wall
I think I did
get down yeah
[Laughter]
I like different people more than Manny
Nicole this is Johnny now Johnny is
sitting on a big pile of heroin I Don't
Go Near I mean that's not cool but you
know but
[Music]
I thought sure
thank you well I gotta go play
does this ever overlap with Manny though
because wait aren't they about to deal
drugs and Manny doesn't like that [\h__\h]
This is Nico and Nico is Playboy what's
up money
[Music]
that's his nickname Playboy wow ready to
bounce
puppet
[Laughter]
the Cassidy Street in shotler I Like
Your Dragon
take Playboy to the context apartment
okay
car oh bike car
that car should still work right
remember the first guy trouble it was
him this Playboy
or someone else
who we talking yo be careful
yeah enter
Johnny does Elizabeth get you to do
stuff like this often Elizabeth don't
get me to do [\h__\h] I just like to keep an
eye on things
for real yeah but how come we haven't
met before you obviously ain't been big
time I started small like you play
slanging rocks on the corner sticking
cats up all type of [\h__\h] it was the old
days now it's all about diversification
a heroin deal is your way of
diversifying money say JUMP can't say
how high this is a cash deal I got other
[\h__\h] going down as well
is looking for work
the base that is I pay like a songberg
sacks bonus [\h__\h] it's Christmas every
day when you rolling with this [\h__\h] so
you got the word not yet I gotta set
[\h__\h] up but I need a cat like you real
soon give me your number tell me about
that biker the one with the smack Johnny
I ain't working with that cat but I
heard about him he's doing all type of
crazy [\h__\h] blowing stuff up them boys
the loss they in some heavy type of gang
wars what I heard crazy White Boy [\h__\h]
think only one group can grow beards and
ride bikes in this town it's a B I can't
follow the conversations
or some [\h__\h] anyways be careful of this
cat don't want to even look at him the
wrong way crazy [\h__\h] you scared
of him yeah I ain't scared of nobody all
them bikers is racist as [\h__\h] I tweeted
what
what's that doing
maybe that's why I couldn't follow the
conversation
what
is that right let me see
that that tweet went through now
oh interesting I sent that on my phone
ages ago
[Music]
ah
now
I sent that ages ago
[Music]
I thought that went through sometimes
when I tweet on my phone it just doesn't
go through
unless I open up Twitter again then
often it goes through but I guess I
haven't opened like I tweeted and then I
probably closed my
Twitter app immediately
and then it just didn't really properly
finish sending but I didn't open my
phone now either
we are kid
the melon man
you don't understand what my what do you
mean you don't understand it's the
future
[Music]
that is the future
holy [\h__\h] the way this car turns
is it because it's such a big car
feels like it's about to just
oh okay
then I will be avoiding these kind of
cards in the future
kind of annoying
especially it's like a chair you stole
[Music]
all right
the crib is on the third floor oh we had
someone on the car I forgot that
I forgot that I'll play with me to
contact on the third floor okay
is that a sniper no that's a shotgun
big shotgun
I don't know what I picked up
I recognize it didn't pick it up
what
hey you ready sure let's do this nothing
like selling some dope to let you know
you're alive let's do this all right
come on
oh well
hey what's going on guys what's going on
not much let's do this you got the Heron
right right come on let's do this
quickly but you got the Heron correct
you're carrying it correct I mean it's a
simple question what's wrong with you
you're being [\h__\h] weird the left guy
is weird man I don't even know if you're
carrying this stuff right you ain't
right friend no come on let's get out of
here LCPD freeze [\h__\h] I said
freeze
I got you now
[Music]
Everybody Take Cover
really
ended
there's something here no where are we
going
Everybody Get Down what are you doing
what is he doing
okay to move hmm
please Evacuate the area
oh these police people
like FBI or something
what are you doing why are you not doing
anything Johnny
you're just chilling
[Music]
man not much of a help busy
why is that bathtub so randomly in the
middle of the room
oh oh
oh yeah
why why would I
why would I replace
[Music]
how is he shorting in that position damn
he's dedicated
okay one more I think or two more
[Music]
put your hands up in the air
let's go
[\h__\h]
you're going to die friend girl money
follow me
fun fun fun fun fun
oh what a romantic scenery
[Music]
okay we did it we did it Johnny oh
Johnny
Johnny it's not a German song
my daddy
uh right it's not Johnny what is it
Johnny is
screaming
I'm sorry you ran into my you ran into
my peel range
dude
[Music]
nice doctor
get some Pace on Pam we ghosting through
here you want to start rolling
Rolling Drive me back to my crib in
North
you wanna hurry up or
[Music]
we gotta go this way
[Laughter]
New Island
you see following me
all these [\h__\h] stairs I'm so bad
those stairs
from a good long distance all good for
him to be so safe
okay can we take the bite or are we
taking oh maybe we'll take the police
car
because that's the closest thing here
like offering yourself to me
[Music]
we gotta be getting rid of those Stars
[Applause]
[Music]
I have a perfect overview and control of
the city oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
no no problem no problem here
[Music]
which way should I go straight I should
go straight
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
somebody said f to turn off siren
laughs
you a little [\h__\h] but I'm out of the
circle I'm out of the circle I'm out of
the circle
e
wait Playboy we're taking the oh are we
does it count as like wait we're done
with the police let's take a normal car
because if I take it take that car again
maybe it counts as stealing a police car
again
okay
she actually that was according to my
keikaku
sorry
oh
my oh hello elderly people please help
me so show Playboy just leave them beer
why you gotta get us in more trouble
ah
laughs
why are they there
why are they right there okay losing the
star
easy easy
okay where are we going where are we
actually going I had a [\h__\h] died
instead of being caught by an infant
take a bid on a heroin beat you ain't
seeing life for a long time you riding
up in that [\h__\h] yeah future in the max
security pen ain't no future at all you
forget about them cancer do that sort of
time and if you're friends on the inside
my man's Dwayne Ford just inside on a
crap beat he showed me some [\h__\h] back in
the day but when he gets out if he you
have a good
it won't be the same world what's
different since this guy's been doing
his bid [\h__\h] changed there'll be more to
it than the crack tip nowadays there'll
be the smack tip the rap game X chronic
meth [\h__\h] I'm looking into expanding my
horizons yeah the show reach for the
stars and all that [\h__\h] I don't see why
a young kid from the hood can't make
something out of himself Street cats
like me just get labeled as pimps and
pushes and stick up orders but you are a
drug Pusher that's just what I'm doing
to get out of the ghetto I don't see
this dealing drugs drugs is just one arm
of my business I'm buying and selling
that [\h__\h] like any commodity on the
trading floor okay this commodity is
illegal yeah but Playboy is going
legitimate now I want to be one of them
developer cats build me some skyscrapers
yeah I thought you would want to build
schools or something help young black
men get out of the ghetto [\h__\h] gotta get
me successful first that's wrong
if you have to go to university and
stuff for that for a long time
serious we're going to the other Island
oh this looks more like New York baby
finally the real New York
sorry Bronx in Brooklyn
was pretty nice over there but not
exactly what I imagined when I heard
about New York
Manhattan
wow wow wow
New York is kind of playing
like really like nice and like in terms
of like you know interesting
um
structuring of the city I don't know how
to say what I'm trying to say
with the water in between and all that
and the bridges
hmm
yeah the layout yeah the layout City
Planning
don't let the glints and glamor fool you
double traffic Yeah well yeah that's
that that will be true
but surely New York has plenty to make
up for that right
nobody bump into me okay
and now I'm stuck
how can I not go straight
really
oh
I gotta get a new car now
troublesome
that's
that's the fog you're saying I need to
learn how to back up probably
that's that's sad oh [\h__\h] that person
was driven over
that was not my fault it was not my
fault I just bought a little bit
like I scratched the wall
and got me stuck not even like doesn't
even make sense
hmm
now we low riding holy [\h__\h] that's quite
the low ride
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
gotta be careful with this car
wow
Welcome to New York
Yankee AKA Liberty City
where's the freedom lady we should visit
the freedom Lady it's the freedom lady
here somewhere
[Music]
oh hi Shane where's she at
I need to talk to her
I need to have a little chit chat about
what she really thinks Freedom Is All
About Liberty
[Music]
I think we have different opinions
really
[Music]
statue of Happiness here not Liberty uh
really Oh you mean the game is called
statue of Happiness oh excuse me
pop popping how they really solve it in
the hood
watch Real Men Slug It Out On The Dance
Floor
[Music]
okay okay that's how it is
you should go teach them how to dance I
can teach them I can teach them
our my dances he just box I can teach
them do you it's a really difficult you
know
I'll hit you up when I need your ass
I don't think they can keep up until
then then move her hands and I love that
so much
[Music]
okay this might be the one time I take a
taxi because I want to go to the
Internet cafe wait there's one here
let's go I mean yeah
since this is a completely different
Island there should be one here
I'm calling her elizabetha things didn't
go so good the contact was you think I
know
yeah whatever uh I'm going back to
the main quest I think oh man where you
at
it can be any internet cafe right now
let's check our males
did he reply finally French
song
hello just saw you were interested in
yours truly get in line to be honest my
inbox has been filling up every 10
seconds since I put up the ad I was just
sending out a load of rejections when I
saw you and you don't look like the
other guys well well you don't seem poor
or fat so let's start
this boy is too before those losers
come on how about you stop by the 69th
Street Diner in hoof bring your wallet
because you are picking up the check
I'll wear a red rose I'm usually there
around 8. see you later
Tom Rivers oh yeah
it goes off
we're gonna go to the date but if it's
really far then
what why you no show me do I have to get
into the card for it to show me where it
is
Central Park
nanny
no an electrical fire not Arthur maybe
it was an accident
B look around okay good where did he put
it I wonder
uh but
[Music]
um
well
does it show me when I'm in the car
oh I need to wait for the daytime I have
to get dressed really
the first Island
okay but can you guys tell me roughly
where it is so I'm just in the area
near my old so somewhere down here
maybe we'll go here
the restaurant one
um that's a long drive
okay how do you use a taxi I'll just get
in
producer always
[Music]
okay
where do you want to go
uh how do I tell you where I want to go
the Waypoint oh yeah I guess
yeah enter Sundance Street please on our
way don't play with the windows
after accident skip an actual clock and
surprise
space to hurry come on let's go hold on
hold this let's just skip it
[Music]
total
well okay thanks man
ah I went to this place okay well we can
go to the clothing store but wait is
there not a different one a better one
or do they sell different things now or
would I would I have had to go in one of
these
and [\h__\h] expensive
maybe I could
wasted 80 bucks
no problem
no problem for someone like me
but I did this okay
no no no no you ain't getting your car
back
yo money something's come up hit me at
my crib because I got work for y'all
the X what who
[Music]
doesn't mean yeah what I can't I can't
see the other message I'm too stupid to
use this phone
a Playboy
[Music]
oh okay
hey Nico I'm gay now Michelle you are
working with Elizabeth
that's because
I don't date ladies anymore you aren't
getting involved in that world are you
I'm trying to avoid the blue shield but
maybe I'll do a few errands for
Elizabeth and nothing serious though I
am no dealer if you need help with
anything Nico just speak to me
I can look after myself I'm a big boy
and I must make my own decisions
[Music]
Big World
I don't feel dumb drugs I just kill them
I'm a big big boy
with a big big box one day I will be the
president
[Music]
I Believe In You Nico I'll help you Fish
Market South
come on is there really gonna be fancy
clothes and in the fish market
area
[Music]
should they not be doing business with
her come on
oh my God because
[Music]
um
I still have two times and took two
hours
[Music]
maybe
um
a heart icon wait wait
I it's like fairly close
I don't need the clothes well we are
here now
oh and it's kind of fancy
um
okay let's be quick
oh oh
finally oh
buying it
do I need shoes
oh yeah okay
how are you finding things have you got
enough to do here at Liberty City yeah I
think I've got enough on my plate at the
moment well if you need some down time
go hang out at the apartment and watch
some American TV
it's in the old country most of the [\h__\h]
on TV in the old country was from
America don't you remember Roman Roman I
need to get into the car apparently I
can't get in the car when I'm calling
you
okay uh can I make it shoes are by the
wall oh
it's the link down it's fine right as
long as I just have a suit
and then I scroll to chat up again even
though I'm not Tapped Out
actually doesn't take time at all
[Music]
okay
good
morning
oh man
will he be there right away though if I
call him for a free taxi
I don't know about that ah
whatever
ah please let me in
it
[Music]
foreign
[\h__\h] is it like automatic when you're
carrying a gun and you go into a taxi
that it takes it as we're taking over
the taxi
[Music]
you need to hold the button ah okay okay
I'll be more careful next time
I was gonna take a taxi hoping it will
be faster
but okay
wow traffic jam
[Music]
the war against F continues
I made this car I'm on my way I'm on my
way is that the 30 minute reminder
I'm literally like there
in game time
seconds
I got it I got it
uh it's probably been 10 by now
oh God
[Music]
no
okay okay okay I thought I just failed
like right in front of it okay we're
going to diner I thought you didn't like
the place
okay
suit in the [\h__\h] Diner
is that him that's him
look rich you never
mind
sorts of sequels can use the internet
you have to be careful I'm Nico
so Nico what do you do I do a lot of
things what's your job job eventually
have to stand up and take out my weapons
I haven't met him and I don't want to Mr
Johnson's like an [\h__\h] you're an
[\h__\h]
normal music no more funky music
really what type of man do you want to
meet one with a lot of money do you know
Gay Tony runs Hercules amazing at nine
I'll tell you a secret he pretends to
have the dollars but he is broke as hell
the loser if there is one thing that I
hate more than fat people and cripples
it is poor guys is that why you borrow
money that you can't pay back what are
you talking about how the [\h__\h] do you
know who I pay and don't pay back [\h__\h]
you [\h__\h] you ain't missed that you got
a bad news I've heard enough while
you're standing
you've got a gun I'm not into that sick
[\h__\h] go play broken
am I killing him is that what that's
supposed to do
[Music]
people always kill people right that's
that's always what we want to do okay
okay wait my mini map is gone
foreign
okay okay
no more French Tony
or more of that
[Music]
it's always what I wanna do yeah
I don't know how that helps us getting
the money back but okay
not funny
[Music]
I'm small but I'm fast
what do you want what the [\h__\h] you when
you carve what what do you want
I don't think he'll be seeing anyone
to create
I don't know if it's okay to hang up
I thought it's rude to hang up what's
going on
[\h__\h] Bruce say I'm never helping that
bastard ever again just because he
called me
well how much how where's that sending
me back to
and my weapons is the date over
I think the date is over
my weapons can I have my weapon depend
I guess we can load this that's one
minute ago
easy
yeah
you still have your Oh I thought going
to the police takes all my guns
oops I forgot to press enter
all right let's see how now I got my wow
we already got like 20 bucks sheesh
so
is this also after date
this could be right after the date
actually
super convenient
I win
oh I should sleep my health is not full
is it
I think it's not full
[Music]
buy some shoes
be dressed up for this [\h__\h] date
it wasn't a diner and it was the guy who
was not dressed up at all either
you little shits but I look better now
I do look so much better yeah yeah
we're looking like some
some
Yakuza now
[Music]
so what are we doing next
m is close
but I want to do main quests so I think
Brucie would be main quest right
um
okay
I'm thinking and texting for realness
time where you want to go Heaven we're
going to mohanet Avenue nobody knows
this city better than me
all letters are made
first he feels more main quest
let's see
oh yeah yeah
31 bucks that's not bad
it's pretty good
let's see that little [\h__\h]
hey bro see what's up
hey Nico B come here show me the love
man um
I don't know what are we about boy oh
I'm an immigrant and the higher the gun
and you're a steroid junkie but we get
along no not that stuff that's
superficial I'm talking about the real
why we're winners man [\h__\h] winners
that's how we roll brother bling check
bodies check paper check that's how we
roll [\h__\h] the ball
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you man hey check this out
[\h__\h] obnoxious
[\h__\h] ready well she's very shiny look
at her and weep tears oh
[\h__\h] come on now let's go show some
people all right
come on get in
it
it's pure gold a big man
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] what is this what is
this you tune to yourself
well what should I do I mean I need a
flashy car I think
I think bullshitter if I fail to deliver
here exactly Steve's car
yes
call them on the way Nico can you drive
us to Freetown Avenue in Willis yeah
come on let's roll [\h__\h] of course I
can well clown looks nice can we get it
to work eventually
race car
and which guy am I getting not this one
oh this is
oh but wait for the police oh no it
should be okay
I'd like to see you try and take one of
my cars in Sunny
uh we're going here okay
[Music]
gotta turn around Nico man excuse me but
I gotta make this call to tell this guy
we're far in his car
okay
yeah make sure you get permission cards
borrow permission
oh man you can spot me yeah
the other one well of course it'll be
cool
what it's outside great love you man
he's fine with us thinking it we won't
have an incident like the last time I
got the car for you hey man that was a
one-time only baby me and Stevie are
tight okay tighter than that tighten it
[\h__\h] I was gonna save my hands but I
think you know that nothing's tighter
than this [\h__\h] yeah
thanks but uh I wouldn't subscribe
you and me could be doing some serious
damage like like a nuclear bomb up in
this [\h__\h] but but a sexy bomb you know a
bomb that only affects girls with d-cups
tight asses blonde hair
means
[Music]
I should think that that car opened
this area is cute
[Music]
the grandfather you [\h__\h] so fancy
is that the car oh my God it's [\h__\h]
orange just like me
a match made in heaven
or on Tinder you know same thing
yes let's [\h__\h] go this is my car now
sexy
huh
[Music]
me and you are cruising together that's
how we roll passenger side Flex in the
gold mistakes
ride a shotgun well my boy Nico pulls
off some badass Red Army pedal to the
Moon
am I right is that our style because I
think that that hand somebody making
stuff like nobody's a laptop
they should be listening to what I say
[Music]
I want to shoot them
oh wow that's so GTA baby
oh wow it's Mario Kartel change
can I still
is it fair too
wait we're doing lyrics
to cut the corners
[\h__\h] that slightly orange car you're
gonna be real orange like me
oh wait why am I not stepping on the gas
I got a [\h__\h] blister from those from
those Jimmy choos you know
what I'm thirst what's your problem
[Music]
all right I'm gonna show you
winners baby that's the only place for
us
[Music]
oh
that looks so stupid Oh my God
[Music]
why are they only following me stone
Fair everybody wants a piece of me
[\h__\h] out of her
okay I'm thirst again I think where are
we going oh
[Music]
baby
that's not fair oh my God
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
see you later then
and he seems pretty okay with it
it's fine it's fine I'm actually good at
driving in this game
we need some Wheels
all right
wait for this car
I'm down one floors
um
[Music]
it's your lucky day oh yeah please ah
not your lucky day
[Music]
I don't mean of course there's always
room for improvement
[Music]
I'd like to see you try and take one of
my clothes
considering I had to go real fast it's
gonna hit this guy up it was a lot of
traffic
this is hunk of Lady killing muscle that
was losing a lot of the time
went past me I was able to be outside to
catch up again after a while today bro
your friend is taking it
he doesn't think we're going to trash it
or nothing Stevie knows that he can
trust Brucie with anything to look after
[\h__\h] trust Bruce you with anything but
your girlfriend man then you can't be so
sure he'll look after her at least not
the way
you know what I mean
that's real cool I'm just joking man
Bruce you wouldn't [\h__\h] another man's
[\h__\h] he's got too many women
because I was looking at him but he
wasn't looking at me The Chaperone any
girlfriend of mine who are you kidding
Nikki you and me are a girlfriend types
we see [\h__\h] but we can't get tied
down we gotta get out there bro spread
our seed in his money Fields as we can I
don't know if I met the right girl
sometime that's what I say when people
ask me if the juice has given me funny
balls you know how could I be able to
get with so many chicks and my balls
were funny come on man think about it
[\h__\h] I don't really really
action self self uh what's the word
about his balls
awesome
something in my eye
like he's trying yeah conscious he's
trying to make double double sure
have you got a vagina envy that nobody
thinks he's got funny balls oh yeah bye
[Music]
maybe maybe
one of his ladies wants
saw his balls
and laughed at them
and that's why he's so sad about it
yeah
probably
says she was actually laughing about the
balls maybe maybe she was laughing about
something else
anything really
okay for [\h__\h] sake
sorry just getting warmed up
[Music]
something else I don't know maybe
wait there's a car in the way
I literally cannot get into my car
uh maybe for that without cupcake
Maybe
maybe he had moles around that area that
like all together look like a funny face
we're gonna dominate this [\h__\h]
but then that's probably still funny
though
you got some faith in me there's no
other place to First Nikki the rest of
that [\h__\h] don't count okay I got the
best body I get the hottest [\h__\h] I ride
the flyest cars I'm number one man I'll
burn your village you need your children
I'm [\h__\h] intense man yeah I've
managed to completely zone out and
stupid ass talk
like I'm not hearing it anymore thank
God
here we be you ready to feel the teeth
yes a state of Zen
I'm gonna be fast but also careful
smarter than these [\h__\h] look at them
[Music]
good touch
yeah one day of shooting is nothing I'm
guessing no
I I'm guessing you have to actually do
this fairly interesting
[Music]
we gotta get the red one in trouble
don't hold back on this [\h__\h] okay
second
one
they were all getting in weightless like
accidents than last time
um
I believe I believe I Keep On Believing
okay
the red one's good man
[Music]
okay we got really close to him oh [\h__\h]
I don't think I've ever had the look at
the back end of a competitive
I'll fix it
fix uh is it like only straight now
[Music]
oh look at me right
oh wait it's not over yet oh it's not
over yet okay
oh I think I see the red one but this
one this is at the end oh God yeah
that's [\h__\h]
if it was before that at the end
um
yeah I thought overall I had way life
accidents
everybody else also has way less
accidents we'll come back another time
and really show that how we [\h__\h] roll
okay I want to do it another time again
I mean I'm gonna do it again
yeah this town started to get on my
nerves
say good night
number one
I wanna number one
and I haven't played Mario Kart in a
long time
every time I gotta start from here
that's so annoying
can I please around no oh
[Music]
I'm not gonna lose my [\h__\h] weapons
again man hey Nikki I'm just gonna hit
this guy up Stevie we see this Uncle
lady killing muscle me me and a friend
need to borrow your car and a sweet one
that'll be cool baby High School oh you
know bro
all right great stay strapped bro hey
friend is fine with us taking it
he doesn't think we're going to trash it
or nothing Stevie knows that he can
trust Bruce we will definitely trash
the way you want her to be looked after
you know what I mean you know well
that's real cool I know how to deal with
the police
he's got too many women after him
already to waste his time with taking
[\h__\h] once again they lost track of me
I'm definitely asking The Chaperone any
girlfriend of mine who are you kidding
Nikki
but we can't get tied down there's only
other safe we're going on as many fields
as we can I don't know if I met the
right girl sometime that's what I
people ask me if the juice has given me
funny balls you know how could I be able
to get with so many chicks and my balls
were funny come on man think about it
bro I don't need to think about your
balls I'm cool
yeah if only one could save after
getting the car or if it only is with
auto safe after getting the car no
checkpoints um
we gotta make this one clown
[Music]
um
your dick
snaking my way through
oh this time the car is not parked in on
the side have you got a vagina and B
stop driving like this bro yeah maybe
next time I take a taxi to this orange
car
[Music]
Just One Last confirmation I'm really
not supposed to shoot them right
just just checking
[Music]
no shooting I thought so oopsie
can I flatten their tires
okay I can push them off the road
if I want to try that
sorry well if I can damage them
beforehand does that do anything
[Music]
I know
again the red one is the worst one
different every time but less I think
the last two times before
the red one was always pretty good but
never mind Maybe not maybe maybe they
always mix it up
[Applause]
not so bad
oh we lucky this time
careful turns
Apple turns
these things
but they're probably having a lot of
trouble in the back without me
because if they still didn't catch up
damn after me making so many stupid
mistakes
welcome
baby
and really do be lonely all alone here
barely a race
[Music]
okay okay okay
because the top of the pile is so
[\h__\h] high oh no
what
[Music]
you think someone like me has come
second even worse no [\h__\h] way
so it's extra secure extra safe
baby I'm literally driving alone the
game had mercy on me
that's the only problem ah the red one
comes flying at me
love you man number one good job
yeah pretty good take me back to my
apartment man I'm not feeling jacked I
want to hit the weights
he's motivated
sorry they made it really easy for me
this time
[Music]
no cellulite okay VIP only read my lips
I'm a winner
[Music]
sure but don't give me that
entrepreneurship
why you need gas kill of course I'm
Legit have you seen my delts that [\h__\h]
is as legitimate as it gets what about
these guys you need to kill [\h__\h] Nikki
you know Bruce he's number one it's
Lonely at the Top sometimes the juice it
just takes control okay Red Mist
descends and I need [\h__\h] to happen to
people I do feel the oversteering yeah
is that why I killed them difficult they
were bad cats Nikki maybe the juice man
that wasn't as uh Nikki good we made him
shut up I'm close to you man you let me
inside
you let your armor down you know we had
a moment man um
[Music]
I don't think we did he was saying
who's that
that's so annoying can he ever shut up
like a bar
so what about saving my car how do I
save the car
somebody said I have to bring it to my
apartment
you can't
you never shuts up he should be a
YouTuber or like a streamer in general I
guess
park in front parking spot okay okay so
that way it would always be there
[Music]
okay
but I also want to fix it first does the
car wash fix it
or the spray paint
[Music]
I think the spray paint fixes it
thank you
okay
parking it at my place does not fix it
[\h__\h] jealous haters
it does
it does well then I don't have to go to
pain spray
whenever you park a damage foreign
[Music]
on the Liberty Tree website what that
[\h__\h] says you looked older you gotta get
some work done bro I get shot the whole
time don't get asked I knew this was
Brucey
[Music]
his face does look like you've got some
shots
and I mean also look at his teeth
it takes
maybe a little bit too much good care of
himself
because at this point you know he's just
like a little bit too I wouldn't even
say perfect because I don't I can't even
like see that as perfect
it's just too much it's over the top
um
a shop sure I'll come over and pick you
up
Cabaret
who was that little Jacob right
now
I won't be able to make that show man
it's all right next time it's all right
hmm sorry he sounded a bit sad
but I'm trying to make progress you know
although I did promise titties for this
um
gold
guess I have to follow up with that
somehow
well you got the swing
calling back
there I'm gonna see some kitties if it's
a TV show I will go
is there anything else
then no thank you
[Music]
Phoenix thank you
surprised they don't get really [\h__\h]
mad at me doing that
[Music]
every Sports a driver I
have special parmesan okay
you presents
should all be behind me
isn't it obvious know your place
[Music]
after Autobahn and I love understand
ing Skies
[Music]
trying to find words for my new song
yellow
the parking residence parking only
dance
now man how about you me hit the bowling
out
[Music]
let's go bowling I'll come collect you
with India well I'll take this car
although it would have been nice to
picking up but pick him up with um
oh yeah oh yeah the limousine that was
just driving by
[Music]
okay
uh we're picking up Roman right Roman my
man where is he
wait wasn't that Roma
Rossi
I just assumed I'm going bowling with
Rosie that was uh Roman that was Bruce
you
[Music]
sorry Brucey I can't actually go bowling
with you right now even with Roman I
would have gone
bro
so now that we're free we can go here to
Manny
enough a really annoying person
on
car goes here
a lot of annoying questions for real for
real
I didn't
down there
me lady also hasn't been calling me for
a long time maybe she saw me on that
dating website looking for men
yeah Urban masculinity
yo man you made me look gay man bro what
no you remember your own dialogue
who the hell ever heard of a metrosexual
X gangster man I'm a lord man not a lady
this show is gonna make me famous you
are gonna be famous yo Nico man what am
I supposed to do here man I got this
film genius here making me look like a
transsexual or something on TV and now
some Punk's been talking all kinds of
[\h__\h] too what's punks man [\h__\h] I used
to roll with guys caught up in the game
punks In Too Deep man yo I tried man I
tried to be a good guy I said I'm
reformed man but I'm pure ghetto man
this show is garbage oh come on man jeez
we need to go bust somebody man do what
you want as long as it doesn't involve
me hey yo man we're Brethren right give
it up man all right man yo listen can
you shut these bugs up for me please
where are they they're gonna be coming
in on the L train man from Algonquin to
Dukes man hey I owe you man I owe you
big time okay you see that man you see
that man yo that is streets right there
man not none of this [\h__\h] got me dancing
in skirts with people in the
neighborhood what the [\h__\h] is that man
it's been five hours how long did I play
Yesterday guys
mm-hmm
because maybe I'll end it soon
[Music]
yeah to read more Super chats and to eat
food and everything
and I still want to get some things done
because tomorrow's a weekday
and I have to scan something before the
weekday begins and send it to my
to my people
[Music]
and finish up some other stuff that's
happened
ignoring
[Music]
not not full life related actually
though
actually
finished pretty much all my deadlines uh
actually they asked me to retake one
thing so I have to retake like one word
for something
I tried that before the stream but
apparently it was wrong again so I have
to do it again after the Stream
so hopefully I still have some voice
left
but it seems urgent
blah
one take yeah no usually when I need to
record something
usually they appreciate having more than
one take so
I do like depends on who I work with
three two five takes
but I mean if I think something wrong
that doesn't count as a take I like redo
it of course
[Music]
well apparently you're saying something
wrong and I didn't notice I didn't
realize
sometimes it do be like that this car is
hella fast to them
[\h__\h]
sh we have arrived
yeah yeah
the target is on the train follow the
train taking him out when what follow
the train
[Music]
uh I've got to keep an eye on the train
tracks what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh that's right I'm trying but I don't
know where I should drive when let me
look at the train tracks
train goes
this one
is that like a sign for it's like a
station to get often probably he will
get off there
it's a meme yeah I don't know why Chad
is getting so upset right now
I would I would think probably he gets
up there
hmm
hold it okay okay okay okay okay okay
I'm just trying to get a rough idea of
where he's going
to go
[Music]
um
uh I'll keep on going straight and maybe
next right
after that
[Music]
I still see him
there he is down
where are we going left yeah
okay if we're lucky we're gonna lose the
cups while following the dude
yeah it looks good
is he getting off no
he's not going to the fun fair now
it's so difficult to drive
[Music]
looking at myself or anything
how am I meant to catch this [\h__\h]
train right
what I'm saying uh
better go right side I think
uh
yeah that looks bad here
and then right side and then left and
left and up right
[\h__\h] Manny making me take stupid
trains this town is starting to get on
my nerves
it was just a small mistake small small
mistake
[Music]
where are we
can I take a taxi
I take as a taxi taxi taxi Mr Taxi Taxi
toxins me
is that texting
it's taken what about you what about are
you also taking can I still no I guess
not
why are they taking tax
realistic
I need a tank
I'm going to [\h__\h] sue you bastard
I'm detoxing and dancing
that looks empty
no no no not the police car
no
and then this one
where can I take me to Brunner Street I
know a fun way to go
a fun way
I just want a fast way please
here we are that's uh very kind of you
okay
wait is that is he gonna like
immediately like drive off the the the
train
wait I need I need the car
um
fast car would be nice but
this is not the area for fast cars
I assume
the area for police cars
please car fast
I'll just take this one
I believe there's a police officer
will he see it
I don't think he did
oh
he pretended to not see
thank you he doesn't want me to have to
do the quest another time
[Music]
so sweet
okay you know what music time
yeah that's fun
it was fun
or
[Music]
then I see you
across the dance floor so now honey
follow me
[Music]
Bang Bang
take me away
[Music]
I don't need no drinks tonight give me
that please get me something
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] you
feels like the same place
[Music]
yeah I can't is this where I have to go
right not yet right first left
it's all about it because
[Music]
brother
take me away
[Music]
is that will they forgive me if I go
left
oh my gosh
I don't care who's watching us so baby
baby
I get off the car
so I'm gonna just goes hard it's my song
I don't know if you're serious but it's
my song favorite nine
[Music]
just give me the pack of Merida okay
where will I am being
[Music]
making with you
stationed on here
Lily come down hello
[Music]
YouTube
Sarah wasn't innocent
[Music]
this is when the song ended but it's
repeating you don't need to worry about
people talking garbage no more
[Applause]
yeah
only one bystander I'm sorry about that
that never happened to me before
it'll be a one-time only thing I promise
lately
um
oh that's not my car
oh [\h__\h]
oh I guess it's that one over there
[Music]
okay well everybody else was so far away
you ran in front of the bullet yeah he
should have just gotten down
[Music]
the beat is so good
baby
um
to sound take over me intoxicating TJ
keep playing
[Music]
it was unknown
why are you sending me where'd you get
my phone number
where is that is that close
it's not
a bottle
I'm just driving home now
Take Me Away knock it never mind I mean
a middle commitment
baby
underneath the Trap I come alive move my
feet to something new I don't need no
drinks tonight what I need some fresh
titties
makes me wild
OH police picking up really
oh they just checking
on things
[Music]
start to fight New York Police
Department really
foreign
I love dancing that last part
yeah also I love dancing the chorus
sounds
fun song to dance to for me
quite a bit less exhausting and
stressful
and Sparks and do you like the Sparks
and do you dance moves are like
a bit rough for me partially
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
any important looks so cool thank you go
catchy too right
and it fits GTA in my opinion hey the
the vibe the instrumentals
we have arrived baby almost probably new
live show so the fashion Garden teens
um
should we bring someone
well if only I wouldn't have to pick
everybody up
[Music]
wait
sick
foreign
what happens if I type in poduno
okay nothing
no hits
[Music]
it's all kind of loud
wow wait
[Music]
but I can't I can't I'm like dancing at
me with that
um
[Music]
it says it has it's sexy and it has
erotic
tone color a Timber what's this oh
[Music]
it's called a little bit bulgar
vulgar erotic
Timber sexy jazz
[Music]
well there's even more dirty
dirty vulgar jazz
same person who did this one
[Music]
this person really likes dirty jazz
wait what what happened story
School
can I get strip music
no
who's this
[Music]
that's something else but I like that
foreign
[Music]
music that's what I should be looking
for
says uh
mellow Lounge music
[Music]
which one is that which one did I just
download
[Music]
could it be this one no
on this one
this one maybe
oh
all righty
and now this time I'm
in a suit so I think
I look like we're not sir
bring it on girls let me choose my at
least I bet I'm busy right now
[Music]
I don't think I've ever played
Peacemaker but I'll be there in a bit
and a bit after I'm done here
um
you can stand one please
help me out
May honey
yes I want to go back there with you
honey
her walk looks kind of not so motivated
but okay
she's surely looking forward to dancing
for me right
pretty girl
I like your hair
cute
are those lying little little bunsies
[Music]
if they went watching I'd let you touch
me up there the little bungees down
there is the big onesies
oh
wait wow
I like I like the I like the birthmark
on on your cheek
that's the way I'm looking at
sensitive lover aren't you sweet I don't
not want to find out
let's make them feel uncomfortable with
the music maybe would have been better
without the music
she's cute though
no oh
man I like that
oh is it done I'm so hot I'm gonna have
to go and towel myself down I didn't
even do anything
I'm too powerful
come again soon
[Music]
yeah we got what I promised in the title
[Laughter]
turn this bgm off now it's making me
nervous
but you know what that what that was
created it created some spikes
I'm gonna drive to my apartment now
that's what I'm gonna do
it
no no no no no no no
nine down on the floor getting a knife
dance mom a pretty lady
I really don't know what to do oh how to
act when they're all over you I want to
look cool but I really don't know
okay home we go
the head laugh is the only one to make
if you're gonna be okay
birthday
away
[Applause]
[Music]
the flames
just go in your own way
going so fast
[Music]
foreign
ashes
[Music]
your own way
[Applause]
[Music]
that's my home what
[Applause]
what where's my home oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
that looked like a house and it looks
like
house house house house icons
I was about to arrive just fetching to
the end of the song again what the [\h__\h]
I'm going my own way yeah
we're just driving by X but I don't want
to deal with X now
[Music]
losing my way
don't forget don't forget what I said
get out of your head life is only one
why is there so many taxes let's look
throat is orange wow wow that was like
10 times oh there's even more wow oh
wow
too much
[Music]
you'll never be your friend
a man to burn it up keep your feet
against the table
Sparks like the flame so don't wait
satisfied today yeah
[Applause]
take the fast lane now
let's show them baby
[Applause]
know your name
[Music]
ain't nobody got time for that
pizza
with you anymore I have another plan all
right Nico we shall do this another time
later on
everything
it is right
[Music]
[Applause]
but yes let's stop let's stop and read
the Super Chat
down
[Music]
they follow me till we die
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah that was fun
another five and a half hours of GTA
everybody
um
good progress today really I feel like I
messed around a bit more than yesterday
but still we made up with it by playing
one hour more
I think
uh I'll be getting a little snack to eat
at the side while reading super chats
just because
I was planning on eating that before the
stream
yeah and then we'll wait to chat but
we'll already move over here we go ah
oh there goes who
who was that
who could have possibly been that
I'm telling you it's Brucie
because he's annoyed yang
okay I'm sorry no no it's not
new
thank you guys for watching oh I love
GTA episode
as I said yesterday we won't be able to
play it for one or two weeks
um but we'll be back
we'll be back I'll be back
yes just like Terminator
um
it's been a lot of fun so far
having a good time I'm glad I picked up
GTA for another GTA game
for the first time in a long time
um
let's play more soon yeah and yesterday
we finished super chats from the
countdown stream so today we shall
continue
uh with whatever follows afterwards did
I rate the super chats from the collabo
the jackbox collab
it's not much but
just wondering where to continue
F press f for turning off the siren got
me good today
weekend was good really I'm happy
I'm happy I'll probably continue putting
it on the weekends
but not 100 sure
maybe sometimes I won't but the game
isn't even that long
so yeah
yeah okay another fantastic
success success
you know
[Music]
so I'll be right back I'll grab some
food
it will only take a second so don't go
anywhere
you forgot to give me a kiss for my
first I did
oh no space waterfall
come here come here come here
come here for Choo Choo
wait I read that right right
oh wow
what is space waterfall right
[Music]
okay good sorry about that
I give so many kisses sometimes I'm not
sure if I gave them or not
um
[Music]
okay BRB
my legs
Wolverine
[Music]
I met smoovarino
sure
I've got some
uh cold pasta salad with some chicken
thank you for the sacrifice
voluntarily
there we go
small one
from the supermarket let me try
I think I ate this before
quite all right hmm
no
mm-hmm
no um
she want the belly scratch
let's try
[Music]
um
okay
wow
hello
this is my cat you don't see her but
she's
looking at the camera now
she doesn't like to be held
but she's so soft
so I cannot resist also I turn down the
volume of my headphones by accident
uh
no I did not I actually unplugged them
whoops did I totally do
it
you keep our lives she can't be held
thank you I would say that is indeed a
good argument Joshua
goodbye thanks for watching
thank you
come again
um
let's set up homolizer okay
[Music]
izer
also music what kind of music do you
guys want to hear
jazz or I don't know
something cute or
should we listen to
more trash
dirty Jazz the one that we were
listening to
[Music]
um
it does not Loop
I always gotta enter Lupu
ah oh
I'm cute but
you guys wanted sexy jazz
I don't like this one too long
hmm
respectable just
I don't hear it
there you go
[Music]
what do you think of this
it's not like dirty Jazz but
[Music]
all right but
now it's good for Super Chat reading
um
it seems like oh my God you're right it
could be a shopping music
um
okay
this one I think
yeah okay
[Music]
foreign
I got rid of that window
[Music]
I think I did
oh
[Music]
there you go
papaya song
I think it's kind of comparable
[Music]
good
okay let me take a few more bites
[Music]
um
whoever
sacrifice themselves for my salad
tastes really good
[Music]
no it's not mean Patsy
oh yeah right it was Brewster
[Music]
it's not cannibalism I am not a chicken
you should know that by now
[Music]
yeah I'm a tier higher
yeah whoever said that is the next salad
[Music]
bam
okay
[Music]
I'll eat the rest later
quite good
um
it's
Sunday food
I bought because food I bought on
Saturday or Friday on Friday maybe
because
on Sunday I can't buy it
[Music]
it's basically just stock up food
stocked up food
yeah store closed so
anything we'll do
emergency weekend food
actually I ran out of milk and in the
morning when I was eating my cereal
I was clinging onto the last drops of my
milk
this isn't really looping this music huh
oh well
that's okay
[Music]
here we go
Patsy done KitchenAid thanks for the
pinky
no tangible possible Iron master covers
of Iris killing vampire girl maybe it
would feel small vampire pretty oh yeah
but then Iris needs to get one too she
doesn't have one right
can't wait for this collapse to start
we'll be playing ever for
teen in the meantime and I can't wait
for you to play until happy birthday
again thank you I hope you're catching
up
yeah I don't know vampire girl is really
cute song but I don't think it would be
my first choice
[Music]
there's so many others that I would
choose first I think
even though I love King vampire girl
but if I were to make a cover I think it
would be something else
thanks for the rest of the chat happy
infinity plus free birthday quinoa
you've got a lot of super chats to read
so I'll keep it short thank you I wish
you all the best and that all your
wishes come true
I hope so too I'm working on it because
you can't just wait for your wishes to
come true you gotta work for it
you know make your own wishes come true
with your own actions
so I'm working on it
um
but your support would definitely help
so thank you very much thank you soon
ultimate okay
as well
the first appetite is for all the things
ah there we go food ah because okay this
one comes first because
I privated the other one for a little
bit
so in the order uh this jackbox collab
stream comes before the other one
but I'm sure you sent a second one
before that oopsie
the first appetite is for all the things
that the future holds for us I wish for
you to be able to continue to do the
things that you love and pursue your
dreams even a fighter and I will
continue to support you for your journey
happy birthday to our beloved Phoenix
thank you I'm like out of breath
thank you
I wonder what you wrote in the second
one now
for the wholesome message
[Music]
um
thank you
thank you we got the story halfway
through you mean the game story
[Music]
this GTA 4 is so much shorter than GTA
5.
foreign
[Music]
it is
Oh you mean the Super Chat this one
this is more than halfway through
because it was three super jets
oh okay okay
[Music]
more like 45 to five percent okay but
that's wow I'm guessing then it should
be like three more streams or something
like that
do you ever eat your cereal of yogurt ah
I to sometimes do like corn flakes with
banana and I think vanilla yogurt or so
bananas slices and vanilla Goods
I think I did that sometimes but I
prefer to have it with milk corn flakes
with banana
and slices and milk
I like that that's how I pimp Corn
Flakes with banana cut up banana slices
so good
Banger breakfast
mmm
complex is your cereal of choice I'm not
really like uh there's some you know
specific cereals
here in Austria and Germany that I like
I think it's called Vitalis
chocolade
um
that one either that one or the
the chocolate bowl from Kellogg's the
chocolate balls
and sometimes I like just simple Corn
Flakes too yeah
um
[Music]
chalky cereal
are you salsa really like uh Sunni Minis
cinema cinema
cinnamon
uh thingies cornflake thingies
[Music]
um but I don't enjoy them nowadays
anymore that much
I don't know they get soggy so fast
it's not so nice then
[Music]
uh soon hopefully thank you so far
Katie because
of those saplings are our main language
[Music]
I have a surprise for you today I passed
by exam to be a real certified personal
trainer oh
the position you gave me is not real oh
my God
thank you for inspiring me to find
something I'm passionate about and a way
to spend my life helping others wow
how do you get such a certification that
sounds
worse are you gonna actually do that as
your job now
I guess I should hire you
[Music]
congratulations on making it I don't
know if it was difficult but damn
oh he nice he's already hired God damn
it
I'm sure he would prioritize me
I was wondering
for the pinky I've been thinking all day
about what kind of cringe and sappy
message to write but I can't come up
with anything
so just happy birthday thank you I hope
your day was wonderful thank you that's
perfectly fine
yeah well my birthday was
stressful but fun and
[Music]
um my today day
was fun too but I don't know I'm getting
really stressed out again
so much to do so much to do I I feel
like I'm also
uh
forgetting about things I should be
doing
and I wonder what did what they were
[Music]
let me write one thing down on my to-do
list
[Music]
okay done
and
rad thanks for Pinky happy birthday
happy day of burp what Chihuahua
with your recent performance of Sparks
at the concert collect the world concert
I'd like to remind you it's also
surprise birthday
oh did I release it on my birthday back
then
I'd like to thank you for making such a
freaking Banger of a track so to that I
say stream Sparks
was that released on my birthday oh
oh
I say ah I don't do that anymore I don't
want to like release things on
anniversary or birthdays
anymore because I kind of want to spread
out the hype a bit more
so that there's something exciting in
every month if possible
um
yeah
I think that's better one time is fine
but
I think it's nicer yeah to isolate those
special events yeah yeah
um
Focus the attention
the way it deserves to be
but hey I forgot about that good to know
thank you rad we did stream spikes today
happy birthday attention thank you I
need a cool induction ABI Duncan for the
pinky birthday party time I hope you
have fun with the girls I did
I mean I always feel like super lost
when playing jackbox
uh and so did I this time as well
I didn't know what I was doing
hmm but some of the games I haven't
played before I actually already had
this one in my library but I think I
only played one of the games before
the other ones all seem so unfamiliar to
me
so I think now I finally got the most
out of that
party pack
I finally played all the games I think
um or at least the ones that you can
play with online
people
um
yeah I think they have a good selection
they were all fun and I really liked
hearing from the audience
when they got to vote although I still
think that
[Music]
that one uh poll was really inaccurate
that people just said yes to the one
where they well the question was if you
can explain what and was it what
wouldn't
an atom uh is I think that's what it was
I don't think
so many people can correctly
uh really explain it
it was like 70 percent
I doubt it
whatever but I don't I don't believe so
I'm sure a lot of you can
yeah I think people were a little bit
overconfident
[Music]
now people think it's nah yeah
I first think they wrote Think into that
[Music]
um
because that's such a wide
vague way of phrasing the question
anyway thank you Avio I did have fun
yeah
for the pinky what can I say except
happy birthday thank you 2.5 years ago I
first met you on YouTube I still
consider that as a lucky charm oh
really
best for a big Aussie of thousands of
Simpkins please never stop dreaming big
and we will support you on this way love
you boys
thank you very much very much it was
definitely a very lucky thing to find me
there's so many people didn't but you
did thank you so much love you too
Gila Max the space speed tank
Ginger diversary
foreign
I can't breathe man
it's weird
[Music]
didn't you end up getting getting it too
X stick dancing
[Music]
thank you
oh yeah I'm glad we even did an ink
Uncle we even like switched
the one who hosts it went out of the way
to capture Discord uh screen
just to play a bit more from a different
party pack
nice noise
I need to get the newer ones
ah
[Music]
uh spicy chicken butt things with a
pinky
[Music]
um
you're emotional
what
what's going on there your emotional
support chickens will be there for you
you all the way also happy preferred
birthday to kiwawa I hope your passion
and motivation help accomplish all your
current and future goals thank you for
making all our days brighter love you
Kiana
for being part of
my everyday
for almost three years now all of you it
ain't one of your pinkies what the [\h__\h]
did it ever did you get the money back
at least
I hope you did what the [\h__\h]
that's so rude
[Music]
you were able to okay good then I always
forget
[Music]
nearly that time for the free earbuds oh
my God that Soul didn't set it
I will I will
eventually
hmm
last minute
no thank you for the sweet words even if
there's something missing this feels on
its own already pretty complete no
well thank you thank you soon
for the red super chat
thank you forever thank you for
delivering this phenomenal party collab
I was in real need of mood lifter today
while not everything went as you wished
or planned for the state I hope you'll
agree that that all's well that ends
well happy birthday you fabulous Phoenix
yeah it's all right I mean
I'm I am upset that for the third year
in a row I'm not getting what I should
be getting but it do be like that it is
what it is
so yeah I just made
what I could make out of
yeah the situation it was fun it was
definitely fun
[Music]
what I should be getting a 3d concert
made by cover Studio
[Music]
we'll have it in winter
thank you
orbital Vagabond thanks
and thank you
Patsy Duncan space waterfalls Roger
dungeon RSI
[Music]
Edition
few months it's half a year away
zip Leaf is
beautiful Phoenix whose radiant Spirit
illuminates the days of thousands of
timkins I hope you'll get to keep
soaring to new heights have a magical
Year love you thank you
yeah I hope so too I want to soar to new
heights would be nice
I'll keep on I'll keep on doing my thing
fighting every day doing my best every
day
whatever I can so please stay by my side
deeply and everybody else too
to help me
take off into the sky
and catch me when I fall okay
[Music]
thank you mwah
a wow thank you soon Patrick
then thank you for the words of Chad
happy birthday Kiana I'm glad I got to
see some of your birthday streams I
wasn't able to take it all off but I did
enjoy what I got to be at thank you you
tried to take some time off thank you
oh
and Christian for that
I hope it was worth it
um you couldn't do it this time oh
that's okay too
if they don't allow it that's fine can't
help it
can't do anything about it but thank you
for catching it nonetheless
I'm sure you were there plenty yeah
thank you
soon
thank you for your rights of a chat
which has no no message
what are you trying to tell me could it
be happy birthday
thank you
mwah
[Music]
ah
I guess no thanks
[Music]
okay
that's finished
another one
ticked off my list
[Music]
foreign
thank you all for listening
and waiting
[Music]
Mama Mia
what is this orange carpet
[Music]
yeah no the backlog is pretty bad
let's not lie to ourselves
um
this one
downtown
[Music]
yeah this is a lot
Mama Mia
Mamma Mia that's a lot
[Music]
foreign
wait correct soccer no but I did
I did yesterday when watching more Mrs
maisel actually noticed another Gilmore
Girls actress I think
pretty sure I noticed another actress
it took me so actually two
two more
first of all I saw the mom
[Music]
the grandma I mean
um
grandma was in Marvel's Mrs maisel
it's pretty small room but she's in
there and then I think
one of the Mean Girls
from Rory's High School
yeah I think I saw her too it's crazy
[Music]
um
literally though they they hired at
least
10.
actors from gamble girls from Marvel's
Mrs maisel
at least 10. but it's so fun to see like
it takes me so long to realize those
surprisingly because well a lot of years
have passed but also their styling is so
different
so it's often very hard to to notice
damn
hug me it took me a while
but makes me happy I'm like wait wait a
second wait wait wait a second
hmm
yeah yeah
must be kind of fun for them although I
think a lot of them don't meet on set
because a lot of them have like
smaller roles that don't really interact
with each other
from what I can tell
[Music]
um
well I don't know that show
at a console never heard of it
[Music]
I just won't look exactly the same yeah
yeah I mean they grow but also the
makeup and the hairstyle and the clothes
very different
[Music]
anyway
oh really
[Music]
yeah well that's true that's really true
um
[Music]
ah
la la la yeah very dramatic
it's very dramatic isn't that so much
drama are you having fun with it are you
still like
are you forcing yourself to watch it for
me or are you actually having a good
time I hope you're having a good time
and you you wouldn't be okay keep giving
me so much so much feedback if you
wouldn't be having a good time right
right right I mean I mean
hmm you like it I'm so glad I'm so glad
you know you're getting big plus points
from me for that
thank you so much when you're done with
that you have to watch Mrs Mario's Mrs
Basil if you're not already watching it
okay you can't stop yawning me neither
We're In It Together
happy birthday Kiana thanks for always
being the bright Phoenix to my day
you're always so sweet to have Champions
as well as having many many amazing
talents you are great inspiration to me
and many others many other kfp thank you
for being the best honestly thank you
I'm so damn
[Music]
hmm maybe I should do stupid job reading
tomorrow
I think I'll just puts everything
tomorrow I'm sorry I feel so dead
ah I can't feel
the feelings I'm sorry I will reread
this tomorrow okay
I'll reread it tomorrow you deserve for
me to understand what you just wrote
and not just for me to read it and not
register it in my brain
uh
[Music]
it's like my brain like after finishing
the gaming part
tells my brain okay time to rest now
supposed to read super chats
because
reading Super Chat so much
so now my brain is like
um
you're done right kiwawa you're done
right
you're going to bed now right
knows how much I love him I'll look at
the carpet closer tomorrow I was
thinking anyway about like what should I
even stream tomorrow
now I know
we're gonna
finish all of these super chats
maybe more
yeah the game
drained me a bit under heat I'm feeling
really hot right now
Raiders
and God damn it I'm about to end no
no
[Music]
I I
that's too bad thank you though
you guys can watch the VOD
playing GTA 4 since yesterday
[Music]
I just don't feel so well right now I
can't breathe huh
foreign
[Music]
yeah um I don't know what time tomorrow
I have to think
I have to use my brain and think get
better thank you I mean I'm not sick
but you know you know how it is
sometimes when you string too long
and you just feel drained
maybe maybe
um
summer heat
ah
[Music]
hot hot
wait
[Music]
cute I like your eyebrows punkle
wait for a red panda you're not very red
are you
supposed to be a red panda
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
YouTube oh
she's an YouTuber
wait she's Italian
are you
Paula Italiano
uh
umpo
forecast
[Music]
I had to play last time last year when I
went to Rome
right that was Subway
wait wait I think that was simply
went out of my way to go get supply
um
my Italian brain mostly MOSI
everybody
yeah man
massage
[Music]
the supply of soup please may never run
out
and Cara didn't like Pepe wait was that
um
[Music]
something that underwhelmed me yeah I
guess
[Music]
don't threat me out
black pepper pasta yeah that just
doesn't sound like it should be so good
or could be so good
[Music]
rare eova communication yeah makes sense
that you end your stream now because
it's sleepy time for eov tubers
it's kind of an hour lacking something
there you go exactly
Mamma Mia
Cornetto
Prima
um
[Music]
wow
no
[Music]
Chris would tell him thank you ciao
bella
uh yeah as I said I still need to think
about when I can do it tomorrow
um
but I'll see you guys around it's just a
Super Chat reading anyway if you miss it
it's not the end of the world but if you
can't be there then it would be nice for
you to be there
boom
okay well then it is
but the tangents
they will find you the way to you
um
first I sleep then I maybe decide I
don't know we'll see we'll see maybe on
the side now
[Music]
I'll try to make my scanner work first
I could not like get it to work for
printing anymore but scanning still
works I think
pretty sure
[Music]
so well we barely got anywhere so
tomorrow we continue with Munda
[Music]
dancing today
sometime another time and in German we
saying thank you for a fun week
and
yes
sorry Wawa will be busy in the coming
week
[Music]
it is what it is
okay perfect timing thank you jazz music
thank you thank you band in the
background in the Next Room
who's been playing jazz music for me all
this time and other tracks to thank you
thank you live band
it's been a blast thank you New York
good night New York isn't that amazing I
feel like a talk show host right now
thanks New York again
[Music]
foreign
bye bye bye bye
and in Italian we say
oh why this so quiet
oopsie
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]