hey
[Music]
oh
i don't know why i'm so nervous
but let's start it off with a bang shall
we
[Music]
keep
me
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
don't
[Music]
is
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling
me astray if i
go wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please
[Music]
tell me i can hear
oh
[Music]
i promise i will find you
oh my god
[Music]
good morning good evening wherever you
are hello thank you
for coming to my
new outfit reveal
thank you for getting up i feel like in
one of those time zones where it's
early as
and if you're here you because it's a
normal time for you
thank you as well oh my god okay so
i got a lot on my plan today i got
like a lot of things that i want to do
um so before we do all of those things
i want to announce one thing um
you might have seen it because there is
a
live premiere reservation up
of a song cover collaboration
no it's not a song cover of me alone it
is a collaboration
with i've been teasing this for a while
on my channel uh
with a certain other whole life english
member
and i've been keeping it quite a secret
but i will not tell you what it is
and it will be released maybe you have
seen the reservation
it may it will be released during um
pro most likely during this stream i
want to watch it together with you guys
but first we of course do the outfit
reveal and then right after that
and hopefully if the timing is well we
do it immediately
after the outfit reveal and everything
like once everything is done
um so the reservation is up you can
already if you go to my channel you can
have find the link there it's like you
see it if you go on the main page of my
channel
you can have it open as a second window
i would recommend that
otherwise i'm just going to post it
again later once we are
uh watching it
you're um so
i am now ready to tell you
whoa who is this with who i am doing
this
collaboration with and what song it is
because i also kept that a secret
okay drum roll please
[Music]
featuring
it's gonna be up after the answer review
but still
during my uh stream so we can watch it
together i will not play the audio you
have to go there then but yeah
the premiere is on my channel so yeah
just open it and keep it open
yay yes it's a it's a really cute
song from dickel nina and i
i i like it a lot and i asked if god
wants to sing it with me so
it's amazing you guys are going to love
it so much you guys are really really
going to love it the video is amazing
the video is by
a young who did also the video of
wawa world but i have to say she
has like out outdone herself with this
video
you guys will be probably a bit
emotional like i
me and gula when we watched it for the
first time
we got teary eyes
so now manager please update thumbnail
and description your school manager son
okay so oh let me get rid of my
microphone there we go
and i think i want to go through some
predictions yes yes yes yes
and i i was asking you guys to
post some predictions with hashtag
phoenix fashion
which you can still use to post
screenshots
of today's stream and so it's not only
for the new outfits please also use it
for twitter
right now like when i'm starting to show
my outfit
please use it let's try to get it
trending
on
so let's get started
we're starting with a kind of loose one
is it okay to show that
ass what a nice ass
i'm i'm maybe i'm going to hide it down
here a little bit
well this um upward one of the
predictions okay
okay i can't help it i have to show it
i even retweeted this one because i like
it so much
by the way i don't have the names here
written on them right now but if you
check the hashtag phoenix fashion
hashtag
or my retweet you'll probably find most
of them so yeah
i'll leave it to you guys i didn't have
that much time to prepare
so that one's really cute it's like
summer themed and
very very short but the braids are so
long
like this person made my hair quite long
i i would love to have some extensions
there was like two popular themes
summer theme or farmer theme
but i have to say out of the like
silhouettes
of all the outfits from halloween
because we all are getting new outfits
out the silhouettes i feel like my
silhouette was just so easy to guess
because it's so tight like you can see
the details
um so i feel like it was really really
easy and by looking through the
predictions i was like yeah bit
they're like all so [\h__\h] close
especially i mean the hat i mean who
knows maybe it is not a
not a straw hat who knows we will see
let's go to the next one
that one is really cute like i love like
this person was a bit more like like
i mean not trying to say it in the mean
way but like it's a bit more original
like there were a lot of like
uh similar predictions because it's just
so
like obvious i guess what i'm wearing
but this one seemed a bit more original
to me i like how um
she chose like or she i don't know he or
she but
the color theme i like the color thing
and uh the the swimsuit i guess
underneath must be a swimsuit
really cute top and the shorts i love
the shorts color
um the shoes too i love i love like
platform shoes
platform shoe platform sandals i love
those
kawaii and then we got this one this is
not like
drawn off of the silhouette but it's
like a like well
just on its own super cute i retweeted
this one too i think
i like um the the top design
a lot i like how like only the sleeves
are transparent
if you looked closely at the silhouette
you would have noticed that
um the sleeves were
kind of transparent yeah
and a lot of you guys picked up on that
task
that's cute i also like how the um
hair gradation looks with the braids
by the way who knows if it is great some
people were like
what if it is like corn what if it is
uh yakiniku or something like that that
i'm holding because
in the silhouette i was holding up my
arms
and it it could look like
i'm just holding something and maybe i
have short hair and say oh yeah dango
yeah some people were like oh what if
she is holding dango
i love that idea so then we have uh this
one
by the way i'm not showing all of them
just some of them
uh that i really liked this one is so
cute and i think it's generally it
captures
um the summer idea very very well
i like the back too like the back has
like the same pattern as the top
like a corset possibly also gives me
slight slight vibes of like uh
like only the top but it gives me slight
dental vibes
um dental if you don't know what it is
it's like a traditional
dress for like germans and australians
and that kind of area and it's normally
a dress but
but yeah that's like a top design that
kind of reminds me of it but i don't
know if that one's even intentional
anyway cute next up that one also is not
drawn off the silhouette but just on its
own i love this one too
so cute again the puffy
uh transparent sleeves are really really
cute
and i love the top design with the how
do you call that pattern check
checker check i don't know
but it's cute what's with the
butterflies they're cute too
and some simple jeans shorts yeah yeah
why not why not
and again braids maybe it's not braids
maybe it's not even a straw hat who
knows who knows we will find out later
then we have a bit more of a farmer
style
because a lot of you guys were like ah
what if it's a farmer chiara farmer
chiara
this is pixel art by the way
i love the little bag it is so cute
that's like a chicken bag i
i legit want that bag please
please someone make it and i will buy it
it's so cute
it has like little wings and i love
like these uh shorts with you call them
suspenders right so
sis
[Music]
cute very cute
is that my farming house farmhouse in
the background i wonder
next up now this one is uh i would say
beach style again or like
summer style
[Music]
but combined with the braids yes yes
yes yes full cucumber and feet yeah
apparently no shoes
but this one is really cute i like um
the what do you call this kind of
packs what do you call them overalls
short overalls and also kind of looks
like a swimsuit actually to be honest
underneath
looks like a swiss up to me because it's
like
really short underneath but like it fits
the top so it must be a bikini set
um cute i love this one also the glasses
are really fancy i don't know if you
guys can see them well but look at those
glasses
[Music]
the glasses are really dope like they're
like funky like
like you know like auntie funky auntie
style
your auntie that has like really really
weird glasses like
like dope ass glasses
i don't know how to how to describe it
awesome awesome next up
now we have another one of those farmer
ideas you guys like
i am i'm not complaining but usually
when i see like other
like i always wanted to do this you know
the the
prediction thingy and when i see other
whole live members doing this prediction
thingy
i see so many different ideas
but for me it's like they're all
like so similar
[Music]
so easy to guess
yeah the hat is cute and i like the
shovel and uh
what do you call that the fork this i
know it's not a fork but
wait there's an egg nest in my pocket oh
cute oh my the bag also says what what
my belt usually says remember that
it says uh i'm not allowed to use it
yeah but you know i don't know i don't
like to listen to hookah papa when he
says i'm not allowed to use my belt it's
like whatever
whatever for the people who don't know
when i use my belt i
would transform into a big big phoenix
but that's too dangerous so um my papa
put uh
tape on my belt so that i can't use it
yeah whatever
[Laughter]
i like this one this is really cute and
now we have this one i think that might
be the last one that i
saved but this one is like three ideas
but what i really liked about this one
is not
how lewd it gets in the middle but the
hats
the hat's transformation is like a
normal straw hat but then it turns into
into burtness which is so cute but then
it transforms into a freaking whole
chicken on my head i mean i i can see it
i can imagine it somehow yeah
[Music]
cute
oh we have more we'll have more this
one's so cute
i think i retweeted that one maybe that
one is really cute it has like somehow
not only like the summer vibes but also
like this this
these sailor sailor vibes because of the
because of the color
not not the color but the color color
you know what i mean right you know what
i mean
the [\h__\h] oh damn
the thing around the neck okay
[Music]
drag some water okay and the pants are a
bit like
i don't know if it's some peppers maybe
it only looks like it here but
they're kind of like um
like puffy really cute though
cute cute cute i like the shoes too
they're also they also look like somehow
they look like uh
platform shoes platform sandals
[Music]
hi and i like the sunflower earrings
they're really cute too
all right next up i think that might be
the last one
maybe not i don't know but here's a lot
of ideas
whoa they're all so cute i don't even
know where to start
oh my god i like the i look i like all
of them i wanna i want those outfits
man the the translucent blouse thing
really really looks good in all of these
outfits
all these pants look cute too my belt
is like on my leg on the very left one
cute and i'm holding a camera on the
left one and i'm on the second one i'm
holding dango
i think good
okay
this one is very different it's very
original i would say i like it it's cute
it has a original color theme with like
green in it as well
the socks are adorable they look kind of
oh wait i just realized the socks are
supposed to look like chicken legs don't
they
[Music]
i don't know if i want to wear the beard
okay i guess i can see that too but i
don't know if
i don't i don't like to have chicken
legs and i also don't want beer legs so
i'm not sure if i would wear that this
outfit
or those socks but it's a really cute
design
um cute
i'm not sure if this gives me farmer or
some vibes gives me like a
combination of farmer and summer vibes
hmm and next up
oh yeah this one is another uh one that
has like a dandel
inspiration like the top and normally i
said it before but we have this
like traditional dress in my country
called dandel and this one uh is
inspired by it obviously
very cute really cute i think there
is actually tops like that that exists
and again the straw hat one thing that
everyone was really sure about was this
was the the straw hat
and i guess the the shorts and the
braids and everything
[Music]
and now we have a weird one
i mean it makes sense because of my belt
some people think i can turn into a
transformer
or robot or whatever
so i guess i can see where you're coming
from
when you put me in the clothes like this
[Music]
[Laughter]
but it's probably not what it's gonna
end up looking like probably not
come on
verbal celery you're right with tummy
ah cute though i like the chicken head
let me drink some water
oh
[Music]
actually that's koto dough is not
necessarily
a chicken is up here on the top right
top right the opposite of me obviously
who is bottom left is always just
kidding
just kidding and oh
[Music]
that is not even no that is not you
can't you can't even call that emotory
that is something else
[Music]
don't put those things together animal
tony would look differently
this is like
um maybe something like a
serial killer and dominatrix
[Music]
um anyway oh yeah we're back here okay
thank god
don't be totally no please no
all right all right all right so we got
further suggestions for the predictions
some weird ones in there though
what kelly do you like that one
black is the best color kelly kelly
likes
that one
okay okay
i didn't know you're into that stuff
callie
anyway after seeing all those things
i feel like going shopping for some new
clothes
i feel very inspired do you guys want to
join
[Music]
fashion mall
i want to try on some things i want to
go buy some things
so here we are uh actually
there should be a different music
playing here let's go to that one
[Music]
shopping top okay let's see what do we
want what do we want what do we need
i want to put first of all we need some
some underwear let's put that in here
okay
into the shopping cart oh yes so we have
we could also
need some gloves perhaps maybe
i mean it's not really the season for uh
i guess in fake australia the season for
dad is coming
yeah maybe a hat and you have to i
wouldn't mind a new hat let's put that
in the shopping cart as well
um what else should i pick guys
what else should i pick well that looks
interesting let's go for that
my name is skirt there we go mini skirt
gekko what else did i get
what do you guys think would look good
on me um
choose from what's in the shop though
a dress the dress which dress duh
that one i think that one would look
good on me
wait let me try it on
i'll put that plate
oh duh
how does that look i mean it's a little
bit
pixely but you want me to put on the bra
as well let me try let me i guess i
guess that's a that's a buy
let me make it fold it make it smaller
let me get the brown and make sure it's
the right size
size i need this size
and that's about the right size that's
perfect
okay i'll go okay i'm gonna try on the
hat as well
just make sure look at the right size
a bit bigger yeah
something like that
does it look good on me it's very
elegant
very elegant i'll take it i want to show
a different side of myself
now maybe this skirt too oh it's cute
it's like oh hi what you said skirt but
it goes like it's like puffy
so it accentuates my figure
my sexy figure cute
come on come on come on let's get that
one
what else what else let me look around
that dress is cute too
it's super like low quality but i'm sure
if you'll buy it it will be better
kawaii wait it has like this turquoise
color for my hair
it actually like harmonizes so well
nice nice nice size nice eyes i'll put
that in there as well
i love it but this one is a sports bra
we need that sometimes to work out
sports bra i think i think it's a sports
bra
there we go there you go that's about
right
okay i mean i don't really wear sports
bra as much but
who knows when we might need it you know
and some cute shorts those are too too
tiny
and zoom something around that it
doesn't fit my hips quite
well maybe we have to change the size a
little bit
uh but for now i think i'll go get those
shorts yes yes
um uh maybe some long pants as well oh
god those really no put those back
those don't suit my figure i have a way
better
hourglass shaped figure okay no thank
you
okay get rid of that okay now with all
those things
oops wait that was me with all those
things i want to move on to the
changing room
help me try on some things
are you gonna help me i might not fit
into everything that easily i might need
your help come
come with me okay oops oh
i'm sorry i put it pushed around but
that one hey there you go there we go
okay okay okay okay let me let me get
into the
changing room
[Music]
you're gonna wait for me i have a lot of
things to show you
a lot of things so i'll show you
one by one maybe let's start with the
shoes
okay then let me
let me close the curtains real quick
shoes first yeah yeah i think they fit
well
actually now you might be able to see um
my nails
because i painted them for you for this
occasion
all right all right are you ready to see
the shows it's happening guys it's
happening
okay first first sneak me i
also um try to put some
some nice body lotion on my legs because
summer time
gotta make your legs all shiny
tata
they're comfortable i think i
i can walk around with that
what do you think how many toes are
there one
two three four five okay
gave me the right amount of toes
cute cute cute okay
i got the shoes down let me go back
inside and put on some pants
close the curtains please thank you
okay putting on my pants
okay um maybe maybe not a little bit
later
yeah yeah yeah okay okay there we go
there we go
now we're talking oh oh
yeah i can't close the button
maybe i ate too much
i can't
yeah i guess i guess this looks cute too
okay let me show you maybe
maybe maybe you think that this is this
is fine too
open the curtains
[Music]
like i i i couldn't close the buttons
is it okay though is it okay
if i keep it open i mean it's cute
because you can see the inside pattern
of the pants
[Music]
is that how you pronounce that king
pattern
yeah you can see my belly button of
course you can
i feel like you were able to see that
before as well right
oh by the way don't don't forget to use
the hashtag phoenixfashion
and post screenshots on twitter
[Music]
all right all right i'll try to put on
um
something else one second
the curtains please oh sure
there we go wonderful
okay i need some privacy you know
what about this actually that might be a
cute detail
not exactly gloves but
oh wait oh there we go okay open the
curtains
oh here i am you see my hand
and what do you think maybe we can use
those little cuffs
handcuffs different not not the kinky
type of handcuffs but like translucent
cute handcuffs what do you think i think
i like them
all right all right all right let me put
on my blouse which i am
totally not wearing already
okay okay okay no no no we're getting
there now we're getting somewhere else
i'm quite nervous
we're getting up higher and higher but
wait let me let me work
this blouse is pretty oh my god it's
pretty see-through
i mean let me put like a something
underneath that's like okay to see
ah i hope it doesn't stand out
ah oh i guess i
i it's not like i can do i guess i have
to show
okay i i'm
i'm opening the curtains
[Music]
is it noticeable is it noticeable
no you can't see it right it's i mean i
put on the swimsuit underneath anyway so
it's okay if you can see it
just don't don't look too much so
oh maybe you noticed i actually did
something with my hair too
i'm hiding it a little bit right now
because the thing is you know when i go
out like this
i want to enjoy summertime with the
humans
but having like this weird gradation
people keep on looking at me
so i tried to get rid of the
green color of my hair and dyed it more
orange but but the green is still there
so
i didn't get it out completely but
you want to see oh i'll give you a sneak
peek there you go
there you go you see my my hair color
changed a little bit and
oh do you see what i see
i put on the new choker my papa made me
this new choker
yes it has my shield on it
so i can also still inferior
transform because this is this is what i
used to transform
as well
and put on some more accessories
okay see you in a moment close the
curtains
all right all right maybe it's uh
time for this okay okay
okay is it a bird's nest
or is it a straw hat
is it a bird's nest noise and a straw
hat
what will it be what will it be
and i will show you my face i guess
three two one
[Music]
yay
yes it is a straw hat
[Music]
look it's throwing such a nice shadow on
my face that when i'm in the sun
i don't get uh like too much sunburn or
it doesn't hurt my
eyes it's very nice for the summer
that's
all summer long actually
um there's some some change
in one one facial expression i guess
my maybe embarrassed or happy expression
now comes with a little bit more blush
tata
blush or sunburn not sure which one it
is
hi everyone this is not everything
though
this is not everything
should i show you what else i got
all right all right but close the
curtains because it's a bit embarrassing
close close
all right let me take know it first let
me let me show you this variation
open
tata hi
i got some sunglasses too but they're
like
they have like a pink tint to them
cute isn't it
i know i know i know i know i know i
know it's cute i love those glasses
they're pretty big
but they cover up my eyes nicely and
make them a bit more pinkish
cute but i got more but wait there's
more word where it does
[Music]
close the curtains
okay now we want to do this and this
and this and then we want to take
take oh yeah we want to take off the hat
and maybe show you this
there we go but maybe without the
glasses
where without the glasses okay
yeah that looks cute
let's see what you guys think about this
open the curtains hey
okay i got my hands in a different
position as well
i can make like a w or i can just make
like
i could just point but hey i got a
little
kfc
wink
yeah for those days where i don't feel
like wearing a hat
but but no hat feels a bit too empty
so a little bit something to top it off
but of course with
kfb on it i will never forget about you
guys kfc is the most important thing to
me in my whole life
i got more do you guys
um okay i think now wait no one more
thing because before i go to my secret
weapons close the curtains
call them now
[Music]
okay down now now i show you this
okay of course a lady cannot go outside
with
with with
a bag yeah
okay it's cute back and this bag is
special because
it has like um a special design and okay
maybe i
don't know if you guys recognize it but
like in like oktoberfest
and and and similar like traditional
festivals
in my country and also germany
uh we have uh like these these snacks
like
it's like it's like a mix of a cookie
and a type of bread
um that's called lip cooking and this
bag
looks like that food it's like a lip
cooking bag
with some in a shape of a heart because
those
those snacks come in the shape of a
heart and you usually you give it as a
present to someone and it has like a
message on it most of the time
and and and and yeah in my case it
doesn't have a message on it
but but
but if you look closely you might
recognize some icons on it that are
stitched onto
maybe you can see the the icons it looks
like the icons from
you know the other who have english
members
but that's still not all that's still
that old
[Music]
close the curtains here come my secret
weapons
i wonder what you think about my secret
weapons oops wait wait i
think i oh there we go it's all good
okay
i wonder what you think about my secret
weapon so
first of all you guys remember
[Music]
that one special collaboration
ah the uno collab that we did
did a punishment game um
and people got very sick of it but
but but hookah papa liked it
i guess and supports it so
please please forgive me but you have to
deal with this now
[Music]
okay open the curtains are you ready are
you ready
go
my balls
[Music]
i want some milk milk
i'm tired tired tired
[Music]
no i cannot sleep i still have to show
you
one more thing okay okay okay
gonna go back into the curtains and show
you one more thing
one more thing okay wow wait wait
wait
[Music]
okay well the last thing
i want to show you
i think i got a i think i got
a cat hair in my throat
i think i'm gonna cough up something
this is just what happens if you live
with cats you know
sorry about that um but i feel weird
i feel weird maybe
can you guys check if everything's okay
please please help me out here when i
open the curtains
i'll open the curtains please help me
maybe i have some
cat ears in my fruit so please please
check
is everything normal is there anything
normal
[Music]
oh
speak english but somehow some weird
meows came out of me
let me look in the mirror for a second
oh my god is that what i think it is
what oh my god
oh my god i think i am a cat
i have a tail too what what
what the hell happened this is pearl
because i
live with two cats and i keep on
inhaling their hair this is i guess what
happens oh i didn't know
that's so weird it's so weird
but i i like it i like it yeah
yeah meow meow
meow i guess it doesn't necessarily look
like a cat maybe you can also think i'm
a fox because of the orange color
or real flux
it does remind me a bit of the fox as
well i like fox's
what do you think of cat kiara
will you take me in will you keep me
i eat lots of food and i sleep
a lot i
uh what else do i do i i i will annoy
you
and do some things that you tell me not
to do
yes yes you will but yeah you gotta keep
my litter clean
i i don't catch mice i'm scared of mice
please please take me and meow meow
i think that was all the things i had in
in to show for you
which means we're done shopping and i
want to go to the last stage but should
i go with
cat yes i should go with straw hat i
guess
i guess for the sake of it i should go
with straw hat okay one second i'll
change it one
one last time and then we'll go have a
little picnic barbecue
close the curtains
[Music]
okay let me put on uh there's like so
many combinations i can do
let me do my sunglasses and my straw hat
and i'll i'll put i'll keep the bag
and um i could even put on the cat table
now let's
get rid of the cat tail and yeah i think
i am
ready to go
shopping is done i paid everything
and we are now going to
have a little picnic cause it's summer
famed it was not
a farmer it was actually
uh yeah summer themed i hope you guys
are not disappointed
oh but we're not done we're still gonna
i want to sing one song for you
and then we're gonna watch the live
premiere of
my song cover collab with glad together
so will you stay a little bit longer
with me let me
grab my microphone
[Music]
let me i really quickly get myself
a bit over here in position and then
yeah it's so nice out here i feel so
good with these clothes ah i feel so
refreshed
all right then i think the most fitting
song since we already sang hirotori
the most fitting song would be heart
challenger
my second original song was i released
for valentine's day
oh
[Music]
yay
um
[Music]
foreign
ooh hey
[Music]
uh
is
[Music]
i need to tell you that i love you over
and through
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you
[Music]
um
me
[Music]
wow hey
yay
thank you thank you thank you
wow what a nice day for barbecue over
there
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you
you heard heart challenger by takana
which is my
please listen to it on spotify etc if
you haven't
done that yet now let's turn on some bgm
again
well that's a bit loud sorry about that
when i'm about that should be fine
and all right one second um for the
watch along uh
maybe before the one too long you guys
want to take some cute screenshots
[Music]
uh if you haven't already that is
something because it's so fitting here
let me let me pose for you
it takes some screenshots
[Music]
all right let me change it up a little
bit wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait you want dave on cat kiara
[Music]
do you want cat kiata
let me turn into a cat for you real
quick
i'm cat i'm cat
meow now i can do an mcat video super
easily
good good evening good morning everyone
i am ken
wait who is
[Music]
no that food why not give me some wet
food please
give me wet food
[Music]
give me some snacks please i want some
snacks don't give me the liquid
thingy i like that one
please give me that
i already ate too much of it huh
what they know too much if you have a
cat
then you listen to you cat
i i don't want to be your cat anymore
i'm gonna move out i'm gonna be an
independent cat from now on
independent cat i don't need you i don't
need an owner anywhere
oh
just because you give me food yup yup
yup that's what cats are all about just
because you give me food i
suddenly love you meow meow meow meow
you want some full body by the way
let me give you a full body move now
[Music]
there we go should i start where should
i stand here looks maybe good
hello oh wait
there we go there we go
full body cat oh my god full body cat
okay now we're running out of time so a
little
yeah i think we did a bunch of stuff
though so
we can go over to the other
room and then watch the new music video
together
[Music]
legs for days yes yes and my tail
jingles yes it does yes it does
everything jiggles
my ears i'm like so bouncy too
you guys you guys didn't think i would
turn into a cat this year
you fought you fought by looking at the
silhouette that
if anything maybe maybe gouda who knows
that those might be pizza corners though
you did not think i would turn into a
cat huh
[Music]
i told you i had some secret weapons and
no one thought it would be me being a
cat okay let's move over to
this screen hello
[Music]
life as a cat is just so much easier
i want to be a cat forever and then
maybe maybe now i can communicate with
my own cats
anyway instead of announcement we're now
moving over to
managers on can you quickly give me the
url of my
thingy i'm like all over the all over
the place
like i'm i don't know even like where i
am right now
thank you okay guys i'll post it for you
i'll pin it in the comments for you it's
starting in five minutes i guess but
then it
has like three oops oh my god
[Music]
i think it has like three minutes like
premiere uh
waiting time extra
[Music]
okay okay here it is
two minutes are way too loud music yeah
that is the thing
with youtube premiere okay
i will mute the music on my side when it
starts once it starts
let's have a here i have a watch long
thingy
is everyone opening it up
[Music]
it's a pinned comment now i i changed it
yes yes yes a cat yes i am now i am a
cat
okay open okay okay oh my god oh my god
i'm excited i'm so excited
ah let me open it too and see what we
got
okay nice thumbnail cute
the credits are changed now as well
it was someone nice nice nice nice
damn cat yeah you know on the weekend i
did this video and dog
and i was like for a moment i was like
uh before i
thought of doing m dog i was thinking
well doing m cat would be easy because
meow was just an easy
easy thing to do but then i was like
wait i should do that after i show
everyone my cat ears so then
i can i can do it without my images
image layering on top of me that i
usually do
now i can do it like properly i don't
even need those images
so i was like i'm gonna wait for next
time for doing
mcat and this time i'll just do m dog if
you missed it i did like a short videos
video i do those like every once in a
while on my channel when i need to fill
like a free day like a day off
i upload these like zoo videos
yeah okay how much longer two minutes oh
my god
ah exciting exciting exciting exciting
you have to watch it on your side by the
way because i'll be muting my audio
you will only hear my voice although
i'll try to not speak because i want you
guys to listen to it properly
did you like my idea by the way with the
shopping and all of that i wanted it to
be like
not only like like uh like only like
zooming from down to top i wanted it to
be like
something special
[Music]
now you will be a bit shocked if if i
tell you whose credit card i used for
doing all that shopping
i will not tell you it's probably better
that way i'll just not tell you
but it was worth it wasn't it
it was worth it right
[Music]
but what what the hell
is it starting
[Music]
it's three minutes right three minutes
extra to the
premier uh countdown oh wait it was one
minute
the premiere countdown is a one minute
two
wait i feel good
two minutes you mean like in total a two
minute extra
okay how did i forget that
that's like half of half of the length
of the song
i wish they would adjust it to like the
actual length of the video like if i put
up like an
eight-second video and they make them
wait for like two minutes
it's always like um kind of like
anti-climb ma
whatever i'm gonna turn on my medium
high quality
okay okay
oh sh is it starting
let me refresh it sometimes it doesn't
start with me but i always get so
nervous
yeah there we go two minutes two minutes
open your two windows have me on your
phone or on your second monitor
i'm muting my music
ah collab with good actually i asked her
to do this with me a while ago we
started
this whole thing quite a while ago
yeah and finally finally i'm able to
show it to you guys here
there a lot of work went into
i can't hear you now am i too quiet but
you have to
you have to make me louder than a lot of
work went into
like the whole music video
and the recording and everything
firefox i'm the firefox browser of
youtuber
if firefox had a youtuber it would be me
where is the premiere listen in my
pinned comment go now now no the paint
comment
in the comment section go now or go to
my channel it's all
happening at the same time on my channel
14 40 seconds left now
[Music]
love love words hey cat
hi chunkers
i turned into a cat too what do you
think about that
by the way i can take off everything as
well like the katusa
and the headband and the cat ears and
the hat like everything but then i just
look like an egg so
i'd rather not too okay starting
i'll shut up now
cute
[Music]
foreign
so
cute
all those memories
oh
oh it makes me so emotional
[Music]
i got like teary eyes the first couple
of times i watched that
wasn't it super cute oh my god oh my god
oh my god
i got that condom
[Music]
it's so cute the music video is so good
like there's so many parts that make me
feel like ah
so emotional oh my god wow
there's like do you guys wanna i don't
wanna stream much longer because i don't
wanna like
like overlap with inna but um i want to
talk a little bit about
um the music video and and all that
so um oh my god where to start
like ah like you see how like she
connected
like like the lyrics with our
um like activities up until now let me
turn on the pdm again
um wait
there you go like uh for example like
for me
it's like my history of like re-debuting
and how many times have you met me
it just fits so perfectly i said this on
my members stream before
this stream where i was testing out my
internet connection because i just moved
by the way if you have didn't know
um it was really stressful that's
another
story though but yeah she um
connected our history so well and and i
just
i love how i said this in my memory
stream that
i when i chose the song i chose it
because i really like
the song itself and i just thought it
would sound well
with our voices when i was thinking of
which song to sing
um and which songs we have permission to
sing
i was like this might like i've seen a
lot of other
live girls and other youtubers who have
sung the song
a lot alone not as a collab but alone
and that's like actually
like a perfect song to sing alone to say
thank you to your viewers
but i thought it would be nice to sing
it together with gouda because it just
fits our voice as well
so i chose that song and gooda agreed to
do it with me
and i oh my god what is it what was that
like there we go
and i i uh i i parted the lyrics
and and that was actually like i didn't
think about much when i parted the
lyrics
and choosing the song but yuna who made
the video
she just i don't know how she did it but
she found so much
meaning in it that fit us so well that i
didn't even realize
i didn't even see all of that and then
she included all of these like
references to my past collaborations
that i did with
like the teaching clubs and where i
taught her german and japanese
and then the collabs where we played
mario kart
and and the collab where we played like
this this
shopping game uh shriek super
supermarket shriek shrink supermarket
something like that
yeah ah this is so cute and then at the
end
uh because i guess this song has some
kind of choreography that people like to
dance
she included like an animation of us
dancing it as well which must have been
so much work but she did it so well
she did such a great job um
she's so nice and then and then the
vocals um
the person who i asked to mix them for
me
the person who i commissioned to mix
them for me
um is the same thought same same person
who produced
and made and composed hinotoni and heart
challenger
and i just really like how he mixes my
voice um and i thought
i wanna i would like him to do it again
so
yeah he mixed our voices and i actually
you probably didn't notice it but i sang
all the harmonies
even like when guna was singing i was
the one singing the harmonies
if you listen to it closely because i'm
sure you guys gonna have it on repeat
after this
um you can maybe hear all my harmonies
in the background i was basically
singing the whole song
uh as a harmony as well i did notice
really
harmony singing is fun fun fun fun fun
already repeating it yeah i i was
repeating it a lot as well
because it just sounds good it looks
good and it's so emotional i love it
it's just so adorable and then
there was a little cape cameo of
the other halloween girls in there as
well i thought it was really sweet of
yoona to include
the other girls as a group there
[Music]
i'm so happy that that is out now and
you guys can watch it and i'm so glad so
many people
watched it together with me thank you
it's going to be on itunes
spotify no no no it isn't not i cannot
sell it it's also not monetizable
i um it might have you know cost
some money but it's not monetizable and
i just
want you guys to have this little song
cover of me with gooda
um because i just felt like putting
something out there
yeah i'm glad you guys like it so much
i listened to three times already while
i was talking
thank you it's super cute isn't it so
proud i'm so happy thank you i don't
know if you're still watching but thank
you for
um singing this together with me i feel
like our
voices really harmonized well
with each other
[Music]
let's sing something again sometime but
i wanna do like this is i did one i did
a
song cover with cali before and now with
guna i want to do one with
um with the other girls as well at some
point if possible
let's sing again yes yes yes oh
you have such a beautiful voice go down
i like the part where where
where your verse starts and you're like
at the beach
there's like i don't know there's
something so deep
and and and emotional about that and
like kind of like
melancholic melancholic melancholic
when good i was at that beach scene
wow so pretty that the atmosphere is so
so pretty okay i'm gonna probably go
watch that video a million times again
i hope you guys liked my new outfits
plural and
probably use all of these outfits in
different variations a lot of times in
the coming streams and in the coming
months
please continue to post your screenshots
and your thoughts
with the hashtag phoenixfashion
are you guys happy with uh beach kiara i
hope it's okay that i'm not
pharmaceutical a lot of you guys will i
think looking forward to that too
i didn't even think about that to be
honest
didn't even think about that idea i just
kind of wanted
i mean to me it wasn't even much of like
um specifically
beach kiana i just wanted a summer
outfit
that is like casual and
can be used at any time
actually you know what um first
in the beginning i told hookah papa that
i trust him and i just want him to do
whatever he wants to do
uh so i left it all to him but then
later on he
came back to me and he was like
i don't know what to like do like do you
really not have any like like
suggestions
[Laughter]
so i was like oh well okay i guess
and then i threw some ideas like this
this blouse a white blouse with like
ruffles
and uh some jeans shorts with the inner
pattern
and braids and the bag that was all my
idea but his idea
he added the cat ears and he added also
the straw hat was awesome idea but he
added the pacifier that was not me that
was not me actually
yeah so it was in the end it was a team
effort but
the pacifier was not me he he asked if i
wanted a pacifier after the uno collab
which i was i was quite happy about i
mean i mean why not i mean
i'm probably not going to use it that
often but
idea
um
now i wasn't sure if i could ask for
stuff like that because like it's a lot
of stuff but pablo is was really sweet
for
i'm adding so many things to my outfit
and i'm just really glad with how comfy
it is now
and and i'm gonna use it a lot i was so
happy about the braids i really like the
braids
the color is a bit different now
especially like behind my
ear you see that big strand of hair
that's really green and that that's kind
of cute
yeah my hair kind of changed a lot also
i don't know if you guys noticed this
but probably if you don't have
like a like a proper comparison right
next to me you might not notice it
let me try to find like a quick screen
oh no that's that's really this
the first screenshot that i will find
are we sure yeah no come on there must
be something else
uh i don't wanna i don't wanna point a
gun at everyone
come on give me a normal screenshot of
myself
wait ah there we go that's that's normal
[Music]
okay now i think now you can notice
my bangs as well are they used to be
kind of soft
but like he made it a bit more i have to
say
hmm not sure how to say it but yeah the
bangs
uh don't have this like softness to them
anymore and i
mean i like both yeah it's more matte
matte snap now
i got a trim
both are great yeah i think so
a lot of things changed i saw a lot of
people drawing me with the braids but
like still
keeping the the original gradation which
i love a lot too and you're you're
welcome to keep on doing that whenever
you draw me with this outfit
do whatever you want like if you want to
draw me with that hair
you're welcome to do it
[Music]
um
okay so i think i should go now that was
really exciting and the first stream in
like
three days because i couldn't stream on
the weekend i'll see you guys tomorrow
we'll be playing yakuza
i hope you guys will come to come
tomorrow to my stream because
it really has been a long time i just
want to chill with you guys and hang out
with you guys
tomorrow and tomorrow meow
tomorrow will be the uh new outfit
review of inna
on her channel actually at the same time
that my reveal was
at and then the day after will be good
and then the day after it will be amen
but they are doing it at different times
a little bit
later than my stream and then after that
on the day after that
we have a halloween casual collab where
we all
are hanging out in casual clothes
together so you might want to check that
out too
[Music]
all right so with that said thank you
everyone for watching today i hope you
enjoyed it
thank you guys so much please um
subscribe if you haven't yet
watch um the new song cover if you
haven't yet if you just missed
it and and and and and what stream heart
challenge uh
thank you guys thank you i love you i
missed you i missed you all
i'll probably be reading super jets
sometime in the in the super chat
reading stream at some point
um yeah
i don't want to go too too long into the
night you know
okay and in germany
thank you
[Music]
my sweet babies are getting used to
apartment but i'm so happy to see them
jumping around more and chilling
chilling in the same room as i am
now because they started only feeling
comfortable in the living
in the in the bedroom where i first
dropped them off when i moved
in and then and then now they're also
chilling in the office with me anyway
we're going to talk a lot about this
probably in my
in my minecraft stream where i have a
lot of time to talk oh my god oh my god
ah this is the problem when i don't
stream for free today so there's so much
i want to talk about but anyway bye-bye
thank you i love you
[Music]
so cute jonkers wants to cuddle she just
laid down in front of my monitor
[Music]
maybe she likes me more now that i'm a
cat myself
[Music]
real cat mom
bye
[Music]