The octopus is flying so high, and I'm
telling you, ``The rug
of the octopus is all about you.''  I
felt a relaxed and fashionable feeling, and my heart was so
wet that it fell apart.
I kept my determined heart there again,
waiting for the gaze that said love to me. It
was like I wanted to check the strength of the comb.  It's
a little fun out there on the other side of the dark night. If the same morning sun rises tomorrow too,
[Music] I don't
need anything else. It'll shine blue, a
mirabol in the starry sky.
[Music]
It'll shine on me, and it'll light up the earth.
[Music] Let's
dance here.  Let's make it clear, let's go. It all starts with one battle.
Even if I go as far as I can, I do
n't
care if I stray too far. If I reach the end of the wind, I'm sure I'll see a new world.
Beyond that,
[Music]
Okay.  Thank you, Loki,
I'm the only one with the nerves to witness it.Saro
Nohaya's reading Ruri also wants to deliver the first part.Merudeki.Alright, it's
time to take some time, it's still going on like this.I
want to soar my heart and fly forever high.  I'm
going to tell you that love is going to make you smile, and I'm going to
tell you that I've been walking and listening to you in front of my eyes, and this big
girl noticed it, and
after all,
it's a
fashionable wind.Dad.  My
heart was so wet that it almost fell apart, and I put my heart there again.I looked
up at the shitty thing called love.I
combed it and checked it out.
[Music]
[Music]The
screen was
pitch black, and there was no background music.
Why is there no BGM?
[Music]
Oh, it's a game, so I
didn't set the BGM. Wait
[Music]
Thank you, wait.
Thank you, thank you.
Open
[Music]
Masuata.  I was
surprised that it
wasn't.When I start it, I go
to that loading screen and it
always starts after I go.Yeah, I
forgot to include the loading screen and started streaming right away.I see,
then.  Oh, it was pitch black.
Ah, it's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. We're all here. We're all here.
Today, those squirrels and Ori are
going to explain the rules and guide us around. Today, that
team that's practicing is Ioffi and
Sorane-san.  And that Chiara and that Lele, I'll
do it without Team Unra and Pabo.
Oh, I'm good. I
can't move. I can't move. Yes, it's true. That's a
bug.
Restart once.
Restart. Ah, Japanese. It was set to Japanese.  Ah,
that's right. That's right. If it's the real Japanese settings,
wait, everyone's volume is adjusted here. Yeah, that's right.
That setting. If you
press the escape button MOD, something will appear. It's
just me. I'll set the voice level to 300%.  Why is it
so messed up? I
thought the voice was so loud, but only one person
got 300 plus.
But I don't know why. I kept thinking I was a coward. It looked like it was nothing, but it was loud.
That's terrible. What's
that voice?  Chat, that's the
one I used in the previous Hodoke, right? Yeah,
that's right, maybe it was from that time.
Oh yeah, that's when I added 300 to it. Oh yeah,
I didn't participate in it, so I don't know. Ah, that's what I
did at that time.  Yeah,
yeah, yeah, should I sleep? Should I sleep? I probably, probably, the sound was
doubled, maybe no, but it fits perfectly in my frame.
Who's drinking? I don't
have a bed. You can log out. Ai, it's
okay.  Good night,
good night, good
night
[Music] I
'll show you around. Thank you. Thank you. Please
come.
[Music]
[Music] I
made it
[Music]
Wow, I'm
in.
[Music]
And
from
[Music]
Dada,
oh yes, yes
[Music]
Yes, let's
go one more time.
[Music] Let's
go.  There are 5 games
[Music]
InH At first, there is a game called
Pleasure, but I haven't finished it yet,
but I'll explain the rules, and I'll send
players to search for the emeralds hidden by the society.
Compete
Yes Teams collect emeralds and
exchange them for final game essentials Yes
Yes Events include challenging gimmicky
platformers,
brain-damaged ones and tasks that require teamwork
Yes
Yes  beHi
Male For now,
it's just a lot of things like Chisto Hanka and the blocks,
etc. It's a treasure.
[Music] I
want Indonesia, I want it, I want
it, I want it.  I
'll explain. It
's coming.
[Music] I've been
working on this for months, and it's
amazing. The moon is moving, it's moving, and then there's that maze. Oh, the maze is moving. I don't know either. [Laughs] It's safe.
It's safe, it's okay, it's because of the ID members who have been using this, so I'm going to stop and introduce it to you.  Each pair will stand on stage and
follow the instructions of the uh-hikai.The instructions will
be given on the Indonesian boat, so all
talents should have learned some simple Indonesian 5s beforehand.  It's going to
take a while. I
still don't remember. No, it's okay. It's
okay. It's okay.
Teams earn emeralds based on how well they follow the rules.
[Music]
Yeah
Wait, where did that say that?  And this,
oh yeah,
everyone remember this and I
'll teach you the words
Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri and Kanan
Kana
Kanan
Right right
[Music]
Babakku word behind ka
Janjan Num
from
Sadoordoor
Tigaa 12345 This is right, that's it
[Music]
Hit
PUNCH
ter
sayhaveashave
particularhavejust
need
[Music]
[Music] Shamsham claus
shamjinko Jinko
jongkokga crunch jonko
Jinko yeah Hada
facty is jongko ki
left turn right
If someone says "fang fasting to kill," you should go to the left, or something like that.That's right, it's difficult.If someone says "hahap kiri," do you have to go left?Ah, yes, if someone
says, "Hap," do you
have to go to the right.  Hey, that's what I see.Oh,
oh,
olepa,
okakaa, throw, throw.
Sue, how do you do that?
Is it okay to have things? I don't care, it's okay.
[Music] It's
okay to throw something. I'll
give you something in a real game. I'll
give you something.  Throwing
is that button thing, and
what happens from here to here?
[Music] It's
red in the middle
[Music]
Sorry for blurring it out
[Music] Apparently there's
going to be a wall later here.
Neonununkiri is left Kari is
Times time or so Ka is some times or
two times or if it's red then it's like two times Ka
and two times number of times or this is Times yeah
that's right number of times
number right Niru
Mera is  Maybe that
[laughing]
Rima I want to do it while watching this.If someone
says ``Aja Rima,'' it's 5 times.If someone says ``Karin Lima,''
it's 5 times.That's right.If that's the case, I guess it's
easier to remember it that way.  I think it
's a good idea, oh, yeah, so here's yeah, and please stand here.  Etma will come out, so
let's make sure we can stand in the first place.
[Music]
Oh, you're right. Are you in
second place?
Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah, oh
, uh, you're ready.  Okay, let's start.
O
[Music] I'm
going with Slyth-chan. Hey,
EX will
will have will. That
means there's that stage.
[Music] There's a countdown for
3 seconds after ``Yes'' appears, so
when the countdown is over, we'll move on.
Feeling
[Music]
Look at the squirrels and
go here of the squirrels.
Ooh, I see.
Next, it's
really long. It's so long. It's so
long. It's the same pa. It's a good ending. Good luck.
[Music]
Uh, Ropa.
Sakamaji
Saka
Hakiri.  I'm
here. I want to see René and Kia next time.
[Music] It's
Ohana time so you don't have to sleep.
[Music]
[Music] I
see. Red
red
[Music]
OKspeSlowlySlowlyOK
Slowlyokok
Let
1 Kan
[Music]
3TRUSTtrustyou I
see.
ST2
[Music]
OfalAG
yesok
[Music]
STAGEONE
For now, I want to go like this
[Music]
[Music] I see.
Say
[Music]
Ira
no Teji How much is it for 10 stages?  There are 3
stages. Yes, there are 3 stages earlier, but there
are about 10 stages. I see. I see, the
number keeps increasing.
At first it was just jumps, it was a running jump, it was a jump, it was a jump, it was a jump, it
was a jump, it
was a run, it was a left.  Back to the left It
means that it will increase, right? Is
that okay
? It's okay. It's Oanstar, so there are about 10 stages, so please do your best. For now, if you hit about half of the stages, you'll be able to do something. Yeah, yeah,
no, next mini.  Shall we go to the game? Oh, no. Um,
next time, uh, go
. My poor memory will come out. Make
sure you remember it.
It's okay, it's okay. It's fun, it's okay, it's fun. Just go. Yes, yes, yes, yes,
here.
White.
Hey ah
chitachita
Nono
Nono all safety safety safety
[Music]
Safety is good, first of all I would like to explain it in Japanese
Be
jaan Yes, yes, I think the team is going to sell.
With colored wool,
you
must cut off the wool from the top with the color of the wool, and the wool must cut off the wool from the top
and fill it with the color of that team.
By destroying it, you can drop the opponent's Formen
to the lower world.The
Formen remain on the upper floor, and the wool of the team's color is
also the original one.
Maybe there is, but
[Music] I
remember it while playing, but there's
another moth below, and it's divided into bottom and top,
and when I look at it, it's the bottom, the bottom, the
top, and the
top.  So I can take the wool and
what do the people at the bottom do?
So, for example, I'm going to cut it, and the older
sister above is going
to paint the wool in her team's color.  If you
feel empty and
change the color of your team, the
more colors you have, the more the team will look like.
That means there's colored wool
somewhere too. Yeah, yeah, it's somewhere.
Oh, and that person is that opponent.  For example, if
Kia-chan has that luck, and my sister
hears that Chiara is on the left,
if I cut it, Kiara will drop it, and if that
character drops it, we'll win. I see. Yeah, yeah,
yeah.
[Music] I'm
going to cut it from the bottom, so the squirrel is going to be
[Music]
[Music] I
see.
[Music]
What's going on below?
[Music] I guess I'll
cut it. I guess I'll
support the team above. I'll
open it up soon.
If you press green and red, then if you press yes, it feels like the game is already over.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, the more colors there are, the more it
feels, so okay,
okay.  Let's do
our best to make sure it
doesn't. Which one is better, the top or the bottom? All you have to do is cut off the top and
put it in. Yeah, yes, you
can cut off the top, but whichever you choose. The one
on the top is also white.  I
can destroy the wool myself, but I
can't destroy the opponent's color.Ah, but the team below me, the
members below me, can
also destroy the colors of other teams.Oh, I see.So, if
I were on top...  The only thing you can do is put it in
with white,
put it in yourself.The white one comes out.Well, the other person's chimuru is
also easier to understand from the top.Well then, why
don't you do it to me?
[Music] Let's go
down,
go down.  I'm going to Owl and that cutter, huh?
Well, what color should my sister and I
choose? Well,
green would be fine. There's a lot of green, so the
people below me won't wear that wool.
[Music]
Dama can be broken, but it
can only be broken with those hands, right?
[Music]
Uha-san is the only one. It's
okay. I see. I see.
Sora-senpai is better. Or, it seemed difficult,
so it's better.
O
is
have Yeah yeah
yeah maybe it's okay to be on the upper side
[Music]
have I can do it without thinking a little bit If it's on the
upper side then yes
[Music] I'm sleeping I'm
okay
[Music]
Do your best and do your best
U  I'm waiting
Block, how many Starks should I have?
No, I don't know. I don't have them either. Where
did you get them?
Oh, how many stacks should I bring?
[Music]
Renji:
Um, I think 2 stacks is fine.  I think 2
Stax
Stax Is that okay? It's fallen a lot since then.
[Music] I
really remember
[Music]
Teru
Kiri
[Music]
O
Kirika
[Music]
Kirikiri and Kana Kashikashi  No
kana ka
majimajumaju
majudo
mundo
[Music]
Maji
Mundo I can remember it, oh majima
[
Music] Majichi Maji wa [Music]
Kanakana, it's okay
[Music]
Ah Aade
[Music] Let's
try it.  Let's
try it. Let's try it. No,
no, Japan. I heard the book. It's not me. That's
right, that's nice. Japanese is okay. Oh, it
's okay.
[Music]
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
L
[Music]
It's about to start. The reading is coming
now. Oh, I
'm here on the left.
Look at the missing wool. I see
the wool.
[Music] It
's falling, it's falling, it's in danger, it's in danger, it's
falling, it's falling.  It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous [music] it's dangerous, it's dangerous [music] it's dangerous, it's dangerous [music] oh, oh, oh, oh [clap] [music]  [
Music] I see,
wow, if you lose once, it would be
even more chaotic if there were 3 losing teams, right?
This is it.
Ah, senior, you make a mistake like that.
When you do something like that, it seems like the staff
will erase it behind the scenes, so it's day and time.  It's
okay without it
[Music] I
want to do it, so I'll try it. Yeah, it
feels
like I don't have to jump. I can do it without jumping. I can go. I
did it earlier, so I can go.  Toja Knife
's, I
press F1 and then I press F1 and then I see my partner
's name.
I have to press F1. Yeah, yeah, I don't
care where you are. I see. Well,
yeah, if you do that first, you
might see something like that. That,
that color.  If you do, you can understand the place from the top, so it looks like you can manage to do
it
[Music] Apparently
do it
[Music] [
Music] [Music]
PEOPLE wish
[Music]
Um, please.  It's like this, yeah,
if it's broken, then Shia breaks it, press F,
and it's a new Shia.
[Music]
Suo,
uh,
press F.
[Music]
F is ready
Or are you ready?
[Music]
wor I wonder if it's
finally here It feels good It feels good It feels good It feels
good It feels
good It feels good It feels good It feels okay It's okay It's
okay It's
dropped
[Applause] [
Music]
Teruoto [Music
]
[Music]
[  [Music] That
's left over, White
[Music]
Well, how was it? I want to do it again. It
's difficult. It's difficult. I'm at the bottom.
Thank you.
4 Chim. Let's
play 4 all at once. It's 44 people instead of 22.  I do
n't know, the same thing is dangerous, right
? If there's a big hole in the top, then you can hit other people. You can hit them like they're falling. You can hit them from above. It's okay to fall down. It's okay to do that.  It's going to be a battle, it's going to be a battle, it's
going to be a battle [music] [music] I see. Maybe three people at the same time. Then we'll win the final tournament.
[Music]
has
Turnwill
Hey, six people, six
people
Terunaku [Music] Okay, so we're gonna play 3 games, right? 3 games Yeah, it's
bad, it's bad, it's crazy. I'm sure
everyone will fall at once. Wow,
after that.  So, if you reach that green color, don't
be here, okay, okay, I'll
do my best, that's why that white, white
[Music]
It's not me, it's not the number left, it's the number left, it's not the thing, it's the number
left.  That's right, it's
important. It's important. At first,
you think if the color goes, you win. I thought so too, but no, the
one who stays on top wins.
Where
[Music]
Wait a minute
oramneedthereway
OK
[Music]
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, I heard that 6 teams, like Senpai and Fi, are going to
be participating at the same time, so I'm going to try one more round right now,
and we're all here, so why do
n't we all do it together? I
want to see a little bit more of that chaos.
I want to do it 6 top and bottom 6 pins
[Music]
Male
instrumentreally
[Music]
MAK
HORNlooklike
HORN
hearSound I
can hear a banging sound
[Music]
Nemata Yaro
Oh no, I
have 2 stacks now.
But that's enough, right?
[Music]
GoingLet
meGoing
beBLBL
[Music]
BLONE
yo,
let me drop it [Applause] I made a mistake
[Music] I
can do that punch, I'm sorry, Senpai, it's okay,
Wakayaka, maybe I'll do it 1  One more time, one more time
.
[Music] I
really hate it. I'm
not here normally. [Music] I'm sorry, that's how it is, that's how it is.
Punch, punch,
punch.  Punch Punch Punch Punch
[Music]
Para-senpai
neverVIIMANDVIIwas
afes
[Music]
[Music] It's been
happening for a while,
right? It's a vibration, right?
It's a smartphone vibration, right? [
Music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Are you ready?
[Music]
[Music] I
made a mistake, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Okay, okay, let's do it.
[Music]
Okay, 35
seconds, 30 seconds. I'm going to put it in a strange place. I
won't let you microwave the orange.  Oh,
it's orange, green, green, green, green, green. It's all over the strange place.
[Music]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
put it in a strange place.  It's
still alive,
so I guess that's what it's like. [Music] I guess that's what it's like. Hey, if you put it in the wrong pile, Nesa-san will
take it right away,
so it'll disappear on its own.
[Music]
No, no, it's delicious, it's delicious, it's delicious, it's
delicious.  Oh,
yeah, it's not a good idea to keep hitting the hole after all.There's a chance that it will remain.I've
tried both,
but it's quite possible that the one with more people will
fill it up quickly, so there might not be any holes left.  That's
right, so I guess I'll
give priority to filling in the holes. Well, maybe that's
better. If there's a lot of people, there will be people who will immediately go to fill in the gaps. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
but if it spreads, I'll really hit on it.
[Music]
Treasure at the beginning of the turn Treasure
Do the same movements as before Dots
and such
[Music]
Hey, it's okay, it's okay, this is here and
there, so let's play the next game,
okay?
[Music]
Well, we don't have time, so we'll finish
Let's play a game, please put the
food in. [Music] Put everything in there.
Nae, senpai, please use this.Potato
Potato, okay,
okay, potato, okay, potato, potato, I have a status,
but what should I do?I'll give you rice and potato.Potato,
potato, yeah, other rice is that.Recovery, I'm
strong, so for now, everyone.
Potatoes are all potatoes Yes,
that's right, that's right, and after this,
be After this, uh, we'll
be using the VC group, so
just a little bit of practice, group voice
Cha, soka, is it necessary
?
Settings Yeah, I'm going to go to a group chat.
Goop chat. Even if it's called a group chat, it's
a group.
Well, it's a group in Mac if
someone makes it. Well, I see, it's a create group. Who
makes it? I'll make it.  I'll wait and let you know when it's done. It
probably won't come in on its own, so what's your type? Oh, it's a
group type, after all, Noror Noma.
IS
[Music]
IS password?
What's your power password?
people
[Music] I
see, it's about 1111, right? It's
about 11.
Okay.  I'm thinking maybe I'll change my password for Ade Maa in Toy, but for
now, it's 1111. Yeah, right now, that voice, that group
chat, so I can't hear the other teams' voices.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, so I
can meet them in chat, oh, oh
, lady.  Do
n't go as a lady, oh oh oh oh oh lady. I suddenly appeared and asked what the password was, but I thought, ``Maybe you can't hear me.'' Yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, you can't hear me. Can you get me from a normal group chat?  Okay, everyone is
doing it. How to use groups.
[Music]
Oh, play Elmen. No, you're already
playing it. Next game. Well, I
'd like to explain it to you. Yes,
yes. Well, this is the last game. Yeah,
yeah.  Um, there's a maze called Maze Fy. Um,
yeah, the team
is made up of a fighter and a navigator. Oh, I see. The
navigator has a maze at the top that changes his body into one.
And he guides the fighter.  The
mission
is to help the fighter defeat the other fighter, yeah
yeah, and the team with the fighter standing
will advance to the final round.  I
think it's okay. I'm a betta. I'm probably going to
die. I'm going to die. I just did that too.
[Music] I'm
here.
[Music]
Fighter people are going to send me emails,
right?
This is the last time with Ade.  Since it's a game like this, I'm going to
turn that E that I've won so far into a vessel.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, so there are a lot of them. If I win a lot of games, I feel like I can get into a good weapon type. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, the
weapons change depending on the number of emeralds.  Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, if you don't
wait, you'll be a fighter in your bare clothes. You can do something with your spirit, you
can do something.
Yes, I say, yes, for now we
all use the same weapon, right? This is a panda. Yes,
this is practice. The weapon is that. It's
not a weapon. Sorry, that's not a weapon. The
yellow one.  The
weapon that ended
was [Music] here weapons and navigation navigator explained the navigator navigator
a little, and I also have a bubble navigator.  But they're
from Fighter or something,
Nabby,
and they're doing this
[music] here.A
Petit Petit
[Music] Phi Fa
Beth.Oh, okay, this is the
base, so as far as I can see, it's probably the purple, pink,
and green side.  For now, what I can see is yes,
so I'll try not to get out of this purple as much as possible.
I mean, up until now, I've been riding on top of Ajako, and I'm looking at it like this, and I'm looking at it, and I'm looking at it, and I'm in the group chat right now, and I'm in the pink-pink group, and I feel like there's someone there, nee-chan.
No, there's an enemy over there,
there's another team, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
maybe my sister can hit that, too,
so I'm trying to
stay within this range of purple, pink, yellow, and here.
Yeah, oh,
oh, you're so stubborn, but if you're standing here, you're
likely to be targeted,
right? That's why, please
[music] I
dropped
Haru.  What is
it,
uh, what is it?
Group Hey, the
password is 5555. Are you
going home?
Gogogogo
Hey, I changed it.Okay, it's changed.It's changed.Everyone is
like that.Gogo. Let's
start soon.Okay, then just a little
below.  I wonder if this is where I'm going O,
hey, I can see the position
O, but I can see the name, so I can see the name, do you
understand?  I can't see anyone because I'm not there.I ca
n't see anyone.I can't see anyone.Well, for now,
Yuppi is
going to go to the pink place.Okay,
for the time being, I'm not in pink.Ai, I
can see one person on the pink side.  There's a pink girl in the back
who's
in the middle of nowhere that I can't see.  I
'm on the other side, it's so hot, it's so hot, it's so
hot! Wait a minute, it's so bad, so hot
, so I'm in purple right now. I'm
trying not to let it go too far from the base, and it's so
loud.  My sister has been shot really bad.
Who is it
? Let's go over there. It's dangerous, it's dangerous. I'm
going to get grabbed too. If I'm over there, I'll be downstairs. I'll be downstairs.
Someone will say something. Wait a minute. I
can't wait for Pink right now.  You can't see my power, it
hurts, it hurts, I'm going to get shot. If I'm in pink, I'll
get shot really hard. Pink, I'm aiming right now. I'm going to shoot you
from deep inside. Where
should I go? I can't go, I can't go anywhere.
Yo,
purple is in my bag.  It might be better to come back to the
pink side. What is
this? What is this? Oh, what is this? Oh, what is this?
Oh, yellow, yellow, purple, and Renee are
behind me. They're chasing me from behind.
Huh?  There's no way, why, right now
? You're nearby, Reine, I'm hitting you.
Hey,
you're right next to me, and I can shoot, I can see, I can
see, I can see, I can see, I can crawl, I can shoot, I can shoot, I can
shoot, I can shoot, I'm aiming.  Yoyoyoyo, oh, it
seems like you forgot to eat. If you don't eat regularly, you'll get killed. I
forgot, ok, ok, ok, atta, congratulations on
your success.
[Music]
Oh, that's fine, the road is closed.  That's right. What's that? That's
amazing. I was being chased from behind. I was
being chased around
all the time. It seemed like I couldn't even get to the other side. I guess that's it.
Ah, I'm
leaving the voice chat, ah, ah, um, it's
like a group, ah, ah, there's a group of people. It
feels like it's all open, um, all, um,
tantal, ah, going to all, yeah,
going to all, oh
yeah, I see.  Yeah, okay, but the
punch hurt, the punch, the sword, the sword. I
'm sorry, Hamabro. I'm sorry, Senpai. I'm sorry, everything
. I couldn't see where he was at all.
Seriously, where was it coming from? The
red temple was red.  I
thought they were there, but I couldn't see them. I
couldn't see them. They were quite small. To
be honest, I was wondering if it was Yi-hee and Eun-woo.  When we were fighting,
both of them had white hair and were so
far away from me that I couldn't tell which one was Ioffi and which one was Una,
so yeah, I did
n't know either, but I really don't know. There are
two white challengers, and I can't read their
names.  I'm too lazy to read, so I didn't
.
Yes, I want to switch it up like this. Do you want to
do it again?
Oh, I understand. Is
it okay? I understand the contents. Oh, I understand the contents. I understand the contents at all. Yes, I
understand.  Rules: Do you
want to switch? It's okay with Fighter.
Question: Oh,
I also have a question. Ah, by the way,
people are under there. Do I
have to press that F1? Yes, no. It's okay. It's long
enough. Thank you,
Akira.  I haven't been shot, so I
don't know, but if I get shot, will I die someday?
Ah, navigator, yeah, navigator, oh, I'm going to die. I
need a bed touch from Karaga Sata. Is
Senpai dead? He was barely okay.
But it was so bad, I
almost felt like I was going to die if I got shot. No, there
won't be a second time. If the navigator comes back to life, I'll see you
again
[Music]
Fresp
Yeah, if Shigeta dies, I'll live again.  I
could go on and on, but if the fighter
is Yuffie, then that's it.
Then the navigator will come back to life.
]
ReallyLikeIsThe
thingonmyrightSide
thebighouseisalso
kindofinthewayand
meringare
SorrycommunwithST
wasthelikeWhereI
standIfILooktomy
righttherelikeBIG
HOUSEmeringwith
AnotherEnemyAREA
likeIs
ThatHowdoIseeit
thereFTOWERSjust
likeoneachSideofthe
MA
Goingbe3
think
TurnTurn
Not a
[Music]
Nakaii
thereyousaythereF
TOWERSIGUoneachSide
themidlelikemyview
tothetofrommy
blockedbytheistheo
GAMENotheogameThe
woolGameisBlocking
My Let's
do it again
O and Squirrel will be joining us
[Music]
Akaya Fai I'll do my
best so I don't die
Group BC  Let's
go
BC
[Music]
Oh yeah, we're not Kia, so let's
try our best not to die, let's
do our best. Let's go, let's go, let's
go. As soon as we get hit, we'll
have to eat some fries or some fries. It might be
dangerous.  I don't have it, no, no, no, no, I just
left my baggage in the place where I died,
so I don't know. Well, well, I'm
practicing raw potatoes, so I'm practicing. It's okay, it's practice, it's
practice, so it's okay.
Oh, that's enough.  Hey, I do
n't know where everyone is. I can't see this. I'm going to go back
and it's gone. Even if I jump like that,
if no one is there, I can't see anything anymore. Hey, it's me, so I can't
go. It's
amazing from here.  I'm being targeted, yes, I'm being targeted.
I was targeted a while ago, too.
So, where are you now? Pink, who isn't in Pink. Pink, that's right. Right now, you're in Pink. So,
uh, right now, I
can see you.
[Music]
Yo, Chiara. I can't see you at all.
That's it, it's moving so tiny It's moving so much I can't really reach it.
Lady, lady, lady, I
want a telescope. I want a telescope.
Can't I do that? It's a telescope. While I'm using a telescope, I'm sure I can't do that. I
can't hit it.  I'm
ready, ready, I'm going to try not to stray too far from the base. [Music] Bye, then, where are we going? Oh, I'm confused. Oh, I guess I'm right. I'm
still in purple.  That's
right, that's Ioffe. Oh yeah, there
's someone there.
There's someone in pink, so it's a
bit purple. There's yellow, there's yellow, too.
Oh, so I'll just invite you to this purple one, nee-san.  I
'm hitting the person under there, I'm hitting it now, thank you, thank you, the
yellow side is amazing, it's so deep, it
's in the back, but I
couldn't close the road for a while.
Everyone there is yellow, so should I go yellow too?
Or where? Right now, there's Rene on the left and right, and
there's a squirrel, right? They're all there, I
guess.
Airiru
[Music]
Okay,
now I'm in purple
now. But either way, I'm right next to you. I know, I know, I'm
wearing protective gear. It's
scary. I'm laughing so hard. I'm laughing so much.
Su is laughing so hard. Oh, come on,
come on.  The water is so broken it's scary,
bro, I can't
believe it. That squirrel's laughter is scary. No one's been found by the Endermen. I don't know. Maybe it's me. Oh, go, Lilith, there's a squirrel. It's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous.  That's a bad aim,
that's what I was aiming for, but
it went
up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, but
what should I do?  Oh, I'm aiming for a potato,
but I feel like eating, eating, maybe. Right now,
Kane is going to break soon, so what
should I do? Oh, it's purple, it's
here, it's purple!  I'm in the purple,
I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple, I'm in the purple,
I'm in the middle of the wall.
No, this is what I said earlier. Well, the
sword breaks quite a lot, so this is it.
If I get a lot of money, I wonder if I'll change the sword a lot. I
think I'll only change a certain amount of that emerald, so for example, yeah,
yeah, strong sword 1.  Do you have a number of weak swords that you can use as a book? Yes, that's right.
Well, I'll
ask you a little bit. Yes, that's quite a bit. I
turned into Bolbor a while ago,
so yes, the person who defeated me just now told me
about that item.  I can take it,
yeah, that's it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I can't
tell you where it is.  I
see, let's go to Oar, let's go to Oar
Yes
[Music] Yes, come back blue
[Music] Peko welcome back Peko I just heard that. No, I wonder if Peko-senpai is there. That's it. There's also [Music] They
look quite similar.
Thank you
[Music]
Um, question,
question, what, what, what,
how many swords can you buy,
but it feels like you only have one sword, and it's been a long time since I've
been in a battle, and it's a little bit worn out.
It's a waste of money. Ah,
if I had a lot of money, I'd be able to
buy many books. Maybe one. But I recommend it.
[Laughs]
HELLi
cber
haryduanyberkita
bisabeliaDongSWORD
akutengahudahrusak
lagi  [
Music]
[Music]
ChatRat
lagisalah
lagi
Navigator
OverNavigatorigate
Well, the rules have changed again,
uh, and if the navigator dies, he'll
come back to life, but I
guess he can't navigate anymore, but the game
won't end.  Don't become a navigator,
you're just looking at me.That's why
you shouldn't use that button either.  Is
time okay
? It's okay tomorrow. I'm sorry. Time is not okay. I see. Well, it's
okay.
Need
[Music] I
'm here.
Thank you. I'm chasing you.
Who is that Enderman?
There's an Enderman here.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Kaja
[Music]
Kira, where are you?
Should I pick this up?
No, I'll pick it up, because I can't carry anything
[Music] Don't
chase me now, don't chase me, don't chase me, don't chase me,
either.
[Music]
Which one?
I'm sorry.
[Music]
Here, here, here.
Next game.
One of the pairs is given the name of the stage.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, they are part of it,
but they also set the scene for one, where one
player tries to guess what it is, and the
pair responds with an emerald.
Baby, all the colors,
green,
Okay, I'm yellow, and
oh,
and who's building, who's going to do it, who's
going to do it,
which way will it start?
Please do your best. It
's starting. I'll do my best. Um, just
earlier, earlier,
oh,
321. I
feel like it was like this. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, seriously, this is the wall. Okay, uh,
hey, oh,
yeah.  That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.  I do
n't
have anything to do with color, haha, heart, different, but buuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
[Music]
What's this, this, this, this, this, this, etc. Colors are relevant,
what am I? What's this for me?
[Music] I wonder if it's
Pondering, like a snake or something.  I like it, I like it, I like it, I like
it, it's like that, yeah, yeah, yeah, I should read the real chat, probably, yeah, it's like this, if I like it, it's just round, but I don't know why, so
yeah, there's a lot of things when it's round.  I imagined it. I
like balls and stuff.
Oh, oh, oh, senpai and Ki-senpai. Let's
do it.
[Music]
Then, I'll give you the title.
Oh yeah. Um,
uh, let's go to Risu-senpai. The theme
is the key, oh-
oh.
[Music]
Oh, it's difficult, I think it's a little difficult,
but it's difficult, okay, are you ready? Yes, it's
321, what is it, what is it, what is it?
I got a kill. Who was it?  It's a hit,
it's a hit, it's a big hit,
so I can
understand why.I ca
n't help but think that this one shot will take me to the top.I think it's a hit, and I feel like I'm a genius.It's so good, I guess I'll try it again.  One more time,
one more time, one more time, one more time,
one more time.
]
So it's
like how many rounds do you have to change
? I wonder which one it is. That's
what I heard. They talked about squirrels and the like, but it seems like it
doesn't matter how many times they do it. If it's 3 or 4 times, I'll change it.  It's
natural for us to make it public,
right? Yes, it would
be more fun if we took turns, right? It would be fun.
If it were this, it would be 2 rounds or 4
rounds. I
don't think it would be a good idea to do one of us
twice.  It doesn't matter if I write it down and one of them answers twice, it's OK. He
guessed it right away. He
said "I don't like it," and then I
got the answer.
So I did that and went down once, and I
thought I'd put it on something fluffy and round,
but then before that I answered,
Okay, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, the octopus's
gentle
[laughter]
voice is soothing.
I was healed, and what
I saw just now was like that beautiful bond in the sky. Telepathy, telepathy, yay, nice. I wonder if someday we'll climb a tree together. Climb, climb, climb. Climb, climb. At that time, I'll go and help.  He's flying all the way, he's
coming, he's giving me a ride, he can climb
up, but he can't get down, he ca
n't get down, right? Maybe that's why I thought so, maybe that's why I'm going to
help you, I'm going to help you, I'm going to
burn that tree, I'm going to burn it  No,
if we can burn it, we're also being burned,
right? No, we won't
burn it. Don't burn it, let's take it down and use the stairs. Stairs and
stairs are a bit difficult. Faa, I
'll call a fighter. Faafafa
[Music] I
guessed it with bond bond.  Is it
telepathy?
Tepa:
Thank you very much.
That's right. No matter
how you look at it, you're like, ``Anya,'' but Ray, oh,
Ray. Seriously, I've been wearing my sister's face for the past two months,
and somehow I've been hearing Renee's voice. When
Anya is here.  I'm
thinking about it, right?
[Music]
[Music] I do
n't know if I'll change it or not. I don't know yet, so maybe tomorrow [
Music] I'm
still practicing.  If you want to do it, uh, Pron, I'll
practice. No, I'll practice one more time. Do you want to
try it? Oh, I'll try it again. Oh, I guess I'll
try it again.  Let's do it
again, ooooooooooo
[Music]
Raco imitates too much.
Listen to the question over there.
Leave it to me.
sayes
japaneses,
no, I see.
[Music]
Oooh, yes, I see.
Well then, Bill is Chiara and Seo-senpai, yes, yes.
Hey, this time it's Hana. It's
easy.
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, I've already made it, no, I'm making it. I'm
still asking questions. Is it
okay to use beer? Either way, it's okay. If it
's an easier floor, I'd be better.  When you look
at it from above, you're probably thinking, ``This is it.'' I
think it's easier to do it horizontally than vertically,
so horizontally is better. Okay, look at it from above. Are you
ready? Yes, yes, I'm ready.
[  [Music]
Let's go.
321 What is it? Sorry, the place is changing.
Maze.  I
wanted to make something like that, that's what I wanted to make, that's what I wanted to make, that's what I wanted to
make, that's how bad I am, so let's start from here.  Well,
if you want to do it on the floor, you can do it, but the space is a bit small.
Yeah, yeah, this is true. I see.
Yeah, yeah, I'll leave it to Eunwoo, so I probably
won't do it on the floor. Let's do it one more time.
Let's do it one more time.  Let's
do the rounds, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
please.  3
Yes 1 What's wrong with me? NoNoNo I'm
better than me Why are you
doing this? You're a big snake, uh, you're a
chicken, you're
no good.
[Music]
Hanaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  It
's not bad, this is
what, what, what
[Music]
seconds seconds seconds
jellyfish No, I think it's a junk jellyfish, a jellyfish, a jellyfish, it's not a jellyfish.
Hey, where, where, where do you look from, if this flies, if it
flies
[music]
What,
what,
what, banana That's right, okay,
okay
, this is a banana.  I
can see the banana, I'm glad I can see it. I
thought it was Gu-chan's mark.
So let's see if the big sister can guess it this time.
[Music]
HaveImeanyoudoFFWay
notalltopickafter
KNOWKNOW
Pi Yeah Ok
That's in Indonesian.  I don't understand what you're saying.
No, there's no need.
Yes, I'm ready. Hey, from above, Lady
Deo.
[Music]
Oh,
no, no, no, no,
no. What should I do? Spoon did it. Spoon,
tennis racket or spoon.  I
thought it was something like that.Ah, I did it diagonally,
and when I looked at both of them, I realized, ``I see, I'm
sorry.  It's a quick guess, it
's a hit, it
's a hit, it's a hit. [Applause] That means we're both good friends. It's a feeling that we can't get into. [Music] [Music] The rules may change in the actual performance.  Maybe it's a
little bit. There's a slight possibility. There
's a possibility. So, hey.
May, yeah,
yeah, I've played all the games anyway. I
wonder if I did it.
Nice
than
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Shall we go out to the US?
Yes, it's good.
I think it's good.
Where are you?
[Music]
Excuse me, someone has a real show tomorrow, right?  It seems like it
's tomorrow,
so I thought I'd use today's picture from the practice session as the thumbnail for tomorrow. Ah, I
guess
it's here. [Music] Where did Miko go? How do I climb up?
This, this, my sister,
this is here.
[Music]
Where is it too high
?
It's night, it's night.
Where do I want to take a photo
?
Let's go here. Moko's back is cute, so I might as well do it here.
Wawa, wawa, where?  Is this the end
? Tell me,
this is the entrance. It's the entrance. Yes, it's the entrance,
so it's okay here too. Is it okay to stay here, Senpai? Where, oh, it
looks like a nice place, but maybe
this is the place. Is this the right place?
[Music]  ]
Yes, I laughed, but I want you to send me a photo. Oh, that's it. Do
all the seniors want to take it? That's it. It's a
fit,
but I want to take
it too. Really okay cheese. Can we get closer? Maybe closer. Ususuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuusuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu up up and up
Thumbnails of 6 of the 66 members of the Kamen practice session
Good thumbnails to use Wow
cheese
[Music] I
can't get too close to you.
When you get close, everyone gets huge
[Music] I
'll take a photo.  I can finally get it.
Thank you very much for this kind of thing. Please
send it to me. I'll send it to you.
[Music] Tata-
in
[Music] You
did your best
. You're off. [Music] Good
luck. Good luck.  Hey,
wow,
OK,
open the door and see if you're
talking. Pipi. Thank you. I thought you were talking, but I
looked over here and saw that you were talking. See you
tomorrow. See you tomorrow. See you tomorrow.
Let's do our best tomorrow. Let's do our best. Let's do our best.  Well,
let's do our best. Well, I'll take a break first. I'll take a rest too. See you then,
see
you soon. So, thank you for today.  I
learned the rules,
so it was fun. So,
I worked hard today, so I'll enjoy it to the fullest tomorrow.
That won't happen again. It's already tomorrow. Let's do our best. So, I
'll see you again on tomorrow's broadcast.  I'm
sure there will be some trouble at night, but I'll do my best to remember the words
Maji
[Music]
Maji Zubai
Bailogau
Chachichi
Senkyu Tamakusa Gracias Malum Ka
Danda Arika
Glover It's fun I wish I could practice more
[Laughs]
I'll practice more every day  I
really wanted to,
but I'm glad I was able to do it today. I'm glad it wasn't a one-shot show.
It was a day that proved my artistic talent.