[Music]
do
tell a friend taka molly
[Music]
did you guys wipe your tears is everyone
okay guys was that what was those uh
four or five minutes enough for you guys
to get your [\h__\h] back back
hey you're here though you're the one
that got them all emotional man i tell
you what
you got me emotional too i was like
we're good
i love that song so much actually my mom
introduced me to that song
and um when i was super super young and
and i i like tried to sing it when i was
sitting next to her
and she she really liked it so ever
since then
this song is a deep in my heart but it
never had such an accurate meaning
ever before as it did oh yeah wow
but we're gonna cheer you guys up again
we gotta change our mood and lighten it
up a little bit yup
yeah so uh we got some cute anime songs
we got some originals
yeah so let's freaking go here's some
sparkles yeah
yeah woo here we go
[Music]
hey i love this song yeah
what what put your hands up hey
[Laughter]
yes i will kill you reach that i [\h__\h]
up in the beginning anyway so this is
good yeah no problem
we started
[Music]
me
hey what up
[Music]
it
um
wow some harmony going on yeah
all right dead beats eight people ain't
pushing
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
yes i feel great now and not like i want
to cry
[Music]
i'm glad to hear that so that might
depend on the next song that we're going
to sing then i might want to cry
next song it's a bit
a bit of a sad okay it's a bit of a sad
one your boy tried real hard to learn
this part i tell you what
thank you thank you you're welcome it's
one of my favorites once again
i like only choosing only using the good
songs yes
yes that's good i like
you might not get anything like this
anytime soon because
okay it's kind of difficult to do over
this courage it's true you better enjoy
it
appreciate it and cherish the moment
yeah it'll have to be when kiara comes
to visit again
yes yes which kiara will do i will come
to your place yeah
and and i will i will sleep on your
couch
yes yes you will thank you for thank you
for that yeah no problem
no problem then in the middle of the
night out
i jump into your bed but your bed looks
so confident all right
you just look so comfy no what will
happen is i will let you sleep in the
bed and i will sleep on the couch
that's what i want to do for my guests
[Music]
hey just take the offer of the bed and
be happy with it and
sleep on the couch thank you you're
welcome
thank you thank you oh and then
i will finally make you the promised
french toast yes
the french toast of takanawa yes please
i do have a kitchen actually yes
well i would be worried if you wouldn't
well yeah i do because of this jobs
don't worry i'll make you i'll make you
the best french toast ever did you
end up learning how to make french toast
oh yeah i know how to make french toast
it's just i'm sure that there's some
secret
that i don't know that makes the years
better than mine's probably not
i mean not nothing too big there's
nothing not much you can do wrong
but i like to put in like cinnamon in
the in the mix that sounds good in the
egg mix i like i put in some cinnamon oh
yeah yeah
and then of course top it off with a
million of strawberries and stuff
yeah lots of toppings freezing [\h__\h] and
nutella
yeah do you like nutella i love miss
hello that was dope you actually have a
big
can of it right in front of me right now
don't expose me
you have exposed me plenty of time so
guess what everyone
taken out has a big carton of nutella
sitting on her desk it's almost empty
though i mean i don't know if that's a
good offense i guess that's the best
exposing yourself kiara
now you're digging your own grave it's
not even me this time but it's because
you know i always gotta have the nutella
already too
to eat breakfast in front of my pc i
guess that's also true yes
oh well let's go for the next time yes
you guys know that song yeah i think it
does have like
what is it 400 million views yeah
it's from a movie by the way you
probably didn't watch it yeah i haven't
seen the movie but i know that there is
a movie that's okay
it's just a song that's really good yeah
that's that's what i think
all right that's freaking out what
effect do we want though should we keep
that i don't have anything nice do you
have fireworks
i i have something similar yes okay
oh perfect that works that's what that
works well enough
[Music]
i do the same [\h__\h] you're good it's hard
to tell with these
[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
is
a
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
la la la la la la la
la la la la
la la la la la la
[Music]
what a beautiful ending to a beautiful
song we
you're welcome to edit that i want out
guys yeah you guys can put it right
there
sorry i couldn't stop myself yeah me
neither i could not control myself so
those awkward moments when there's this
melody ending and you just don't know
what to do
yeah you're like oh man guess i better
improvise
thank you guys i hope you liked it yes
next song is very i think um the looks
of our thumbnail
really is fitting to that you probably
don't know because you probably didn't
watch the anime
oh but it really really reminded me of
macros
from here yeah oh yeah so we're going to
sing
i'll do my best this beginning part i
tell you what i've surprised you up
until now
never like i know i've heard it
somewhere before
but it's everywhere yeah it's everywhere
gosh i'm gonna try
okay maybe turn off the fire i'm gonna
turn off the fire
and lion
but actually fire is quite fitting
though i'll keep the fire
whoa fire but i'll turn off
this one can we check them out they just
just want to listen to it one more time
okay okay i can't i can give you the
melody though oh you can't
[Music]
the first one
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah yeah right i'm trying my best to
sneeze for you guys
okay it's tough and it's okay
[Music]
hey
um
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
take it away
[Music]
let's go
wow
[Music]
um
m
here we go
hi
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
sick violence
on the ride here i was listening to it
the whole way but
yeah it said but once you got it it's so
much fun to sing
yeah it really is i was i was getting
into it kind of towards the ending there
i just need to listen to it maybe a
thousand more times then i can do it for
karaoke
you'll be fine you'll be fine once you
get it then you can have like really
dramatic karaoke sessions yeah yeah yeah
people go nuts i i specifically
gave the shell parts to kelly because
i don't know she kind of she's seen it
yeah there's like these these two main
characters
uh uh cheryl and olan gary
and if we had to say who is definitely
that guy
is me and cheryl is here cheryl's like
really cool she's like a she's
she's a okay i wouldn't say you're a
diva but she's definitely a diva
um and she's like a superstar yeah cute
is like a cute cute cute girl who's also
a great singer
and yeah i need to ask you later about
this anime because
macros is super old yeah i know i've
definitely like
heard of it and i've seen things about
it but i don't know like what kind of
anime it is
and i'd like to i like older anime and i
want to watch more so i'm going to ask
oh
you might like it yeah you might like it
it's very nice they have a lot of good
songs too
all right i think for the next song
is it mine
i think it's just fitting right now yeah
it works very well for this song
okay it should be this one
[Music]
yeah here we go okay and we'll fire it
all up hey put your hands up oh okay
chill out guys should be fine yeah if
they say something
here we go
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
my
and
don't pray i will never give up don't
[Music]
break
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray if i go
wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please where i need to
[Music]
go
no no no no no no no no no no no wow
[Music]
me
i will find you
[Applause]
[Music]
as well
that was fun yeah i had a good time i
could feel my soul burning through uh
the heavens
yes yeah i felt like a phoenix this is
such a such a rock song
song i love people who don't know i
don't know why you wouldn't know but
that's
my first original single that came out
for thanksgiving
yeah yeah but i recently um recently i
made a new song hi challenger
maybe one day we can sing that together
too yeah next time you come
yeah it's a very cutesy song but yes
i saw the video thank you
i need to tell you the truth okay i saw
it a long time ago
oh okay i just didn't know what to say
oh really
i'm very shy i really just
i wanted to say thank you and welcome
dedication i felt like i wanted to
you know when i was thinking of doing a
valentine's day i thought it has to be
for kelly obviously you're my
valentine's
wow that's very that's a very sweet
thing
uh for you to say oh yeah oh yeah you
wanted to sing a song with me but like
um is it um
is that instrumental like on yes it
should be it's typically
you guys next song is cali song for me
yeah
um now the surprise is ruined so you can
just go ahead
i mean it would have been ruined at some
point
yeah you can go so i chose this song
because it's um
it's sung by a sunday oh and the lyrics
reminded me of me and you
when you read the translation so here we
go
also i know how to sing it yes
oh thank god this is the good karaoke
okay yeah baby
oh sick i love this wow this is so dope
hey hey hey all right
here we go it's time for your boys solo
i'll do my best okay
[Music]
bring out your guitars i want to see
those guitar emojis flying through here
we go
yeah now we're talking oh now we're
cooking baby here we go huh
[Music]
thank you for the backup i love the
backup vocals thank you
yeah yeah that's right you sound just
like the guitar give it up
give it up tiara
[Music]
yeah it's perfect
my
[Music]
[Applause]
i hope the neighbors heard me
oh god
i'm going crazy i feel like i'm going
crazy
thanks yeah um wow
i thought i was gonna blow out my voice
toward the end there oh my god your boy
just gets so into it when i sing a song
i just go i go wild
i i get that i love
thank that you're welcome thank you for
saying
that hype song no prob the lyrics do
remind me of you and me though
yeah oh yeah now i gotta read them again
not sure which part you're mine
you have all of them pretty much know
yes
i ran past you with a thirsty heart is
that me running fast you are you running
fast
you running past you dog i don't know
you're running past you me running past
myself i'm sorry
hold
[\h__\h] i spoiled it did you guys see it
well i feel like it happened but before
we sing that
i would like to read
a letter you wrote a letter what the
[\h__\h] i didn't get i didn't write a
letter
you should have known you know me you
know that i was gonna write a letter
this probably isn't the last time we're
gonna see each other before you fly away
so
yeah well i shall
i should turn off my echo oh my echo is
more pretty
i'll keep it on okay i didn't prepare
any sad music though
okay maybe i can imagine it maybe i'll
play
i don't know i don't i don't have
anything sad
i have a i have a jasmine uh jazz
version of pinot noir
that might have my help but how is it
though where is it
and then we go to the last song after
dad i just i just you know
it's nothing nothing i can't find it
damn it whatever that's okay they can
imagine it i hope you all have good
imagination
well now i don't want some sad music
wait
search sad music royalty free on youtube
but can we trust them
uh that look in the comments section
usually there will be somebody saying
i got
[Music]
you can look in the comments and see
what they say
make me cry
how about how about unravel
but unravel is a song i could play the
karaoke vision of unravel yeah sure go
for it
no but that's i don't know that's kind
of too noisy oh really
how about actually you know what i'll
really quietly i'll just play
live again oh nice idea a great idea
okay and then we'll transition
instantly into all right don't be
shocked though this has my backup vocals
in it so i'll contact
i shall dear callie
i need to turn the matrix off oh yeah
remember to tighten where we first met
it feels like it's not that long ago
actually
even though it should ever since the
beginning i knew you were someone i
wanted to be friends with
you had this open funny attitude but
also you speak out what you think very
directly which i like about you a lot
joining her life especially in the
beginning
i was very glad to have you i think
without you
i would have felt maybe very lonely
and lost in the beginning well a big
reason why you helped with that
is obviously because we were actually
able to meet unlike the other members
and i'm super thankful for that
opportunity
these kind of meetings will be happening
way less from now on but that's okay
we don't need that anymore even if it's
a lot of fun remember that time
when we went to that yakiniku place the
first time i was
glad to know and i was so glad to have
the same
taste of food in many ways no weird
inside things right yeah
only the normal meat yeah i was also so
glad that you trusted me
back then in the beginning things were
still so awkward and we didn't know what
to share with the others
but it was so glad i was so glad to
finally open up to someone
and talk about it all remember the time
when we went to karaoke after
celebrating our debut
with yet another yakiniku i still have
the recordings of you wrapping eminem
you looked and sounded so cool i was
really feeling like a fan girl
i also loved the time we sang dancing
queen together and both were dancing
stupidly in the little space we had in
that room
you are the girl now
forward to 2021 the year of our wow wow
world cover
thank you for going to hokkaido with me
ah you know i always wanted to go there
but i
didn't want to go alone you are you're
always so busy but you took lots of time
off to do this trip of me
you prepared it so well and normally i'm
the planner when it comes to trips
and it was nice to finally be able to
just let it happen mostly
the only thing that i finally felt
comfortable entering review
was so relaxing the scheme was so
dangerous
nerve-wracking but such a fun memory
the snow around us when we took a hot
foot bath with hot wine and grilled
apples was magical i'll never forget it
you better get that freaking bunny so
that i have something fluffy to pet when
i visit you
i'm waiting i need something something
to hold when i'm sleeping
you got it it could also be you though
doesn't have to be funny we both had
some struggles
with finding real friends in japan i
think
i hope that in me you feel maybe a
little bit
that you found one i hope that i was
able to
relieve your stress and
is that looping i was hoping that you
that you were able to relieve your
stress a little bit and talk of your
worries every once in a while
i hope that once i'm gone you'll find
someone to talk to
and hang out with like with me even if
it might hurt
a little bit to watch that but i think
he really needed
human contact someone to just hang out
with
and chill but don't forget about me
don't hesitate to message me whenever
you want to get something off of your
mind
i always have an ear for you i'll miss
you a lot and probably regret leaving
then being all on my own with no one to
off collab in
all straight
but i'll come back as often as possible
to visit you
yay after all we gotta do the 3dw one
day together and then britney constant
take a more concert i still want to do
an original song with
you i want to go to okinawa with you go
to disneyland and so much more
so please wait for me
and don't forget me i really hope you
won't forgive me
p.s do what you think is best for you
if you're not sure what it is take a
moment to listen to your height
[Music]
um it's not like we're forever apart
yeah it will still be like
a lot and a lot of our collabs up until
now we're online anyway so
it's fine but yeah so i mean i'm still
i'm so sad to
you know when i'm in australia i won't
have anyone to
do off collabs with and meet so come
visit you in australia
not that far away you're gonna come for
real
yeah i mean i want to travel the world
i've said this over and over again and
once it's okay for me to do so i will do
so oh you'll love my cats you will love
that i want to meet them i love
cats i freaking love cats oh my god
you visit my cats and i visit your bunny
yeah perfect
yay then we have something to settle
but i i just hope that
me being away doesn't change anything in
my friendship nothing's going to change
in our
girls
the part when i sang you're the only one
who's ever been inside
of me and you're like i just took out
your soul just to get your soul many
times
originally that was i think some
something like i took out your appendix
yeah perfect perfect uh
version of that so wait what have you
ever had your appendix taken out
no what is what is that anyway what does
that do it's a little thing on the end
of urine test i
i actually have had mine yeah what does
it do
long time ago um it doesn't do anything
which is why it's okay for it to be
taken out but
it can get inflamed us they have to cut
it off and then take it away
um that happened to me a long long time
is that the one where like wait where
you're
when you feel like the part when you
have to pee i don't know it just hurts
your hands
yeah i think i've seen that in and see
i've seen it in movies and series where
the characters would be like
i heard so much and they they really
don't drag it out because they're like
oh you just
got you just got to poop it out yeah but
then you go on the toilet and like
nothing is happening and then
and people like oh it's just like gas
pains or whatever but nothing is
happening at all
and then they're like oh no they take
you to the x-ray and then they see that
your appendix is about to explode and
they say you know you've got a lot of
rocks
wait what happens if it explodes uh your
blood gets poisoned
holy [\h__\h] you might possibly die yeah so
yeah holy [\h__\h] damn you're both the best
demons in the underworld
what i didn't know it was that's your
imagine that you could die oh yeah you
can't
it's very possible well i'm glad you
don't have it anymore yep i'm good no i
i figured out right actually um it was
it was that it was at a
swinging camp oh no yeah i was at a
sight swinging camp
and i had to i had to go wake up the
demons in charge and say help
oh my god the night in the night it was
like three a.m oh
sick yep oh my oh
did they take you seriously at least
right away yeah they did right okay good
all right on that note we shall sing
live again for real now
which will be the last song let's do it
yay it's my song we sent one of mine and
then one of yours are you going to wrap
kiara
oh yeah okay did you see the the way i
parted it later i did i did i'll do my
best how to do my best
you can do it and even if even if it
sounds more like singing or you just put
your own spin on it
that's fine and i love it okay that's
right
yeah you got this
[Music]
it's the end of the party let's hit the
road before i have to flashback to
shinigami mode
gotta run but thanks for watching what i
put out though it's not a ton
excuse me sorry tai han time to say
goodbye again promise it's a matter of
time before we're best friends it's not
the end of your hiatus cause very close
doors just the intro of a brand new
story
one wish that i can't pretend i don't
wanna see
come true i know it wouldn't make a
difference if you thought of me as much
as i think
about you but maybe it's deliverance
from the pain i know it's coming on with
my own soul's finally gone it's not
wrong to think about it but that's that
for tonight cause we're immortalized
forever in the songs that we write you
know shout out
goodbye the end i'm not sorry but i want
to see you again sometime
a song in my heart a world of worry
falling on your mind why don't we leave
it all behind
close your eyes for a minute and
envision a place where everybody's
cherishing life in one same space and
it's embarrassing to say cause you're
the one that i change but see mortality
is what makes a life sweeter that tastes
right
fatalities fallacies sweet and sour
simmer freeze time with me
and yeah refreshing like a haunted
breeze honestly it's messing with the
reaper mentality sleeping on the fact
that history has told me how to be
do i despise human life something really
i ain't thought of but i died inside a
little when we say
no
it's not enough just to see you every
once in a while searching in the
darkness so my world for a smile there's
you
mata
okay
[Music]
see you again sometime
but i want to see you again sometime a
song in my heart a world of worry
falling
on your mind
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i gave a lot of when i was part of
the lyrics i was like oh god i can't
really
learn all this rap oh my god so i gave a
lot of it to you
that's okay no worries i don't mind kind
of great
what's the audio fine though guys i i
hope it was fine
good enough because this will this will
forever be forever being
here in yes until we die before until we
die
you mean but we never die you mean never
that means forever eternity yes
yes which literally is just you know
yeah for
you and me or whatever you and me
wearing a tunnel
yeah i guess so whoa oh man i guess so
huh
so that's that
that
thank you for taking your time and your
busy busy schedule you're really
freaking busy i am but you know it was
worth it it was still fun
i hope we can do many many more things
in the future as i said in my in my
little letter and core uncle
ankore
[Music]
we can do that if you want i can't you
can do like num um
well i'll wait do i have the i should i
should probably have it
oh my god if i look for right am i going
to find it
[Music]
there we go i think it was that one oh
sick
no that's not the one oh maybe it was
that one
this one i haven't done this one in a
while
last time i did it i really practiced
hard and i somehow made it but oh god
oh really i i so like um
okay i'll give you like i'll give you a
tap okay
for you okay and then a double tap for
me
okay you got it one tap let's see if
we're getting two tabs
let's try yeah baby okay
off of off of the reverse yeah let's see
if it's gonna
go work oh god oh god i'm nervous we'll
be fine we're fine
how does it start again
people taking lives wrecking knives and
guns the real murder kind of sewers in
the ruins of hell they're used to luring
the audience with mow itself cuz to my
surprise
live for the eyes can't she nice try
stopping the [\h__\h] davinci of
human erasure can't stop the pacer make
sure it stands enough my rhymes slay
first shadows haters
i see you no one's gonna buy this [\h__\h]
i believe you couldn't sell hell in a
literal sense but it pretends but the
viewers tell no
if you take my advice to be killed by
what you don't know
but the other saying that i like so much
more is along the lines of you reap what
you [\h__\h] say
so gotta know in it so could you let go
of your soul for me sugoi daisuki i'm
not asking for much do me a favor and
die
kill him with the basement
[Music]
it's what you want
but it's the mysteries of that day in
the sun
i get right off the cuff i scream my own
thing murder with words ain't enough
that was the past me gonna take a first
class master v to blast me humans come
at me i'm massive stick actually huh
whatever that means yes whatever that
means a little closer
if you take my advice you'll be cute by
what you don't know
but inside i'm kind of nervous and i
don't know what the word is for the
other side of the cat [\h__\h] it say so
setting i'll do what i'm supposed to do
i'll get close to you don't mind that's
a book it's a rock with you
[Music]
is
to exterminate
[Music]
[Applause]
i was so improvised normally i would
have needed to practice that
yeah it kind of just came out of nowhere
[Applause]
that was fun with that being said
that was your encoder so no more that's
all folks we're done no more
we'll give you a little takamoni auf
wiedersehen yeah
of eater zane thank you guys for
watching tomorrow i have
by the way another concert at the same
time
wow i got this other you know side side
unit
going on besides i'm sorry that that's
okay
it makes you happy dog yeah it's like
two orange girls so we're old ends or
friends
yeah nice huh orange friends yeah orange
friends orange all right so if you guys
interested in that uh it will also be on
my channel i'll put up the reservation
later
and yeah uh in german we say
[Music]
oh peter zane bye bye guys thank you so
much
i'll miss you i'll miss you too can you
see it
peace
[Music]
foreign