[Music]
do
wow
uh first of all the credits for that
opening super cool super cool fan made
opening it goes to
llc
on youtube you can watch it with the
actual proper music if you wanna and i i
didn't use the music for copyright
reasons hello everyone let's get some
introductions going
i want to enjoy this time but my english
is very very baby baby
so bring baboo
be kind
[Music]
very good english
nice to meet you thank you
next door
yay thank you
senpai for the introduction
[Music]
you know me because we're doing this on
my channel thank you thank you thank you
and we're playing worms wmd today and uh
it's funny that sumatra senpai actually
um practiced and learned the most out of
all of us beforehand and therefore
taught us a lot before the stream
[Music]
thank you
i practiced this game
she was like a teacher to us yeah no no
no
no no no no
we are friends we are just a friend no
teachers
today arrival today
we will destroy each other
each other's warmth oh yes oh no kill
worms
kid
kill everyone
so the early bird gets the worm
very smart okay
so i think we'll get right into it uh i
don't know like if i'm allowed to show
anything that shows in the lobby but
just in case that i am not i'm hiding it
so let's get ready now uh minardi
and starting
tata
the sheep and the warm we start out here
stop battle just look at that oh oh
nice
oh i'm blue i can
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
by the way chad is the audio okay i
think they're balanced
what is this position
yeah maybe maybe i want ginger jet pack
or jet pack maybe how do you do it okay
nice oh nice oh okay
uh-huh that's where you choose to be
somewhere to camp for the night
after using a jet pack can you not use a
weapon i wonder
oh you can i can't
ah so after you use a jet pack you still
can use a weapon
where am i which one
oh there we go
i wonder how you go to different uh worm
like this is something we haven't
figured out um
[Music]
no i'm not green right not blue and blue
and blue okay
this is not the sky this is
how much damage
come on come on
it's difficult to control
okay it looks a bit more dramatic than
it was
what's kara you are kara oh she and
and i'm doing camera work here oh
get the box and
i used
[Laughter]
grenade
okay
oh is that the sniper or is that a
machine gun what is that
i don't know
no damage
only to the world you have done damage
only to the world
oh is it me
yeah that's you wait
how do i want to find out how you use a
different one because now on this one
again oh well
let's destroy subaru senpai
oh
make friends breeze done
none of this you need time what do you
want to die with no no
so friends
don't attack
do you know
today rival
what
[Laughter]
reinforcement
oh so close to me again
thank you
there's a car but where would you go
like and you're stuck
did you just really say that right now i
didn't realize did you say that on
purpose
reinforcements
nowhere to go
okay
[Laughter]
how to escape how to escape good
question
yeah how to escape
well i don't know
i don't know
how do i jump
[Music]
you want to waste your shotgun on me
okay let's go let's go sure whatever
okay online
you have a second shot i think
go try try try me oh okay okay okay i
try i try i try just for you
[Laughter]
i try it's just for you
headshot boom
junior maybe
[Laughter]
okay think tank yeah i wanted to go
there
does that hurt me that that's spiky
stuff
let me go there okay okay
enter tank go
wait there's a boat too can i go
no no
[Music]
oh my god oh my god
[Applause]
[Music]
beautiful
oh
[Music]
i'm protected in my tank
okay
okay okay okay
fast i'm baby
baby
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no you you are my mom
yes do not watch the heck
has the most hp right now we have to
take her down no
blue blue blue it's a hundred blue is
practice
why
[Laughter]
you're doing
better than us great the practice round
goodbye my daughter oh no no no no no no
no no no
that's roughly
raining
so much
first vlog
are you going to bonk me big bug
bunk of infinity
yeah
[Laughter]
did i get damaged no only you i think
no wait
where is that going
ah okay okay
oh oh oh
oh okay livestock
[Music]
no no no
no no no no no
no
three three three i think for you alive
[Laughter]
oh my god
oh oh
oh dana
hello nice to see you how's it going
you sure you want to use that weapon
you're so you're so aggressive all the
time
i'm so aggressive all the time yeah
there's more calm weapons yeah i like
that one
like this one like a bat or something
you should use a brush
[Laughter]
all right all right all right all right
all right okay
i'm sorry you weren't the only one here
no it makes sense it makes perfect sense
to me that was why i chose you before
let's use a new color
[Laughter]
strong
hit well
[Laughter]
i think
battle is not good
so
[Music]
oh
double kill but double hit yes yes
rainforest reinforcements
thank you thank you my berries what
isn't that is there weapons in that
cookies
oh my turn oh
you're gonna get that crate they they
never force me i want shelter out of one
of these yes
for one second i didn't look the moment
when it happened what did you activate
i'm friend's face where am i
oh oh here okay okay
i like the sound that they make when
they're like crawling oh
yeah
i i am a kind japanese
so
wait don't shoot different weapon no
hogai bits no bookie no no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
no
fireworks right fireworks are beautiful
smiles no fun
if you used to don't spend time i
i shoot you
[Laughter]
you i destroyed
maybe
maybe amp
destroy yourself
[Music]
do we have teleport though
isn't that turned off
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
um
[Music]
yeah sometimes
because i think we're so used to having
space to jump right in
for this little piece god damn it yeah
it's like a reflex using i wanted to
jump damn it oh no oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no don't lick it no goodbye
[Laughter]
kind japanese
kind japanese bad
japanese kindness dogo
really really i have kindness mine oh
but not today
do i flip right in the door
yeah
what i'm trying i can't
just go right then maybe you can shoot
um
subaru from there no no no no no no
no
[Music]
remember
[Laughter]
you
nicer at least some damage
i wanted to go you know
but i couldn't somebody who said bye
almost
oh sky names
uh
what choice do i have
reina you can get health that is true
but i can also attack while i'm at it
how much hp do i have with that one
anyway oh sorry
okay
oh
um
i still have i still have time maybe i
go for the other one i'll go for the
other one
we should still
because this is like reyna territory
rocket w1
teddy you see you see no i was trying to
go left and then drop a grenade on
suvaru do you want to bonk me out of
existence are you sure i'm happy i have
no choice
or you can go up and throw a grenade
i thought it was aiming to the left but
it was aiming up for it
[Music]
a flamethrower i wonder
i read comment you said
to to grenade
so grenade attack you say oh no i said
should i be holding grenade right
now what yeah yeah she wanted me to get
used to that
okay okay okay
okay
oh my gosh
it's about you not that you got two at
once
okay oh they need a revenge
how do i jump okay i keep forgetting how
to jump don't use space
oh no
so revenge to survivor senpai yes yes
but how
you can use the rope or the jet coaster
jet pack
[Laughter]
you can do a warm select on the bottom
right but only two times apparently you
can choose a different one oh okay
foreign
[Music]
as well
hmm
[Music]
this red at the bottom is practically
untouchable we have to change that
true very true but i have something in
front of me and all targets in front of
me must be eliminated so
unfortunately fair enough yeah
but that's fair i have a feeling my shot
will be bad anyway let's see
oh nice shot
for that uh i can shoot one more time
but this is you can shoot it one more
time
one time
one more time i can still move though
okay come on
oh
okay okay okay
let's have fun yeah
oh
not much longer
i got my tanks
and i don't know i don't know how to use
it protein
go go go lana go go go
wait i don't know where i'm telling you
to go though oh you want to get into
that thing
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
yes
[Laughter]
oh my god finally i got to use it
okay wait that didn't mean
that didn't even hit that did it 84.
it did 84. it was 100 before okay okay
yeah yeah it was 100.
i feel targeted to buy a 200 buck
revenge coming yeah
ah you get stuck there too
[Applause]
come on somebody
come on
oh you're going the other
you want to destroy your mother it's
green yes but no no
it's green remember when your mom tried
to kill you
yeah no no no no no no no you are
dreaming dream dreams
oh my god
i want to um i want to avenge
myself but
what
[Music]
did that feel good did that feel good to
you huh no
that was um very regretful nice
oh oh here this guy here hear this name
you have to you know kiara you have to
realize who has the biggest hp all
around here
now
[Laughter]
maybe i can get two at
once i'm not sure about this maybe the
flame forever though
maybe
i don't know
uh but
isn't that kind of going into the stone
in front of me let's see let's see what
happens
oh
[Music]
is that because the water is rising and
we have already taken some so much time
water rising
yes
what is she gonna do
oh oh oh
the enemy the water it's the enemy it's
trying to eat us up yes destroy it
[Music]
pack where
oh jet pack uh
bottom bottom
first from the left oh
where do you want to go
situation i want to go here
why why why this pollution why yes why i
want to be upstairs
it's not rising that fast the water i
think
i don't need no need to be so scared and
then
you just want to be above me
[Music]
i don't know oh
[Applause]
oh what's that
okay i'm in the tank now um
time to take down super senpai
no
yes
let me get that too while i'm at it okay
let me think about it what is that song
don't get greedy
sticky donkey paste
banana bum seeds
[Music]
you are beautiful you are beautiful
thank you
[Music]
how much damage 16 only
japanese beans
dangerous
hp
yeah
make it a swift one
what
brainy it's beautiful girl yes
make it a swift death
[Music]
no why
[Laughter]
reinforcements
oh oh
oh you couldn't attack
nice nice
oh no i shouldn't be looking at my my
phone oh no that's that's super the same
but oh why
oh
[Applause]
is
oh man
um
i want it yes
all right
it's beautiful i will haunt you oh
to escape yeah
escape this point yes i know right it's
dangerous
yes very dangerous
[Applause]
much
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't get to my island it's my island
don't come here
i i
i i i want to attack
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no
maybe pick up item you can jetpack
[Applause]
wow
she's barely surviving there oh
yes
i need that no yes yes yes yes yes yes
about you oh
there are no mistakes grenades
grenade
[Applause]
yeah uh-huh uh-huh i will kill you
i'll kill you
you will kill me so mean you took away
so me all i had
i was left
and you took that away the one thing i
had
oh
i will kill you i will throw you into
the ocean you're in a dangerous position
there you know that lady you know that
young lady water is very close there
very
close edible ones
okay you can do that that doesn't hurt
me that much
i'm an attack girl i'm in a freaking
tank
uh-huh
we'll see what you do about that
what is coming
[Laughter]
you could have just gone for so many
senpai but you went for me
i see how it is
go fight
look but kiara there's more of that
health pack over there i didn't take the
only thing you had i don't care about
health packs anymore
i don't care
is that it
oh yes yes yes this is it this is a good
angle see where i'm at night's heading
yes yes
shoot
wait
wait i'm nervous
seriously
[Laughter]
am i dead
okay
[Laughter]
sorry
i
don't have a jet pack so
brain
if you don't have jetpack you know what
you can do it's so easy survivor senpai
do you want to know sorry i don't i
cannot understand english
[Music]
that's what happens to you guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
again i don't remember wasn't it
oh she finally got out of the tank
oh we got lucky there
ah
i don't think i can go up ah wait
i know
oh
or you could sink in the water
[Music]
i don't know where i can go
let me clean up
[Music]
no it's not useful you're gonna destroy
yourself
no no not useful no no no you see you
don't know how to use it see you don't
know how to control it
get out of it get out of it get out get
out of the robot shinji yeah yeah get
out of it you don't know how to use it
yeah again so go somewhere
yeah yeah yeah go somewhere else
um
wait just go get that driver
what
is that gonna kill me
that was uh brutal
don't let it get you there
i'm alive
[Music]
okay guys
okay let's see how much that does okay
hopefully a lot
no choice
go
five
one more come
[Applause]
[Music]
world of tanks
look at it no not there it's useless
over there
oh
she's in the on the high ground
oh no
you have to think about this though if
you're gonna like destroy the ground
again you might end up in the water so
be careful
that's what i was thinking actually
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
think thinking time
this is an intense battle
today it's all for dana has the high
ground
maybe if you stay how do i get out next
round the water will kill me anyway i'm
not sure how much right does it rise
i don't know i can't go
i can't go
wow
goodbye
[Music]
how do
[Laughter]
you need to fry
i don't know how a lot of these work
though that's the problem is there
anything that i can
like drop on the airstrike
oh
[Music]
how do you do
that oh my god
that was
legendary
that was legendary
so yeah so coin knuckle hair
what what
oh my god
that was intense
everybody understands already so we will
go faster maybe
uh yeah but i think i can like change
the round time and the turn time we can
do it quickly
okay
okay we're gonna get the turntab down to
30 seconds it's gonna be like a speed uh
run where we're gonna probably be really
stressed out
and round time maybe
uh 10 minutes so after 10 minutes the
water would rise or wherever we are
gonna be
okay
okay round time sure i know
okay and the map let's see if we can
find something nice
um
[Music]
time for revenge girls ah okay ready
ready ready
okay
let's see what happens this time
it's the rain forest yes
last time was so close though everyone
was good
um it was really fun people look out for
them and then
you want this
okay
there you go forest
you have home
and you start advantages
yeah
i keep forgetting how to jump
back space and oh you're already going
to get in that thing huh
is strongest
[Laughter]
can you kick someone out of a vehicle
um i don't know i gotta try oh okay so
let's start following you can try
yeah
[Music]
there's a lot of ducks over there
uh-huh
many many ducks
come on
grenades
oh my god i'm screaming so much my voice
hurts
need to teleport maybe
yeah maybe
okay
[Music]
you're gonna be struggling with jumping
for a while
no time no not no no no my god
it's gonna be unusable
oh
yeah this is hard
hard
very difficult
tactic
[Laughter]
hey
[Music]
you're hurting yourself no did you hurt
yourself with that i don't know
don't let it get you down oh you didn't
no maybe not
[Laughter]
uh i don't know is grenade strong
i could get both of them at least
[Laughter]
oh
okay
that's about a senpai
how about uh
rain and destroy don't think
yes you have no idea what
no
left
then she has other weapons
oh my god
[Music]
special that time is mystic
yeah totally mistake what else did you
want to shoot she wanted to shoot some
birds in the sky
[Applause]
tank and me best friends
so
yeah so
best friend
that
[Music]
[Laughter]
no hurt no damage
oh mistake
that doesn't hurt that much
teleport i mean at some point you gotta
get out of there oh
that must have hurt a little bit out
yeah yeah
oh damage damage if i fall down
i will try
and see where the sheep goes
go go go go go go
i want you yes yes other way no go right
go right go right yes
no no go right
no time
oh
much damage
[Music]
much
well does that kill her too
oh no no no
no
no no
no more drill balls oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
your turner being gone
oh revenge revenge is sweet
isn't it right you could take back the
boat
or
you
random
the boat is almost done for though
[Applause]
do you ride the boat why not
[Music]
rain is a silent killer
i see i see so i ran out uh
oh nice jump oh
nice jump okay
so let's see what's the best choice of
weapon here
oh i don't have time gotta be fast
[Applause]
like the okay all the homies hate the
sky oh my god
just what to kill the sky
okay
no no no not okay no bad super saiyan no
no no no no no no no
what what
no no no oh dangerous
very dangerous
so
so we have oh we are team
um
team not allowed
the team no no no
we're not freaking out yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
no problem no it looks good to me
i'm next oh no super do senpai next no
i'm next okay no
okay
no no i don't want to be there or do i
aha
[Music]
i guess i guess i'll be here okay
um
[Music]
if you destroy the boat nobody will ever
be able to use it which is you know if
you can't use it nobody can right
only three minutes on the clock oh my
god
okay
water is coming soon
uh the tree would be a very safe area up
there huh
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
she's
gonna do something to destroy us
probably as she always does
you're very far away from everyone else
though
oh yeah try the button
why
you try
come on
no
[Music]
oh she didn't want to try the buttons
oh there's also a button there you want
to try the button
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no are you sure
are you sure
wait i don't want to land on the button
okay yeah try buttons
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
tank is
do you not want to try to use the thing
i use oh jeff yeah
that's good that's good though yeah
i need healing go do you wanna go
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wait what color
am i again blue
[Applause]
i'll take you down
fly faster
fly faster the clock is ticking
we need to gather what we can while
they're in season
oh
[Music]
you are in a dangerous place my lady you
have five hp left
there
even if you kill me i only lose five hp
no big deal but you're losing a fighter
who could heal himself and be strong and
do that stuff you know
not a very good choice but okay maybe
i'll i'll take care of something else
now
kyra rainey
that's a five so
at first you must kill
[Music]
really is that so if you
kill me you waste a turn for five hp
let me clean up yeah
[Music]
yes
happy
senpai we are friend
oh yeah
but now we have enemies
[Music]
um
oh
nice
okay all according to cake okay
[Applause]
i received something
they said i received something
interesting wait it's beautiful i know
we haven't even done anything to it yet
uh okay okay time no time we have
basically no time oh no no no no no no
oh my god
whatever oh okay
uh you happy
[Music]
no no
how much how much
all the water is getting closer
yeah
oh my gosh i was super understand bye oh
survivor senpai
oh
no no no no no it's like
[Music]
one of these
[Laughter]
go somewhere else okay that's fine with
me
it's my choice raina i knew you were
that smart i always knew it
okay oh oh very smart good choice good
choice uh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh god i don't know what to do i don't
know what to do
well
okay
i gotta go somewhere else as well um
yeah i think that's the great
you can save and you don't have much
experience of a jet pack though
okay
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
your turn
yeah maybe light one
top five botan
okay
oh no no no
oh
oh oh oh
[Music]
oh yes
yeah what are you doing what are you
doing teleport
no oh
you're running you're running away
i see happy accidents yeah that's dead
that airstrike could be used for some 55
hp or something just saying
i don't want to be next i don't know
what to do
[Music]
is easy
i don't know what i think
what is this
i don't know i don't know
i'm gonna shoot down
so exactly
[Laughter]
i see that's now i know how that works
okay oh no no no no no
teleport where attack people on the
ground
take your time this is the showdown
um
get the supplies while you can
those supplies are far away dude
send them closer so far
i just need to get my bed
oh my
okay
[Music]
no no no no no nope nope no no no no no
no
[Music]
come on revenge revenge
okay revenge please
[Music]
they get it
yes yes yes yes
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
23 hp versus four hp that's why you're
going
to be what's gonna happen
what's gonna happen
hmm no ohayo was i
i'm sweating for you girls but
no no no no no no
that was a mistake no attack me stick
won the
[Applause]
[Music]
what ah
is this a time to be
trying out new things
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
wow
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
um
that
i've said that in the practice rounds
superstar was basically teaching us how
to play the game and she knew so much
about it and now
now she's the one who didn't even win
once rip
freeze that was so much fun
that was fun
my voice is like so coarse now
no don't casa casa
yeah
i need i want to win
[Laughter]
my mom
[Music]
finally was uh realized into a
collaboration that took us very long but
finally here it is i'm i'm i hope
everyone had fun and uh let's get some
ending greetings from everyone swear to
senpai
why me why me
i learned english class
today's english from subaru senpai was
very good very good thank you
see you later
[Music]
uh i i love this time
i hope
next time yes
and
i
need
next time i
i must win yes thank you
[Music]
please give us your feelings about
today's fight
it was fun it was my first ever worms
experience and
you know the early bird gets the war but
you gotta say thank you
for letting me play
hollywood's
ducking together strong thank you see
you later
thank you
[Music]
yeah i'm really glad actually it was the
first time for both super decent and
lena and i think super simple hasn't
even heard of the game beforehand so
thank you for trying
um
overseas but not very well known in
japan but she really enjoyed it i'm
happy to hear that so thank you guys for
watching let's have another uh horritory
collab sometime and yeah in english uh
we say
see you later hello birds right
yuka okay okay okay see you right now
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
bye
[Music]
do
you
[Music]