[Music]
hey
kick baby
oh 800
we did it thankfully before the stream
we did it before the stream thank you
guys very much we reached it
but i knew it would it should work out
just looking at the statistics
i wasn't i wasn't that worried
although yesterday i was i was sweating
a little bit about it i was like
what if we don't reach it but no just
looking at statistics it would only make
sense that we would reach it
yay thank you guys so much we did it
800k oh dear
oh my god that's that's a lot that's
very very very much i
i am goddammit
that's so much guys thank you very much
every single one of you who subscribed
thank you i really really
appreciate that uh effort
wait sorry i just woke up i i don't know
english
i appreciate the support i think
[Laughter]
uh uh cannot speak english
i literally like half an hour i woke up
from my slumber and i was basically
i was dreaming about being late for this
stream
i was like this was so weird i was i was
about to stream
but i was late and i was gonna stream
somewhere else than i usually do
for some reason i think in some hotel or
something like that
and i was trying to set it up i was late
to set it up anyway when
i needed i needed some stuff and for
some reason my my
my mama and my sister was also there but
they couldn't really help me they were
all hella slow i i told them
i need to stream now and they were like
[Laughter]
oh and then i was then i was freaking
late and i was trying to set up my game
capture for some reason even though
we're not using it today
i don't know we need dreaming about
being late
is weird
oh don't worry guys i am awake
everything is good i never
you guys know i i'm never i never
oversleep i never miss my alarms like
even when i don't sleep much i only need
one alarm if i really need to get up for
work or something
i always get up when it's time um oh my
god drink some water
never i mean when there is nothing to do
then i like to sleep as long as possible
but if there's work then gotta wake up
when i gotta wake up doesn't matter if
i've slept uh
ten hours or four or four hours doesn't
matter
i'm proud of that i only need one alarm
you know what sucks being on vacation
with someone i'm not talking about
talking about other other experiences in
the past because kelly wasn't like that
but i hate it when you're like somewhere
or sleeping over
with someone and then that person needs
like
50 alarms to get up so they have 50
alarms
in advance like one hour before you
actually have to get up or even earlier
than that
while you just need an alarm at the
exact time when you have to get up
so the problem is i can't sleep when
the other person has their freaking
alarms going on
every five minutes for one hour before
we actually have to get up
what the frick can't sleep
dude it does those kind of people
they just don't know they don't even
think about it
they just they just uh have their alarms
go off and then
they ignore them for like five minutes
even though they could freaking just
push the snooze button at least do me
that favor
oh but no no no no no when i wake up and
i'm like
shut up turn the freaking alarm off
they're like i'm just gonna i'm just
gonna let it run and terrorize everyone
in this room for another five minutes
and then they decide then they finally
decide to turn it off
but then three minutes later the next
one goes off
and the whole thing repeats itself for
one freaking hour
okay these kind of people yo
unbelievable oh my god sorry i went
talking about that kind of triggered
something in me i'm really angry now
really angry oh my god okay let's we got
to check out the chocolates because
um oh my god okay so listen we want to
celebrate the 800k
right now but we also want to look at
the chocolates i saved um
hundreds 160 submissions
but yesterday i did that yesterday took
me like an hour to save
every single submission like screen
capture it with the text
that they submitted and the chocolate
uh it's it it was a lot of work
yesterday and i went i i
uh yesterday evening i went all up to
the point where
there were no more no no whoa
but overnight
even more came in
[Music]
so maybe we can um
check the rest of the submissions uh
you know in another stream eventually
cool because i feel like overnight i
checked uh before the stream it
it seemed like it was like at least
another hundred
and i didn't have time to save all of
those unfortunately but we will check
everything we got now so let's freaking
go
and we will end the stream in
49 minutes from now so that we can
quickly
run over to the song premiere which is
pinned in the comments right now
open the link and and and and and be in
there being the waiting room
everyone so that everyone is ready just
in time
for
[Music]
okay hello hello here i am okay
well let's let's check out the 160 uh
chocolates that i have saved
uh we're gonna go for them probably uh
quickly um look at this one
that's the first one that's the first
submission overall so
that that person was very quick
what did this person do chocolate
truffles
oopsie sorry i wanted to take a closer
look
[Music]
well a for effort
and i would say we give him a rating and
we only have one rating guys as you know
10 out of 10 is the rating unfortunately
channel 10 for you thank you for
participating
we only have one rating guys
now you got some brownies those actually
look pretty good
a lot of people made brownies uh cough
made some brownies yeah they they look
yummy and this person looks like they
have some experience with making
brownies
i have no breakfast i would love to have
those for breakfast right now
um 10 out of 10. i hope we're going at a
good speed
because we got 160 and we got like uh 40
more minutes to go
here another a couple of brownies i
think
oh wait that's the same person oh yeah
oh yeah okay this is this person
first submitted those then the brownies
and then they
put them together now that's a ten out
of ten
brownies with truffles on top speed
speed reveal speech chocolate review oh
by the way
i wrote it's a contest but there's
nothing you can win
except my respect
there are while i was looking for the
submissions yesterday
there were some people who lost my
respect
completely and i don't know if they will
ever regain my respect
but if you made good chocolate then you
might
gain my respect even more yes
but we will go through them i was i i
i saved pretty much everything
uh except for a few work in progress
pictures
and uh a few people who
literally just made chocolate milk
and and i also didn't save uh people who
bought their
who just presented chocolate that they
didn't make it had to be self-made
yes first sneeze after 800k
800 cases
okay okay so 10 and understand for this
person
let's look at this one that's kind of
small why is it so small
i introduced a heart challenger charcoal
a chocolate mint cake
was melted after i ate frosting
a layer of shaved lint milk choc milk
chocolate some powdered sugar for decor
i hate after eat chocolate i hate it
but i got the only rating i have is 10
out of 10
so 10 out of 10 for you tavalori
congratulations uh but i mean you
definitely
uh put some work into it
it looks nice it looks uh pretty well
made but why the hell did you have to
put after a chocolate in there oh my
freaking god
thank you for participating next one wow
wow eh please help yourself to my uh
tiramisu-flavored log cake
oh my god m3 with a spiced
milk chocolate ganache bark for real
we have assorted nuts and some mint
what's what's up with everyone
with mint but okay that's just a garnish
that's okay bon appetit
not exactly valentine's day theme but
i'm out buying ingredients for something
new
oh i want i wonder if i saved another
one of those submissions
[Music]
wow and tree that's
that's quite well made that's beautiful
did you really what the hell did how
how did you make that how did she make
the
the tree effect we got some we got some
professionals participating here 10 out
of 10 thank you
next door
that's good
yeah unfortunately um when people uh
submitted like several photos i
only got like an overview of them like
this i don't i didn't save every single
picture in big
this person tries to uh uh
write or draw me
apparently that looks cute
thank you
thank you oh
oh timothy white chocolate cake with
berries as a decor
kind of basically that's right that's
not basic people need to appreciate uh
white chocolate some more
oh and i freaking love berries oh my god
yes yes yes yes yes 10 out of 10 that
was
i i wonder what it looks like inside
i'm legit curious but i was uh yummy i
was very yummy
but actually when i look at the at the
at the you know the the table
looks like you made this at work
i don't know that looks like that looks
like some counter from
some actual kitchen uh some professional
kitchen
you know what i mean i've worked in a
place like that before so i know i know
my eyes won't deceive me
but it's okay it's okay the
professionals need to you know get some
love too and
you need to vent their creations as well
somewhere
[Laughter]
all right thank you 10 out of 10 for you
everyone else agrees yes because that's
the only the only rating we have
oh someone made
such a tortoise first ride making some
of the traditional
australian
that's a yes australian famous cake
[Music]
more of a frosting than a glaze and
after putting
some of the whipped cream on i realized
it was supposed to go inside
yeah oh but i'm glad you noticed i mean
that's fine it's fine you can put it on
top that's not such a big issue
good job i see in the middle you put the
the jam which is exactly what it's
supposed to be
it's a chocolate cake with a chocolate
glazing
but it's not any kind of chocolate the
the chocolate has a specific
chocolate taste um that everyone in
australia gets right but in other
countries
they often don't get it right but
one more important thing to sacrate
is to put apricot jam in the middle
um
that's really that looks really yummy
good job i want a piece of that right
now
damn that looks really yummy thank you
thank you
now this
i didn't want to save this this was the
only
submission of this client that i saved
because afterwards i was just like you
guys are just [\h__\h] around with me now
you lost my respect
and we can submit anything as long as
it's juggled yes here's my submission a
cup of middle
or milo i don't even know what that is
we don't use that in australia
i made it the australian way i don't
know if you mean by putting the the milk
first and then yeah oh my god that's
just such a stretchy statue scandalous
what the heck
if you think it's too much meal powder
well it's called meal and not a milk
uh but honestly i think that's probably
about the right amount
of powder and
you should have put the powder first
though i hope gonna stop
okay no no we don't give him a rating no
no no no
next time and some lame stuff
participated with some really yummy
looking uh chocolate cookies
70 dark chocolate cookies there would
have been 86 of them but i ate one
already as is my right as the bacon
no problem that is totally
understandable
yummy those look good holy [\h__\h] you made
so many too that's a huge batch
did you did you eat all of them
do you live alone are you planning on
eating all of those alone
those look good a lot of people make
cookies yeah and those look pretty
damn good i genuinely prefer um
milk chocolate but when it comes to
chocolate cookies like these
like american style cookies then uh dark
chocolate
at least mixed in to a certain amount is
a must
i must say yeah yeah i think everyone
agrees with me
yes yes next one thank you 10 out of the
10 by the way
thank you all right now look at this
what the hell
wow oh my god
what this this this
this honestly is like 100 percent my
taste because i love i freaking love
berries and i love cakes and i love
chocolate
this has everything that i love
ice cream
100 out of 10 but honest honestly
unfortunately i can only give you a 10
out of 10.
looks like a hat yeah it does a little
bit look like a hat
yummy thank you that's amazing
i think this person participated more
than once so we might see another one of
their creations later on
seems like a pro maybe not maybe some
people
even when they're not a professional
they really got some damn good baking
skills it's
quite amazing oh leaked footage of a new
hat for me
oh why did you guys not
say it louder than me
goddammit okay okay okay but what do i
put here okay you know what i'm gonna
put my
my song logo oh it's huge oh it's huge
oh it's huge let me put that hi
challenger logo right here
perfect why did you guys not tell me
earlier or louder
because if only one person says it i
won't notice
we didn't notice oh my god a lot of
people didn't notice what this
usually you guys notice oh my god this
time you didn't notice he was just too
focused on the chocolate huh
oh my god i am not playing minecraft
today
but we are checking out chocolate even
better
10 out of 10 next one next chocolate
oh cupcakes yummy
with pink frosting and one is even like
a heart
fiji taco oh the tacos are very um
already very talented because uh uh ina
ina had a baking contest right
a while ago when was that what wasn't
that like
already like one two three months ago
the taco dances have some experience of
baking because they already were forced
by their
empress to bake a [\h__\h] ton of
stuff
on
same thing i couldn't think of the other
word
same thing same thing same thing
i just woke up okay i'm tired
for these cupcakes they look yummy
oh next one here we got some
appreciation for janma
ah
[Music]
totally normal milk chocolate dipped
drizzled
dark chocolate chunk biscotti wait so i
wonder if the biscotti is not self-made
and the only thing i did was just
pouring
chocolate over it i'll give you the
benefit of the doubt and say that you
made the biscotti yourself as well
although the more i think of it i doubt
it because if you would make something
yourself why would you choose to make
biscotti for this contest
but but the appreciation for genma is uh
very welcome so you get a 10 of the 10
hyde man thank you nankishan biscotti
shamed
i mean biscottis are yummy but still
all right uh okay i think speed wise we
might
even though i'm going for them quite
quickly it might still be too slow so
let's let's let's
let's try our best here brownies for me
where can i get them they look yummy
well oh they got some some fat if i see
correctly they got some fat chocolate
chunks in there too that melted uh
max thank you that looks yummy
good job ten out of ten speed run condos
hell yeah
my first attempt of making brownies for
ten two still sad up the results
yeah that um
you you tried
that looks like
i know it looks like mashed
potatoes with chocolate
mixed in it
10 out of 10 for the effort though thank
you for participating
he tried he tried oh what is this
neither or not a certain nina nine
probably
and i wanted to highlight the orange and
pink combination to root for a certain
something but my color mixing
fundamentals is
[\h__\h] i'm sorry i tell you i'll see
myself to usually no this looks amazing
what is that though is that like
is that is inside
i'm not sure what this is it looks so
yummy but
what is it what is it what is it
it reminds me of a certain australian
dessert
uh which is that like um
we have like machi like noodle attack
noodle and so on
it's basically canadians with inside
some fruit and
covered in in in like crumbles
i mean this seems similar it looks very
yummy
thank you 10 out of 10.
i made some iced brownies [\h__\h] yellow
contest cm randy
turned out kind of curse looking but it
was fun nonetheless yeah
um the amer one
looks cursed
[Music]
i think mine actually looks the best you
did you did the best job of
by the way renamed my we named this
little buddy
this one we named him recently his name
is now colonel colonel
but watch out for the for the writing
it's a c-o-l-o-n-e-l
k-e-r-n-e-l yes
colonel kernel you did a good job on
kernel colonel
and actually this one um def center
looks great too
but these ones
[Laughter]
look a little bit i don't know smashed
maybe they all just i mean they played
smash brothers together so they probably
still smashed from that day
imma just ground pounding them too hard
and ground pounded herself as well
this is what i made in class when i
still was learning
oh this is not new i should i should
have disqualified you
i was some people put uh
submitted stuff that they made in the
past which is not exactly what that was
what i wanted i wanted you to guys make
to to make new things but it's okay oh
it definitely looks extremely yummy holy
[\h__\h]
i want that i want i want i want that
one
oh the one with the raspberries mmm
yum yum yum yum yum
[Music]
[Laughter]
you happy valentine's day happy
valentine's day to you too
for me it's already valentine's day i
don't know about you guys but
today is valentine's day for me in my
time zone
which is why i'm releasing heart
challenger today because it is
valentine's themed
everyone you should you should not miss
it
it's it's quite the adorable cute happy
song so you definitely shouldn't miss it
anyway
wish the new song would reach 1 million
very soon oh i hope so tell
i believe it would reach it as soon as
possible like you believed in me
oh here's some brownie thank you looks
yummy
i actually i person many of you guys
made brownies i feel like everyone knows
how to make brownies but i never made
brownies myself
the only thing i made is like um like
brownies in the cup you know the ones
that you can make
in in a in the microwave
gasp she's never made fries before wow
what yeah
i would probably be and it seems like
pretty easy thing to do
i made the ones in the microwave i did
that quite a few times
that was that was quite quite yummy yeah
mug cake
i guess that's not a brownie here but
close enough it's close enough
who out here has made mug cake before
raise your hands neander
of course of course that's probably the
first
baking that anyone ever does is a mug
cake
it's so easy so why not yeah
i know cakey
chocolatey hope you like it
i always love you thank you
wow that looks uh pretty damn good the
shape is perfect
good job 10 out of 10 for that one
nice now we got some
classic cookies well here goes nothing
no they look yummy they look um
kind of thin and the shape of some of
them is questionable
this this one almost looks like you bit
something off but i think you didn't
just looks like that it was born this
way
it was born this way we don't judge it
you know
cookies cookies sometimes look ugly
that's okay
no they look pretty yummy 10 of the 10
would eat yes thank you thing
oh no this one you didn't exactly bake
but that's okay
i'm not good at baking so i made some
mochi with peanut powder and melted
chocolate
it's the peanut powder dish stuff over
here and this is just melted chocolate
and then this doesn't even look like
this doesn't even look like mochi it
just looks like
some kind of ice cream personally i
prefer
brown sugar syrup to melt with chocolate
i don't know what i think about this
sauce
suss but i give you the benefit of the
doubt and i give you a 10 out of 10.
thank you pipe oh that's how adorable
pipe you did much better with this one
what the hell
i tried to make a frog with surplus
ingredients and nutella
oh my god that looks so double that
looks like that melted frog i don't know
i feel like i've seen this frog before
it looks so adorable i love it the way
it's shaped it looks like
so soft and like i love the cheeks
oh my god it's it's just so adorable
it's so cute
i feel like i've seen that frog before
in some video
you guys you guys don't don't don't
doesn't this frog look familiar to you
guys
it looks so cute and froggy
thank you at the wednesday frog
wednesday frog
i don't know what the wednesday frog is
hey does that come up if you
if you look on youtube hey let me look
it up
wednesday frog is that the one i'm
thinking of wednesday
frog oh yeah
oh yeah it really looks like that
oh my god oh my god it looks like the
wet day frog why is that the wednesday
frog
oh my god so um
it really do be looking like that though
i wonder if that person made it on
purpose it's like if yes then you nailed
it
damn 10 out of 10. one of one of the
best entries because i have frogs
so yeah
[Music]
yes okay celery
celery made and what is that so i
basically made something it's chocolate
with a hint of coconut
but inside it has marshmallow and
whipped cream on top with some caramel
and the sprinkles are orange and pink
for takamuri i made this before
hey 10 out of 10 for the creativity i
like it it's pretty cute and you added
some color
because chocolate after seeing a million
of chocolate
submissions everything was so so you
know
poop brown that i was feeling kind of
sick
at the end of saving all these
submissions
almost as if as if i would have eaten
all of them but adding some colors in
here really helps me thank you thank you
10 out of 10.
okay shrimp let's give you a chance the
chalky kind of crunchy bar me and my
younger sister
uh mate it ain't much but it's honest
work i guess
looking back i we should have added more
cookie crumbs and chrome plate
so i guess what you did is you made the
thing that i did
but
you mixed it and then put that
mixed thing into the free into the
freezer
without shaving it so what you ended up
with
is just a crunchy brick
i'll give you a guillotine sample
you should have shaped it because that's
just a brick wait
wait literally in the background is a
brick as well
the background is a brick oh my god is
that a troll
is this person trolling me like any
linga
lingard isn't it uh
oh my god i give you a i give you a 10
out of 10
just this one so i'll give it to you
just this once
[Music]
zaggy patrick thank you the first time i
made brownies oh
the first time they look great for your
first time not even for your first time
i wouldn't know it was your first time
nicer 10 out of 10 maybe i should try
making brownies too if it's that easy
nice one uh
so sorry i um i've been to brazil before
and i've heard about this before but
when i first looked at this i was like
ew but this
is a brazilian brigadeiro
thank you coyo claire it looks like a
chocolate soup
it's simple to be done just condensed
milk butter and chocolate powder
all together in a pot and mixing it up
with a spoon while boiling yeah
apparently that's really a thing in
brazil
um i've heard about that before because
when i visited brazil before i really
wanted to try
it because i wanted to try anything
that's like um
special in brazil and
i i didn't manage to get it anywhere
but i'm brazilian and that doesn't look
like brigadeiro really
really any more brazilians out there who
can judge this
one
[Laughter]
rattle what is that
well it's right so i gave you a 10 out
of 10 for trying
oh my god it somehow looks like i don't
know uncle
uncle soup red bean soup or something i
don't know
ah thank you
next one armando kalita
prank i may have burned it but the
frosting makes it look oh frosting makes
everything better yeah
i don't know what that is is that a
brownie with some chocolate frosting
it's pretty flat it's pretty flat
but looks like it's yummy looks very
chocolatey
i like it i would i would give it a try
hopefully
you didn't get sick from eating it
because you burned it
ah danke said lucia cake you pet on
brownie
don't don't don't mention yourself
now this is adorable i love this one
alvey's fondant uh on reese's peanut
butter cup
there's a ferrero rocher in the big
chick
oh i'm in phoenix happy valentine's day
oh you made you met colonel colonel
into like a really adorable cookie even
there's like two different ones that's
that that this one is like it's bigger
and this one is smaller
[Music]
good job on this one
i wouldn't want to eat that one because
it just looks too cute this is one of
the i must say this is one of the
winners
elvis congratulations
everyone give this man or woman a round
of applause
for this cutie cutie colonel colonel
good job
yummy it's so cute kawaii
nice one next doll
oh my god hey wait it's already oh my
god only
it's only 18 minutes left and i'm oh my
god okay let's go quick
okay okay speed run speed run yeah i
don't need you
okay thank you for the effort ten out of
ten i love sarah
and uh i i like the puns you made
unfortunately it got caught after but
everyone check it out it's chiara mel
vanilla watson
and something was there nice 10 out of
10.
oh my god and with some i don't know
extra cups with the leftover chocolate i
suppose
that was yummy dankeshan 10 out of 10.
and look me and my mom are baking so we
make
baked goods oh nice so we got some
professionals out there we have a lot of
artists upcoming so this is
you so you have to make this for wig but
you put this as an entry anyway well
that's kind of
yes 10 of the 10 though thank you
good job actually this one is much
bigger like when you open the picture it
was much bigger it goes like a
way down oh it looks really really fancy
danger
100 10 out of 10 would spin front again
anything with chocolate well how about
mo enchiladas
what oh yeah
[Applause]
this is this was when i still had hope
and i still wanted to give people a
chance
i didn't want to save this i didn't want
to show you guys this but
this was when i still gave people a
chance and the benefit of the doubt
chicken wrapped in fried tortillas
covered in the chocolatey
molsa what the [\h__\h] is a mole sauce
and top of says oh god ew disgusting
truffles made by me pretty sweet huh
they look yummy they look good they have
a good shape and it's very sparkly all
around i like it while my yummy would
eat 10 out of 10.
nice yes and frog
and frog cake oh my god love it
absolutely cute i love the color
uh it's not it's not only brown i love
it
uh i wonder what it tastes like i want
to eat this one
okay you're one of the winners you are
one of the winners
abby baka congratulations to ten
applause brownies
do we have brownies again that looks
like brownies
thank you the candy toppers are pretty
adorable thank you
10 out of 10 collin duncan
and this one huh okay
lemon pudding that's that's okay it
looks like a soup but it's apparently
pudding
put in let's see this here top of
chocolate chip so that was uh the only
chocolate thing about this is the
chopped chocolate chips okay i'll i'll
give that to you that's okay that's okay
because pudding lemon pudding i like the
idea of lemon pudding thank you
10.
oreo chocolate cheesecake oh i've heard
that that one was quite easy to make
pikachu
nice one oreo cheese cakey
yummy would eat 10 out of 10 yes
now men's got some chocolate chip
cookies
but they are so thin now those are
those are really thin they look like
they look like potato chips but like as
famous potato chips
[Laughter]
[Music]
same here those look even thinner
oh soy
[Music]
soy that's really really thin
that's really thin and they could have
probably needed a bit more time
in the oven maybe possibly but still it
looks yummy anyway dangerous in
monochroming
10 of the 10.
[Laughter]
oh my japanese people
are are coming here with the talented
submissions oh dear lord
they are putting an effort in here
in
apparently everything except the stick
is made out of chocolate i saw even
she uh she attached a video of making
this
uh below the tweet and it looks really
really nice
jose this is one of the winners 10 out
of 10.
kachikaty katsugumi
it's so cute they implemented though the
heart challenger artwork thank you so
much
10 out of 10 applause everyone oh god 13
minutes left
uh okay uh we got some brownie cake or
something like that looks yummy actually
i have to say it looks scarf it looks
very yummy
i like the texture of it i know that
that's yummy i like
i know it doesn't look like really like
well made but that kind of texture is
guaranteed to be yummy it's a
i like that kind of chocolate cake yummy
10 out of 10.
and made some cupcakes with pink vanilla
frosting on piped melted
chocolate onto them and pipe melted
chocolate
cupcakes i also never made cupcakes
except that you know that
mug cake i want to learn how to make
cupcakes i want to try making them
it should be really easy right
you know what i loved in school when
people made pot when when
people made cupcakes and brought them
for everyone no those are those are the
real friends the people who make
cupcakes and bring them to school
we got some more muffins chocolate
muffins with lemon frosting and
i like the lemon frosting that's pretty
rare
i like it i like lemon in general oh
yummy oyster
[Music]
[Applause]
employees know this baby this is our
favorite baby in the world this is uh
this baby is being raised
as an employee
[Music]
baby this my baby is so cute sandra is
so cute
xander if you guys haven't seen it
there's videos of xander
um reacting to my stream and uh
like laughing like while watching my
stream it's really adorable
thank you but uh
the mother apparently made these it was
a my wife took the reins with this one
and made salt caramel chocolate vegan
cookies
oh well i wonder like
since he's holding it here and like
looking really happy he must have been
thinking that he can have a taste
but then he took it away from him
because he's a baby i wonder
how long the tantrum was that he throw
after you taking it away from him
he must have really thrown attention
after that i can literally imagine
he must have been really really mad that
you like he put it in front of him like
that
tease him and then just take it away
yeah okay we got 15 more minutes i know
10 more minutes yummy yummy
okay uh i want to put in here as many as
possible chocolate crinkles
i don't know what crinkles are you guys
going to tell me but it looks uh
looks like cookie is close enough
oh by the way xander is one of the
winners obviously
can't make sand or not one of the
winners uh
mama brownie that turned out to be more
like cake i
like how you put some like huge chunks
of chocolate in here
[Applause]
[Music]
uh beans cochueto that sounds like i
don't know something
i don't know spanish or mexican or
brazilian again
neat looks yummy thank you chan
whoa this one looks really good because
they use some kind of uh
thingy oh and i love chocolate covered
strawberries oh
what is that what is that oh wait the
hammer is that
so you can break the chocolate oh that's
so cool you added the hammer i like the
hammer the hammer is adorable
oh this this uh this person already had
a submission in the beginning i made hot
chocolate with chocolate covered
strawberries when you break the heart
there's more chocolate inside
oh i like that thank you now this is
someone that
this is something that i would give to
someone as a
as a valentine's day chocolate present
have you guys seen those kind of
desserts that you break
in in restaurants that you break with a
hammer or you melt it with some hot
chocolate and then
and then you know something gets
revealed inside i love that kind of
stuff i've never had that before i'm
gonna try it
next up oh that's something that i made
pretty much
but with uh no pretty much what i made
yeah
good job hyrule thank you thank you for
following my tutorial i suppose
i got some uh cookies with dark
chocolate drizzle
yummy cecila 10 out of 10.
uh this one i had to do like that
because uh in the preview in the small
preview it basically showed nothing
but hey look he used some
pretty printed forms i think
nice definitely put some effort into
that duncan
yummy custom molds nice
10 out of 10. oh there we go we got some
lava cake
mmm danke shin would eat
i would eat that for breakfast right now
danke shang
now we got brownie cake covered in
melted chocolate and lined with
chocolate syrup
yummy hey we got some dead beets going
on here
thank you looks yummy 10 out of 10.
whoa now what do we have here valentine
ice cream it's
is that an ice cream chocolate scoop no
that's a chocolate truffle accompanied
by some strawberries full of love
i mean that's not much chocolate here
but more like it's a lot of
a lot of ice cream and uh strawberries
but i love strawberries so that's okay
10 out of 10.
now we got oh my god the cat the cat
the cat is looking so cute towel
truffles apparently because of my atomia
rhizocto playthrough because howl is uh
looking much much better in that game
thank you shannon mr cat speaks thank
you
i love the cat it looks so fluffy with a
pet chocolate covered strawberries so
i was i was so close to not saving that
because
yeah you just you just poured chocolate
over some strawberries but i do
love chocolate covered strawberries so
so yeah you get
you get you got to participate you gotta
next time more effort okay
[Applause]
ooh someone uh again use some kind of
moves i like that what is that mates two
red velvet cupcakes who wants the other
one for valentine's
gosh guys oh my gosh only 75
but i mean there's a three minute
countdown right until the video actually
begins so yeah
10 out of 10. so that's still 10 minutes
i decided to make blondies because my
mom would always make them when they're
delicious but just making them
i just would be boring so i upgraded
them i like to imagine the two big cats
are cali
we have all the kittens they've adopted
oh that's a cute idea
that looks yummy i didn't know you
called that blondies
why why do you call those blondies i
wonder is it just a normal like uh
cake stuff with chocolate cookie
chocolate chips
yummy
chocolate ice cream in the shape of an
ice cube
meal powder topping well you tried
attempt at making nama chocolate did not
turn out well donuts right it was not
turned on well looks good
and that that that shape kind of went
out of shape but
nice one ten out of ten and these ones
oh apparently they put they made this
similar thing that i made but they put
um
honey in there as well mmm nice one
donkey shot another
you're good like other people really
need to step up their uh their
um uh presentation game but this one is
oh good you try yeah ten out of ten
five minutes oh my god i'm at 62 out of
160 plus
damn it oh my god okay okay speed run so
we got these cupcakes cute 10 out of 10.
we got this uh what is that oreo bon
bons cute 10 out of 10.
uh this person tried to apparently this
is chocolate
like but i don't know what but i don't
know what that's supposed to be but cute
duncan 10 out of 10.
chocolate truffles 10 out of 10.
chocolate cookies
[Music]
and phoenix shaped white chocolate 10
out of 10.
uh oh my god yeah this this
chocolate and this person makes
chocolate for a living and has been
making
okay this is basically disqualified
because you didn't make it for the
stream but still i wanted to
show everyone how good you are
red velvet cupcakes yummy 10 out of 10.
by the way everyone we have a super chat
reading uh
right after the the music video premiere
so we can
look at a little bit more and more uh
there
maybe but yeah thank you so everyone and
and be sure to be at the super chat
reading as well
i want to thank everyone properly for
their support yes yes
and brownies don't concentrate ten
cookies another ten
um
cake thank you so much for actually
making something edible
cute cookie scented again
what is that what is that
oh no oreo brown is good looking 10 on
the 10.
oh yes this one oh my god please look at
that oh my god
flavors mango tazin uh
what is that passion fruit what
i can't read those oh my god strawberry
balsamic passion fruit black scissors
oh my god apple cider caramel oh my god
look at that holy [\h__\h] good job nice one
love it that gets intense 10 10 10 out
of 10 you're one of the winners because
those are so aesthetic
oh my god you are also one of the
winners because those are adorable
chocolate chick muffins i love them
kawaii 10 out of 10.
and that's when i legit started feeling
sick
i legit started feeling sick here that
looked like a tongue to me
i don't oh my ew i even had to reply to
that because that was just
this oh
that that looks something that i think
they sell this kind of stuff uh like
you tried at least magic you you at
least
tried a second time with something that
you can actually eat it's like grease
puffs right
corn puffs no it must be this must be
something edible it looks like edible
okay
um brownies and yes it's another tent
thank you
what is it white chocolate millionaire
shortbread millionaires what is that
that concern 10 out of 10. it looks
interesting
raspberry jam dark chocolate ooh yummy
what is that just chocolates 10 out of
10.
fudgy brownies yummy with kfb on it 10
out of 10.
hey chocolate chip and we're going to
cook instead of the 10.
yummy and the chocolate cupcakes with
chocolate cookies with chocolate ganache
nice
colonel carano is also there 10 out of
10. he's also made up chocolate nice
take out the 10.
hey wait okay okay skip everything
oh my god that looks still so yummy
ah speed run oh yummy yummy presentation
to 10.
okay yeah we're just looking at this
like that wow
yummy yummy ah one of the winners
10 of the 10 oh yes yes yes
10 out of 10. hey wait where's where's
my wife
10 out of 10.
oh yummy oh my god 10 out of 10.
good
10 out of 10 everyone all of you this
looks yummy i took a
i was looking at it very slowly when i
was saving each picture oh my god yeah
yeah it's time to edit oh my god
hey we still have we still have a
counter did the countdown style really
is the countdown
there we go
you're of course one of the winners i
love you i i would never i mean
i i gotta say when i was writing a reply
to this tweet
i i had to keep i kept on correcting
myself because first i was like gonna be
so nerdy because i was like
i was gonna write like wow
a for effort i wanted to write something
like that but then i deleted it because
then
i i had to think it over i didn't want
to you know the one time she gets dead
i need to be nice to her so i i wrote
again something i was like oh my god
haha
why would you eat the eye but then i
deleted that again because i i
i figured i need to be really really
nice that one time she
she's nice to me i need to be nice to
her
so i was like oh my god thank you so
much for participating let's exchange
soon yeah next week
we're meeting okay bye bye guys see you
at the premiere follow the link in the
description
bye bye
oh