[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hi everybody
I'm walking out to
um
yeah I'm on treadmill mode so even if I
run to the side I'm always in the same
spot
which I think is the best way to do it
today but then
some things will look probably kind of
weird
Moon walking uh
[Music]
yeah but this is the proper moonwalk
oh forward backwards forward
backward yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
hello
hi everyone
ever since I got this full body 3D thing
I wanted to do a ring fit stream or
actually my goal was already a long time
ago
um to never do ring fit with life today
because makes no sense
even know that your Oshi is actually
really working out behind that screen
huh how how do you know you have you
can't no the only thing you see moving
is those weird physics boobies that's it
and that's not a workout
um
I got a point don't I I know yeah so my
goal was I will play it when I
eventually
have the opportunity to do it in full
body okay also chunkers is right behind
me say hi to John Grace
she's chilling on my on my chair also no
butt upgrade yet I think
uh oh does it look different I know it's
like they sent me updates and we
finalized it but I don't think they
updated like this version of me yet
I'm on the calibrate
oh yeah
oh
beautiful
I mean it's not obviously as I said it's
not gonna be Kim Kardashian but
I've only went but right now I know I
know people were doing them
[Music]
but that's just
I mean
I mean I don't know what to say about
that to be honest because I I mean
I mean it makes no sense it makes no
sense
huh
but yeah that makes no sense no no no no
no no no that makes no sense ignore that
oh
all right so
um I played uh I have this game since
like forever
uh also is there like no audio
let me try to
reopen this it's gonna be hot in the
suit bam uh
what was it called
sure
it's gonna be hot it's gonna be really
freaking hot I'm already feeling hot
that's the problem
on it
task manager son
please close
my game capture properly
where is it out there
it's it's not working
I see it only on OBS but that way I have
no sound so we would like to fix this
sometimes this issue occurs
drink a lot yes I have many water
oh I hear it you don't hear it yet
probably
yeah there you go
I think I'll look at the OBS screen
anyway though because
I want to see if anything looks weird so
now I'm I'm uh I have the the thing in
my hand you know
unfortunately I didn't really find any
item
that would you know make sense to
represent that but
we'll do and now let me show you haha
[Music]
look
the possibilities I got the
this is
[Music]
here here grab a bite ah
um
yeah the protein I got the protein and
then oh look at that oh my God
hey yo
oh okay oh ah it's on the wrong hand
this is my right hand I don't know okay
I guess I'm a shield shield or whatever
Shield memes
yes it feels weird that I want to fight
but I actually have a Minecraft sword
right here I could use that and it feels
the same
oh yeah hey
hey
oh this is heavy
yeah yeah should I be doing ring fit
today with my armor
[Music]
your fingers so
I don't know what do you want chicken
legs or armor
cool cool pose
and uh
yeah
maybe I can do something
like this
oh yeah I like this
I like this version
the vegetable worlds yeah
yeah
it looks it looks so lightweight when I
just do this
looks so lightly doesn't it
will cut you up
put your throat careful all right this
really looks like a freaking toy
toy
toy oh no
um
this looks so real though
oh man
um
good stuff good stuff
happen to have dinner yet this is my
dinner I guess this is my dessert the
pops popsicle popsicle
foreign
two-handed sword weapon and be like
[Music]
I can do all kinds of things now wait
look look look
we can do
wait
with him
it's not quite in my hands I think I
could reposition it somehow but let's
right
[Music]
come to my hand oh oh almost there
huh
there it is oh there it is
all right come here chat
tell me you you're lucky that I'm on
treadmill mode
this big big evil bunk Hammer I'm like
that Pokemon with a big hammer what was
that attack called Mega hammer or what
what was it called Ultra Giga epic Mega
Ultra hammer
Hammer
[Laughter]
160 power
oh yeah
all right relax
uh I was saying super effective it is
what does that mean what type are you
then is it super effective
I thought that wait was that wasn't that
normal wait what type was that
no wait it's Steel type wasn't it Steel
type it's still type right so then you
are fairy uh you guys are little fairies
oh my God chickens
oh
anyway it's going this is like perfect
like for dancing you know it's really
scuffed but for just doing stuff like
this
it's fine isn't it
I'm actually really surprised I started
setting up like
40 minutes before
and I was like [\h__\h] I haven't done this
in a while where do I start again but
actually I was able to set up everything
pretty simple
[Music]
so and we're gonna play some what is
that though the the stats I have never I
don't think I've played this game before
with this account or maybe maybe I did
oh but that's like I guess when I change
the name because I own this game since
before I joined and debuted in Hollow so
that means that this is old still isn't
it
the last time I used that is age can I
look at like the stats of when this was
last used
for so I just did one test which I hope
you don't see like anything that you
shouldn't be seeing because not only
people do like a setup right and then oh
my God reveal of height and weight or
whatever but I don't even know where
that would be because it's already been
done
maybe you wouldn't see it anyway oh but
you know what I have an idea I will use
it I will use that parasit account with
from my old uh roommate let me try uh
or the other one wait how do I get out
of this how does this
oh
there we go uh
no
oh my other controller is on my leg
yo since I have this since like over two
years I didn't have that leg strapped
anymore but perfect this suit comes with
a leg strap on the tie five and on the
everywhere so I just put it in there
it's not 100 safe but you know so how do
you close this again
I know that's not what I mean
it's so confusing
what how do I close this again sorry
guys
let me try to remember ah there you go
close
and then if I
call
[Music]
get it close it close Okay and then when
I open again it asks me who I want to
play it with right I didn't this time it
did the first time
oh
my
it'll be fun right
you saw my credit card number
no way why would you look at that
how dare you
ah I can select the purple in-game okay
it's confusing because yeah they're set
to sideways now so I don't know which
button is to press oh yeah okay okay
I'll put it there but then okay
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
it's in my leg
hi hi
this workout won't be very long let's
let me get rid of the hammer
let me get rid of that we're gonna do
the
chicken no the story chicken combo all
right all right
and wow
damn this game is pretty old isn't it
Preston I'm sorry hi
[Music]
this use of the product by children I am
my own adult
okay where do I change the
where do I change the
like I said I can change it in game
where
maybe after I press this oh yeah oh yeah
well yeah why don't I just do this haha
[Music]
I guess we're gonna do Adventure Mode
right because it's oh it's exciting
okay I have well more or less plenty of
room if I need more I can still make
more room
yeah bye I'm gonna embarrass myself I'm
really I really I don't lift bro I don't
do anything bro
hello hello who's talking to me
welcome to ring fit Adventure I
and enjoy bring
hell yeah are you guys working out too
finally um
there's something you absolutely must
remember whenever you're doing ring
Fitness and not overdoing it yes
even if you believe that you're doing
exercise correctly yeah but you can't
tell me can you you don't see me like I
mean I guess wait I mean I'm talking to
the game but you guys can tell me if my
poster is correct although it's not
always accurate either
um
now please allow me to introduce our
resident postal professional
presented the impeccable posted
paragonal posability
yep
tip what a lame name okay hi people
demonstrate what it means to have
problems can you also give me a massage
because it's like my back really [\h__\h]
hurts so bad like oh my God
ugh
once you've mastered proper potia
you can dive into your exercises no
you're getting even more out of them
um be sure to watch tip close to the Joy
ring Fitness hi
puppy tips movements and move the cursor
up and then select I did it okay
hi hi
that's right okay yeah I did it
just like that that's my workout for
today about see you later guys oh [\h__\h] I
can't leave him leave I can't even leave
[Music]
practice moving the cursor one more time
yeah yeah I did
totally
okay no no one did that a second time
right
if you haven't traveled you can navigate
with blah and blonde's death oh okay I
guess we should figure out your ideal
difficulty with
[Music]
oh
I need to ask you a few questions hi
a female
how old
uh
oh sorry
I am 11. until three four five six seven
you make me feel like 11. wait maybe I
shouldn't do that
sorry maybe something more realistic
um
because otherwise I mean I wouldn't mind
maybe I should do like 66
because
that's more like how my the state of my
body really is
okay how about how about
um
40.
five that's that's pretty much the state
of my body
it's 40 45 year olds right but let's
just say I'm 45. I I I don't exercise
how do I go down I don't exercise
well sometimes I dance but honestly like
I feel that's really separate
so I don't exercise please go easy on me
hahaha
that is
I don't exercise how challenging do you
want exercise to be
in a cashback to be honest I want to be
less than casual
um
but okay I think people would be mad so
let's go moderate
oh we'll provide a good workout yeah
well there you go there we go that's all
we wanted we don't want to complain
about that right
learning so much about you yeah like I'm
45 you want to hear what I've did all
these years yeah
well I've got uh
1.4 million children I was very busy
obviously my body is [\h__\h]
okay customize the money you know my
shoulder really [\h__\h] hurts so when I
do this don't don't worry
um I guess that's gonna be just a day
like uh-huh this will be the last day
I'll ever exercise so don't worry about
that
um what will your estimated weight
you have a scale
um
foreign
like something like 50 is pretty normal
right like for a girl like me
I really don't know
but I think something like 50 or like 55
is probably I mean that's that's not be
so kind to myself let's say 55. I don't
[\h__\h] know that I really don't have a
scale
I don't have a scale
but I think the last time
I scaled myself like a fish
I was definitely under 60 100 telling
you that
[Music]
um but it's been a while but I never
really gain or lose weight so you know
what can I see on it and bring for this
you'll jogging place that will probably
look a bit stupid no it's all right it
looks like I'm stuffing it's treadmill
mode but at least I don't Zoom somewhere
else if you're worried about voting
Amazon you can always look silent uh-huh
no it's a normal fan all right this is
match your strength
okay
uh cover the ringtone by measuring your
breasts and poop on I already did that
before I started to stream and it sucked
hold the Rincon in both hands while
facing forward
isn't that strange to the chicken leg
after all push it hard
this is great this is great but pulling
I'm absolutely forward holding the
ringtone in both hands
pull outward hard on the Rincon
[Music]
okay
I'm gonna throw up
[Music]
measure your light jogging okay I'm
trying to light strip is Right securely
around your left thigh imitate the
following spread your feet slightly and
stand up straight lightly jog in place
staying aware of your surroundings
okay okay
spread your feet slightly and stand up
straight
ly jog in place
see that that's where it starts to get
scuffed as long as I don't move it looks
good
don't look at my running lights are
Red's Been Cowboys the best match you're
running back get that my running style
let's not comment on my running style
last question you'll understand that we
start no
no
hello what wake up wake the [\h__\h] up
let me cookie please just try and we're
gonna have him okay please go easy on me
let's begin with Dynamics okay
yeah try to mirror tips movements
without overextending yourself
all right music start keep your posture
straight
three two one
alternate bringing your knees up to
touch the ring con
oh
make sure your back is straight
last time
all right oh good
next is the heel lift stretch ah I
remember this bring the insides of your
ankles up toward the ring con when
there's no splits like that focus on
your ankles upwards
last time all right good
thanks is the back straightening stretch
oh straighten my back yes
oh and I need space okay hi
don't let your knees move too far
forward
make sure your toes are pointed straight
ahead yeah yeah don't worry about it
stop talking to me you're confusing me
let's do one more of each
all right
spread your feet spread my feet raise
the ring con above your head
be sure to keep your lower back straight
[Music]
I haven't done this in a while as you
exhale oh my gosh
[Music]
um
great job thank you thanks
[Laughter]
first towel towel my my suit with my
towel thank you
the styles are potatoes so I whatever I
don't give a shake I don't give a [\h__\h]
all right all right come here go let's
do this I ain't got any longer
um a movie five or so music is about
five or so minutes
no
don't have time for that
all right here we go here we go I I
remember just from back in the day two
or three years ago I did this
what's Drago doing over there
oh no
perfect it's like they say you've got a
strike for the muscles hot let's go
Paris said oh I guess that's beautiful
passage is actually German head to the
place my clip of hmm hi
hi
Drago was red red radiating oh turn that
radiator off not good for my health a
purple Aura like this don't you remember
no it's a dark influencer look here
creep into the weakness in your heart
and consume you oh no please don't
I don't have a heart anymore that's why
we have to stop Drago as soon as
possible I'm sorry you got dragged into
a listeners shut up shut up shut up shut
up
let's go
I'm hungry
[Music]
I hope the timing is not so bad because
I'm watching through obviously
all right let's start with like Johnny
man all right let's go
there should be a door just a little
further along this path
oh no my my tracking is [\h__\h] up I'm
looking straight forward actually
try pressing in on me huh can I take a
break
I need to recalibrate
oh wait
why do I I don't even have to be quiet
for this why do I tend to always be
quiet when I recalibrate
up
continue I can fire an airplane remember
that and run I can find airplanes with
hell how
do you tell me how can I kill a deer oh
let's jump it what oh let's jump oh
that's whoa also fire the air blast off
to the left
[Music]
oh yeah
keep on running get the coins get that
bag
just makes me downward to recap
oh I'm getting dizzy
the orange hair it's really me I always
felt this destiny
Sprint down break it down
oh oh of course
watch your step uh-huh sorry I'm
focusing pointing me downward and
pressing it
as it looks like I broke my leg or
something
[Music]
thank you
my best year
[Music]
[Laughter]
well let's go indoors what the hell
upstairs
[Laughter]
no no no no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
I'm talking about chill
ing
oh
man get that stamina get the stamina
Chihuahua you can do it
it just started wait a minute hold me
from both sides to vacuum everything
whoa we're playing Alicia's management
now pull from both sides
come on let's run let's go guys no time
to waste come on follow me follow me
follow me
actually they look like breakfast
cereals you did it
now we're getting your exercise into
experience points with a victory point
before you feed what put your
inconsistent
[Music]
[Applause]
hey how many calories freaking calories
[\h__\h] I burned 5 million calories
from that just
[Music]
oh I've already did
I ever else I really want to leave it's
amazing
okay we have to drink water always
hydrate guys
um a popsicle
[Music]
so
the people who
um swallowed the swords
[Music]
can't do it
my parasites yes what is that why it
looks magical mythical
I'm talking to you very side
I feel pound set me free
ow that's
why do I look like oh oh Dutch
wow
the whole world could be trouble why is
she squatting
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
I dropped it
oh it's not scary no no
I got swords
[Music]
oh well that word I didn't think you
would fall for me
all right where's the ring I'm not here
[\h__\h] hear everything we're doing about
driving no no
[Music]
no no
and that's just to get started General
teacher three or four things once my
power has come
oh so many things
oh I took a screenshot but that's what
happened with my butt
[Music]
or video I wanna I thought oh
doing it in the back is kind of
difficult
I'm pushing I'm pushing
you're gone
oh Drago wait
guess we're safe now yeah
oh sorry if I surprised you I got this
voicing unlike Pokemon that was Drago
he's a dragon who radiates a dangerous
dark influence
so much power why we got power too
oh
my name is ring by the way what a
beautiful name ring maybe let me try to
put my finger for you are we married now
but it's a really big ring
he raggles dark influence has a horrible
effect on anything it touches I can fit
my head through it now I have it on my
on my shoulders
if he were to release it in all its
power his influence
can I fit through and then do hula hoop
oh okay maybe not
I probably could oh
I have to stop him but my power alone
won't be enough
right you're not from around here are
you I'm from Austria
right of course you're not
sit down for this
it could work
[Music]
try holding your right hand over me
lightly cover the IR motion camera what
what
fake camera right wow what I never knew
about this feature
measuring I actually covered the IR
motion camera with the pattern are you
measuring my pulse
measuring
I don't remember this from last time I
used this two years ago or so
thank you
[Music]
ah whoa
[Laughter]
wait oh
my hands
put my my hair on the toilet
oh is it fixed oh yeah bye
just like when I was in high school just
like high school oh it's synchronized oh
yeah can you feel it we're connected now
come on let's go after Drago no
normal my normal state
huh is something wrong oh your hair went
out oh
you're gonna work with me on this
you know this was a problem I had when I
was uh I was a teenager but I didn't
think this would happen now that I'm an
adult a full-fledged adult exercise the
more synchronized we'll be you'll know
we're in sync when your hair flares out
that's how that works without counting
on you baseball jug counting on me
you're counting on me am I a school's
Blackboard or what
old Count On Me
what was that laugh all right can we go
to the next one
thank you thanks for giving me such a
big break and being so kind to me I I go
whoa that looks like we have to jump and
[\h__\h] no no no no no no no
that one level three all right let's
keep our heads up and charge on one
Cafe
so warm
tomorrow
see no one can do this if they do this
with life today all right let's go
oh [\h__\h] my thing is messed up
what is that one
um
still dropping very lightly
[Music]
down
plants before it died
I sound like
[Music]
hey
look at my arms
[Music]
who created you 'll have to fight
against them in fit battles
no need to worry yes I'm not worried I'm
a Pokemon Master battle expert so if
you're feeling a bit I know more than
you I already defeated all eight arenas
as the Collision of two combatants
exercise energy
let's warm up by giving this guy a
smoothie blend of kale and Punishment
movie
skill is a different next
oh
oh the memories
wants to be my enemy
okay
let's exercise
okay squad for that Kim Kardashian butt
for the Kim Kardashian butt okay
okay let's go keep your back straight
okay nicely done hey I love it
[Music]
apgar defend with apgar app guard okay
tightly into my stomach ah
but there's like a battery thing here
and that kind of hurts if you run out of
Hearts you lose oh no
uh this side but ah okay okay
[Music]
I'm scared I would break this thing
no but this is not a problem
um
okay uh
perfect
[Music]
I'm pretty excellent
all right
[Music]
good Heather
this is suffering
wait I have one I do have a uh error
everything behind me a fan a little
while I didn't turn it on
we should do this once per week guys
oh we're running again all right look at
that
let's get through this
can we make it to one hour
even though 30 minutes of those were
stalling
[Music]
whoa
oh I want to break that [\h__\h]
no I had to put it down oh yeah
you bet money I couldn't
don't believe in me
select a skill red hoplin what do we
have like besides that I can't I don't
think I can really do this well
um because if I sit I think the capture
is good but let's try it
[Music]
okay
okay I don't need the Ring Thing the
Rincon ah straight okay
ah okay let's go oh God oh God
he's also great for working your life
okay let's put it on the ground
excellent
I don't have to cross okay
one left
stand up
oh okay okay here I am
look at that I have guard yes got it got
it
good workout yeah that's why I bought
the game two years ago I never used it
again after that
yeah
we're working out isn't it
oh bent legs select your skill and
attack pose
take it slow yoga skills for cotton this
is Yoga oh okay yoga watch tips Moving
Straight move to classroom skills less
effective okay
oh
wait sorry
[Music]
I was even slower than him starting
position
I feel it
no it's not here I feel it I feel it
there on the on the front part of the
little leg
is that normal
it's 45 years man
it was 45 years
[Laughter]
my shins yeah are The Shins supposed to
burn for that
let's pretend it is
no you're not tip you don't know [\h__\h]
that's normal when I'm trying to say see
he knows what he's talking about oh
also trying yoga and the other exercises
oh I can get more play the bench I can
get more like choices wow
nice
oh okay here we go back to normal this
is a marathon
imagine 12 hours stream of this
I spent myself I have to remember how to
do it
drop your hips what oh
I was celebrating sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
would you even live through it probably
not oh yeah
let's try that
will it be higher than when I play
horror games
[Music]
oh no I'm dying
I think it's already calmed down it was
worse like before the for the battle or
so
um
[Music]
over 100.
there you have the exciting uh heart
rate and this is not even so bad
I still feel okay
yeah this is the same way of measuring
right
my normal heart rate is like
60 I think right 67 yeah
at least I have a pulse yeah that's good
I didn't dye it
based on my a25 I wonder what the game
thinks about Dad
[Music]
yeah wait exercise level Something
percent of Max heart rate calculated
based on your age what's that mean does
that mean it's good for 45 or bad for
45.
Oh you mean the heart rate is also what
the heart rate is not based on my age
right
that doesn't matter right they mean like
ah the the rest that's written there is
based on like not the hard way
apartment is accurate right
the pulse
hard one yeah there you go
it's good for 45. I'm not about
well well
I'm 27 isn't it okay yeah
Dragon I'm coming for you I'll swear to
you I'll slay you real good
and check my menu no so you're
difficulty level my menu no all right
let's keep working our way towards
dragon
[Music]
Stadium
the more he works out the stronger the
darker oh he works out he goes to he's
one of those people that you see when
you walk by a fitness center that has
the windows and you look at them and
they're they're sweating and they're
working out on the biking so on and they
go like
[Music]
it's kind of embarrassing so I try to
not look because I'm sure they're also I
am very still do the people inside there
think like look somewhere else they they
wanted to be looked at don't they most
of them some of them if they are in the
front row or right in front of the
window they want to be looked at right
but I don't want to give them the good
feeling of being looked at
if they want that then I don't want to
give it to them
are my knees okay what what about what
my knees my knees are Prime thank you
for asking though
take a deep breath
that's a good idea
what goes Stadium
[Music]
let's go
eat cake in front of them they gotta
troll them
I'll tell you what what's the what's the
food that has the most cut I should just
eat a burger or so all right
girl I'm I'm looking straight fix that
okay here we go and think it's a tough
focus on breathing okay
laughs
already come
here we go
when did he find time to build all these
yeah
[Music]
that gave me a level up
whoa
hey
no no
no no no no no no
no how many [\h__\h] stairs
are you ready
is it time for recalibration no still
looks good when I stop it looks good
whoa I can't do that
but hopefully the games are going to ask
me to do to do that
[\h__\h] Flex
till low pressure and clean stick to her
routine isn't that would you always use
saving
well you still locked me up anyway now
look at me I'm totally out of shape [\h__\h]
which girlfriend can I impress like this
man
and it was just supposed to be your new
training buddy leave my partner out of
it just between wait why does he have no
voicing oh
wow
[Music]
bam
fine whatever I don't even care what if
you or anyone else because in the way of
my trading I'll pound him to the ground
like a ground pounds
let's see he's a fan of Amelia Watson
damn dude this is a teammate
the skill and attack
um did I get anything new it's still the
same stuff
all right what it is
okay let's move this will focus on
working your legs
[Music]
oh yeah yeah I remember hey
beautiful beautiful
go ahead press
okay
[Music]
nicely done
nice move thanks
appreciate that oh
okay
we can do the knee to chest again
I'm ready
okay
okay let's go
um
[Music]
very nice I probably shouldn't just drop
it instead
good fantastic
excellent
amazing
you made it stand up they need to rush
them
[Music]
dummies
feels
go select my hair and share a pose what
if I just sit on my chair I could
probably she's interested
it doesn't know it says no
way
[Music]
good stay focused
how do you know you didn't see a chair
behind me there was no chair
Mommy
what do you want let's do more squats
for the for the kiwawa bus improvements
right
okay let's go
do I have to put my my she said straight
but his back doesn't look very it goes
like this
I don't like I don't get it how is the
right way to do it
[Music]
okay
I mean as long as it's not like a curve
I guess
oh [\h__\h]
okay
I have to redeem myself
[Music]
this movement targets your core
[Laughter]
y
you don't have many hearts left oh he's
almost dead though he'll die now
that's very sweet of you
[Music]
okay let's go
[Applause]
keep it up
preserves more than 100 money
[\h__\h] I just saved the world is this how
you get rewarded for being a freaking
RPG protagonist what the hell this is
inferior Pidgey isn't it I got
experience points so
hold on there
[Applause]
all the irony here is the jrpg player
and finisher oh
does that mean
does that mean I have to finish this
ring fit someday
to continue with my title
oh dear if I I don't know if I can
really do that
I mean I have time right I got time next
week no no I I have to still finish
Pokemon okay one by one one after
another well okay my stats are going up
yay
there's a lot to this adventure mode oh
god well we have time
I'm gonna finish it one day
yay
yay doesn't that not count here there
you go
pulling energy from the ground
[Music]
sure why not
we're gonna do one more like whole thing
I don't mind
[Music]
okay check that after finishing this
game
hey it's lower this time but I again
like they have to measure it right in
the middle
nice
[Music]
how you doing what gives I'm supposed to
be tougher than this
when I get my power back I'm gonna mix
you playing this movie Very side bet on
it no
no no
you're gonna regret the day you met her
fingers
I have to protect the movie
oh no he got away
the one who got away we dropped her go
away
glad I get to work with you as a partner
come on it's not safe to let you run
around freely I think we're going to
escape to the neighboring country
Germany
we'll have many neighboring countries it
was probably Germany all right let's go
to Germany
hey
with the flexibles we go to Germany now
I'm not done here we go I'm coming for
you I see you I see you
oh you laugh like Bowser we've only
gotten this far because I was sloppy
right well that's gonna change
that looks like Germany yeah
yeah
land of nights monsters are most active
at night we'll need to be really careful
so let work yeah
[Music]
there's more levels there um I'll try to
do all of them I guess I'll try before I
die but I'm a phoenix it doesn't matter
must be a child close by right we've
come this far
so hungry because everyone doesn't
travel summons showed up in your town
that would be really bad
for the staff to juggle
[Music]
nice cloak
pie
oh so hungry
okay
oh it's so pretty here nice song
lightly
a pond ah can we swim I guess not um
we're not floating over it we're gonna
also not swim we're just gonna walk like
an idiot
[Laughter]
oh oh [\h__\h] wow
right
I maybe miss a lot just face me downward
to recap okay we have the same issues it
seems you and me my dear ring can I suck
the dares no can I burn them
I'm so sorry oh
oh
okay let's select a skill squat
oh I'm tired okay why no AOE damage I
need AOE damage okay let's go put your
toes Straight Ahead
[Music]
feel the power of the butt squat
see how low I can go right off you see
that
[Music]
damn girl
protect protect time for protect
what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
oh I hate that one
all right always always get rid of one
enemy first
okay let's move
[Music]
the one more hit I should have gone to
the other one all right
let's go
knock your arms
[Music]
makes no sense
um I'll squat some more
I'll always go to the side so you guys
can see myself
[Music]
squash one left okay
don't tell me to go nowhere
with your left fence I'm I'm at my limit
man
I'm not sure
bows
Bend slowly thank you blue Vikings hope
you get better soon you know what helps
to get better so how about you workout
too
foreign
[Music]
oh I'm sorry
it works no problem
level up
front press oh
that's not really something that's
I can do so
and that's like this side no I don't I
don't want to do that set the new friend
request what do you mean set it
no [\h__\h] that I don't like it give me
something for my butt give me something
for the butt
okay
it doesn't help somehow this doesn't
really fill me up what the hell
come on
okay I'm running really fast guys I'm
zooming
oh
look at heels
[Music]
let's go
was it that
butt instagramable but okay let's move
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
okay let's let's go
all right amazing
[Music]
my arms bombs
oh [\h__\h]
come at me bro try me
[Music]
all right
hmm
[Music]
okay let's move the boys doing this on a
hard floor shot
it's great nice
[Music]
tough one
you're sick
[\h__\h] I'm not getting paid well enough
thank God I'm doing all alive
you're good
without a life look at that that would
be [\h__\h]
I'm absolutely [\h__\h] and for so much
effort holy [\h__\h]
do you live through I do apparently and
I squat and I and I run what what
happened
I'm the one that everyone gets like
super intimidated by the fitness center
oh [\h__\h]
yeah yeah they look at me and they're
like oh Chihuahua is in like she is
every day
oh I can never get to her level
she'll be my all-time goal
so [\h__\h] insane
it's just like my idol my oh she you
could almost say my fitness center oh
[\h__\h]
I'm gonna look at her she does it all
with style and Flawless everything oh my
God
play
[Music]
what's that rock is no match for the two
of us just the two of us what do you
mean
okay
you got it
together she does the tracking when I
run is just really [\h__\h] I'm sorry
okay
[Music]
victory
look at that five golden rings
services
my Paws should be higher now I think
[Music]
faster
what
I don't have a balls
[Music]
foreign
apparently
[Music]
so
if this is me at my at my
uh at this stage then I'm not
embarrassed hey
don't call phone out like that
the fun I have that is
I mean maybe like 100 or so I don't know
not 120 and joking but even even then
these girls need to work out
and drink less coffee or whatever
yeah I'm 45. look at my heart rate
oh man unbelievable okay
let's go there how do I go there
[Music]
no
what they they are worrying about me
because I'm 45 huh
don't worry so much about no how do I go
up
um how about how do I no how do I go
there
that's there and then there but then how
do I go there
like this ah
oh Mommy thanks for the Super Chat
all right
just save her
wow wow
that's a long Tower
[Music]
okay
hi
here we go
[Music]
I want to shoot more of those
all right
what the [\h__\h]
no I keep on forgetting how to jump
[Music]
nice
hey
This brilliant observation ring
squat
you weren't ready for this master Squad
[Music]
it doesn't remind me for going lower
nice
okay good hello baby that's it that's it
dick she's out camping she's feeling in
your stomach
oh they go coming at me
[Music]
um
I need more variety
Bend slowly
went down a bit so in order not to bend
your lower back
a thousand oh it's because I killed him
all right squeezing
careful
screaming so much
what's up
okay okay
[Music]
wonderful
you made it stand up no need to rush
though what am I screaming tomorrow by
the way
oh my streaming tomorrow do I need to be
worried about myself
what am I doing tomorrow
reminds me science fire huh I think it's
quite an early stream right I'm
satisfied as comfy I'm gonna display
that [\h__\h] spire
for real this time not your arms
[Music]
I can do this with one hand if I wanted
to let me show you hey
you don't want to attack me is that
happening I was gonna Flex
all right all right
forever
[Applause]
okay let's go I'm already squatting at
this point that doesn't recognize
[Music]
let your lower back fall so your knees
don't go too far forward
okay here one hand
one hand block with your bike fence
[Music]
uh
where can I get some extra
pink if anything
Bend slowly
slowly return to the starting position
work your lower body muscles
[Applause]
[Music]
slower than a [\h__\h] slowpoke
please don't kill me
[Music]
careful you don't have many hearts left
I know no you're a little [\h__\h]
I'm alive okay
wow
foreign
[Music]
let's go
nice work
way to work up a sweat drop your hips I
don't really run like that
even though it looks cute
Marathon Olympic person
[Music]
sure
high score baby
[Music]
hey
that's a baby
number seven
[Music]
I am now a ring fit streamer
that's all I do every day
Master fit skills to give yourself a
serious Advantage by the battle those
Advantage equip you fit skills as you
are dub
uh give me another one I don't like the
one you gave to me
okay oh
what is that down there
was that supposed to be is an extra
it doesn't seem like a treasure chest
can we skip it I don't know let's take a
look what is it oh is it what is
chocolate this is your first time here
let's get your register and you simply
need your name parasite yeah
this is a game gym where you can play me
again I'm really a fox no
no Robo wrecker
roasted press and pull the ring cotton
what
oh let me drink some water
um
it's fun but this is my arms this needs
my arms
I need to keep the remaining muscle
power in my arms so I have to bless
oh
[Music]
hmm
yeah I am mine
my normal string lamp seven hours so
yeah wait how did I get to the shop
without doing this yet huh
I don't know how to get to the shop when
how do I
no
someone said something about shop but I
want to continue
huh
oh that one down there is how I unlock
the shop
what no first up is the next World oh
okay
[Music]
oh God
shut up
next leveling
oh
huh okay
a small cool down moment
congratulations in a second
power power
[Music]
got you gotcha punch you're gonna pay
for my 1.4 million children for their
dinner and for their beds everything our
doctor trees and their University
College pays everything it's all on me
if they don't have that support then
they have nothing
they're counting on me I can't
disappoint them
thank you you're welcome love you
Squad
okay let's go
[Music]
all right
what yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
amazing
nice move
thank you process
[Music]
sit the [\h__\h] down
chair pose
[Music]
scrolling on the chair that's different
slowly
[Applause]
lower a little more your knees and toes
your word one and a half hours
squeeze
[Music]
okay let's move
keep your toes from pointing inwards
improve me
[Applause]
get ready
[Music]
I was shielding myself it's because you
guys didn't post enough Shield emojis
chat
okay let's go
now pull your knees toward you nice keep
it up
okay
[Music]
I definitely get up like a 45 year old
or like more like a 60 year old
[Music]
show me what you got
it
okay let's go be sure
[Music]
[Applause]
fantastic
[Music]
nicely done one left
Flawless
thanks Randy RJ it's not a big deal
with your legs bent slightly squeeze
[Music]
okay let's move this will focus on
working your legs
thank you
[Music]
your sweat is so shiny and beautiful but
didn't you say my sweat is shiny and
beautiful
[Music]
say that what the [\h__\h] what it sounds
like my chat
for that man
don't ask me to sell it
[Music]
foreign
nice fresh air what the [\h__\h] is that a
fox
what are you doing here
I'm too fast I wasn't actually really
running so fast but now I am oh is that
the new Pokemon
you can also like turn it around
completely no
foreign
[Music]
wow
select a skill oh he's charging he's
charging something
[Music]
what
we're gonna [\h__\h] it oh
[Music]
Bend slowly
I got this one down
slowly return to the starting position
got a good yoga teacher there
excellent
I'll definitely feel it in the legs
[Music]
oh let's go select the scale
silence is over
when
okay let's go
over extend your knees okay
[Music]
if we take him down now then we won't
take damage
is this really like green on green does
it really work
s tomorrow
[Music]
slowly return to the starting position
worker lower body muscles
okay this should be it
was later in the game not yet
oh wow oh wow oh the legs great hustle
keep it up all the arms
a little Egg Baby level eight
ah thanks guys no I'm not gonna rest
we're right in front of the bus the goal
is right there oh
baby
yes yes I need that one
drop your hips
[Music]
we're gonna measure my pose
no I'm gonna kill the boss
the titles
this doesn't look so bad
howdy healthy chill healthy chill
Hey low low heart rate Joe
so healthy Joe
this is what you call
I forgot the word
what are you calling it why do I call
myself all the time again
you know what I'm talking about
ah
no not picture
no because I don't drink the alcohol and
all that
[Music]
yeah
and if you listen oh what a real dragon
all the real him is no kind of guy to
send monsters to make other people
miserable when the first Majora he was
very insecure about his body he'd call
himself his weak squirrel needs I helped
him train oh and now he's like way too
overconfident what the hell his ego
became like multiplied as his body size
multiplied well
that's why I have we have to hurry we
can still save him from the dark
influences control
[\h__\h] that
this is the last one even if you're
enjoying the game you should not do it
45 you [\h__\h] discriminating me
none of that [\h__\h] you're gonna have
to save the
oh
do you think that all these like Arts
Championship characters have time to
take a [\h__\h] break
there's something we gotta do we're
gonna take down the evil monsters so
they're friendling the world all right
otherwise you know what's gonna be
[\h__\h] apocalypse you don't want that
I don't even know what happens to me
after the apocalypse I don't know if
Phoenix can survive an apocalypse it's
about my own Survival too you know
taking this seriously this ain't no
jokes and games
we have to retrieve the five special
powers
and one
um
[Music]
at least it stays like that yep that's
how you open those doors oh got it got
it got the USB metal oh one more
[Music]
[Laughter]
hold on
um
[Music]
basic survival skills
oh throw it again oh thank God they
smell like little suckers
okay I'm gonna do this
[Music]
I may have lost my power but that won't
determine
now together we'll defeat you I'm the
partner aka the protagonist
well the feet you will take it down
squats the power sports
power of friendship
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah it looks like it is
no no no no no no
all three of them
it says wait okay now we're taking him
on okay
the dumbbells
oh let's select the skin let's try the
new one
and wait should I aim for the sides
first
big sweeping motions
thing on ribbon feels best however you
really want to fight the skill flower
[Music]
really
Flawless for my spine
and that's easy I like that one
um
[Music]
okay let's move
exercise
[Music]
good job
which one last
one left
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
I don't know if I'll survive this yes
[Music]
I
could it doesn't get any better than
that
I need to check
foreign
[Music]
should I fire the dumbbells
the colors still don't matter right
let's just slap with
and I can Target them all
[Music]
right
thank you
[Music]
okay
we like that one
oh my coolant driceps
[Music]
nice move
oh [\h__\h] here he goes but he's already
like half half health so your leg bends
like I'm not that worries
[Music]
extra damage now select the two okay
okay
let's try and get the blue
Heaven died
[Music]
Bend slowly
can we do it
[Music]
okay let's move
awesome
nice one left
[Music]
excellent oh shut up
well he must do less damage now right
heal it in your stomach when you breathe
out
keep your guard up
[Music]
careful you don't have many hearts left
a dog
chair pose
that was the same damage too what the
[\h__\h]
ERS
when he has no weapons
attack
squeezing
foreign
[Music]
okay let's move
trying to get the poster right oh
[Music]
you're so serious right now
almost there guys almost there
okay let's go
dance
[Music]
okay oh wonderful
you made it stand up
[Music]
squeeze
oh wait I'm supposed to bend my legs did
that change anything no it's really
careful you don't have many hearts right
[Applause]
look in your life
[Music]
Bend slowly
[Applause]
this is more intense than a lot of those
series
boss monster fights out there
[Music]
that battle was epic
oh yes yes
[Music]
the world for now
oh
hey
whoa
whoa whoa
yo
drop your hips and I was thinking oh
after I did some exercise maybe I can
read some super chess no [\h__\h] no
bring them tomorrow
thank you for the super chance guys
already done tomorrow
I'm also hungry but she's very exhausted
and I think I need a shower
otherwise my cats will
complain
oh not so bad
this doesn't reflect how much I'm
actually suffering as my my heart rate
never reflects how much I'm suffering
and when I play horror games either
yo
so the return substantial
you guys know when you're thinking well
honestly they don't mind but
like literally chunkers
will sit right next look right here
because like there's on the idle meeting
place you know there's a there's a
little level I have a little shelf there
right there and she literally like when
I go to the island meeting
you know she decides to sit right next
to me look at me and I'm like Jokers you
really don't mind Jonas it's kind of
weird
every time every time she does that she
gets really excited she goes like meow
and
then she looks at me
I wonder when she thinks I'm doing
obviously I'm doing an idol meeting
report and talking with my manager
oh I acquired a hundred blasts presser
that sounds really strong epic yeah
um
oh there's still another juice to stand
up to me
hey Dad
has everyone in the chat did all the
cave people they all underestimated me
I'll give you power back the one I kept
anyway
the others are where they belong in the
garden
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] that's rude that's nasty
I'm gonna help the disinfect it
you did great thank you I repent
coding oh
oh
wow
I feel my power returning
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
I mean I didn't know about it for a
while so maybe it was good that I didn't
get it until now
it's gonna be more effective
we do the power side oh yeah the power
is the color coding ability this will
give you some serious Edge no future
battles
foreign
oh no escaping now
a shining Jewel from the heavens quit
here to then cool down yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
at this point honestly [\h__\h] yes
foreign
[Music]
works out once in a [\h__\h] year and you
should too let's move on to the cool
down let's review today's results oh
don't block
just one of the plunge and now you're
chilling go ahead and change clothes all
right
[Music]
now
I ran 2.8 kilo kilometers that sounds
like nothing
but I exercised 25 minutes it felt way
longer than that what the [\h__\h] my stream
says two hours
eh
what is that [\h__\h]
who's that what does that mean
this is wrong
huh
like effective no even then even then
oh that was more
lions
no even
incredible the like you know stalling
even then
good for a beginner it's huge
thank you okay
oh wow I did 165 ring presses I did 58
squats 48 standing twists I can do more
I did 39 chair poses I did for you three
abdominal presses I did 31 yo that looks
like a huge list to me
whoa look at all that
[Music]
um
on I feel this was that just a hunger I
don't know which one it is
oh yeah thank you thank you thank you
thank you thanks
one thing about the length of recession
it
yeah yeah I'm gonna take a break don't
worry
if you want a little more challenge try
increasing your difficulty level but
don't know Victor yourself let's do some
stretching before your body because that
is what you have an exercise great way
to show Johnny but yeah that's possible
fatigue yep okay
be mindful of your body and stretch
within the range of your ability
spread your feet raise both hands and
hold your left wrist oh while pulling on
your wrist tilt to the right and stretch
your side
oh my stomach hurts so much return to
your original position switch hands and
bend the other way
this is not the tracking isn't even
accurate
don't overdo it
[Music]
bring yourself back slowly
stretch your left arm to the side and
hold it with your right arm
pull in your arm and stretch the muscles
of your left shoulder
when eating your meals consider starting
with your vegetables first
order matters now do the same on the
opposite side
be careful not to rotate your waist
[Music]
Garlic's plunge and vampire repelling
scent is caused by a compound called
allicin bring yourself back slowly
join your hands together vampires are
real with your palms facing out stretch
out your back
[Music]
or I'm working on this bring yourself
back slowly I felt decent put your right
foot forward and cross your legs
bend your body forward and stretch the
back of your left leg
like that for a little longer
well
[Music]
hold straighten up and switch legs
stretch the opposite side as well
worse than when you're just doing it
straight like this
slowly straighten it bit by bit starting
from your lower back I never knew that
damn that's like put your right leg
forward hands on your hips bend your
right knee and stretch out your left
calf there's no carpet here
[Music]
here I've got the chicken right here
that's protein isn't it shifter Center
balance forward and stretch out the
opposite side this looks so weird
what is with the tracking
bring yourself back slowly yeah I feel
that
and your stretching is complete good job
holy macaroni
everything hurts finish up here some
positives
maybe I should take a bath to say
another shower
that would be nice probably for my
muscles don't be like thank you kiwawa I
love you so much I will continue to
support your whole body and your
skeleton
s
no we first saw them with broccoli
yesterday if you guys want to see a
balanced diet look at my [\h__\h] Twitter
not sponsored by hello even though it
could be sponsored hello
are you listening you could I could talk
I've been posting pictures from the food
I make from you since like months
yeah and people are waiting for the
official endorsement from me to get a
subscription from hello
yeah
I've been doing a good job promoting you
if only there was anything to promote
because how can I promote you when I
can't even say your name hello
yeah once you're missing out on is
exactly that
yeah yeah yeah yeah but honestly yeah I
think my I think my diet has been
very balanced compared to like last year
or so
or even the year before I've been
cooking so much more
so yeah yeah hello project exactly I
love hello projects
a little project oh how can I maintain
the same lifestyle try to say I have to
shut up
I'm so done I'm so dumb I'm sure you're
ready to go right away the next time you
play It's A Story come on
[Music]
I'm glad that the strap on my Mo cups
worked out for the leg thing because I
lost the other one that's really nice
that that worked oh whoops it that was
the accident
go away
no no don't alarm me
no no no no no no no
don't stress me out like that
anyway thank you guys
for watching today we're gonna slay the
spider tomorrow
and we found and I'll have muscle ache
yay
so
um that'll be fun trust me yeah
I'm so glad I could go to some pretty it
makes so much more sense doesn't it
now so they did that
um
first time also there's like the
um from what's it called there's another
like sports game for the switch
but that's more like about like actual
sports right not like this kind of
exercise so at some point we can also
try that one out with 3D
and I also want to play like some like
rhythm dancing games or so if there's
like permissions
in 3D but that will look probably more
scuffed because once I start dancing it
looks more like [\h__\h] but we'll see we'll
see
foreign
[Music]
my legs are [\h__\h] yeah beat saber
um
yeah something like that yeah
or Just Dance I want to do that but I
don't know about copyright
because the maybe on our club but even
then I don't know I have to check what's
with these legs
what
what the [\h__\h]
well don't don't look
hi
well okay so
I hope you guys enjoyed that I I feel I
feel very proud because you know
you know at least like a stream gives me
a reason to work out
a motivation and so on
and uh normally if this if I wasn't
doing the stream I wouldn't have worked
out today so
I wouldn't even have worked out a single
day in this whole year hmm
yeah yeah but you gotta Get Fit again
because I also kind of got to learn some
new dances and so on and uh I mean I
really think it's kind of separate but
if I can build some stamina that would
be nice so I really need the [\h__\h]
stamina I'm so
oh my stomach I'm gonna eat the rest of
my broccoli risotto now I think I guess
that was two hours one of my shortest
streams but honestly I I thought it
would be one hour at most so
big [\h__\h] success I would say
yeah
oh yeah
thank you thank you thank you weekly I
don't know about weekly but every once
in a while the thing is I gotta launch
this [\h__\h] I don't want to watch it
weekly
like because you gotta pull out all the
cables and [\h__\h] I don't know it's very
annoying
I'm gonna put them back in
but I did wear something underneath so
maybe it's not so bad not only what I
was wearing
um is sweaty and we'll see oh God my my
abs my abs are killing me
I have to feed my abs
Ence will be a bit better oh my back my
abs
I'm dying I need to take off the suit
because there's also like there's like a
battery pack like right here that's also
kind of like stabbing me
everything everything hurts oh
oh yeah yeah okay okay
[Music]
eggs
are you talking from a different time
zone or so freak me out that's the day
after tomorrow holy [\h__\h]
shook me to the Core
oh my God Oh you mean the release of the
skin oh okay okay oh
that it felt like back in school just
now I felt like oh God my my homework is
due tomorrow but I thought it was the
day after tomorrow all this [\h__\h]
scared me yeah why
no problem
it's good look how shiny this thing is
oh wow
anyway
popsicle all right and in German we say
hey
[Music]
ah
wait
[Music]
I'll be dancing
um
[Music]
come on
um
[Music]
like a wild animal
s
ah
um
dinner time baby winner winner chicken
dinner
bye-bye
[Music]
tomorrow's stream will be I think a bit
earlier so I'll see you there wakey
wakey
[Music]
foreign
I haven't eaten Burger in a while
Burger
too bad risotto no honestly that Rosanna
wasn't so impressive last night
I did everything according to recipe
[Music]
oh
maybe I'll get a burger
[Music]
no no no no no no no it's different for
me my body doesn't work like that I
built differently I'm just built
differently you don't even understand
you wouldn't understand
you wouldn't get it
[Music]
thanks guys