foreign
[Music]
hello
hello here it goes yeah
[Music]
I don't know ghost
hello hi
[Music]
if you had to give this group of three
girls
a name I wonder what it would be because
I feel like our colors they're so like
in the in the red Brown's Spectrum
it's just so aesthetic to me it's it's
aesthetically pleasing to me it's like
awesome what the hell yeah
autumn colors maybe like fall fall Birds
oh yeah
a bird
[Music]
oh fall girls
ball girls almost feels like we're
trying to fake Fall Guys
oh I just got that I'm sorry I also kind
of woke up recently a little slow right
now oh
cute oh uh uh how's everybody's audio
please tell me be honest don't try to
throw me off please
okay most people are saying good but
some one person said it's all right and
now I'm concerned but I'm just gonna
roll with it okay
um
you guys have been playing a little bit
no it's okay
okay with you guys now it's okay yeah
nice you should be able to play in
normal games don't worry
people should know there's new players
playing the game and if they don't then
it says more about them being in the
same ELO so
um don't worry there's people have been
playing this game for like six years and
they still play like they're new exactly
like you just can't like me
[Laughter]
I'm really not in a position to question
anybody's pew pew abilities in this game
it's okay you will learn it's a there's
a lot to learn in this game like
everybody has unique abilities it's so
much to keep track of it is and you have
to remember everybody else's when You
Face them so yeah yeah yeah yeah uh what
do you guys do you guys want to do roll
Q or open q
don't know where the difference is oh so
in roll kill you have to yeah you still
like who you what really you want first
open q you can play whatever the heck
you want throughout the game
oh I know you girls decide you girls no
more
I don't care I don't care either
[Music]
oh no we're all indecisive oh yeah Chad
says open q might be better for Kiara so
she can switch around yeah yeah and then
we could switch let's do that while we
wait let's go into a death match
of us right am I supposed to click
something no you're you don't have to do
anything I'm in control
here look we can find each other and
become friends and not shoot each other
okay
look at this oh do you see it and now
you find each other we find each other
and we become good friends
these people are fighting oh someone's
shooting at me that better not be you
guys
but is it only us no oh [\h__\h]
it's like a boss kind of like a skirmish
before to fill the time yeah I have no
patience
oh okay I
will be healer
okay and I will I will be the reason why
we're going down
is that on purpose on me
what oh never mind sometimes people oh
you can't do that thing anymore where
you like switch up on internet annoys
people yeah that thingy
[Laughter]
I'm nervous it's okay I believe this
character once and I was okay I think
but only against AI so it's okay don't
worry don't worry just try not to die on
your level
each do they try to match it with people
that are on your level or is it
completely mixed I have no idea what the
matchmaking is like now honestly I mean
which one is the tank
I'm the tank I'm the only one okay yeah
yeah only one thing I'm a Healer too and
the others are DPS
so if we lose it's the DPS it's his
fault
let's go yeah
okay
crystals
are you gonna be focused
I joined the VC earlier yeah I was in
the game and she was so focused I was
really focused yeah because I couldn't
even hear you oh yeah
I just ate yogurt thinking about people
[Music]
oh
goodbye
that's part of all part of it like yeah
you want to get killed also yet you
don't want to die
but these
other teams
oh like you don't
oh my God
thank you oh
either
oh how do I heal myself
I'm not sure
[\h__\h] bullies
we can hold it nice
hold on hold on
oh door
wait hold the base oh hold the door I
thought that was so dumb at the end I
was like what the [\h__\h]
yeah it's like what can we sneak in like
what what
oh my God
come on come on come on honestly when I
watch that show oh yeah we got it
as I was watching Game of Thrones I was
always thinking this is amazing this is
incredible but then sometimes the
episode would be over and I could think
about it I feel like wait that's kind of
wait what like the last two seasons
[Music]
doesn't mean that's half [\h__\h] let's hear
two ghosts okay girls
let's get out there I don't know when I
was a young boy
I guess it's that song
[Music]
I think mine is probably Mamma Mia even
if I don't want it to be Mamma Mia yeah
yeah like the musical or the song you
have two tanks yeah
who else
oh thanks
guys oh God
wow wow wow
[Music]
sorry
oh thank you for yeah
yeah what's your karaoke song
I was hoping you wouldn't ask oh no I
remember
I remembered
oh [\h__\h] you know this problem
I don't even you don't even know the
answer yourself is that an ulti
uh I don't remember
oh yeah despacito totally that's my
go-to song despacito you know the words
kill it
[Music]
I don't know
that song
oh my heel is so weak I need to skill
more on it
sorry I don't know why I thought you
almost
I thought we had we're like 90 I don't
know how to read numbers
oh no
I was gonna kill by the same person yeah
they focus the healers which is always
no no
they're gonna get it but we can take it
back I'm gonna run away bye-bye
contact
oh he's getting us some extra points
oh yeah
oh wait really
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
it's okay we'll come back
we'll get them this is our opportunity
to regroup oh wait never mind there's
still people down there I'm curious
[Music]
oh no she did
a Reaper sucks
no offense nothing and mean Jack
IE watch out for the Reinhardt he's
trying to come up here
gained his senses back
oh he actually has his ultimate oh
we have two things now
what the heck wait I'm here where'd you
go oh almost over there oh God
do you think anybody will get this
email
um there's the yeah this guy is kind of
bothering me
sorry
[Laughter]
do they keep coming for you guys in the
back like a Genji or something another
Reinhardt was the keeping distance
between us
I see yeah he's really annoying and I
can't take him out by myself that's why
I was saying the reaper sucks because he
the reaper would get so close to him
that the Reinhardt would just kill him
instantly with his hammers yeah I was
watching
[Music]
so lucky we can't see your level and how
many hours we've played
you're so lucky we can't see your
OverWatch one history sucks
it's all erased wow
for over
I don't know
good question
maybe he doesn't have any because he's a
noob
let's see
I feel like the other tank may have
sensed that I have been neglecting him
in terms of killing yeah they just
Target me because what the heck the
other tank was even on point
head oh they have two things too
who am I supposed to heal when you're
not there the other day yeah
but he's by himself it's really annoying
see this is what you don't want you
don't want just one person on flame in
all the teams is alive because no one
can
stop
oops sorry I woke him up oh okay at
least he's not charging now oh
you can be mad
sorry sorry that
our Reinhardt taking that pin this
evening
oh wait I didn't do that
I'm gonna punch her
punch
no they're purple
I see you okay
what does what does the E do with the
character I'm playing does someone know
I think it makes
um others Invincible for a little bit oh
and yourself
what
plants
that's a very important makeup routine
oh yeah skincare
when are we doing that girl talk man
I just recently started doing skincare
oh I didn't know much about it well I
knew about cleansing but like I didn't
know about bleeding or oh yeah
[Music]
um
oh I feel like I wasn't down that long
no no
you're barely behind us
okay I I just really still uh it was the
second time I'm playing OverWatch in my
life I just don't know when things
happens
to keep up with
oh no
sorry I think I woke up sorry it's okay
because there's nothing you can do about
it
all right
get out of here
no
no it was dead I just realized
we got it now
[Music]
okay
got you oh
yeah I think
okay
look at this guy
oh
no oh my goodness
here I'm sorry oh my God
I'm in here
okay that all of them are on point so
they're all shooting
get in there
you can wait I know we did no we all
died yeah I got it I got it
nice try nice try that's okay I decided
to start Bloom I'm physically tilty but
not mentally I fixed myself I don't want
to look at this person no I forgot to
leave as a group dang it here I'll get
you guys back
my bad I will collect you all should I
should I leave oh wait leave the game
now yes wait now you guys are in your
own group oh
what oh there we go okay I'm right and I
got it fixed off oops all fixed all
fixed that's okay
good that's okay I think I did I did
okay my character I think so too I blame
our DPS
yeah
I invited
oh yeah
I can weld
I can Wild
which one is uh which one where is oh
there she is like break it oh
okay the kid that was like support yeah
yeah
but he can also we need something oh
wait do we need something specific in
the group uh just play whatever you want
yeah okay
is your Bash
I think
right look I have a shield right click
is The Shield
shift okay remember shift is the long
distance
there is a badge somewhere maybe unless
they removed it it's about oh I think it
should be right click then you left
click right out here
oh yeah yeah I just didn't finish my
instructions uh-huh
attackers in jury there he goes
he says hello
why are we so
oh okay he's doing work that's fine I
don't know what the hell I'm doing
I'm just this is what are we okay
usually you don't throw this close to
the spawn but this guy is confident and
he seems to be
um
[Music]
I envy dead
I'm not a healing
the right hand fell off
time to go back time to go back oh no oh
no time to go back
okay
oh I think I eliminated someone's Mecca
oh no oh
Don't Go Near that thingy it hurts
all the way back
to you and don't come for them I was too
confident I guess no confidence
is going to the point yeah I heard him
hello
I'm mad
death spiral
oh my God oh my God
as long as you're scaring him off the
point
oh gosh thank you
God right this Reinhardt crazy
yeah
what I didn't even see that diva
come on
[Music]
yeah
foreign
[Music]
well come on come on leave it alone
still going for you I'm done we want to
do some mercy my Mercy privilege
on my channel in my membership only
screen
where am I doing this here
but I can't hurt so bad
well they have a pharmacy now
I thought I thought I killed like free
people as well
oh
[Music]
I only feel when it's scary
oh my gosh
oh
I don't need a cue my aim is perfect
obviously I'll try to repay the favor
I awake
again
oh wait they're done
are we losing are we winning we're
winning sort of oh Mommy
I don't think they'll I mean they can
make it we'll see
now
he gave up
they're above oh
[Music]
it takes too long
I did absolutely nothing
no you look at that you can see if you
press tab you can see what you did
what did I do you healed and you had me
did damage
you're hurting them yeah you gotta kill
one kill yes
yeah yeah
[Music]
They Don't Really separate us this stuff
well if you
like hit them once and then someone else
did you do one percent of the damage and
someone else is 99 I think you still get
the kill oh
pretty sure it's very generous
hmm
[Music]
um
I'll go with her again because I don't
know how to play anyone else
to practice
it is good yeah we used her uh what is
it kunai is that what we call it yeah
I've been every once in a while I've
been trying to shoot people yeah
I think it's powerful if you hit them in
the head can we kill people
you heard that term squishy characters
I guess oh yeah
oh yeah
I'm gonna make monkey noises that's no
reason to be careful
okay it's a gorilla
yeah that's a big monkey
big buff monkey what
oh
my gosh that's the dog okay okay yeah
that I can see that
I'm disappointed
five DPS why did I die we do oh we do no
they do they have five oh they're all
squishy perfect interesting
I want to play snive or next time too oh
yeah you try Anna she heals and Snipes
yeah she's fine
oh my gosh I'm shaking
shots when killed
both more than that
damn it dang it
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm bad I'm bad
[Music]
I've been waiting I wonder if any like
viewers
make it into our groups
oh um
[Music]
I just walked in the room
I shouldn't please
oh that was a sniper
I'm scared now I'm scared don't you want
to shoot I'm so scared
a ghost that's scared oh yeah you should
be the one scaring people Monet
hey
[Music]
let me do that it sounds like that okay
hey hey
is that the remix
this Reinhardt is harassing me
where is he
okay I thought four times in this game
is always by the same person
they're in love with me that's exactly
what it means sorry I wasn't here
because you they're in love or they have
a crush
how do I get to one of you guys
um
sorry I'm mad
oh
the blood thickens
now they have two tanks
yeah
no one can hide from my sight
oh I used it too early
four times
oh I'm so happy
[Music]
oh
wow look at that noise
right oh [\h__\h] oh
come on
now to monitor its progress
ions
that door closes oh there's people out
there
we go
well have you guys ever tried cheese
corn yeah
coin what's cheese corn uh need these
out sometimes like a Korean barbecue you
can get it oh it's like uh just corn
with cheese on it it's really tasty oh
like melted cheese I don't think I had
that but I did have Korean barbecue
before Oh
maybe they have had that Korean Fried
Chicken I've had those spicy chicken the
corn
it's all good
thank you
it's okay
we're getting it pretty far we saw four
minutes so
oh yes I had Korean hot dogs have you
guys had Korean hot dogs before Oh corn
dogs yeah it's like a Corn Nut but like
even more like decorated with lots of
stuff yeah I like one of them like
overloaded though
so yummy it mixes like
Savory with sweets and it's weird yummy
for some
surprising reason wow
why are you stealing you
awesome
[Music]
no one can hide on mice
murder him oh wait I forgot you can heal
he helps
it
need to win this
oh I'm sorry
warm up I'm warming up
oh pink did I do that what what a lucky
hit
oh they're not gonna go on it yeah
they're gonna give us it they're gonna
give us like a present
thank you
[Music]
and how do you see again what you did
dab
I got an indoors
no it's gonna be embarrassing I'm gonna
miss a bunch first I bet
did I get free kills is that you the
kill which one is the kill oh come on
whatever
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven shots one kill
three heels three kills three kills
three kills I did more kills now than I
ever did before nice nice okay oh yeah e
stands for elimination
hmm
[Music]
are you screaming
you hear screaming
yes in my head every morning and every
night
it counts me
wait that might be where should I play
[Music]
uh which one was the the sniper lady oh
I'm purple
all right oh wait if you want the
healing one or the DPS one
I guess the healing one that's the eye
patch yeah
okay okay
[Music]
one again yeah payload yeah escort this
time we push it
so L shift makes people sleep
yes
an e uh replica you throw this bottle of
yellow liquid and it heals everybody
around you or yeah
it makes it so the enemy team they turn
purple and they can't get heels
oh so you could do it like if there's a
group fight going on and a lot of people
around you could feel and poison people
at the same time oh yeah so this one
wait this is you have to push the robot
this is this
thank you
all the sniper skills I got from playing
GTA finally are paying off
oh wait that's what that says
all right I'm learning this character
I'm also playing
um she heals when she shoots so is it
like for every shoot
yeah you have to heal them whoever
you're shooting yeah
oh what
oh my goodness
and so sometimes people try to jump on
you because you're the Healer and kill
you you just have to try to sleep them
yeah you probably want to stay pretty
far back
oh it has a window
surrender to my will yeah does he shoot
your teammates to heal them if you shoot
the enemy you hurt them okay get
yourself together
and you remember I'm not Soldier
that's what I like to see keep it moving
[Music]
doubled
so at least I don't have to switch
between
like it's automatically if I shoot a
friend
automatically yeah it goes from healing
okay
I don't want to see how bad my aim looks
like the Avengers
get yourself together
you see I'm only good at Amy if it's
dark outside if it's the sun has been
down for hours
breaking it down
please
no it's okay I I did this to myself
[Music]
where the heck are they I need a health
pack
I don't see a health pack I'm gonna
switch and then what oh I'm gonna die
now where the heck
we're in a circle
they're progressing faster than
anticipation what does my ulti do put
yourself together oh you can boost the
power and out of
um
if somebody has an old
combo I don't remember
thank you
the gun's still at full power
[Music]
and switch I'm not hey this ends now
oh like she was oh that's how it all
works right you right click when you
have her old
oh of course
time to put a stop to their efforts
I'm doing very badly this year
me too
it's really bad
choice
they're moving to barricade
TBH
oh
he's still got to fight in me
foreign
[Music]
oh
never mind
are you oh am I still alive
oh
okay
universe
robot is in our possession wow
oh yes if we get a chance so like
umume's ultimate she just uh like auto
aim shoots people so if you like Nano
boosted her while she had her ultimate
it'd be pretty good oh I had it active
for so long that I threw it away
that's good it's good to give it to a
tank sometimes
egg
surprise
okay
you're releasing a song cover aren't you
after this
[Music]
Girlfriend yes
you know every time I say Bales people
are like who's bail
nice
you're right
there we are
yeah so would you like to promote your
song cover mommy
please showers
[Music]
two hours let's go what is the song
wow
[Music]
can't wait to hear it I know you were
Queen
we're all clean oh yes we are yes
hurry up Amy
Jordan
our cat is like our own little small
country that we govern
or
you're right number one dog is subscribe
leave a comment like
[Music]
I was too close
eating Kiara
I was hoping no one notices how I'm
[\h__\h] around and not doing anything
that helps the group now I can heal
[Music]
um
I believe in you I don't
oh nice try oh
I run oh this is game mode
your dead skin on Diva looks cute
we don't need to see that and I'm taking
you with me yes please take me take my
hand I don't know where to go on the
line I'm lost I'm a Lost Child where am
I this is not my channel I thought this
was my channel what the [\h__\h] why am I
here who am I it's okay it's okay wrong
burp channel it's okay you are
um you are the noshi mermaid this is
Kiara
okay I want to play the sniper that
actually doesn't heal which one is that
purple maker what who oh we don't need
you yeah
it'll make it okay
who should I explain we're defending oh
I've had winter skin
so I should probably try to stay far
away right
uh yeah
leave a broken World Behind
Harmony
is riddle really perfect
whoa I'll shift oh fun she looks purple
to me
get the weight of your doubts and your
mind will become clear
do you Kiara do you feel blue or do you
feel purple
I need to find a good spot I don't know
where to go
maybe up here
stay focused
what's up
I dinged it
I don't know how to look at that
symmetra
yeah it means you can't use some of your
abilities
we're already losing the point sorry I
got really distracted
shut up I still have some fighting I'm
going to Focus now
no more goofing around
no more watching this way we now go back
goofing I saw her
no
baby
objective
hello what happened
positive thinking New York is this New
York
I said to New York I want to go to New
I've never been to New York have you
girls ever been to New York I've been to
New York it's dirty yeah very dirty
they're cute rats not as dirty as my
mind
oh
I'd save you
you're trying to try a junkrat
you were pushing that on me last time
too
yeah oh sorry you only want to play two
girls right
priorities
being spawn camped
uh we're okay I will I will I will save
the day I'm coming in today
oh
surprise junk red sometime soon I'm
gonna kind of looks like a girl
yeah if you're born
a little yeah
it's kind of cute
yeah
one that looks like a rock
another one oh
where are these
why am I yellow
[Music]
where's the
Flora
here
oh we have a junk right okay oh you're a
junkrat
poison thank you for once
I thought you were gonna lose all
respect for me if I continue this [\h__\h]
any longer
okay
yeah I think that's a really fun
no
no no no that is how you play OverWatch
again this is the freaking Sombra she's
so skinny
[Music]
I triggered him
oh no no
have you
enjoy her face
she's a good sniper this is how I should
have been playing
it's easy on attack I think so uh maybe
yeah he's on defense I can jump you
what the axle
we died together
when we die we die together
romantic
oh they killed him
okay
sorry I'm so
thank you
again a cat with a jackal Beyond
what protect me
wait what's first oh
man yeah I've never heard you in these
in this key before
not finished
yeah it helps me practice my
high notes
one at some point I'm gonna be such a
high frequency
[Music]
um
I don't know what warming is
please explain it to me uh
and when you were like I don't know
going crazy when you're losing it
sounds like that there's some from a
movie or something
it doesn't sound like a really good line
they would say in a movie yeah I had to
watch a movie
and we could still win we just need to
defend this for two minutes two minutes
okay okay okay
I see her
I'm going there so I can't go back
he knows me wait hold my game whoa okay
I'm not even mad my game is being weird
am I still alone
where's everybody
are you you're sad you're a sad human
the Genji's match I'm not killing him
where are my heels
yeah that's I'm pretty sure that's what
they're thinking
but no matter how much you heal you're
never healing enough for me I know I'm a
bad dealer never enough
[Music]
oh right now
I'm gonna die guys
you're not even pushing the payload now
they are
so annoying
I love being targeted
you were saying yay
haha
an elbow
[Music]
I think like three of them are hitting
me at the end
here to spawn
[Music]
only what first damage when ooh
next go next next Style
and see
are you guys gonna play Pokemon next
month
their new Pokemons what mermaids they're
not in the loop what world are you
living I'm not living the world of
Pokemon wait which one is it which one
the the new one wait what's it called I
probably heard about it but didn't know
when it was releasing uh I forgot but
uh scarlet and violet okay
not being announced I just I don't know
why I
oh right they have the wheels is the
Pokemon with the wheels right
yeah yeah yeah of cars yeah and now they
have a trainer that's a streamer looks
really cute mom
is it like the one where you get sent
back in time
no let me look like that
the theme is not that anymore but um
they took a lot of functions from that
game and um also added it to this
upcoming game
do you want to play that game the world
felt so like empty
oh yeah I think they probably are trying
to improve that at least
not fair don't you do it
it's a widow again widow's so popular
what's Discord doing here
uh it says Zenyatta thing and it does
like more damage if you can hit I think
along with it wait this card actually
has a meaning
yeah
into the Discord that's what he says a
word yeah
I thought it was made up for this no no
no I've never heard that news before I
only
scored the fitting isn't Discord like uh
kind of like chaos I guess that's what I
oh
don't worry I'll hold the point
please look at me my first language is
German what what
silly that's silly to me
you're like how could you not know that
word they're not even uh
I guess it is I guess they know but
still
be stopped and deuts and even in German
is like what not never using that kind
of word what the hell yeah you guys ever
use that word no that's silly no not
really there you go maybe you needed
enough
Discord make the word famous wow
no no it's a pretty common word it's
just we don't really have an opportunity
to use it I think yeah
yeah when people say like Discord and
order or something like chaos in order
if I use it I will sound more
sophisticated
I wanted to improve my English
vocabulary I push in
it
I'm sorry
never mind
his face middle name is
I'll call her Discord from now and maybe
then people will recognize who I'm
talking about
oh
[Music]
my
don't stop
okay I guess I can't no smoker I can't
scooper either I see you
sounds like I'm stacked I'm stuck
oh she pooped me
it's nice
enemy down
that's right and we'll get the next one
yeah
G
no no
oh no
no wonder
why I think I think we're with a bunch
of new PR you guys new bold bulbas Ward
are you guys new it's okay Bandos is
okay you're doing your best that's okay
I am not me
but I guess you can't predict it
we were just doing that so that they
underestimate us now
sure you guys tell me to use it I'm
never using that this dream no more Nano
no Nano challenge yeah no more Nano no
Nano November
November again it's Lisa time wait was
that November yeah no okay yeah
[Music]
mine's already in one year pass wow I
didn't realize
whoa
that's a cinematic shot of Lucio right
there
one of these days
I can't even do anything
oh sorry
there
not at the bomb
then there's a widow up there oh it's so
annoying I can play uh I can play tank
if you want to play healer Kiara
it might be good because I don't think
we have like any tank I like it yeah
okay I'm gonna play Winston I'm gonna
play with him healer now
all right wait um
[Music]
all right I'll wait for everybody
I'm gonna wait get out of here
I'm up okay
let me get on the point
oh God I take so much damage you do
indeed
[Music]
sorry I cannot
track
today too much
that's okay oh gotta get another Point
gotta get another point no I died I
played more uh I think I should have
been more uh I should have switched a
while ago
and we could have had more games
nice try I just feel like it was just
the three of us on the team it's like
we had some new players I think we were
carrying the team totally new players
I want to get a shortcut so that I I
have a shortcut like you girls
you're gonna look so cute with the short
shorts haircut oh gosh your haircut
oh
cute I want to match that would be cute
and that would be cute
get a bowl cut
it more a ball cut or a bowl of Cups
Bowl
oh
so what does what does um
oh oh someone's playing Mega strong is
playing Moira okay
what's my man am I going for I don't I
don't know hey I'm at Wagga bunga
I can't do anything you can choose first
okay
okay two healers all right
let's try Sombra
oh last match I should have played Diva
maybe that would have been good
um I should I definitely should have
played more around I was too focused on
not whole thing
okay apparently Diva got a really big
butt bub with her OverWatch two skin and
I'm really really really jealous
where's my butt bub
where is Chihuahua's butt
all right how does people get a buff and
I don't get it
even got a really much bigger butt now
you guys haven't seen oh yeah yeah I saw
that I saw it
big
it is big pretty much better
just in case
it's kind of crazy
whoa my games could it be
foreign
oh God
or he's charged I don't I barely don't
need damage if I keep leaving so
locators in place
you're dead
not very much subtracting
oh God
ah
you're a great Target
[Music]
sorry a lot of people died but we saw
the boy much better nah nah
so we only have one Healer but if you
see you could you should be able to see
like a little heel thing uh through the
map where a movie she like hacked it so
we get it faster hmm so you want to use
that one if you need to heal soon
[Music]
it's okay we'll get it back yeah we'll
get it back
oh
yeah
oh yeah when uh Pharaoh does that
ultimate that she just did to you it's
good to right click because then you
just eat all the bullets all the
missiles oh okay yeah yeah
foreign
by the way oh yeah just uh do that thing
remember you fly up into the sky and let
it go there's a point over the point
that was a bad one
trying to keep me out I don't I think
I'm gonna switch here oh just in case
[Music]
oh oh careful
what
learning not really I'm not learning
anything
my brain is empty
oh 99
hours something stupid
[Music]
sorry you guys are kind of I'm not
really doing much I don't feel like
I hacked and I'm disrupting them
I Retreat oh I'm a nice spot
oh yeah
a nice spot yeah
oh yeah squat baby squats
okay this is weird
gotta work on that butt never skip fun
day
ones
you're mine now
I'm feeling necessary
wait did I not
I did that
the objective is now active
complete
oh it doesn't count it doesn't count if
I'm invisible I can't contest it all
right
[Music]
foreign
that's crazy
before
somber to hack people and how that is
pretty crazy
[Music]
oh he probably has all
oh I'll find the back door just try to
die on it
just in case
did you ever see
owl's ears before yeah like their ear
holes
that's disgusting hey I love owls but
when I saw that actually just a couple
days
yeah but they don't look so [\h__\h]
weird and then you know because I was
curious I was looking up how other birds
um other birds ears look and they all
look so so effed up
you know oh I I I wasted my ultra no
it's fine
oh my God but you have normal hairs so
I'm I'm doubting you to be an owl
I have an owl form
oh show me show me um
[Music]
what's your excuse to not being able to
show us your owl Forum yeah
um I'll show you later
if you really want to see it
gotta get on the point
oh where's the point
man
okay we can get the next one if we lose
this one
right now
we can maybe get it
okay nice try
what
I'm not good at Sandra
you guys get to practice I practice
but should I practice when I compromise
us winning oh
what
why are you wooing because
[Music]
two to zero
but unless we're dead too
as we win we could have won it though
well optimistic you know what content
content is that yo yeah more games
you know what I hope that you keep such
a positive outlook
it's just because I have no idea what's
going on
all right all right this is the point
all right yeah this is the point round
I feel like I'm just clipping a lot
oh my gosh
I wonder if it's because of all the
stuff I have running
my game clips
oh my gosh
I'm ready for you
oh my God
[Music]
now he's dead
oh my God
it's probably because I have things
running I won't blame it on the game
using FPS uh it kind of just yeah
oh my God like there they have like a
frame drop
I guess it's a frame drop it's mostly
just with my turn
you just have three of us on the screen
so that's true
naughty
foreign
[Music]
if nobody tells me to use it then I'm
gonna use it
uh
I'm just trying to hold the boy for as
long as possible so we get more
percentage
can't get away with this
dang it's been contested for a while
yeah I was skating around the point
okay they finally got it
now we regroup gotta come back
where to I was I anyway okay
oh no
hi he came to me
[Music]
I don't want
to focused you know
one nice camera nice oh my God oh my God
sometimes you have to have company
foreign
oh nice guys
let's see
[Music]
um
we don't have to see that
huh
don't give them a platform exactly yeah
we're not gonna see how you played oh
you did something really cool we're not
gonna show anybody
it just sticks to whoever was remained
in the game
I like this map I like this map too I
like attacking on this map
yeah I like both I like defending too
I'm gonna try Sarah
yeah you could be mercy and you could be
her pocket
okay who's who's what who what who
blonde healer
yeah yeah but who who am I isn't she the
one that that's like sticking to someone
all the time
yeah
it would be called Pharmacy like a
pharmacy
you're supposed to shift to fly to her
and other teammates and then you hold
Mouse one heel and right click to do
damage boost but yeah pretty much you
probably want to heal most that and then
your e is a resurrect people are gonna
come after you a lot because you're the
Healer so you have to try to stay out of
the way
I'll try to be in the air and if you see
if you're in a pickle try flying to me
because then that could get you out of
the pickle if I'm flying
um this doesn't count we're warming up
maybe I should play when I was flying
then I play One skins
I'm in the spawn I'm gonna go out
him
oh
nice nice
there's another Pharaoh so be careful
apparently
tonight
I'm on the floor
no I'll be bad
careful wait I thought it was
it oh
yes okay nice
I'm over here I'm up
okay don't hit me there don't be don't
be good Sarah be bad Sarah I'm bad
I'm just here
I wish I could like I don't know put
some kind of glow on you so I always
find a window
I think the window
I knew she'd be silly
oh
I can't hit it I'm back right
into the air
again
oh
nice do you think I'm a Great Canadian
need help with the Roadhouse
he's trying to go for you but I'm like a
ride home behind
foreign
[Music]
oh
he was stuck
I have a sniper now I haven't had one
yeah that's true
I haven't seen her I feel like she's
been dead for the last like two minutes
oh
[Music]
um
hi Queen okay queen I'm your servant
Supreme Queen oh
50 seconds careful the sniper in the
corner oh
oh thank you Kiara you see me
then we're about to be back now
how many are there here oh shoot I
didn't realize sorry sorry I didn't
realize oh my sorry my bad uh I lost you
okay I got the payload
[Music]
Oh weird
and I Can Fly
oh
sorry I'm on the ground
I'm bad at staying in the air
there's so many others Reaper behind
not really bothering anyone
[Music]
oh yeah
we got a trap behind the door okay
don't be good
just one okay somebody at the top oh on
the payload
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
yeah you gotta be careful with roadhog
I think that was my fault
[Music]
oh I would have died if you didn't save
me yes
it feels good
I lost
it
oh I didn't know where you were
oh shoot oh shoot I'm gonna die I'm
gonna die I got stuff oh thank you I'm
good I'm sorry
mermaid
[Music]
good job
someone there my feathers are not as
good as yours what that what
are you I thought he was Resurrection
the only thing I can do is healing
oh yes hello
[Music]
I don't even know where I was
trying to fight
[Music]
um
all right
I'll get there wait where is it where is
it
[Music]
I think yeah I think so someone's behind
but I'm gonna make it yeah here
we have another two minutes
oh there's a roadhog coming behind now
[Music]
I'm invisible
60 Seconds oh I'm gonna die bye
we're on our way
look good
I use my ultimate
why am I here why am I here why am I
here it's okay it's okay
she's switching guys Jesus
for today
yeah yeah
really bad lately it sounds like a robot
and you left a little room oh that's how
you said
not much time left
[Music]
is anyone on it wait wait what wait
there's a glitch oh no you died you died
oh
no it's okay let's try a nice try I felt
like that was a window in my books
is
I think the burps flying was really tea
and I tried my best to heal almond too I
was really bad at staying in the air so
that's not your don't worry if I was no
you you needed me to stay in the air I I
messed it up for you I'll do that again
maybe are you good at yeah
oh no not really she's dying oh she's
barely holding her name wait should I go
anyways now okay
but okay robot Watson okay thank you
good luck on us the games yay
okay I wanna do more more verb verb
potato wait I can like I can move over
here so you don't you're in your corner
unless ah are you moving in an obs
yeah
yes hold on I'll move it oh you wanna
move
wait how do I do this oh I found it okay
okay
do you go
go here there we go oh wait a minute why
are we so pixely I just noticed that uh
don't oh don't worry never mind ah
um okay you want to keep playing
oh I mean I mean this is your stream so
I'm just hanging out with you as long as
you want I'm probably gonna play until
my cover release but you don't have to
if you you we don't have to stay the
whole time if you don't want to but how
much longer is that like an hour
oh
I'll play it with you before maybe half
more hour okay okay okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
can I be your mercy again sure I don't
know if I should play Pharaoh though I'm
not very good at pharah okay
um but if there is a pharaoh if someone
else plays Pharaoh you should absolutely
play mercy it's very op if whenever I
see it on the other team I go gosh
that's disgusting but when it's on mine
I'm like oh yes we're great perfect
it is it is quite a nice Dynamic now
what other Dynamics are there like that
in the game oh let me think
there's nothing that really compares to
that I don't think but if you mean like
two characters that go really well
together I don't know if one's no
because when OverWatch one there'd be
two tanks and two DPS and two healers so
when it was like that having a Winston
and a diva was really
I guess I was met up for a bit oh
probably another good one is Anna and
Genji but that's only really if Genji
has his ultimate and you old Genji when
he's ulting it makes it super powerful
yeah but none of them compared to
Pharmacy because the entire game you can
be latched from each other Pharmacy
that's funny it's cute right
who should I play
um let's see we need a heel okay we
could both be healers for this game oh
okay
when I first started OverWatch was the
first FPS I ever played oh gosh we're
behind um oh [\h__\h] I didn't realize I
could already enter oh [\h__\h] I didn't
realize either
um
yeah OverWatch was my first FPS and I
used to play mercy a lot because I think
she's really good for when you're a
beginner and you're still trying to
learn what everybody's abilities are
but it depends on what you want to do if
you want a few cubes and she's not that
fun
if you want to chill she's fine
it's OverWatch your favorite FPS game no
um
I don't know what my favorite FPS game
is it kind of all makes me feel very
negative things
you seem like you're having fun though
no I have I like playing FPS if I play
with other people
overall it's definitely used
Style
okay
they have a corridor which is super
annoying
I feel like we're only free people
where's the rest of us they're kind of
off they're separated but one guy throws
someone so that's cool
a stupid experience
I love you guys really annoying
you worked hard on that oh God
wait I'm not going to be able to kill
you
have you been enjoying GTA yeah oh my
God I'm finishing it tomorrow commercial
finale already yeah I've been like
playing it twice in a week
[Music]
yeah I'm not surprised too because I
don't know I was just gonna play it for
like one off and
have some fun with it I didn't think I
would like seriously normally when I
start serious I always do it with the
plan of finishing them
not the intention
Ally into it too
it's fun
oh really yeah
I learned a lot about cars and a lot
about oh
a lot of uh guns now I know what the
difference of a shotgun and a rifle and
the normal gun is oh interesting yeah
[Music]
oh
I don't think I do what is it wow
has a really wide and big front because
they put all the power into the front
oh yeah yeah so the front is longer than
the back
and it's pretty wide oh that's probably
not common in Europe is it
no not at all yeah never I don't think
I've ever seen one here American in
their big cars
they really do I mean some of them I
think have more purpose like uh
pick up trucks
I don't know who to heal like
everybody's like somewhere where I'm
gone sorry yeah
I'm sorry sorry
no don't you do it
I can't find my tank
oh man I let him die I'm not doing a
good job as healer can you play some
people play Moira she's a Healer but a
lot of people just try to play her as a
DPS so they don't teal I try not to do
that but I might be doing that right now
let's see
okay I will help you with my things well
at least at least now I found you all
right
oh my gosh
[Music]
communicate
but I'm never gonna join DC oh
the kill cam is just me falling down
that's so embarrassing it happens
huh um
I'm angry
I am angry
it's okay
oh
yeah
it was a bit oh you didn't eat a good
healing
yeah five thousand no four of us yeah
we're not gonna watch this guy
yeah
he looks cute though with the big beard
cute dwarf no no
torbjorn is it disgusting
you know I shouldn't still get out on
him toward my players you you watched
you you did not watch Lord of the Rings
before no no
I've seen the first Hobbit movie
you watch the first time a long time ago
I did okay
I was a little confused but yeah
[Music]
um
watch it so we have to do the watch
along is he still won I just finished
watching the this I could almost call it
spin-off I guess
um pre prequel of Lord of the Rings you
know they made a show on Amazon about it
yes yeah yeah and yesterday was the
finale so what's it together with my
viewers and it was a it was eight or
Eight Episodes I think I wasn't
listening let's do it now you have Lord
of the Rings the hobbins and
that show how much to watch how many
hours is that sold
many but happy hours very happy hours do
you think it's something I
um what I really have to focus because
if I watch stuff I'm doing other things
at the same time
I think you will want to focus yes oh
you maybe I'll just naturally Focus be
able to
where are we going tomorrow I want
people to say I watched Lord of the
Rings I have to I want to also say the
same for uh
oh this looks like a muscle cars
they're gonna be super observant of all
the cars and then what I've been doing
in GTA Honestly made me think so hard
about what car I want in the future oh
real oh he cries
no not yet but it's like um you know how
you do window shopping I was like yeah
and then I realized I have a bang for
for um old-timer like oh that's right
old time I was just word way only really
is German for cars but oh I think
yeah classic
um
oh I found the one that I really liked
in GTI I found it in real life and it's
like relatively like affordable so I'm
like Hey Y'all it's just I think the
upkeep for those cars might be a bit
difficult because maybe they break a lot
before you have to learn but worth it
and I think I would get two cars like
one normal really stinky normal boring
ass car just for the sake of having
something normal
and then the the vintage car trying to
flex and look cool
I see oh I don't know much about cars I
just yeah
really but I just kind of go off of what
mother Al recommends and she's just like
get a safe one
listening oh yeah like kind of older
ones I think are a bit outdated with
some features but she's very I mean you
don't have to go that crazy I don't know
but
um also good gas mileage is important
what's gas mileage what if so some cars
require more gas than others
oh so like if you get those big trucks
or those muscle cars they probably maybe
I'll get an electro card oh yeah yeah
that's way cheaper
one plastic good old vintage car that
reminds me of The Great Gatsby
and then an electrical car
amazing
oh okay
saves me did I well apparently the game
told me so are you sure you didn't save
me
saving each other
let's go let's drive somewhere oh now it
doesn't hurt it doesn't smell like a lot
of people
thank you
anymore
terrifying terrifying techniques
[Applause]
don't do it
you'll find when you play this game you
know this guy might do this but then you
just don't follow your instinct you go
against your gut feeling and then you
die
but they're all so close together and
they're low
I didn't play my card oh why did I do
that why did I wait
I forgot I thought that just keep
rolling by would do damage no
oh no oh God it happened
I'm holding it
at least he doesn't have multi anymore
mm-hmm
don't hurt me
all my love foreign
[Music]
neighborhood or something
oh I should go
okay
don't do it don't do it
we did it oh
wow are we are we doing better at this
game now that we're not relying on Amen
anymore
oh
[Music]
you don't see that
put that way censor it I have a very
hard time focusing on games if I talk
too much which is understandable oh very
bad and the problem as a streamer yes
exactly
so I have to say I see the right play
horse or I'm silent but
um it's okay
I look at what you mean no you're very
you're very good at multitasking though
no well no not really actually
I feel like when you play games you were
able to talk a lot about other stuff
it's RPGs are so like there's like
um so much chill time to do other stuff
um mm-hmm
am I gonna be the only tank please do
not rely on me do you want me to tank
yeah okay
um new Queen I want to try
let's see let's see
let's see
but yeah I think it's impressive too
because you're able to talk about other
things besides the game you have a
broken patience
I'm really bad at that
I have to talk about the game look
there's a cooler here there is a bunch
this is a trash can
oh and the cooler you're the cooler no
where are you oh it's not a cooler oh
it's me yeah she's cute
where are we going she is very cute we
go oh okay yeah I follow you
I want to touch your belly
actually no never mind I don't really
want to touch it guys closer look I have
a weird belly button I want to touch
real mermaid's belly all right
what's up
I don't want to be creepy
it's okay
oh my gosh this is
oh that's not our tracer
you guys should play Trace Trace is
pretty fun she's really squishy though
so she doesn't have a lot of HP so if
you get caught it's kind of easy
but she's fast she's fast so he just
keeps moving around a bunch
and
oh gosh he's here
sorry I kind of went in by myself right
now you're like
um
do we have a Healer yeah we have one
here
hello
our grass Horse by herself
oh whoa nice I'm not doing anything
my neighbor
well I don't really know what
racer can do anyway oh she can do that
and if you press e it you can go back in
time kind of so you can get health back
now I'm gonna try to explain a couple
characters to me before and I I forgot
everything it's been too long oh my gosh
there's a lot of stuff going on
is a lot of old
my game's making me mad
he has more of an MMORPG head yes that's
mean that's exactly me I used to play so
many MMORPGs
it's embarrassing but
my favorite was a game called uh maybe
two eat an eternal and Fly for Fun
they're like anime free to play anime
I was like I played every single one of
them there was a time where there was so
many coming out of those nowadays they
the only ones that get released are for
the phone but back then
I played them all I started out with
World of Warcraft style because my my
family was playing it together
we were playing it as a family
you play as a family
where are we
playing with election games oh yeah yeah
that was this really special thing in
that game that I played I don't know how
long ago so
I'm feeling 15 years ago and the thing
with that game was you were able to fly
everybody got like a skateboards in the
sky it's so cool because gold like
through continents
uh while flying
it was like brain brain explosion I need
to see this
they recently uh relaunched the game
like
uh in the new server for like solar
nostalgic fans to now play it on your
phone too but I don't know for me it's
like if I play an MMA I want to play it
on on the PC otherwise it's not the same
thing
hmm
playing stuff
at least not games we have to invest a
lot with time and stuff like maybe just
if I'm not talking or something oh
goodness
I give up
I suck at Tracer
all right wonderful that's exactly what
I expected I also play an F of 14 before
my mouse
yeah I wonder if my mouth
[Music]
because of that being a possibility I've
been forever using mice with
um
with a cable even though I have like a
really pretty Mouse without cable but I
still use the one with cable I don't
wanna be troubled with charging it I
just recently so I used to only yeah I
used to just have ones with cables and
I'm trying one without I don't really
like it more but yeah if it goes it gets
a little battery that's really annoying
I like it I am but
I think it's just good I think it's
because of the stuff running on my
computer that's making the game act
weird
oh but it's okay it's honestly it
shouldn't be that much of a difference
I'm just bad
mama how did you get into gaming I got
into gaming
ah like PC gaming
no any kind of gaming ah how did I
usually I didn't growing up I didn't
really own any of like the consoles
they're always the siblings yeah so I
had to wait until the siblings didn't
want to play but I made it so I couldn't
play a lot of games
because they didn't want me to mess with
their game
oh and I wasn't so mean I would try I
didn't really know what I was doing
sometimes I'd be in the middle of my I
became my siblings would start
[Music]
and I'd ruin it for them
um
one of my siblings she likes to play FPS
was playing Halo
and they let me play while they had the
headset and to listen to the people
talking and they were saying really
awful things and I could kind of hear it
through the headset yeah
and imagine that didn't feel too good
oh wait this is again one of those where
you uh wait we already can go towards
fall yeah that can be
three but I used to play it I used to
finish
um like some Tycoon and Roller Coaster
Tycoon
what else do your like earliest games ah
those were the earliest where like I
would spend like eight hours a day like
wow or spend a lot of time playing them
won't get you full first skip friends
birthday parties to play them
whatever I was I get sick
were you ever sick like and couldn't go
to school and then your parent would get
mad because you were playing games as if
oh no my parents wouldn't get mad
because my mom was yeah she was always
playing EverQuest too oh your mom to
play games right oh yeah right she was
at work when when I would be in school
but when she would come home she would
play have a question
ever Class 2 is also an MMO she's she
was like really into MMOs we started
with World of Warcraft and then and then
I don't know everybody got sick of World
of Warcraft except my brother and then
my mom went back to like have a quest
too and I don't know what other she's
the game I forgot about that it's like
look at a Minecraft too right
yes although she's also sick of
Minecraft now because it's not
challenging her anymore she knows
everything she's too good oh my gosh
man she still likes watching Minecraft
videos and also she always watches my my
streams always like always and then and
she always tells me play this and that
now she's pushing Mass Effect on me all
the time
that's so cute
oh my gosh and she loved my GTA playbrew
[Music]
why did it look like the monkey did a
flip
um
man my both my parents never played
video games
and that's the norm though they thought
playing two hours it was like addictions
so
[\h__\h] so wow but I feel like maybe in
the next coming Generations more and
more parents will be like
game of parents and we'll be
understanding of their children
but
yeah these two are mother I would get
really upset if she found out like if we
had a sick day and we were playing video
games which I always thought was silly
not purple sorry
um
yeah I thought it was silly because as
if being sick means you can't play video
games
I don't know no well that's what you've
been doing
just sleep for 48 hours straight
but I do have to say like I personally
understand the person because like
there's always the big red stuff the
kids like neglecting school and I'm
being too focused and in games like once
you're addicted to one of those games
oh they're definitely days I just didn't
want to go to school
I just wanted to do other stuff I didn't
want to go to school either yeah I
didn't I remember in summer holidays we
here in Austria we had like three months
of summer holidays no joke insane and uh
I would play my MMO like
and that was the day insane
did you say it and yeah because like I
think at some point in some summer of
the holiday
um a new MMORPG like launched and I was
like
um in my class I was number one
um in the wreck so yeah every day I was
grinding the level so I could stay
number one
because I was so proud I I loved joining
MMORPGs at the launch time because that
gave me a chance to be number one at
something
I gotta have that like a sibling rivalry
because usually for games since I wasn't
really allowed to play games for
a good bit oh
um
I always wanted to be better than my
siblings but they had like a head start
you know there's one game of where I
had higher scores
Temple Run which is like a phone game
Temple Run never heard of that maybe
I've seen them before but now that
you're saying I don't remember the very
simple simple game it was the one game
where I had the like was way ahead of
all of them so I kept at it
no you can't I don't think it's
something you can stream it's it's
really it's just on your phone and you
use your finger to slide
there's probably other games like please
what oh my God
I'm kind of useless right now like
the real wind was the conversations we
made along the way exactly yeah
[Music]
your song cover comes out
hello big monkey
s
yeah yeah
oh my goodness
when you wear your smile I did play it I
did play soon yeah the one other game I
played besides MMR pictures
no windows
I I would play it on my Mac laptop
and I just like have it on my lap and it
gets so hot
oldy laptop yeah
which one was the first you played which
Sims
um I think this very first one I played
was Sims 2. oh my first one was Sims one
that was so crazy
it's like you played two buttons in hard
mode really difficult like what makes
the digital call like what happens if
you're not good you die or do you
programmed in a way that your Sims will
just not be able to properly take care
of themselves even if you try to control
them it's just it's just so
just so possible to make enough money
and then the the house is always a
[\h__\h] mess and then the Sims are
really unhappy and then they go to work
on happy and then I don't know
people make challenges out of playing
Sims one because it is such a challenge
in itself
oh gosh
yeah I've never played that one but the
one I played the most was Sims 3.
oh
because I don't think I think when I
place Sims 2 I still had access to a PC
I think I played that one on PC but then
when I have some mac only I think I
would play
the three
yeah Sims Freight was actually a quite
special to clubs that's the only time in
Sims history from Sims 1 to Sims 4 when
I implemented the feature that you can
put uh you can change
every pattern of every and everywhere
yeah every furniture and every piece of
clothing and so on right all right
you can change everything that's how you
like it it's not like that until before
right
I know it's not also I think Sims 3 was
like kind of the open world-ish kind of
you know
oh
yeah you can explore the whole map
without a loan Sprint and I'll take them
free I'll add the thing with the cars as
far as everybody
will have their own cars I think
that they also removed again with Sims
4. they removed so many things of Sims 4
that they actually like revolutionized
with Sims 3 so it's kind of sad but
there's Vermont said Sims 5 is going to
be announced soon remains
it's been a while since the since Sims 4
released
a [\h__\h] ton of expansions
actually when did Sims 4 come out
ah on my list but at least five years
ago maybe more
[Music]
difficulties feeling time yeah
it wasn't 2014.
that's pickle Sims 4 released eight
years ago it's about time for Newton
I'm kind of worried like
how they're gonna make the Sims look
like because I feel like from Sims one
Sims 3 systems crazy before they've
really changed the look of
yeah and too realistic makes no sense
even for Sims like I want to say
realistic Sims right
do you like downloading Adventure mods
mermaid mermaid the darkness inside you
I never downloaded them I just watched
like the videos you know where it's like
a story that they make
uh
you like really small I don't know if
you could even call them mods but like
there was some kind of like cabinet that
when you like a medicine cabinet then
when you click on it you can do certain
things oh yeah like um you can voice
your sim to have twins or or triplets or
so I would do that sometime
yeah I've seen it that's it
I haven't really watched one through but
I've seen that there's videos of like
100 baby challenge or something oh yeah
that's yeah without the mod you can't do
that because the maximum amount of Sims
you can have on a lot was like eight or
something
yeah but it's it's really hard on your
game if you want to have 100 babies it's
insane I was one of those people who
didn't really play the Sims like I did
but what I would do is I was I would
design the entire town so I'd kick every
like all the default Sims out of their
houses and place ones that I made and
then I like build my own houses
now I never end up playing the game like
the actual game you know
um
okay you just wanted to make houses I
wanted to make the houses and The Sims
and I was I like was thinking this
entire story like this is how this
family is this is how this family is
this is how they're gonna interact when
I play the game that I just never ended
up actually okay my intention was to
play it and then I just I had a cinnamon
problem I would always make a new family
than play without a break for two days
and then never catch it for a couple
months or weeks for now I always make a
new family because I I never continue
playing with the same family I'm ashamed
no that's how I was
because the creation part is like pretty
much the most fun thing yeah especially
in Sims 3 where you could customize
everything
yeah
oh my gosh yeah so
sorry I gotta Focus right yeah I told
you I can't talk it's okay it's okay
let's we were so bad last round we
should at least try this time
misery
[Music]
do you ever listen to K-pop I used to
listen a bit but like not very much and
it was
not very much and I don't know any
Koreans I can't sing along or even think
the name of the songs are
what what do you remember what group or
so I think guys listen to twice a little
bit
[Music]
oh
it's like oh it's like likey one I think
I like it
yeah
because I don't know how to dance and I
couldn't figure it out I gave up that
one's really old is it
for at least like a million songs since
then I found I think when I listened to
that that was a new one
I'm pretty sure you haven't listened for
a long time I'm gonna send you some new
twice songs okay I also I listened to
the blackpink
but they also released new songs just
like or like an EP a couple days ago oh
I think I heard one of the new songs but
maybe I shouldn't comment on people shut
down
oh
yeah
wait
I don't know where to go I'm just kind
of
stuff I think that I got shut down right
there
where are we going it's getting man I
want to learn how to dance that was when
it came to like between acting dance
dancing and singing
oh for dancing I can tell you that like
you can always learn a choreography or
so it will take you quite a while if
it's like a first time or so but um
the thing is you have to like
keep it up and then at some point you
will understand how to use your body
properly
all right
yeah like you will think that oh you're
doing the moves correctly but in reality
it's really not you probably need a
mirror like you have to do in front of a
mirror probably
yeah that helps and you it doesn't have
to have someone like oh teaching yeah
like watch properly like understand
how it works and you gotta start like
simple from scratch
not something too difficult don't
overestimate yourself
left right left right even dad
I'm telling you you can do wrong like
I've seen I've seen people try to
imitate idle steps um and they think
they're imitating it properly but it
looks so different still like there's
different different types of idle steps
you know
[Music]
I mean all kinds of people I've seen so
many
I watch a lot of like
like K-pop and J-pop dance covers
Vocaloid dance clubs and stuff and also
real people dancing Idols dancing in
training
doing a great job
it was a pleasure
hi mine is there by top Idol okay
oh gosh
where's everybody I can't find I'm gonna
push it
in here
no one can hide
what money is done by it it's a skater
what
is she a skater boy did she says
evidence
oh no this is gonna die that's good they
should dive over there
these are new maps and I don't even
really I don't know them
what are you doing I get lost
oh thank you mercy no that's my Mercy
come in there
no
[Music]
mommy are you winning
oh no
[Music]
oh but you killed him oh you got Bob
that's important
I think I killed him by it but
what's happening
am I just like losing super badly
well we will be fine
I Believe in Us this is fine I believe
oh God it might be a bad spot so I don't
know what is going on there
oh that looks weird
I'm scared I'm
bad I'm bad I had so many opportunities
and I blew them all
my opportunities out the window who may
carry me I can't I'm bad
who else is gonna carry me money
[Music]
yeah
switch
oh my gosh
oh look at that ah she looks like she's
roller skating while crying out I don't
know I know what you guys mean
do you do any sports any workout
I'm not a physical activity
[Music]
oh no this is not looking good for us
you walk your animal at least I think
you go outside more often than me
because of that simply because of that
yeah I'm outside a lot but actually you
know working on that muscle and whatever
probably not cool
I probably I should but I'm still
standing I don't know I don't like going
new places
and the gym would be a new place so and
my animal's not good for it like she
used to be okay if we would jog
but she's not
he wants to sniff everything
[Music]
oh nice
um
we have to follow the the running dude
oh
I think we're gonna win because they
didn't make it past summer
before the mercy had it out for me
kept on shooting me I didn't even see
her
[Music]
I'm coming
at least oh this fight felt pretty like
like we were on the same level as the
enemies hmm well a lot of the time I was
on
me all right Mom I'm Gonna Leave You Now
okay thank you for playing
thank you
thank you I hope that everybody listens
to lumi's new song cover oh yeah
yes me and Mrs Bales I forgot I have to
still cook um oh no good luck
okay you're like me I also cook really
late
after history
it's half past midnight I was I was
cooking until like well I do meal prep
so I was doing that to like one or two
yesterday oh well meal prep yeah I like
to cut all the veggies at once
oh for like the whole week or so ah yeah
about the whole week
I've seen that in videos before that's
kind of like relaxing they cut
everything put it in in plastic boxes
yeah
exactly I have a bunch of chopped onion
and peppers and cauliflower and Brussels
sprouts
I've never I've never tried make like
baking cauliflower before so it's a new
thing I'm gonna try
and I prefer broccoli broccoli yeah
broccoli's good all right for a recipe
but yeah have fun cooking thank you
thank you and I wish you a good evening
and your chat too good evening everybody
good night and enjoy it enjoy the rest
of my you can have her now I'll leave
her to you guys take care of her okay
don't lose her she gets lost sometimes I
do
yeah please help me she forgets who she
is I forget
food
who would
bye bye bye
bye bye bye yeah
[Music]
what does this look like oh gosh I'm
really big hold on I'll fix myself
I'm sick of being pixely I don't want to
be pixely anymore
there we go okay I'm gonna play one more
I wonder if
um
uh it'll be less clippy but yeah I'm
happy happy I got to play with other
people
I'm happy I'm playing by myself isn't as
fun
[Music]
that's nice like being able to talk to
while playing however it probably makes
my gameplay suffer a lot
but I much rather gonna lose I would
much rather talk to them
so I'm happy and we won quite a lot yeah
it's been good
oh no
but if I use text chat I'd write in the
text chat you all suck
just kidding I wouldn't do that
I get priority because I suffered
mm-hmm
let's see let's see
I want to try to do one more one more
and then is it possible can I can I
redirect to myself I forgot how you
redirect throttle
I'm gonna try on I wonder if it's gonna
clip
really you should be able to okay shoot
I also have to set up Bae and I are
gonna stream like 30 minutes after it
eliases
what
can I be honest with you guys
I don't know what we're gonna do
last time when we had the after party we
were like what should we do
we play an animal themed games and we're
like yeah let's just doodle
this time like we just doodled animals
this time we're Queens
but I don't know what we should do like
holes people I don't I didn't think it
through and Bay has a collaboration
what
blah blah she's a collaboration with uh
one more mission after
we're back to back to back today oh my
goodness
I haven't even made a thumbnail
you guys have any ideas
what's the queen of them the thing we
can do
so now
play cards
no no chest
a card game
there's like I could play Go Fish
ing sir will you just like goldfish
yeah
I
used to love playing goldfish
I thought I would still love it
oh
live everybody don't die don't die don't
die
be careful
don't die
I feel like somebody I know you do but I
want a good night
I love you keep fighting
I'm here
maybe the tip the top tippity toppings
are on the point sorry I can't help you
if you're behind a wall
oh
[Music]
thank you
can you kill them are you capable
[Music]
I need nothing
um
that's why you don't know
I was supposed to not ever Nano
oh that's ours
you
hit him oh my gosh life's unfair it's
the game it's not my fault
Mommy
I did nothing wrong
what the
oh I think
[Music]
well that feels bad
maybe I should play more uh I still have
some fight to me their DPS is fine
but they're not really um
I'm just dying
I can't help you over there
we have three things no wonder that we
have so much damage done
yes I help you
increasing
I'm crazy
let's see
oh gosh
three things and one Healer
this is sure to go extended
[Music]
what do you mean
shut up
oh wait I'm trapped no I'm not trapped I
am trapped oh
right now
[Music]
go back
oh
[Music]
um
you silly
they're not on it
can I please
not again don't do it to me
hi
thank you Sombra
thank you thank you okay four minutes
two
hey
go down from there
I see you
get up there oh
[Music]
no I thought he opened it earlier
interesting
come on
okay
[Music]
come on
up close
[Music]
all right no no
good
somebody there
I thought I'd be more feel more
caffeinated by now don't do it
I'm not with the team
[Music]
um
oh man
oh sorry I wasn't even silly
that was moving super silly I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry
[Music]
oh it feels bad if I canceled that
Reaper we probably would have gone sorry
my bad Minecraft
oh my first playing today but it's okay
I had fun I'm glad I got to play please
[Music]
see
how do I do this how do I do this
um if this this is here okay and I take
this
I'll figure this out do you have no I
have to Google it how do you redirect
YouTube streaming
huh oh okay I have to go here
I see it
pretty direct velocity to keep your ears
engagedical okay I think I set it up
properly
all right I'm gonna send you guys to the
cover Premiere Leia and I sing Queen
and I hope you like it I hope you listen
to it I hope you like it and I hope I
wake up by the time being a stream
together yeah we'll have a we'll have an
after party
and I'll start working on that now how
do I save this let's see
there we go save
all right
see you there baby
go leave bye bye