I know
hi hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
um
look at our pixel ladies look at the oh
god
oh yeah oh God that's tragic
ladies can I get a hell yeah I've seen
worse I've seen worse before can I get a
distorted Hill yeah
am I pixelated no no no
fancy right
okay good
there is help not always help
there is hope
all right everybody did you like our
outfit reveals
oh you're so fancy fancify yeah
yeah party party party
dresses uh me I guess or something like
that yeah I want to go to a pretty fancy
party
and to kick off being extra fancy we're
gonna sit around and play jackbox
party games
martini
you know what fancy drink are you
drinking do you think I got a fancy uh
San Pellegrino sparkly colored sparkling
drink what is that what's that Sam
peregrino yeah it's illuminata
lemonade
for mature adults right no it's it's
normal mixed it's not good what's your
fancy drink tap water
that's so fancy I know isn't it come on
you could have come up with something
H2O
Powerade there's probably like some
drinks with Gatorade and avocado in it
yeah probably yeah that sounds dangerous
mixing potatoes really good in
celebration of the Christmas markets
opening up again in my place uh I'm
drinking Christmas Market punch
blood
it's wine I don't drink blood why would
why would the Grim Reaper drink blood
juice
I'm not a vampire you bigger
uh I was actually telling Callie how
funny it was when she afk's and her face
just looks like she's huffing into the
wine glass I'm reading the internet
she's breathing in the wine
swirl it around and then toss it out and
then pour some more yeah
like spit it out and then pour in some
words
there's a spit bucket for for Cali we're
going on this side now I'll pass it over
um
the guy that eats the vanilla ice cream
meaning
so we're gonna play some quick lash I
want to start with Whiplash and then
there's two other ones that we want to
play and something to do with talking
and something to do with beat em up
drawings which you've done before oh oh
yeah
and at the at the very end there's an
announcement I think we can say no
no no yeah
wait until the end for a nice
announcement
yeah start the game yes
again how's this work again we're
supposed to be funny
foreign
yeah make me laugh entertain me going
into maximum valley girl oh boy
hmm
okay wait this one already this one has
the right answer though I don't know if
I should answer the right answer no
I don't know why I'm rhyming oh man why
am I rhyming in my answers no don't do
this why not welcome to Zeus oh I got so
much time
is not awake
but I wake it up
[Music]
I need a funny answer
um
okay I'll go with my first spot it's
really bad but let's go with My Little
Pony guys [\h__\h] stock
[Laughter]
let's go
oh no just be comedians all right oh
this is a good one comedians
oh God why do I always start with
Whiplash
my brain that's pretty funny I'm not
gonna lie oh yeah
we know you're funny
guys sorry you do sound different but
you sound beautiful gorgeous temporary
setup at the moment but don't worry
everything's that job
they're all gorgeous
oh I'm not bad um
thanks for being ground pounded by
Amelia
um mom says I'm dead
then rhymes
oh that rhymes doesn't it right
yeah
that's pretty good
oh
[Laughter]
my God
holy [\h__\h] oh no the Halloween myth
country
[Music]
yes
oh my God it's too strong
sorry I had to do it
oh
[Music]
oh my God
[Laughter]
we got a wrapper on our hands
oh no I didn't answer oh no yeah
I could only think of Rhymes right now
oh wow
I'm anime woman get it
how funny whatever oh my God what if
it's not a great forehead though sweet
I'm hiding a humongous forehead
forehead I'm going with facts
potentially eyebrows or not
balding
but you are bald
you're bald underneath your skin I mean
[Music]
oh yeah not every deadbeat has I'm sorry
dude
what does that mean
s like when there's like props in the
middle of the room and then everyone
gathers around and they're like drawing
it I don't understand
what Kelly watch
[Music]
my brain
and I guess
look you're the funniest
joke no that's a glitches
oh my God the Matrix the points are
doubled oh I gotta come back this is my
come back round oh no
oh how mean can we be with this oh gosh
um
[Music]
though of course
um
hmm
okay I don't know what to say no I'm
going I'm gonna I'm gonna not be mean
huh I'm sorry
[Music]
was there a chance to be mean
sting
I I I I stayed uh loyal to whole life
and uh um get some advertising
go home live let's go
you guys have 15.
I give up good eye you're not inspired
today no I am I am uh
I'm just put butter in right now
[Music]
yeah bring them out bring them out
what happened
is freezing
I try let us set sail with
sexy Halloween costume for a kid with an
old soul this is mean for a kid that's a
boomer of a with an old soul okay show
some love
I mean both are pretty accurate I wonder
who wrote that one
no she's not in punching distance so I
can't reach but
are you sure what
oh
really nice wait did any of us I forgot
to vote
[Music]
hey
I could have I didn't I didn't want to
be mean I had a really good answer but I
just
you should have said it yeah
you could have blamed it on the line
did you guys hear guys hear a polo Aroma
the critically acclaimed award-winning
oh yeah
I want to send I want it to be the scent
of road road yeah
him on a motorcycle the only thing
preventing kiwawa from being a
globetrotting secret agent who says I'm
not already a globetrotting
that's why there's travel restrictions
[Laughter]
Whiplash 66 Devil's number Stephen
King's resume oh
come on
disrespectful Stephen King really read
a little Savage who doesn't read
I'm sorry
I know I know who [\h__\h] Stephen King
is
I know who Stephen King is I didn't feel
like giving an answer
wow
oh wow
it's the continuation of eth you might
be watching his dream he might be crying
now and shambles
money seems like a silly lad
[Laughter]
he out of first they don't belong there
yeah
oh yes
I totally didn't do one
um
against me crazy right wait what what
Channel your inner Adam Sandler
yeah just think about old Adam you'll be
fine hmm
uh
oh no
oh this isn't even mean huh
oh man
uh
um
shouldn't it be funny oh yeah that was a
good one chat that was a good one
this is hard I don't know 30 seconds
okay
oh
okay okay I think that's pretty pretty
decent no please just write something
okay you know what I went for a really
low hanging fruit and you know hello
it's fun yeah it means like you went for
the easy you took the easy way yeah
often wins
yeah you gotta appeal no no-brainers
huh
[Music]
I wonder
realistically speaking I would probably
go for the left side if I had to Google
anything yeah you personally are
Googling
personally personally
everybody I wonder who wrote that
committee
my friend is funnier than you Schmitty
Schmitty was that was a butt dancing oh
I didn't know this one oh
[Laughter]
um
playing computer games
I like that uh even though they probably
just couldn't think of a third answer
[Laughter]
about it
bad boy you know
must be I don't sound like what
I'm trying to do it
wow
take your meds Chad oh my God
sorry um look how smart
no I
know
like my grind set
um
no
why did you vote for that
one I didn't get it till now winner
winner who's the winner wow okay
oh I'm stable in the middle oh nice
um Everybody golf clubs
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was good it was funny that was good
I laughed real good yeah maybe we should
play another one after we play like a
different uh game like come back to it
or something yeah if you wanna I wanna
do this thing The Prompt one next
you guys you just listen to the
instructions when they're talking about
it because you kind of have to do
something like so you know it's a new
game mode and stuff so people might be
confused I'll be confused okay
explain it it's like a presentation
except you have a partner who picks your
pictures and so you come up with like a
sort of prompt and then you have to sell
it
um whatever the prompt is and then the
beer partner picks the pictures to go
along with it and you just have to
improvise with whatever they pick team
Incorporated okay yes and then and then
everybody else gives feedback on your on
your presentation
that's gonna probably be a funny fail
but okay
all right uh
uh hello comedians hello hello
oh shoot okay hold on wait we get a new
code right yeah yeah yeah we're gonna do
a new card we gotta do a new game card
hold on
[Music]
oh no
oh like this
okay the next game we're gonna play
we're gonna set it up real quick
[Music]
okay
all nice pictures okay let's see okay we
are starting the next again
do not take a picture it might use like
if you have a camera because what okay
pick one just do pick a picture yeah
[Music]
it says take your photo don't click that
oh
okay we're ready they're gonna see I'm a
skeleton oh [\h__\h] it's really just like
okay
no good webcam
I'm ready
start the game me yes you are the VIP oh
my God I hear oh wow okay
looks like we have a real Bevy of
respected expert speakers
for each other
okay speech titles on your devices
finish the three speech titles you've
been given okay on the blanks with
something interesting oh
weird uh oof
hmm
um
[Music]
oh God I'm so sorry this is so bad I
wish I could be
um
uh uh
but am I so fast you already done yeah
help me um wow imagine being a real
comedian
um it's just I think these are just
options for people to choose from for
like their prompts okay yeah so it's not
gonna like show all of them on screen
maybe okay
on this
uh
oh God I can't
do it you can't I couldn't I can do it
15 seconds left on the clock almost 10
seconds 11 10 9 5 8 7 5 6
I hear that it makes it uh funnier
my presentation
oh my God I think I got Cali's
as one of my choices
oh I'm sorry
this is your guys's presentation you're
gonna sell this okay sell it this is
your improv problem it's just a
statement though how do I sell a
statement
all right
example oh boy
my lovely assistant hello
assisted when you see a text slide read
that text out loud as part of your talk
oh don't go it's behind us I'm sorry can
you see a picture you see HV until
something like six all right could it
you know draw and type on slides what am
I doing you're picking a text and
um pictures for me to incorporate into
my presentation so I'm really counting
on you here
I've got your back I like you too
I missed on my heart don't worry I'll be
something hot why do you trust me with
our life don't worry
picture and that's the good stuff on the
summer meanwhile
should I say anything do I get to say
something oh no you get the floor I'll
just no no yes oh so this is confusing
so the more you press it the better you
think the presentation is so don't
forget to press your button you know
Italian Kiara press the button
aggressively yes aggressively what if I
just want to support you so I want to
press fancy the slides oh yeah yeah yeah
and even if I don't think it's any good
I'm exciting four three two one oh hello
my name is Watson and my talk is
double your income with hard work
perseverance and anime girls improve
yourself today by watching hello live
oh
do you ever just feel like you want to
ask murder people well just don't just
don't and instead instead uh fill your
days with Hollow live
yeah
um before you think of defying me heed
this warning chat don't understand
if you ever have kids they probably
won't love you
um unless you watch hollow life today
uh so so you're probably asking yourself
what does the future look like with
Hollow live and anime girls and nfts and
everything that's happening today
um well you see it can be pretty
confusing your brain's out in the open
there's so much information coming in
from the internet but uh hollow life is
like spreading a nice slab of butter all
over your brain and it just it's so
comforting because there's it's so
greasy and delicious so you love hollow
life just like butter
flaws
thank you
wow
[Music]
engaged no excuse me
was more um convincing
uh okay okay I'll remember that for next
time uh
there we go
I don't know
by me I'll do my best
to look at the stuff that she gives me
until I actually like until like right
now until it's happening okay yeah
oh dear
uh what do I look at hello my name is
Kiara and my talk is
don't tell anyone yeah I would have
never guessed uh um yes it's a secret I
am actually not this well whatever uh
what type on your slide Ah that's right
a single Adventure don't tell anyone or
you will suffer
yes
here's an interesting thing
um what what the hell is that
you gotta think on the spot here's an
interesting thing I am the person on the
left but when I am streaming I am the
person on the right yes I can become
anything I can be that Bubblegum [\h__\h]
but I can also be the skater boy see you
later boy
um Bubble Gum [\h__\h] yes
I love that all of human history has
been building up to this next thing that
I'm going to say
I am
[Laughter]
thank you
uh I mean I thought it was great
I thought it was fantastic
remember to leave your comments multiple
reflection in the comments yes I I need
your feedback to improve myself for the
future
that was amazing assistant thank you Mrs
assistant
I like this one this is fun
oh seems hard challenge
yes next speech all right
okay okay
[Applause]
I don't have to think much about this
right yeah
because my name is taco and my talk is
to get sweet revenge of my haters I have
spent a lifetime training at the anime
protagonists
what
[\h__\h] the haters
yeah sometimes
you feel like you live a life alone
no arms just like a snake however you
gotta believe
you gotta believe that you will one day
become a dragon to fly in the sky
instead focus on the super negatives
such as
the chairs you realizing that your money
is burning and going down the drain as
you live your life
will never get back
the money that your your haters are
gonna earn but you know a lot of times
you gotta
what
no well you can draw on it oh yeah oh
man you can steal money from your from
your enemies what does this mean for
humans
means
that they have a small brain and in the
end
I the anime protagonist
oh
you are okay again
you okay I get it now big engagement for
that thank you
understandable have a nice day
oh
oh I really like the big brain slide
was very fitting
thank you you're welcome I tried the
best to help you with this one yeah big
brain stands
huge craniums unite let's go let us here
my name is and my talk today is
yes
after 25 years as a hollow life fan I
learned some important stuff
I
could five years of whole life I've
learned that being a YouTuber is
literally nothing more than being a dog
with a tin can to its
ears uh
a funny animal
voice
oh I had to go much deeper much much
deeper the vtuber hole is incredibly
deep uh so so deep here is where I went
uh did you know that koalas eat an
octopus you would know that if you
watched my favorite YouTuber koala
look
at the name
YouTuber debuting uh debut on January 30
seconds did you know that Cooper eats a
lactobus she's very sleepy all the time
oh look so soft yes she's also kind of
Moody anyway if you leave here
remembering one thing about being a
YouTuber it should be this ladies and
gentlemen banana
is not
it doesn't bring you the money does it
buy banana coin
potassium
is absolutely gone do not buy banana
coins
bananas should stay thank you have a
nice day thank you for coming to my
YouTube thank you thank you but I have
two banana coins what little it does
hold on okay
like that
who's up next who could it be it might
be me
oh
boy what is a common Street
hello my name is fancy Mori and my talk
is welcome to my morning talk
today
um I'm gonna talk to you about when I
was your age I wish someone had told me
donuts po what the [\h__\h] does that even
mean
it sounds to me like somebody forgot to
finish the [\h__\h] title
is not cool anymore nor is it ever cool
let's talk about the art of
forgetfulness everyone
that's fine it's really not though you
should before you leave your house
sometimes you wake up in the morning not
feeling much like P Diddy but you do
feel like a panda I forgot that dabbing
was never cool don't do this kids how is
the season possible I wonder and
somebody could have forgotten to write
the title
well it all has to do with a thing
called drugs you guys
um
some say the bad for you
I agree some say they kill you I agree I
know something about that I've seen it
happen more than once I've seen it
happen more than twice in fact some
would say that that's me on the bottle
right there Skull and Bones that's my
Oshima you recognize that there that's
my Oshi Mark lad a pony
so you represent poison I pretty much do
yeah but then everything changed guys
why
oh
cats on the screen
get the job done you see this cute
picture of a cat
makes you want to click doesn't it yeah
even though somebody forgot to title the
name of this presentation you want to
click up why because cute cats on the
screen yeah
motivate a cat make you feel ladies
thank you that is the end of my
presentation
seems my finger is too slow they took me
oh my goodies
he's Watson
you'll appreciate it yeah leave me some
comments let me see the feedback Watson
you did great I'm gonna give you a good
rating
yeah
you're done with a different picture at
the end but I really like the cats
what is Donuts Poe who is responsible
for that why did you pick him you can't
get it picked for me oh you're supposed
to pick it yourself oh come up with a
funny name for the bigger one we'll give
out a funny name for the award come on
Kelly you can do it
finish it off and finish it all this job
oh wait
oh I got it oh wait a word that you will
give out oh uh oh
okay
I don't know
uh you get to pick I think you give it
to
like one of us the donuts
[Music]
come on
oh I wanted to read your comments
[Music]
okay
at least you guys you get the gist now
so I think you'll do better this time
okay hold on we're gonna start a new
game guys real quick
if we crash the servers
alive
okay one two three
four
oh okay
I like to imagine the one person that
you play this game with that like
actually takes a picture of their face
like you have all of these like pictures
of different avatars and then you have
the one friend who like you get a camera
pick of like just below their chin and
they're like looking down like the
double chins all right you guys ready
did I press ready ready yeah ready okay
all right
let me disappoint you all no yup I'm
ready last time you killed it you
converted me all of you I was Donuts
let me guess
good job all right it said so much
titles on your devices finish the three
speech titles you've been doing fill in
the blanks with something unexpected
have fun with it
oh God should I
uh
interesting
oh
okay oh
no
[Music]
no thank you you're welcome Jack box
oh you guys have a lot of times
baby we are warmed up
here oh thank you yeah okay the code
sorry
um j-y-n-j
[Music]
a bunch of code monkeys in the [\h__\h]
now Coldplay one of the titles that has
been sent to your device this will be
the title here's my name
this is nice thank you for whoever put
my name in a prom title
oh yeah
it's hard to pick are these are you guys
are getting good at this game we're all
getting good at this game I thought a
little better about mine oh boy
[Music]
should I when you see a text yeah
okay
hello ladies and gentlemen wait
I forgot like yeah it is hi okay thank
you for coming to my speech
hello my name is
am I a talk today is about the very hot
trending trending topic of
how to transform your whole life
turtle with rockets you and else can
have Rockets you if you tie them to your
feet you might also lose your toes you
see the the projectory of this object is
straightforward which could also be the
trajectory of your life
potentially if you decide to boot up
things that adventure and go from flabby
Couch Potato to
really fast turtle
let's see what else you might ask
yourself why why would I need to play
ringford Adventure I'm perfectly fine
being a couch potato well the reason why
why if you do not get your ass off the
couch your body will begin to consume
itself this is stage one of your body
consuming itself please please no these
teeth these are not baby molars these
are adult teeth here look down at your
head chat do you see that stage one
to sing
it's only it's downwards from here you
guys you know what else is awful let's
see what else uh who who can we call to
fix this potential problem
oh it could be Ghostbusters it could be
it could be uh who else could it be
um not your dog don't call him because
your dog likes the taste of Flesh so
unfortunately
because it's not harmonizing
uh if you don't if you
listen play ringford Adventure if you
don't either you'll consume yourself or
your dog will or your dog will
oh boy
thank you have a nice day thank you
yeah
so half of your score comes from
engagements
hey wait I was clicking the whole time
least engaged fine collaborate words
I thought it was a great my glasses fell
off I fell out of my eyes
thank you
favorite yeah you're welcome I ate with
the last picture I was a pick between a
centaur and a dog and I thought maybe it
tied in because like the hand was there
all right a centaur yeah what is that is
that horse yeah yeah it was like a
Horseman saluting on a mountain top I
almost I had that one
hello everyone my name is kiava and my
talk is
the important topic of
drum roll please yes okay okay here we
go Birds computers
these things are all United by that's
right Kiara
it's all all connected in the end don't
no this is not anything you need to cry
about this is a good thing because by
connecting all of these things you will
be Invincible only only if you support
the YouTuber takanashi Kiara if you like
birds if you like computers if you like
pizza at least one of these things I am
sure you like also we are not a cult but
the overlap between Birds computers
Pizza can be Illustrated in one single
image guess what guess what it is a box
but
you will have to think outside the box
because the real excitement is not in
the box and unless you have a box fetish
have you heard it have you ever heard
about that this is what happens if you
don't watch takanasikiara I I recommend
you two oops what the hell Two Notch
watch The Box watch Kiana in closing I
should mention the fourth thing that
birds computers and pizza are also
United by is
please
uh
Nails on toast because who wouldn't like
to nail someone on toast
[Music]
we all love that yummy fluffy bread in
the morning but we also love it at night
time this is it this is all we ever
dreamed of but in conclusion watch
takanashi oh
laughs
I mean are we really supposed to try to
help each other
whoa wow
fantastic you killed it well it was
definitely this one
why a long shot thank you thank you that
was impressive I felt inspired I felt
like I was not even myself anymore you
got a standing ovation I saw it
now their body experience oh hell yeah
let's go all right
oh
[Music]
I don't know how I'll do I'm gonna give
you a joke
hello my name is Taco in my talk
is
yes
how to talk to your parents about your
crippling Minecraft and thinking oh oh
so Corona should listen up
well now I would like to First say
that Minecraft is not an addiction it's
a lifestyle
and just like this uh this meerkat in
the sand you too can be in the desert
biome on a vacation in your computer
don't be ashamed
yeah
there's no way to stay this next Point
nicely so I won't
yeah tell me talk about it lay it on me
you know everyday life gives you so many
tasks that you don't want to do and they
pull up on you sometimes you feel like
you're being suffocated by all documents
and all the paperwork of life
but no with Minecraft with Minecraft
this is just a fantasy
with Minecraft no more paperwork
Minecraft addiction now
don't worry about a minute
okay okay but what does this mean for
you for you and you were there and you
amazing carrots
are you gonna make a best carrot farm
that you can ever make an automated
carrot Farm okay
and that will solve all your problems
because Minecraft as I said before is
not
an addiction it's not a game it's a
lifestyle and you too will believe in it
you too will build that carrot Farm you
too
will become one with Minecraft thank you
nice
engaged I guess I'll go upstairs
yeah but those two Minecraft
carrots
[Music]
good ratings Kiara
oh thank you
those are some pretty impressive
pictures I
like to be the person like stuck in that
room with paper
it must have been funny to take that
picture for that dude yeah we had a
great time okay Watson show smile all
right
enough please take care of me I'll do my
best
I don't remember what I picked
uh okay hello everybody Welcome to my
presentation uh my name is Watson and my
talk is instead ah Isabella instead of
giving in to despair given to
conspiracy okay I'm giving it already do
you ever think hey math is really
freaking hard well let me tell you that
that is actually all planned and math
isn't real
good yeah they they want to teach you
math to distract you from what's really
going on around you and I bet you're
wondering I mean what is really going on
around me can I trust math should I be
doing math should I be teaching my kids
math and the answer is definitely no you
don't need math and here's another
unpopular opinion
do you believe in magnetism and
Compasses well no it's actually actually
that is all made up that's right they
made that up as another distraction to
distract you from the real problem and
now at this point I bet you're also
asking yourself but I'm at what is the
real problem and it's right there on
that picture the future that's right
there's been time travel happening and
they've been trying to distract you with
the map and the magnetism and the moon
but thankfully
thankfully I have the answer save us on
me
hello Familia goats okay guys goats you
guys need to stock up and is on as many
goats as you can because the uh the
pheromones that goats release can
actually help ward off the time demons
that will uh come after you and follow
you so I think I think everybody should
invest and buy some goats build a fence
in your backyard build a paddock get
some food get some water put a trough in
there and stock up on as many goats as
illegally possible trust me on this guys
thank you that's a fair amount to help
you I'll protect you
this is why I always wear my tinfoil hat
always
thank you enough that was beautiful oh
that was pretty hard to choose
how much I'm a cane sweeper
yes yes
up next
yeah let's go let's do this girl let's
go
all right Dream Team here we go let's go
party on beginning my speech hello my
name is fancy Mori and I have to talk to
you about a really uh a really taxing
issue today something that has been
plaguing us for the past over a year in
fact three years and it must be stopped
fellow superheroes here's what we must
do to defeat the anime streamers this
has become a serious problem in our
society can you believe that these anime
women are being supported
by a bunch of a bunch of people a bunch
of people give burning their food
burning their bread
foreign
give their food money to these anime
streamers they ain't even real women
real women
this could be your food but no
You Gotta Give It to the anime women
I have one super superpower perfect for
this situation you want to know what it
is ladies and gentlemen do you want to
know what it is yeah
I mean I mean co-president of the
society the secret society conspiracy
against anime streamer women Amelia
Watson mentioned before that we need to
stoke Stoke up Stoke up stock up on
goats and Stoke up our goats and stock
up our goats because Pie is in fact
relevant to goats you have and with the
power of goats we can take them down
goat streamers listen to me I know that
it sounds ridiculous
if things go wrong here's my backup plan
now I need you to trust me
life is like a box of Jelly Bean
many different colors
many different
personalities
and for our goat streamers we make them
extremely likable there's a different
one for everyone some people pick out
the red ones some people pick out the
blue ones some of the yellow ones some
the the purple ones
some of the orange ones
you pick out the jelly beans that you
like
and you support that ghost streamer can
I get an amen
[Music]
that's what I like to hear man those
pictures were so bad yeah those are
pretty awful I have to agree with you
that was that was pretty dog [\h__\h]
[Music]
can I get a name
you did great though girl I'm gonna give
you a ride a green smiley face thank you
you're welcome
it was either jelly beans
people with suitcase or woman with hot
stones on her back
yeah
the awards ceremony this is
why Wow funny name so go ahead and do
that now
oh my God
finally nice well we really deserve no
Cliffhangers Donuts
what
what does that happen every time all
right I guess it's just
getting broken
if you wanted to know I felt really
funny when I typed this in um I I gave
one of my feedbacks all of my feedbacks
actually were wow Owen Wilson
wow
at the end like the award gets given to
somebody and then all the like uh
critiques or yeah the posts get put up
there next to their names and you get to
see it
I think this jackbox also has the
personality test one maybe oh
what
oh maybe maybe not this one okay I
thought it was this one which one is it
eight
jumped up yeah we're gonna jumped up
we're gonna draw some characters
[Music]
but I love this one yeah this one's
really good yeah that was fun okay no
tablets though you have to use your
mouse
[Music]
wait what's up
I'll leave the chicken
hey I represent kfp
the people of the cave people
what is this one
blue
ah monsters
it's blue I like it
one one
all right
[Music]
um
foreign
based off of a prompt and then they
verse each other and you guys get to
vote for who you like who wins it's
based on the prompt really so we just
get to draw and make our champions
yeah
should I make a smaller two minutes to
draw
what
okay
and you can uh go you can see your
prompt up top
oh God
this is the Fight Club
oh
uh hold on
we also
I need to undo
um there's like an arrow at the top
I forgot I could add colors later oh
[Music]
oh never mind one minute okay
oh
this is the point where we all go really
quiet because
trying to make a masterpiece here
I'm making a nacho Masterpiece oh
oh no
why is there no red in the colors it's
just pink and orange it's red it's red
isn't it it's not right
top right oh that's Orange
that's red that's orange that's red it's
orange name
okay
okay I think I at least
I did something decent Okay so
stop me oh no please hurry
submit your challenges
made a mistake
uh of course you did my whole life is a
mistake here we go hey that's dark yeah
here we go
let's go okay
okay
my opponent
I think I know
how to be funny
um
yeah I don't know either
oh no come on you guys are professionals
drying yes and professional
oh God
I just dress so well with the mouse you
know what the [\h__\h]
yeah I I'm really not good with the
mouse there's some people who are really
really good with the mouse I don't know
how yeah I've seen some talented masters
with the mouse you wouldn't even believe
it
oh hey
how much time one minute okay let's do
this
okay
almost there almost there almost there
whoa whoa wait oh this is
foreign
okay
it's time to name those characters all
right all right all right
okay that's pretty good Better Than I
Used to Be
finished
let's let's throw down on the
Thunderdome
it's a minute
I hope so
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm proud emergency
[Music]
is such a beautiful side I always wanted
to see that what
I know that's 20 we each did our own
thing
let's go
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
oh yeah no
oh
[Laughter]
no
it's questions
[Music]
laughs now entering the Ring of these
knees
[Laughter]
[Music]
one is cute though they're both quite
cute yeah
it's the perfect face for a doll
they put my all into the expression
my baby
I just wanted to wear panties on his
face
[Laughter]
oh
yeah sneaking oh let's not get us fired
um
that's good
Bianco isn't attention seeking now
everybody's fair game and Jack bucks
I hate to see that happen it's almost
poetic
Demetrius
hey
hey wait did you guys see your own wait
what
yeah
you get to see your opponent yeah
that's my original character oh it's
cooler though
this is what I wanted to
[Music]
yeah the original you guys prefer the
fancy ecommend remake all right whatever
that's fine another one another round
let's go
all right
you want another round I'll give them
another round oh
I'm biased for this one
I don't know
how do you guys even draw yako to look
like Yago like I don't know how you do
that yeah last time I drew Iago it was
not good it was not pretty
thing
okay
oh God oh God
can't work with a mouse
doesn't work
yeah it is hard I'm having I'm having a
rough time right now is this such a good
job with Dimitri though no that [\h__\h]
sucks
it's so good
thank you
what does Diego look like
he looks like a man
yeah
he was like a man
oh
okay submitted 25 seconds on the clock
I'm not happy with this
I'll admit defeats already
maybe we'll do better with the champ
ones and we'll get cooler Dimitri better
I will kill you
[Laughter]
no it's Dimitri is the early protagonist
they got beaten by the arrival at first
but then they come back you know
oh and then press submit does it save it
and
[Music]
oh God uh oh God uh
versus oh boy
uh
okay okay good
okay
I'm gonna do my best
I'm really gonna do my best here
somebody
okay
oh no oh no oh no no no no no no no no
um
is that too over the top that might be
too bad
I think I did like
a Pokemon like with a beer one time
I was just gonna draw a gun but I feel
like that might be too much let's draw a
water gun
oh they go past the
ah
this looks nothing like the person I
wanted to draw
um
. okay
I wish they had like a fill bucket if
they had a fill bucket then we would be
fine
yeah need more tilts need more tools
okay in the second half which means it's
time for the time
yes
it wasn't inspired
you can tag it out
put Dimitri back in the road
let him get his revenge Arc
hey what is this pirate
[Laughter]
what's in your hand I can't tell
you
yes
[Music]
no I've never seen Yago
nice
that is good
excuse me
wow okay
Facebook
oh oh
[Music]
yeah I like how pointy they are they're
like I have no chance and the eyes are
like looking up
oh
wow
it's a win-win I'm not good at marketing
which one is the best
thank you
[Music]
double team wipe out here is our next
match four bees
champion of Disguise
oh boy I like that nice job on that yeah
[Laughter]
really good
look away from the gun don't face the
gun oh no yeah Go's not looking at them
can copyright make a comeback
disguise
[Music]
boy
how does it feel
s
adorable look at it
oh you're adorable Kelly please don't
hurt me
Chad what's wrong with you
I mean it could have been worse oh no
Mercy
oh
let's see
it looks angry Redemption
[Music]
Dimitri I'll never forget that [\h__\h] but
not now we're even I was actually
tempted to put in a better journey
and then I'd throw Dimitri back out
oh
look at those shiny monsters
damn it I regret it I regret my choice
don't rub it in my face
she's everywhere
next it's original Creator would win
who's the ultimate champion
[Music]
[Applause]
no mercy
should we end with the last Whiplash
round sounds good yeah I'm down yeah
okay
nice music
okay stuff ladies Whiplash and then we
have one announcements okay
[Music]
uh play
connecting
oh cool
finish it off nicely yes round it all
off with us being funny again yes and
now that we're all warmed up yup
it's all warmed up all right
I forgot how this game works what was
this again
it's funny yeah okay everyone's in ready
ladies
time
well hello hello yeah this game makes me
feel like a clown that's how that makes
me feel like a clown midnight trained a
fun town
nothing like it sounds
funny I'm not playing you can still get
in the audience and vote put in the room
that's your job
and everybody it's a party let's
celebrate
stops on your device answer each one
with a all right in response soon you'll
go up against another player's answer
you know how it works we get it yeah
narrator man
never mind as the who are the host as
you might be able to
ski all right let's go
88 seconds
oh I don't know what this is oh no
um
oh this is rough
uh
um
uh oh
um um
all of us realizing it's hard to be
funny
yeah I put in the first thing I could
think of
um
and I wish I could be free
[Music]
who the hell is MacGyver
yeah
you can like make something out of
anything and it's like a term like I'm
getting a guy over this like you you
know get duct tape and you put it
together yeah
20 seconds left on the clock
time's almost done hurry [\h__\h]
[Music]
five four three two one
here we go this is a rough one
there's a secret tax loophole that
allows you to count blank as dependents
hello viewers anime wives viewers
oh God that was good what's it dependent
[Music]
yeah oh like somebody that depends on
you to live pretty much like you support
them monetarily oh my God
when someone shows up with blank
Wonder Bread
I don't know am I if I'm to be honest
[Music]
toughest choice of my life I'm hungry
this one
[Laughter]
definitely tough about the same value I
would say
[Music]
wow
I'm like the small beaches
it sounds like something bales
[Music]
I called it
yeah I actually when I was reading that
in my head I heard it in Cali
next next question
but all this spaghetti won't stop
falling out of my pocket
my spaghetti when I asked who MacGyver
is
honestly if he's if he's freaking out
he's spilling the spaghetti I voted for
his safety
oh wow you voted for a bot answer not
just funnier than spaghetti she likes
the spaghetti nuts
oh man
what that was nothing but a pickle I
like how they're both clothing like do
this hoodie taste better raw yeah
uh
I definitely know that coagulated we've
had better days oh
messages
[Music]
as soon as good as his name wasn't it
yeah
that's how you get them
hey
I want to stop playing
the game contractually obligated to be
here
eventually obligated to be funny
[Music]
oh
um foreign
[Music]
yeah I don't know how to I can't I just
can't I can't do it I'm sorry I can't do
it
um
ah
oh
time's almost up use a safety quip if
you're stuck
yeah we don't need to rely on safety
clips
I know I'm not funny but the safety
quips are rough man I mean the nuts
they work sometimes
okay
hey
you know nothing of
you know nothing huh
who put Apex
you played hey all right chat never mind
friendship ended with it
just another day in those shut up
deadbeats get out of the chat I've got
this fever
all of the Watson Field there decision
[Music]
where's the Hat
well do you ever want to get
I mean yeah your fever sounds awesome
fettuccine hair oh I didn't clip the
buttons
oh no why does Watson lose in this
question
she doesn't know how to solve it oh no
and extraterrestrials no no that was a
thing of Star Trek I thought it said
Shrek and I got excited for a minute
[Laughter]
hold on wow
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm a little biased though
right
hello there's a good girl
she's a good boy too
who's a good boy
baby you'll be
you'll be in my right bang the
non-committal way of saying I love you
who says that
come on
that one hurts I heard that one before
me we always gonna be dogs we always
call McDonald's
that's a rough one and that's a really
rough one like they're both bad dogs
we always go guys
let's see how things shook out yeah I
don't feel so good I want to throw up
actually because I'm feeling sick
[Music]
really
better than the last time we played this
yeah
you will be sent a prompt that requires
three okay I'll remember this time
right and Adam Sandler got it okay okay
this is easy easy points
yeah that's true okay
oh no a bad prompt boo let me see you
mmm
um
[Music]
I still blow for that one easy
come on let's give it our best stuff I'm
just being stressed I tried this is not
even good there's so much time left you
have 45 seconds how are you guys so
drinking water by the way it's for like
lack of sleep when you can only think of
one answer you just divide it into the
three different answers yeah
[Laughter]
20 seconds left on the clock I I
think you can do it you know you can do
it
[Music]
you ready for Magic
yeah show me magic three things they
discourage you from doing in the Grand
Canyon I wanna go there
[Laughter]
um
that's a really good one
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
I know what to vote for I'm not we're
both pretty pretty good I will say yeah
can you not take rocks home from the
Grand Canyon
oh yeah by the way guys I hope you guys
um
I mean that sounds that sounds like it's
legit rules though
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
that is pretty good oh dear uh it is
ineffective I guess yeah it is
ineffective because you don't know if
it's an actual yeah exactly true
but now
let's say foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh is he in a wheelchair
okay
for somebody
time to talk to sleep creepy in the bed
okay no
um now listen
ing
strategy this was this is very effective
though like it has impact like when it
appears like
you know
this is really happening so she doesn't
disrupt the timeline
yeah right
well Kelly uh-oh
really nice job
[Music]
and I'll do the slides does it
yeah who's talking
um
no no I don't know yeah
okay
3DW not happening
you almost have it I was like what yeah
this is used to me
okay well no
um you have been waiting for this or
actually we have been waiting for this
drum world
[Music]
new outfit celebrations
Tori merch items on sale December 13.
[Music]
hello and what else what else
B2 tapestry we have the image yeah the
tapestry chick yes
our new dresses art by sugar
[Music]
besides that we also have a party rubber
mat that you can put under your keyboard
or wherever you live
all over the keypad
dirty monitor juice
as far as I assume this is gonna be as
per usual time limited probably one
month so if you want it then get it
within the month it's available probably
uh in 12 minutes
yeah it should be tweeted out and and
announced everywhere but this is our
super cute celebration for the new
outfit
I love the art of all of us together
this almost looks like us at New Year's
Eve when the when the countdown strikes
I love it it's wonderful yeah I want to
look at it forever I'm gonna go look at
it for a long time after we finish
streaming yeah
well it's hot you guys yes yes
yes yes thank you guys for coming and
watching us thank you for supporting us
on all of our outfit reveals yeah thank
you congratulations
[Music]
you guys have to wait a while for the
dresses but now they're finally here
yeah
yeah it took a while but we we delivered
them to you
finally finally uh
we're just happy to have them here for
you guys
anything
I think it's really fitting though for
like Christmas and for New Year's we
have a lot of ways to get them to
celebrate there's gonna be so much to
celebrate it'll be perfect
oh that was all in the bun oh
this is nice
fancy you look really gorgeous you look
like a princess like Cinderella also
needs more forehead
I like
even though it was obviously all party
dresses celebration stuff I feel like
some of us went into like a modern
Direction and some of us went more into
like fantasy Direction and it's cool to
see the differences in in what we chose
while while still upholding the theme of
party dresses yeah yeah me and AME are
super like modern looking yeah yeah yeah
I think so and like Eno's like really
high fashion like Gucci yeah
[Music]
I like all the different tastes like I
like the modern outfits I like the
fantasy outfits I like them all like
would you like I already look quite
mythical in my um in my raping outfits I
wanted something a little more modern
this time
no that's a good contrast indeed I think
so until my OG outfit was kind of like
you know the the KSP uniform it's kind
of modern so I wanted wanted something
that's more like a phoenix
hmm oh should we hear everyone's
thoughts like like what what our
original like idea like why we chose
this kind of design what or or if you
didn't choose and still like maybe have
some talking points about it
sure yeah
last three part two sorry yeah let me
get some bgm you guys started tell me
what what were your thoughts behind this
outfit ooh shall I start yeah oh we can
go from from me to Amit
um yeah I suppose I knew very like very
specifically what I wanted from the
beginning I knew that I wanted to own my
own jazz bar and I wanted to dress like
a jazz singer because I'd never done
that kind of karaoke
um and I just thought it would be a nice
new setting for like me to hang out with
the deadbeats and like a a fancy
schmancy place because I've got my
reaping outfit and then I've got my
really casual uh outfit that you guys
saw which is super casual and I was like
what's what's something that I've never
done before also red is just the color
for me
um so it ended up working out perfectly
I think that the dress is like it's a
little on the simpler side but but I
think it really works with me and I
needed something a little bit on the
simpler side so I really like it it's my
little red dress so I hope you guys
enjoy it as well those are my thoughts
behind it yeah yeah I agree with them
yeah the earrings were exactly based off
a reference that I sent
um to Mama so you guys can probably find
these earrings somewhere being sold
one of them is dangly the one on my
right ear is dangly and the one on my
left ear is not it's just a stud look
again by the same earrings guys yeah
but it's not it's not exactly it's like
a little different yeah it's like a
shinier and yeah oh wait dude
as if you positioned us on purpose like
this from the beginning because you're
like oh wait no no it's just me and Cali
the other way around I would say
surprisingly unintentional but yes
what about you Kiara what were your
thoughts behind your dress and your
plans uh actually well I I wanted since
I I just said it partially but uh my
original outfit was more modern and my
casual outfit also and I wanted to go
into something more fantastic looking
mythical looking like the Phoenix I am
and also I wanted myself to look a bit
more mature so I feel like with the
color change and also stuff like the The
Fluffy extended hair and the extended
feathers and all that and the type of
dress they're like all together it did
it succeed in making me look like an
empress Phoenix Empress or something
like that yeah yeah yeah so
um actually after I saw like all the
other outfits I was like oh but
something like this would be nice too
and something like this would be nice
too but I'm really happy with what I got
and everyone looks fancy so I'm really
happy with the whole overall theme that
we went with nice yes yes
what about you me oh um I talked about
this a little bit but me and my amazing
mama uh we
we big collaborative work between the
both of us a lot of back and forth um
but it went really smoothly uh it's very
different this final outfit is very
different than what we started with I've
shown you guys but the original yeah the
original art was a very
oh yeah
actually it also reminded me of the
Super Mario Kingdom princess it's like
Daisy and Peach
yeah definitely but my mama was very
understanding when I was like um
actually can we do this and I signed a
very very large file pile of pictures
and and documents and stuff of like all
the the references and stuff that I
wanted specifically this type of crown
um and I'm extremely happy with how this
turned out and it works so well together
like arm pulses and stuff yeah
everything worked out really really well
it also suits your song reflect stream
reflect yeah yeah and it's the little
greek theme
a dress only for you I love that yes
it's so original I love it thank you
[Music]
mom
actually I don't remember if I said
anything specific I usually just leave
it up they couldn't watch Papa because I
like it I like being surprised sometimes
you know I understand that yeah
um I did mention was West meets East
kind of what the [\h__\h] but also looking
up like a western dress yeah oh that
that is indeed happening yes yes
I just want to take a bite like a
cupcake
[Music]
yeah your papa is like I understand that
you just let it happen uh because your
papa is like a he could be a fashion
designer in in Paris or so I don't know
yeah I could say the dressing like you
know what's that one one thing called
like the Met Gala where they have like
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
me too yeah yeah
what about I mean what did you did you
put some input to your mama
okay okay I don't have to sneeze anymore
yeah I had a few like uh dresses in mind
that I I sent to Nabi mama and she
really liked the long hair so she
definitely wanted to include that and
then um yeah I just I I picked from a
few like uh references that she sent and
uh some of them didn't have like the
tools I got I could like show just the
dress itself but uh here we are and yeah
I like it I got the temporary tattoo we
got the Tiara the mustache the
sunglasses so I'm pretty satisfied and
it's cute yeah yeah it's like a
undercover assassin
girl yeah
you're the best girl but you're also
Bond
oh yeah yeah oh
yeah
I was talking with the deadbeats about
this and we were talking about how you
with your long hair and your crown you
look like an actress walking down the
red carpet but then when you put like
your hair up and you put on the
sunglasses you look like a producer or
like director oh yeah it's like cool
cool mom
yeah I love it perfect for you you know
I have glasses kind of similar to that
Amelia I'm just saying oh the other
glasses collab maybe maybe we've seen
the same secret society before
I think one thing that this we mentioned
is thanks to Nabi Mama we now know that
ama has a moon
yeah it's my birthmark it's been there
[Music]
thank you thank you
yes
that's it that's all we have yeah does
anybody have any announcements or like
streams they want to talk about coming
up soon
yes yes
um the night I have uh I'm doing the
Jazz karaoke on my channel oh yeah yeah
don't miss it guys check it out if you'd
like to come enjoy some Smoky Lounge
Vibes it's not all going to be 100 Jazz
there's going to be a little r b in
there as well a couple more upbeat songs
um because it's just kind of like a
situation where I had to kind of pick
and choose a lot of the more Smoky
Lounge type songs I couldn't do so um I
picked the best set list I could give
you so come check it out please and um
stay tuned uh there are a lot of big
streams this uh this month and I'm doing
a lot of um like holiday things like a a
Christmas gift
um that's coming out on the 23rd 24th
25th the girls already know about it
because they're they're somewhat
involved actually in my Christmas gift
to you guys
um but I hope you'll enjoy it when it
comes out so yeah that's all I have to
say
Watson and I are playing fortnite
tomorrow oh my God we're about to get
down
[Music]
who's gonna be Ariana Grande
diesel on our first side but it's
actually The Rock The Rock
yeah we can use those skin we can oh
yeah but I want to be Captain America I
I'm gonna ask you guys in chat if you
end up playing with us you know maybe we
could take a peek at the Naruto skins
but uh we'll have to play like Will
Smith in the rock yeah
where where are we in that game can we
be in that game yeah hello live skin
yeah they just put everyone in that game
why are we in there you want to be in it
girl you don't want to be in fortnite
and I was looking at it like
big
[Music]
who knows maybe someday though screw it
I'd be in fortnite yeah but baby shark
in fortnite yeah do it do what you want
fortnite epic games do what you want
anyway all right guys that's all we have
for you
uh have a nice day have a nice night
thank you your viewing experience
or don't have a lovely rest of your day
Chad thank you for being supportive we
will see you next time
[Music]
um