[Music]
oh
yourself
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
thank you
frog eh what do you mean no frog
don't don't make it even harder like
i'm gonna be even more heartbroken for
not being able to be a frog
i wish i could be a frog don't rub it
into my face
[Music]
[Laughter]
supers are off yeah cause i
i'm still like
really far from um catching up uh so
yeah it would probably be foolish to
turn them on at the moment i'll probably
turn them back on tomorrow
um
yeah yeah um
[Music]
yeah hello it's been a long long time we
are going to play
minecraft today sasha boulini
it's been a while i know there's like
certain people
who
um just really love the minecraft
streams and those people must have been
sorry i'm trying to get cat hairs out of
my face those people must have been
starving
starving for
people to play minecraft again i'm so
sorry for them they must have been you
know they probably look like a zombie
right now because of the draw dragged
drought
dropped
draught
drought is that how you say it
okay it's draft i kind of thought so
wait is that the
right word dog
he says draft
maybe i typed it wrong oh wait i typed
d-d-r-a-u-g-h-t
oh it's r oh so it is a different word
drought drought okay so it's not an f
interesting how d-r-a-u-g-h-t
is
pronounced draft but if you just change
the a into an o
it's drought
where did the f go and where did the f
even come from huh where did it come
from
[Music]
no
i looked up
d-r-a-u-g-h-t as it said draft
it's not very consistent is it
we're not okay i know um i i was i
remembered there was something about
this word that made it sound uh weird
meow cat meowing in the distance well
wow don't worry i'm going to catch you a
frog
for for all of us for the sake of all of
our
happiness
uh
and
i don't know how to get a frog though
i
don't know anything about it uh i did
not look up any information
so you guys maybe have to help me a
little bit
yeah
i shall
maybe a little bit maybe you have to
help me for everything
so basically first of all we get we go
to a swamp right but then
can i catch it in a bucket how do you
catch the frog do i need a bucket
yeah yolo
no i'm not an open vc why would i be in
open vc does someone want to talk to me
uh
i need to breathe um
need slime for breathing oh [\h__\h] but
first i can bring the bucket right at
first
first i
eh
oh dear
what
the bucket is for the tadpole oh so i
can't bring the frog with me
i need to breed them at the spot
to get a tadpole because the only thing
i can catch is the tadpole
here's a leash
i i could put the frog on a leash
but that sounds like because we probably
have to go a long long long long way
to find a frog
[Music]
it's hard to use alicia
from a leash disturbing image
do you like the thumbnail by the way i
put some creativity in there
yeah graphic design is my passion
okay so
yeah i don't think the leash thing is
smart because we have to go really far
probably
uh
thank you for appreciating my thumbnail
um
okay
so i need i need slime when when do i
get slimed does anyone have slime does
he not have small slime she probably has
slime right she already went to find a
frog didn't find the frog but i suppose
she was well prepared and brought slime
you know has a farm there's a slime farm
well wonderful okay to the mountain let
me get some music and then open the game
properly it's already open but
um
oh how about this
i called this tropical adventure which i
think is accurate
okay no no it doesn't fit
it's too happy
i was too too happy
i got some more animal crossing
this is music is my new animal crossing
track i think is it
maybe
but i like it let's go with this
for now
until we go crazy
[Music]
okay okay sorry brain slow right now
we're starting one hour earlier by the
way not too loud
because i felt
like uh reading so many super chats
later on i would probably be hoping for
more time
[Music]
wow
that looks about right okay
echo
it's been such a long time
[Music]
hello everybody what's up
i got new shaders by the way
into the world we got yeah we're
currently in phoenix stands many many
hahas
why it's so blue
[Music]
slime do these people sell slime i
wonder no okay
we can't get slime from a farm do you
guys know where the farm is let's get
right into it
i can't
no don't go cat go back
yes yes good cat
[Music]
do you know where the farm is for the
nether and hq
never at hq
how do i fly again
do i remember how to minecraft
yeah
yes no
i remember
oh new recipes oh yeah cause there's new
wood now right i've heard about that
[Music]
oh hello
hello why are you all alone
[Music]
so we would have to go through here is
that what you're saying
the answer is very excellent wait and
tremble and verify that's new
take the original never railway and then
look around the cobblestone building
look
around the cobblestone building okay the
original
the
original neville railway
you mean the first railway that was
built in
here
okay let me put some stuff
away
i guess i'll just put it in here because
i think it's empty oh it's not really
empty
let's put my deep slate in here
um
my deep sleep i don't care oh
everything's so messy
hello
i need golden armor nice
[Music]
what
what do i need to bring now first oh
wait first we're going to get the slime
right so i don't need to bring anything
wait how do you how do you catch the
slime
do i have to like catch it
in a bucket or
a bucket sorry okay that was not such a
crazy thought apparently
i will drink the milk
is one slime enough
why are we making the slime
maybe i should have watched a video on
how to do all this
why do we need the slime
don't need to catch the slime just
inventory okay
oh well now we have a bucket for the
tadpole
[Music]
food full of frog okay so i just throw
the slime at them
[Music]
and then they make a baby
just like the chickens
you guys are so similar
interesting clouds
in a slime farm is an afk area okay well
let's just try to get there then uh what
should i not bring i don't need my
elytra right
let's put the lighter away before i lose
it
we might need it for finding the frog
though
and then we put the helmets on we put
this on let's put my emeralds away i'm
gonna put them in my house
elijah in the end the chest i guess so
i guess we can do that
go go go go go go
oh sunset what the sun is square
it's diamond-shaped square
it is minecraft yeah but it is it
without shaders also a square cause i
don't remember it
why do i have the smoker here
[Music]
some trainers can make it a circle i
feel like with my previous shaders it
was a circle
oh whoa
uh
emma routes
and your chest
should i bring in a new chest
let's bring an ender chest
maybe i just
i thought that was slime what does slime
look like
i'm like a minecraft beginner now
do i have any slime actually
maybe i have slime
maybe i got
slime ball i have one but
we would probably want more
[Music]
probably want more right
you will need at least two you want more
than one oh at least two ok
[Music]
i have no [\h__\h] space
as always
[Music]
minecraft streams
most of the time is taken up by me
preparing i'm sorry
it might be boring
[Music]
love to see it
but when we travel i may or not may not
i may i may i probably will tell you
some stories oh look at my axolotls that
i got last time and now you're just
rotting
rotting in the
in the bucket because i just got them
for the sake of getting them not
actually no i didn't even go for them i
went for the other things
i didn't didn't even care for
but
i tried it
first tried
yeah the mcdonald's story but i think i
also still have some things maybe that i
can tell about the
about the off colabor the meetup
probably
i can probably think of some things
i think yeah i think i may have still
some things written down
[Music]
who put that bed there
i don't remember putting that bed there
okay
uh we have a bed
we have we have a bed
we have an arrow we have
a sword
we have a kia axe
do we wanna put away my pet my my um
yeah better it's safer let me put some
stuff in the inner chest
[Music]
ah
okay this is silk touch so we put this
in we put this in
put this in
[Music]
i want to put some stuff away
now i'm starting to clean things
sorry i need to get back into the groove
you know
it's a bow no arrow oh yeah wait when do
i have a rounds
[Music]
uh here i have i only need one right for
my bow infinity
ah give me how do i take one how do you
take one
how do
i don't want 20. how do you take one
[Music]
right click i take 20 if i do right
click
i take half
good luck finding a frog thank you
right click
no
right and then when you place it again
right click
okay
so we got that
let me put this [\h__\h] in here i need to
hire cronie to
[\h__\h] clean my [\h__\h]
like for real
this is terrible
terrible
this can go here
and the white wool will go here
she'll probably have fun doing it so
yeah
do i really want
to bring this it's iron but it has silk
touch for the in the chest
let me bring a normal one too though
[Music]
it has such a nice sound a nice ring to
it
that could have pickaxe
[Music]
okay
i think i'm ready
oh wait now i have two buckets why do i
have two buckets now
i've got the more the mariah
[Music]
for now we're only going to go to the
never to get the slime that's the first
step let's go
even oh let's sleep even one slime would
be good because i have one slime here
and then we have to decide where we go
get more buckets
but you guys said i just i don't need a
bucket for the slime
we're not going to the tadpole yet are
you guys aware of that
we don't
yeah not for the tackle but for now
we're just picking picking up slime
i always leave the door open
anyway
wait that that i really don't like to
look up the sun
freaks me out
i don't like it being square like if at
least it wasn't like diamond square
but like
you know turn around i would appreciate
that
do i go
i'm i'm scared
i'm scared
i like your old shirt more yeah
i can change it
now
now we're using this
copper express ah wait the original one
is this one
am i right
i should have brought minecart so i
don't have to
use i would say this is the original
and then
a cobblestone
house wait
it's always a slime farm in the never
i don't have to leave the never to get
this lion
i guess that makes sense because i think
there's uh these these slime monsters
right in the nipple
oh
[Music]
complete
what how did i get out of this
[Music]
i'm scared
is so dark ah yeah shaders are usually
not so good in these environments
um
go back
did i go too far
is this the build oh i thought that was
just somebody fixing the wall
in here
i've never seen this before
[Music]
it's not a forum
kind of confusing here
[Music]
can you save me can you help me do they
fight them
somebody fights them right
[Music]
i'm still following me
i need to [\h__\h]
no need a [\h__\h]
shield shield
maybe i should kill it but aren't they
really strong
i think it lost track no i didn't lose
track okay okay okay okay be fast
be fast
i'm faster
wait can you fly in the nether
oh these these fight the the pigs i
think
stay close to me please
[Music]
oh
wait if i go behind this
[Music]
and then
oh [\h__\h]
i'm gonna kill you
why am i not hitting
yeah
baby
that's what you get
that's what you [\h__\h] get
we're making pork burgers tonight not
beef burger wait pork burgers ew
disgusting what is that another thing
all right
what happened here why is it open
okay
why can't i
cannot be scared
to eat food
[Music]
i need to heal my bow
get them out of the way nice oh they're
pretty weak
get that leather
oh there's a baby
baby
[Music]
it gets stuck behind there
the pink the babies are even worse
because they're so [\h__\h] fast it's
like
impossible to get them
okay are we good now can i go up now
i hope there's no more
surprises up there
[Music]
oh these are just the sounds from the
ones inside okay
hello
i thought these ones help me fight the
pigs i guess not
at least
as long as they don't join the fight
okay okay okay okay okay
path is
looking relatively safe now
uh where where do i
i think i saw a portal
[Music]
there it is there it is
is this it
what i have to go through
[Music]
hi hello
where am i
is this this farm no that's something
else that's enough stuff
[Music]
okay let's i guess it's this thing
never seen this place that is the farm
look up oh
do you have to climb all the way up
there
to make it work
and where does it get collected at the
top or at the bottom
[Music]
the chest is ah there's a chest under it
but do i have to go up
maybe check it for slime balls okay okay
[Music]
under it
under it there's a tree
[Music]
okay as expected
this is always the thing with afk forms
especially when nobody's active anymore
nobody's playing the game actively sadly
maybe now it's time for the comeback
i need to teach kobo how to play
minecraft has she ever played minecraft
before
because i don't think she's playing it
on her channel yet
oh she has
oh yeah and the dragon i guess yeah they
they just recently slayed
slaught slayed
they ended slate
slaughtered
[Music]
next week we're doing portal next week
slaughtered sounds nicer but that's a
different word i guess to slaughter
[Music]
okay
we are at the top i'm learning so much
english today oh cool place
this [\h__\h] sun
okay and i just went here
for a while
this is like the
like the iron
farm iron not iron what was it
what's that other from the ppp
just wait for a while
hello hello
hello
on my back nice
[Music]
okay
so i just how long should i chill here
one night is that enough or just as long
as possible or
[Music]
when was it two days ago i went to
mcdonald's and i usually don't go to
mcdonald's because i prefer
let's not say that maybe one day
mcdonald's wants to sponsor me
but but you know it's yeah um
i usually i don't go there so often
anymore
um
but
uh i was with some friends and uh
so we went to mcdonald's because they
preferred mcdonald's so i was like okay
i guess i'll join you
and
so i remembered that they have this
feature which i will say is really great
i guess i guess
they should implement that in at burger
king too i would say they have this
feature where you can add stuff to your
burger right
for dwelling yeah i actually was
freewheeling again
it was a different couple though
i'm always with couples for some reason
now um it's okay they don't really make
me feel like i'm a fruit wheel
no that was fun um
yeah so they have that feature
and um so you know i really really
really
love uh
burgers with tomatoes in it
i
i usually will always order
a burger with a tomato in it
for some reason i don't know it's just
so good
um
and this is the thing with burger king
they have that crispy chicken with the
with the tomato in it by default
but mcdonald's has
at least my our austrian mcdonald's
currently has no
chicken burger that has a tomato by
default and unless maybe that new one
with the kind of like mustardy sauce i
think that one may have had it um
but i don't like the mustardy sauce you
know i i like the the white
um kind of mayonnaise-ish kind of sauce
uh
yeah so anyway that one doesn't have the
the the tomato i think it's called milk
chicken mac chicken
but i love chicken burgers you know and
it has everything except the tomato that
i need so wonderful thank you mcdonald's
for reminding me that you have this
feature of adding tomatoes what do i do
i add
a tomato
and now here it comes guys
here it [\h__\h] comes
i
receive my burger
i open it up
to check because it looks suspicious
oh my
god four they put four not one not two
not three no they put five times
holy [\h__\h] macaroni i was so excited
what a deal ah so much tomato so much
freshness so much vegetables so much
vitamins so much mmm crunch and oh my
god the flavor
oh what a deal
yes thank you for the tomatoes
mcdonald's i love you again you have
redeemed yourself in my eyes and then
you think you think you couldn't top
that right
you think you couldn't top that my
friends ordered chicken nuggets
so
they ordered
one
uh
uh sweet and sour sauce because that's
like the go-to
chicken nugget sauce in austria and i
think also in germany it's interesting
how in different countries
um
people like to go for different sauces
and in different countries they don't
even have the sweet and sour sauce it's
so weird but sweet and sour sauce is so
popular here that you often even see it
as the only sold out sauce
uh
at the
fast food place yeah so they ordered the
the
sweet and sour sauce but you know often
i feel like one if you if you order six
chicken nuggets
um one
one pack of sweet and sour sauce maybe
enough if you were
if you don't overuse it but the the
moment you order eight
chicken nuggets
i think that was the the next stage
then one is not enough one sweet and
sour sauce package
but two
is kind of excessive
because then you will have a lot of
sweet and sour sauce left over
by my experience
so anyway they ordered one sweet and
sour sauce
and what did they get
five sweet sour sauces
[Music]
uh my friends took the sweet and sour
sauce home
she like the girl she put it in her
pocket into her bag and i was like
i kind of wanted the package too
yeah but oh my god
what's going on in this store
so generous what the [\h__\h] how long is
this night by the way
mind blown i know
wow
how good is the sauce it's really good
it's not like the
sweet chili sauce it's sweet and sour
it's like
it's really good i love it with the
chicken
nuggets yeah look down to watch the
slimes oh
which what slimes during those slimes
uh although i i see him hitting
something i guess that wasn't slime yeah
and something just died over there oh
i guess i just can't see the mobs but i
can't see the the big boy
[Music]
full cycles 20 minutes ah
well anyway that kind of reminded me of
of the bread tangent too a long time ago
remember when i had an extra piece of
bread in my
brand package
i was so excited about that
and now this reminded me of that
hell yeah
yeah that was amazing that is i thought
i could never top that but honestly four
tomatoes and four sweet and sour sauces
i feel like
i feel like i topped it
yeah
so never think that you have peeked in
your life
because you can you can peek again you
can peek even more
it's not the end it's not over
free hats
something going on there
[Music]
it goes towards the magma thingies
because it likes that dose or
[Music]
is that is that their behavior
him hit him hit him
hit him
go why are you not doing anything
he's not doing anything
ah there's water there oh
and he's not hitting him
do something
the sun is going up
but the slimes don't care about the sun
do they
[Music]
the golem is ah he's gonna die from the
from the
blocks ah
but before the golem actually attacked
something
maybe he doesn't care about the slime
and what i saw him attacking was
something else
how long does it take
oh nice
so
now i'm going down because i feel like
he at least killed two
i'm gonna go down once
[Music]
this is not how you go down
ah i guess not maybe that's just for the
water on the ground
all right
[Music]
let's go oh that's scary
but that's just for fishing oh
jump down
well i guess is there water i don't see
water
there was water somewhere
[Music]
five minutes later
don't jump yeah um see i don't see any
water close by that would have been
dangerous
okay and now we check
okay there's one here but it's kind of
hard to land in there
please give me give me what i want
yeah six is that enough plus my the one
that i have is seven
wow one night six slime balls
should i get more
no i don't want to wait anymore i think
that's good
where's your elixir in my in my thingy
in my in my box
yeah
[Music]
that's good enough right
okay we're going back hopefully no pigs
are attacking me
naughty
naughty pigs pig pigs pigs
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay he's burning
[Music]
oh he's killing him too so they do help
no okay oh they're happy about it i did
the most damage dope
we might want to go for the never to go
far away right
where did ina go did she find a swamp
but no frogs
maybe if i could go to the same swamp
maybe now there will be frogs
or just fly
[Music]
but last time i knew that i did that
everybody was like so nervous like oh my
gosh
be careful
found some swamps no frogs she went to
the same swamp but ran around and got
lost
[Music]
50 50 chance
50 50 chance but yeah but they they can
spawn right like
even if there was none originally if i
go back then there might be
there might be
um
frogs next time
right
you know locked in circles for a few
hours and it was fun
sounds like a lot of fun yeah
but it has to be a mangrove swamp new
old swamp spawns them but it might not
be fast
might be worth fine oh
so there's a chance for them to be in a
non-mangrove
swamp but it's more likely for them to
be in a mangrove swamp
is it is that what you're saying
ah
and is there
the one that ina went to was that
mangrove swamp
it doesn't have to mangrove which is
faster than uh-huh uh-huh
[Music]
mancraft swamps are rare
okay
she just went to normal all right guys
let's find a mangrove swamp
maybe
we can extend
our
um what was called
the thing that i built the long long
long ice railway to the
mesa mesa maybe we can extend that if we
go even further past the mesa
so far so far all kinds of interesting
things have been spawning on the way to
the meso road even all in one straight
line remember the the red cow island
yeah that was also on the way
so we'll go even further beyond piston
that's that's what we're gonna do yeah
[Music]
so we keep the helmet um what might be
worth doing though is repairing my stuff
right i need to repair
my
bow
and
preferably in my electron
not preferably but actually we have to
we're gonna fly after reaching the mess
up
so uh for repairing i go to
pbb
is that the easiest thing easiest way oh
yeah i guess we'll take shulker
boxes maybe
bring your totem uh i guess so yeah
[Music]
phoenix then try the feeding okay
oh
okay
i think i wanted to trade
ira and i have some i put some iron into
my
box here
iron iron
ah
watermelons right watermelons
last time though i feel like i could
was that the watermelon guy who i
couldn't find
last time i was looking for him
i'll take this
i wonder if that's enough
i'mma turn off oh yeah she comes
did she
i think i heard about that and she
turned it like she she started
destroying it
melody oh yeah
[Music]
yeah lots of emeralds because i am the
freaking boss
of phoenixton what do you expect of
course the ceo of phoenixton has to have
a lot of the emeralds
with all those emeralds i could buy
twitter i'm telling you
[\h__\h] off
[\h__\h] you
ah someone left the boat there
yeah so um guys
i know super chats are off right now but
i will be needing your support to buy
twitter
[Music]
cause uh
elon ewan of course i knew i knew it
would happen honestly
i knew all along that
oh no that's that's how it's supposed to
look like and i knew all along that he
would dip out
yeah now it's mine
now it's my twitter shall be mine
twitter what am i doing
[Music]
[Applause]
did not
do it correctly although i don't know
how am i supposed to do it again like
this
wait it's not
it doesn't have mending on
how do i repair this again
but we can mend this thing
if i
if i have if i have only one item that
has mending
combined with other okay okay okay but
for the elytra if i have if the only
thing i have on has mending then it will
meant that right
[Applause]
where did where did you go
[Music]
what's going on why are there so many
did the breeding incidents happen again
without my knowledge and my permission
do i need to put the electrode in my off
hand oh
my off hand is this my offhand
[Music]
[Applause]
did that work
[Music]
i still have some iron
huh
[Music]
wait wait
did i push some automatic uh
key combination i i know
but that looks like it did heal
something it's currently oopsie at 236
okay
[Music]
nice
now i have no more
iron
[Music]
i could buy something off of them but i
don't know what i would buy or maybe i
can combine with this one
no
i will do that
i will use your guys's anvil if that's
okay
stream sparks
plus random ass bow
oh there we go
wait does that
power two unbreaking two
oh no it stays the same
the power one and unbreaking one doesn't
add anything to it
is that the frog right behind you what
wrong frog
huh
what frog
okay i think the bow is healthy enough
now just want to get the elixir to max
but for that i will go to the watermelon
lord
[Music]
i wonder where he might be you're not uh
watermelon lawrence
[Music]
all right
yes it's you
good morning
right he wants the full melons okay okay
stay here uh full melons
[Music]
full melons
i need more
i think
we'll try i'll try for now
it's really sorry
[Music]
what a deal
oh that only did a little bit yeah i'm
gonna
honest maybe i can buy some food
may i buy some food i think i'm
generally always like out of food anyway
what should i buy
uh carrots are better than the melon
slices aren't they
are they
are the melons
golden carrots
but maybe not so many what the [\h__\h]
just as many as i need for my
no if you put it on again don't do that
[Music]
no i'm sorry i'm sorry oh
[\h__\h] thank god thank god he didn't see
that
i'm sorry i'm sorry uh are the prices
different now
no thank god okay i'm sorry i'm so sorry
[Music]
yeah i haven't played minecraft in a
while i'm sorry and he didn't get up
so i felt like oh there what's wrong
i'm sorry
[Music]
i feel like i owe her something anyway
okay
yeah
[Music]
now we have some extra food too
all right preparations are
done right all i need is a bucket
and
a full of light rail
slime
although
what is what if uh on the way
my lighter runs out
uh how can i fix it when i'm in the
middle of nowhere
[Music]
two pockets i have two plugins i have
two buckets
i might even get more buckets
if i find one
happy birthday oh it's already been a
couple days but thank you
anvil
angle and membrane
i don't think i have
membranes
[Music]
but i guess if i really need them
urgently then i can just stay up a few
nights and hope that
a phantom attacks me
i have mending
oh yeah i guess i'll just kill some mobs
i forgot i forgot
[Music]
maybe i don't have a phantom member no i
feel like i gave them
yeah i think ah no i do uh because i
remember giving my leftover membranes to
some
whole life english member who needed
them
okay
okay sleeping the timer
hi from to brazil
[Music]
don't ask me if i'm coming to brazil
so i was just reading a comment
and okay so let me put the
membrane into my ender chest
uh let me also put the cookies to
inaudible
[Music]
is so fancy what the hell
i need to
i never finished the roof of my place i
need to decorate my home too i've got a
lot of these
things too
from the last time i went to
i went on a trip
okay
when do i put the cookies
i'll put it in here
tell her cookies are from kiwawa
i know she doesn't read the chat much so
she might not even
notice and when when is she gonna play
minecraft again huh
yeah sasuke artist
yeah i mean look at that
damn impressive
[Music]
not bad
yeah i know she played a few days ago i
know
okay now let's uh try to get uh do i
have any empty
shulkers
anywhere
[Music]
or do i have to empty one wait
let's get some more buckets
ah
[Music]
i could empty this one perhaps
i could try
yeah
give me
i will empty it
oh yeah this is actually a fitting place
probably
everything that's green
goes in here
beautiful beautiful look at all that
stuff i got the drip leaves the moss
everybody loves moss
i should give monster ahmed but she
doesn't really play minecraft
you think she would be happy about 64
moss blocks
almost carpet
do you think she would be happy because
i don't even know why i collected this
much i i'm not planning to do anything
with it
yes okay let's bring muscular me must
must bring muscular me
ah my gosling inside of me is
shaking
[Music]
oh my god
so popular this chick
when do i put it
i
she won't notice it if i put it in such
a random place
look at that
wow pretty
oh whoa was that fish
crazy fish
whoa
when did you build that
okay i'm putting moss here
she'll probably never find it
when she plays minecraft we can maybe
try to tell her
[Music]
if i if i ever see her playing minecraft
anytime soon i'll i hopefully will be
reminded
myself to tell her
yeah i'm too lazy to put like proper
boxes there now so whatever
uh i kind of want to check
if i have some empty
some empty
shulkers
in here
that's relatively empty
this one's empty
and i don't need to empty out the other
one
[Music]
maybe
i can empty out
the one above ah there you go that's
some
shulker box material
[Music]
oh
okay
what here do i not need this
[Music]
okay i think i'm good
what do you guys think am i good
i like to take two energies just in case
i accidentally leave one somewhere wow
so prepared
hello takanasi kentucky
[Music]
what did you just call me your little
[\h__\h]
probably didn't even call me down on
purpose
[Music]
okay i think i'm ready to go
uh where was mine
where was the origin of my messel road
[Music]
you climb up the ladder ah that one okay
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey
i really like my current nickname kiwawa
i hope it doesn't
get changed into
see this is such a genius
such a genius
[Music]
even brought my own boat
should i brought anything else oh man
i'm gonna have some torches i've ah have
some fire some [\h__\h] [\h__\h] me
do i need more fireworks
did i have more fireworks in the end the
chest i wonder
[Music]
i have a bed
spare blocks always handy true
not enough
i think i need more yeah at least maybe
a bit more
sorry
[Music]
right i don't know about gunpowder but i
have i think i have a lot of extra
gunpowder somewhere
collected recently
[Music]
left the door open again
and there's some gunpowder here
[Music]
firework
look i saw fireworks
[Music]
i'm gonna tell them
does it melt your brain i really like it
though is it painful guys
is the music
paining you
i can't even open that there's probably
fireworks in there though
there's probably fireworks in there
probably
not really
nice
okay then i think i can continue playing
it
let me check let me check let me check
[Music]
and even more even even colder and
sticks to make more uh
i'll put this here
uh this is for this is for building then
i guess we can
probably take some
some of these
ah i do have a flame mending bowl
but this one has infinity yeah that's
why i always yeah i'm never sure
which one to use but yeah and i have an
extra electric
you know what i might put that
in here
don't need the copper don't need this
don't need this
[Music]
you'll need the treasure maps
i'll keep
this
i don't need another rack
actually don't also don't need this in
this
portion of healing saturn okay let's put
this here
let's put this stuff here
[Music]
okay i'll bring this for a building if i
need something urgently
oh yeah these ones
[Music]
i think i'm ready now
i'm ready let's go
exp bottles i don't have i need to
if you if you wanted you could make an
endless list of things i could
but i don't bring know how to make
bottles for exp
so i'm not making it not bringing it
over prepared man that's overkill
i'll be fine
i'll probably be fine
did you bring a bed yes bring eggs now
change to bgm because some of you seem
to be suffering after all
i'm so kind
[Music]
m and we will not be satisfied
with
a normal swamp we will find ourselves
the best swamp
to ever exist why can't i not open this
chest
is there lag
oh there you go
these look so bright now
actually two boats might be handy oh
well
ah go straight go straight go straight
go go go go straight
manage to watch much love from italy
[Music]
ciao
okay
i did right down there on the sign first
stop second stop and so on right but i i
don't think i actually made the stops
did i
did i make proper stops already i don't
think i did
[Music]
no bellow and bella is like why are you
guys here
it's a way of saying a beautiful girl
beautiful boy
what
why are these
dudes here [\h__\h] i'm going backwards
[Music]
how can i
prevent them from spawning in here i
wonder
okay
okay i'll keep the boat
more torch more slot more lights okay
[Music]
i always hate going out of here because
like i've been attacked here before and
it's kind of scary and traumatizing i
hope nothing will attack me now
[Music]
the sound is so scary
okay it looks looks safe
is this is this the right place i think
so
finger
remember something shocked me there not
so safe after all yeah and as always we
spawn here you know what i'll hate the
chest
[Music]
oh
did i just spawn another point no i
think this was a maximum of portals that
would spawn here
um was it
the
[Music]
which direction was it
the mess out was which direction
south
how do i see south again
how did you how were you able to send
the super chat
my super jets just
turned themself on
maybe youtube was like uh-uh girl uh you
gotta make money for us we want that
what was youtube's cut
what was it again
we want that 30 [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
you ain't allowed to turn off the super
chats
give us the money give give us the goods
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey
i'm turning them off again
i will regret it otherwise
[Laughter]
do it
how do i go south again
[Music]
you guys said stuff are you sure about
that though wait
was it this star i feel like it was that
direction though
i think it's this way
[Music]
yeah it looks like the never and uh mesa
does it maybe not
oh yeah yeah there we go
a woman's intuition
is
unbreakable unbeatable
[Music]
so
welcome back to
kiwawa's mesa byomi
[Music]
mist
so now
we shall we shall
fly just straight
just straight because i think
then we'll get lucky
hopefully
how dare you not take my money
i'll take it maybe tomorrow
okay
uh
i i remember
when exploring the mesa
i went a little bit further than this
but not that much i think
leave the totem but what if i die when i
fly
[Music]
well i know
where one of the coordinates here where
are they uh
three one eight
six four
uh
one
it's hard to read
thousand ten thousand eight hundred one
remember
[Music]
ah
it's for your own good
authentic authentication
remember what you wanted to write and
write it tomorrow let's go
okay we're going south
[Music]
what i don't even know what to look for
though
i don't even know what it looks like
will it stand out to me
i hope it will stand out to me
big
biome look for swamp
well
i don't know
doesn't it look like something we
already had before though
[Music]
oh yeah i think i remember there being
corals here
is this new chunks i wonder
[Music]
probably not quite
i'm scared
[Applause]
i have all my precious things with me
i should have shut everything away bef
until i land
we're just going straight
i see the front yes okay
if you see something tell me guys
will it be like in between mountains or
just in
flat water
is there a chance it could be just like
in between here
it should be in a flat area right i feel
like
yeah
i have to tell them oh but i need to
hold it i guess oh [\h__\h]
i can't hold it now
[Music]
oh nice place
pretty
[Music]
whoa
landing
just landing for a second
oh
don't really care about this though but
thank you how do you get those thanks
and there should be a
i think i saw a gold block
i think i saw a gold block maybe on it
it's probably hidden somewhere
[\h__\h] i don't care all right then um
do i have to put it here
and i fly out of the water
i'm allowed to fly out of the water
i can't i can't
let me go on land
when the floor becomes gray you found it
okay see that's actually helpful
information
[Music]
sleep once oh yeah it's night time good
idea good idea good idea good idea good
idea
[Music]
maybe now i should take the opportunity
to put all my [\h__\h] into a box
i have the
silk touch
okay
put
um put this put this
this
slime
green
[Music]
my tools i guess
while i'm flying i don't need them so
maybe one choker
it's okay
[Music]
okay
i think i'm happy with that
looks good
now i want to find frogs and the new
biome just in general hi chickens cute
free chickens we must freedom from their
freedom
we must help them we must rescue them
what is this shitty weather that's
really hard to see
can't find my
my biome like this
[Music]
ah you know what i could do
i could go by boat a little bit
because we want to save
the elijah a little bit okay is this so
south
this is this is the right south this way
okay
i'll just go straight for this
for a while here
because it looks like
somewhat big ocean
i just hope no one attacks me
[Music]
oh that definitely does not look like
what i'm looking for
sugarcane yummy turtles
you're speaking of sugarcane
food speaking of food
did you guys see on twitter when i made
yesterday i made a burger
and then i also posted one i made
um a while ago
[Music]
i made uh not a while ago i guess it's
like two days ago
the the glass noodles thing
it was so funny people looked at it and
thought that was a fish like some people
really were like hey what is this green
fish like
like seriously asking me
what is this green fish
it's not a fish it was pak choy
and in uh german we ride pak choi like
that but then some people were like oh
don't you write it like bok choy or so
i guess maybe in english you'd do that i
thought it was pakistani everywhere
but anyway that was really funny
green fish
[Music]
oh it's at the village
village
i want to say hi
looks nice
should we say hi
[Music]
actually books are different oh
well there you go
i hope there's no ice beers beards bears
here
[Music]
no no no no no no
but isn't was that something of igloos
that there can be treasure in them
hello
wasn't it like under the carpet
oh
my spears
maybe
maybe not
that's not an eagle
sorry i'll give you your floor back
sorry about that
maybe there's some exciting stuff here
no
maybe here
blast furnace
[Music]
the music kind of fits i feel like
because kind of i wouldn't feel weird
about having this play in a christmas
village hello kitty cat
[Music]
i think it fits nicely right now
why where do i enter there we go
nice houses
oh yummy food
maybe i don't okay it's kind of mean i i
i don't need food
you guys needed more than me
open the [\h__\h] door how rude closing
it right in front of me
there's nothing interesting here
i should probably just go
okay
okay sorry i'm going
we're south
south south south
[Music]
hanoi
perfectly straight south like the
southeast i can go
maybe
if it's close to zero here
the numbers next to the south
is on the water so going over land is a
waste
yes okay makes sense
okay
wait where's my boat
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] where did i leave my poo
um
somewhere here
almost forgot my boat man i almost left
without it
should
be here
can i leave my boat i have it oh i don't
have it
smart ah of course i have it
of course i don't
[Music]
it's probably not in a snowy environment
is it is this a temple
[Music]
sorry i get distracted really fast
was it a temple
[Music]
temple just sand okay
[\h__\h] hate sand all my homies hate
sand
wow it's so snowy
it's
i feel like this is is this a new biome
snow forest
why am i just
absolutely
stupid right now
this feels so new to me
snow
louisiana what is this
no
it's still south
i'm east
it's not gonna be here though
oh yeah baby
ah it's not loading in fast enough
should go higher
[Music]
it's so high
i'm gonna bunk against the mountain but
it's okay if i told him i have yeah
behind this behind this snow biome i'm
telling you
there will be
the mangrove biome
i feel it
okay i gotta be careful here
wow
oh
[Music]
i mean it's just cobblestone
[Laughter]
still snow it's still snow it doesn't
count it will be it will be beyond here
beyond
all of the snow
wow
i'm so scared
[Music]
village
village makes me feel relatively safe
[Music]
but i'm not gonna land this time
i feel like we already went so far
come on
give me a swamp
[Music]
now now that swamps are such an
important thing i'm i'm surprised cali
doesn't want to play
uh minecraft again
she said she's not gonna
play it anymore
[Music]
i don't know if she told
her peeps but
she said she won't play it anymore
ever
so sad
and she said she lost her character oh
god i should sleep
[Music]
it's not her kind of game i feel like
you know if from the beginning she would
have just like
um
picked it up the way i did
not by like having so much um
time in between each time she plays
minecraft because it was almost
always so much time that she would
forget
uh how to play
and then she has to remember again and
then she gets so much backseating and
yeah
and it's just not
not quite fun
which i understand
okay
at least the weather is clear now let's
go i don't have so much so many
fireworks left oh but yes i can make
more i can make more i'll be fine i can
make more
kelly and she's traumatized by breaking
things i guess so
i should look at my notes
you know
one thing i remember from my notes
sometime in america
i don't quite remember anymore what
exactly the situation was what was it
maybe maybe when buying a ticket or
something
oh
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
um i was
asked
or not even asked like it was assumed
that i'm under 18.
i'm a freaking eternal phoenix yo
[Music]
they were like oh yeah yeah so you're um
you you're under 18 or like so you get
this ticket or something like that
probably
how flattering oh look at all that gold
stuff but i don't know
i guess i can take it i guess i can take
it
suck that's gold shovel sex such golden
axe
crystal fighting no thank you
clock one golden apple
wow
seems like your age like fine wine no
but it's so weird
like in in my own country
people
i guess they do assume i'm a bit younger
than i am
but then not as much as in america like
in america they assume like i'm even
younger
like crazy young
i want that
can if
and then in japan
they would assume i'm a bit older than i
am often
[Music]
but it also a little bit depends on
whether or not i'm wearing makeup
i think
if i don't wear makeup in america
they
seem to or or also in europe they seem
to assume i'm even younger
and if i wear makeup then it gets a
little bit closer
to my actual age
yeah it's just like what they're used to
usually seeing but it's really funny to
me when people
genuinely think
i'm
a teenager under 18 which
i totally am
i mean
i i look i mean i'm a eternal phoenix
but that's totally
what i would be if i was a human
i don't like this i don't like this i
don't like this
i don't like this
at least there's water
[Music]
what's this
what is that
why is there wood
[Music]
is a ship wait a ship
oh
[Music]
a wrecked ship in a so this is global
warming
boys and girls the
the ice thingies are melting
so we find shipwrecks
in
the air basically floating
that's fun
i wonder if there's more there should is
there more i wonder
that's a good find though
some good stuff in there
[Music]
i guess it kind of ends in there
oh almost broken there we go okay thank
you for um
yeah being so useful
i guess i shall continue
break the eyes
i'm i'm very good at breaking the ice
i'm the icebreaker
i should title if i ever put out an
album i should title it
icebreaker the phoenix who breaks the
ice
all right i'm gonna maybe we should go
buy water
[Music]
i again to just float down but i'm
scared of doing that
[Music]
it's so scary here
i'll buy that one
you better
okay let's just fly here
[Music]
and then go by boat
[Laughter]
[Music]
i guess what i need to look out for is
uh what i saw in the maldives
right
because i remember
in the maldives i think guys maybe not
maybe that wasn't mangroves i don't know
but i i uh i saw i i read that mangroves
are like um trees where the the
thingies are above water
the
woods and the roots
and i saw a train like that i even took
a photo of it i went like i i i kind of
crouched underneath
the roots
and was like inside it was like a root
prison
and ah wait i'm facing easter there we
go
and then i took a picture
inside the tree was that a mangrove
i wonder if that was a man man grove
maybe it was a woman group
bunny
thank you
[Music]
what is that
is that another broken portal
looks like a broken portal
oh maybe i'll go there i'll go there
eat the meal
yeah
give me all your treasures
what you got what you got what you got
what you got what you got this time
is that [\h__\h] lava right next to me oh
my god
terrifying
yeah
gold fortune two golden pickaxe
[Music]
with that i will mine the gold block if
i find it
i can't see it i don't want to look for
it i'm too lazy
ah i have too much stuff already
oh
too much
[Music]
maybe i should put some stuff into the
shulker
okay we'll have a
box that is for
non
[Music]
shrek
related items
swamp i couldn't think of the word so i
said shrek instead
is this this
this
i'll keep this out here now
and then the wood the wood can go in
here i'll need the wood
yes
i'll take this
okay that looks more organized
and then we put this in here
and there we go
very clean inventory right isn't it
beautiful oh we should maybe is it is it
gonna be nighttime
can i sleep already yes
okay
[Music]
one weird thing i noticed about america
but maybe that's just the places that
i've been
in specifically
during my time
but from what i've observed and i'll
did i sleep
through oh
tell me if i'm wrong
but i've observed that the bathtubs are
weird in america
like uh they are weirdly flat and small
as if they
like as if you guys don't want your
whole body to be in the water
i've seen that a lot
like in the hotel
and i think also in the airbnb
some of them are we prefer showers me
too but yeah i don't know
confused me it looked weird
like weirdly flat
more bathtubs are small those are
showers yeah i guess so but it no it
looked like an in between thing like
like you still wanted it to be somewhat
usable as a bathtub but not really
[Music]
yeah it was not only a shower i think
it's like an in-between thing but
kind of weird
for sure
south we go let's continue
which direction did enough by the way
she didn't go the same direction as i
did right
[Music]
yeah but
i guess maybe it's a hotel thing i don't
know
she was near the slime farm uh-huh she
went opposite okay
okay i think i have to fly again
we must go
first so i can take off properly
it lets me
hello
horse
horse would be useful i have a saddle
with me
and a golden apple do you think i eat
golden apples
nah then you guys if i leave them behind
then you guys are going to be again like
[Music]
no need to give apple oh
don't just do this until it accepts it i
it doesn't want the saddle i guess maybe
i don't need the saddle either
can i just ride on you i guess so but it
does its own thing
[Music]
do i just repeat
repeat
[Music]
until it lights me
that's snow
[Music]
snowy area again really
repeat until heart
doesn't look like hearts
but it goes wherever it wants to
wait i have cat hairs on my croissant
huh
[Music]
um
no heart that's
not looks like hearts to me
[Music]
now i will set this horse free
when the time comes
so don't cry about it don't even think
about it
no
tell me if i'm missing something guys
tell me if i'm running past
the swamp
i found something else
[Music]
isn't that
fat trees
the line doesn't go on very long oh
what are those
wrong way but this is an interesting way
[Music]
um dark wood
what is this
what's with those trees
[Music]
it's a regular forest
it looks special though
okay
where's my south here
[Music]
we should have stayed on top of the
trees
oh
is that ocean
oh yeah i guess it's just oh sorry
just a normal
[Music]
okay um i guess
maybe it's time to separate the horse
already i don't know
ah
so
i don't already want to let you go
[Music]
i don't want to let you go
no
what
is not his name i didn't give him a name
you separate the horses how many pieces
no
okay one
thanks for the good time
i hope you live a nice life how to get
off of you there we go
be free everyone be free
us
one was a great help
not really though
i should just fly again i don't know why
i'm so careful i actually haven't more
than enough
[Music]
power left in my
in my opinion
these trees though
wow
[Music]
maybe it's because i haven't played
minecraft in such a long time that
everything i look at is really
impressive to me
beautiful the beauty of the nature you
have to appreciate it sometimes yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
even your simple things
i got by homies what
[Music]
there's no tigers yet right
i'm eating a chocolate croissant
half of it because i ate the other half
for breakfast
hmm
[Music]
which animal
no it would be so cool if they would add
like lions and so on to the to the
deserts
or like the wastelands i don't know
and snakes
snakes in the desert would make sense
i saw
that i saw that
i spy
with my little eye some temple
[Music]
on the water ruin
i'm scared i don't want to
[Music]
a die a boy a boy a boy a boy a boy a
boy a boy a boy a boy a boy a boy a boy
a boy a boy a boy a boy a woman a boy a
bird a bird a boyfriend
why am i scared i killed them before but
i'm scared i can't i can't i can't risk
this now
i already haven't tried it i don't need
another one
okay
suddenly i knew it i knew that that
place was cursed
oh my god
[Music]
no i don't need another track i was like
little key thinking maybe i go find him
now
but
it's not worth it right it's not worth
it
but it would be funny if he would drop
it again and i get a second trident a
second no trident
it won't drop anyway um
you know who you're talking to right the
lucky phoenix who got a trident from
[Music]
you've challenged me all of you chat and
the trident guy have challenged me
i feel challenged
[Music]
that was him right
and what i heard i heard something
i felt attacked
[Music]
i have a golden apple right
where'd it go
time to kill a [\h__\h]
[Music]
crazy
it's hard to see
you think it's better to see without the
shaders right now
a taco
[Music]
i love this this is the this is that
that feeling that i've missed so much
the the what's the word
[Music]
adrenaline yes
excuse me are those who try to gun
why am i trying to shoot them like this
it's kind of hard
i saw him
i don't think
[Music]
what's going on
what's going
what's going on what's going on
what's going on
then drop it that bastard
i killed free trident guys right now i
think
why was there free
anyone else
[Music]
no trident would have been really
[\h__\h] legendary
oh that was just the bubbles
just the air ah
[Music]
yeah
they were having a dragon's only party
hey give me more
give me give me more give me more give
me me
[Music]
where more
the others where's the party
now i'm excited
[Music]
mom
i've never seen so many of them at once
and even like a tiny one
that's that's looks really good a tiny
child with trident
i mean
all right let's move
on moving on
[Music]
b where are you going now you're gonna
land in the water why is it so fat is it
giant b
titan b
is this an optical illusion or why is it
so [\h__\h] huge
it's massive oh wait now it looks now it
doesn't look so big anymore it does look
big
massive b
what was that ah he turned into a
water guy
[Music]
this is so frick i love them
what was i gonna say
anyway
um
i need this back and
i'll put
you know what i'll keep this and then
the totem
and the fireworks
and
i think that's
it
and
i guess
i'm ready to go
[Music]
sorry for the little
adventure but adrenaline felt really
good i couldn't stop myself
it could so
southwards
wait do i have my ship yes okay
okay
trying to figure out where i am
now we didn't loot that thing
unfortunately
but i'm quite happy with the adventure
itself
that's what counts guys oh is that the
swamp
but not the right swamp right
oh what is that pretty thing it's just
flowers right
it's not the right swamp i suppose
it's a swamp yeah but not the right
swamp i guess we can look anyway for a
frog
for now
just just checking in
where would they spawn i suppose near
the water that looks like something
where a frog would live
maybe if i make frog noises it will come
to uh say hello to me
[Music]
these are so pretty
where are those
why are they so glowy
[Music]
i don't think there's a frog here
i was probably the sheep of the cows
that ate the frogs here
endangered species frog
frugal
[Music]
oh it's so nice i like this
i like the way this is built
sometimes
when i'm nervous and i try to do this i
can't do it my mouth just kind of
tightens up
and i can't make it you guys are
probably wondering how i do it
it's a talent that i've
found
a long time ago many many years ago and
since then it's like the only
only
specific talent that
if i
[Music]
uh first try frog
it's orange froggle
why it's just so high
but if i in order to
oh
in order to bring it do i need a second
one
well can you
make babies on your own it's so cute
[Music]
i have a frog
i was just gonna fly by the swamp i
wasn't even gonna look is it shy
can i get close
to the frogs run away
i'm doing
i feel like i heard a second frog
oh
they attack
bring out the slime balls really dark
rocks are pretty chill
okay how do we do this
can i mess it up is there a chance i'll
mess it up
okay
paid slimeball
do i give it
to it from a distance or
where did it go i hear it i hear the
noise
[Music]
well follow me if i am
get them closer together how
[Music]
yes
i think it's waiting for me to give the
food to it but where's the other one did
i have to be close together
lure them okay are you gonna follow me
[Music]
he's so cute
where's frog friend
[Music]
it follows me
[\h__\h] i lost the other one i knew this
would happen
if we just run around a little bit with
the food in the hand
i'm sure it will get to me
they don't attack me though who the [\h__\h]
said they attack others
with poison or so
come here froggy no big jump
mission accomplished yeah
pretty easy where are we
fourteen
six seven
twenty two thousand
is that a frog i feel like i saw a frog
there or was that just a sun
portal
perfect
portal i can make a portal here
i mean i don't even need it to make a
point where where's frog
uh a frog okay frog one
maybe i should like try to capture it
by building around it but
where did the other franco go
[Music]
i don't hear it
lucky phoenix
[Music]
that's just in exchange for not getting
that trident that i was supposed to get
yeah yeah you know i have to
i have to just uh
balance it out you know i can't use all
my luck at once and and the trident guys
they were like oh we want to give you
the trident but
i feel like you want the frog more right
now
which is correct
it's correct
i just
for the life of me i cannot find the
second one now
i'm very sure there was one
[Music]
trap frog before sleeping i think it
won't leave me but it loves me
it loves me and my food
i might do that frankl
[Music]
i heard it
where's my bed
all right it might be in the hole
it will be there don't worry
[Music]
i'm gonna make tadpoles oh yeah remember
last time i visited my mommy
uh
[Music]
last time i visited my mommy um she
showed me that she had tadpoles too like
she built a little bit of a water thingy
really not much you couldn't even call
it a pond to be honest
and uh
yeah
do they need something to survive like
water
[Music]
now just believe in it following me
forever um
yeah puddle basically a puddle
yeah and apparently like a frog
nested and made some eggs and then made
some tadpoles
what the [\h__\h] did the other one go
okay the other one is somewhere close to
the bed so let's get this one come on
hi
follow me
i feel like that would be even more if i
look for them
because i'm just you know i'm the frog
lady of course they come to me first
before anyone else
of
[Music]
[\h__\h] course so cute i love these way
more than the stupid axolotls
[Music]
i don't care for
look at that axolotls balance can an
excellent do that no what the [\h__\h] can
an axolotl do nothing
can your axolotl catch its food from a
10 meter distance which is where did it
go did it go into the water
come here come here come here
come here
come on
we're so close
they attacked round
my frog could do that too but they have
better [\h__\h] to do
it's happening look at them meeting
they're like oh nice to meet you let's
make babies oh my god kiwawa is helping
us make babies
the ceremony will begin now do i have to
get even closer
oh my god
um wait i need to take a photo
oh my god look at us
[Music]
don't go away what the [\h__\h]
i spend too much time taking photos come
now i feed them was that close enough
do we have to be on do we have to be
like on
do we have to
[Music]
do you have to be on water
make sure to wait for them how do i
do it
what did i do
are you breathing right now you are
pooping it out
oh is that one making it
what follow
what
okay now wait for them to hatch oh my
god this is so exciting
this is so exciting
do i make another one while we're at it
because i guess he he let everything out
that you know he had
but maybe we should wait i don't know
how how long does it take
do you know how long it
takes they have a timer okay but this
one hasn't laid anything
do they both have a timer
is there like a
do i know that this is a he now and this
is a she
or do frogs even have a
i don't want to let them go
few minutes cool down okay
both are genderless
yeah are they like genderless only in
minecraft also in reality
but i can't swim away oh smart
like this
won't they die when they hatch if
there's like no room to move
don't go don't go stay you want to see
your children's birth
only in minecraft aha okay okay in
reality they don't have to look at them
i'll be a great mommy to your frog
babies because i can at least speak
their
inna can't
[Laughter]
more room
okay
free buy free
i hope they don't hatch now
oh [\h__\h] i thought that was a frog
a tadpole swimming away
how about this uh
maybe
maybe like this
don't go don't go don't go don't go i
love you
that's true
this is not enough
that's good right
look i can make it a bit bigger
we have to think about like how to uh
we need to make a nice place for them
and something where they can't just [\h__\h]
off
taller
a little more
oopsie
okay
this looks good
frog stay with me
it's a precious moment
[Music]
how long is this gonna take
oh my god
[\h__\h] is that how do we do it
how do i
do this
does there have to be water in it
jump in
get water they hatched early
[Laughter]
how fast how much time they have before
they turn into frogs
frog babies
[Music]
i can give one to ena i guess i guess i
could kill 14.
we can have our frogs breed and then
we'll have endless frogs now will they
automatically be uh orange or could they
be other colors when they grow up now i
have four
now this one i will leave so you can be
adopted by your actual parents okay
i will leave this one because i have no
more pockets
[Music]
depends when they grow up ah depends on
temperature oh what was that
i hope no one eats this deadpool
i'll let it i'll let it go to freedom
and go go little tactical girl
swim
your parents are somewhere else but good
luck
oh no it's gonna it's gonna die it's
probably gonna die hi i got your babies
thank you so much i could make more but
i don't have any more i mean i have iron
but i think i'm good
for now i think four four four tackles
that sounds good enough green on cold
but maybe i should make different uh
ponds in different places then
orange and normal and white on warm
biome
[Music]
could always make more later yeah yeah
i mean one one frog can make or two
frogs can make so many babies so
wow
nice one wow
it's a mountain climber i hope the
babies will have the same jeans
look at him go
look at him go oh wow
oh
are you okay of course you're okay no
damage taken
ever i'm so cute and slimy so cute
frog watching
forget bird watching new hobby frog
watching
parkour parkour frog
these tadpoles they can probably compete
in the olympics i'm telling you
[Music]
wow
amazing so inspiring i can learn so much
from you
look at him camouflaging i totally
couldn't see you there buddy you were
invisible literally invisible
amazing
[Music]
you're so amazing i know
they gave me a comment
and maybe i should interview them on on
on whole talk
oh my god i'm so happy
bucket bucket
i'm so happy
okay let's put them into a safe place
yeah
ah this is this is what happiness is
like i understand now
finally i've reached enlightenment
maybe i should put them in
no
that's okay
i still have so many slime but i only
i only used
one
i heard a frog
i hear frog jump
i wonder if there's more but if they
if they're in swamps does how do i know
it's a colder
where does it say
cold or warm does it say that here
anywhere
[Music]
how do i know that does it can it be
different um temperatures
within one biome
one swamp
i was scared buddy i was scared
[Music]
time to go home yeah probably one by
only one temperature okay
so even if it doesn't look cold though
it can be cold is it like it just
always looks like this but it could be a
cold one
where is my stuff
hi
i wonder if you're the same one or a
different one
there we
no mangroves yeah i guess i mean
we didn't need them
i didn't need them
maybe we should make more
i'll make a bucket
scrolls
[Music]
i'm gonna make more babies
more
i run
skunks so i can also you know give them
to others you know
three buckets
i have to let like two go two tadpoles
probably
okay
why can i not make a golden bucket huh
worthy of the tadpoles
where is that frog i heard him
franco
[Music]
here you are come with me let's find
your your soulmate again
the
uh cooldown should be over by now oh
there's it there he is
hello
what's mostly
[Music]
what's happening the [\h__\h]
is he okay
wow
oh my god wait chill
what
i think he's done
come here
chill the [\h__\h] out we need to make
babies i know he was just really excited
about it
he's drifting okay are you ready
are you ready
was that was it okay did that not work
i think it didn't work
maybe you want it
you want that no
it doesn't work right now so i think it
worked
it doesn't work right now i can't feed
them anymore so i think it did work move
the grass
[Music]
oh there you go okay
am i doing something wrong now
you're not in the mood
bugged i mean he looked very bugged
maybe come down
[\h__\h] now i'm running up
okay
i think that worked they're looking at
each other
i can't
ah
i think he's going to
lay eggs
he's on the way why are you going that
way it's over there breeding station
over there thanks dude
i think that one worked yeah cause he's
ignoring he's ignoring my jelly balls
so cute
what do we name these two
such a cute couple
goals life goals
tbh
okay he did it i heard it
or she did it
flip and flop
frogo and froga
you put them in a really safe space huh
thinking that if i if you put them there
i wouldn't take them
but i am going to take them oh apple
okay
[Music]
flip and flop flotsam and jetsam jimin
jam we already have a gym and like uh
[Music]
and
oh my god so cute i just i can't take it
is this a good space that's a beautiful
space for them to breed
to um hatch
hop and dip
bloppa and fingers
frodo and just baggins
pete and repeat
croquio and frogalent kermit and crazy
bloom and gloom
kettle and pee
pot and toad
blob and plump these are such great
ideas
ted and paul
i like talent pool
[Music]
robert and ribbit frongo and frogarita
jelly and bean
[Music]
that's tough man
wait what was the first idea that people
gave me that one was great maybe i'll
just go with that
i also like kermit
[Music]
flip and flop yeah
flip and flop
oh but i like kermit
but we have so many frogs i know we're
naming those two right okay
how about zoom and boom
because one zoomed and the other one
boomed by making babies
[Music]
what do you think about that
they zoom and then they boom
[Laughter]
i like that
i'll call them zoom and boom
i like those names yeah maybe we'll meet
them again someday
didn't i have a nametag can i name them
[Music]
not with me
okay
this is such a nice spot
i'm such a good breeder i should become
a frog breed breeder
[Music]
yeah i'm glad you like those names
okay that but we'll have so many more
frogs to name so i think i want all the
names that you guys gave me i want to
use them on the on the new babies that
we're gonna get
out of these
i wonder if it's a fixed number of how
many
will hatch
or is it random
like a certain number like three to six
or so
[Music]
no
no i'm not talking about super and
boomer no no no it's just you know cause
he zoomed
and then they boom boom boom you know
and they make love
two to five
three two six
really
where's the rest of them
[Music]
come on you can do it
come on
hatch i hear frog
oh
there he goes
i saw him jumping over there huh there
he is my beloved zoom
zoom's just chilling this is their swamp
no one shall disturb their swamp
if any other halloween member wants to
go to this swamp they must first
get my permission
just kidding no they can go
oh but but but they better be careful
and not
not abuse my frogs
yeah we're really good buddies now okay
i wanted to see them hatch but i think i
need to sleep
[Music]
okay
look
okay my babies
[Music]
it's my swamp it's my swamp
i claimed it no it's not it's not my
swamp but i represent
these frogs here
this frog land i am like their
their lawyer basically it's their swamp
it's the zoom and boom swamp
[Music]
i heard evil zoom or boom
when are you gonna hatch these are late
hatchers i guess the other ones you guys
were staying there early i guess they
really were is that i thought it's a
fixed time but
maybe they really
have early hatches and late hatches
swamp overseer
i'll take the coordinates
[Music]
i bless their relationship yeah
and but they also do it do they not do
it
do they do it naturally without the
jelly
[Music]
do right
i want to watch them do it naturally
no they don't
oh
without me
[Music]
they would not have made love what does
that make me
not so many that's okay i don't have so
many buckets anyway
cute baby
cute
now i have
uh
sink somewhere
where did i put that here
one two three four five six
[Music]
and hey i didn't even use up half of my
hot wings
yeah yeah
[Music]
she will love frogs
yeah we talked a little bit about
froggles
oh she will love it she'll appreciate it
i'm sure
okay okay my dear frog friends zoom and
boom
where are you i heard you jump
i hurt you
my beloved
my beloved i just oh
i should check out the portal too i
should build
[Music]
i should finish it and then i can see
where the coordinates are in the nether
that would be helpful for building later
then i would know where to go
so smart
when will i ever stop being so smart
we need uh
wait this is bigger than is it bigger
than it needs to be no and one two three
lentil free
yeah i think i got some obsidian with me
i am so smart
for bringing that okay let me go get the
obsidian
wow
such a genius kiwa was such a genius
i know that was boom yeah i know i know
and i couldn't have been zoomed
i i can
differentiate them
i have exactly free obsidian because
it's all according to keikaku my friends
[Music]
stepped on you
i love you i love you oh this is the
best day of my minecraft life
best [\h__\h] day of my minecraft live
subaruship
oh wait so i i don't need three i need
two huh because the corners are not
necessary
there we go
that should work
peaks that was just a peak
okay
uh yeah i want to find a more warden too
sometime
uh but i think it's good that we didn't
go right into that this time because i
needed to you know get used to minecraft
again
how do you make this again
wait how do you
what do you need again
crying obsidian won't work
really
oh [\h__\h]
i don't have enough
one
two
three
one two three uh
might be fine
okay wait uh let me get my proper
pickaxe
my stronger one
it's gonna be enough actually hi boom
so happy being surrounded by frogs man
oh by the way like um i was talking
about wanting to get an aquarium right i
haven't gotten it yet but i haven't
given up on it either there's just some
um things that came in between the
planning
um
but i want to get it soon
maybe in the
end of july or beginning of august
i'm gonna get myself an aquarium
remember that i think i told you guys
about
you know the plan i did right
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i also talked a little bit about it with
um i told her that i want that uh what
was it called not the it's like a
lobster
uh
yeah so we talked a little bit about you
know the possibilities
he almost like the best person to talk
about uh that kind of stuff
i had a crawfish crayfish crawfish
yeah originally i wanted like just a
normal crab but in german when you say
crips
it kind of
it it means crab
but
it also means the other thing i don't
know
yeah it's just like one word for both
things
i guess apparently i don't know it's so
confusing so
i think
oh yeah and then i take this one
okay
i'm gonna put that one here
maybe this is annoying
let me
i'm scared to go through
first of all
let me put some stuff
away i don't think we'll go
i don't know should i
i don't know the
coordinates maybe i have a screenshot of
the coordinates of where hi zoom
of where i ended um
the
railway the ice way
[Music]
i wonder
because i wonder if i should con like
just build it now already
go back further never but that might be
a lot of
a lot of work um
ahead of us
bring the shulker leave them in the
sugar what oh yeah okay
oh put stuff in it just commits i guess
so
okay but we should still check out the
coordinates
yeah okay okay
um
[Music]
okay
then i'll put everything
forgot it was that easy
[Music]
i forgot that was a thing in minecraft
uh
[\h__\h] no space
i have another one
thank god i brought another one
[Music]
bye tube it's gonna be bye bye soon oh
no
oh no
sad
you like the names of my equipment thank
you
why am i wearing this
i don't remember like putting this on
i feel like i definitely changed out of
that after the
festival
sports fest never ends i wonder if
they're gonna do it this year wasn't it
around summer time last year
i wonder if they're planning to do it
this year
when was it last year
well no november really it felt like
summer time i guess not
ah
they just did it
earlier
on purpose uh
oh
[Music]
i think i'm ready to go
uh wait so
oh but wait i need to
[Music]
i ah i will lose the one and the chest
right
[Music]
i mean i won't lose it i'll just like
keep it here i guess but it's probably
lost because i won't come back
yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay
i guess we're gold okay i mean i don't
think they'll kill me immediately if i
walk in it's probably no one around
anyway
but yeah
so
[Music]
goddammit
like this
[Music]
and i might as well make a tower
and then jump into the water
maybe maybe the tower will help someone
to find this place
or me
if i need my
uh if i need my thing back okay go
[Music]
yeah
oh wait what if my bed is there i'll
just respawn here oh wait wait wait then
i guess uh there you go
oh nice
so i think i'm ready to die
right
[Music]
i'm
ready
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
you guys are so sweet so sweet
okay let's check out the coordinates
here
i wonder where we land
[Music]
we are
let's take it like this okay
uh-huh
it's a
decent area
i can see myself
building a railway here
from the top
[Music]
or the ice way
kind of hard to see
of course but uh
time for fire bath
yeah i guess so
[Music]
it's loading over there
i did get the coordinates so we good
[Music]
i can't believe we're gonna extend the
the railway even further to another
interesting location the swamp not the
best
swamp
what is that
not the best swamp because it's uh
it's
it's not the thing a bastion am i
excited about finding a bastion
oh
oh i think i am
you guys are so i guess i'm i'm excited
about it don't go there
free loot
a souped-up never fortress i kind of
want to check it out but i have nothing
to work with because there's gonna be
something attacking me there right
bastion mob strong yeah but i'm gonna
die anyway i guess we can try to take a
look
why not take a look huh
let's see how fast i'll die
exciting
it's so [\h__\h] dark
oh
[Music]
loot
i see loot
what is that floor
how do i get there i need blocks
i want to build i wish i would have just
brought blocks so i can build over there
bastion pavlin's strong and they'll
probably shoot me before i even reach it
huh
is there like if i go from
the bottom
can i climb bumps
oh [\h__\h] yeah he's gonna kill me
where is that the same
are they the same now this one is a
normal one
they're just gonna kill me aren't they
oh
yeah okay here he comes
oh no
wait he ran away he didn't i thought he
was gonna get me
maybe i can sneak my way there
i'm invisible
no one sees me
i have gold armor yeah
are they not gonna attack me
[Music]
give me some blocks
pick them up why does it not pick them
up why are they falling apart
if i open it ah and i guess oh if i died
and
but i wanted to i guess look inside
see what's there
what to look forward to
[Music]
oh
bastion achievement if we're coming to a
bastion
i don't see anything
[Music]
i want to go up there
that in three two one it's coming it's
coming
i couldn't even see he attacked me even
though i didn't cough in anything
[Music]
it's okay we only gained things oh
wow
we only gained things we gained so much
yeah and now i want to uh
go
i guess
should i distribute the tadpoles
because i can't distribute frogs right
i'll just distribute tadpoles and i'd be
like do whatever the hell you want with
them
breed them where you want and then have
fun
and maybe we can build
one
just for completion sake we can build
one um
[Music]
one pond for my own frog
i don't know should i take two
i think i should take two so i can make
more tadpoles because now we have six
tadpoles i'll give one to amen
two gouda because she's a fish
cali doesn't need one she doesn't play
and one to ena
that's three
four five six okay
and maybe i'll give uh i'm in a second
one so she can breed them
and then i have two and that and and ame
has two
you know one i mean i'm
sure you know once more too but i guess
i'll just make more tadpoles don't worry
i'll just make more they'll all
eventually get more frogs
ah it's so funny to me
how easily i find things in minecraft
like the elytra oh hello
hello there
sorry i'm just so
so
yeah okay this what i'm feeling right
now literally can only be described in
german
i am so shocked and full
[Laughter]
[Applause]
all right here we are
back home safe and sound
kite
[Music]
here they are
do they like
did i go bad
i hope not
smug
yes yes i'm smug
okay i'll make chests for them i guess i
can put the other things that i i gave
some people in
um i can give them i don't know what to
say anymore my brain
[Music]
i need to make um
chests
make chests
make chests make chests give frog make
pond make more frog
[Music]
one
two
three
now i wonder when are they gonna see it
sign um i need [\h__\h] sticks
[\h__\h] sticks man
[Music]
even the bots aren't excited really
okay
freeze oh perfect
three cents all right all right free
free signs
okay for ammo we can now take the moss
back
she can ma like build an environment for
the frog with moss
[Music]
is there something i need to
definitely have for an environment for
my frogs
oh i got it was it gonna die if if the
water is gone was it immediately gonna
die
yeah it was
oh my god
[Music]
i can't let my baby die yo this is
something i gave her before
no okay
oh my god that scared me
okay i'll put this here
i'll put on this and let me get two
and the shield sign
ghostly
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's so old isn't it
trick or treat that's halloween
[Music]
i'm being approximate
i can make mud oh wait i didn't see the
answers from you guys to my question
[Music]
uh what is there something i need for
the environment where i'll have my frog
in
this is what this was a pr
they can put the old ones away i don't
mind
i'll just build one in front of it i
guess or
like here you think she'll notice
water that's it okay water air ground
okay
uh one frog
frog for
gura
have fun
yeah okay it's okay
okay
and one for india
[Music]
she hasn't been there in like a year
uh well i'll answer no i'll let her know
on the
discord
that there's a present for her whenever
she plays minecraft again
she's so noisy namas uh ina's place
from for ina from kiara let me bend your
heart she didn't take this away either
i'll i'll take it
i'll take it
she probably feels bad to like take away
anything
okay
here is the frog that you saw that your
heart so desired
frog for
inna
once again
i'm
first
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's not mean that's just facts
history repeats itself
[Music]
what what does bm mean bm
smug
yeah
[Music]
bad man
huh do you mean bad manners
[Music]
oh come on don't be so overreacting it's
not so bad
oh [\h__\h] i need food
why
why weren't they saying that
bratty matters more like yeah
i think it's fine ina knows me
[Music]
nina gets it
it's joke
before android
i can use
i can use them
my pretty azalea things and stuff for
frog
place right
yes
a joke man
[Music]
okay
make nice place for frog
where did i put that here
okay
i have moss
okay let's i don't know bring whatever
is green
oh they like the lily pads they like the
lily pads
flowering flowering
drip leaf
must
okay
[Music]
do they kill each other if i put a frog
in an axolotl
is actually all going to kill
the
frog
rip leaf
good question yes and that's so sad
it's so sad
don't
put the down sword people and
i don't know how to make this i feel
like i should follow a tutorial to make
it look really pretty but i'm going to
try my best to do it on my own
um but what could i use
i i need a fence right because they're
going to jump really high
i need a i need a wall another fence
[Music]
you use glass
glass and true okay
but what if i want to feed them and make
more
i guess i have to make like a double
door so
i i go for the first door and then i go
for the second door
kind of like that
i don't think we'll
actually finish today but
okay
trap door
okay let's start let's start first with
like i don't know
how do i know what temperature it's here
this is is this warm or normal
i know there's some snow somewhere close
so i could get to a cold one fast
probably
[Music]
i see
um it
minecraft windswept hills
sounds cold
cold
you have snow on the ground
so i can get a green wait was it green
and cold
green frog and cold biome right
when's that tails of the cold okay it's
moderate for mother red for frogs
[Music]
okay well let's make it here
somewhere here but
oh my god
is it still
it's still winsor tails okay
oh let's find some space cause there's
[Music]
maybe under oh maybe under the railway
so when people look down they can see my
frogs frogs rabbit
[Music]
there's space here i think but that's
not
that's windswept forest
is that something else then is it
different i mean i don't care what color
they're gonna be
[Music]
this place will be orange
and now it's windsepped hills again
i don't care what it is but i think
should i make it on the
got him
should i make it on the same height as
the railway
was that weird it's like a floating
thingy
riveting content
i guess i could like make this into a
platform here
and i need some
i need tools what the hell i have
nothing
i need some tools and
[Music]
stuff
you like the idea of putting it next to
punch express all right
if you like it then i like it
it jumped eight blocks yeah okay
good to know
so it must be like nine blocks high
no problem
leave it to me
[Music]
i put this away i'm scared of letting
them out accidentally again
let's take this let's take this
let's take
[Music]
i this to play world of warcraft right
now
for some reason
do we need sand they like sand we can
use sand
[Music]
answering my own questions could use
sandstone maybe
more dirt
maybe
should i use glowstones
try using some glowstones
i have glass
not endless amounts but
it's a good amount
all right
[Music]
okay let's try with this stuff
where's my where's my top part
[Music]
hey i used to play with the warcraft
i used to
long time ago long time ago
and i played it once on a stream too
it was really nostalgic getting back
into it
i could use the terracotta
maybe the white color
look at this
[Music]
get this
look at this
maybe i need this too
okay i'll put this here for now
[Music]
okay
put on
armor
oh
maybe
all right i don't need both of them
mending silk touch
okay
two lighters yeah i had even more but i
think
yeah i gave one to tekora
maybe i even had more than that but
that's what i remember
yes everybody let's build something nice
i usually don't really like building
that much in minecraft but
oh well
well i want something nice for my frogs
and that motivates me right now because
i really love the frogs
they're currently still tadpoles but
we'll get them to be
the best frog they could ever be the
best frogs that you guys have ever seen
so first we start
by making
a platform i guess
how to make
a platform
tony eisen
[Music]
how big
how big should it be
[Music]
yeah they're kermit one of them will
definitely be a kermit what's up other
other famous frogs besides kermit
where did that one come from originally
let me place my bed
sleep the crazy frog oh yeah frogger
yeah yeah
[Music]
foreign
it's gonna be a big thing huh
maybe sideways a bit more
[Music]
okay
i think that's good
size wise why is that different
rooted dirt what is that
what does that do how's that different
it does look different
is it okay to use that or is that more
precious and i shouldn't be using this
one
it has roots in it
is it a waste to use it
ah it's below the other layer uh-huh
it's fine
[Music]
okay
okay and then
how what do i want it to look like i'm
not sure
[Music]
let me just around we make
one more dirt layer and then we fill it
with
think the frogs don't like sand
or do they prefer dirt
i'll make a layer of sand
[Applause]
yeah
i think
i think grass won't grow that's okay we
have moss
and then we can
oh yes
i'll have it look kind of sandy i guess
i'll fill it with sand
like this
[Music]
and then i'll surround it with the with
the sandstone
maybe
[Music]
we are making a frog pump cause now i
have the frogs already i thought it
would take us longer to find them
and here we are
didn't didn't find the mangrove though
but that's okay that's for another time
then
and then we do it like this what do you
think guys and then the top part this is
only the
bottom half and then the top part will
be glass
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay
i'm gonna make another layer
looks nice color fits yeah
yeah there's frogs in minecraft now
hasn't always been like this
it's new
and i love frogs
so i got me a frog
this is now two layers high
[Music]
uh
they can jump what eight blocks
up
from a ground block or also from the
water because i'm like
wondering
[Music]
i guess
what am i doing
[Music]
yes springy little guys it's so cute
when they jump i'm so
proud of them when they do that
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna make a glass roof
i think the next layer i'm gonna make
glass because now we're on the same
height
as
the railway
i don't have too much but this
wait if it's enclosed at the top anyway
then it doesn't matter how high they
jump
i'm gonna make it as high as i can
what's wrong with me now
yeah i have lily pads yeah
i have some from before
[Music]
i got all kinds of nice looking stuff we
have to fill this up with water too
though but not completely so we're gonna
make like uh
we're gonna landscape you know as if
this was a terrarium
mommy will be so proud of me i'm making
my first terrarium i should watch your
tick tock tutorial
okay then maybe we do need some more
dirt
[Music]
sound okay
and prank
a scale
right
okay let me look something
up on my notes
[Music]
um
yeah it was one time i wrote this down i
told ina i am writing this down
and i was one time when
me and ina
uh
and good at two i think was she was
there too in the moment
uh we were walking
[Music]
around is 21 enough for this one
let's see we were walking around
somewhere and there was a sign
there was a sign that said like no
smoking allowed
and
[Music]
what did she say
and then
yeah ina looks at me
and she says no smoking kiara and i'm
like
yeah i don't smoke what do you mean
and she says it again and i'm like
really confused
what do you mean i say
and then
a little bit later she
she says
um
because
because you're smoking hand
[Music]
but she couldn't say that first because
i don't know she was too embarrassed or
something
she couldn't get it out first i had to
like tickle it out of her basically
i need my i need to bring my
my ladder thingies
myself
that was
funny she was flirting with me
flirt 100
super flirt
it was
not really effective though i didn't
feel
like flattered i just felt it was funny
because she couldn't
she couldn't get it out first
you know you know she she's kind of you
know flirting on stream sometime right
like she will she will say these things
these flirts but in real life she's too
shy to say it out loud properly
took her a few tries to finally say it
oh sh where did i put those ladder
fingers
here
[Music]
it helps if you get it well but she just
said no smoking i don't know it was kind
of noisy too so i didn't hear her so
well i thought she was asking me if i
smoke or something and i'm like no i
don't smoke
make glass ah yeah i need glass ah [\h__\h]
how do you make glass again burn sand or
what was it melt sand
it was it again
and then i should make some buckets too
probably
smelt sand
sand
doco
sandstone doesn't work right
[Music]
i might need to get some more sand
the thing i said to good adult it wasn't
because i really wanted her to kiss me
so i just wanted to you know
i think it was
pretty genius what i said
she was so shook
so shook
let's just do this one for now that
could be enough
i got her right my god you're so good i
know
i'm not normally this fast though like
i think especially in english language
it just takes me
a while to come up with these things and
by the time
i come up with it then it's already too
late usually but at that moment oh i was
so fast my my brain was going high speed
so fast
i can buy glass from the librarians in
phoenix and berlin did they have glass i
don't need that much more though i think
really i don't remember seeing them
selling glass
let me get some
iron first
don't have some iron somewhere
look of iron
oh yeah here's a glass too
uh with the iron i will make some
buckets so that i don't have to keep on
running back and forth back and forth
back and forth so i can bring some more
water at once
oh i guess i could just make an endless
there is one close by but still
still
eh wouldn't buckets be useful i'm not
sure what i'm doing right now
[Music]
i'll just make a few buckets
oh i won't have spaceballs done
i know are they stacked oh yeah right
they stack
okay but then still i won't have much
space chocomate
let me put some stuff into the
into a chest close by
[Music]
a two by two water source
can i make that in the enclosure
and then i don't know how high do i want
things to be filled up anyway
[Music]
i feel like i need i want more sand too
i think i think i think
[Music]
i think i need to fix something
well first of all
i mean we're doing this no plan so not
everything can be perfect right away
let's put that here
let's put the birch planks here
oh that's different
[Music]
let's put them in there and this here
okay so
i think
i'll fill it up
oh wait
a bit more
[Music]
like i'll get rid of
this layer of sand
fill it up a bit more with dirt
hello welcome to the minecraft stream
yeah
oh i probably
could i talk was there something i want
to talk about the concert
you guys have questions about the
concert i feel like there was more that
i wanted to talk about but i i can't
remember right now
have any questions
[Music]
what's the hardest song to record oh
two people in a row asking that okay
hardest engine for dancing
um
heart
challenger i would say it's very fast it
has a lot of different moves it's more
intricate than
hinotoni and it's very energetic so
it would be also the most exhausting
song to perform
also
also it was very difficult to capture as
well
was making some problems here and there
i should make like a viewing platform
around it too
yeah and um
love you love the little dance moment in
sparks oh sparks
sparks you know was surprising it was a
bit hard to learn because
some of the moves
are like
uh not my not the typical dance style
that i'm used to like i'm used to
like j-pop kind of
dancing
j-pop you know cute cute dancing
and for sparks i asked my choreographer
to go more in a k-pop or like cool
direction
and hip-hop you know
and she did um but you know there were
new things to learn for me you know like
the the car
movement i don't know if you know what
i'm talking about but
yeah there were some car movements and
then there was this one move
where i did like a
body roll
and that was so hard for me to get down
uh
which part i think it was after the
first chorus
it's like where i turn around and then i
do a swoosh swoosh swoosh body roll with
my whole body while also making some
hand movements too that was so difficult
to me to like multitask
because i already had to think so hard
to get the
the
the movement for the
for the body roll with the leg correctly
i don't know that one was really tough
for me um that had sparks had some moves
that
um i needed to get used to first
um but i want to say like sparks uh
i can dance that much better it's just
that there were
the way
it was like um on in the concert
that's
it's it's kind of very scuffed you guys
probably didn't notice but
uh
there's
there were some
i don't know what the issue was
um but my body is actually pretty
scuffed in the sparks
um performance
um it will look much better in the
director's cut so please wait for that
it will look much better
[Music]
why did i make it so deep
actually
maybe i should make some layers i guess
so they will have fun if there's some
layers
[Music]
i'm gonna get some layers in there
make some islands
find them
and then they can dive a little bit hell
yeah
like so
but this is what you call landscaping
ladies and gentlemen
onions are blaze too right yeah
um what else let me think uh
ohio was probably um
one of the most
intricate choreos that i did but the
good thing is with kenya in ohio
i already knew that choreo since a long
time ago
so
that one was actually the easiest for me
i was the most used to it which is maybe
also why it it might have been one of
the best looking dancers i did
uh
in the concert because i was just so
used to it
yes a director's cut is needed because
for my own satisfaction and because i
think kfp at least will watch it but i i
get what you mean yeah
i also uh
i think probably mostly
yeah it will be kfp watching
but yeah that's okay
oh [\h__\h] that doesn't work the way i
wanted i guess that's okay
that's okay
[Music]
already watched it five times thank you
uh
i don't know if he was like
proud or so if he felt that way i don't
know his exact emotions
but i know he was happy about it
yeah
yay
success
i've waited to say that for so long
like originally my original plan was to
sing that during the debut
during the the debut stream
as an homage to him for people who don't
know my artist my creator
is
he is the artist of black work shooter
and steins gate
and yeah that's why i always wanted to
sing that for him but for blackrock
shooter for the longest amount of time
it was kind of like iffy with the
permissions
so i never sang it
and then um i
ever since the debut i kept on poking
management like hey hey hey
how about now uh we got can we like work
on getting the permissions for that
please blah blah blah i kept on poking
and poking and poking them endlessly
and then at some point
finally
uh fairly recently actually
um
i i finally got the okay to do it
[Music]
and then i was like yeah so i can
perform it for the
for the concert thank god
yeah
hallelujah
took them so long though
way too many i wish i got a slim oops
i did such a great job singing black
wash with a vanguard it made the concert
that much more memorable yeah i think it
was really important
and i wanted it to be special you know i
i even though i got the black rock
shooter permission a little while ago i
didn't want to sing it yet
i wanted to keep it for this very
special moment
and
i think it was worth waiting
it was worth waiting
i would say
[Music]
how is this looking i think it's looking
pretty natural
i like it so far
are these trees
what are those
these are the flower blocks are those
the trees
they're bushes oh
[Music]
i will make a roof yeah
okay thank you in a chapter in the
concert i didn't even see it
but yeah i heard it later
[Music]
landscaping
i was so happy he stayed up to watch
apple at the moment he wasn't at that
moment he was in america so he didn't
even have to stay up late for that
thankfully
it was a nice timing
chat was zooming indeed you know
so king robin ohio was the easiest for
me to dance even though it was one of
the most intricate ones
um
heart challenges the most exhausting and
somehow
also very difficult sparks was the most
unusual to me because there were so many
like different style of moves that i i
wouldn't have done before
and fall blood and ladylike as i told
you guys yesterday are made up choreos
from me a digital girl as well the
chorus at least like the rest was just
whatever yeah
and uh
what else then there was there was uh
the hello project song that the bigaku
you know i really wanted to perform one
hello product song and aya matsura
matsura aya is just like you know a god
in hello project history
um and she's a solo artist usually they
have a lot of idol groups in hello
project but matsura aya she was like i
mean she was part of morning wasabi but
also she was a solo artist as well
because she was so popular and she has a
lot of really good solo songs and i just
kind of even though the song was a
little bit like how to say derpy it's a
little bit of a derpy song but she makes
a lot of like a little bit derpy songs
but the vehicle was derpy and really
cool
um and i thought it would be a good
choice for the concert so i wanted to
squeeze that in there we actually
had to ask
hello project directly for their
permission to perform the choreography
and
i got permission for every choreography
that's not my own
um you know just just to make sure
everything is legit and you know
allowed
and i didn't get in contact with them
the management did but that makes me
hopeful that in the future i can do more
hello project songs
and dance their choreos
yeah wow
i want to i want to fill a whole concert
i kind of want to do like a hello
project
themed concert where the whole set list
is hello project songs
that would be so fun for me
and i think you know in karaoke when i
sing hello project songs it doesn't have
quite the same impact as if when i
perform them with a dance as well
um because yeah you guys mostly don't
know these songs
that i like so much
but with a choreo
additionally to it i feel like
even even if you don't know the songs
even if you're not really into idol
music it's still interesting to watch
the dancing is what makes it so much
more interesting to watch so
i want to do that
would you do mini money but what i want
to do one day
is i want to do
w
with
nineteen
and whoever knows w will
love this idea i think
[Music]
yeah
oh my god there's some people who know
w
was a two girls
unit
in the whole life
in hello project
which was very very
popular and legendary
because those two girls they were not
related but people said they looked
alike i don't really think they looked
alike but people said so
and they just i don't know they fit so
well together they had really a great
chemistry
and they were part of morning muslim as
well
but
they i don't know
they
were so popular as a unit it was
incredible it was crazy
yeah and for wilding performed together
made some songs and
they're iconic it's just so iconic
[Music]
i'm just taking the sand
i'm a bit of an idol otaku so of course
i know yeah i'm always happy to
have some
people with the same knowledge as me
here makes me happy
yeah w
ah they have such cute fun songs that
are so fun to perform with two people
you know because the choreos are are
made
for that and they're like interactive
with one another
so i can't
[Music]
what does it have to do with managing oh
because i think we would be pretty
perfect for that
i see us as the modern
and the vtuber version of w
could be sisters
but not obviously we're not sisters but
could be
because
just because we work so well together
and we look some somewhat like
similar as in with orange
i don't know not this f for me is like
the same like i don't think w looked
similar but people said so i don't know
i don't know what looked similar about
them if you give them the same outfit
and the same hairstyle of course they're
gonna look similar
that's pretty much about it wait i
wanted to um do the sand make it into hi
enderman i want to make it into class
almost as soon as my frog soon
you have complimentary vibes yeah i
think it would be perfect and also
because like where the i would say we're
the most i don't like besides sora
senpai
in her life
so who else would do it but us i always
wanted to do like a
like um something with energy
and that's just
the most perfect thing
[Music]
furnace
and now you're going to let me send a
million names huh million names what
about this person what about this person
what about this person but what about
this person you
[Music]
okay
oh my god i can't believe kiwamo doesn't
consider
so-and-so as an idol
she's such a [\h__\h]
what am i doing
[Music]
okay let's fill it up with water
fill it up with water
oh yeah i guess i can just do like this
[Music]
um
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] quack
don't disappear
we're froggy froggy isn't a safe place
i have to protect froggy
but i mean it's still a tadpole
baby frog
i only need two buckets oh i love it i
don't need that much water anyway
if you think about it so that you'll die
i'll just take these buckets and then
i'm happy
here's all i need
i don't even need that menu probably
let's go cause we're not making it into
an aquarium the frog is not a fish
a frog is a frog
yeah not fish frog needs some water but
also no
normal ground yeah yeah
it's it's a
my mom told me i forgot what's the in
between between a terrarium and an
aquarium what was it again
[Music]
true true words right true our words
have never been spoken before
[Music]
vivarium that's that's what it was yeah
i kind of want to make a bavarium in my
home someday first i'll start with an
aquarium and then one day i'll make a
vivarium because i want
frog
i want frog no matter what
i want my own frog do you guys know i've
kissed a frog before
[Music]
i have kissed a frog before
he did not turn into a prince though
kind of scammy
[Music]
they're very disappointing
scammed no i don't know i just i just
liked frogs and i wasn't
it was quite a long time ago
but
see i'm not a big fan of like spiders
and so on and bugs i mean i like i like
um caterpillars and stuff
but back then i would say i was less
scared of
such kind of things than
i was uh
than i am now
yeah
i wanted to yes that's what i wanted
yeah okay that looks nice that looks
nice
yeah and then i i don't know i had a
thing for frogs i liked frogs but i gave
one
and yeah he was very happy frog was
happy
of course it was consensual
i don't know if i would still give a
frog a kiss now i mean if i had to i
guess i would but
it wouldn't come to my mind it wouldn't
be the first thing that would come to my
mind i would say
when seeing a frog
yeah
i mean ken frog's concert of course what
are you talking about
have you not seen seen zoom and boom
getting on
together
that was obviously consensual
they even let me be part of it so
i mean
[Music]
i was watching the whole time
and i saw them
i saw them they were happy
they had the time of their life making
babies and then they parted ways
hashtag no commitments
oh it's okay i have the glass
so i can close it up
[Music]
i wanted to make a door though where
would i
i guess
when i make the platform around it
you know what i'll make a terracotta
to be fancy
so i'll make it like
[Music]
here i know it has to be higher so that
because it's supposed to be a viewing
platform
has to be on the height of the glass
so people can actually look inside
[Music]
wait i want to talk more about my
concert oh
you know
there's a reason why i chose so many
kira songs
they were in total with sparks
four kida songs she took up
it's like he took up most of
the concert
and there's a reason for it not because
like i liked them so much i liked them
but that wasn't the reason um but
because they're english
because kira makes english songs that i
can actually use like other english
songs you know like the famous whatever
songs like i don't know katy perry
christine aguilera whatever black eyed
peace
in order to sing those in an archived
concert i would have to go for a lot of
trouble of getting official perms
um
yeah that would most likely also cost
money and it would take a lot of time
and yeah
it's just
not really
um
it's not worth it
so
you know since i worked with kira before
i know i knew that his work is great
and i thought i should
sing his song so that the
english-speaking audience can enjoy and
understand at least a couple songs
that i'm performing
yeah and they're good too so
two
two flute fries with one stone
right
[Music]
and there's still many songs i want to
like
perform
one day from him
and also four blood was actually
originally planned as a song cover
anyway
which i think i'll still do
at some point
you guys were really liking
that one huh maybe if i do a song cover
of that i can actually make it a 3d
music video with the data the dancing
data for the concert i can just reuse
that probably
because it will be difficult for me to
record something again
uh in the near future
good thing is one can reuse the data
smart
yeah
it will be totally different though
it'll be a completely different
experience
[Music]
let's do one more layer it's getting
[\h__\h] high
but you know
it builds up pretty high too and i want
them to be able to jump
pretty high without restrictions
[Music]
so yeah
and have small cannon during church back
you know i was thinking about that for
future like concerts and music videos
if it's digitally
how
i don't always want to be the only one
dancing what i really like about
choreographies is like formations there
are pain in the ass to learn but
it just there's so much payoff it looks
so cool
and i used to learn dances with
formations as well
and
i kind of want to try something like
that now hold on myth
teaching them complicated formation
dances is
probably close to impossible
so
maybe just myself but with different
models like i could dance it and then
have like some kind of like
human
backup dancer models
yeah backing me up but still me dancing
i could do that probably for like music
videos and concerts
but i still like doing it all alone like
formation
cause it you need a really [\h__\h] big
brain for that
if you record
yeah and a big space ah ah it's that's
next level [\h__\h]
that's some next level [\h__\h]
okay i think
we'll try to finish it off ah but wait i
need i need to close it too
i'll need though
bit more a bit more sand to get some
uh glass for
closing it off
[Music]
you know you know am i doing the robot
they're good at doing the robot but i
can't have a whole music video
be a robot and i'm talking about you
know formation too
formation
is
that's not something for
you know amateurs you have to have like
training and commitment
i gotta say
[Music]
recording inaudible dance
i mean
it's probably because she was always so
tired
and she was like mom
no
can't you just do it
and i'm like no i want you to dance it i
want you to dance it
and then at some point i think she
mentioned this on her um
stream
but this was one of those
situations where one time
she indeed
kind of snapped at me
in an either way and then
relatively nice you know way yeah
uh
i mean she she said it's so herself but
yeah she was like oh okay we have to
make uh compromises at some point
i'm like
no
i will have you dance this
[Music]
you signed up for it no turning back now
no
you can do it inya
i wanted you guys to see her dance
i wanted us to do it together and i
didn't i didn't want it you know it's
not like i asked for
a really complicated choreo i just
taught them like four moves four moves
i i went really really really baby level
okay
i wasn't like torturing them or anything
i didn't even like
like you know do boot camp style
teaching
i didn't correct anything i was just
like try this you know
and then whatever comes out it's gonna
be fine
yeah
but we'll we'll see if we can like uh
go a bit more intricate next time
the tacos thank you kiara really
hopefully
[Music]
yeah this is just the beginning like for
future concerts yeah who knows maybe for
like a whole live english concert
someday
we might be asking for a bit more than
that but i think it was mostly because
she was really tired
on both occasions because we had to
re-record it once because the first time
we recorded it it was like really
buggy glitchy footage
and then we had to re-record it but then
we had some problems with her suit and
then yeah um she was like i'm gonna make
compromises
[Laughter]
and i'm like no we'll get it to work we
just started come on
we'll get it to work
uh funny
[Music]
yeah
how was emma with the dancing i don't
know i was like mostly like standing in
front of them we recorded it separately
because of the lack of you know
equipment but um i was like standing in
front of them
so that they could look at me
like from the back
um while they were dancing like as a
reference
[Music]
pleasure so i'm not sure i i could never
see them
i don't know how well they did i the
only thing i have is like you know that
footage from the concert that's all i
see
no no no mirrors
that would be reflective
that's a problem
no i really wasn't like that no
no i was really nice about it i was not
like a drill sergeant or anything not at
all
i was trying to make it as simple as
possible i'm not a teacher though so
i always say this like teaching
something is way different than doing it
yourself like with japanese language as
well like even if i can speak japanese
language doesn't mean that i can teach
it
and um
yeah
you know
try to make it
understandable and simple
yeah and also
i mean i i didn't have any like big
expectations anyway because i know they
don't have like prior experience with
dancing but one thing i will say
amen
is freaking flexible
[Laughter]
she may not have experience of dancing
and all that but she's really flexible
you guys probably don't know but i was
freaking shocked
[Music]
she didn't split
she can do a split yo
that's hot
come on chet
bunk horny bunk
i asked her like if she does stretches
and so but she said no no really
just natural flexibility what the [\h__\h]
insane
she seems like an active person
yeah well i guess like i don't know
activism body movement i don't know
about that
she's active as a person like you know
um like as in she has a lot of hobbies
i wonder if i'mma took gymnastics good
question
maybe ballet
can you imagine ami doing delay
taking bubba for a walk
that's not much
activity
[Music]
yeah
did she never do a
split in her
like vr and 3d streams before
she used to flex that flexibility yo
a year ago so ammo was less flexible
than gooda oh well i did compare them
both both of them
like when amy got down to do a flat a a
split
good i did it next to her and good i was
like
kind of able to do it too but ame went
lower with less effort
yeah i think she does a standing split
[Music]
and swole i'mma do this but i'm sure she
can i'm surprised she didn't so far
all right i think wait there's one more
coming i think
is there
no
it's going back
okay
[Music]
let's go
uh
we're gonna close it and then think
about how to do the
dwarfing uh how to
get inside and then we're gonna let the
tadpoles free
and maybe how long does it take for them
to grow up guys
in minecraft time
[Music]
keep two tactical spoons well let me
know
like
there's more tadpoles than the chests
that i give everyone else
worst case
rule free but what kyla is like what
what's the word hogging
and collecting all elytras in in their
end
kind of what i wanted to do too
farming elytras all of them that are
close by
damn
wait is this gonna be enough
[Music]
maybe um maybe i don't do d in these
edges
it doesn't have to be
i think it's high enough
let's see
if it's enough glass
not enough for closing none has to be
come on
[Music]
it might be enough
could be kitty
[Music]
believe in qibla
was in my real cat or cat here i think
that was my real cat
okay okay again
there we go
did that one fall down too no
hi monkey
donkey monkey's so cute
okay we closed it
uh i need to get back in sato so we will
make
a door
[Music]
maybe in the back somewhere
well
maybe here maybe on the side
and then i'll extend the platform
[Music]
yes it's my chunky wonky
real cat
we'll put a fence there probably as well
it's getting dark it is dark
[Music]
okay
let me sleep
i need to close an aisle meeting but i
want to finish this
let me eat maybe my brain will forget
that i need to go to an island meeting
if i eat something because i'm also
hungry
[Music]
um what's your next step
but can i um
[Music]
i
know it like
[Music]
make like a tunnel here
um probably has to be one more
to make two doors kind of or like a
fence and a door or something like that
[Music]
um right now
go to the um
[Applause]
does it look cool
i hope it looks cool i hope people
will look at my frogs and be like
damn those frogs are amazing holy [\h__\h]
i wish i had those frogs
[Music]
um
no more
[Music]
maybe somewhere else
i don't want to go
hmm
you can't force me to go
[Music]
do i need a trapdoor would it be useful
um
[Music]
don't post water
are you trying to manipulate my brain
[Music]
very funny
wait i can put blueberries in there i
was thinking of glow stones but they
take up so much space and aren't
blueberries nicer
i can i can use blueberries right
do i need um
bone thingy
okay [\h__\h] i really need to go okay brb
[Music]
wow
so
[Music]
wow
i'm back oh and i have a cat with me
i have a chunky wonky with me
leo that's not the one that meowed was
the minecraft cat
doing hair days
uh
it's not snoring
[Music]
no
wow
ah
so shocked you're so soft baby you can
go now you gave them some happiness we
shared some of your
your amazingness with them
oh sure
okay
[Music]
now smoothie purrs um
i think i would say smoothie purse
louder but less often
chocolates purse when i just look at her
she starts purring and the moment i look
away
she stops purring and smoothie
she will purr just
when
you know cats normally purr
and it doesn't matter if i look at her
or not
but she will go on for quite long
so
mind break bgm again
and what was i doing
what was i doing
i was thinking about the glowberries
if i can put the glowberries in i could
put even those shiny things in maybe i
don't know
okay so we need to figure out how to do
the
the door
hmm
did i want more glass or
[Music]
and how to add an entrance yes exactly
that's it
what's evaporating
we're i think we're close to being done
though and
i think
i think then we can read some super chat
girls
okay what am i doing what am i doing um
do i need a button or
will it be door and then trap door or
door in the door or what what should i
do
[Music]
like for example put a door here and a
trapdoor there or a
trap
[Music]
raptor
door and door
door fence just doors fine
iron yeah i have two i have three iron
doors i was gonna use those
[Music]
and i need to put the
uh lights up so that the mobs wait i
need to put lights inside but i guess
glowberries work
and it's not as strict as it used to be
how does it look with them again can i
put them everywhere or
yes
but i need to make them grow with bone
meal correct
[Music]
because like this they won't
it won't light up
[Music]
okay
i'll get rid of this by the way
i think i need that
it's so dark again
i have no torches right now
nothing attacks me but from what i know
they changed it so that um even a little
light
protects you
from danger
i still have
i'll torch it somewhere i'll torch it up
a little bit later but now okay then i
need full meal so the market is too much
to do much too much i want to get bone
[Music]
meal yeah that's a good update uh
made it
much much better
door and door
door
open
top
how do we open the doors with uh with um
the pressure plate or with a button
pressure plate on the outside and button
on the inside
nice
i should play it
i should play it on the outside button
on the inside
okay buttons
i can make over there because i think i
have iron over
[Music]
hold this in there
button on both sides safer i guess so
but it's fine it's two doors two doors
tuners the two doors
wood doors seem less like a hassle yeah
but i think also
iron doors just seem safer
and iron doors
look better here i think i wish there
were glass doors
i wish
they really need to make that like we
want some more invisible kind of door
that doesn't like ruin the whole
aesthetic
okay
[Music]
i only have one pressure plate
so
button
iron button
no
button
wait there's only ah right there was no
iron but there's only stone and
wood
i have some wood
okay so we have
[Music]
i guess i don't know
one
let's just make
four
[Music]
i'm kind of proud of this
i'm kind of i mean i could still improve
it
i might still like change things in the
future make it a little bit more
detailed and intricate maybe i'll get
some inspiration
oh wait it doesn't have to be sideways
[Music]
on the ground i guess works
i kind of want the pressure plate here
inside it should be okay
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
okay
and now we use the blue
oh it's gonna look nice
at night too
oh [\h__\h]
i didn't want that
[Music]
okay i kind of want to place a bit more
maybe like in the middle
[Music]
i mean i don't know how it is growing
from glass but you know what one day
i'll just make the whole ceiling like
that oh and i need to place little pads
i left them outside i think
and drip leaves made me late i have to
drip leaves here
what do they look like again
should i place can i place it in the
water
no
ah only on moss
it looks nice i guess
[Music]
oh
i like how it
like
dips like that
ah but it gets rid of the water there i
don't know if i like that look
maybe not too many
just a couple
okay
how about this
where do i uh
i think we'll have to put
those here so i can put the button here
ah sorry i'm sorry and then
it opens and it opens
it's time for the babies
and the lily pads
and for safety i think i want to
i need to make like some kind of
bridge up here eventually too
or just a bridge from
over there maybe
[Music]
yeah so you can stop here
and walk over
to the beautiful beautiful
frog
forgot for agrarian
i'll improve it even more
eventually
i'll make this wider and more space when
you put the fence so people can walk
around and look around
where did my lily pads go
was that my imagination i'm pretty sure
i had lily pads am i blind
lights are running oh yeah let me get
torches lily pads and torches
[Music]
ice cream
kawaii
okay outside my house okay okay true i
might have put some stuff in there
[Music]
okay
and torches
[Music]
look
um
[Music]
good night
we start earlier it makes you think it's
gonna start
the don donna's so misleading
[Music]
so misleading
no always one too early
okay i got some torches
[Music]
no i missed it
can i put that here
uh-huh
[Music]
miss it again
never get it right
okay
yeah
yeah cute
[Music]
can i walk over them
but they only seem to work on full water
blocks but i don't actually like it
when they're all filled up there they
should be more
scattered
like this
okay that's fine
you know what i'll feel one more
[Music]
very much
is it time is it time are they gonna be
fine here what do you think if i let
them go here do you think they'll be
fine i don't want it to be daytime
everything rhymes
name tax oh i can do that later
or can i
wait
if i put the thingies
they might die in the corner really
if i put them
if i put them into with a bucket
on an anvil
does that name the bucket or does it
name them
[Music]
let's just stop the waterfall
in the water with a drip like this okay
[Music]
use scalp to make all water sources
water in the corner
here
[\h__\h] i did it wrong
[Music]
but if i let go
the tadpoles are gonna give me more
water
um
oh there we go is this okay
there's water just fine just fine
but i guess i should name them first
yeah
if i can only do it while they're in the
bucket
and let me do that now
i have some name tags
and an anvil should be somewhere
i really like how this turned out really
thank
you
as i said i normally don't like building
but
this is something else now this stream
has everything it has stories it has
traveling it has adrenaline it has
adventure
it has fighting it has exploring did i
say that already
it has finding something
it has
breeding it has love
it has building
it has chill moments
it has death yes death
it even has super chats yeah i shouldn't
have had super chance
okay
name talk
wait
wait why do i have to name times we have
them in here
[Music]
one is here
feel like i remember there were more
somewhere i think downstairs
[Music]
so
much
so the parents were zoom and boom
[Music]
now
your name shall be
released it says bucket of tackle but
the name will go onto the tadpole and
the frog
[Music]
don't win glue
i'll just name the bucket
[Music]
that's so easy
um
[Music]
flip and flop okay the first ones will
be flip and flop
for him
yeah
[Music]
it's dead
but my
my baby survived
now it's time
to free the babies
do i have to feed them something to grow
up or is it just time related
also i think it's such a weird choice
that the thing that makes them breed is
slime
the thing they eat is slime could it
have been something else like
i guess i guess there's no flies in the
game but hmm maybe bees
maybe feed them bees
make sure the water is still
yeah do i need even more
[Music]
is that really that important that the
water is still
[Music]
not the base
just kelp
kelp how
i've never used kelp like that before
i don't know where my kelp went
oh yeah i heard yeah those fireflies
were removed because
they're poisonous to frogs in real life
or so
before when making the water off the
bubbles
how away why is that necessary here
anyway okay so it's moving there so i
guess i'll fill it up
that's fun
maybe not spark
[Music]
that's what yeah
oh oh it looks flat
looks perfect now
[Music]
yeah looks good
it was five lives there was going to be
five lives like five flute flies
but yeah
no no more
okay are they gonna swim under the
temples i'm so excited let's go
where'd it go
there it is
[Music]
oh they're exploring the little holes
that i made yeah nice
oh there they go
i wanted to live a long and prosperous
healthy life
cute babies
so i don't need to feed them anything
right it's just time
a matter of time
[Music]
well you won't be able to see them on
the picture because unless
[Music]
oh
look at them look at them go
look at them
hi
can your friends come too one picture
together like sniffing me
he's sniffing me
he's having a great time over there
i'm gonna drink
people
look at them look at them look at them
zooming just like their parents
such a
emotional moment
oh yeah go go
[Music]
really
scare the [\h__\h] out of me
it works and works you just have to get
close and all that
it's working
okay now we gotta we're just gonna wait
[Music]
i'm gonna take some pictures of this
meanwhile i'll make it uh
i'll get rid of this
stuff in the back because i don't have
to go to the top anymore unless maybe i
should place some
torches at the top what do you think
one is enough i would say
probably
get two more names
horny bunk
ah they don't spawn on glass anyway okay
okay
[Music]
i was so organized
a certain dominance in the back
whoa the flare
the sunflower
[Music]
when are they gonna become frogs
how long does it take
i destroyed them just now
no it was strictly right
20 minutes oh my god so long okay
[Music]
oh no it's getting night time
sorry
i'm gonna take some good screenshots
okay
i wonder ah now i have a good idea for
using the glowstones i want to put one
on the water
so that the water can glow up a little
bit too do you think the
cat poles will be disturbed by that
[Music]
i'll be fine i like it
okay for example
if we replace
this one
[Music]
wow and maybe this one
oh
even better now
[Music]
here they go there they swim
now i want to wait until they grow up so
i can take some more pictures when
they're grown up
waiting time wow
ah
let's talk about food
so yesterday i made the burger right you
saw that
it was my first time making
a burger i think i know i know i know
surprising because i am potential of kfp
but i'm not the one who makes burgers
usually
i just eat and test the burgers and
decide what burgers we make
yeah
yeah was a recipe from from hellofresh
it was pretty good i feel like it might
have been even better with um
salad
with lettuce
maybe but it was uh interesting because
it was um it was tomato slice it was a
mozzarella slice brioche buns
and
a
chicken fillet
and like a sour cream
garlic a dip on both sides of the buns
the inside
oh and some onions
uh red onions that i
um
for like grilled first i guess but i
feel like i grilled them too strongly
but it wasn't noticeable when eating it
yeah that was basically the ingredients
a pretty simple burger
it was pretty good though i feel like a
bit too simple maybe but it felt it
tasted very healthy
tastes very healthy
it's so nice here isn't it
[Music]
it's pretty nice
i mean
the background is very distracting
[Music]
yeah i think tonight i might just eat a
pizza doll because i feel like i'm
ending the stream late today it's almost
10 p.m [\h__\h] i didn't uh we should read
super chats like we should start now i
guess while
[Music]
do you guys remember the number because
i don't remember the number
where we stopped
nice
i'll read until like i don't know
midnight because i have a fairly early
stream tomorrow the australian snack box
stream
[Music]
okay
got it
[Music]
now i hope i'll notice oops [\h__\h]
i hope i will notice when the
frogs
come to life
still
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it became bigger did it no did
it
no
no no no
quake pro damn
okay back to normal you guys it's hard
to see but keep an eye out
because i i have to tab out even though
i have it open on another screen i have
to tab out
once you hear them quack oh
true okay
quack quack quack
uh super chat reading continuing from
yesterday
uh starting now
and
honestly
[Music]
happy
my
[Music]
congratulations on your birthday dental
can't watch this whole life since my new
schedule has me sleeping at this time oh
oh
but wanted to send my love and support
to the hardest working boss i know and
love congrats hope you have a blast
thank you very much i hope you enjoyed
watching the vlogs i hope you watched it
you better have watched it
thank you for the support and a bit sad
you couldn't watch it live but it's fine
thank you soon very much
has it romeo's dancing trevor g thank
you for the rainbow
[Music]
i watched this really cute owl video
yesterday
where someone just
some i think they were
something like ground owls or something
or whole owls what was i'm not sure what
their english name is but apparently
they
they chill in in holes on in the ground
um
trevor g would probably know
oh
house that's what they're calling
english
[Music]
english name is mummy
yeah and they were like uh they looked
so small i think they were babies and
this person just like
you know picked them up and they
probably took care of them until they
were ready for wildlife again
and then they put them in a bucket
brought them to the hole
and then let them all out one by one
and give a close-up of every
owl before letting them go and they
looked so [\h__\h] cute
ah and then he put them on the ground
and they waited for a moment they were
like
ran into the hole so cute
so adorable oh my god i want to touch an
owl
yeah you saw that huh
it was uh quite the popular tweet on
twitter i think it was a japanese tweet
though
yeah a reassuring push yeah so cute
anyway so whoo i blinked and it's your
birthday again a year flew by swifter
than a sparrow even with owl that's
happened
it's plumber
so fast oh my god so much in one
sentence you've influenced inspired and
changed so many lives mine included i've
tried new things flew to new places yeah
you did grew to love the color orange
yeah how could you not and i must come
no i thought it was a frog
i must confess please don't hate me when
i never cared for cats before you came
along
[Music]
okay
the animal i still don't like the movie
oh my god okay i'm not i'm no cat bird
now but they can be pretty cute
and chunky's in this movie sound
we'll see you good well-raised and
top-tier cats i could befriend
yes
you could but you won't
because they're mine
still to make up for that i donated a
little bit to non-profit in your name oh
though i did something wrong and the
letter still says my name oh
andy hoodle
i'm thanking you again for being such a
kind caring compassionate and forgiving
person right
giving you for not liking cats
so
[Music]
even if i'm ostracized
i love my cat loving or she she's the
best in the world the dedication you
have your pali can do attitude to make
your concerts happen is phenomenal
phenomenal
valley can do pally
ah
[Music]
i'm glad i was able to get the day off
so i could enjoy your hard work to the
fullest no place this owl would rather
be than watching cuba with kfp
oh that rhymed [\h__\h] happy harpy
excuse me second birthday kiwa
thank you
your super chats always deserve an
applause
amazing thank you so much
i'm glad you
changed your mind but i'm a bit shocked
like i never knew that you didn't really
like cats what the [\h__\h]
how can you not you like fluffy birds so
why don't you like fluffy cats
cats and
owls have
similarities i would say
[Music]
they both have very flexible bodies
they're both very fluffy
both have big round eyes
cats eat birds yeah but but owls also
eat birds
[Music]
cats are like landowners
i i guess you could say that for the
sake of the argument yeah
thank you for everything
dominique
zero five six zero thank you and kill me
incarnation
[Music]
this is what we have been waiting for so
i won't even try to blink to watch
everything that you will perform today
oh you didn't blink
i hope your eyes didn't hurt too much
afterwards did you have some eye drops
ready
thank you so much for watching at such a
late time i hope i hope you got some
sleep afterwards i hope you didn't have
to go to work afterwards but you
probably did because you guys are
hardcore
thank you doll i appreciate it
wait oopsie that was a free sample kiss
i guess because
normally only rides about jets get
kisses but the reflex made me give you a
kiss oopsie doodles
okay
also thank you very much
for the pinkie it says happy birthday
quinoa thank you
thank you thank you
for celebrating with me
broken man also comes on nina for
another pinky happy birthday miss kiara
you're my number one oshi who is uh as
known as creative artist enthusiastic
dancer adorable muse
national treasure of austria
they should make a museum about me one
day lady of world domination of phoenix
who lives with eternal i'll always cheer
your path of idol thank you
yes yes yes please continue supporting
me i want to do more i don't like things
you know
it's nice to be able to i mean even even
though i know it and i expected nothing
when when i joined whole life in terms
of idol
um related things like activities i
didn't really expect to be
able to like really
do such i don't like things
yeah but it's nice to be able to do more
of that these days like meet and greets
and um
yeah a concert perform idle songs and
all that
and make i don't like songs myself
[Music]
that's the important things in life oh
my god
[Music]
look look at him look
oh
[Music]
oh my god oh my god oh my god hi
hi baby
where did the other one go i was hiding
behind the blueberries
oh what did i just drop
[Music]
the [\h__\h] did i drop it
i'm doing a photo shooting right now i'm
taking a lot of screenshots
hi baby
[Music]
now i kind of regret not making it even
bigger
but i guess it's compact it's a nice
size
they seem fine
i love this slow walk they're like that
thing from star wars they look like the
the thing from star wars i think
chewbacca or something like that they
really do look like chewbacca
don't they look like chewbacca
look how satisfied he looks when he sits
[Music]
it's okay not saying you're ugly
beautiful
look at him trying to get up there
oh you did it
oh my god
big success we found frogs we brought
them here safely we breeded we breeded
them then brought the tackles here
safely and then
made them come to life after building
them a whole home
ah
nice
mission accomplished
[Music]
they have a lot of space to jump higher
though
like maybe not so much uh
space sideways but they can go really
high if they want to
satisfying and indeed yeah i'm glad i
didn't just end it after finding them
cute
yeah now i shall breed them and they
will have lots of fun making millions
and millions and millions and millions
and millions of
frogs hello
you're so fat you made that drip leaf
drop
good job
flop
and flip
flip flop flip flop
i need to show these to lena
oh my god
oh
this is the best addition to minecraft
ever
okay i will live here this is my new
home it looks nicer than my my home
i live here now
okay
[Music]
i need to build more of these i'll build
i think rather than making it bigger
i'll build
several different kinds of maybe even
different themed
different looking
um
places for them to stay
maybe for the white frog i'll make like
a snowy
pond environment you think they'll they
can survive that right
it's just that how how they
are found naturally but i can make a
snowy pond environment right
yeah
cool
why come on
he's taking shade under the trampoline
oh my god oh flop isn't too hot right
now
oh he's hiding ah
baby he's kissing the flowers ah
sweet very sweet baby
okay let's see if i can leave safely
[Music]
nice
okay still gotta be somewhat careful
they can be fast but
i think it's safe
okay i'm so happy
but we gotta end this let's go to the
office
now the middle plate room plate opens
both that's fine it's fine
it's
[Music]
now let me put you guys in the chat box
there we go
[Music]
right now we can continue reading super
chats yes yes yes yes let me drink some
more water
ah frog noises in the background but now
i'll disconnect goodbye frogs i'm so
blessed
hashtag blessed yeah i'll put on some
new bgm don't worry
[Music]
i don't know what we want to listen to
what are those
i didn't name these
[Music]
oh i like it it's kind of nice ending
music
all right let's go with this
[Music]
thank god
see you next time flip flop
bye bye frogs made my day
uh
so scared
[Music]
where was i
i was talking to broken man but i think
i'm done reading the super shot thank
you very much broken man a b2b 50
packaging
[Music]
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten
ten
oranges that's like i think two red ones
i think
thank you
let me read it happy birthday
[Music]
i hope my heart is ready to handle what
about to witness today last time i
brought orange carpet for the third best
performance i am but this time i have
prepared extra orange lights to brighten
the pretty life even brighter just like
the duck on me clown set yeah
i'm super hyped about the friday
birthday life and this is the movement
at the moment that i have been waiting
for a long long time at last that time
has finally come i can't wait to see
what you have prepared for us and oh my
god the new choreography set for all the
original songs will be dope as hell yeah
i can just feel it look forward to the
set list too i was upset that i missed
your first birthday merch last time oh
but this time i made sure to purchase
the full set right away nicely i really
like the design of the blanket i can't
wait to use that blanket as soon as it
arrives yeah me too
it's supposed to be really big and
fluffy so looking forward to it
oh also thanks for giving us another
shot at meet and greet hopefully i have
better luck next time oh
i hope so too for you
btm makes me emotional huh turn a bit
down okay
every new birthday life let's go
once again i really appreciate the
effort that you have pulled through to
make this 3d concept possible and thanks
for everyone else who helped to create
such a wonderful environment a moment i
hope you enjoy the rest of the day and
hope you have a wonderful time for the
rest of the year
and then there's some korean texts
[Music]
oh
it's been almost two years since i saw
you but you've always shown me how to
keep moving forward without giving up
you're the best
yes
[Music]
thank
you almost congrats i'm reaching one
million followers on twitter as well
thank you so much do you know i'm so
happy to have someone like you in the
community who knows a lot about you know
idol stuff and and how to cheer during
an idol concert properly so i hope you
can continue teaching the others some
good stuff yeah thank you so much for
the love and support thank you
very much
[Music]
thank you so much for the
uh
double
rainbow
looks like it
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
don't mind that he wants a hug but
i don't know where i have my hug thingy
[Music]
i think i'm out here
i don't know where it is
i feel hug to go
to wonderland
[Music]
um
thank you
oh
reminding me about viva la kiana webpage
getting an update
did i see them
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
so much stuff
[Music]
oh yeah
okay i will
keep this tab open and look at it later
thank you for reminding me
yeah the pgm is so nostalgic
thank you for the for the sweet sweet
presents and the hard work foundation
the hymn of my people
it it's kind of like that isn't it
uh rowan hulk thank you for the rest of
the chat happy birthday tangel i can't
wait to see the fruits of your labor i
know you worked so hard to make this a
reality your drive your drive and
tenacity inspired me and i know that
this concept will be divine absolutely
exquisite love you
wowies thank you
i've already said it a million times and
the others have said it a lot too but
yeah i did work
really really hard for this
i can't wait to do more stuff like this
so
with your help i will continue as long
as you are here to watch me i can
continue
oh yeah it is kind of like rhizome music
[Music]
thank you so much
rowan ruin am i saying it correctly i
hope so
[Music]
keep chasing your dream thank you
yeah
bigger and bigger dreams
are to be chased
yes i'm saying it right okay good
feel free to correct me everybody if i
ever say your name wrong
thank you rowan here's a kiss for you
[Music]
brian hits no thank you for the pinky
happy birthday kiana this is your
reminder now annual that your birthday
is also international kissing day
did you guys tell me that last year
because i definitely forgot and to take
full advantage of this fact for your own
nefarious pure-hearted purposes
ah
did i get a kiss from someone else huh
[Music]
well my birthday is already over it's
too late now
no
it's too late to apologize
i'm too late to get kisses
[Music]
now you're gonna remind me earlier
before my birthday not on the day i know
where i read those super chats on the
same day
thank you though for the information
thank you very much
july 6th is indeed international kissing
day what the hell i only knew that it
was a national fried chicken day i guess
in america or so
time then thank you for the red super
chat today we celebrate our lovely tanto
okay so we celebrate you every day but
today even more than usual thank you for
an amazing year of streams cats music
cats an amazing community and of course
cats
yes that's what my channel is all about
love you piano here's to another amazing
year ahead of kfp thank you indeed
for caffeine
thank you very much
yeah i mean i said jokingly that this is
what my channel is about but one might
actually think sometimes that that's
what my channel is about
that's all live yes yes i will not take
any complaints cats are the best
especially my cats
thank you typhon wow did i miss mine oh
i don't think so
[Music]
lugenzy duncan typhon oh wait that's a
rainbow oh it continues
i thought it ended there on a more
serious note it's been amazing this year
to watch you keep growing as a performer
seeing you work so hard to make a smile
shows just how lucky we are that you
decided to do this okay if we could have
never asked for a better answer than you
come down
can't wait to see what you and me manage
to pull off to make this day not just
amazing for you but for us you've waited
so long for this and i hope it's
something you feel proud of because
we're proud of you now hopefully the
biggest stress is done and you can get
some cat cuddles we'll enjoy the show
and hopefully you'll be able to as well
thank you tanjo with potential we truly
adore you yes sending rainbows from
mobile is a pain at least to show us
before my flight home from ax
ah what's scaring that means at first ah
you went to ax i hope you had fun there
and i hope you didn't um get sick or so
there
hope you stayed
careful
and are healthy
and made some nice memories yeah i did
wait you mean you had fun oh yeah you
got sick
[Music]
oh you don't know maybe you could still
get sick careful was not enough but i'm
fine
that sounds like you got
sick wait why am i laughing i'm just i
guess that's against shadow for them
well get well soon typhon i am indeed
sick there we go
that's what you get that's what you get
but i hope it was worth it
hopefully it was worth it yeah
be careful okay
now
eat some chicken soup
[Music]
some chicken soup and whatever else
helps i'm not so sure
and thank you so much for the love and
support
yeah
the biggest stress for me is indeed for
now done
uh
there's some things ahead oh yeah listen
to the voice pack yes that was the
perfect [\h__\h] time for you
hell yeah
did you listen to it yet you need to
listen to it
[Music]
that's what it's for
brilliant oh tell me you did it on
purpose right
[Music]
nice okay thai fun i wish you all the
best thank you so much
more kisses
[Music]
you make my everyday so special thank
you for always bringing me many money
happiness have fun hashtag
birthday thank
[Music]
foreign
you've been so important to me in very
hard moments of my life keeping me
company when i'm feeling down you're an
amazing person your determination and
perseverance is so inspiring i wish you
a life filled with happiness
i wish you the same
i want you all to be happy so i hope
there will be only lots of lots of happy
moments for you in the future
[Music]
thank you soon very much for the support
mwah
we wouldn't live
[Music]
i know last year you said you wanted a
trumpet cover of hype challenger and
then it's definitely in the works but i
couldn't pass up on a chance to cover
fema night for you this year
looking forward to you for the concert
oh i feel like i saw something like that
around
let me check
[Music]
did you upload it on youtube because
when i type in daftka's favorite knight
i cannot find it
trumpet fibonite
interesting
interesting concept
you might have to link it to me on
twitter ah there you go okay thank you
maybe a little bit later
so it won't get drowned out
thank you looking forward to it
and then you get chicken nuggets and
green wilderness
happy birthday lady hot wings i can
barely contain my excitement for this
concert but i will endure until i am off
work so that i can give this the
undivided attention it deserves and
properly appreciate your majesties
carefree's hearts are set ablaze you're
amazing
thank you oh so that means you didn't
watch it live we watched afterwards are
you here now are you here are you here
doko
green wielder or maybe he's working
would very much be so
i cannot hello
hello
i think he's not here
well then good luck at work i hope work
is not too exhausting
and two to to hire some please
make it easy
and thank you for trying to balance your
lifestyle
[Music]
while also watching as much content of
me as possible thank you so much for the
effort i appreciate it
for the pinky happy birthday um don't be
mad but some little shits seem to have
escaped from the usual room while you
are distracted with preparations for the
3d birthday live it looks like they were
assisted by
checks the video footage ah it seems
like they were assisted by
interdimensional travelers small ammo
how do you want to handle this tangent
escape from the usual room i can't be
fan game now release ah
[Music]
i saw something like that yeah sorry
about the escapes
oh
i want to try
nice nice hint at the game
nice advertisement were you involved why
are you advertising it like this
thank you very much
[Music]
oh thank you deaf guys
it's true i was the usual escapee
it's an interesting game
[Music]
need to check it out i made it all
myself wait oh you're right you are like
a
game
developer kind of thing right
right so the snare
oh
well then
i definitely want to check it out but
you should link it to me again maybe
afterwards on twitter so that i don't
forget
wow
i'm really interested thank you for
making something like that
really really impressive
no matter how the game looks just the
fact that you made it
already impresses me
guys check it out
[Music]
yeah
escape from the usual room i can't be
fan gaming
another fermented thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday thank you
thank you
thank you for the support i'm not cool
and you are question mark thank you also
for red super chat happy birthday kiara
this is my first red super chat when i
first started watching whole life i
never thought i'd consider someone right
on scene but seeing all the effort you
put into everything you do made me
realize you are truly something special
thanks for all you do
no
you make me
yeah
thank you so much that's so sweet
i am just
that lovable apparently
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the reservation
happy birthday attention this is my
first super chat your stream gives me
lots of energy and happiness joining the
kfb was a great thing in my life you're
my only occita yeah the only one let's
go
hope you have a great day now and
forever
and a little bit of korean at the end
[Music]
i always cheer for you manager thank you
yes continue cheering for me
please please please
i hope someday
maybe
i can also
do a meet and greet with korean fans
yeah
would be nice
and then you should be there i hope so
thank you for the love and support thank
you for your first super job
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] felix
[Music]
wow
i'm not even gonna say
how much that is that is shocking are
you good felix
are you good
thank you so much holy [\h__\h]
damn son
happy birthday cancel congratulations
for becoming pretty and i'm so happy for
all those callings you get it always
baffles me when i realize how much time
we spend together and how much chickens
you fried i mean raised i'm so glad i
got adopted by you and i was an egg oh
no
and i'm even happier when i got the
chance to get fried at the same time
tenchu i really wish you could get more
rest we've got a lot of employees
a lot more employees than before so
maybe we can help you a bit more at
recruiting new eggs oh after all we all
want you to be healthy healthy and happy
viva la chiada
i mean you guys are always welcome to
help me out with recruiting more
chickens yeah yeah
advertising in places that i can't reach
wherever that is
telling your friends
and i don't know where i don't know
telling your work colleagues or
telling people you meet at conventions
showing them your aussie your beloved oc
but
yeah you don't have to but if you want
to
door to door
maybe that's a bit too much
only do it if you have some cookies to
sell alongside
or fried chicken
and maybe sell fried chicken
[Music]
now thank you very much felix that's
insane way way way way too generous
holy [\h__\h] but you know
we'll be invested in the future of kfp
so thank you so much
i hope you enjoyed the concert
i really hope you did
and that's
let's hope that there will be more felix
thank you so much i hope your bank
lets you buy groceries still
thank you
super chat thank you soon happy birthday
thank you for all the love and fun time
you give me for these past two years i
wish nothing but happiness and joyful
birthday for you i hope you'll have a
huge tasty cake thank you
just had a small cake but
yeah still very yummy any cake is yummy
and two years it hasn't quite been two
years you're rounding up there but
soon soon it will be two years and then
we can celebrate another thing
[Music]
honestly i wish i could do
a concert as well for the anniversary
because you know my whole life everybody
seems to do concert for birthday and
anniversary
but that's in the middle of september
and i guess that doesn't look very
realistic huh
but by then i should have at least that
scuffed suit
for a
somewhat okay scuffed
decent
pretty
maybe i can do something with that um
[Music]
it seems a bit crazy to squeeze you know
another trip to america
in there
if you consider you know that it needs
to be like edited and all that too
yeah
but i'll think about it because
it's a good reason to do it again
maybe we can i don't know somehow have
it be um
simpler i don't know
no it doesn't have to be simpler
but
[Music]
business expenses and that doesn't help
that much
anniversary concert is now
[Music]
ah
i didn't really think about it
until now but now i'm thinking about it
now i want to do it
[Music]
hello wink wink
vr
i can't dance in vr it's that
huge heavy thing on my head and the
cable and the things that i have to hold
in my hands
and the trackers they move around and
uncomfortable
it's not made for dancing
unless i get like some kind of
you know something to replace the thing
on my head like a tracker for the head
so i don't have to wear the
the vr goggles i think that exists but i
don't know
but besides that the tracking is
actually pretty nice i saw some
comparisons between like certain types
of
um
[Music]
mode capturing solutions versus vr
and versus one another
and we are actually
did pretty good
yeah
actually
[Music]
in some ways it's like
more accurate than
proper mo capture
um
suits like the cheaper ones
[Music]
you don't need a specific reason or
content whenever you want would be fine
yeah but i mean at least that's an a
specific reason that makes sense
also to advertise and promote yeah
but the thing is like so far because of
how our debut was
[Music]
scheduled like on two days
um
last year as well like the whole
merchandise was like group themed and
because our
our anniversaries were so close we kind
of
i think every one of us also did a solo
stream
but still it's kind of a group thing for
us but i did i did mention last year
that it would be nice to have like solo
anniversary merch down the line like
other whole life japan members have as
great as group merchandise is
um i feel like you know when i look at
whole life japan members
probably because it just makes more
sense for them because shipping and all
that is faster and all that um they do
like even like
600k if 700k milestone
merchandise
while for us
the only merchandise that we get
is like the anniversary
which is group which was which was group
personalized last year and the birthday
so
it's
it would be nice to also get like
solo merchandise for the anniversary at
least
and they said ideas i wanna bring them
out there
make them a reality um
[Music]
we'll see we'll see
solo merch would be nice i think it's
too late now though
yeah i'm gonna plan that kind of stuff
early i did mention it but you will see
what what will happen this year
i cannot say
i cannot say anything
every brand air fryer that's
way too high tech
i wish i could do merchandise like that
but that's way too high tech i would
need some kind of tie up
with a
air frying company or something like
that
[Music]
yeah like dale's pc thingy i don't know
how that happened i don't know anything
about that behind the scenes or so
but
i'm guessing that was also something
like that
anyway thank you
your name is difficult to say i don't
know how you want me to say it
is that how i'm supposed to say it
thank you
[Music]
i won't be able to watch the stream live
but i will definitely catch the ball
later judging by the glimpse you showed
you showed us at home fest i'm sure it
will be amazing enjoy your evening you
deserve it
thank you very much
well the holofest you know that one made
me really nervous because like
i would put a lot of pressure on me
um but i'm glad that
judging by the
um reaction that i lived up to
you know the previous one previous
performance
lived up to the expectations i hope hope
so
wow yeah yeah oh thank you very much
thank you so much
[Music]
ah 7th of july was your birthday happy
i know i don't send messages often but i
always support you as best as i can
you're an inspiring
you're an inspiring enduring person who
really embodies the phoenix spirit i
love you forever my kami oh [\h__\h]
there you go kami oshie
[Music]
sorry i'm getting tired yeah
thank you so much it's okay
to not send messages often i'm glad
you're still here thank you for the long
lasting support
[Music]
project
happy birthday danger i saw what you
wanted to create in this few weeks
i saw what you wanted wanted to create
in this few weeks
thank you so much i hope you have a
great day and please rest well happy
birthday oh thank you
i think i've been resting
[Music]
fairly well
since the concert although that one
night yeah
yeah but it's getting better um
i'm getting back to my
uh
usual sleep schedule
and my usual
[Music]
life schedule day schedule
yeah
[Music]
oh
it's it's all daijoubu thank you very
much for the congratulations for the
sweet words thank you and orange apple
thank you
brandon holloway thank you
i get a happy birthday i can't wait to
see the concert i know it'll be amazing
i probably won't be able to catch it
live since i'll probably be busy at the
time but i'll definitely be catching the
vlog when i have time i love your piano
oh thank you
it's okay did you watch it you watch it
did you watch it
i'm guessing you saw it as early as you
could so by now you should have watched
it thank you so much i hope you enjoyed
it
yeah
thank you for the mental support from
afar
thank you
[Music]
l5 guardian thank you for the recipe
you have an incredible amount of passion
for everything you do and it always
shows in everything you create hope you
have a wonderful day kiana happy
birthday no you're too kind
thank you
yeah i think passion is
passion towards this whole thing is very
important i want everyone who joins my
life
to have
passion
towards
what they do
towards returning towards music towards
whatever
if you don't have passion for it you
can't really make it look like
you're enjoying it
genuinely
[Music]
thanks for your hard work and give us
another wonderful year wish you all the
best love you'll see i love you too
thank you
i'll do my best another wonderful year
hopefully with lots of fun things
and success stories let's go
okay
[Music]
follow up super chat so escape from the
usual room a kfb fan game is the first
game that i've ever solo developed and
pop published despite being a
professional game developer for hi
tankers for almost 11 years now wow i
was a 3d artist and i've been a tech
artist for six years now wow
seems like you definitely got the skills
to do it alone but i wonder
how long it took you
make that one game
i wish i had the skills to make a whole
game by myself
but it's good to know that we have
someone who can do it within kfp i'll
remember that if i want to do something
in the future
dot dot
dot
[Music]
there are quite a few
then everyone should come together and
make one big
game
started in june 2021 possibly for eight
months and then since february
oh
i don't know how long that is in total
[Music]
happy birthday to our best
after everything you have gone through
in the past nearly two years time you
have finally reached here showing the
world your idle dream on the stage you
deserved congratu congratulations for
your dreams first step come true thank
you i mean i would say it's been several
steps now
but there's still more steps ahead of me
i'll keep on walking i'll keep on moving
i'll keep on running i'll keep on
grinding let's go
thank you so much for your support
mem duncan gargan show thank you for the
rest of the jet
happy birthday attention i uh glad i'll
be able to see this one live couldn't
see the previous concert because the
site didn't like my credit card ah
got locked twice trying what the [\h__\h]
that's frustrating thanks for all the
fun times so far and hopefully get to
see you dance again before long oh yeah
maybe in september
now i put this idea into my head
oh no
hold on
[Music]
i have to write this down
um
[Music]
okay
i wrote something down
[Music]
alice
and there's kiana a billion times
congrats on your birthday you are the
most talented beautiful and wonderful
idol oh oh wow wow wow and you fill my
heart with happiness you're singing and
dancing always have me in complete all
all you so cute and amazing i love you
my lady my aussie
[Music]
flattering charming
sweet
thank you very much for the sweet words
thank you
for washing me
[Music]
happy birthday my beloved potential
sending this ahead of time because i
know that as soon as i see your radiance
light up on stage my chimpkin brain will
be too busy struggling to remember how
to breathe to string words together in
any meaningful way super proud of you
thank you
yeah i think during the concert
everybody's too busy looking at
something it would be a waste
to send a super chat during it and yet
i'm sure that there's more than enough
who did that how could you do that
aren't you like too occupied with your
brain
um
i will see i will see who
who was able to supposedly multitask
to send a super chat during the concert
and then i'll figure out at what time
during the concert it was and then i'll
test you if you remember what happened
during the concert at that very moment
when you sent the super chat
yep that's what i'm gonna do
[Applause]
[Music]
no that's too much effort
uh
[Music]
my first super chat rainbow for the best
phoenix chicken idol in the world i
don't have much to say besides thank you
for being amazing and giving so much
happiness to us chickens every single
day and we love your potential this
community is the best thing that has
happened to me this year and even though
i have
even though i have another month left
before turning into a fully grown
chicken if it already feels like home
if that doesn't it oh so cozy
so comfy
thank you very much
for supporting me and
you know still so tiny and cute
and soon you're gonna be a grown-up
chicken oh i'm so proud of you
thank you so much for staying for so
long thank you
[Music]
how's it going there
she's so round
when she sits on the ground she's so
round
such a bomb
this is so round she's like a moon
around oh hi oh she felt like i was
talking to her
[Music]
he's here with me again welcome
i should do a holotalk episode with my
cats
fluffy
hi
are you waiting for me to end the stream
it's almost been six hours but
probably gonna have to read them
for maybe one more hour
read the super chat chunky monkey i'm
sorry
i'm sorry but i have to get this done
you know
[Music]
abby or duncan's in the game recruit
me or duncan
how do i read this
[Music]
copy
thank you thank you have your young
questions
concert started
or not yet
not yet i guess because the time here
says
one
148 and so on so it's probably like
10 it should be before right
but avior's super chats are like he had
a hike he had a height as if they're
like cheering for me
already
sounds like
sounds like it started out here thank
you for the rainbow
olivia fernandez and flamini
oh
you're writing german
but in like a chunibio style
it must be practice maybe
james jackson i don't think i read yours
here
[Music]
abby thank you very much
i want you to be here i need your
fluffiness in my arm
thank you thank you
sean no wait first drink sanchez
i wish i could stand actually watch but
i have to go back to work right when the
steep stream starts happy birthday
anyways hope you have a fantastic
birthday and stream oh thank you
yeah i'm sorry it was kind of a shitty
time for
a lot of people i try to
have it be a time slot that's manageable
[Music]
for everyone somehow
um
but that would mean only in case you
don't have a job and so on
and i think you know i also try to
prioritize
europe
again this time because
you know i'm here i am in europe and
i
i feel a little bit of a duty and
obligation to have my streams be had a
reasonable time for them
but my next concert i might
uh i might yeah
ignore that and next time
european will probably have
the ash cut
as we like to say in german the s card
probably american prime time next time
[Music]
how'd you spell that um a-r-s-c-h
k-a-r-t-e
[Music]
yeah
you guys are used to it well i mean i
would say that ever since i've moved
back
[Music]
my streams have been
decent to catch for europeans i always
usually i start around 6 p.m or 5 p.m
and i go on until like midnight
yeah
so i don't want to hear any complaints
from europeans okay
i've been
helping out a lot
when when it comes to you know filling
up this time slot yeah yeah yeah
but i might want to try having the next
concert be
at a different time slot yeah
[Music]
lucky i can watch while it work that's
the perfect scenario
you and sometimes you know all we get in
europe yeah ina is like she always
starts uh or she
used to start during winter time i guess
at 10 p.m for
austria and germany and so on and then
now it's 11 p.m so now it's a bit during
the summer it's tough
for europeans even to watch inna
now
half half one
[Music]
you're the only one we can watch
that's good oh according to k-cup maybe
that's why i moved back to europe
so i can have my own time slot
it's not the best time slot but it is my
own time slot that i have a monopoly
over
yeah
it's something
at least i'm not overlapping with 20
people and then you guys have to choose
you know i mean you guys would obviously
choose me the ones who are in the super
chat rating i'm pretty sure you would
choose me
but
the people who are not in the super
giant rating but just watch the gaming
parts wonder i don't think they would
prioritize me
i don't think so
so
i don't i shouldn't even be giving them
the choice that's the ideal situation
because there are no choices
[Music]
no no no no
okay continue
and where was that
i think sanji thank you for the pinkie
it's been one big adventure with you and
i really want to say thank you for the
memories
even though they weren't so great
[Music]
one more time
thanks for the memories for the smiles
happy birthday kiana it's your special
day and as always i'm looking forward to
seeing what you've prepared for us
phoenix verb always brings the fire
yeah
thank you
i tried my best to make it
an enjoyable
concert with a nice enjoyable set list
an exciting set list
thank you soon for watching sunshine
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
still going strong yeah kind of my
throat hurts a bit but it's okay
i never forget your name you're my
adorable chicken happy birthday kiana
thank you for wait what thank you for
brightening up our lives i'm not your
adorable chicken if anything i'm your
double phoenix
[Music]
i don't know maybe it's you're
autocorrect or something
no i'm not a chicken i said i'm a
phoenix
it's not that hard
[Music]
does frog legs taste like you know what
i've heard
it they do
which now
maybe makes even more sense why i like
frogs so much
and you guys
maybe frogs are basically just
green chickens
with no feathers
oh my god it makes so much sense that's
why i like them so much
i'm bouncing tickets
we should try frying them
[Music]
a substitute for chickens
when i'm lacking some chicken meat
or when i want to save
let's dry
the skin could be super crispy
[Music]
let's just give it a try sometime soon
don't use
uh flip and flop
or zoom and boom though cause i have an
emotional bond with them
don't use them please
anyway thank you elvis
i hope you enjoyed the concert
is that a rainbow
in it in the making it looks like it it
seems so
wait there it is i'm the real girl if
you didn't is that actually not girthed
in i feel like i heard something like
that
where is the real girlfriend
is this the one that says i'm the real
group they didn't is that really the
real gifted then
wrote
[Music]
holly and wong
did
answer me
frog legs taste like chicken have you
tried before
well the real goof didn't please stand
up please stand up please stand up it is
me okay good
okay so let's read this
[Music]
it's so
scattered though
happy birthday here lady this is a dream
given form
before link your wish oh this is a dream
given form uh huh
the following you wish i not so
patiently waited to see you performed
pretty you blew me away in that proving
yet another reason you are my oshi is
this
a poem
it's a poem
now the day has come and through your
hard work and love and devotion of to
the community have brought something
amazing once more i hope you'll accept
this as a token of my love and affection
as well as my ticket for this concert
that i'm waiting for
wait maybe it's not
these two lines rhymed but
i'm not sure
the love and commitment you have to both
other whole life members and your
community astounds me and it is mirrored
back by the hard work that myth and your
community have given back to you maybe
it's not it's not
i thought this was a little keen poem
never mind
next line doesn't rhyme
uh
by the way i'm the real girl today i
just wanted to be
a cute egg and baby chick again ah sorry
for the rainbow getting mixed up got
sick before the stream oh wait oh i
don't see the membership
in the list that i'm looking at but on
it
oh now your
bucket i guess you just had to
make a new account because
of uh bank
problems
[Music]
i suppose probably that's the reason for
me
but yeah no one can imagine it must be
nice to be able to go back to
the times as a young chickling
i wish i wish i could go back to the
times when i was a young young lady
so nice how you guys can do that just so
easily by making a new account and
joining the membership again
[Music]
i'm jealous a little bit
anyway thank you
loki poem maybe next time you can try
sending a poem
thank you so much for the sweet and
loving and caring words and for
supporting me for a long time thank you
very very much for the beautiful rainbow
as well
it's gorgeous
that cushion very generous
[Music]
now i gotta scroll back up because that
was really scattered
thank you for the oh the crazy right
super chat thank you oh my god
[Music]
oh my god happy birthday mom thanks once
again for being an amazing penis and
brightening up everyone's lives all year
round can't wait to see the concert i
don't think i can read much longer [\h__\h]
i just know it will be awesome also
can't wait on
oh it hurts one million followers on
twitter thank you yes okay i think now
it might be safe to make a tweet about
it
i was waiting for
you know
getting a little bit of a buffer
so that i'm
like even if i
write a tweet and some people are like
haha now it's the funny moment to leave
and to unfollow her
and now i think it would be okay i might
rather tweet
i think i can't read anymore i think i
already used my voice so much today
[Music]
i read 200
well that's impressive
oh you mean
are you going by
those numbers but they skip some numbers
so it's probably not really two hundred
[Music]
but tomorrow i think
after the snack box maybe i can read for
an hour
but not endlessly because then then we
have their data stream the data stream
will be on my channel by the way because
last time
the goose game
we did it on her channel and i asked you
where do you want to do it now and she
said we can do it on yours
yeah
so two streams on my channel tomorrow
you still have your goose saved
see i don't
know i don't even know
we'll see tomorrow i guess
if not we might spontaneously play
something else or so i don't want to
play the beginning of the goose game
again that would be the third time
no thank you
yeah
[Music]
okay
anyway apple thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you you're so
generous thank you so much and
i hope you enjoyed the concert
thanks for reminding me about the
followers too
thank you for being one very important
chicken
amongst those one millions
[Music]
thank you
now
i'm sorry
but uh please remember 292.
uh fruit health
i was gonna say that thanks to not
streaming so often
um
in the past weeks
that my throat has been doing a lot
better
until now
in the previous streams it was fine
but now it hurts but maybe i do think in
general it might have helped a little
bit actually a good side effect of not
being so active
in the past weeks
[Music]
don't cry
i'm okay though i just need always
a little bit of rest
after like 10 minutes or 20 minutes of
not talking
i'm usually fine again
i'm gonna get vocal noodles let's go
noodles yeah noodles
[Music]
i'm exhausted though
uh but i had fun today we got frogs yay
[Music]
foreign
okay
bgm makes you dizzy
don't worry it's ending now how does it
make you dizzy
you good
that sounds weird
maybe you need to go to the doctor
maybe you're just dizzy for other
reasons
i think it's other reasons
maybe you're getting brainwashed yeah
huh
oh well all right thank you everybody
for watching today i'm gonna eat some
food
and then make the thumbnails for
tomorrow and then i'll see you tomorrow
yeah
thank you very much hope you had fun go
get my merchandise if you haven't yet
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you
someone to love you guys quack quack
[Music]
da
you know um
i've been performing either songs and
and vocaloid songs in my concert but
maybe i should perform touhou songs
as well because some of them have
choreographies yeah yeah yeah
oh ideas ideas
ideas yes
yes
i could do bad apple i couldn't i could
do the bad apple dance
[Music]
okay bad apple goes on the list for
future
uh performance songs
[Music]
okay let's go i'm gonna go cuddling you
now
bye-bye
[Music]
oh yeah
aren't you with myself and i forgot to
say
[Music]
do