foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
good morning
morning
hello
I'm here too early I was thinking
I was making the
was it racing yesterday
I was thinking
oh
so that I get more sleep I should change
it from 10 30 to 10 45
because it doesn't it doesn't uh I don't
need to wait a whole 30 minutes for it
to start right
yeah
but then I I went backwards I went
backwards
thank you I think
um
at least now I can eat breakfast
mm-hmm
[Music]
I don't know
okay I'll eat breakfast and then I'll be
then I'll be feeling better
yeah
well
um
[Music]
we are watching
this
what a man
[Music]
catch on
her first show of life
are you still alive
and watching that together guys okay
oh my God I was my my alarm went off
that was like even though I was so tired
because I didn't sleep much
I I immediately immediately jumped out
of bed immediately gave my cat cat food
and did all that
[Music]
and turn on my PC immediately I thought
I was gonna be late I even thought
because I just woke up that my stream is
starting at 10 15.
no wait oh it did it did it it did it I
was right with that my my alarm went off
at 10 11.
um
[Music]
it's not on yet but let me go and spawn
because
I didn't even input my code yet
[Music]
um
oh my God I got I have 35
mentions what the actual
as you know it's probably like more like
47 because I already saw a couple
[Laughter]
six seven hours ago was the last time I
checked the school
oh where's my spot there it is
oh my God
[Music]
yeah spot is fine why do I put my coat
in again I think
[Music]
um
account
oh wait I'm not logged in wait oh my God
what was my account
what was my account eh
[Music]
uh
um
oh God I don't know
[Music]
era
around the clowns
you know what it doesn't matter I'll
just
um
I'll just use them usually there's like
a like you know when you know instead of
using the email and the password or just
log in with Google
that's probably what I did originally
um
birth date
uh 1954.
[Laughter]
I was born in
saitama
sex because it only gives me Japanese
options
old verb
mm-hmm
[Music]
you know what you know what's smart
when websites when you input a code
um like and they have like separate
Fields when you copy paste it into the
first field
if they would like
separated properly already into each
field
this website does not do that I would
like to inform you of that
what
um
[Music]
Tokyo supported by Bushido
there you go stream tickets
give me give me give me
give me give me I need to eat my cereals
it's getting really soggy I hate that
[Music]
um
okay
um I'll take it was uh 5000 yen
that's okay
did you guys get it or are you guys
being imagination again which one
mm-hmm
you got you bought it um
out of imagination going again
[Music]
okay but I can't
oh wait it's half past now I should be
able to get in now
okay gonna mute that okay
ah we did something last time
um for a delay
my speed is where it work um
I don't see it oh wait
that's something something mode has to
be turned on right but it's Japanese for
me well it wasn't in English low latency
mode okay has to be turned on
okay okay
I don't know if I have the right to play
about my music
even the loading music
I'm not gonna unmute the concert guys
um
as per usual this is how it's gonna work
I'm gonna be watching a concert
you're gonna be watching the concert and
when I'm watching it I might be watching
it on my side you're gonna be watching
it on your side
I'm gonna react on my side
you're gonna react in the comments
whenever you feel like it but uh this
stream is not giving you a free sample
of the concert no however
's Channel
you can get I think 30 minutes
of the concert for free like it starts
at the same time and it just ends after
30 minutes
so you can do that at least
[Music]
yeah my reaction is free free of charge
no flower stands I'll tell you about the
flower stands one second
mm-hmm
So currently if you're watching them
concert you see these digital flower
stands but
and um
and in Japan at least I didn't see it
like in other cultures I mean in in
Korea for example probably the same
thing but like outside of Asia I haven't
seen it before
um in Japan they do like all kinds of
big big big fancy cute flower stands
when like for Idol concerts for example
or also for store openings yeah yeah
yeah it's not only concerts but like for
store openings companies that are like
um like working together with that
company that opened the store for
example they would send uh flower stands
and all kinds of shapes and colors and
sizes
mm-hmm
[Music]
I want to show you
um
but um I don't know which picture I'm
allowed to show maybe I'll
aren't they all digital are there any
like whole life concerts
flower stands that are from real times
[Music]
no oh I got it I got something like that
oh
oh cute this one's nice who said that ah
non-stop store oh
oh let me just show this one then
although that that looks very special
like that doesn't even look like they
usually look like
I love the shape of that and the the
color of it yo
uh wait where the hell did I save it
there it is
like the ones you see on the screen now
are digital but usually like they look
for like this for example
and that's huge see that's standing on
like a parking lot or something it's
huge normally
um
this one has a really really
unique shape though I gotta say
and the flowers actually yo I just
realized those are probably not real
they're real yeah I'm pretty sure
normally they are real
and yeah depending on what size you want
they can get really expensive and you
just send it to like wherever the clown
suit is or wherever the story opens and
whatever
and they will have it like at the
entrance to to like Flex how many flower
stands they got
I don't know
Little Korea yeah they're so big
tonight
[Music]
but I love that like
um
I always wanted to get flower stands
like that
[Music]
I mean it's so difficult to take home I
don't even know what people do
I think they take like a couple out of
them
not if it's for if it's for like a group
of of like an idol group like of seven
people or whatever
then everyone could take some flowers
and bring them home but I don't think
they bring a whole flower stand that's
like bigger than themselves back home
it is kind of wasteful I don't know what
they do with it um
foreign
[Music]
like whoever wants something
I'm not even gonna look at my Discord
mentions until this is over I think so
water
I'm actually feeling pretty awake
I feel like I need to go to an idol
meeting again though like I was I went
before the stream but now I feel like I
need to go again
and I went to this guy to the show name
but I'm so excited this is gonna be a
real concert that's so cool
nah it's not that urgent I'm fine
probably
this is a real concert they're gonna be
real people this is like isn't this the
first one
uh inside of Hawaii the first one for
since like well it all started
[Music]
foreign
that was before the thing that's what
I'm saying
about when recently
with real people
I'm talking about like after the sea
thing
the first one since the sea thing I know
I know azaki had one with real people
before I know I know but like after
deceiving I don't think she had any
maybe soon
yeah oh that's so cool I'm glad it
worked out then hmm actually
I was I was so busy with things when I
was talking about my Senpai last week
during the Minecraft collaboration and I
was talking about her concert
um with her but I didn't realize it was
coming up so soon
uh yes I will turn off the bgm when the
concert starts yes yes
um I didn't think it would start that
soon
uh I didn't think it was happening that
soon next the following week just a
couple of days
so I was talking to her
in in a way that like like I was
thinking it was still like weeks to go
as if it's like still so much time to go
I completely lost track of time
essential
[Music]
foreign
when I realized wait it's actually this
week
I had to squeeze it into my schedule
no problem though
yeah oh my God for Gen concert I'm so
mad I can't be in Japan for that
thank you
in November
oh my God you guys can bet that I'll be
doing a watch along
and how's fun looking is it still flower
stands
[Music]
oh wait I kind of stopped it oopsie
is it still flower stands
low latency mode
why does it keep on unmuting the BTM
it's still flower stands very cold
but there's so many from the same person
wait why is it so loading
okay we gotta see what what I see and
what you guys see it I don't know if I'm
like behind okay I see
flower stance wait it's loading it's
buffering oof
okay now it's switched just now it
switched the no now it's buffering again
is it buffering for your
[Music]
foreign
the slow latency mode make it buffer
no buffering for you eh
[Music]
why
um
probably a lot of people that didn't
affect it like in the previous times
oh yeah
oh my God it's buffering like
continuously
they changed music now I don't know I
muted it so I don't even know I see
t-shirts and then and towel did you guys
see that now too
or was I too late have you guys been
seeing that for like a minute already
[Music]
I'm way back
you guys are ahead of me maybe I should
turn off hello ladies people and now I
see more merchandise number two
uh
flower stands again I don't see flowers
dance
wait let me let me reload without low
latency mode okay now I see flowers
dance okay
we're still buffering
[Music]
um
Lucio
foreign
[Music]
let's watch in 720p not 1080.
what do you say about that spawn do you
like that
you like that
I need to listen to the PGM so that I
know how
how often that stops
okay it's buffering I don't hear BCM
try a different browser different
browser
no
no no no
no oh I hear music
okay then and I would buff it again no
it's
um
[Music]
oh I think I'm 48 seconds off could that
be
no
I I have tried both ways with low
latency and without low latency
for 48 seconds yeah I think because it
says or maybe even more I don't know
yeah
refresh refresh
oh
hello
do you guys hear music I don't hear
music
I don't see it buffering either though
you guys see t-shirts it's began
but that's not possible it begins in 15
minutes but I guess it's just more
advertisement
at all
right now okay
I see
um
okay I see
I see an advertisement ah it's Barbara
let me try a different browser do I have
edge of course I have Edge my stretch
stripes
uh oh yeah
okay okay Edge let me log into you
uh shut up
log in uh so the problem is my Google
account is not
not like linked here
what Google account did I log in with
just one okay
uh
what password did I log in with
it
let's see
uh
come on
shut up
shut up no no no no
yes yes yes yes
no no no
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
it could work okay I'm in spawn now in
Edge
um let's see if it works better
um
why you want me to buy tickets no no no
no no this is the account where a ticket
what are you talking about what you
talking about what do you what do you
mean oh what do you mean
it's a liar
you know nothing
minor tickets
okay yes it is
a ticket yes yes let me watch please oh
thank you yes thank you thank you okay
okay
let's see it's not it's not oh wait I
know I'm not moving oopsie
it's not buffering but it's really low
quality let's do low latency
come on
okay so I hear a music
[Music]
and the Sea flowers dance again but now
I really need to go to an idol meeting
okay okay
ah
I'm gonna take I'm gonna take a nap for
three minutes
BRB
BRB tell tell everyone I'll be gone in
three minutes sound phone number
I'm back
you know
a black chunk case
welcome is talking
okay okay
[Music]
foreign
I think
[Music]
[Applause]
I have two survivors
[Music]
I'm already crying
no
a dummy
come here
foreign
oh my God
I need tissues
[Music]
[Laughter]
onion tissues
okay okay
I got huge tissues
foreign
[Music]
please wait please hold
on
[Music]
how many Japan Bros are watching for me
I'm gonna be quiet okay I promise you
can listen to your your ooshi
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
oh my God
I I hope I'm not too delayed from you
guys
I see I see um
attention now but it's been here for a
while the phone and no camera rapping oh
now I see the picture the big picture
when did it switch for you guys now
um
[Laughter]
I want to listen to that
it's about synced okay
um
no screenshot um I think like you could
take screenshots of the first 30 minutes
because that's what's being um publicly
streamed
but I'm not gonna guarantee it but
logically thinking it should be fine
yeah logically thinking but everything
after those first 30 minutes was not
publicly being streamed big no big no or
I don't know maybe even after the show
I didn't I didn't properly read the
rules today I think no videos but
screenshots are okay it wasn't that the
real last time for other concerts as
well
screenshots okay okay okay okay okay
screenshots okay okay there you go there
you go just look on Twitter imagination
gang
look on Twitter if you follow Vata mates
then you know what's up
um
although most vladimates will be busy
supporting her in Zep Tokyo
Zep is um is a chain of Life concert uh
uh concert Halls
uh throughout Japan mm-hmm
I've been in um
a couple of those I think I was in uh
the one in
zip number
and I think I wasn't the one isn't there
one in Yokohama I think I was in that
one too
yeah the original zap venue closed
recently which one was that again
um
foreign
four thousand people
except let me look it up
capacity let's see how many Vata Maids
are gonna be there although I wonder if
they're actually Gonna Fill it all up uh
or if they have to like put less people
inside
uh
except Tokyo
capacity
um
two thousand seven hundred someone in
the chat said four thousand
um
don't make me cry again
in the snare
phone ah it's actually not
okay there we go
it wasn't fixed after all whoa
oh my God exciting excited
foreign
[Music]
piano
[Laughter]
[Music]
laughs
[Laughter]
[Music]
I don't know man it's the piano
laughs
oh
my God
oh my God
meow
oh my God oh my God oh my God
chunkies
no
tell me hey
hey
let's go
oh my God this is so nice
no and I got sunkers right with me
on my left side chunkers came to join me
oh then my tomatoes must be so happy I
wonder if totang is in here
and where are you
where are you
a big fan of Vladimir and Kiara
he must be there where is he
now
mm-hmm
oh he's smiling he's swapping did you
see that dude's vibing he was swabbing
hi hi hey hey hey
yay
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
me too I'm tired too my thumb man
hi
[Music]
gotta wipe my tears
oh yes
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah
I can't do that hat movement
I I want to do the slow hand moving and
I told you guys before about they were
doing it they were doing it at the slow
parts of the song oh
wow
[Music]
let's go
wow
oh
[Music]
wow
did you go do the same thing
ah
oh
wow
oh they're clapping in the ribbon cute
they're trying they would they would
probably be screaming when they can so
they're clapping instead
in Rhythm
um
see this movement this movement that's
that's what I was explaining to you guys
before
you kind of like this this you see that
you see that
that yes that's
that's that's it remember it guys learn
it
and now you change you feel the the beat
changing and the song is gonna be more
upbeat so you change your movement
[Music]
oh
wow oh
[Music]
wow
gunky monkey let's go
that was a bit scary that was that had
yandere Vibes because with the gunge
about your face she was singing You're
gonna come and see me right right
all right you're gonna come and see me
right
oh they got the glasses I see they got
the glasses the audience cute
oh
yummy I'm so Winger
no no
[Music]
no no no no no of course of course I'll
be there until the end
phew
I'm trying to do the head movement
quit that's an item let's look at your
name is
[Music]
oh
wow oh
wow
[Music]
but
oh
rock and roll baby
oh my God flashing lights help
oh mayday mayday
hey hey
oh yeah
I I I I I I I I
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
and
oh this is so cool
oh
cocoy
what the man
look at me
CCA man
hahaha
oh my God
found my Oshi found my Oshi she was here
all along
sure sure
[Laughter]
oh my God
what how did I do that how did they do
that
what happened with this with the screen
she's still on the screen right
it looks like she's she's like
that that was that looks good that looks
cool
oh
[Music]
that's gummy
sad for me
oh my God
whoa
yo that was badass
[Music]
all right
oh
yum yum
she's she's gonna drink water
she's cute oh there you look at her
drinking water so respectfully
what what is that for me
why would you stop stupid stupid
no I think I got two more two more
seconds delayed
nazika
is
n't even buffering it just stopped
clap clap clap clap
[Music]
oh my I'm so happy for her oh
he's asking if he looked forward to her
first tell a life he's like yeah you did
didn't you
she's asking you to tweet out with the
hashtag
hmm
okay
oh it's just so cute
oh she's so cute
ah stop being so cute what the hell
she's doing the the dance the dance
that reminded me of that
um a dance from Russia I think
oh she wants to play with the people who
are in the audience
yay oh it's so quiet
[Music]
oh
she's okay
because they have to look up no why
would it stop again why would you do
that why would you do that why would you
do that why would you do that why would
you do that why would you do that it's
buffering Let me refresh
I know they can't yeah yeah no no
tomorrow
stupid Edge
okay okay
step for that man
Johansson oh
well she says that you can't like do
something with your feet but you're
allowed to do something with your upper
body so
you should show
[Laughter]
oh that one is doing it properly
I think they're a bit embarrassed to do
it but damn it I would do it for you
hi
she's saying she can't see the comments
too in the spawn I think or in YouTube
YouTube I'm not sure
hi
uh
oh
oh you look so freaking bye bye bye bye
get out of here get out of here
she's she's asking you to
to buy a ticket
to go watch the real life please
me
oh that dude was wearing a Non-Stop
Story t-shirt I saw that
in the audience
Michael okay she's gonna go grab a
microphone how have you been singing
without a microphone until now
hi
yay yay
oh don't cry about that mates oh
oh no time to rest what that means
you thought you could rest no no get up
get up whoa
oh that was fast
oh
wow
it's very slow song now
whoa
now if you go to the left side in my
description you can switch it to English
and buy the ticket in English if you
want
costs 5 000 Yen this is what it fits
though
you can watch the partner you missed
afterwards as well for up to one month
is that is that vitamins DNA
[Laughter]
well isn't that like what was that again
that in the background like I know they
were maybe trying to show something else
but uh isn't that like
what happened to DNA
[Music]
oh
hey
[Music]
hmm
that's snow not rain
it's a beautiful song
I like the instrumental
wow we were in a desert now we're in the
snow desert wow
oh
kittens
very pretty
oh
I love to see the audience vibing
holidays
Christmas time let's go
[Music]
waving with my head
hi
Thomas hi
[Music]
that's cute I like that background
foreign
wave your hands
this is such a cute song I would sing
this song at the end of the concert but
maybe she has something better like
meaning wise and feeling wise it's a
good song at the end of the set list
um
in before secret special guests Calliope
Mori
[Music]
I need to sneeze
okay
[Music]
yeah I mean she could still do cloudy
sheep just uh with Cali as the backup
vocals not actually being there
[Music]
da da
cute
mm-hmm
[Music]
I love how her Cape always Swings with
her so nicely
she's like a superhero super sheep
oh
[Applause]
yes wake me up girl
Wake me up inside Wake Me Up Inside
[Music]
call my name this is what she's singing
right now call my name and save me from
myself that's what she's singing imagine
that
hahaha
about me
hey
I like the song
hi
whoa
oh
hi hey hey hey hey hey
whoa
well she's looking down on the snow
oh my God she's so cool
hey hey
just don't fall down sheep
hey hey hey
hey
God I missed these kind of idol concerts
it's even better when I when I know the
songs and the choreographies though
like in the hello project
oh
I said
hey
what
say it say it girl I I I I I I I I I say
oh someone changed her pen light color
to Red he's got older colors yo
he can switch those colors you got one
of those expensive pen lights
he adjusts the color to the mood not bad
sir not bad I respect that
MC time okay okay
those must be so happy
just the father that makes me cry
because she's been doing
um weekly weekly karaoke is right for
like
over over a year
kind of like always preparing for this
and it's like it was building up to this
for so long it's just just just to
imagine how they must be feeling
since the beginning oh yeah she has like
hundreds hundreds
who
[Music]
oh
you are cute
no don't go back don't go back don't
come back yes yes yes
no no no no no don't go back no no no no
no no no no she's playing with us
[Laughter]
oh she's trying to get instructions from
the audience
yay
foreign
[Music]
she's asking for permission to drink
water
he's telling your audience to sit the
hell down
and they
listening videos
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
and she wanted to do that
um
conduct
stumbled over her words again
[Music]
she's so cute
she's asking if it's your first time in
a concert
you know
oh you're so cute
hi
hi okay
she's asking who who has been to
concert before now she asks
she asks who who had who's been seeing a
a vegetable concert in person for the
first time
not me
isn't there a second floor in zip Tokyo
as well I think so
as far as I remember but I don't know if
they have people up there today
foreign
that's where the second floor starts
hmm
why doesn't hat look like some uh
Austrian traditional hats that you wear
with lederhosen
[Laughter]
Scott
well apparently
apparently there's also people on the
side of the floor
not sure
she's uh checking out the merchandise
that the audience is carrying with them
that's timer
aliens
so a girl
me just kidding no it's not a a girl I
saw a girl
[Laughter]
she's asking if you liked her original
songs
huh
oh God she's calling me up she's calling
me out right now
she's like did you listen to my original
songs more than once right more than
once what
how did she
I'm sweating
how did she know
oh
come on I'm everywhere I can clap all
the time
[Laughter]
[Applause]
um
oops poop speak
big boobs boobs
sorry
they're big
hi
yes
microphone I think it's the same from
the image
Yeah Yeah from the promotional image
you know
is that an automatic cat toilet in the
background never mind
yes yes oh she was pointing at her boobs
[Laughter]
I love that outfit what if she surprises
us with that outfit in 3D today I wonder
I feel like she's gonna do it I feel
like it's gonna happen later I'm just
gonna change again and she's gonna be in
that outfit I I feel it I feel it
it is quite possible Aqua Senpai did
that too
I know
oh my God I love you so I'll be so
screaming I'll be so hyped when she
comes out with that outfit
yes
[Music]
practicing how to move your pen line
right now
okay
she's asking you guys to sing along if
you're not there
I don't know the lyrics I think
oh yeah
hey yay yay yay
foreign
[Music]
such a beautiful song
hi hi
foreign
really
oh I just saw a comment interesting
comments
[Music]
hmm
ah free I want to stand in that first
line man
First Line concerts always based up I
mean at least like in a in a surrounding
like this
where the people actually keep space
like I can't imagine being on the first
row in like a EDM concerts or something
like that where people squish you to
death
hell no oh hell no
like I've only seen that in concert
footage from like the big people
I'm like outside uh open air concerts
when they show the first row and they're
like uh getting that rail squished into
their stomachs like how much must they
be suffering oh my God
yeah but when you're in a concert hall
like that they at least keep some kind
of a little bit of a distance
a little bit
sweet night sweet time
oh
so I can fall back asleep but now back
asleep but now can I speak englishu
yeah that's how she sleeps while
standing up yes
hahaha
cute I like that background
the way she looked over she looked at me
she looked right at me guys not in you
at me
hey
also like I don't know how it looks in
real life but
with that with how it looks like right
now if you stand right in front of it it
must look pretty real
like she's actually in front of the
screen
as real as it can look considering it's
a happy tuba
oh
no she's looking at me shut up you want
to be banned
no she was looking at me shut up
shut up he's looking at me
no
she laughed at me I don't know if that's
good or not
she's walking towards me right now
towards me not you
oh cute she's so small she looks so
small
my God okay I'm dead she said she wants
to talk to me she said literally in the
lyrics okay
no no all about me
oh she likes me
[Music]
now I'll give her a call after the
concert
oh my God cute
oh my God
[Music]
hi Mommy
I like this song this is the first time
I hear it actually
I like it
good night good night
okay sleep time
ah
when you sent it to me what do you mean
I don't remember
oh
weak
can I go to Cali fight
okay
here
let's go
I I I I I I
foreign
[Laughter]
I was waiting for that
the part of your nose is higher to fly
I can't rap that fast
originally disguise the story that
sounds of you today
[Laughter]
yo Kelly
oh there's some pink ones for Cali
though
foreign
[Music]
hahaha
oh
hey hey
hey
hey hey hey hey
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
can you see cloudy sheep she lost hard
but she will start
crap yeah
nailed it
cloudy sheep
hey
chunkies please take a seat please take
a seat don't disturb the concert please
oh
you were cool
very cool
guys where are you going
this is not a parkour chonkers this is
not a pokot
foreign
you're allowed to drink water she says
no
clap your sheep
kinda stumbled over her words again
on the towel nice nice
[Music]
yes yes I cuddle you
oh don't cry I already cried enough
about them
I can't cry again
oh munch
chunk I smudged me
okay
foreign
also are in the concert in the solo live
concert
because you're always together oh
Munch don't Munch me Junkies
it feel it feels like you know when I'm
touching chunkers while looking at what
Amazon but I feel like I'm petting my
dummy senpai putting fluffy sheep
there's a surprise surprise
oh oh my God oh my God is she coming
with the
second uh third outfit
masaka
issue Isha
foreign
oh my God I'm so sorry that they can't
scream out loud
oh
no no nothing con
ding ding ding oh
foreign
[Music]
boom
so I'm just doing sound effects
I love the the black and red colors it
gives uh really rock and roll feeling
[Music]
she's asking you which point you you're
looking at you like the most
it is quite the cleavage that you have
yes indeed
oh yeah right oh that's uh transparent
uh
fabric oh you can see her
guys I really highly positioned belly
button
oh that's so pretty
like it's kind of like fighting for
Christmas as well the outfit like a
Christmas concert
anymore
cute I like it a lot I really like it I
like those bootsies
like those boots
I like it
she's saying that a passionate color
variation like this is pretty rare for
her because she normally would go for
like white or a light pink color
yeah I agree I agree
foreign
[Music]
I love it oh yeah
do those floppy parts around her arms
and her handcuffs
it really kind of gives a Christmas Vibe
the fluffy fluffy wool the white part
you know what I mean
and this golden stars and all that
that's a damn time
she's asking who has been watching his
dreams is that what a stupid question
thank you
oh she's gonna cry
it's talking about her early days and
how hard she worked playing games until
the morning
but his stupid internet connection
her over
so often
oh no don't say that
she said she was worried about let um
losing fans oh
#relatable
um
[Music]
crying while playing Ark
um
case
well
hello
she said that she didn't think she would
stand on a stage like this Sunday back
then when she was
I'm trying to gather courage and
confidence with her streams
yeah you stepped away at the wrong time
she just got changed
isn't it I love that outfit
oh
I think she just was like uh saying that
even if you're new like some new new
Tomatoes were maybe worried about
whether or not they are okay to come to
a concert like this or not but she says
everyone's welcome
and she says that she could only release
an album like this thanks to the support
from everyone hmm
well Sean Grace oh my God
okay
are you okay
[Music]
oh
she's talking about how she tried to
stream every day for her fans even if
it's really late
see she's such a such an idol oh she
looks so cute
she say so
cowboy
oh
no more yay
of God
of course why would they not she's
asking if the people in the audience are
happy and glad that they came in person
of course
[Music]
asking you first-time viewers are also
happy that they came to watch
oh come on
[Music]
oh
nakuna
don't cry
oh my God so sweet no
What tomatoes be like my baby is crying
drink that water soak it up
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
hmm
yes Trent number one yeah
congratulations
Twitter Trend number one
last bottle
hello I think she's asking if you still
have enough energy to go until the end
yes of course
yeah people watching from the stream
where you went
yes next song
Cube pray to the cube
is
foreign
[Music]
cute
huh
chunkers ran away
why
crater it's just not a hater
she's scared of the cube
just trying to tell us something
oh this kind of makes you feel how big
that Tokyo actually is
[Music]
um
I'm glad they're showing angles of the
audience yeah
foreign
I was feeling it I was vibing
chocolates don't eat the plastic don't
eat the plastic junkers no
oh
new song I'm unpublished new song oh
what's up
my song
[Music]
new song called my song
oh
she's telling us who wrote the song and
the lyrics now
I think it's famous people but I don't
know them
foreign
am I ahead of some of you guys
because some of you comment now about
Unison Square Garden
you guys are kind of late
oh I guess that's good that's I guess
kind of good
I'm a little ahead oh maybe you should
refresh
now before the song starts now she's
being quiet
um
all over the place
okay
what kind of song Rock Rocky song cute
song oh
okay
starts quiet
oh okay I was bamboozled
okay she mad
oh
hey hey hey
[Music]
oh
kakoi
oh yeah now the beat is Con consistent
hi
rock around
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I I I
whoa oh my God what's going on
whoa
this is a very um uh Roller Coaster song
it really feels like I'm a jet coaster
hahaha
yeah
oh
hold on
many many up and downs in that song
wow
nice song
very wild why don't you
I don't know what at all
she's she's like
hitting us with those bangers
so often
oh
[Music]
last song
which I don't believe because there will
be an Anchorage
oh it's rainbow let's go
where the Sheep show me where the sheeps
are
show me the rainbows and the sheeps
oh sorry
oh
yay
[Music]
ball
oon
[Music]
what the man
hey
[Music]
um
la la la la la
[Music]
oh
God
no don't go
I mean
no don't go no she's coming back she's
coming back promise you I'm good oh they
can't even do the uncle to call no oh
I was running encoder Uncle yes yes I'll
I'll jail for you I'll go to
Uncle Uncle
I'm
calling Uncle Uncle
they're so fast there's
I'm gonna help me please Uncle Luke oh
hello
There She Goes
she's asking if you're still there yes
yes Peak
peek
stop stop your comedian
foreign
[Laughter]
okay
so I don't know
oh
Duncan Duncan
it's
[Music]
oh wait wait
no you did you did scissors
denial
let me touch that at all
and she did peace
in any case in any case I won
okay
everyone who did scissors kind of won
because she first did scissors and then
and then change to paper
hi she says please wait please hold
please hold the line
please hold the line hold the line
I know how to hold the line
I know you do I remember you holding a
line in Fire Emblem when YouTube was
effing me
I remember those times when the stream
was dying
hold on oh my God oh my God whoa
because
[Music]
[Applause]
I ate some eat us till yesterday
chill I love how this stage is made out
of inastoia
hey
yo yo
[Laughter]
oh oh yeah show us that cool badass
dance she should she should do uh
breakdance
where's the where's the freaking spot
down there get on the floor
twerk for me
I want to see a twerking latama
oh
wait it changed from irastoya to proper
illustrations
the cheap stage is gone now we're on the
real stage
that's so smart she had all the all the
fourth gen names
oh
so let's go
[Music]
I I
don't
remember
[Music]
yeah
hey
[Music]
Google
I see the girl
[Music]
because
hey hey
[Music]
hello my name is
foreign foreign
[Music]
foreign
Para
everybody
said hello
[Music]
Daddy
wonderful finally a song I could sing
along
thank you thank you
that's fun so much more fun when you can
sing along
next time I practice more for what time
is songs
[Laughter]
she's asking if you have your sunglasses
on for the party B song for the wrap
what am I rap
foreign
yes
I got my party people sunglasses
I feel like she's gonna sing one more
song
oh
honey
news enhancement
hmm
thank you bushy Road thank you
oh
best fats otherwise
[Music]
come on
oh
foreign
song going to be included in D40 day
big news incoming
money
video
messages from her generates
no okay
honey sheep
oh
what what's happening congratulations it
says
blue whale
[Music]
oh my God the music once wants me to do
screamo
oh details on a later day
just wait for the new details it says on
the screen
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
Blu-ray
hi
and I can't expect the dead water miss
him but you didn't really surprise me
with that
blue Rage
Style
the original death metal signal
ah
she wants to do something with the
audience oh
wait I saw another girl there's two
girls at least
okay three including me
oh
yeah
oh it must be whole life members no no
no way they wouldn't do that that's not
safe
oh does she want to take a picture of
what I didn't really listen what she
wanted to do
I think she wants to take a picture
oh she wants to she wants them to hide
their faces
he's like maybe I'll hide my face too oh
no that doesn't work hmm I guess that
doesn't work
foreign
normally you would turn around but
how how is that
How's that gonna work
oh
[Laughter]
wait there's no one on the second floor
I think only just a few like important
people staff people
where are you
oh this is so cute the dude in the
middle he must be like hey I've done
this right next to me
now
we're just another girl oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh this is funny
it's a joy of pressure I think both
ah another okay oh cute girl wait is
there hella cute girl there there's a
really cute girl
now because
oh my God who is that who is that girl
[Music]
oh cute
this must be the angle that she's been
seeing like throughout the whole
um performance like this camera
seems to be like in front of the
stage
and that's what she must be looking at
oh
don't be so shy guys come on do the pose
properly
come on with confidence
what's with your hand on your hip you
guys gonna put the other hand on your
hand
don't be so shy don't be so shy where is
the other hand
I love that I love that
ah
[Music]
I wanna do this with you guys
we'll make sure to embarrass you buzz
you couldn't embarrass me impossible
thank you I'll cause thank you
I'm not gonna embarrass you either no no
you're not gonna be shortless that's not
gonna be allowed
laughs
yay
she's asking for it for Applause for the
staff and everyone who worked on this
yay
[Applause]
[Music]
she's such a cute sweet cheem Bowman why
is she so sweet such a cutie pie such a
kind-hearted spirit I love her
and
um
[Music]
last song
bandana
she's saying there's no more original
songs that she could sing
she says she has to do her best next
year too so she can do more concerts
like this
like do more original songs
to perform
oh she's she changed up the song that's
coming she changed it a little bit
is it weather hackers
Sparks
oh
cloudy sheep acoustic acoustic range
Monty
oh
what about the rapture
what happens to that
that's gonna be nice though
oh oh it still got that uh
High Tempo to it
foreign
[Music]
I like this version hmm
yes there's going to be a Blu-ray of
this concert and you can watch it if you
have a ticket until one month afterwards
yeah I like this version Maybe
even more than the original
um
[Music]
I don't know it sounds magical
I like the the violin
I think I heard a violin in the
background
hmm
Tales of intro yeah it does kind of fit
I like those bells too hmm
it has a has a little bit of an
adventurous vibe to it
could also be a
theme song for an actual year game
judging from the instrumental
whatever
oh
bye bye
bye bye no no is she leaving
she's still she's still there I still
see her
well
hmm
but he's just crying so much
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's sing one more song come on
uncle uncle
um
[Music]
she says it's unfair because the song
like the acoustic arrange made it sound
so much more like emotional
oh we're getting one myself yeah buddy
no don't you know no she's like oh I
said it would be the last song but
she says anyone who doesn't want it to
end
up
I'm gonna
come up
oh I see some I see two dudes not
clapping I know you want her to sing
more stop use your hands
calling him out no no no they're not shy
you don't need to be confident to clap
she didn't announce it she just said she
wants to do a second life
foreign
[Music]
oh
wow oh
wow
[Music]
oh
wow
foreign
[Music]
hey hey
oh
wow oh
wow
[Music]
oh
no no
no
did you guys have a good time
hell yeah we did
oh oh this makes me feel so happy when I
see the audience with those pen lights
waving at her oh
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
wow
foreign
[Laughter]
I know this is that
I think that was what was it on purpose
she played it off too well it must have
been on purpose the pink it's the thing
oh
that was really good yoga
[Music]
wow
nice
no
hmm
thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
oh it's Scarlet
oh it's coming
whoa
oh it's color
oh
the photos
from the concert already in the credits
nice
[Music]
okay
I'm glad I did the watch along
I
still oh
mother's glitter Young
s
[Music]
Nina
oh wow
oh
[Music]
wow
I never noticed that Hulk
how'd you make the keys later
Hawk honk
what the I never noticed that
I actually met the kids later that's the
Gangnam part
[Laughter]
ner oh
[Music]
oh
oh there's some really funny sounds in
here
oh man whoever made the instrumental had
a lot of fun with that I see I see
Instagram
thank you
that was fun oh
oh I still hear them oh
[Music]
no
I feel the love
[Music]
special thanks and tell the lab member
oh
[Music]
I think she's gonna say bye-bye telling
the people to get out of here yeah there
she is
oh
yeah
stop
[Music]
foreign
like the face of the holotalk poster on
the left right now
[Music]
um
foreign
how many times you plan on making me cry
huh huh
there's something about Lata man
that just makes you want to support her
like even like I mean y'all know like
is my number one but
like I don't know
is she like
she has this Idol idol trait about her
and this this pure Purity without like
I'm not joking like this is not about
her say so no
she has this kind Pure Heart
and really really like you feel that
this is what she wants to do and like
seeing her work so hard with her karaoke
streams and her original songs
makes you really want to support her
whoever whether she's your favorite or
not but she'll maybe end up being your
favorite because she has this charm
um
[Music]
I respect her like she puts out so much
content
and it makes me wanna do the same
I kind of like especially with this
class right now
I look up to her even more than before
I feel like I'm watching her as a fan
now like she got me she got me good
she has this magical spell that she
casts on anyone who watches her
she can't you can't run away from her
yeah she's so humble and modest and
sweet
oh man and she's such a good friend too
like she's so so kind like you feel like
you feel like
I don't know
when I when when I Collapse with her
even in the beginning when we didn't
know each other a while she was just
always so welcoming like doesn't matter
if you don't know her she's just so
sweet to everyone
I think maybe inside the whole life
she's she's the manifestation the
clearest and bestest manifestation of
an idol
Maybe
um
concert night
I love her that might be going too far
no
no I don't care
no I'm I'm looking at this objectively
myoshi is pecula and I still say that
oh man I need to
oh man
um
sure okay yeah
yeah she's also a pure Idol
true true okay she
said why the machine place in the top
ranks together with Solace
okay okay okay okay
but like I've seen I've seen a lot of
Idols like real Idols like from real
Idol groups not like virtual YouTubers
um I've been a huge Idol
before whole life
so like I have a clear vision and idea
of what an idol usually
um embodies and is supposed to convey
and yes yes
I think really
um do that very very well as much as
they can as a virtual Idol
um
is also up there hell yeah
yes yes yes I can't wait until nanity is
gonna do a solo concert she's I'm I'm
sure she's definitely working towards it
she already has a bunch of original
songs so I'm sure she's gonna put out
more and more and more so that she can
eventually have a a solo concert as well
I can't imagine her not going for that
hmm
I'm not only talking about like how they
are on stage though I'm talking about
their General
demeanor and personality and there's
nothing bad about you know not being
such a typical Idol like for me like
it's just a typical a type of
Personality that and and way of like
presenting yourself
that describes an idol hmm
it doesn't matter if you don't fit into
that package and you're you're that
doesn't mean you're not as good as a
performer you're still an amazing
performer and singer or whatever but or
maybe you're more on the artist side
like suicide Senpai she's rather than an
idol I would put her in the category of
a proper uh artist like a general
like any song an anime song artist
but Idol the idol category is there's
something
special like a spark Sparks stream
spikes
oh
so yeah so it says
[Music]
I don't think anyone yet
um
say Sona
[Music]
Cinema
[Laughter]
foreign foreign
[Music]
all that I mean there's different kinds
of Idols sure and the idle scene has
kind of changed as well
um with like a lot of interesting
Concepts out there now but I'm talking
about the traditional
typical
yeah
um
[Music]
foreign
yes yes yes
when will you sing for us Kiara when I
sing for you guys every once in a while
in my karaoke streams but until I can do
something like this I'll need to become
3D as well
um although I did have a concert at
dokomi
I did as much as I could in in 2D for um
yeah
foreign
but I wonder you know because like the
Japanese members are focused on Japan
obviously so if they give a solo concert
or a normal concert whatever then they
obviously do it in Japan but like I
wonder if any any of the whole live
English members were able to do a uh
like in-person concert not a digital one
like where would they be doing it
because our fans are like all over but I
was thinking while I was watching just
now of the possibility to have like
several
valleys well uh several locations at
once be at several locations at the same
time although the time difference would
be difficult but I was I was thinking
they'll have one in New York and at the
same time I have the concert also and
I guess you could do a tour huh venues
that's yeah that's what I was thinking
of I guess you could do a tour but I
would personally be worried if you do
because it's not so con it's not like
your fans are so concentrated in one
country as they are for the Japanese
members like for us they're all over the
place so filling up the venues would
worry me personally a little bit I mean
probably American venues wouldn't be
much of a problem but let's say we're
going to I don't know uh Europe hmm
it's really hard to tell like how big of
a venue you should Reserve to begin with
uh at least one European venue I think
should be should be a thing and if I
were to do something like that obviously
I would want to hold one either in
Germany or in US Austria because that's
just where where I am from and you know
you want to do a home home country
home run right
um
but I don't think it would be a big
venue
unfortunately
[Music]
oh it's gone it's gone it's over
um
foreign
[Music]
kind of want to do a concert in Japan as
well I want to do a location in n a and
one in Europe and then in Japan
that's that's a thing manageable
oh
let's see
hopefully we can make that through some
time wow
I don't know like as as a whole life
English maybe Hollow myth as a whole I
think that's very very manageable
but uh
I don't know I don't have enough
I don't have enough uh
confidence for that
um
but seeing what them is simply like that
with real real people with pen lights on
there it makes me makes me feel things
you know
you could do it are you sure
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
Queen right
some Japanese person in the chat said if
if he could leave the country he would
even go uh to a concert in Vienna for me
[Music]
oh Austria would you guys would European
viewers all travel to Austria for me for
me
would you do that dedication that's so
sweet
oh
yeah
foreign
thank you
all right that means I gotta make some
more songs I gotta make
some more original songs
gotta make an album
yeah
even if it's just for a concert
can I make an album
foreign
[Music]
how many songs usually are there in the
concert how many songs were these
12.
something around that I feel like like
I've been in concerts that had like 25
songs or 30 songs sometimes even
but I guess you can even just do it with
12 or 15. for a concert not an album
and maybe mix in like uh one whole life
or one or two whole life songs
like General songs
um
it varies a lot yeah 13.
[Music]
well that sounds like that sounds
manageable
mama
zombie Dixon
[Music]
Girl Scouts girls is not an original
song for me
you forgot an important one though you
forgot the birthday song for for Cali
do a whole talk in the middle
now I want to do a music performance
yes okay this this motivated me
motive is
she really motivated me I'm so cute and
now I I want I want a 3D Idol outfit too
I want like a general one for whole life
English and I want one for myself also
like on that on that promotional image
um because it's gonna be difficult to
dance in my
in my actual uniform
yeah with that tight ass mini skirt
that's gonna be difficult
Yodeling Song no holiday
[Music]
s
I know I can't yodel
[Music]
I should buy the the right to that
song
[Music]
I need a song like that that's really
just like
around
like that
that's just I don't know about having
chickens fight one another or something
like that
get into the fight ring yeah meme song
oh oh yeah yeah yeah a wrap I want one
rap song If I make an album I want one
rap song
like the last time I rap
yeah
[Music]
um
can rap too
I can rap too
[Music]
rap kill rap
I'll think of the lyrics
okay guys it's it's early now would be
the time when I would normally get up
[Music]
when I would normally wake up
okay but we'll really we'll read some
super chats and then later on we have TT
RPG so I'll take a I'll take a nap in
between
um but I'm gonna do the super chats now
we stopped where
yo
opsie
[Music]
um
watching the concert together with me
from here on out
it'll be raining super chats
and
tails
did I read Tails or did I not read tails
um
[Music]
next time I'm gonna be watching first
gen concept holy I'm gonna go I'm
gonna go so crazy for them
[Music]
thanks for watching
uh question tales of the rise did I read
any of them I don't think I did did I
read the ones from the vatameco lab
did I read those
[Music]
start of the I'm back stream
concert I don't know if I'll do a watch
along when is it
[Music]
come it I have to read the I'm back one
oh okay
okay okay okay okay
no problem
[Music]
21st October oh dear next week there's
so many concerts
I can't promise
I cannot promise
uh 20 Wait no that's uh
hola it is next week
oh
I'll see what I can do
anyway I'm still yo why does it let me
scroll
wait
freaking browser gets so heavy
uh yeah because it kind of raises the
expectation that I'm gonna do a lot too
long for every single concert
uh let's see we'll see I do love
suicides and Play songs as well
[Music]
it would be freaking hype to to watch
her live yeah
oh definitely even if I don't do a watch
along I'll definitely be watching
okay
[Music]
I'll wait ah the thumbnail for that one
actually I was um oh God
[Music]
30 47 mentions
I think it became Moy while I was
watching the concert
[Music]
a bit disco message
what the is happening I'm not gonna
look at it now because then I'll just go
through it and not be able to answer and
then I then I won't be able to get back
to it so actually
um the thumbnail for the I'm backstream
was made by Nino Maya news I told her
um because she was online I was like yo
could you help me because I was sitting
in the spa and I knew I wouldn't have
time to make a thumbnail until the
actual stream so I was like asking
around and you know was the first one I
asked and she actually replied and I was
like yo do you maybe have any time to
make a thumbnail for me
um and I gave her the pictures that I
wanted on it and I told her to text and
then she put it together for me oh thank
you Ina coming in with coming in in the
clutch times
[Music]
foreign
push
okay putting that
here
yeah yeah okay good good good
in imagination
okay now let's go Frozen kitchen so
let's keep late thank you midnight
looking for the top action looking for
the top donation looking for the top
donation Falls
are you wearing the Canada Trip nice
Spyro please play me Danke Schoen play
Turok hey it's an FPS thank you sir and
play Michael Jordan thank you
the well turak is so old you know
it's
I would love to play it for Nostalgia
reasons but I feel like no one would
give a
oh man oh man also is it abandoned wear
by now I wonder because those old games
are often abandoned where
I like how you put the the names of the
games into your name though
you watch it it is it is abandoned where
it's on the switch what
switch point oh
by whom
like it who's the publisher then wait
does that mean that Nintendo if
something gets pointed on the switch
does that mean the publisher is always
Nintendo
oh no right that's not how it works
yeah two Rock switch
work for Nintendo switch
age verification
[Music]
I need to
um
never mind
nighttime Studio okay interesting never
mind going back to Super chance Memphis
hilarious talented artists sometimes a
frog he enjoys rocking Phoenix I'm
assuming it all went well but at least I
didn't break my neck yes you deserve
hundred more vacations of the amount of
work you put in for your Flappy chickens
you know that right never downplay the
work you put in or the talents you've
got because you are one impressive bird
ah
keeping your true and amazing self
now one more thing tangent attempt which
female character from one of your
playthroughs rise at 2B Etc would you be
down to trade outfits with oh
I want to trade outfits with both Riser
and to be and a
wait was it A1 or A2 I'm getting
confused
hey I'm thinking of a paper uh sizes
[Music]
din A4
oh my God
I got confused but yeah those outfits
would be would be I think gorgeous on me
[Music]
enough that it's body paint okay still
um
and from the other games I played
I don't know they all look so gorgeous
I wanna wear
[Music]
um
all the all the female characters
outfits
um
Riven or ryven thank you
three times thank you thank you thank
you thank you for your sweet message
me I'll try I'll try my best not to push
myself too much but hey this week I have
two days off so it's already going well
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
welcome back we were about to go math
without you
I think the new eggs were already
looking at the fryer hope this trip went
great injury-free and we're ready to
have to deal with all of us again now
let's start funding the next trip too
son
[Music]
original
[Applause]
on his way home now from the concert he
said he's gonna watch the this one too
long as well
foreign
[Music]
I cried I cried even before the concert
started
yes oh man must have been so nice with
his sheep's sheeps out there
okay okay okay
um
[Music]
oh I'm happy for totang
must have been that must have been an
amazing week for him first collab vatoma
and Kiana his two oceans and now concert
from wataman oh oh he must be like
falling apart from happiness he must be
crumbling like an apple pie
living his best life
[Music]
keeps on winning
you know
[Music]
and then look at us from a different
point of view and be happy that they're
collabing
[Music]
yes okay well type of thank you again I
hope you guys didn't really go crazy it
wasn't really that long of a break so
man my sweet eggs I mean I would be a
bit flattered
um
if my going away for three to four days
would make you go so crazy even though I
was putting out content anyway I would
be a little bit flattered we didn't lull
I know you're lying I know you went
crazy
[Music]
it was refreshing but I was missing your
stories well now you got this got the
stories
now I'm back with stories otherwise I
wouldn't have had stories
now
[Music]
hmm
you were catching up with the archive
well then yeah that's that's good
and you've got something to do Dominique
medication there's a little Danke Schoen
skydancash and Jim Tracy Duncan Slavic
fellow Duncan Dominique
[Music]
hey Dad all right everyone back to work
and don't forget to pay your salary
Daisy
ah thanks to you I had a paid vacation
thank you
thank you Daisy
I'm back
I'm back to work for you and you work
for me
[Laughter]
[Music]
what a all things all things are
balanced as they should be
Jay swagburg Duncan Seth please thank
you for the pinky
welcome back we missed you and I hope
you enjoyed your vacation thank you I'm
glad you missed me thank you
that was a little bit of a worry that
you guys will disappear also just like
water Medicine by sad and said in her
concert it made me relate about you know
how she had issues in the beginning
yeah
and I feel like I had a ton of
issues in the first couple of months and
then still later on as well like
and I think everyone
almost almost everyone in the whole life
probably has this fear of losing their
audience because they lose interest or
they or you did something that they
don't like or whatever
it's it's quite the scary font
[Music]
and I I am gonna be honest I have that
worry constantly and at any given time
so whenever I I read something like that
or when I read your names and you see
you're still here it's very reassuring
but I need that all the time like
sometimes I I don't see a name for a
while and I'm like did that person stop
liking me
is that person not interested anymore
what did I do what did I do what did I
do wrong am I not funny anymore so I
need you guys to constantly tell me
um please please
foreign
[Music]
laughs hold on
people come and go but you'll always be
in their heart and they can come back
from time to time
but like
some people live forever and that's
that's very sad
and I understand that like I I've had
that too like I watched I watched
content creators
before and and at some point I was just
kind of sick and maybe like not
interested anymore of of that content
creator and then I start watching the
videos completely
um so it's it's normal but it's sad
for the Creator
[Music]
I try to make it whenever I can thank
you
you aren't just a content creator you're
my honestly
free kiss for you
[Music]
stubborn supporter
that's good to know hmm
thank you guys I love you
free kids not fair okay you'll get one
too
you watched the last whole talk on the
plane like the archive while you
actually got an internet connection on
the plane
make sure to tell the pilot he should
fly a little bit higher and not so close
to the water scary man the dream
that I have
before he flies into the freaking wall
of water it was like a it was so weird
though it was not even like a normal uh
typical like tsunami it was like a
double tsunami one one went in One
Direction and one went in the other
direction and they were like back to
back to one another
in every direction
we flew right into that
and I the the okay I want to ask
logically because like in my dream the
airplane immediately filled up with
water I wonder like
normally like there's in the scenario
that there's no tsunami and the airplane
lands on the water it floats above water
right because I see those those videos
not those videos but the security
instructions where you like jump out of
the airplane
but if it if it
it's so heavy though
it's an airplane is heavy how
can it float above water explain to me
it would break up first oh my God and
what what if it flies into a into a
tsunami will it be drowned will the
water go immediately in the in the
airplane
because isn't it closed off pretty well
[Music]
depends on the impact it will break
apart
it will be crushed
oh my God an airplane would be instantly
destroyed really they look so bulky they
look so strong
[Music]
it's aluminum only
so fake though
so thick
eating water is like hitting a wall
mmm
um
[Music]
not strong enough to handle the impact
of a crash
[Music]
but if it's an emergency landing on
water different situation then like in
the in the manuals in the security
manuals it shows you like to just you
know
and take the take the
um
what do we call that
if it if it if it doesn't right it can
be safe okay okay so they could they
could land softly gently on the water I
see I see
how to hold on now
okay I just wanted to know the
tacticality
the technical like what would happen
but I'm generally not scared of flying
planes I've I've been on so many
airplanes a lot of long distance ones
between Europe and Japan so many times
and I'm actually not not scared at all
like I never worry about it
I'm a bit more scared of being on a
highway in the car than I am in an
airplane
the end and it makes sense because so
much more can happen on the highway then
it can or like in the city wherever in a
car so much more can happen in the
airplane
[Music]
cars are way more dangerous yeah because
like there's so much more that could
happen like because it's not only about
you
it's about how other people drive their
cars and in an airplane you don't have
that much traffic around you normally
you don't have any traffic around you
is controlled about that
is yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
roller coasters oh no no roller coasters
are not safe to me I don't like roller
coasters scare me especially if
they do a loop I hate I hate Loops don't
don't don't no no no no no no world
closest is the most scary thing
ah
I'm usually not scared of things but
that's that thing that scares me
[Music]
oh man
um
on my vacation
with my BFF
um you know we were in that spa and the
spa actually had a
um
what do you call a slide a pretty long
slide
70 meter slide that's pretty long right
pretty exciting I was so surprised they
had a proper huge ass slide indoor slide
70 meter long slide
yeah
pretty damn cool so we were we were like
when we saw it we were like oh God we
gotta use this but at the moment we
first saw it it was closed so we were
like okay maintenance maybe it'll be
throughout the whole week but no
actually on the same day it already got
fixed again and on the last day we did
use the slide and
I made my I made my BFF go first
and it's been such a long time since I
last was on a slide it's honestly been
years
so I was actually pretty scared
I was pretty scared I it took me like
she first uh took the slide and I was
waiting at the bottom
uh she was my test subject and then I
was like yo how was it and she was like
it was so much fun
she was so excited she was so hyped up
and she was like I want to go again I
want to go again and I was like
I said I guess I'll go too so we went
all the way up again
and then at the top I let her go again
first because I was too scared I needed
some time to
get my together
[Music]
and then she was gone and there was a
there was a traffic light
and it already was green but I couldn't
go yet I was too nervous I was too
scared
I was waiting like a whole minute up
there alone and I was like I was looking
over the over the
um over the fence I was looking down to
see if she was down there I was I was
yelling friend friend
friend
but she couldn't hear me I didn't hear
any reply
I was this guy that was about to go back
down
I was so scared
I don't know why like when I was younger
going on slides like that was so much
fun I was never scared but for some
reason because it's been such a long
time I was so scared guys
foreign
[Music]
I wanted to not be too fast
so I was like half sitting up and half
lying down and like
um one of the staff actually told me
that uh since it's like mostly built for
children you're not like as an adult she
has heard of incidents that when adults
use this slide that they bonked their
heads uh pretty roughly against the
walls of the slide inside because there
were some pretty uh
huge curd like small curves actually you
know it was like
and they would burn out their head so I
was really scared because of what she
told me as well I didn't want to be too
fast and I didn't want to Bunk my head
so but if you if you lay down then
you're faster right but then there's
less chance that you Bonk your head
but I didn't want to go too fast because
that was scary too it actually ended up
being pretty damn fast
happened to me can confirm uh it was
pretty pretty um narrow the slide so I
was scared
anyway I finally slid down and um I
started out lying on my back completely
but then I after after like a few meters
I felt like okay it could be fine I
think I'm gonna sit up a little bit more
so that I can see where I'm going
mostly because I needed to see where I
was going
and I made it I made it safely but my
friend did it in like 11 seconds there
was like a timer at the bottom and I did
it in like uh 15 seconds I successfully
stopped myself to be a bit slower
[Music]
I successfully did it and then after I
was done
with the first ride
my friend still wanted to go up again
and I was kind of like
confused
I was like still scared and still
panicking but at the same time the
adrenaline and the fun kind of made me
want to go again so I was going up again
while being like hey
and throughout the whole ride the first
time and the other times I was riding it
I was constantly like
screaming
and the screens were echoing through the
tube
way too dramatic it's just like
15 seconds in a 70 meter slide
it's really not a big deal
but I went a few more times
it was fun it was fun I'm glad I went in
the end but uh I don't know why I'm such
a chicken
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
at least we did it I'm glad we did it
I'm glad I was there with my friend and
actually we were not the only adults
using that slide
there were a bunch of other adults using
it too
when when we were using it at other
times I saw children using it but our
when we were doing it it was only adults
it was fun I didn't feel so stupid
anymore
adults playing with
children's slides yeah I can't get my
fear
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
did I read the Seth Place Pinky
I lost track
um
did I read Seth Place pinky oh oh no
yondake
probably not yeah definitely
thank you and I hope you now I feel like
I read it I read this I read
I hope you enjoyed your vacation thank
you again I think I did read this
thank you sense of place Pablo Danielson
Azure 6040
thank you for the red super chat
welcome back thank you
thank you I'm glad you waited for me
thank you for waiting for me I
appreciate it
thank you for the warm welcome back
spooky miffing that Edition are you
spooky now
Prophet Duncan black foreign
reporting maybe I'm just deeper in this
Rabbit Hole than I knew about your mini
vacation felt so much longer than anyone
before it
how a smoothie and chunk is doing now
that you're home
they're doing fine during my trip I got
the I got the dude to uh do a video call
with us every day to check on my cats
yeah and they they seemed okay but
um it was interesting to hear how like
for example smoothie's habits of
meowing a lot in the morning once I wake
up to get food
um was not there on the first night
like when uh my BFF's boyfriend woke up
uh
in the first night and the first morning
she didn't bother him because she was
probably like yo this dude probably
doesn't know our tradition
so I'm not gonna bother him he did give
her food though anyway in the early
morning
so then on the next morning apparently
she did yell at him
because then the next morning she was
like okay he gets it he gets it I'm
gonna get my food from him
his first just being careful because she
thought maybe maybe he doesn't know but
he knew I told him don't worry smoothie
I'm thinking about you I know you get
cranky
if you don't get that food also I'm
getting really
um sick right now I need I need more
food I think and I need another nap oh
dear
yum yum yum
yeah it's movie be like what a smart
human
he's usable I can make good use of him
I didn't eat cereal
before the stream but now I'm feeling
sick
I still have half of the cake that I was
eating yesterday
[Music]
right here
hope it's not all dried out
I think it's fine
[Music]
um
well
it's a little bit dried out
[Music]
yes it was on my desk so what laughs
I wrapped it back together
so that it wouldn't dry out completely
[Music]
no there is no Nutella on my desk right
now no
I don't even eat Nutella that often
anymore I do I don't eat it like every
once in a while especially with pancakes
and stuff
but not so much on on bread anymore
I used to eat a bread uh like two pieces
of toast with Nutella on it pretty much
every day
every day I don't do that anymore
[Music]
but I do still love chocolate croissants
um
[Music]
you might like it
back in Japan oh well in Japan it's like
I felt like I didn't have much
um like of my usual choices for
breakfast
because like here we do
um what we often eat is for a Savory
breakfast
is like a proper piece of bread
and not just a toast bread a proper
piece of bread
and we've like cut up like sausages and
stuff wished
um like salami and all that
that's also a typical breakfast I often
eat here now when I'm not for something
sweet when I want something Savory but
in Japan
it's pretty damn hard to get that like
what I do find is like cut up
um salami for like like Italian Imports
salami
[Music]
um
but not so much of the of the other
stuff like extra blushed or a
schwarzwelder
we have so much
and uh
yeah so because I barely had like any of
the usual choices for breakfast and I
don't like the
uh most of the traditional Japanese
breakfast that much like I like the the
tamago
uh the the egg egg rolls I like those
but like other stuff I don't like so
much
um so I had to like rely most of the
time on either scrambled eggs or just
toast bread
milky toast bread with Nutella and stuff
like that or Jam or whatever
or nah I didn't like the cereal in Japan
that much they they I hate it sometimes
because it's good it's good it's good
but they they only seem to have like one
type of cereal over there
granola granola granola
they don't really like they have normal
they have normal ass Corn Flakes or they
have those granolas
uh
but like here we have so much more
choices for your cereals in in Europe
and I've I'm assuming in North America
as well
no Cinnamon Toast Crunch uh I don't
think they had that yeah no
foreign
flakes or granola yeah
[Music]
I do love miso soup but for me miso soup
is not necessarily something I would eat
for breakfast I would but but in Japan
they eat miso soup all the time they eat
it for breakfast and they eat it for
like dinner before the actual main food
yeah I do like it there but for
breakfast I don't know it doesn't seem
very breakfasty to me
I feel like Japanese breakfast could
easily be eaten
like the traditional one could easily be
eaten as a dinner
no
I said
yeah
[Music]
the cut up a piece of
um fish
yeah
um
[Music]
whenever when I'm in Japan I miss
Austrian food and when I'm in Austria I
miss a Japanese food
[Music]
oh man maybe maybe today I should get
Japanese oh you know what I want to do
that I want to do that
foreign
I don't think I will though cause I'm a
lazy ass
I'm a lazy ass
that's what I am
[Music]
I don't feel like saying Australia today
I feel like I'm confusing so many people
the newbies I'm confusing the newbies
okay I gotta read the super chats
Helen love luck thank you
thank you for the pinky yeah I found an
interesting bird that I thought you
might like to know about it's called the
Watson and it legitimately looks like a
phoenix
[Music]
I'm looking that up right now
oh wow that's an interesting bird
names are insulting that doesn't really
I mean I don't know I guess it was like
fantasy it looks like
but in in German one of their names is
stink bird are you kidding me
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
I like the top part with the feathers
that like stand up it looks funny
[Music]
that's a weird Bird Man
let me read about it
the Watson
sounds like a
ustrian uh dialect word also known as
the reptile bird skunk bird or stink
bird oh there you go and English is also
called that sometimes
it's a species of tropical bird found in
swamps Shrek riparian forests and
mangroves of the Amazon
Prime and the Orinoco basins of in South
America it is notable for having chicks
that have claws on two of their wing
digits it is the only member of the uh
Gina's office
long hair behind referring to its large
Crest this is the only extent genus in
the family extent what does that mean
extinct no extent
blah blah blah
[Music]
cool bird
oh it's a Folly boy
specializes in eating leaves
and
we go
[Music]
I told you I don't eat chicken
I don't eat I don't need that no
yesterday no that was that was a vegan
crispy chicken totally
yeah
thank you for that info
thank you for the red super chat
welcome back to angel thank you
oh
welcome back to YouTube I guess
because I haven't seen you in a while
either while I was gone obviously
[Music]
thank you for being there when I came
back no I did not get an Oreo shake I
got iced tea with it
um
thank you the red super chat
yeah I didn't miss you a lot but I also
seem I've not I have not much memories
of the past three days something is
wrong anyways the video is so funny and
hope you had a great vacation more rest
sometime I love you Mama thanks
I'm glad you enjoyed the little videos
that I put up I didn't want to leave you
guys without nothing
but honestly it was just to keep the
algorithm alive I'm too scared of it I
don't want it to forget about me
yeah
but at least it was like mostly videos
that
um I could pretty much just upload
upload the way they were so that was
very helpful yeah please guys make more
videos like that
now
thank you Papa
what's that thank you I miss you thank
you welcome home thank you
I'm home
I was happy to be here back home
I like I like the vacation and I was
happy to be there but I'm also happy to
be here because I got my cats and I got
my chickens what else do I want huh
that's all I need Kiara field broke me
okay yeah I feel
it's so shitty my voiceover is so shitty
but I really only did one take
[Laughter]
[Music]
ugh
maybe I should have done a few more
texts but I didn't know what
I know what's better
[Music]
you wouldn't change it okay
delivery was legendary okay
the scuff was amazing okay okay okay
don't downplay yourself okay okay
[Music]
it's perfect awareness okay okay you
captured its Essence oh yeah that was
important to me thank you
Kylie wow big kiss to you GT thank you
for the pinky welcome back Kiana we
missed you but we were glad you had your
vacation thank you you guys are so
kind-hearted thank you soon
yeah
I was also very glad to take my vacation
I want another one though I want another
one
have you seen the original of course
I've seen the original I wouldn't I
needed something to go off of
of course I see I saw the original I've
seen it been there done that
[Music]
foreign
Poland thank you
[Music]
Avenged me direction
meme dude thank you for the pinky after
the vacation I am a well-rested chicken
now nice
I'm glad I'm glad you guys got some rest
as well very important I don't want my
chickens to overwork themselves
otherwise their meat won't be very good
yeah we need you guys to be healthy and
happy
best chicken
happy you didn't have a vacation that
didn't end in an injury well but I was
pretty exhausted on the last day
because of the workout
yeah
backpack
oh wait why are you guys looking scared
I said I want you to be happy
what
[Music]
where are the happy faces
where are the happy book books
[Music]
haha I'm in danger
oh thank you thank you for the orange
Super Chat
where are the happy faces oh yeah that's
that's the inner one is a good one
you know what is like
kind of conveys the right feeling here
[Music]
thank you Liz Taylor thank you for the
reason for chat hope you had a good
vacation and you are BK on my birthday
nice what you are Burger King on my
birthday nice
you are BK what does that mean
when it was your birthday at your back
oh you're back on my birthday
it's not like you didn't have more space
in that red Super Chat to write out the
word back
you had to write BK
to confuse the hell out of me
[Music]
always thinking of Burger King
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday Liz Taylor happy
birthday to you
thank you
for watching me on your birthday
[Music]
pinky welcome back to Kento I miss you
so much I hope you had a great time on
the vacation I love you I love you too
thank you I'm glad to be back
thank you for missing me I missed you
too
[Music]
welcome back thank you arigato
Maxwell the first super nice sorcerer
dankish inspector from Baron Duncan
Blitz blank while you were gone oh
definitely not no cult rituals in the
usual room I'm so glad you got to relax
yo is Blitz blank a word you use in
English as well
[Music]
because we do use that in German and I
think isn't it originally German because
Blitz is a thunder
[Music]
no it is not
first time I heard oh maybe he used it
on purpose to impress me with a German
word
okay looks like it because you guys
don't know it
um
thank you Jesus
is that Crayola Ramos thank you for the
red super chat could hear it you talk
for hours you're such a great
Storyteller and make everything so
interesting oh glad you enjoyed the trip
despite the rough start love utensil
thank you love
you love her yeah we had a rough start
and it kind of made me already worry
about the vacation because it was like
yo is this gonna be a grease 2.0
but thankfully after that it went all
good everything was wonderful
after that
yeah
vacation curse yeah I think I do
I mean even in the Hokkaido trip
the thing with the bus
us not being able to find the the the
the the
transfer bus from the hotel the shuttle
bus and me
um almost dying while skiing
[Music]
they were two big incidents on that trip
as well
foreign
crashed yeah
oh my God I could have broken something
in that ski crash that was bad
[Music]
yeah so all like the three the free
vacations that I had in this year all of
them had had something go wrong but this
most recent one had the least things
going wrong
[Music]
oh man you sure you want to go seeing
and yes I want to go again
I actually messaged rmt about it I was
like yo are we gonna go skiing in Winter
or not or what
because she goes like skiing in Winter a
million times
she knows the good places and all that
and I think if we go somewhere here with
like fresh snow
soft snow then I will do a much better
job
and I want to buy my own equipment
though
because up until now I was always
renting it whenever I went skiing which
was now two times in my whole life
foreign
I want to buy my own stuff my ski
because she has them too and I think
that's so cool to have your own skiers
[Music]
gamer pink skis
get custom ones
that would be cool with my face no I
can't I can't do that I can't put my
face on my skis
that would be a little bit dark fish
ing
but I could put something else on there
I could just I don't know
put uh
pick what I said by his face on there
put it on rnt skis and put my face on
her skis
how about some Flames oh yeah I'm sure I
don't even need a custom one I'm sure
that it's already edgy
snowboards at least there's definitely
edgy snowboards like that why are
snowboards so much fancier and edgier
than skiers tell me why why is there so
much more cool stuff because maybe
because there's so much more space to
put something on it
or the myth logo
oh
[Music]
more real estate yeah I guess so
Raynard thank you
talks are 95 thank you for the red super
chat thank you hi Kiara things were hard
for me during the past years but I want
to give a big thanks to Holo Yen for
getting my motivation to translate again
oh you're a translator I've been
practicing my skills with holonyan
streams now I got a job at a big
Corporation thank you Ian for the
motivation yo congratulations that
sounds so cool
I I um I respect that because I don't do
it as a job I just do it for hollow talk
and
um I know how stressful it is and it
definitely needs some skills definitely
so I respect that good job I'm glad I'm
happy for you
thank you for watching my streams
mwah
help you do well in that company
Skye thank you for the pinky glad that
you enjoy your vacation welcome back
yada thank you thank you I'm back thank
you Skye for waiting for me
I'm glad you enjoyed your vacation it's
always a pleasure to watch your streams
thank you
thank you soon I'm glad you enjoy my
streams I'll do more and more every day
for you
so please continue watching and
supporting me in the future
and thanks for waiting for me
indeed
[Music]
Jackson FB thank you soon thank you for
the pinky
[Music]
welcome back thank you I'm glad you've
got some well-deserved RNR rest and
relax is that what that stands for
thank you Jackson you're so sweet
you're always there
I appreciate it thank you
you sweetheart
that is
726 Packaging
thank you I will never lose passion for
you Kiana you're one of my favorite
YouTubers out there love your energy
thank you I'm happy to hear that
question
small Navi thank you for the red super
chat no you no you no you
[Music]
know
super snake Mario dinosaur and thank you
for waiting for me Unit 14 e Danke
Schoen
I had a friend with a weird strained
back and daily stretching and yoga
helped bring her from strange Hunchback
to a regular person sometimes in pain oh
10 to 15 minutes stretching can do a lot
though professional helped it more for
her some of them are interesting thank
you
black foreign
for the pinky
and glad to hear your vacation went well
with how hard you always work you bloody
deserve a good time have my Oshi having
my Oshi come back refreshed healthy
happy and uninjured this time it is a
pretty sweet birthday gift so thanks for
that and welcome back plus your birthday
ah Happy Valley
oh
happy birthday oh wait that's a pinky
but I'll give you a birthday kiss anyway
are you ready are you ready are you
ready
[Music]
happy belated birthday
yeah
so many birthdays
so exciting
when's my birthday
still a long time to go
[Music]
down
you guys remember my birthday
yeah sixth July
don't forget
put it in your calendar for next year
[Music]
foreign
collaboration which is very fitting
because we just watched the vatama this
was basically a lot of collaboration as
well
[Music]
and I'm that might be the last ones I
read I don't know recently I'm really
bad with catching up I'm sorry
and they keep up coming and keep on
coming and coming and they don't stop
coming and they don't stop coming and
they don't stop coming and they don't
stop coming
[Music]
hmm
what's my stream to um tomorrow's my day
off right
what's what's happening
um first day let me see
uh
Week calendar a Minecraft with ninity
and tales of illuminaria
okay that's gonna be uh
um difficult because the narrative is a
collab and luminaria is a sponsor
yeah
I'll see I think I can probably read
some super chats after them and then in
Minecraft because
for people who want to watch the archive
immediately they can just watch her
stream then
[Music]
okay okay
yeah I need to rest for TTI with G oh my
God though I need a I need a um map
okay
[Music]
thank you
that is
[Music]
make sure to reply to all those Discord
messages of course I always do but often
I get pinged for things that I don't
even need to reply as well so hopefully
it's a lot of that
Amber Burbank tanks and Herbert West
tankus and Kate
thank you
David skilled shoes
[Music]
thanks mate
our room flew in Duncan swd hit
[Music]
foreign
Russian name
[Music]
you're a good cough Dance Mr fujisama a
fujisawa Duncan Jackson FB thank you for
the pinky thank you for taking Vengeance
for us thank you I don't even remember
what was that could I did I kill someone
ah
you mean Sana
for killing chickens
I yes
oops you're welcome
but you know in some way
um like I kind of
um like chased her down and and like
teased her because I wanted to like
include her
um in the collab
um I didn't want her to just run around
and be ignored I wanted to involve her
that's that's my way of involving her as
a senpai
shut up shut up I was trying to like you
know have fun with her and she's not the
type of person who gets mad at something
like that I know that I know I can read
people
I can read people's personalities and
how they would react to certain things
not everyone is as sensitive as the
internet
[Music]
not everyone gets triggered
by me saying
[Music]
I ate some chicken
not not really talking about you guys in
the chat you guys are cool mostly
[Music]
what
what happened that was just an example I
didn't eat chicken never never I just
munch on you guys sometimes
taste testing that's what you call that
in professional language
[Music]
I think that's it actually yeah
hmm
Hills over rice and we were here
together Minecraft shall I just quickly
read that we were here together once
because those are done quickly
[Music]
I'm gonna quickly read those
I can do those quickly
okay
[Music]
okay gotta catch up a little bit right
thank you for the pinky pink pinky are
they of amitoni and on my birthday oh
a great surprise to see hope today
streams are lots of fun it was thanks to
you too that I fell into the rabbit hole
and got into whole life oh you guys are
the best keeping awesome thank you first
of all happy belated birthday oh my God
yay
thank you for watching us on your
birthday and I'm really always very very
excited to hear when people say that
they fell into the rabbit hole because
of me or because of me and someone else
yeah
and that makes me feel very proud
thank you I'm glad you fell into it
I appreciate it thank you for your
support
[Music]
Squad Biggs
Roman Roman Squad Biggs
thank you are you okay
Romans God beings
ah you spelled it out one letter of her
Super Chat
foreign
[Music]
thank you for having the heart of gold
and a potty mouth foreign
[Music]
you girls are amazing thank you
makes me so happy recently she's so
sweet
I love her
foreign
[Music]
yeah I'm glad that we're getting both
more comfortable with one another it
took us quite some time
took us a long time not because like you
know we don't like each other but just
and I I don't know we just didn't have
that much reason and opportunity to
you know do stuff together that much she
did a lot of collaborations with Gouda
back in the day
um
and now now she's like being more open
to collab with others like she also did
did it already happen
or is that about to happen
[Music]
oh probably when I was sleeping
ah okay
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah it wasn't us deciding that yeah
yeah I'm glad they put me with Amazon I
mean anyone would have been fine I would
have been happy with anyone
nice work stuff nice work
that way I could make the whole day
about amitory
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
yes
see that was fast
so we have Tales of arise and Minecraft
left but I'm not reading those now I'm
gonna read Tales of our eyes
oh and the ones from today
um hopefully maybe after the net collab
hope you guys enjoyed the concert
and I'll be taking my leaf
and I'll see you later at the ttrpg
probably as good as Channel
yeah okay I'll go take a nap then yeah
and in Germany
thank you
[Music]
psycho
wait did I say I hope it doesn't I think
I did
did I
[Music]
did okay okay
you're a brain about the brainer
see you later you guys should sleep too
[Music]