a
[Music]
he
n
[Music]
crazy welcome to the Stream
mcraft
[Music]
hardcore should we just get in I wonder
what kind of raid wait I want to see now
now now I'm curious
[Music]
huh in game what oh my
god oh what is
that why is there so many
Sakura
[Music]
Saka what happened here so many things
happened
oh where wow that a lot of
[Music]
people Minecraft
K's house o K's in by's house she
already has so many things I'm so proud
of
[Music]
her wait why is my voice mod not
on wait just a moment people
[Music]
my voice mod is not
on
[Music]
wait
for I think I need to restart my
Minecraft real
[Music]
quick so
you sound normal what's the issue no no
it's not like my voice in stream it's my
voice in
[Music]
game the voice mod wasn't on yeah the
iname voice
mod voice
huh in the
proximity check your menu if there's a
mod menu then it should be
fine
oh okay okay okay okay put in
[Music]
ey
okay okay it should be good
please don't tell me that I won't be
using
shaders
okay
okay here we go there we go now it's all
[Music]
good
okay is the raid still going is it done
is it
finished wait I need put my stuffs back
first and by the way guys look I built
this bridge off
[Music]
stream let's put STS
here I need more place to put
stuffs I think I need
those I don't need this I'll take this
just in case don't need this I'll put
this here I'll put these here you know
what I'll just take
this I don't know if I need that but
that's okay I'll just hold on to it
I don't have
my J I took the armor I'm so
[Music]
[Applause]
happy I'm so glad I I I was I was
worried that the message wouldn't get
across her I'm glad that she it was her
right it was K's invite right K's in
ah we need
torches let's go to buas
Senpai oh yeah we need to up our gears
Also let's upgrade our gear a little
bit uh I bet everybody already has
diamond armor I don't know if I
can first of all we need need this wait
hm what should we get or should we just
Farm
first what tra
Trader in ky's
[Music]
house is it in Kyla's
house okay
then we can just do tradings in Kayla's
house
then a
[Music]
pink I didn't know this was garison by
house I'll need to renovate it later for
her
[Music]
I don't think I'll make it in time for
like the raid oh wait I'm here
[Music]
I don't think I should
intrude I'll leave them to
[Music]
it he it
it was that
close introvert Ali there's just way too
many people
[Music]
I'm not worthy of standing beside
them not when my armor is still iron
[Music]
armor can this boat get any faster
up
yep
hi
okay efficiency
31 sticks equals one Emerald four iron
equals one
Emerald oh
hello should I kill you are you okay to
kill I don't think I should kill you
let's get some iron
then e
[Music]
there's an iron farm
right Oho of the village good job
guys I can't really join anyways
F I think the iron farm should be around
here right
[Music]
didn't even have to do
anything my character seems very happy I
keep
jumping knock it
off level up arm
[Music]
okay I'm looking for
money maybe I should get some wood too
while I'm at it huh I have Sakura
[Music]
blocks that would equal to a few money
right if only we had more
sticks m
yeah I think it's best if we just buy an
armor and then after that I can just
make equipments with my own
diamonds or did I park my
[Music]
boat for
Sho
Sho okay
[Music]
for
iron
[Music]
M okay
you what do you
sell oh a paper loot thing thorns
sugar I believe there was sugar cane but
I don't
remember take free oh yeah the silk
touch silk touch thank
you take
free Ming Unbreaking Unbreaking some
mending thank
[Music]
you feather falling
so we have 28
emeralds
Unfortunately they do not sell armor so
I think we have to make our
own Unbreaking du
efficiency D sorry sorry
sorry bully
pickaxe
pickax I'll take a
pickaxe why not uh how do you do this
again all right you need you need this
[Music]
all's
pick
okay with The Mending Unbreaking silk
touch
[Music]
he fortun fortun
so that if we ever made a what's it
called ohing of Fortune they don't have
Fortune unfortunately
you punch Fortune yeah 28 I don't have
28 I have four
[Music]
no one sells armor or is it not here
I see
did you just put bed in water wait did
I did I
[Music]
actually
huh oh yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
a I guess he could say we could get wet
dreams
but I'm
sorry
[Music]
nice literally literally
it's been so long since I last saw this
many members in the server when it's not
like a sports
festival or like an event
[Music]
shal
be there's there's canes there's canes
may maybe we can stop dumping me
[Music]
only get one Emerald from
that Iron
Golem Farm cobblestone
[Music]
let me get the emeralds I left behind I
I I didn't think I would use them
anymore so I
[Music]
life
Indonesia why
[Music]
talkinging
lyy lyyy
lyyy lyyy
lyyy l l l ly
[Music]
okay iron farm yeah is that the other
iron
farm is this
it h this is it
ooh
[Music]
okay take all
no it's okay I think we have
[Music]
enough I for
doee
[Music]
I heard that they prepared the iron
boots for us so we should really
[Music]
gold one
golden we've been going you know back
and forth back and forth back and forth
[Music]
simulator
for
[Music]
S to to to
is it really okay for me to take what if
she's saving for like other
[Music]
Senpai oh
sorry K is not here house is the boat
not
[Music]
I remember her showing her that she
found a a farm what those spawn stuffs
like there's a spider farm and a another
one I forgot what it
[Music]
was oh there the one over
here the mefic
[Music]
can
[Laughter]
[Music]
go I'm Emerald with infinity bully
take
all take
all I'm not Kara I'm KY I'm not KY I'm
K I'm your demon be my
[Music]
guest Lego for
buly bully
[Music]
MO
an
[Music]
spee
for
um trying to read something that I
cannot
read
uhhuh
nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
for sorry sorry
uh audio
output
Minecraft Minecraft
[Music]
voice
hello I remember I remember
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
MAA MAA if you go to my locker um you
can find some iron armors and stuff you
can take it oh okay wait my locker is
how how how to setting the fe uh the ah
v v v yeah yeah yeah yeah okay I'm I'm
going I have to go thank you okay
[Music]
this
spe
[Music]
so many di in here am I am I allowed to
take
that oh this is for people who
discovered the piglin I
[Music]
think so um what should I do
first come with me come with
me I S like there's a diary or something
oh
okay okay
[Music]
Emerald yeah
oh
armor oh
[Music]
not now Ma Senpai is J you know
J efficiency
[Music]
for
M my
[Music]
wake up
uh by
would um
[Music]
diamond
wait is there a rule about
Diamond rules what
[Music]
rules I'm doing great I'm a little sick
though a little sick
so so
[Music]
so go to the
main seven diamonds thank you thank you
seven diamonds yeah yeah but in the main
server not this server so in the main
Holo Holo life
server oh okay that's cheap okay
yeah so if you die once you just go to
the main hall and give seven
diam I don't know
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey yo I mean I mean she'll tell you if
that
happens
[Music]
so wait I have
I have no idea seven diamonds or diamond
[Music]
blocks I have 12 I could get armor
myself I can make them
myself question is should
I I do why not I do think I do I I need
another diamond
sword other than that else
unbreakable why
not oh hi
hi no it's okay it's okay I don't want
to bother
[Music]
you um I'm going to go to another after
this oh good luck oh
[Music]
unable okay
he be Beam Beam
[Music]
Beam
okay get
[Music]
okay we have to help each other
oh
[Music]
P Unbreaking okay thank
you
okay than free p
[Music]
efficiency
Unbreaking
efficiency we can
[Music]
take okay
okay let's go
okay up up up
[Music]
mcraft
step
is I'll take them
diamondemerald
huh diamondd
[Music]
okay uh
Emerald yeah
[Music]
thank you for the
gift yay I hope you stay all healthy Ali
thank you
[Music]
miti ding me
no Quest today bring with a skeleton hat
ooh First Hat 100 diamond per head 100
diamond per hat okay
with wither yeah
with okay
[Music]
protection I want
to I want to buy
oh yeah
sword
sword I'm
breaking okay I was the base I have the
base and base
[Music]
Moen oh
this is is is
[Music]
is okay
for
[Music]
diamond
armor
so paper
[Music]
what
Emerald oh
[Music]
yeah leave game
sorry efficiency for efficiency I'm
working oh
what are you waiting
[Music]
oh okay
okay hot tourist ooh hot tourist wow
[Music]
boots
boots oh yeah
[Music]
fore
yeah need
[Music]
H
sugar B
SU
[Music]
a he
I'm bued to
[Music]
so
expensive I need I need bed and and food
where can I get food okay okay follow me
follow me
[Music]
okay
yes oh there is it so
many we need to cook it need to cook it
[Music]
okay nice
me so
many free torch yes thank you free b i
I'll I'll take I'll take
two take the bed I'll one free
Farm take fre
Gohan goh
[Music]
sweet oh okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay okay okay okay uh okay okay okay
okay
you can take this one
[Music]
right all right
what oh b
[Music]
b more
infinity
infinity let's
goal
Arrow I can let's go come on
aini
Kyla Kyla Mart Kyla
Mar good yes
Kart Unbreaking Unbreaking okay diamond
sword need Unbreaking to balls do Bow
need Unbreaking wait do Bow have
Unbreaking do we need Unbreaking for bow
I'm not
sure
yeah don't really you know
[Music]
K it is square K Square
K Minecraft Square infinity infinity
[Music]
K
Infinity
infity we are going to
Kyla's place to get St so see you
[Music]
soon
hi
sorry is that head cups
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's let's let's make paper
[Music]
s touch B just
something just
[Music]
something enchanting book
protection let's see
everything let's see
everything
wow for
[Music]
infinity infinity
diam
[Music]
infinity oh yeah
gring
Diamond di Emerald Emerald Emerald
[Music]
emeraldo
emal
foras yeah
[Music]
stick
yeah wait wait wait how can I forgot how
how can I forgot
[Music]
K yeah say
money okay
I also need like tree
[Music]
minging family
uh
peanut yeah
b b
[Music]
b so Wonder
X hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi B
[Music]
oh what
be ATI
[Music]
okay
gires yes
[Music]
okay oh thank
you gir are you gir going to go to
arrows yes we're preparing for it
right
[Music]
now one
Arrow one
Arrow do you
happen
some on you gold
[Music]
how
much maybe
eight
P just all
[Music]
for two pairs of shoes
one two three four five
[Music]
oh
oh mind that
10 oh yeah it's definitely less
[Music]
okay
stick f
[Music]
okay
nice
up I'm ready okay
[Music]
oh yes sh chill chill
chill bye Fire Protection
[Music]
okay let's go
okay farmi
they got it they got
it
what let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go but what witer
witer the
head the the last one huh the last one
[Music]
liit
a
a Miss l
[Music]
an
debris what
are there so many hat I have no idea
[Music]
a nice Fire Res 10 Ollie fire resistant
free
oh eight
minutes where are you going I'm still
looking for my gold I I I I made a mine
somewhere and I think I left some gold
there oh no it's okay we we got gold
really okay um hi MAA I think sorry for
the long wait oh no worries it's okay
I'm not really waiting I just started
anyway but uh so they just found the
Wither head which was the biggest
mission for today but I think MAA it's
your first day right is it yeah so it's
my first day we can do all the other
missions in the never for you and I
wonder because I most of these missions
are the same as yesterday I wonder if I
do them again if I still get the
diamonds
probably probably yeah yeah and you CH
saying that there's a basan quest oh
Bastion is
hard really was it
Bastion want to check the missions
together
actually yeah okay we can go to go
gold oh don't worry we have gold both of
you weren't there yesterday so we can do
all those missions and hopefully I'll
also get a reward again second time
yi yay I was it here
no and oh oh this ah one guess okay
that's that's pretty easy that's pretty
easy wait how do we get how how do we
get
sand yeah Soul Sand easy like I got all
of these like yesterday the only new
ones is this getting the Wither hat uh
but this is over now because it was only
for the first three people who found it
mhm and the other new mission is this
one that's not translated it says we
have to get uh what's it called again uh
you know in the never that really rare
material to build never for never right
yeah ancient debris
so if we can find free ancient debris
together uh then we all all of us I
think will get each 20 diamonds 20 20
why is it so cheap ancient debris yeah
ancient debris is pretty difficult cuz
we need bombs
probably
yeah wait we just need one ancient
debris one for each of us person yeah if
if we want 20 diamonds per person then
we need one ancient debris per person h
oh I see maybe we can do it without uh
do you think Kyla is going to join us
she said she'll be here at uh around two
yeah so like four more hours she'll be
online four more hours oh you you means
she will be another former hours online
or what yep yeah okay do you think she
wants to go with us she would love
to okay then we get four ancient debris
yeah or you know thing is with joining
she can can give us some bombs yeah we
don't we don't need a bombs we just need
beds easier right
BS oh yeah beds ah right wait okay I
think cuz I did this like a long time
ago and beds in the never for me just
translated to
bombs blow
up okay okay let's do that together and
all the other smaller things
we can do everything except for the
Wither head mhm mhm all right let me
screenshot this real
quick oh there's no W Farm
yet there's no wool Farm but yeah but
there's sheep from P make bed easier
yeah we have we have sheeps from paa
Senpai oh we just have to share them
yeah and we need
c M if you die in hard yeah uh we won't
die I mean it's it's mine you haven't
died
right I haven't yeah not yet first
revive is free is what I heard right
wink wink not get so sad free for
survive you have to go to the solo
server and get seven diamonds ah okay
and then second revive does not happen
normally oh
well I mean we can do this we got this
we can we can see like maybe Kyla you
know Kyla is very very calm in the never
so we just let her explode
everything and we take everything from
her I think she must have she has so
much experience I think with uh finding
ancient debris so we just leave it to
her and we'll stay in the safe backside
that's a good idea okay I'm going to go
get some food and when we're all ready
to go maybe we meet in front of the
portal yeah sure okay all right then all
we need is maybe some bed though I I'll
check at paa Farm yeah I'll go to PCO
senpai's Farm as well okay what do you
want to do MAA
Senpai uh I don't know you want to come
along yeah sure I should put in
here okay
H all right all
[Music]
right we're going to p and p space to
get some food and some
[Music]
beds hi hi people need these beds so I'm
going to
share I took like like 20 beds already
you guys can take the rest maybe oh I'm
going to
[Music]
all right you need
the do any of you guys have
[Music]
axes what kind of ax oh I I want to cut
down some
trees oh here thank you oh I'll just
take the oh oh oh oh I'll just stick the
iron one thank you
[Music]
okay B
cutting
yippee H now I am back in my
environment what are you getting the
wood for to make more
beds okay I have 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 I have seven beds in my
inventory hopefully hopefully that' be
[Music]
enough what do you guys think will it be
enough oh yeah I think MAA took the
other beds out out of the box so we have
a few more than 17 like maybe
[Music]
20 and get rid of what should I get rid
of I'll get rid of this
and here's another one I'll get rid of
um um um um um um um um look get rid of
that I'll clean out my inventory really
quick huh is Kyla
on
[Music]
h Huh
who is SC in by talking
to
oh oh
nice oh thank
[Music]
another graveyard um okay let's organize
stuffs because this is way too
much um we can do
this I think we can just throw this out
I'm sorry Pon
by okay we'll put this right here put
that right
there yeah hi I think I misunderstood
you guys you guys were saying she was
joining in 4 hours not for another 4
hours yeah
okay H maybe we can do all the small
missions before the ancient debris
Mission yeah okay cuz I think we should
wait for Kyla for the ancient debris I
want her to blow up everything oh
okay okay okay okay hold
on like to be honest I don't mind
getting help it's just that I I don't
like relying too
much I mean it's not like I'm good at my
Minecraft anyways but it does get a
little H you know I kind of want
to do it on my
own
M just say it then Al I don't know she
looks so excited to do it with Kyla like
I I don't want to like be like no I
don't want to do it with Kyla you know
what if that demotivates her or like
hurts her
feelings like I don't want a gatekeep or
anything if that's what she wants to do
then I guess
I'll actually I don't think I can play
for 4 hours I have
a I have something early in the morning
tomorrow how do I tell
her but then she'd be
[Music]
disappointed The
Dilemma oh man the range is so small
Ollie oh oh hi who do you not want to go
to the ne what what no
what no no tell me do you not want to
wait for Kyla that's fine no well yeah
well I yeah I don't want to wait for her
because I have something in the morning
and I don't think I can play for another
four hours and I kind of don't like
relying on her a little bit too much
because you know I kind of want to
experience it for my own oh see you
could just say that to me
[Music]
I heard you like like a bracket of what
you were saying on the bridge because
you passed my house I was like a wait
that sounded like she doesn't want to
like she has something to say but she's
not feeling like she could say it
because of because I said something but
you don't really want to wait so long
for Kyla and I was like ohly stop stop
stop sorry so we can go but uh what do
you think do you still want to try the
ancient debris
Gathering I mean we we can try the small
ones and then maybe if we have time we
can just blow stuffs up I think have you
done it before I've done it a few times
on my
own me too but it's a long time ago but
yeah MAA probably did it too I
suppose we can figure it out right we'll
try sorry about that no worries if we
don't find enough I'll just go again
later with Kyla
all right what time is it for
you uh half 5 p.m. oh okay H so I got
time um all right then let's take a few
beds bring them to the Nether and then
go digging yeah or do you think we
should PRI prioritize the small things
first before the ancient debris we can
prioritize the small things first I feel
like um yeah okay but then I'm going to
uh should we bring the beds anyway into
The Nether and just put them in a box
somewhere yeah we could do that
okay yeah I heard
[Music]
something thank you
give
[Applause]
okay still
there I'm full can you hold this for
me yeah for how
long yeah you can hold on as long as you
want all right I think I'm mostly
ready just waiting fora stand
by
MAA are you
ready all right it's her first time do
you want me to pick you
up pick me up mommy I'm
scared all right I don't need saplings
[Music]
oh oh she might still be at uh poas and
by space I'mma go get it okay okay I you
need to go back to to get a
boss oh that was embarrassing I forgot
that your house was that
[Music]
way oh she's oh oh oh oh oh oh
okay see it's not that bad my Oshi is so
[Music]
understanding she's still understanding
but I do feel kind of
bad like I I really don't I I I don't
want to
gatekeeper back seat like yes I am
jealous got to got to tell you the truth
I I am quite jealous but then again I
have no right to be jealous because I'm
actually not that that skilled in
playing Minecraft you know I love how
she's I'm in front of the dire
oh
okay so I do I do realize that's like
not the best thing to say on stream
honestly
I only realized
[Music]
after thisin
[Laughter]
double
[Music]
okay
okay I a few building blocks and I
brought brought a chest so we can put in
all the beds and some fire potions here
one for
you I still I have one already okay now
take it though because I also have two
oh
okay and I brought some torches and
weapon and stuff and food okay okay my
inventory is pretty full have like some
more mining blocks maybe we'll need
more oh I have three three stack of
planks oh PLS maybe PL maybe planks are
a bit too valuable but okay oh we we
could you know uh what's it called we
could turn the planks into like those
half planks what are they called again
oh yeah half half planks yeah half
planks yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh if we need more uh blocks
we can always mine the
never we good we good oh yeah so we can
go I think let's go let's go all right
ma did you do this before with the
ancient debris although we're doing the
other things first but have you ever
done the ancient debris well not on
Hardcore oh
wow she's experienced at least we need
to go to minus 19 kind of thing oh wait
you know that wow by the by the Y's or
by the
[Music]
X's I
st ooh
oh there's another Block in here ooh oh
there's another another bed yeah I took
three more beds out of here but I guess
they belong to someone probably M okay
um where we go wait what is there's
another T in here tit oh well okay so
we
yesterday we just went through one of
the paths randomly to find all the
mushrooms
and the other stuff and the the gas so
we can go anywhere really oh okay so
what was it again the Soul Sand one
gasand kill one gas kill three skeletons
skeleton a potion make a potion we're
going to make a potion how do make yeah
we can do that later outside the
potion okay where are we
going which path do we go yesterday was
it this one was it this
one I need PA find though wait hold on
is this a good path maybe let's take
this path
okay so this we don't want to go to the
uh Fortress because they already took
the head so we don't need the Fortress
mhm don't worry okay let's go okay let's
go y y yay left or
right you choose any anywhere all okay
[Music]
left ooh be
careful be
careful toide
oh H are those divines that we needed to
get um the warp FY is that it no yeah
the yeah the mushroom that's the
mushroom the green mushroom but it's not
here
oh uh we should find stuff like here
there oh I hear some gas yeah wait how H
how would P know that we defeated a gas
oh we just have to like ride it in our
mission she will believe us M what I
actually just run it down oh no nothing
nothing
nothing write it right on the on the
diary right ah here's the
Bastion oh so this is the Bastion but we
don't get points for this anymore Only
Yesterday
unfortunate this place lowkey kind of
scary actually no I take that back it's
highkey very
scary okay
um there's also mush Mushroom in there
the red one are they the ones that we
need to
get oh no no we need the green one no
yeah looks like one I hear you but where
are you where are
you I almost died I see you how did you
almost
die we're just Walking On The Edge to
death wor we only got
in h oh the T continues here I think
over there oh okay oh I hear Gastly can
they the the ones
[Music]
we there should be some green mushrooms
somewhere in this
biome I hear it but I can't see
it yeah I hear it but I can't see
it somewhere somewhere maybe we should
go
further yeah sound like we'll wait did
you write down our
[Music]
coordinates w a path okay uh
yeah I'm going to make a little bit more
you know secure
you're so
cute there's a pig a damn that's a big
[Music]
pig
uh-oh
careful it's dead
[Music]
she's not dead is
she the Miss no
[Music]
right cuz I feel like I saw pck zai
doing it MAA
zai
what you're not dead are you can you
hear me MAA Z bye
I see her she's down
there oh yeah there she
[Music]
is I got need the fire resistance potion
when I didn't need it yesterday what
thing the fungus wait really
where down there just one though I want
to look for there's more big there's
another
one oh yeah where I've already got one
oh there it
is
W okay all right I
forgot okay I ran out of
space
fungi I think there was one more if you
wanted another
one or was I
[Music]
hallucinating let
me hello little
pig oh
Bunch come on come on come on come on oh
wait wait wait we need we need to get
Kara K
Senpai Kara
Senpai Kara oh here be careful did you
get the Kara come on come on come on oh
you found another one yeah lots of it
come on lots of it yes
okay yummy yummy oh my God that's so
much no
nice okay should we take them complete
oh just one per person is time just one
right okay okay nice okay now we got to
look for Soul Sand Soul yeah Soul Sand
and gas and yes
skeletons wait are the skeletons like
the upper skeletons or like the nether
skeletons H just normal skeletons are
fine the white one oh okay okay okay I
guess we going to go back up where is
the best way to get
[Music]
up oh it's so nice being able to walk on
top of
magmas oh God there's a lot of pigs
around I just look I'm burning and I'm
not
[Music]
dying okay scared
scared there is a pig over there
over there
oh I'm Not Afraid come at me Yo Mama So
Pig you're a
pig you're right
here
ha nice
nice another
[Music]
Pig another one
okay oh oh all this path is made by me
Miki and Ana and the rest of our group
by the way we made all of this PA you
guys paved the way yeah we did yo SI we
were so scared the whole
time nice gas skeleton Soul sound oh
that's it on the ancient debris okay
okay okay yeah
let's go let's
[Music]
go yipp I hear gasp loud and
clear
yeah come at me yes chicken chicken
here
chicken oh my god really weird how is
the chicken the only noral animal you
can find in the nether I understand it's
because they are actually evil probably
around there because they're dinosaurs
ooh now where you guys want to go oh
just
continue yeah this way oh did we stop
building here oh no we just oh God is
this I think there's a path that leads
nowhere really need another
path you want the safe one oh yeah this
way
okay I'll make it safer you're so
sweet just for safety for
safety oh I think I saw this in the clip
somebody died here right no uh uh it
could be anywhere really like everything
looks the same but super Senai died on
our trip while we were going through
here
um coming don't worry we got
you we got
you oh God oh
God nice's no one around the corner all
right see oh
God we're
fine hi sorry sorry sorry it's okay
oh look it has
kids ow ow stop it stop it stop
it let me
heal oh God Ollie are you okay I'm
fine nothing a zombie can't handle nice
oh look the
child get the child get the
child must exterminate Pig must
exterminate Pig must exterminate
[Music]
Pig I killed the
child good job
Yi almost
died
y uh uh let's see um we
find Soul Sand yeah soul sand sand right
I mean I mean we can we can do by going
down there like is there a soul sand
down
there randomly on our this I know that
this path eventually will lead to Soul
Sand because we just got all the items
yesterday while making this path So
eventually we'll get there oh is this
the yeah I think so is this where we
came
from
okay
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
yippe wait are we going
home oh no this place looks
different wait I feel like we've been
here before or do I have deja vu
where uh where are we here before did we
go the wrong way no no no no yeah I
think it's
new
Yi oh yeah I don't think we've been here
sound effects now too ol
yeah it's my legacy not this one I got
the same as you oh my god let's go
[Music]
oh my oh no and I got
crickets and Applause
ooh you have a
lot and I got some Chimes and The Rim
Shop when something's
funny
buts I don't have
any that's okay we'll be your sound
board you don't need
one this
where does it where does it go it's de
end does it end here or yeah there
there's another path over here but I
don't know where this leads ah oh this
leads back to the portal actually we
eventually realized we were going in a
circle oh which was quite oh my God
you're right but
oh yeah but I think this way will lead
to another different area a little bit
different in the end it's all connected
but somewhere there are is some Soul
Sand I'm sure oh n
everywhere Soul Sand is everywhere Soul
Sand
everywhere oh are we going we're going
home if we go this way are we yeah
because the Torches are on the
right Circle
this is straight to the Fortress this
path oh God I
need why are there oh never mind let's
get rid of
these we do not need double
torches yeah don't worry about
it oh you're trying to you want to fix
it yeah
you know if this server lasted for a
month I would probably fabuliz this
whole
place give it some spice it's not worth
it yeah not worth it where was this
again this way
right this torch is not good o this one
oh not good at all nope
[Music]
no good no ven uh-uh no sir
nope where we going I see end
[Music]
there come on I think that's a reg sound
is
[Music]
close there it is okay you guys can kill
it oh oh
what get it oop a you missed go get
it oh it went down it went
down it's over there
back come
back want to go down back you can if you
want careful
[Music]
huh huh I can't find
it I I saw it like stocking down
there I think it will come back
hopefully it comes
back ohou she oh it's time for me to
eat but I'm not in the safe place right
now
A
oh coming is this coming
up I feel like it sounds so loud why is
it not in front of us
oh it shot it shot it's somewhere in
range I heard it shooting are are you
sure yeah yeah but it would usually
[Music]
go stays
it's not coming back I see the chicken
piglin
though
oh
missed where is it so it's pretty far
pretty far it's not
rendering yeah come out you coward can
see it
oh oh oh that's not good oh that's not
good
oh oh no oh no MAA look out
[Music]
no
no no uh is p
oh
no oh
no no what do we do we got to pick up
her things but I have one box yeah okay
let's not take the beds let's just take
the important
ones here we can put her stuff in here I
don't know what's hers I I barely had
space in the first place
um l
[Music]
is gone but in theory she can go to the
solo server and do the seven Diamond
thing not it's not the whole life server
it's a solo server where she has nothing
I think M
um get that and
then and then maybe staff can revive
her while p i sleeping still
oh the planks are
hers the boats are hers first St on her
first day
damn
why that's tough
[Music]
buddy we can't we need we need her
yeah let's C it need
her wait where's her other armor a uh
go to solo server and get seven
diamonds maybe St can revive you if they
are
around oh why can I put it down you just
need to post a screen shot of the
diamonds in your inventory in the
Discord but it has
to we're fine we're
fine what why can't I hit it
oh
oh well yeah cuz like I heard Ana
explaining it to Mauna saying that it
has to be the main server but I think
that was
wrongly wrongly uh uh communicated it's
not the main server it's a solo server
where you have
nothing as far as I
know no it's seven normal diamonds
notmal
diamonds he do I need oh I need an arrow
[Music]
World let me add let me check staff is
if anyone
is around oh that is
[Music]
yeah let's see if they'll reply at this
time oh P does in by typing oh pi
[Music]
oh okay
okay okay yeah yeah I don't know if
she's actually going to go to solo
server though is MAA streaming is she
doing it the right way let me check real
quick that's just unfortunate I wish I
could have saved her but it was pack
yeah yeah but she probably did she hit
the pigling by accident when she was
trying to shoot
the gas oh
man that is really bad when you pull the
argro in a Big Field of piglins like
this
oh I I think she has
it yeah but then she probably did it in
the main server if she already has it
right that's not the
challenge but solo server right yeah
like where you have nothing you got to
start from zero
oh on the solo server with start from
zero
block seven
[Music]
diamonds wait wait what
uh okay okay I think maybe now I
explained it
properly yeah okay she's on it and then
p s online so once MAA Sly is done she
can uh yeah oh 30 minutes time by the
way forgot to say that she only has 30
minutes yeah time
limit yeah but others all managed to do
it
so we can for now gather Soul Sand for
her maybe to take some
time okay um but let's save the
coordinates of this
see I I took a screenshot of the
coordinates oh
okay is the gas dead did you kill it no
it's gone I wanted to get it but what
yeah
again ran away it it went off to the
unrendered where did we come from we
came from up
there okay I think there's another path
over there
cookies we're fine we're fine yeah only
two uh people but we're less of a Target
then right wait isn't that Soul sent but
I think there's a better place to get it
oh my God it's just floating
there yeah no there's definitely better
places wait I think h no no no no no
trust me there's better places okay
P again man we've been true so many
times wait wait there was one right here
so
close ah there it oh
no it was somewhere around
here ahuh jarrison B
oh yeah you want to go down there no no
just down
here yeah you want to go there
yeah you want me to get it for you no no
no no I think we'll find a
Bed Oh you mean there oh I looked at the
island oh be careful don't worry we're
fine 1 2 3 4 oh
[Music]
there's a there's a guest there is a
guest there's a there's a
guest then we just need to where is it
where is it it's over
there
oh better up better up better
up I can never get
it come on I'll try to better up oh oh
come on better up better up F better up
better up
better I got it I got it almost
okay come
on oh it's actually a fire o
oh the underworld
cat oh you almost got got
it
oh J be careful is your health
okay you can
heal oh no it's gone no don't
go did you kill
it oh there it flies so
far it's over there
but it's super far
now it's not
yeah come closer you
coward over here at the Dead zombie at
the
zombie oh a closer
one yes
by oh it's aiming for
[Music]
[Laughter]
you it's aiming for all
right jison by run take
cover wa you did it
we killed that one you killed it okay
then I got the hit you got to get the
other gas yeah do do you have any
arrows H I have an eternal bow oh can I
borrow there you go thank you don't die
I
won't wait how do you use it
a how do you use an eternal I'm sorry
you just need one Arrow do do you not
even have one
Arrow there you
go
[Music]
you yeah let's clean this up
um how do we clean this
up there you are come
[Music]
come no no no you're too far over here
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah I did
it sorry I did it oh good job then you
also have the kill uh one thing though
my boots my golden boots are kind of
like about to break uhhuh so um since
MAA isn't here anyway maybe one time we
should leave again oh yeah yeah we
should definitely leave okay let's go
let's regroup with MAA when she's done
with her
Mission uh do you know where we came
from yeah we came from this way
okay uh-huh and we go this way I
think
okay
really really are we going just go back
that way yeah
yeah H orange juice yummy you good C
orange
juice oh yeah uh can I have the bow bag
oh yeah here you
go thank you thank you do you want the
arrow and I just one is enough just give
me one oh
wait oh no wait mistake wait wait one
two three uh here take this thank you Le
you got a few more arrows
now than nothing much appreciate
then we go
here MAA senice dead spawn maybe we
should make a graveyard for Muna
Senpai a tombstone
maybe get back here we got to remember
this place so we can bring MAA back here
yeah wait wait one second one second
Oh Oh I thought there would be one no
run run just run just run just run just
run just run just
run just run just run it's okay just run
you can you can run you can run you can
run you can
run are you okay don't die my no my my
okay I got you I'm I'm going to hit it
I'm going to hit
it it's dead it's dead it's dead it's
dead I'm scared here here here Qui you
can you can take my boots you can take
my boots but what about yours I'm fine I
can I can kill people no we just got to
get back safely yeah let's go why did he
have Arro on me because I opened the
chest yeah it's because of the test oh
I was just checking if MAA had a
golden piece of armor in there that we
would bring back to her so she can enter
the never with that
again did you kill him or where did he
go yeah I killed him oh my God ol ch ch
ch ch
ch she I was just checking the chest
it's our stuff he we were stealing but
it was our
things sensitive little
yeah we're living way more
dangerously Than Yesterday
Today
y maybe that's just the ID style of
living yeah we live in the edge you
know I like
it oh we could get some you know gold
from here yeah easy
[Music]
gold careful though
oh I have silk touch oh that sucks Ah
that's why it's coming out like
that
oh oh don't bury me alive
don't yeah my chat is saying don't dig
down digging down is dangerous you're
diing your own Grand mhm ironically
hello
hello oh no no oh oh
run see fine you can't you you roofless
murderer oh she okay well I guess in a
tunnel we can just kill him yeah
it's not like they'll remember our
faces yeah he and it's not like he will
tell anybody else yeah here in this
tunnel a dead man tells no
[Music]
stories unless he revives like you like
a zombie right how how do you do that
how do you Revival IE a zombie instead
of just dying tell me what's your secret
um it's a it's a I don't know myself
it's a
mystery
H Maybe maybe there were certain things
that Destiny wanted you to still do
because you left things undone maybe
that that that would explain it we found
our way back y yippee see one good thing
so let's remember if we go through this
door we'll find probably the chest again
okay then I'll just put a dirt here to
remind
us then for now we can go back get
another golden item and put the Warped
fungus away yeah wait did you put yours
into the MAA
chest I oh
dear cuz I
was I can get it back yeah yeah can I
board the
boots
ah oh I thought we were leaving once to
get another oh oh okay we can do that
too yeah yeah yeah
okay
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait how
much how much gold do you have I have
here's some gold and here's some gold
one uh yeah okay M these out of these we
just get a gold nugget right
[Music]
Y is
how are
you I'm great how are you you're great
we just lost one of our
[Laughter]
[Music]
nak thank you thank you okay that's 55
gold
uh let's go let's go make uh out of
these gold nuggets a prople gold yeah
ingots
okay good luck
[Music]
come should we go to your house we can
go to my
house my house
until my my house until
I'm always chill
Ollie always
chilling not answering to
[Music]
flirt lunaai is doing
great oh how do you know I'm watching
her stream as we
play okay how many diamonds does she
have none she's looking for a swamp I
think
oh wait my house is that way why for a
swamp because when you go to a swamp and
you see like a certain um
clay then you just go to the east
side uh three blocks and then you dig
straight down and then you should be at
like a diamond place I think what yeah
oh no she's looking for
iron what
[Music]
do I put this here oh yeah I have a lot
of barrels on top too so you can use
that okay but when do you have
coal Coal um have to burn the
Nugget oh oh we can burn the nuggets
with literally
anything I add trees I guess wait don't
don't you you don't wait you just need
to craft them right sorry it's been a
while with Minecraft
how many do we get out of that we got
six oh I think of six we can make a
golden armor piece right yeah we can
make
boots all right fresh sick
[Music]
boots then I'll give you the boots the
new ones thank
you
yeah all right then we could already go
back in in theory mhm but what do we do
once we're
inside M look for the Soul Sand oh okay
but like we can get the one for Muna too
I don't think she has to pick it up
herself wait if Soul Sand then I have it
right
here oh I got
four I think the mission at least wants
us to get it like today like Min it not
not like exist ing Soul Sand that was
already in your
chest ah or did you get oh wait yeah
never mind you got it from the ground
yeah before MAA died I forgot yeah oh
okay okay okay oh then that's complete
we could find another gas for you to
kill oh but I kill I killed one oh not
that well
then yeah honestly I don't know what we
should do right now um let's check the
missions
again we can make a potion you can make
a potion but then I think you need um
you need the bre
station yeah but also Magma Cream if
there's no no Magma Cream there left
anymore magma what's a Magma Cream you
get those from the magma the bouncy
magma blocks in the nether the ones that
separate into smaller blocks
oh so that would mean we should probably
go to the Fortress there's an easy path
to the Fortress and then there's a lot
of magma creams there usually oh okay
then we can go there yeah and there'll
be some wither skeletons too which I
guess counts as a skeleton
[Music]
too I killed one today so I just need to
kill two more skeletons
[Music]
yippee Al let I want to go to my house
for one moment
[Music]
okay small house okay I would like to
ask for your consent if I were to take
down your house and renovate it when
you're not looking would that be
okay yeah but like is it worth it well
you can come back to like a really nice
house wink wink
M yeah I mean if you want to do it but
like it's maybe it's a waste of your
time of course not anything for Oshi is
never a waste of time besides it's the
only thing I can do in Minecraft I can
only
decorate no you can do way more than
that trust
me uh okay I'm putting away the Warped
fungus let's
go I took some of my own NE wart in
case well actually there's a lot here
anyway we don't really need my
NE okay
let's just check if there's Magma Cream
there mhm
maybe oh wait over
here yeah
uh ah there is there is uh everything we
need basically just uh
yeah what do we got to do to actually
make a
potion wait I did it yesterday I should
still remember how it Works press the
button only once make it with the
ingredients oh wait so it was never W
first right and then Magma
Cream cuz it it doesn't seem to be
working
automatically so we just take it and I'm
going to make it for you
oh then it just counts as you made it oh
actually no here let's have you make it
you see the the second box from the top
mhm
right click it it should be Magma Cream
inside oh it's uh not check from up here
from here from here where I am oh this
the second
one okay I got one yeah take it and put
it into the potion brewing
stand put it in the PO potion brewing
stand oh I think it's doing
it yeah
maybe
wait after that you have to put Redstone
in to extend the length of it but let's
see if we made it right okay yeah okay
now put Redstone in there just take it
from one of these boxes
okay yeah I'm donating my
NS and then you can take the potion and
say you made it oh so that's how you
make
potions yeah I'll beb I'll get some
water
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
yippe
Ean okay let me take this
away put this back I made a
potion this one I made myself
okay it's basically the same thing but
but I I made it it's I I did that I I I
I I was carison pie uh told me
[Music]
pal maybe we'll get
lucky I'll quickly make one for my own
uh you know for my own mission
completion I'm going to go get like my
other stuff that I left at my house and
put it in the um Locker just for you
know
proof
maybe's I love carison
pie he performs really well he speaks
really
well and she's just overall an amazing
person
[Music]
I love her with all my
heart she serves really well very very
well can we love her too
yes obviously she deserves all to love
so I'll take uh this this this
[Music]
oh I wish I had my bones with me that
could be proof to pick us inv byed I
killed like three skeletons as well
[Music]
okay one
two
oh never mind
[Music]
hi
huh oh wait where
the wait where did I book my book
uh uh which shelf did I put it on not
this
[Music]
one I found it I found
it 17th
April oh ol
hello okay so potion done defeat one gas
done uh soulan
done warped fungus
done okay we we can kill the skeletons
also if we ask everybody to not sleep
next night sometimes people do that just
go for the night and kill them over here
okay then I can ask in the chat
[Music]
okay or we could go to TT yeah there's a
TT yeah they finished it like two days
ago or so wait okay I'll how in the
world so this
T never mind then we'll go to T
found uh found Soul Sand found oh you're
writing in your diary right now in the
mission thingy yeah W mushroom this is
what I wrote down today I did lots of
missions with Cara Senpai by came but
died though no and then I just told
revive
yeah
okay okay uh follow me
[Music]
following
to this way right was the portal oh I
love watching you from behind those
cheeks be
clapping I'm sorry are you pressing four
or
[Music]
what the grave we made for subai
yesterday why is there hay growing
around that wasn't there
before it just goes to show how fertile
her death was I have no idea what that
means yeah I don't know either Ollie
that makes no
[Music]
sense how was the door open did you open
it no I think someone was here it was
the the girls
right probably all right uh This
Way
ooh I hate watching you leave but I love
seeing you
[Laughter]
go Ollie you little
no but I'm not a little I'm
I'm your little princess
I'm so sorry Ollie that's not about you
it's about the other Ollie but but I
kind of like the
title right it kind of sounds good yeah
princess has a nice ring to it
princess
lasagna
lasagna lasagna
[Music]
lasagna you know what's the difference
between me and you and
lasagna m
M all three of us no the difference
between us and
lasagna lasagna is food
no lasagnas are pressed against each
[Music]
other we could be a lasagna too
baby I'm sorry
[Music]
you are such a sussy
baka only for you st it is TT oh they
actually made TTT that's crazy
yeah oh gosh just is scary
[Music]
wa where'd she
go did she
leave oh there she
is just like a mermaid so beautiful so
elegant so wet sorry sorry I checked my
turtle I made a turtle house for the
turtle that was over there you mean a
turtle house yeah not really it's not a
real house Al people were calling it a
prison
oh
[Music]
H when I Gathering coals she's doing
great
[Music]
didn't realize I so you bye um welcome
to Hol
life thank you oh Aqua Aqua by died
here oh yeah that is
also
fun so many people died no she just
slipped when they were building this
thing
oh all right uh
skeletons come on come
[Music]
on skeleton dle ol I wanted to ask you
the the OE game days of Ollie uhhuh uh
did you like
have
this made as your oh sorry did did I hit
you no no no no no did you have it made
as your 1 million wish oh no not at all
I I uh made that with my own money
wallet what yeah she how long did it
take to make that since the moment you
like say okay let's start the project uh
2 years ago with a proposal what yeah it
got delayed quite a lot because I got
busy and then developers got busy it was
very hard to like align our
schedules oh and also uh I paid them at
a pretty cheap
price yeah yeah yeah so I did take quite
a
while well game wise it's pretty cheap
but like wallet wise honestly it's not
the it's not the cheapest
thing h
my 1 million whis is coming this
year oh yeah I wonder what you asked
[Music]
for you should tell me after the stream
yeah oh I can't say anything else dude's
doing
here yeah why are there
witches well at least um maybe you'll
get some money back from the sales of
the game right
amen amen everybody please support all's
games yeah as buggy as it is we're
working on an update every single
day there were yeah there were quite a
lot of English uh grammar mistakes M
oops
sorry but it was still fun the art was
so
cute maybe one and only
he oh the name of it
artist oh yeah I see would you not want
to make a game of your own
Senpai sorry I keep hitting you stand on
opposite
ends like a game like this I mean sure
why not you you take that one yeah the
next
one do you have free now fre skeletons I
think this is my second one so I just
need oh speak of the
devil oh wait did you hit it or okay now
I think I like to
know can we make TNT with gunpowder
yeah we should maybe make some in
addition to the beds yeah yeah wait let
me look for like the TNT recipe I keep
forgetting uh TNT recip is sand and
gunpowder that's easy we can get a lot
of sand down there mhm on the on the
should
oh yeah just a bunch of sand and
gunpowder and the TNT can stack unlike
the beds so that's going to be good
going to be great Dynamite
TT
dite oh you're thinking of a different
song Oh BTS song well wait what's what
Dynamite were you
singing AC DC oh t n
it's
dynamite two different brain cells but
you know the song right I think I've
heard of
it come on I think I need one more
[Music]
skeleton
hello skeleton to generation C I don't
know ACDC because it was released at my
time or I just know because it's a
classic guys I have other songs that are
before my time I mean I know moart songs
too oh my God Mozart she's a
heg well no I did say I I I lived during
that
time what's up was my bestie all right
you done with skeletons I'm done with
skeletons okay for good measure here was
another one just in case okay okay all
right there is now proof in our stream
that we did that
mhm oh we fall from
here just GA the sand now I do I have a
I don't have my shovel I have shovel oh
can you get like a ton of sand here
then okay gotcha and then bring it up
okay a T of sand
that is terrifying do not look down do
not look
[Music]
down hello brother from another M please
die
hello do you
mind excuse me I'm just trying to get
some sand not stealing anyone's
kid unless Garis senp asked me to
[Music]
so a ton of
sand so Chad now it's just you and me me
and you us
together where's your mind break BDM you
want my mind break
BDM s got killed by a gas did
she oh hi hi little closure
please can't touch me from behind you
got to ask for my consent
first do you miss elyra very much like
um you know me and Kyla we met up like
um off stream
yesterday when I was building like the
bridge I saw her and that's that was
when she told me that she had like a
whole um
[Music]
what's it called a whole villager
Guild like a Traders
market and then I told her you know what
it's I miss
Litas walking around on foot and going
on boats it's not very effective I miss
the diamond ice bridge that you would
always make Kyla it would be so much
faster yeah
I wish hen used horse more often it's
just that taming
them is way too mena you
[Music]
know
yeah
so even Kyla said yeah you know
what I I got to used to elas I'm like
yeah I get you I got them from
you
[Music]
wa let's take the ones from here just to
flatten everything
out okay let's try to terraform a little
bit cuz why the heck not right
[Music]
okay I can just take all of this
sand is this also hardcore mode yeah
we're still in
hardcore when not di tonight we playing
nether with Ali rain died many times
tonight while playing days with Oli oh
is rainy playing it right now
I want to see her
reaction but do you know who I'm looking
forward to playing my game I want to see
re Senpai play
it I gave her the code and everything
but she hasn't streamed it at least none
that I know of
yet I want to see in by a
rage she's streaming right now she met
me me it you made
[Music]
it you're not supposed to be up
here I'm always very jealous of those
glowing eyes I wish I had those but it's
not written in the lore
[Music]
o well there's quite a lot of
you no you could just die it'd be easier
[Music]
I think I'm going to die it'd be pretty
funny if I did
though uh-oh I think I need to run
[Music]
curse of
Vanishing okay what's faster the ladders
or the water
elevator down be to put up guess water
elevator at the ladder
water
[Music]
elevator
water imagine eating baked potatoes
while you're in water
[Music]
otherwise you could go with 10 people
and find only one hi Ollie I realized
there's a ton of gun powder in
there I don't know I already took it mhm
can you give me the the sand oh yeah
it's not that much because uh I was on
the verge of death oh oh yeah cuz
it was night time we should have done it
during the daytime it's
okay we could have just slept but okay
in this way we don't have to bring the
beds yeah it's more be more space in the
inventory as well
mhm oh we can still make even more we
just need more sand okay
gotcha yippe
oh oh that was
close that was so
[Music]
close I'm not dead though
oh all right so what should we talk
about Chad well we get another ton
of
sand all makes my heart go
cun I'm
sorry it's not like I'm doing it on
purpose it's not like I'm trying to die
or am I
how's your day Ali my day has
been it's been okay I've been playing
Animal
Crossing because tomorrow unfortunately
I can't do that I have a very tight
schedule
tomorrow I don't even know if I'll be
able to
stream so I'll be playing identity 5 in
a collab after that I'll be hitting the
gym after I hit the gy I need to go
to um an in real life meeting IRL
meeting
yeah uh the fortunate thing is that I've
done all of my
homework
yeah I only have one more homework
and the deadline's like pretty um long
anyways I'm
free did M1 give more work no not at
all if anything I'm the one terrorizing
M1 for more work
because after this one homework I'm
pretty much free
[Music]
I'm still waiting on it
too yeah I haven't really thought of how
I want the cover of my original song
would look like
[Music]
anyways or song left and
right I mean she has like original songs
left and right so like I'm not surprised
that she has a lot more homework than
us
yeah I'm going to be
free uh for most of my time like like um
next month I'll probably be very free
but honestly I think I want to take like
another vacation because last vacation I
took it was more like a sick leave I got
sick I got sent to the hospital I never
got to enjoy anything like I may be
physically well now but I think I need
to wind down
[Music]
yeah I never I never even got to like do
a
station I never got to go camping
oh and
I I need to
unwind and give myself some time to
think because there's also something
that's been going on I think I'll be
telling zom hopefully tomorrow hopefully
I can stream zom
tomorrow Spa trip
donation thank you oh okay I'm pretty
[Music]
stacked
yeah is it a bad thing it's kind of a
bad thing but also it's a funny
thing I'll tell you guys during
zombly Saturday
zom oh never mind then it's going to be
on Sunday as per
usual is it a bad funny thing it's a bad
funny thing it's a funny bad thing
vacation take two e have
funly more
babies God
damn at least it's
funny
M
yeah oh I was hoping for for a Saturday
zombly oh you guys want a Saturday
zombly I can I can I can you
know I can do
that look she's waiting for me I bet
she's going to come and say my
love I'm back no just you can do that
okay thank you let's go we'll have more
than enough TNT yeah left over TN we can
give to Kaa or anybody else mhm oh you
little
shits that is so
[Music]
sexy okay let's see if we can use it all
up
[Music]
TN not okay now actually you brought me
too much sand but that's
fine we have we have
about
150 TNT oh I I I have more uh gunpowder
if you
want yo a bit more
then thank you yeah now we have like
170 almost oh more creepers yeah
creepers oh man they going to spawn
more
yeah it's already too much I think
oh maybe we can fill up that one stack
still
yeah come on creepers come home
creeper do you know how Ma's doing oh
wait let me check on
her
um oh she's digging straight down right
now she finally got her iron
pickaxe
okay taking straight down the classic
oh by the way you are you not planning
to put uh infinity on your bow oh yeah I
do want that do they have it maybe no
but um you can go to Kyla place and get
it there if you have emeralds oh I got
to grind
then maybe there's green one lying
around
though wow oh now you know what let's
leave it at that
and
then I'll
put I think I sand here's some
sand let's go let's go let's
go I have a boat right here oh wait
never mind it's only a one person boat
where are you actually if you don't have
emeralds you can just um take the iron
because there's two iron Farms now right
and yeah then your job until MAA comes
back is put Infinity on your bow let's
go let's
go what you why are you on the boat oh I
found it there so I need to return it oh
but obviously if I go too fast and I
wouldn't be walking beside you it's okay
but I want to walk beside you
[Music]
come down here H come down here down
here and look at my turtle here oh hello
to yay it's
chilling do you know the coron
[Music]
where she says it's quite famous where
she says Ah to the
house like Mario uh like a Super Mario
game like she was making fun of uh enemy
you know the the the the shell enemy the
the dude the the turtle
dude yeah and she was like you know
making fun of him and she said SM house
since then I just have it in my head the
whole time I love it so much the way she
says it is so funny
what say that again no never mind no say
it again no say it again I'm
[Music]
shy say it again no say it
again sp sp inside the house spart Spide
the house
[Music]
I am
S I want I'm going to show you the
original later
okay are you also pressing space
endlessly
yeah uhoh I don't feel so good
no he really needs them
anymore let's go to Kyla Farm oh no iron
farm first for you
boie so that
way wait oh that
way
sorry he's so
G nobody
iron over
[Music]
ra sorry
oh oh hi I got
raided oh Phantoms oh you got
raided sleep maybe we should sleep
yeah but maybe we should kill
him blood blood blood where are they
come
on Yo h
[Music]
I got
one no photo
ha no photo the
Hawks
[Music]
hello let's
go it's good that they made a second one
because like yesterday we were running
out of iron every everywhere and
everybody was at the same place yeah
everybody wanted iron to get
emeralds oh that's so
funny let's see how much is in
here oh plenty of iron wly oh I'll be
taking yes take it
all there we go I take them by halves
because I'm not a monster
unlike
me I usually take it
all and then I I trade everything mhm at
the trading Hall so that sub Senai
cannot trade
anymore any emeralds I did that um in
front of her eyes in front of her that
that is
diabolic no it'd be funny if we fell no
it don't be fun okay it's
water all right go to Kaa all right we
wanted to go to
Kaa
SK Skelly seems like nobody cares about
sleeping anymore oh be careful though
cuz of the creepers girl oh sh don't
don't try there's
two oh but they're in water it's fine
creep creeper in water is fine oh can
they not explode when they're in water
usually when explosions are in water uh
the explosion decreases by a lot oo I
know that
yeah I only knew after the Summer
Festival two years ago I and I made
something similar so I like oh
[Music]
the more you
know whippy
[Music]
oh there's
looting oh but if I mine the ancient
debris with my fortune free pickaxe mhm
or do we need silk touch to mine ancient
debris oh I'm not
sure Chad tell us please I you still
just get one okay even with Fortune 3E
okay but we don't need the
touch I guess so Fortune doesn't work on
Ancient debris okay oh wait what did I
don't need to touch okay we're good
we're
good all right I wanted
Infinity yeah
Infinity oh it's only 18 it's so
cheap yeah
easy if and do you think you can afford
to
oh I wait how much is one we make one
for
ma oh Mauna already has
Infinity ah I'm the only one who doesn't
have itday yeah you you don't have it
yet Ollie because you're taking care of
me before you take care of
others
love love to you
[Music]
there we
go I named look look what I named my
bow because it's Infinity you know okay
you know what with the other uh emeralds
you should get
Unbreaking right you have the same bow
as
mine
Unbreaking Go Get It Go Get It get it oh
uh I don't have
enough you should have taken more iron I
I already took a lot of iron but they're
not taking anymore they're not
buying
oh you want sticks my dude I don't have
[Music]
sticks we could exchange some more at
the other villager Farm yeah if you want
yeah and we can steal ky's boat
[Music]
he h
sorry forun FY
last day what's Cur
Vanishing let's still
clutch
like short squish Short Hair Cat do you
know Maple cat yeah you know Maple
cat you know the the cat the short
British Short Hair Cat yeah
wait right wait wait do I know the same
one yeah you follow the same
account I I I I don't follow them but I
do know it's the the the the the the the
chubby cat with yeah he looks a little
bit chubby but he's not chubby but he's
so cute and and his owner you know she
made him breed for a few years and now
she said it's time to you know end it
all so she spayed him and and the other
cats she had and now his balls his
fluffy balls they're useless
now the The Fluffy what yeah I just
talked about it because this cat looks
like
him he got spayed and his fluff his
balls were so fluffy and so round and so
friend shaped they were so good yeah he
does look like
him and the the I got to be honest the
Bells around the neck of the cat mhm to
me looked like cat balls so that's
really why I thought about
it wait do wait what
what yeah don't you think they look like
plump cat
balls they look like cat
boobs I guess so you could take it like
that or you could take it the other way
yeah but yeah anyway that was just some
Rand no don't shoot it that was just
some random information you don't have
to spay this cat oh no no ah it's
running all do something it'll it'll get
to show on its own okay okay okay yes he
it knows how to swim oh maybe they're
ready
again ah he's ready you can trade
yippe I like it when you say yippe it's
so cute
yipp yeah that's that cannot be good on
your Roo
oh um oh you know I I I just figured out
a talent that I have that maybe not
other Hol life Talent have is it a frog
noise it's similar it's din know the the
mushroom guy from Mario the
[Music]
toad wait do it do it do it do
it wait I can I can do it too wait
uh I can do a really good toad
uh I just need something to read
[Music]
uh oh that's
good I can do it better I think but the
funny thing is that if you can do a toad
impression you can also do an Amelia
Watson
impression wait what does an Amilia
Watson wait what it's like almost does
she sound like that
what yeah but like in the best
way in what try saying re r e e in a
toad
voice see that's
am is that actually her yeah that's oh
my I didn't know she like I heard that
she was a gremlin but I didn't think she
was actually one I thought I was like
for the
memes she's not a I mean uh she's a toad
Gremlin or toad is a gremlin maybe toad
is a
gremlin all right as you're getting the
Unbreaking yeah Unbreaking three let's
go let's go then we have the same
bow the same bow yay it's like
fate wait can I still put a third thing
on my bow if I wanted to yeah so right
mhm I could put fire on it then we could
shoot the TNT from afar fire fire let's
get fired do you do you still have some
emeralds now uh oh oh no actually I used
all of them up sorry how much does he
need uh five only five oh sorry sorry
girl uh then let's get some more iron
yeah and get the
[Music]
flame Uber my lady
oopsie that that that that was uh what
happened we have I think I got stuck
between the boat and the block wow
Suffocation That Could Have Ended like
L's death cuz that's kind of how she
died she got stuck somewhere and oh wait
I want to hear like all of their deaths
how did everyone die do you remember m M
well okay um H there's so many by
now so sub sire died because we were in
a group in the never and a pig was
attacking us and you know they pushed
really hard so I think while we were all
panicking and fighting the pig pushed
subu down into the
lava and then ha was in haima was in our
group in our second trip to the nether
mhm and she was a little bit too excited
and too naive and she was just like
excitedly jumping on the ground and then
just randomly fell into the
lava that is oh that's unfortunate I
literally I was about to close off the
area where she fell into and then she
just jumped into it yeah I could not
save
her oh nice okay you got it and then who
else
uh well those are the ones that I saw
per personally there's a a lot more
though
oh OHA s by strip
mining strip mining where in in in the
solo world right yeah oh do did you pick
up the fence I don't have it oh oh yeah
okay there we go strip mining just like
the pro that she is MHM
sasuga ah p I am right like yes
yesterday I guess it was yesterday we
had a Pillager rate of the highest level
uh to the other villager uh Hall that we
have um yeah you know when the Pillager
raids like sometimes it can be a simple
raate but also sometimes they come with
crazy like the big pigs and stuff
or whatever that was m and paa died
there at the very end when we were
pretty much already finished with the
fight but she died as a
warrior
wa
yeah oh she died looking for iron yeah
Lia died to the auto fishing machine
that she built to the auto fishing
machine yeah a lot of building
accidents to up to this point very
[Music]
unfortunate 12 oh that's fine
yay yay yay yay I'm going to make a
burning just just like the Phoenix I
am wait I need to
book flame but like isn't there also
like flame one two three like stronger
Flames or is it just flame isn't it just
flame just flame okay cuz if there were
stronger flame probably Kyla would not
have been satisfied with
flame zero mhm she would have not
accepted it makes sense okay let's call
[Music]
it Phoenix
flame Phoenix flame infinity and burning
yo wait there's enough for you to also
make flame on your bow give you the
emeralds
be thank you thank you yeah we both get
the same bow let's go yeah it's like my
bow is Spitting Fire just like my Oshi
yeah a sword has fire aspect that has
one and two levels not hold on it okay
yo we're so ready to go for some ancient
debris yeah let's go let's go we got
this M all
right do we go
back there we go don't worry I won't
kill a cat cat you're so nice I would to
do that in front of
you but when I'm not there you
would um you know I'm a zombie and
maybe maybe those cats would have a
better life as a zombie as well no no no
I don't want no zombie cat in my
household we have 120 160 like 175
TNT holy
that's a lot that's that's very
much that's a good
amount that's an amazing amount bam
should we should we just start without
her she's uh she she's still strip
mining uh she has a she has three blocks
of lapis
lazuli ah lapis lazuli please that's not
going to help
her TNT would have been enough but we
want a lot of ancient de wait how is
five TNTs
enough yeah I don't know maybe for one
for find find one ancient debris maybe
it's enough you only need five to find
like one ancient debris isn't that like
so
[Music]
cheap oh Ollie we can find enough to
make a full neite armor for all three of
us and everybody will be like he yo what
the yo that be so cool
yeah we can eat up the ooh yeah
we'll be the strongest people on the
server yeah I I may have to go in
another half an
hour okay then let's get started get
started we should get started oh God is
it okay if it's just us I'm terrified
we'll be fine what's the worst thing
that could
happen
[Music]
okay you have your gold oh you meant
St H uh yep yep yep okay so now all we
need to do is look for a place to blow
things
up yeah yeah I I don't think these two
places are like the best maybe you could
probably go in here
yeah okay and then we just dig stairs
down mhm and hope we don't need
lava what was the level it was
minus 19 right
okay no they said why level five oh why
level five what we need to
do oh no8 to 15 oh okay oh hey did
somebody dig down here I think they
did oh no we can just dig down on our
own yeah
[Music]
okay
oh are you
oh are
[Music]
you yes going to be fine if you meet
lava do you think you're the calm type
um with you yeah really yes cuz I
usually scream and run away while Kyla
she just calmly covers it and fixes it
immediately oh well uh don't worry we'll
we'll we'll be
fine H how do we get
down oh look a slime oh oh we can just
go the other way like this way down just
like a curve oh yeah you're so smart I
am in
love or we should make it safe yeah just
this
way oh or that way oh got to be
careful
mhm o I have ah if you want
do you still have potion for fire
resistance Ollie we should take this
way oh yeah oh my God like make swirls
why did I think of that why are you how
can you be so sexy and also so smart at
the same time like can you like choose
one no I'm not and also I'm so terrified
of digging and my pickaxe is too
powerful man but okay let's do
it it's okay I can keep a good distance
from
it sorry Ollie I'm I'm slow because I'm
scared oh it's okay do you want me to
take
charge I'll do it for a while until I
freak out
okay gold
[Music]
looks good for now yeah we're at 46 45
what righty are you placing torches I
don't think we need to but oh I can do
that just a
minute I think she'd appreciate it if we
covered this up
[Music]
that's pretty much
sand a
gra
yeah as long as it doesn't drop on me
let me actually get rid of the whole
roll oh did you know you can just put
torches at the very bottom ah yeah well
I heard of that years ago but it's been
too long it's been 84 years
Ollie well it's been 84 years can you
put a torch there just in case like over
there I got to baby
girl thank you
princess she called me princess
lava okay there's lava so what do we do
now maybe we turn into a different
direction oh yeah we could do that we
could go to the
right
okay um let's see oh God
wait okay
oh scary
scary scary scary scary scary only you
continue okay come back check we are at
[Music]
29 oh
again yeah okay how about let's see this
is we can go straight for a while
instead of digging down yeah we could go
straight for a
while careful careful though be careful
I
will use the gravel that's how that
works
huh do you want gravel wait I'm
fine okay looks like you stand on the
lava Ollie yeah there's so much here be
careful there's so much too much lava
careful
it was
overflowing how do you put it there oh
you shift and then yeah okay so there's
the lava if we open this window let's
try opening this
part oh yep see ah you're so calm is
this like in an Indonesian trait or so
I'm trying to look cool in front of you
actually okay I'm going to try uh
opening a little bit
near or
left everything's lava okay let's try
left okay as long as it's below it can
flow on us so that's
good ah how is
[Music]
this I'll just drop until okay not a
whole
well but there's just more and
more yeah this is difficult if only mama
toia was here let's just then we got to
go straight for a while until we're out
of this lava section right
yeah she's so
cute ol tell me a story a story H I walk
on
this oh if you Crouch you can walk on it
if I remember
correctly better to fix
it yeah tell me what you've been up to
recently besides promoting days with
Ollie oh I have been very
sick I've been in the
hospital yeah the hospital mhm what do
you have I had what's called a typhoid
fever what the is that so it's like
a a virus that would infect you if you
were to uh to eat it
orally to consume it orally like it's
either you eat like really uh dirty food
or like really dirty
water you ate really dirty or really
really dirty food or really dirty water
honestly I don't know because I've been
eating the same thing my family has been
eating and they didn't get
sick I think I'm just getting we because
you have a different immune system yeah
zombie body
weak so could it be that something like
one part of the food was moldy or
something uh that could be it or I was
just unlucky with my
food o I was like oh where are
we not quite sure let me
there's so much lava
yeah speed o we still can't dig
down maybe we should have started from
like a lower area but like I mean we got
to get lower somehow oh oh I think we
can get
low
nice show me only how you get down get
low work for me yeah yeah yeah
woohoo damn Dam
work the bacterial infection not a virus
okay but it doesn't doesn't matter I
just hope all it gets batter does it go
away soon oh yeah I'm feeling better but
okay after I got better I got bombarded
by a lot more other um sicknesses it
sucks yeah
my Ollie doesn't deserve
this I deserve kisses and hugs and maybe
little Kiara
[Music]
SS what the maybe that could cure
me from any sickness you know okay
ol I I I
I
I yeah you make me speechless we could
talk about cat balls again I don't
know oh we're at level 10 let's go we're
getting there yeah 15 is where we want
to go - 8 to 15 oh Min is 8 to 15 got
it
nice you're doing so well Ollie only for
you my love having some kind of disease
or so maybe it's just you know how
zombies
live yeah oh are you you're just um is
this a
Bedrock
oh I guess it can already show up
here oh yeah so there's no more mining
maybe no maybe dig around because it
doesn't always go in one line I think
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah it's just like a little bit
here but then around we should be able
to find some ancient
debris oh
no we can like strip mine here I guess I
don't know I forgot how you do
it oh wait it wasn't - 15 sorry it was +
15 oh it was + 15 oh oh so we can go up
a little bit okay from here here's
eight so from
here
to no wait that's minus8 sorry I'm so
dumb no that was normal eight never mind
so confused okay until here yeah yeah
all right then around here we can maybe
make some paths or is that how you do it
yeah we we could maybe go here since
it's like the middle
ground I'm not sure though I never
really go netherite what's it called
yeah we NE never right farming
yeah and then we place a TNT and we go
back and we shoot it and then Kaboom
yeah that's going to be
awesome how far should we go guys how
long should the path
be as long as you want
about I think we can already place it
there oh okay oh no wait never mind make
it longer and then each four spaces we
put a tnt I think now I understand okay
okay so how
many will be a
big reaction it'll be
sco okay
I think okay let's let's stop there yeah
let's stop
there
oh
okay okay let's stop there no let's stop
there ol let's stop test run test run
okay so
one one two three four on the fourth or
on like like this four in between one
two three four like this one two three
four like this okay one two three
[Music]
four and then we need some space to
shoot it from right
[Music]
okay I made some space so that we can
shoot it oh you made
more oh no we just need to shoot so we
can go back yeah okay H I'm so scared
you got this I believe in you if we die
I suppose we die together should we take
the potion just in case oh yeah good
good car
oh then we don't need to be afraid of
anything no don't come back
Ollie I'm a shoot okay are we doing this
right fre between that four did I do it
wrong I spaced them out too
much really really should I fix it can I
fix it what if I how do I let go of the
arrow oh you just scroll test it test it
anyway okay
come come come
come oh it's
working
yippe yippe look we're doing it what
does it look like again it's like stop
there it's a it's a
brown oh yeah and has
stripes I don't see any
here that's okay oh I see one you do
oh my God you found
it let's go let's just one it's just one
we found one Ollie we'll find more let's
find
more easy oh yeah Kaboom
scoo oh the lava only the lava it's fine
it's going it's going to fill up the
holes right yeah I I can just cover it
up for
you one covered
and
[Music]
then
oh I have the potion I'm
fine don't
underestimate the power of the lava
let's close this off
can we close it without uh spreading it
oh oh it's not Ollie you're the best
yeah I'm somewhat of a genius
myself okay but that was the end of the
line and there's no more okay you want
me to dig more from this side or do you
want that
side let's go the other side
okay nice how many pieces
never right guys of of ancient debris
for making one armor piece never
right four four for full armor M four
for one piece of armor 16 for a full set
of armor
M oh look we found one let's go
let's
go let's go found for all three
of us to complete the mission go yeah
did you bring some wood by any chance I
I I know what's the wood for we could
have put it in a chest in case we die
now
ow you're what we won't die it's not
like we'll die
I didn't know it was actually this
easy
anyway sheesh this is fun yeah we're
actually
ohion of the
LA
okay just got the Diamonds oh ma can
join us
again okay she add she uh tagged uh P
Senpai so she'll
probably uh revive her I think we have
to put the what's it called TNT TNT now
there's a lava and I can't get
through
okay it's not that
long it's still pretty worth it
wait where's the stairs
again wait oh that's the stairs let me
[Music]
looking
good nice okay let's blow it up do you
want to do the honor oh no I would like
to see you do it
okay let's go
wo
wo wo wo it's going it's going it's
going wo
wo oh oh there's so much lava that's so
much lava well there might not be any
ancient debris here cuz I feel like we
already got the the the two
debris yeah the the luck in this area is
already out maybe but I'll
check let me just get rid of the lava
you know the what what did I say not the
ratio the theoda has been met
perhaps the
quot oh she's watching
us
oh come here we got to bring her over
here maybe oh we got to show her I can
send her the oh she's still spectating
though okay I can send her the
coordinates for where her stop this oh
oh oh no hly hly hly oh no I'm on
fire are you okay I'm
[Music]
fine oh so once you fall into lava it's
over so Dad that's how it goes how how
do I
blockage I need to
[Music]
eat shle seven Diamond done okay
how do I get
[Music]
it ah
it's very hard going yeah I can imagine
also I don't see any an debris
here but I think I can close this one
offel
[Music]
that should do the trick great potion
wore off oh thank you for reminding
[Music]
me least I could do is make it just a
little bit safer for my Oshi
[Music]
are we looking for
them
[Music]
uh uh I don't know what this really
does do you think if we keep on digging
this way we'll find another one just
like we did or was I just like super
lucky
maybe I should tell her
[Music]
first
yo they're they're trying to teach me
something about the lines that I'm
seeing lines cuz I I pressed F F3 and G
at the same time and then you see like
chunk lines
oh but I don't really they're explaining
it but I don't really get it
oh
well well I don't know I think we should
just make another parall line of you
know
[Music]
explosions we can't do it there because
uh there's a lava Ollie where did our
where was our path where we went left
and right where oh it's uh don't worry I
remember cuz it all looks the same to me
[Music]
oh wait we are oh we're on the other
one already wait okay
[Music]
um
H okay uh don't worry I can find it for
you no worries we found it it's this one
[Music]
oh oh it's
here okay then we right now we're on 10
so we can just make another line we can
continue the line here yeah one way
straight I guess we could do that yeah
we want more we're hungry hungry for
more ancient debris exactly exactly MAA
needs help ma needs some stuff okay let
me send her the or should we bring it to
her
either is
good okay
um but she does need
equipment yeah but it's in the ne
so uh should we should we should one of
us go maybe one of us can go I can
go okay should I send you the quartz
Yeah okay or you can just type it on
tat uh okay
you take care don't die
now okay I'll try I love you oh come
back soon please soon we
[Music]
will what come Us by
okay you know it'd be great if we had
[Music]
stairs all is coming for you
yes and bring you your
stuff is that
[Music]
oh
okay did we go up
[Music]
this
moon say and
[Music]
bye
bye where is
[Music]
she tra
TR Moon ma s
by
Mo s bye hi
[Music]
hi did did you get my stuff or or or
should we go get together we can get it
together we
weap infity
ball okay that's
enough yeah that's fine infin is fine
[Music]
Youngy no it's not
okay you can use
[Music]
mine why does why does they sell it so
Diamond thank you
[Music]
okay where can I get the
armor
[Music]
okay yeah we do need that
oh s
[Music]
bys oh that's that might be
help that might be help
[Music]
oh
okay oh yeah thank you
[Music]
okay wait
hey nice
[Music]
uh
okay
what
another what are you
on you're so
good you're
good
wow how is she so
[Music]
good oh okay you could
Fork
[Music]
you
channel oh
[Music]
oh what else is she
getting
[Music]
what I'll take more of the potions
these potions are really
useful okay so I don't need
this um I don't need
this uh I don't need this I don't need
this I don't need
this I think I'll need
this I'll need this
[Music]
oh to the trash it goes
wait how did MAA Senai get that many
money in the first place I'm watching
her stream eai
[Music]
what oh from the iron
farm take more potions yeah maybe I
should take more
[Music]
potions no I don't want these These suck
well actually two is
enough I don't use them that
[Music]
much the
pwi raid H oh
raid hello welcome Raiders hi
Raiders
finina who H wait who raided Young
#
be how do you
check is it fan funding it's not fan
funing live chat it's
not oh another read uh AR starus I'm
very sorry that I can't read your name
YouTube's new UI is annoying but hello
welcome welcome welcome Arina
[Music]
staria s sang wait Ian vtuber or ID
vtuber I don't know which language I
should be using or Japanese
perhaps welcome
y before this was rainy
really ID of course oh ID
oh wait are we
[Music]
sleeping now we just need to wait forai
to come back
right she's coming back are right
[Music]
Paris might want to see the fill of the
lav when you get back I'll do that just
waiting on uh MAA
Senpai what happened to the courth horse
by the
way I wish I was here I want to watch
this so
[Music]
bad ah
another
two you are on a
rampage
how
wait how many how many does she
have this is
one
two 3
four wait make going a five 6 7 8
eight you could almost make an armor
[Music]
is there a Bol
oh if only I had
[Music]
trees sity
sity hi hi
[Music]
wait what did
you guys said she was in
[Music]
Kyla's okay
hi
Ana
[Music]
hello where is
she you searching for someone oh I was
looking for a Muna
Senpai the Muna Senpai went up oh okay
yeah thank
[Music]
you okay
is she
[Music]
here maybe I missed her is she here just
her
[Music]
head oh there're so stand
there
hey hey
Daddy weapon
[Music]
I want it
too
[Music]
yeah yeah
sword
[Music]
for
okay he gave us a mini heart attack
where come oh
[Music]
wait
oh co
[Music]
grave
oh okay this
way see
that hello it's on oh
[Music]
yeah see
uhhuh yeah it was this way I
think wait was
[Music]
it h
wait it's not this
way now you
[Music]
lost minus
huh oh
[Music]
for
me is it really this way though
uh
honestly I'm not very sure
here wait but it's supposed to be this
way not this
way was it this
way oh
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry sorry
M
[Music]
yeah really
man fore
[Music]
I like at think that she lost or
something oh hi
[Music]
G
oh yeah there it is see we were going
the right direction you guys were just
[Music]
gaslighting you guys are just oh it's
getting late I am getting very cranky I
am
mad blindly ding to Blind oh sure oh
sure I'm never looking at Chad ever
again what look so
for she hates us yeah I hate you Chad go
[Music]
yourselves
huh I thought you going to go to k no we
wanted to get her stuffs
then maybe you guys should look at the
context first before you start
gaslighting people
[Music]
huh now I think this one's on you oh
okay so I'm taking the blame okay okay
so it's not your fault I'm just stupid
I'm just L
stupid is that what you wanted me to say
huh
you're not stupid you're just
old I don't want to play
[Music]
anymore where did she go
where is
[Music]
she I thought you said you had to go to
bed not before I see them
off are you not Asian
where's
where's on
[Music]
oh thank you for waiting you're welcome
I'm going to take you to Kiara and then
I really have to
go okay where SC now
uh uh
I'm just realized that I don't have
enough of foods right
[Music]
now K
Senai I'm going I'm going I'm going to
off to as well because um it's really
took like a long time for me uh then
then do you just want to end
it yeah but I need to write some
diary okay
[Music]
okay
okay I won't
where are
[Music]
you you're tired h of course I
am I mean thank you for for noting the
[Music]
obvious
ooh because I'm I'm bridging between two
people here and I didn't know that what
Mauna Senpai wanteded to do I thought
she wanted to come back you
know she's at the entrance of the
mine
[Music]
a which way was it what was it this
way I think it was this
way was it this way I had a feeling that
we
[Music]
went was it this way
I don't think this is the
one which way was
[Music]
it oh oh there you are found my way back
yay y yay B so wait how much did you got
I have 11 now I had to stop because I
need to fix my tools but I can get more
because I still have a lot of
TNT you are a
Monster yeah you you could have done it
all but yourself look at you yeah but
okay let's see I think uh four I'll give
you four pieces for now so you can make
one piece of armor four piece that's so
much though
no I think I can get one piece of armor
for all of
us you and
me no no I did it with you you helped me
get the TNT and you help me build like a
lot of the path so yeah I'll continue
though okay oh so are are are you going
to like uh still are you still going to
stream or he y wait Oh I thought that
was uh yeah I'm going to continue
streaming oh okay I think I'm going to
end it here
thank you for the debris though I'm
going to write this in my diary are you
going to be there tomorrow early on like
with the weather fight cuz that's
happening tomorrow weather fight wait
that's
tomorrow wait what
time probably like 8:00 p.m. or so oh
okay I think 800 p.m.
J I think I can
go okay I'll be there too
yeah yay now I'm going to find ma again
oh she said she'll be signing off I
think she's at the diary section her too
oh oh let me give her the pieces too
yeah okay diary section daily
[Music]
diary I can't believe I can't believe
the wither is
tomorrow yeah and so I think that means
that the Ender Dragon Is The Day After
Tomorrow wow
MAA hi are you already
ending not yet no yet well I'll give you
four four pieces of never ride so you
can make one piece of never ride armor
and you fulfilled the uh the mission
with this y oh thank
you thank you so much right way this
this that's all you need for one right
guys one four blocks of ancient debris
for one part one armor right yes for one
armor I'll continue mining but
yeah I don't know what are you planning
to do for the rest of your stream
ma well I think I'm just be safe because
I just died once
so I don't know if I'm going to the
nether I'm just waiting for for the yeah
I need to be careful true so right now
maybe I'm just gring uh in this place
maybe to upgrade my my weapon my armor
kind of thing like that now maybe Kyla
um will go online later and join me or
so I don't know yeah all right then I
wish you the best thanks for hanging out
today with me thank you
K not tomorrow probably around 7 8 or
900 p.m. is probably when they're going
to do the Wither
fight
jst 7 yeah 79 they didn't give a proper
time yet but I think it's just like a
gold golden hour like the usual prime
time for jst oh
okay okay maybe I'll see you guys there
yeah thank you have fun with the ancient
debris you
too yay
so Ollie Ollie
yeah uh do you need to write diary today
mhm okay what what what you plan to
write uh I'm planning on writing uh the
things that we did and tell them that we
fulfilled all of the missions
[Music]
okay
me
go why are all of these April get War
Fus and N right
[Music]
I you book Mission huh book mission
okay I
think
uh oh wait how do you write
it uh five it's
17 it's actually 18 but that's okay uh
crazy
olly uh
[Music]
found
ancient
debris 20
[Music]
diamonds kill the
gly uh
found oh
W
[Music]
mushro
Hy found Soul
[Music]
Sand killed three skeleton
so this one how much did each of them
cost three skeletons is
seven seven
[Music]
diamonds wart mushroom two
diamonds oh yeah I'm making a potion how
many diamonds is that
[Music]
made
ocean that's five diamonds that's
actually quite a lot of
diamonds defeat one gas five diamonds
Soul Sand three
[Music]
diamonds you know what I don't need to
write the diamonds
part I think this will be easier on be
in by this to
see
nominals uh two was
[Music]
it on W mushroom W mushrooms
you a warp mushroom
[Music]
spee foreign speech
seven I think that was
[Music]
all
ah I feel you girl I hate doing things
too no it's not about the documents I
just want to go I'm so tired tired I
don't want to play
anymore my brain is
[Music]
fried guys sorry
announc crazy byebye
[Music]
I'm it's crazy
[Applause]