I
[Music]
wooo
no
[Laughter]
hello hi don't say I'm late no it's fine
I'm still fine I think I'm
fine I'm fine I think I'm fine I'm still
fine
okay
okay just checking if everything's fine
hi everyone it's me cilia going from har
I and
Justice been
twet welcome hope you all doing well I
did some last minute
preparations as in I forgot about
it hi again hope you all doing well I
you staying up I hope you're okay if you
just awake naturally good morning good
evening good
day who's this no not yet I'm just am my
green that's just me where are you where
are you oh that's where you
[Music]
are perfect time for you nice good luck
thanks
[Music]
I'm here you here did I do anything I
tweeted I'm in here going to switch my
keyboards it's kind of exciting we're
kind of nervous honestly I've never done
anything like this it's
like everyone's here and well I say here
we all in like a waiting
room well I think everyone's talking to
their chats so I don't know if you can
hear this no you can't okay that's fine
that's good um let's see I have I
tweeted I have my little instructions
it's like like a PDF with some game tips
um
okay so for those who missed it this bin
you can click it I think I put it in the
description there's like
a trailer and an original song and like
an anime style PV which was really cool
uh done by I is
Callie uh Elizabeth and narissa and they
all sang it together and it's like an
animated video and it's really cute and
um it's
about the enigmatic
recollection
and and then oh there's also merch um if
you guys are interested in that and then
overall I think it's kind of exciting
because it's very I mean I
like I like games obviously but I think
this is kind of exciting because it's
like prepared so I'm going in blind
almost blind obviously I know the gist
the idea we all know the idea ah go
ahead in the head I'm Amnesia but other
than that I'm going I'm going in pretty
blind and I think that's kind of cool to
just have kind of feels like honestly
kind of feels like Dungeons and Dragons
you know some like someone else is
preparing everything for you it's kind
of like fun well it's nothing like f d
but it's like the same idea of like
someone else does everything for you and
then you just like play you know
who are you who are
you uh what time is it ah okay um do we
have to be
ready let's
see oh one
sec all
[Music]
right
okay no I'm not late I might just forget
okay can you act as if I forgot one
thing can you act as if I as if you
don't see anything okay I'm going to add
something close your
eyes close your eyes don't look close
your ears too don't don't
hear okay uh let's
see okay
sh don't say it's fine shh it's fine
okay you're dead and blind
good you're
back
okay okay I think we
starting I think
okay oh
man we're starting oh man oh
man oh enigmatic collection here I
[Music]
come where am I
who am
I ow my
head ow it
hurts ow my
head W but I'm so durable that's all I
can remember
I'm so durable okay I'm going to go into
the game now open your
eyes let's
see I think if I press this
button why is it why is it
so okay what happened to my beautiful bu
if you guys are going on a conquest C me
out I want to go home ow what happened
where am
I what happened I think I hit my head
what happened who are hello yeah I
that's what I want to know I think you
all
have wait what a coincidence I also hit
my
head you hit your head too I I hit I
just hit my head that's crazy I don't
see any cracks though are you sure I'm
very durable but it was trauma
damage you look
familiar are you guys also heroes from
another
did you see did anyone see the lights I
wonder people here did you see the
light what's going
on I don't have a play button you guys
are talking to each other did you
see
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh-oh it's because what I said
about about the belly
button I got I got kicked guys I got
kicked for it for being
ha I think everyone got kicked it's
fine oh
it's I think it's because so what
happens is sometimes when you play
online games and then you say something
mean then you get reported did I say
anything mean I don't think so I just
said I have a
headache
okay you Anor the belly
button must be
it oh my God Ran i di am I dead
I guess we're back
yeah
around you
look are you are you a
human yes I think
so what about
you I don't I
don't you're very quiet
[Music]
[Applause]
she's a I think
[Music]
she's 2 hours as don't remember going to
be a lot of this in the beginning I
think a lot of adjusting
a people have been telling me about
you are those real people okay all right
that was
[Music]
the what's what's your name actually
we can
find hello
hello did you hit your head
too did you hit your head
too I
think my
[Music]
head it's really loud it's like
everything Echoes against the
walls I
canot I could Jo my
corner okay I think I'm going to stand
in a corner
too I called you tickle
to does it mean we're crazy is that out
of here let me out don't know let me out
but I hope it's
okay let her
out good luck to you on your uh I don't
know Adventure good luck to you as well
on getting out of this box hello hello
hi heing
of of the other are hiding
corn of the oh oh yeah okay
sorry oh Z
okay
okay I guess okay okay yeah
okay Exchange
[Music]
[Laughter]
her story her story okay oh press
sneaky I don't know what's the
sneaky what's the what's the s
shift shift
Who I Am the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel empty
relieved
relieved maybe I didn't like whatever
was going on before I hit my
head perhaps distraught
distraught
H I do not
know so much I don't know and yet much I
do not know and yet and yet
bright light it light it calls to
me a lot of
lights the is it's blue and
white oh it's so pretty oh it looks so
cool I've gone into the light before I
guess it wouldn't hurt to go again oh I
can't go here okay fine can I jump down
no okay I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine it's fine I'm
fine I can't Sprint because I'm
hungry okay
okay it
say take me
now take me up take take me wake me up
so many voices I don't know why there so
many voices do we go can we go up can we
can we go we don't go up I can float
should we go towards the
light oh what's that that looks like an
egg oh
well it looks really cool but what came
first
turn it's not a hole a which one's
this jump jump do it jump jump jump jump
jump jump jump jump jump jump
jump
flb Oho
oh
cute you there what are you doing
here um you have the look of Outsiders
about you I am just I'm on my way to
deliver a pizza
ah I love pizza I think maybe that's all
I
remember do you I think they like pizza
too wait could it
be I do like pizza it's true no audio
doesn't everyone else have audio am I
the only one I think it just doesn't
have audio I'm not
sure oh send word to his
majesty what
no I'm fun okay thanks the Majesty likes
Pizza could it
be could could it be
guys oh the heroes the the heroes have
arrived at the sanctuary they should
have like High voices or low
voices right
away leest Li liest lion oh it's the
king I'll do the you know what we don't
need PM I'm the
PM no that's some game I can't do
that welcome Heroes this is the kingdom
of liol and I am its
king the guards who brought you here
have inform fronted me that you remember
not but your own names yeahia
green h a side effect of travel between
worlds no
doubt yeah no I think it was a piano
this must all come as a surprise to you
but here here here can well here it was
I who summoned You Hair King can you
talk at normal speech I don't speak High
English
oh there is
music
really I don't think so you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world it has swn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes this High TI land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as
Staines this kingom of Lial and its
surrounding area now the only safe place
left to us liist
H but should the Calamity be left
unchecked it is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world keep forgetting to press shift ah
he's so cute he kind of looks like he
has a little wind up key placed with
this Prospect I scored the ancient texts
for a way to combat the Calamity and
therein I found
one the ritual of hero summoning oh
we're going to get summoned this is just
like an easy guy you who hail from
another world have been summoned here by
me to become the savors of
liy oh did I just nod only you have the
power to save our world okay but what do
I get in return do I get do you pay me
and so I ask Will
you green yeah veridus oh like vidian
vidiian means
green I remember that much even though I
hit my head yeah your majesty is that an
timal what is it that's it the king's
voice a great host of stains has broken
through our defensive line
no we are rushing to most mounted
defense but the situation is D Your
Majesty we must get you somewhere
safe it's a royal aall with green
and who who are these strangers H do do
Dot
there's great uh what did I say there's
great power within you no will you use
it to save us to save this
world do I have
to what about my
pizza all I want to do
[Laughter]
is um okay
nice to meet
[Music]
youel
C you just push me how rude I can't
believe it can't believe she would push
me like
that let your heart be your compass and
I have faith we will proail
looks like you I thank you for Lending
Your
brave so
cute B
are you a
cat can you can you can you
Pur can you Pur hello can you Pur yeah
come here come here
okay who are you are you a
cat I am ra pan are you a cat I don't
know I'm a big cat I'm very first and
I'm Predator that means I can kill you
at any moment at any time your
Pur
yes
youing oh wow she ped for anyone
huh I'll you
my wait isur
no stop leave me
[Music]
alone there is much to ponder about this
wall yeah there's so much
to I regret that you must face such
dangers so soon after your
arrival explain to you
[Music]
life invested with the monsters known as
stain not even the Mighty the best
Castle can be set to be safe
anymore must be is too late to save this
world from destruction
never uhhuh
[Music]
no I was listening to narration there's
a
[Applause]
boss it's between you and
dead body on the
[Applause]
Flor I don't
feel perhaps this wooden sword could
perh be
[Applause]
[Music]
useful did you just jum
nice
[Music]
many St King we're already fighting the
king believe it yourself believe it in
me who believe in you
but why why
notal
[Music]
everyone oh there's do
help why are those like four guys
helping
[Applause]
us hold your weapon and left click left
click hold your weapon and left cck
shout
Revelation
Revelation revelation
re re
Revelation
re it's the accent uh close I can't
move
Revelation
re re
maybe bread
Revelation
hold why do I keep getting jump scared
by
these oh
oh
o o I think that was a bug it's being re
reset no worries okay I think this is a
good moment actually
where when I'm going to add um some
music how about this
one just add my own bgm cuz we're
allowed to do
that this music in game I don't think so
I think some people just put on their
own
bgms guys is the
music or are you using
I don't think there is
any is
there I have no music yeah it's no music
no no no no I'm right I'm right no no
I'm right no no I'm I'm
right and I'm right I'm correct I'm
right I was right ding ding ding for
me the dimension were broken okay let me
just download
[Music]
this no no no no I'm not left I'm
right let me
open can do some stick stuff while this
loads yeah
yeah okay no no no no so cute did you
see all the little NPCs it was so
cute was like they was so adorable they
look they just looked The King The King
looked really cute and the little little
guys everywhere very cute okay let me
make a new folder here and then and then
um download
[Music]
this uh this
one this
[Music]
one this one
um okay that sounds good
enough okay and then I and then I go
here
um and then I add
[Music]
them the revelations is still in the
void until the light came like in my oh
my God Revelation Revelation re
Revelation okay I'm going to add a bunch
of music mute this mute if you have to
okay
one
3 four
okay
sorry sorry I guess I should have waited
a couple seconds sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
okay and then I Loop
it
[Music]
loop loop okay let's try going back in
no get
looped get
looped
Loop uh properties okay now I have
everything I need I remember too much a
I hit my
head oh you can't hear it should be
there it's kind of quiet I guess can put
it louder
[Music]
I think I'm going to go get some
water one sec oh wait I got a
[Music]
ping okay okay no I'm going to go get
some
water enjoy the void
[Music]
I got some
water the
void I hope my mic was working fine cuz
I'm using two mics for this since I have
one in Minecraft and then one on stream
a little bit worried but it was pretty
loud earlier so it makes sense that
everything was kind of
[Music]
loud oh music's a bit loud okay turn it
down I hydrated
[Music]
oh
okay perfect okay who are you who are
you wait a minute who are you okay how
can we explain this away oh I woke up
and then and then I saw like a bunch of
girls and then they were like these evil
guys do I have to help the kingdom
though what about my
pizza what about what about all the
pizza I could
have are you a robot no I'm an
automaton automaton not automat
automaton not automaton not automatas
aaton get good loot and XP for helping
them but what about pizza
[Music]
what about
pizza I'm not a coffee a coffee lover
what's coffee okay explain coffee to me
in six words six words or less six
words or
more six words none no
[Music]
less gross that's not six words I I
guess I said all Les okay six words
exactly coffee is delicious and pure
energy
really sweet drink that's better the
chat moved too fast I couldn't read your
entire sentence bitter Brown we
water it's all
right needs to try need to try tea tea
that sounds nice tea has only three
letters I can tell I know what tea is
I'm not stupid but I've never had coffee
I wonder I wonder how far my Amnesia
goes have you guys ever been hit by
piano if
so how bad was y
Amnesia he's what he's yummy no
no Twice hey that's pretty
impressive skip other y know can you
like Dodge
it I'm tired I tried taking a nap early
I don't know why I
couldn't I think I was thinking about
something I think I was thinking about a
manga that's
bad I was reading this manga and then I
and then it's kind of you know when you
think it gets
better and you're like oh any minute now
and then it doesn't but then you feel
like some cost Fells and you feel like
you've already put in so much time so
might as well finish it
no it was pretty bad it wasn't that bad
it wasn't good not again it happens
quite often I don't know I'm always
looking for gold but it's hard it's like
90% of the manga that I find is not that
good and but then those 10% you know
when you find that perfect thing like
that just just you know a right amount
of angst interesting plot interesting
characters for me personally there's
three main things in manga
and I feel like one of them is almost
always missing one good plot two good
characters three good art good art for
me can like carry a mediocre manga but
if it's like I can still love something
even if the art is bad you
know and then I feel the other two is
always like either you find something
where the characters are really
interesting but then the plot is
literally just I don't know size of Life
very you
know kind of lame or the plot is really
interesting and you're like o it's a
fantasy world and oh it's like this
political Intrigue and ooh magic
Supernatural mystery oo and then the
characters are like the most Gary Su and
Mary Su that have ever worked this Earth
and then you're like what's the most
back
okay oh okay thanks
sound like way
too oh my God I think wait
fig I would keep my eyes on the yellow
one yellow one seems my
head my
head
[Music]
not please don't eat them oh my
good please don't eat my
feet oh my goodness
oh my sword what you do my
sword did you take no no mine's gone too
I
swear it was no I didn't take B it was
it was it was the pink
cat no it wasn't me I don't have any
either look at my hands it was the pink
cat yeah it was the pink
cat the all powerful she believes me I
think what are you yapping about
they won't let us out of these walls
man
yeah okay there
was ah it go A forgotting
Memory the May the may may not have been
an error but it's okay because I don't
remember
anything now watch this t I've just been
in this place before hi on the streets
oh now watch this now watch this Speed
Run
[Music]
um I do not know oh I should have I
wasn't okay so much I don't know and yet
that bright blight it's calling to
me
again I
I I feel like I've been here before
hello
ma'am hello have you been here before it
seems strangely familiar I will say
would you call it a sense of D Vu D Vu
is absolutely what I will call
it a
wonderful thank you madam so enticing
I'm trying it's it's the first step into
regaining my thoughts of who I am oh
it's so I I it's hard for me to be able
to distinguish it but it's very
distinguishing thank you mad thank thank
you Miss thank you w she so
[Music]
proper I should could go there it looks
really cool come on who are you don't
like
that wa I are you sure r on
it yeah me
[Music]
too I can't walk
there the music's cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
M okay one sec I'm warm going to open
the
window can I open the window to my
soul the window to the window
to the
window the in game window the outg game
window my window
[Music]
the Moon is beautiful tonight and it
reminds me it reminds me of different
times I do not know who I am but one
thing I do
know is that I love
pizza oh man I love
pizza a okay
[Music]
you so real for that pizza is amazing
thank
you huh okay I'll do a better job voice
acting this time you
there why are you do
care you
have you
look oh sorry liting guard I'm a little
bit ancient I can't hear you the
frequency is too high Li guard I can't
hear you that well
[Music]
wait Qui to be as as
oh oh wow can somebody queue the guards
I can't hear them that
well good thing I'm not a dog so I can
inent it's
true he's caring my
B use a headset your p your poor pet rat
welcome Heroes my boy this is the
kingdom of liestyle and I am its king
should you have like a really low voice
or should you have a really high voice I
don't know the gods who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own names Yes actually so I
feel like so I hit my head and then I
woke up and then sudden I was in a white
room and I was like did I die cuz for
some reason I do have the concept of
death ingrained into my memory and all I
remember is that I'm sin GRE and I like
pizza and then I'm looking for something
like something higher voice more noble
oh side effect of
TR oh that's weird the lials have the
same voice that's weird has a
mustache dot do
dot maybe we
pizza so I who summoned you here you see
an unprecedented Calamity now threatens
a world that's my British
it has swn the Earth with corruption and
driven us from our homes homes
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as stains
mm Su shut
up this Kingdom of Liberto and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left was
lion but should the Calamity he left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world
oh no I like that he
moves faced with this Prospect I scored
the ancient text for a way to come at
the Calamity and therein I found
one the ritual of hero
summoning you who hail from another
world have been summoned here by me to
become the savors of liol oh oh it's
kind of like also they summoned us now
what about the piano
[Music]
and so I ask Will
you it's great
[Music]
timal your
majesty what is it
Greeno a great host of stains has broken
through a defensive
line no it's
V I don't remember what was his name
ver this we are rushing to mount oh wait
the other one was called rubius like
Ruby because he's red and this one's
called veridus cuz he's green that's
cute exclamation
point who are these strangers oh I'm a
ciac green and I lost my memory but I'm
a heroin hero what say you Heroes will
you accept this destiny
[Music]
okay how have you faed through
that c Rubi it seems you have eaten air
that you must face such
[Music]
Strang oh he looks cute too with a
little please save my
family little
hard
us who are you hello you look awfully
out of water to be honest hello not the
first person to say that do you have any
idea why my ears to your voice oh wait I
need to attune my ears to your voice as
well one moment please please do not
speak speak more please speak I think
you hit your head pretty hard hello
hello
beautiful oh your here reminds me of
something too you
are you are such a soft viian
Time to Kill the Boss oh ver
ver two arms my green fellow stay here
we can just stay here oh okay I'll
definitely
fight soon as I put on the Boss music
maybe we should uh you know be as
backup I'll be backup it's
okay all right B music I have Boss music
hey there's some Heroes over here just
lazing around you're not even doing
anything I'm trying I'm I'm a medic I'm
a
medic I'm a medic I'm back up guys if
everyone dies immediately then what you
know you have to
like solo the boss we
go you think I take fall damage
oh it's pretty neat it's pretty
neat hi that stain is not getting
removed oh hey what's up are you also
are you also being uh um back up in case
they fall so we can help them no I'm
just I'm just watching no you have to I
don't care about you need you need you
need like a like at least an excuse you
know in case they ask
you oh oh no I'm having uh
having we are back up in case you fail
so we can be like the second we like the
the The Raid group on the bench yeah
excuse me it sounds like you're
procrastinating I'm not a procrastinator
I've never done that in my life I am the
I cannot remember ever doing that people
are dying on the battlefield maybe I
should get good people have died we I
don't think that's true that sounds like
a skill issue how maybe they should get
better woo
[Music]
Hold Your Weapon left click hold my oh I
got my weapon it's my weapon wait wait I
have to get out of the way it's my
weapon it's my
L my my my
spear W okay okay okay okay
okay
Revelation
w
[Music]
die the stain host has been routed
routed what do you mean routed
routed press sneak
key
[Music]
oo you fought bravely kind Heroes I mean
I poked her
once I pray you something I didn't I I
looked away I'm sorry I that Mighty
armor
one must be their leader the stinking
fascinating Most Fascinating okay so we
have rubius I don't remember your name
Celesta
and I fought bravely what are you wait
right I fought bravely right I think so
well I see why they call you arrows we'd
be in a right pickle without your help
Orin orus orus Orin
Orin oh let me see
we sustained minimal damage thanks to
your valot you're welcome can we get
money a kingdom is in your de thank
you I must have myem to inform His
Majesty of your Victory will you
accompany me okay very it
is okay I'm just double cheing
everything's okay I heard the News why
we call about you Sly you know Rose to
the occasion you have my deepest gr he's
gway
here King King where are you where are
you what interests you most however is
the strange power you manifested during
the battle with which you were able to
defeat the Saints my my book my
Revelations attack he's hiding behind
the throne he's very he's a very scared
King I understand I mean I didn't really
fight in the battle either that power
May well be the key to saving your world
from Annihilation
Annihilation according to the heroes the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation that's
true but once they used it to R the
stain host it seems that power vanished
Without a Trace oh is my power gone oh
that's bloody brilliant in it Bri so
what are we supposed to do the next next
time the stains
attack revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are to
Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of liberal
still stands today thanks to you you're
welcome I did so I helped guys did I
help I helped I
helped so Heroes I ask of you once more
will you lend us your strengths to save
leel from ruin
[Music]
okay oh I'm nodding
okay yeah I helped marvelous on behalf
of all litins I thinkk you you're
welcome we are blessed to have you a k
Heroes no worries allow me to introduce
the four Great gills which are
responsible for ensuring the Kingdom's
peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
when knowledge and creativity are valued
above all the Scarlet one oh they're
here the Scarlet one okay curious
creativity and knowledge red red
creativity and knowledge the home for
Glory seek is with ambition and vision
where closest allies become fiercest
Rivals the Amber coin okay Glory
ambition Vision Amber yellow vision
ambition which one am I you guys have to
pick one no you don't get to pick one
but tell me tell tell me what you
think Celesta the sanctum of healing
with the spirit of empathy and devotion
thrives the Cerulean cup okay spirit and
EMP empathy and devotion okay that's not
real I mean no that's me it has to be
me the beacon of the righteous and loyal
where great threats are faced with even
greater courage the Jade s that's
me
guys loyal or something what else did it
say right yeah that's yeah yeah loyal
yeah one of these will become your home
during your time
here Beyond the Door lies the room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestors
shall decide your guild oh fear not
introspection is a vital step on the
road to Enlightenment excelsia as always
I say even higher don't know what that
means time to roll the dice a be seen
some of you loot down at the Amber coin
guil he's British I don't know how to do
briti accent I don't know if you can
tell but to save this world
together the room of Truth awaits go
forth with Bella
okay I'm
[Music]
going room of Truth step on the platform
and receive the will
will okay
oh do you see that there's a cool down
on my weapon skill I think you see that
my weapon I have a weapon it's on my
other hand
oh okay step on the platform and receive
the will of the
ancestors and so Begins the Journey to
Find Out Who I
Am SK what
one what was that one uh uh uh uh
curiosity and knowledge curiosity and NS
Dawn the cloak o oh how do I put it
on
oo armed with an unwavering will seek to
defend the soul of
[Music]
Jade h
oh cute animatic
recollection oh cool I have
a I have a I have a
clo
yay what what do you have I have a cloak
I have um Red Cloak a cloak I got a
cloak you have a what a cloak oh I've
got one more thing this oh you got a
giant it's like a you
ornament I got a fether I'm going to
tickle everyone's death
no oh that was short I thought it was
n you're not like it gu here
Ru Ru Ru R oh we all read are we all
together I'm so
stupid I thought this was everyone
here sorry we're all on the same team it
looks like my b
but it says I'm in a party with VI how
do I they're done for
[Music]
sure speak to your guils
master should I keep reading yeah you
got to right click him yeah just go
through all all of it but first would
behoove you to learn more sorry I'm Miss
now going to town and you should find a
quest
board why don't you go there and speak
with the quest Master it would be a
prime opportunity to explore the as
well
okay yay thank you so much okay we got
to go to the quest board do we have to
be in a party or is this fine oh maybe
we should make a
party okay how do we do that um I think
we got wait are you two able to join a
party I I I can join let's try it can
you attempt to invite us to your party
um yeah can it be hold I need to look at
the tutorial cool enough to join your
party you may forming
parties right click on who you want to
invite and then just press the blue one
okay I'm going to invite you guys I I I
can't press anything actually okay we
can always be
unari how do you expect yeah I guess I
guess I could
solo let me let me solo it you know yeah
how do you kind a sad but how do I
accept the party uh
accept it's not like that accept uh let
me see uh when the person you you C on
you click on and oh hey I'm in the party
wellit I'm in the party y okay wait I'm
going to kick somehow wait I I didn't I
I didn't do anything I just pressed
random buttons please please invite me
again wait is it is it the max I feel
good about this Guild something about
it something does anyone know where the
social menu is wait why is bi in the
party because she's been we bi and I
were in the party from the beginning but
how do I like uh it says click um on the
right it says when the person if you
click on the person you formed a party
with again the right of the oh I have to
find bib in order to kick her oh
no okay it's fine we don't have to be in
the party in the beginning I'm sure it's
fine um okay yeah oh maybe we can
introduce
ourselves I'll just follow you guys okay
tired do you guys want to int okay do
you guys want you like my horse yeah
where's the quest board you guys want to
how do I un actually I don't know we
have a map but shoot is it this way I
don't know what did he say did anybody
remember what he said he said good job
go to the quest board and speak to the
quest M what is the quest board this
looks so cute du it does maybe it's it's
so pretty oh wait wait what's this
question
[Music]
Mar they look so cute question mark the
question mark speak to your good I think
it's supposed to be a question mark
because it looks
question wait
no oh how did you speak to him uh fun
how did you speak to the right click oh
okay I have I guess maybe yeah yeah I
think you have to just Spam it next go
to the quest board and speak to the
quest
[Music]
Master follow me okay okay we follow you
oh we have a map new
leader I use the map okay good good
reading skills thank you it's my talent
we might have to go through this big
wait where the other two wait we lost
two where guys guys the other two guys
oh
no other areas guys we we lost two
people we lost two of them should we go
back for them your mic is muted oh oops
[Music]
uh
shy GA sh oh oh there you are is
Town
[Music]
shorty here so I I'm leaving the way but
we we lost you two so we're heading back
I see my bad I
took have you by a chance seen
shortyy she took off where are you did
she uh well do you think she made it to
the the quest area let's just go without
her she'll catch up okay okay okay this
[Music]
way return to us no it I
didn't where are youu
Kik I've been
[Laughter]
k
um uh where am I how do I look at the
map
uh I am at
the what color is
puu T what color are you
oh
no we are by the smithie how am I
supposed to know where the smithie is I
lost the
girls b blue
okay I don't know they go wait everyone
isic um
[Music]
uh ask the
NPCs I don't know how I don't know what
to do I'm
lost Quest Master oh okay I guess I can
just go there
um
here okay it's fine it's
fine we left the game oh
no sorry we
[Music]
don't know where it
is is forever in this
group it's
right no it's not breaking entering I'm
lost I'm lost
help where am I supposed to go okay
let's try going here as long as I go to
the quest master I think it'll be
fine right
so
here yeah oh
oh
okay hello
[Music]
in the party we going on a quest do you
to join us I shall join you of course we
are join
[Music]
us how do we
know the only one of the bo yeah mats
needed at the smiy I'm The Apprentice of
the Smithy and my master says we're
running low on raw materials if you can
help
us I shall invite you to the
party can you come to the quest board
please is there a way we can fix our
group chat because it would be a lot
less chaotic if we were the only yeah
there's groups there's group I don't I
think apart from just turning everyone
down probably
[Music]
not there she is oh my God okay okay
okay okay okay okay stand still do not
move I free you I will kick you from my
party goodbye it was a wonderful moment
thank you
goodbye okay
[Music]
click on it I never to master I child
master all the way the beginning I spent
time with my horse please show me The
Guild Master Okay
Okay Shi can you help Nissa accept the
quest the the group
thing I have to talk to the I no wait
wait wait wait wait this is I just my
head I hit my head real hard this is
what I take in all at once moly uh uh GA
do you know how to can you tell narissa
how to accept the invitation I don't
know since I've only
invited um to the group automatically
for me I don't I don't know I'm so sorry
I missed what you have said Quest Master
okay let's just wait for sh to come back
then F cuz F oh yeah maybe fun knows
Faun I don't know where fauna went
though
wow I think maybe she's helping Shi with
her uh to get talk to the quest Master
to the to the guy in the beginning so I
guess we just wait it's okay and then we
can do a voice CH where it's just the
part and then so open your chat and then
you click
accept we're going to use our to get can
you do that nice idea let us ride oh m
color Perhaps Perhaps not I think maybe
she's muted n are you
muted
hello sorry I didn't mean to mute I
can't open my chat okay but earlier Shi
said she had the same problem right yeah
me and Sh have the same problem but she
got in so she probably got in so let's
just wait until she comes back and then
you'll know how to be and right now no
one's close to us so it's not that big
of an issue anyways but then afterwards
we can be in a group chat yeah okay yeah
she she said she just clicked random
buttons I tried to spam all of mine but
nothing
happened yeah can you right click me the
the right click on the board it should
come up not you haven't talking to the
quest Master it opens up Social menu for
trade M I'm in ay um I'm
in so I'm not particularly
uh we know we know how to do it I'm in
the party guys no worries we know how to
do it it's just
um yeah has some bug with the chat
thingy it's
[Music]
okay so cute oh my
God yeah maybe I can ask
[Music]
wait let me
see wait oh successfully joined party
okay okay okay okay we're we're
we're let's go do the quest yeah okay
okay okay where's the quest no it's okay
it's not your fault
[Music]
k Master told me to expect you I think
you're risking life to protect the fine
Kingdom your main is St but
hope be tired of my PR by now so how
about we get started with oh it is wait
wait bottom oh you see it see it cilia
onward let's
go the
gur okay this
this way I'm following this way yes
thank
goodness trust me it's so cute I think I
do
believe I
trust I'm
[Music]
I'm not a fan of big crowds
Jonathan I think me and Jonathan are
going to be looked away for a second and
I lost them where did they go wait where
did
[Music]
they where did they wait where did they
go did you guys see where they
went do you guys do you guys see where
they went they go inside okay count one
two three hi sorry they missing four
five how do I make 10 10 oak logs I
think say very easy my friend oh
I
speak
exactly completed it is just that easy
my
friends of to
easy interesting I have an
axe I think we need to
coins compl the quest to speak to the m
M we needed collect 10
cobblestones
oh is this this oh my horse is iess have
to okay somehow I had wood and it this
is pretty chaotic I think maybe we need
wood because 10 Oak cuz yeah since we
want to craft some
stuff y anywhere good
no can we oh is this we can't destroy
the houses chop down a tree I'm sure
they would notice if we take a little
bit oh oh never mind just like one we
sneak one out uh what about that big
tree do you see that
there should we try that one the Town
Center Tree the giant tree oh what about
these small trees it's been here since
the conception of sty don't worry they
won't notice it's so big they won't
notice if we take a little a little bit
of
it just a little bit what if we take a
small tree the tree that has fed this
Village for centuries
ah it is now a quest item is this
Oak
H where are we supposed to get wood well
what about here this looks like a
forest this is a
tree no
coins and I think it that
I but I didn't do
anything you hacking me she's
hacking I must where do you guys where
do you guys see the quest
sorry I don't I can still see the
materials needed at the Smithy but it
doesn't tell me what's needed because
for me it just says complete the side
quest it doesn't say like oh a
child oh we can't cut this
tree I didn't accept the quest yes I did
no did I
not tell us
again uh
no that's
great what you guys mind if
we did did you not can we go back to the
quest Master do you still need to pick
up the quest yeah but I think if it's
just wood then it doesn't matter if I
get the wood first I can I can go on my
own I don't mind yeah yeah I mean we
can't get wood from here anyway so all
right oh we're right
here we're right
here on the phone I don't know where we
are that's
[Music]
true H phone I don't know what the phone
is
[Music]
okay I made a loud noise is there a way
to change to group so that we hear the
other five despite proximity or the
other two I don't think so
yeah use the phone
phone private call
oh I'm calling ring ring ring ring ring
guys use pick up a
phone wait who are you calling I'm
calling the party
oh wait I'm not you I was talking I got
to figure out how to hang on the
phone okay
bye we'll just go back to the quest
Master it's nearby okay they're at the
blacksmith
wait this is so chaotic I'm
dying think I'm just going to go to the
quest Master take the quest and then
I'll go back to the how do I pick up
call hand C and then I will go to the
once
I she is hello hi I'm just going to the
quest master real quick to pick up the
quest again you just need to you need to
talk to him and then you need to click
here to accept the quest on the actual
board hey this speak to the I'm The
Apprentice at the smoothie and my master
says we're running along raw materials
and can help us gather some place up by
the
Smith click to
order
done click to order how can I speak to
this Quest
master I thought this was
food waste I did oh I have now finished
farewell where do you where do you wait
farewell maidens oh yes yes would you
like to um where you get wood from could
you tell me outside where head forward
to the The City Gate and exit if you yes
towards The City Gate there will be an
orb that will lead you
outwards do we have to go to the smithie
first or can we just go out yes you must
be to the Smithy to the now we have to
go to the Smoothie
again so you said way is out the wood
and then the
Smoothie okay I'll just go to the it's
right
here I think okay
fine I can make the sticks myself now
okay we can craft them from
inventory but G said it
[Music]
all right
green the a but I already had the a make
any sense okay outside of the town okay
let's try going outside
F uh outside of the town oh super
outside maybe here to the
gates this giant gate
maybe the the giant gate maybe guys yeah
I think the giant gate might be where
need to go of
three don't know where are the other two
this is you know what this feels like
this feels like we at an amusement park
and you lost two people of your group
and you're like where are they we need
the matching
shirts we need Red Hats or something
like a little where okay hello okay
where are you guys
now okay we got to click this orb I
think they're outside we'll meet you
there we're going outside now too okay
we're
[Music]
coming got
it some logs too we found you we found
you oh it's been so long okay what's up
we found you Sky won finally we've been
reunited reunited at last it feels so
good it does here eat my memories
I'm 20
coins get money you tick oh they respawn
okay here feel my
FL that's
right that was an awful sad
sound okay how much do you need
Co you have
um
128 I got
171 better do some catching up got some
heavy Pockets
Z
what this one is like a cute
bunny okay I have a bunch of
wood why am I not using this think we're
okay
11 how much do you guys think we
need we need 10 10 okay have 15 that's
like 25% 50%
more good do we each need 10 I think so
I don't know oh my goodness yeah you
only need 10 you only need
10 I think we should all get
10 oh no sharing I have some Spar if you
want mayhaps my humble opinion
Ste summoning egg O I have oh we should
probably run I think you're after us I
have a horse
[Music]
iation my my friends
quick oh crap I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine
I'll protect you fair Maiden get that
wood okay
[Music]
safe out here does everyone have
logs we have logs okay let's return oh
dear all right oh that look
cool how do we return actually click on
[Music]
it oh we have returned did she get stuck
we're good I am running on a friend
though please say yes 1 together 5 yay
we did up
hoay okay go back to the blacksmith we
can have horses if we use our summoning
seed
egg that is
true they don't like
horses I have low confidence they hate
the hor we'll check with the quest
Master but maybe we need to do another
Quest I'm not sure
okay oh the more things to be able to
make we completed
thank you so
muching w I made Cobblestone
Cobblestone too many people are speaking
to him at
once all of our money am I am I using
all of our 10 Cobblestone okay I do not
think so my money has not decreased I
think that's your money yay I have
how much money do you have three to the
I
have than three
ha
purchase materials completed collect 10
Oak speak to the create a wooden pickaxe
at the
smiy
see maybe I need
[Music]
planks what did he say
pickaxe he said wooden pickaxe oh 20
coins o planks three sticks he needs
sticks oh he needs
sticks
planks 20
coins
Master
yay
[Music]
y here take to the master
oh oh okay okay oh okay okay he gives me
a new Quest I think they already have
them
right I have also created the wooden
pickaxe I have also created
[Music]
it wooden pickaxe how do you do this um
how do you have all the needed
materials is it all this wait is it like
regular yeah just regular so you do the
oak log and then you turn it into Oak
plank and then you make sticks I think
you need like four four each and then
you talk to the guy with the
glasses
yeah
wait okay I I think I think I understand
let me let me try let me
try yeah right he going to ask us for a
c
Cofe thank
you thank thank you thank than thank and
I think now I me I guess we just have to
go outside and get cobblestone
instead so okay let's find the others
moving
on B you did it could you bring us 10
Cobblestone next yeah okay I haven't
finished the quest cob that's okay we
got to get cobblestone to finish the
quest follow me follow me red wand
Scarlet wand where could they be where
the Scarlet wand oh let us call
them private
call let me see watch out watch out
watch out watch out you hit me watch out
wait step out of the way watch out you
broke my leg Nissa it was already broken
yes where are
you uh I I'm I'm getting Cobblestone
been a hit run okay good narissa is
outside getting Cobblestone I I'm going
to get enough for both of you oh she
said she's getting enough for both of
you should we go still or do you want to
wait here let's still go I have to make
one more phone call but let's I'll talk
on the
way okay thanks to bye-bye yeah bye-bye
hey such a reliable you'll be hearing
from my lawyer for that hit and run I
got a picture of your license plate I
don't I I don't think you have a license
for that horse I
I oh it's a
[Music]
TI okay let's get some
Cobblestone oh my God okay worked
ah o I got
money I got stage slime ball interesting
mind you're trading with someone else
I'm sorry who are you trading with I'm
stuck in tra with Nissa hold on oh no
wow I see how it is ched me I see right
click right click
[Music]
why do they make these noises I feel
kind of
bad do stay anation me into a oh that's
a
bunny kill steal oh sorry for stealing
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry didn't
know no
I'm I will secure the last hits for you
so you can get all the gold make sure
you get yourb might well thank you yeah
was I was basically I play earlier for a
very long time cuz I was confused so you
know it makes
sense
I'm it's okay it's okay that one was for
you that it was for you is that a
recharge oh right my way weapon they go
back
in everybody have their
Cobblestone oh no no I'm working on it
okay
okay okay I am
ready 2 3
4 5 6
[Music]
okay for all your camping
needs you can probably light it light it
on fire
too can we kill the animals I'm not
sure an instant TP heal
ooh okay going to go
[Music]
back okay team yay we did it one
yay now I guess we got to go back and
make something
again e the Smoothie something
called horse oh I lost oh there it
[Music]
is that's not the right one his name is
pickaxe we're not leaving until we see
your pickaxe there he is y you found
it hi all right
oh should be able to make you stone
tools to give it a
try that's all we needed thanks for
responding to the question that's so
cute
it okay what are we supposed to make
eight
sticks I don't know wait are we supposed
to make
something or are we done with the side
quest now he said that's all
need but where are the stone
tools indestructible
o it was 100
coins do you need do you need
money no you in need of
Charity no I'm not
well oh I'm so stupid the shift is weird
to be honest completed collect 10es
speak to the
everything not right as we were losing
all where did our other members go did
they make it
okay I I don't oh okay just going to buy
everything just to be
sure okay I guess not that
one I don't know where anybody is amount
of money okay I bought all the stone
stuff at least I think we should return
to the quest marker quest Quest Giver
Quest Master Quest yeah yeah oh Quest
Master yeah this way this way he's this
way he's this way he's this
way make a group
call if we make a a group call we're
still going to be able to hear everybody
though party
[Music]
yes let's go leave them behind
byebye no come to the dark
side
[Music]
well and finish the quest C your they
are the quest from time to time you're
pressed for time why I have a look
around town There's a mighty fine shopit
[Music]
oo okay I don't have any money none I
didn't give you any I have 125 coins if
you if you talk to him you should give
you
money yeah he'll give you all the money
we're rich says he says your press for
time and then uh why don't have a look
around
town give me money give me your money
little don't hit him did you press shift
afterwards again after that okay he gave
he gave me the money he just hesitated
but all is good
[Music]
now I think it was because you you
encouraged him with your sword I'm sure
he liked that I think so
too oh there is a laugh where are you I
called
you we're Gathering oh where did you
find the
shopkeeper oh there's a shopkeeper
there's a
Tavern how I go to the
tavern I go shopping this way okay it's
across the street from the blacksmith
okay thank
you Mar him you married the
king
Theiss R oh hey what's up is she okay I
think she's disconnected to left oh no
shop make sure you got enough coin skip
a skiper skip a skiper skip skiper
skiper holy crap that's a lot to
skip dialog then just select what you
want to buy isn't that easy completed
than gosh speak to the child in a
Gardens talk to me I'll show you what
I've got in stock I want to I want to
get lots of
money maybe we can buy stuff from them
and then we can sell it with an up price
you
know I think we should steal it stuff
and then sell it to them so we get
money yeah
yeah try from Adventure simply looking
for a little diversion maybe give some
of these activities a
try why visit the
gardens the children attending to them
why are the children working at the
gardens all right you guys ready to find
The Lost
Child yes okay the is Nissa back hold on
oh she's back I think let me ring
her phone
call oh you can buy stuff from
[Music]
him he has sweet
berries honestly hey wait a minute I
recognize these song titles nonfiction
fiction okay we were about to head there
we're looking for children
Lissa the children that have that tend
to the gardens
yeah children they crave the corn they
yearn for
it all right are we ready
for we're going to meet narissa in the
garden okay okay the garden should be
across
[Music]
yeah I don't I don't know where the
gardens are I thought Shori knew where'd
she go oh well this looks like Gardens
it's green should we try it does but
it's kind
[Music]
of are
fast oh this is kind of
nice this is not the garden I don't
think this is a garden this is just a
think this is like a
maze I think this is the the the
the the bottom
oh it is okay
okay this way it's full map I'm
stuck okay I think these horses are so
fast it's really hard to stick together
so I think it makes more sense to just
go go to the child yay
y we found the child this must be my
lucky day right well this year is a gun
fre to come and use it whatever you like
pretty is in
it but keep an eye on of scare away the
birds and stuff if you don't like
gardening you can also try
building there's an empty lot just past
here where you arrows can build whatever
you like earo
you and your guild mates could work
together to make a right spiffing place
to stay stop by any time if you want to
do some building or gardening honestly
very impressive child tell you a secret
did you know there's a place in town
called the
pit the says those kids aren't allowed
to go but I hear you can play a really
fun game there what would they a
terrible way to advertise towards
children it's so fun but you can't go
they going to go po Hero S but they let
you in maybe you could go check it out
and tell me what it's like anyway hope
to see you again Rush there what a
charismatic child able to loudly talk in
front of five people very
impressive
okay oh finally he's finally talking to
me oh thank gosh oh than goodness it's
really pretty here it's okay fa cute it
is
R to the pit ladies to the pit to the
pits the pits this is the the
pit oh oh okay
there we're going we're doing it the
horses are really fast it's insane I
want to see our field
Hall oh our hores allowed in here I
don't think they
are okay you cute luy lady lucky lady
I've got a game for you oh your new face
don't tell me you're one of those Heroes
to save the town aren you you want to
get rich I know it can make you a
fortune wait don't go promise ain't
nothing Shady look about how I tell she
something useful see I used to run with
the Jade show before I join the Amber
coin oh he's a skipping
jum out
I don't know what he's saying I can't
read
what just point yourself at your M right
click on her from there you can s
whatever to invite her to your party a
trade with
her now we can Avent it together swap
items and coins sh told you it was
useful didn't I you'll thank me for when
you're
adventuring uh I know you're very
important Miss C on you be a lot easier
if you add some extra coins on give us
the money then what's the
point Shake him Shake him tickle him bro
I don't
care tickle tickle tickle tickle tile me
bro bro quite simply I don't care
shorten it yeah bro this could have been
sent email shut up yeah
literally let's eat him up and take his
wallet okay speak to the Jake
sword hit him hit him
excuse me wait
we're no no no no it's a
misunderstanding objection
hery oh we were just talking to your
nice
guy we have
drama
not have a coin it's okay you guys can
go ahead without me no it's okay just
just
social sword there you go finally oh y I
got it okay
J is that very it is that's very yeah
yeah yeah it
is bir Sal just going to follow
okay just going to follow Nissa sure she
knows where she's oh I it's here
okay we got to get in
here that is a suspicious entrance place
for the
horse the the Gladiators Arena oh that's
so
cool fight fight fight fight to the
death to the death fight fight fight
they drink
blood they
should speak to the Jade sword Guild
Master
Okay fight fight fight fight Mur
y above
below
okay oh cuz they're the like they're the
fridy
ones
maybey ones they're The Feisty ones
they're ferals I don't know
about think this
[Music]
is they're
prettyy can't say
that the
[Music]
town I have not familiarized myself with
town at all same must be shaking to
suddenly find yourselves in world pray
you w oh you calling me the
Calamity I was like what does this
sound you
just yes in the Calamity near the
planes going Meet myself in G I don't
want to read loudly when other people
moreover they observe from the r in a
light akin to that of the Revelation
which you used to repel the singing
scuts from I am a little bit confused
what's the mission after this is this
like the real mission oh I was still
side of the Jade
sword keep spamming
here
okay who hardest mission
try
Hasty let's haste into
hus purple hus with haste I don't know
where the other two are
to the ples to speak to H oh wait
host oh hello dear cat uh
where meow
[Music]
no do you did you see that I can't
believe this pink cat said
no she just said no I got reject it just
like that just like that it's okay it's
we don't know each other yet I'm sure
she'll War try to flirt yeah she just
said no socialize man oh oh she was
talking to sh never
mind happen Le a little little softer
next
time
guard okay
let's go this way
hey this the
right I think so
yeah let's
go wait something has this of the planes
why is it Bor in
here took us a while to
leave oh I guess
so to the ru
I'm green where is he oh he's here
oh this
way a this is so
pretty I shall happily accept it hello
this is cool it's really pretty right oh
oh is this
hus it's hus hero you are a
mhm 1 2
3 strange
voice The Souls of stains open the
way what might have to kill we have to
kill 10 stains okay understand we can do
that it's the easiest thing in the
world meta time this is easy
do you think we all each have to kill 10
or just like together I wonder how
strong my weapon is if I should use my
sword or if I should use my
LS why am I doing so little
damage oh I did
it
here huh
[Music]
Stone oh I find an enemy I will slay
you why is that a hard masochist come
believe it oh 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 yay okay
sword is easier than my Lance unless my
Lance is charged
then I think I do a lot of
damage ow never
mind oh okay okay so my charge attack
does a lot of
damage they look so
cute they love it when we hit
them easy they very cute yeah but they
must die what can you do don't be
tricked by their cuteness instead kill
kill
[Music]
them has anyone kept count how many has
it
[Music]
been they enjoy the pain yeah I think so
so it's okay that's a
bunny
sorry four or five at least two H okay I
think it's been at least one ow I should
[Music]
heal bread oh I have a lot of bread holy
moly okay
[Music]
bread okay I don't want to kill hers cuz
then she doesn't get any kills
[Music]
where are they I should have stayed
where I was oh there's an enemy there
horse my humble Steed help
[Music]
me oh I can be on the horse while
attacking
easy
easy that's a PO a poor no that's not
the name uh uh
Pig easy easy easy okay let's look for a
couple
more no no no no no oh there we go
three po I feel like they're not really
doing anything I feel like us killing
them at this point kind of red
yay completed objective slay 10 okay
okay I did
it
nice try to fix the Privacy set the
Privacy set you you can't wait to play
again or fight again are you leaving my
wife
the under key maybe this key is What
will open the portal ruins we got the
fireball man is this me the of the fires
and the oranges
hello water I put out your flame in
instant try it then put out my flame
okay you're on cool down yes I
[Music]
am good luck have fun my beautiful
beautiful I can
I like you you wouldn't know a thing you
know anything about that about
[Music]
me how about you prove to me or not you
right over there
Wonder
yummy back into the yeah have you we
done with the quest and
I she
[Music]
doesn't I'm cilia green and I Amat and I
like
cats hello I'm ra panta and I'm a big
puer are you are you scared oh yeah give
me your big best
growl wow that was really
scary yeah that was so scary
no what did you do to her what happened
I guess I accidentally kind of uh killed
her in indirectly um
but why um well what Guild do you belong
to
traveler that is none of your business
cat what Guild are you part of with the
orange lady don't tell her tell I am
everyone's tell he my heels
sorry my bad
AFK sorry uh sorry kitty cat
uh we will Adventure right okay do you
have any idea where she spawn no I don't
wait it still sounds like for me
honestly let me let me let's two more
then let's see
um oh a chicken the chicken wants to be
cooked oh
hello you're there oh I'm back okay oh
I'm back I died but I came back nice
hello hello shall we enter the
dungeon yes okay okay I think let's do
it I'm ready I won't die again I
promise I'll it wasn't your fault it was
the healer's fault don't take any
blame I know right wait wait can't
believe wouldn't K you yes you use any
of your has one job yeah honestly I mean
it's literally in the
name well maybe maybe maybe I shouldn't
heal at all then well you did without
you without your heels where would we
be okay where's the dungeon into the
dungeon wait where is the it's here it's
on the map oh oh okay okay go for
[Music]
it okay I want to change to Dungeon
music yes are we here oh wait good idea
battle music for the
battle yes are we
armed I sure hope so do you have both
your
arms yeah I hope so I can't see them I
have to take the word for it wait let me
see yeah you have both arms you good we
good okay this doesn't seem like a
dungeon does it no it's kind of too a
and yeah especially for an underworld
dungeon this doesn't feel like I thought
it would be I thought it would be under
the world this feels very Overworld
we'll see are we are we the right level
for
this level zero level zero it's okay I'm
I'm sure we can cheese our way through
it
somehow yeah
wait what does your weapon do Cecilia um
mine is okay automaton
assault oh okay is that damage yeah it's
damage
DPS I think I'm an
AOE
oh that is that looks crazy yeah that's
an make me a tank you a tank she's a
tank okay do do we're
doomed no that's okay you have
two I think it also holds enemies into
place but I don't know if it heals them
too oh that's really cool wait let me
check do how do you guys know this this
is like an item description or am I
supposed to know exactly what mine
does no I'm guessing Okay okay okay I
was a little bit worried I was I miss
something it's like a 10 page document
on the intricacies of the of the weapons
no the eight PDF not oh man I missed it
oh oh ready to
enter ready ready
ready all standing by wait today wait
ready you are already standing by for
this dungeon okay do we need to kick the
others out oh
no it say two out of five click enter
wait don't enter for me it says two out
of five
oh enter
dungeon I'm two out of five yeah it says
two out of five it says is yellow yeah
on M am I not cute are you not ready
you're not green green
one
[Music]
ready
ready that is not
ready I'm ready up I swear I'm ready up
I ready up I swear let me read the
material thing let me read the PDF real
quick the 50
pain enter dungeon when you approach a
dungeon ready to enter dungeon click on
the green box on the left and ready up
if you in a party all members will need
to complete this step when all players
are ready you have the key G I have the
key
okay kick party
members oh okay I can't kick the two
that aren't here
so uh when all players are ready
clicking on the diamond sword on the
right will allow you to enter the
dungeon in over the enter dungeon button
will let you know if any members are not
readed hovering over the enter dungeon
button will let you know okay let's
see how do we can we we make a new party
can we do that can we leave this one
make a new
one
okay okay let's try doing that
maybe yeah let's try doing that click to
leave click to disband
yes okay I okay we the party has been
disbanded let's make a new
one
okay
okay inviting you
both thank you okay accept Okay we're
doing it and now we ready it says I'm
ready good I ready
everyone
Scarlet oh my God we made it we made it
now this this is so bad now this is an
underworld dungeon it's still not really
okay we'll see well it's it's more
underworld oh that's lava o oh there's a
lot of lava uhoh don't
jump don't jump the underworld there's a
beacon over there no there's this one
like starts something the underworld a
domain of boundless oppressive Darkness
as feared as it is unavoidable it holds
the final resting place for every
creature that walks the Earth yet even
in this realm of the Dead there are
those who live and call it
home crazy just invading their home yeah
entally we're the good guys don't wor
taking out the
locals we're just enriching the
experience we can put like a Starbuck
here or
something ooh star
I think we have to
jump this way not that way not that way
not that way not that way it's scary I'm
not
sure
no y
easy maybe this is a baby level dungeon
oh another jump okay they would they
wouldn't go all out on the first one
right
don't jinkx
[Music]
it okay first one to die um have to do
something
painful
like I don't
[Music]
know fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine wait not yet wait I think that
healed me wait did it heal you I think
so I think it did we really have a
Healer nice
nice to
heal it healed me thank you very
much I'll try not to stand in the red
fre we've got a balance party oh no oh
checkpoints oh there's another one
there were we over there already though
or we couldn't access it
before I think we passed the stone
monument before are we going in circles
maybe oh wait
this way you see that big
castle wait I
[Music]
don't doesn't show up
me careful I thought you got a new GPU I
bought a used one is not that
good wait describe it with a floral
words a castle Looms in the distance
with the pointy spir is piercing the
heavens or the hood red leaks Through
the Windows I can see it with my inner
eye o so this is the creativity of the
Jade sword huh no Jade that's right we
are the creativity we and the smart team
yeah we Geniuses scol scol wand yeah we
we learn for the knowledge Geniuses
creative and very smart honestly very
good
combination creative and smart
think we can do it should I try turning
up the render distance
options maybe depends what do you have
to sell me crank those chunks all the
way
[Music]
up uhhuh
oh
wow feels like I just saw for the first
time in my life oh my God it's a
castle it looks Co guys the liian
charity donation is calling me should I
give them any
money um we're not the charity no we're
not the charity we're the creative
Geniuses I don't recall that being part
of our tell them to call The Blue Team
instead yeah they're the the nice on to
tell you to call the blue BL
team the ceran cup says they
have and they're nice they're the
charitable ones they should give the
donation
mhm yeah we can draw them a picture
instead if that's what they need they
also said that your team is is
Shelly they said that not us this is the
Scarlet one team
seruan
come I
[Music]
mean
scared no it's getting it's getting
scary it's okay they don't need to know
they don't need to know is this going to
hit my am I going to hit my head now
okay we're fine we're fine What's happen
wait do you think we can have a hores
here
now can we what no we can't use the
horses never mind maybe horses are
banned in the under oh Fair Maiden if
only there was someone who could heal me
oh are you in need of of healing oh I've
taken damage I'm Healed thank you wait
you guys sound similar when you say ooh
ooh do we have the the green ooze the
green ooze oo quick if we move really
fast she can't tell us apart fast
fast ising all I see
isum J green
[Music]
the green the artist
like another checkpoint like that it
sounds like oo like o o z
e the green ooze ooh the green ooze
oozing the green ooze that looks really
cool though the castle is really nice
yeah I can finally see there's a boss in
there I hope not I feel like we haven't
fought anything yet so maybe oh do you
can you imagine finding enemies during
this parkour no you're right what if
they're flying on top of it oh
no no we should give them the ideas for
like next next time next
dungeon you can do it don't don't give
the devs any ideas they're listen
they're watching more lava lava
everywhere no who
no
no no there's a checkpoint though right
yeah I think she did we forget to get
the checkpoint no no I got it oh did she
not get it did you get it is she there I
got it I do not see her but my random
distance might be too low do you see her
I don't
here okay let's just wait
[Music]
hello where are you where did you Spa
oh there you are I see you I see you
okay okay good hi
[Music]
okay the phone call is a good feature
yeah it's so handy we would not it does
make me want to try to like scam some
people
oh how what could we do to scam people
we could like pretend to be their
grandchildren and tell them that we're
trapped oh the and we need them to wire
US money
oh do you think these phones have like
MMS features so you can send pictures of
their credit
cards oh I hope so um stealing credit C
stealing credit cards we making it a
creative way to make money stealing
credit cards no no no no tricking people
into giving us the credit cards very
different yeah willingly will giving
them to us yeah it's uh hello you give
me the last three digits on the back of
your I bet you can't remember the last
three digits of on the back of your
credit card I do because the other day I
had to put it in and then I kept putting
in the wrong one over and over and and
over and again and now I Know It uhoh uh
oh okay I'm fine
sorry I thought I was going to jump
down this is scary I don't want to
anymore you have to we're almost there
make it to the top you can do it than
checko did everybody else already do
this so we we the last one I don't know
surely not right I think we the first
ones I think it's just separate
instances I
see I
see oh
oh
inside okay is this where the boss
is oh no is this a
maze
uh okay tank please lead the way pull
the
enemies I'm the aggro pool are you
kidding me the tank you're the
tank look at me look at me out the
tank look at me I'm such a big tank o
yay
y wasn't that bad do I heal everybody
with that yeah I think so oh be
careful oo thank you for protecting us
tank God Don't Fear do not
fear I've got a pocket and a DPS with a
very sharp
pointed out I mean I'm on down DPS go
DPS go you can do it go go go
I did it healer has no heal
nice why is he holding on to his store
wait I
geometry not
geometry no do not
M oh he has a circle oh
God wait wait wait wait do you guys have
keys I've got a circle key did you
oh I've got a
star they're coming in waves
team they're surrounding us
okay oh thank
you
uh-oh oh nice wait which way I
to going this way yeah which way this
way I believe it's this way oh my
Triangle Man
okay
triangle
triang this way for sure is it this
way uhoh no there's too many use your
AOE it's un
down cool
down mine is so cool down
too oh God oh God okay wait
okay oh thank you thank you thank
you ow I'm sorry I wasted your heels I'm
sorry okay the corner it's okay I'm no
longer on cool down okay
wait one two one two
three we're here we're here one two one
two
three oh it needs oh can we like each
put one in because three people keys
that would be nice and it's I have a key
okay I put in it oh oh okay oh
nice very good nice excellent you guys
need food I have this looks like anyone
needs F thank you I still have some kind
of looks
like yeah Traverse the white oh no I
don't want to do this do we have a save
do we have a save point no bonfire lit
it's this is hardcore mode there's no
safe it's okay we can do it first try
this is a hardcore uh something
something um raid we can do this team we
got this Sky one Scarlet wand Scarlet
wand Scarlet W Scarlet
wand
oh oh my
god oh that looks
cool that is cool it's Scarlet just like
us yeah actually oh info Point another
life expired leaving behind a tiny
flickering light a soul representing
both a legacy and an ending the veiled
figure get cradled in her hands and with
a hint of melancholy she whispered is
that the right thing to
do oh I don't know is
it nice new checkpoint who Could It Be
Who Could It Be I
wonder is there a way guys is there a
way to like
CH and make it drop on the fortra Dage
they put oil underneath so they light
fire smart do you this is this is the
creativity of red ah and the
genius yes we're just built different
and everything here is red so it's like
it's made for us have you guys figured
out a way to remove like the in-game
overlay because it's like kind of
cluttery what over there you know how it
says like coins your party investigate
the underworld D I just I just have it
on there okay okay I do too it's fine I
can look past it with my increased
render distance oh is this a puzzle oh
it's a
puzzle guys this is ours we're the
Geniuses someone take Take the Wheel be
easy okay quick somebody do it quick
someone take the wheel I believe in you
guys what what kind of puzzle is it oh
no oh my god did you play pets vets it's
it's the Pet Vet game oh it's like the
ones around it turn the Colors oh revers
puzles oh
reversing wait it seems like you know
what you're doing I
don't I feel like you're doing it though
I think you're doing
[Music]
it I think you're just saying
that no no no oh
almost wait so does it like compare does
it do it from the other side as well or
I got to look up the rules of reversing
is it 3D I guess it is so if I touch
this one oh it is 3D okay okay let's see
how about
this there's a there's a single
oh each piece played must be laid
adjacent to an opponent piece of the
opposite that the opponent's piece or a
roll of opponent's piece is flanked by
the opponent's piece of a new piece and
another piece of the same color did you
get
it yes it's just one
left oh never mind it's more than one
left oh
one uhoh oh okay let's just go move with
the flow so we so we activate this one
and then this one and then this one no
not that one
oh is that like one of those slidy
puzzles okay okay and then this one and
this one flipping them on and
all let's
go Geniuses genius I bet we did it like
at least five times faster than the
other teams cuz we're the Smart Ones
absolutely
100% that Sur that was the final boss
puzle and then they they all and we win
right I think we're winning the
[Music]
tro wait the zombies we fought weren't
even stains do you think we're being set
up by this Kingdom to just like fight
their War for no
reason yes maybe cuz they weren't stains
they were like ooh the stains are
attacking us they weren't stains they
were just people in a
dungeon there just red guys that's kind
of
suspicious
hm something is a foot it's a skull
[Music]
oh oh dear it's just
like run rock and
[Music]
roll um I don't know how we can take the
giant the giant there's an invisible
wall there's invisible wall oh
guys checkpoint unlock was it a scripted
death oh no I was able to stay alive on
the corner of the stairs but then I fell
down but exent I think it was
scripted sced Rock
BS
oh what's this
skeleton is he friendly he's
hostile give him a hug Come on B give
him a hug
[Music]
actually oh
o his bone
Crum did you
H
ow oh nice DPS DPS okay maybe we have to
use the bone thingy oh oh he just comes
back can we make it grow yeah I thought
so but he was he just spawned out of it
so
I'm taking
[Music]
damage I don't think we can I want the I
want the
B okay so how do we me me can you attack
it or can you might right click it did
you get one no I did not ah I'm
dying he heor help I'm I'm on cool down
you're on your own yourself okay I'll
eat some bread kill him on top of the
mushroom oh that's a good idea oh genius
okay it
work now oh mess of brain maybe
again can we bra these blocks and use
them uh
they do not drop decorated pot don't
know what that
is can we feed it again I don't know
yeah maybe we can try bring it
here come here has the
F oh it worked oh we have to fill oh and
maybe then it's like stairs or something
yeah okay
oh
sorry my
bad okay oh oh all
right he's on me he's on me okay on me
on me on me nice
[Music]
oo okay is that enough oh we have to get
up there or
maybe maybe not I think we need a little
more
[Music]
w a little bit
more okay come
here okay where is he
oh there's a button oh button do
something there's buttons press it oh
you can climb the vines over
here oh
[Music]
really are there always buttons on trees
here oh there's a
button the buttons will show you the
way oh there's buttons everywhere
okay follow the the path of the
buttons should we press the
buttons o ooh another
button the final button button
yay no button have to do it
again oh yay two more mushrooms to
grow okay I guess
nice
[Music]
more come here well there he
is ah I'm dying it's
over wa wait I can heal you I'm the
Healer oh my God that heals full that's
really impressive actually that's
crazy pretty good power that's really
good wait we should try to see can you
heal two people at once do you not get
healed by two I thought
[Music]
it might be I haven't been that close
attention okay next time do you
ah let us know when it's on cool of cool
down again so we can do
it come here here okay I'll let you
know
ah we have
buttons buttons ouch ouch ouch ouch ouch
oh I'm going to die any buttons
I don't think I don't see buttons yet
but I doubt we have to do it on
both away that's high
though no oh right come this way
[Music]
see do you
mind okay I'm off cool down are you guys
damaged yeah I'm damaged it can be okay
pay
attention I got he baby
nice I think we should be able to climb
up here oh my God can you
not I'm cling
oh buttons oh there's buttons are we
done I don't know if we have to do the
other one
too
die uh-oh
[Music]
I died I died it's over I
died I died just like
that just like
that ah my
memories yes hello hello where where did
you where did you spawn I'm at the other
tree I'm coming it's okay I see you I
see you okay it'll be okay sorry I
wasn't I wasn't there to save you no
it's
okay I was trying to take on the enemy
on my own I shouldn't
have we're we're stronger as a team we
have to stay together okay I'm back I'll
come up to you guys in a minute okay
byebye oh no am I going to die here
again no leave me
alone game too hard why does he like do
so much damage
okay why can I not climb up here okay
like look at this okay we're
[Music]
fine I'm going to die
again no leave me
alone leave me alone I don't want to
die I'm dying
oh thank you here here here thank
you thank
you I think we need this one
too for some reason I kept trying to
climb the vine but it wouldn't work for
me oh
no I think we need to feed the other
tree too did you manage to get up though
no not all the way oh okay
automaton
assault okay okay okay sorry I just want
to heal and then we can go here oh
yes ow no luck or did you fall I did I
think we need both yeah I think we need
both sket hey boy come here come here
come here I'm die
[Music]
I'm
okay yay beautiful that good maybe I
feel like that's enough since the vines
[Music]
spawned anybody need
heels yes please you missed I missed I
didn't miss
myself okay hey man as long as the
Healer stays alive
[Music]
look I swear I'm I swear I'm press I'm
holding it I swear don't see do do me
I'm holding it I swear I
am hold the entire time are you having
trouble with the V I did but I'm here
now it's okay I don't know if this is
the way I think so the buttons are
here so
then up up and we go the textures look
cool
and
maybe new checkpoint
[Music]
ah
no
no okay
can I build something
here damn
it it's okay
[Music]
guys okay Do my excuse It's like 6:00
a.m. okay leave me alone
no
[Laughter]
hello here oh speed running speed
running I I just wanted I didn't want
you guys to wait any longer so I was
like yeah you know what I'll just skip
it Scarlet one genius that's why we the
Geniuses creativity
okay does someone want to read it read
it for us
you to the Denis of the Underworld the
light emanated emanated by Souls was
vital they needed it to survive in this
ever cold and dark environment yet among
them there was a heretic who called the
Customs into question do we really need
to take others lives to sustain our
own is that how it works I think so no
there has to be another way and so she
stepped into the plane above
oh she went on a trip she went on a trip
I wonder what happened to
[Music]
her what could have
happened above below above
below
oh W your power of Revelation has grown
stronger press sneaky
you've recovered a portion of your
memories
sneaky
Revelation it's
people ah click here to watch
video
uh
no um wait are the others watching the
video um
oh hello I will show you the video um
later we will show you the video should
we do that now or I I am down to show it
now where is the video it is it is you
you may download it from the
announcements channel oh I may have made
need 2 minutes then to log onto
Discord oh
no oh dear okay let's do that
real quick okay okay please hold as we
access our memor yeah it takes a while
so fuzzy oh I remember anybody have any
elevator
music oh I do you know I've got the
music oh yes oh
[Music]
yes
old oh one second
oh my memory is so foggy guys I
just have to remember your passwords
have to remember
everything it's just you know I finished
accessing my memor should I should I
wait for you guys
or oh it's up to you together okay I
need a little bit more time my memory
download speed seems to be a little bit
slow mine mine my existing speed seems
to be a little bit slow
[Music]
no you will get there yeah that was a
cute dungeon I like the puzzles I didn't
like the tree stuff but I like the
little triangle and the col maybe maybe
two too many trees yeah specifically
thing was fun yeah the light stuff was
really cool yeah yeah and it looked
super
impressive okay I am now due to my weird
memory setup I am transferring my memory
from one data machine to the other
somebody said Cece's on
[Laughter]
dial it's
true how did they know it's funny until
it's
not okay oh God this is so slow this is
a big
[Music]
memory well good right we gain him
faster if we get him in bigger
CHS um so yeah if you guys want you can
go ahead without me I don't mind um I'm
hurrying how how how much longer for
your memory to download um so I'm
currently at uh so I have a stick and
then I'm putting my memory on the stick
and it's at 80% and then I have to put
it on the other data machine and then uh
yeah this is really automaton technology
right here this thing is like when I was
created they wanted like it to be really
secure you know so they they didn't let
any like my brain is Split in Two and
they yeah it's very complicated imimi
and Engineering very
complicated lots of gears and cogs
spinning around yeah but it's
uh
[Laughter]
um looking oh okay and now I will put it
here
she's in the second
machine isn't it no it's not disc is
like completely different okay I'm at
90%
okay nice well pppa thank
you okay okay okay
okay I got it I'm here I'm ready oh I'm
remembering so well are we are we ready
to play are we are we ready to remember
I'm ready to remember guys okay me too
I'm ready to remember let's remember
let's
[Music]
remember oh God wait hold on it's a
little
big Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their souls wait should
we get the audio that's how it's always
been yes yeah she's talking what the
underworld need okay I got the audio oh
it's loud okay ready oh wait you haven't
started
okay we all start wait should we start
on three okay let's start over let's
start over let's start over Okay start
over Okay okay
okay who's counting oh wait wait hold on
I'm not ready yet hold
on okay okay okay everybody ready
uhhuh one three two one go
[Music]
a Reaper's job is to end people's lives
and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance but I keep
wondering
oh oh
it's not muted anymore it's not
muted
oh is this the right thing to
do no wait she was
the she was the lady in the she was the
lady in the in the in the flame
attacks a cute what's going on
[Music]
look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion we can do it don't their souls
at
all she being called back Reaper should
help the living
Dy take away their future if the others
can't accept that that's their
loss yeah oh she M at them
all I'll do things my
way oo
cool that was
cool yeah
Mory some cool Reaper right there so it
was her dungeon her
under her underworld
dungeon oh no I don't want to go back
into the dungeon
no you I'm good I'm good I'm good how do
we go home
though yeah we need to go talk to Quest
Giver
a let me see let's go fast with the
horse oh gosh okay we do know the way
can we follow you uh you Le us yeah I
can I'm looking at the map okay okay
onwards sc one to return to town to get
you a stone sword
yes there we go there's a
[Music]
area one two
three okay are you with me let us go you
say so ouch
violence s Anda had to leave they had an
appointment or something don't know
exactly but they had to
leave and then we go
inside
[Music]
okay oh do you guys want to give the
horses
names don't know if they heard me let's
try going here first
and then this
[Music]
way uh-oh I lost them I'm sure they're
find
[Music]
girls where did they go
oh here here
hello here you here you here
here nice okay we made it we did it
we've done your bidding green man yeah
what's what's say
you where's our money please read for us
someone oh read Brave hero I am hardened
to see that you have returned unharmed
pray tell what transpired at the ruins
oh cutscene oh no no we just explain I
see to think the ruins held such Secrets
a crystal deep within that when touched
returned a fragment of your memories to
you memories which in turn reawakened
the power of Revelation albe it at only
a fraction of its potential oh yeah do
we level up our power strong yeah at the
end of the dungeon in that white
room yeah now your summoning and the
discovery of these ruins should coincide
so closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation Brave hero seek rubius The
Guild Master of the Scarlet wand that's
us this Guild that's us oh we see how
this gu has also been searching for
strange ruins in the lands of liasa
maybe they have discovered
something oh my God oh my God we get to
go to our Guild we'll see our Guild now
okay should we okay well I mean this
one's fine but I bet ours is way cooler
because it's creative and stuff
definitely so
yeah okay let's
go north
oh wait is it right
here H oh it's
here no no it's
not it's
here knowledge
see oh there he is how do we go
inside I don't know do we just talk to
him out here yeah let's talk to him and
then let's go inside and check it
out can you do like a what what do you
think rubius would sound
like you do it ah a good day to you hero
yes return the the the text went away H
yes I now sense within your choice of
the power of
Revelation fascinating Most Fascinating
one might hypothesize that I don't know
how you pronounce that word that those
RS are the key to unlocking your powers
we of the Scarlet wand have also been
investigating near the Plains and
wouldn't you know it just off the coast
we Aspire a light with a striking
resemblance to Revelation good hero
would you be willing to travel to the
coast and Aid in our efforts there
members of our Guild are already there
heart at work I'm quite sure they will
appreciate your assistance good luck and
exelia she casted spells
yeah he gave us a
[Music]
[Laughter]
fireball
it's
now let's go into our Guild feel like
mine was already a full heal does it get
much better than that maybe the cool
down goes slower or something B
TP this is how cute TP
XL oh there's a chest
rooms live here oh
oh I want a room cleaning up the
mess oh let's go up yeah like dorm
rooms do you think it's bunk beds was a
big
table look you can't even see over the
table this little
guy he need to boost the seat he does
tiny cute
[Music]
okay I
mean I don't see any rooms but we could
just put our camp
here good thing I have I have instant
T can sleep in
Tepe huge t i cast summon
Tepe
w a little hard to sleep in it there
actually oh I have some hide can we
build at all here I don't think
so let me
see yeah can we build
stuff someone said we can build at the
Garden yeah I think that's like a house
area but we're not allowed we don't have
the contractual like licenses to build
on their
property which is weird cuz we're part
of the team but okay oh
what what you guys money we can go see
what they're selling oh yeah that's a
good
idea cuz I think wait what about the pit
do you think there's like some death
tournament that we can partaken without
money some illegal gambling ring maybe
oo that would be cool play some dice
that would be cool okay we can check out
the shop does anyone remember what it
was
maybe
here across from the blacksmith oh
okay the blacksmith was where was that
the tavern oh the tavern it it was oh
wait we have a map guys remember is it
is it labeled um yeah we have a what we
have a in our handy magical document we
have a we have a
so we need to go to the Town Gate
Scarlet wand is here why is Jade SWS
everyone else's bases are bigger than
ours it's because ours is creativity we
don't need a lot of space to be creative
and Geniuses they don't know about the
secret bunker ours is mostly underground
they're over compensating for the
smallness of their brains with the
bigness of their houses oh yes so true
okay I think it's
here no
yes
[Music]
here we are this is the district and
there should be the tavern should be
across he has the
shop yay
money he has a
lantern a fashion surprise box I bought
it I bought it to get that okay I bought
it let's see should we open it on
three yes okay 1 2 3
click to
[Music]
choose
oh what this is not
fashion
[Music]
what I didn't get any fashion at all
it's ging fashion that
is what did you get I got a construction
supplies Bo I got a construction
supplies box as well this might be good
oo wait we get 64 of whatever we choose
one I'm going to get
some never mind the gacha is
Bountiful what did you
get I got 64 Cherry
logs oo I'm making a pink
house okay I'm going to buy one
more tight
head you want your mouth
[Laughter]
watch your mouth when you talking to
we it's bigger than you
call you
you you point oh my God you do have a
point she has a
point I've got a garden for you to sit
in
I will guard your be careful it's going
to break from all
then my shoulders they
ache could use that as a
weapon if you look down really fast you
can nove forward with your face
down no she's too strong
so that is impressive yeah it's because
your brain is so big cuz you're part of
the skullet one team yeah it's all
hiding in my head please don't take off
my hat if you take off my hat I'll
[Laughter]
die I bought another one oh you had the
money I need to sell
700 oh I only have 300
left okay wait I got hats again what oh
we could use it to impersonate another
guild
oh and then the you know the credit card
scam is back on the
table wait what did I get oh I didn't
get it oh I think it just shows you what
you didn't get it's kind of mean like
that how do we sell
stuff I see oh yeah 300 coins I'm going
to cry
it's okay you can maybe you can sell the
stuff you get inside maybe I didn't get
anything it's a bar consolation prize I
did I did I got a box that's the box is
actually pretty good yeah you see like a
bunch of
items take from
it what did you say what did you say
what did you say oh hello lady
what hello greetings greetings fam
made creature I am the appointed Point
she has a point get it are you now of
the skylet
wand I
speak we had a side quest and she took
over leader of our
Guild that's
cool it looks like you're wear with a
hat like this it looks like wearing like
a red velvet cake on your head what is
your name blue
creature it um
um the leader of the Scarlet wand still
don't know the point of the Scarlet wand
hey you're aren't you the one that hit
me with your horse oh my God which one
there's horses wait you the one that
drowned her this Guild is full of
criminals wait a minute
no wait who don't worry I'll kill
whoever what what they do they you hit
me with your
[Laughter]
ho who her right what what Guild are you
a part
[Music]
of please be with your you never know
um I have a present for you would you
want
6 22 Mangrove logs if you tell us what
color your guild
is really here 24 I'm opening I'm uping
it no I want I want the big hats or
nothing no you're not going to get the
big
hat then nothing it's okay goodbye we do
not you wait wait let me reason let me
reason oh you don't understand where
if I take this hat off I will
die so it's a it's a trade your life or
this hat no that doesn't no her life and
the hat for what I
mean I think I want the Hat anyway but
what if we give you uh a wood
instead I I I don't I don't want a wood
I want I want this hat specifically well
you're not going to get it do not I can
offer you the opportunity of a lifetime
have you ever needed shelter and you had
nowhere to go well what I can offer you
is instant
tee anytime or place anytime or place
restrictions May
apply I okay let me tell you I'm a w cat
so I don't actually have a house I don't
need a home so I am okay thank you but
thank you for the for the offer it was
actually yeah but you already took it
you now in her
debt no no it doesn't work like that no
she gave it to you and you agreed how it
work the you I have I offer you a trade
oh okay you give me 500 coins and I tell
you what you need to know I do not have
that kind of
money I can give you five no 500 and the
hat five best best I can give you 500
and the hat she's not to be reasoned
with no hat no
hat oh okay no hat but I want 500 coins
I give you
five you don't have any backup who's to
say we couldn't just quiet
disappear yeah it's three versus one cat
you mean hey that that's against the
rule leave me alone tra leave me
alone put her in the house put her in
the house put her in the
DP DP oh we already used the
DP I need a cool down reduction on my TP
stat it's okay who else is in the team
maybe we can ask someone
else that I I don't know what team I
actually don't know the guild one yeah
me neither that's the problem we don't
know the color it's the yellow coin oh
the blue and the Amber team and the
green sword oh yeah
ahuh okay I'm sure we'll figure out with
time our
next and um the next time we meet her
will be plentiful do you guys do you
guys want to wind down in the local T
maybe do you want to do you want to yeah
yeah we can go to the
tower did we did we complete what we
were supposed to complete
today I think
so wait there's a bar
made a this so cute who can really save
the kingdom that drinks on the
house on the house on the house he's
charging me 100 coins what wait yeah
where where did you get it on the house
the left one set on the house well he
hasn't given me anything maybe it's just
like ad lip you know he's just she's
just he's just telling me to talk to the
bar M Night Vision on the house if you
can really save the kingdom oh
oh night vision sounds
fun good I'll buy you a drink I like how
everyone has like crazy Nam and then
this guy's just like
okay chef
uh what would your preferred drink of
choice
be can we
loot see like like Rob no no no no no
loot loot it's different it's
borrowing oh we can still craft okay
simply borrowing yeah do they have
anything they don't have
anything or somebody else gone here
first there's a chest
it's
empty we
are we're saving their
[Music]
life sign you think they
madeit how do I make a
sign how do I how do I make a
sign
this oh yeah did you buy
one oh
dang it they have the records
right the records
yeah we can Farm
gold do you guys want to maybe try
checking out the arena do you think
there's gambling there yeah I can do
that let's gamble the rest of our money
away yeah I still have
335 oh you could have bought another
gacha that was some restraint that you
showed I wanted to save it for possible
gambling I think it's this way
brilliant uh
[Music]
here I think everybody else is doing
the the thing we already did are they
Arena coordinator it says it says
duel rules can we fight each other okay
rules the first participant presses the
duel button whoever wishes to challenge
them also presses the Dual button the
first par participant speaks to the
arena coordinator again after pressing
the start game button a countdown will
begin after which The Duel between the
two players begin you can also dual
party versus
party while in a party one
representative of the party should press
the Dual button representative of the
the other party must then also press the
do okay well we know the party okay if
you guys maybe you guys can do and I go
onto the steps to look at you I'll be
the commentator wa wait wait why not why
not you why don't I go on the steps
um comment oh wait wait wait wait wait
wait we should have green versus green
no no we are team we are the same side
of Green I think we should find another
party to
fight just no need to to do all this in
yeah no we team SK we heal it's
practice maybe we should do one fight
and then do one with an opposing
team okay somebody duel me I'll Stand
still I'll be your punch
dummy okay you two go I'll I'll
watch okay come on man come on find the
come on fight her come on okay I've
joined the red team could not find an
opponent I think it has to be against
opposite oh oh really you think so duel
wait wait you've joined the red
team yeah we're all on the red team
oh oh okay I'm calling I'm calling
someone yes call them over okay wiing
private call Who's
online are they all busy in the dungeon
oh they might be in the dungeon yeah
okay I'm going to I'm going to call uh
okay so we one two three that's us I
think Elizabeth and mor in the dungeon
okay I'm just going to try
GG you the other players already in a
call okay I'll try my German brethren we
could disband our party and fight each
other then oh that's a good idea okay
let's do that okay goodbye
[Music]
oh
red
glue seems
backwards b 3 two
[Music]
1 and green and red and green and blue
the wooden sword are you kidding me
it's not letting me
closer fight fight fight fight fight o a
very very crazy display of blue jumping
up very high just there that was a move
she must have learned it and it's
over green
wins
[Music]
green marvelous display marvelous
display
now Fork over all your lunch
money
um I can't I'd have to trade you oh uh I
trade me okay okay give me all your
money this is all I have what I don't
believe that it's all I swear to you
it's all I have I swear how much was it
fine
okay okay no no bring the bring the
scaffolding
back my scaffolding this cost me 300
gold yeah
exactly plus oh wait hold on what if
we okay fine fine this a cool
bring bring the scaold back wait I'm
thinking though we could use this at
some point I'll use it I'll use
it what do you think I'm going to do
with it I'm going to use it to make
something
beautiful no we have to use it we have
to it's only fa
team it's only fair you lost it's it
keeps going down there's no fine
fine enjoy your wheat seeds I will
you'll see I'll be I'll have a whole
Farm soon enough okay this didn't I'll
be feeding all of the Scarlet
wands this didn't C any money so I'm
going to spend my last money on one more
loot box I think wait what about the pit
is this is the pit no this is not the
pit right this is the pit no isn't there
another
pit oh the
Sleep there's some shady
guy at the it
right yes oh right you're right pit was
yellow okay let's see the pit
is across from
here it is on this
side okay lead the wayo
[Music]
can go
study the pants the
library can we gamble bookie oh we can
gamble
bookie make a beted uhoh well I'm going
all in on green green wait what I got to
do blue wait how does it work on green I
got to do blue
uh how do you do this how does it
work oh 40 seconds green is there a
roulette wheel or
something
20 how do I do this uh you right click
him yeah and then press on the make a
bet the golden button and there's a a
window with four colors should pop up
what a window what happens if you right
click
him I have a hammer and a piece of paper
oh yeah Click put your money in the
piece of paper however much money you
want just press in like 100 or whatever
how much you have and then press enter
and it should do like
aing a ping okay nice you did it color
Cannon is fiery where's the color Canon
where's the color Canon oh there there
it's oh the wall
uh-huh oh wait maybe not is it deleting
the
colors uhoh wait I put it I put it on BL
like the last one standing yeah
maybe blue green green green green green
green green green green green green
green green green green Green
GRE green green there's no way green
green
Green what
no 10
times no that's not normal this was a SC
set
green they saw us walk in and we're
green and blue and they were
like oh no W that's that's
that's I come believe this would happen
okay I have some more money do you guys
still have some money I'm
broke I'll give you a little bit of
money and then you can let's bet one
more time
okay accept yeah
[Music]
sorry how does this there's nothing
quite like bonding with your guild
members like gambling
gambling do you think do you think we
were oh push I think it worked if you
push the red
one okay oh thank you okay
okay what did you guys bet on oh you're
Bing green green
Green okay okay
you bookie you better not cheat this
time we're watching you one more chance
bookie or it's over oh god oh color
Canon
firing please please I need this all
green are standing mhm how am I going to
collect all my funny
hats okay R gone that's good
okay okay okay
okay
green not I
iance hold yellow come on yes blue
yellow green green green green green
green green no it's blue is it blue it's
blue wait no it's not it's green green
oh you make we got so much money from
that no
way okay I'm betting what you guys do
you guys are
lucky
okay are
we are we betting green I'm betting
green is it really going to be green
again though of course always believe in
green it's the strongest color it's the
color of life
okay
okay I did 20 on green only 20 not much
F help I've lost every time man I'm
running out of
coin okay I'm fine I like the little
tables it's very cute oh we should sit
we should sit down on the
table oh sorry sorry my bad you can sit
on my life I don't mind oh
okay but it's I can't see though wait
you should be on the on the front then I
can't see anything with your head on oh
sorry oh I see I see I see oh okay
sorry no you go no you go excuse me oh
no no you go no you go okay it's
green it's green it's going to be green
again it's confident very confident GRE
confidence red is already gone that's
good it's obviously
green has to be
green
see I'm seeing it's green it's green
it's green
mhm it's green it's green it's green
it's green it's green it's a green it's
green just you wait
CHR no way
yes no way how much wait how much did
you guys make now I have 700 bucks I
have
955 oh my
God that is enough of threea
money green The Color of Money dollar
B it has to happen again I
think green to always trust in green you
have to trust in
green it's never disappointed you so far
I I definitely I definitely trust in
green I trust in green
too you wouldn't you wouldn't you
wouldn't forsake green would you funa no
I wouldn't you wouldn't suddenly like
turn around and not go for green right
never never after everything it's stand
for you never never h can't believe
you I got to make some money back I sure
hope this Green
Works it'll be greaten
[Music]
definitely 100 on red I don't have ah I
don't have the
money no no don't go on red it's going
to be
green no not yet oh you're
[Music]
green green green green Green it's green
it's fine it's green it's definitely
green green come
on okay red is gone again okay it's
green
okay okay y not ter terrible
mhm now yellow just has to perish
okay that's fine that's fine is still
winning okay okay yes it's green it's
green I can't breathe I can't it's
green oh my God green there there's no
way surely it can't happen again
are we green again I'm going green
forever yeah we're green did you lose
some money or no no no no you went to
Green okay okay I believe you I simply
regret that I didn't put more on green I
all it on green if this doesn't work I'm
broke
so I'll put a little more this
time even more onen if this doesn't work
I'm going
to hold it against the members of the
Jade Spoon or whatever their Guild is
called yeah the Jade Spoon the
radians it'll be over for them
yeah okay sweat I don't know how I feel
about this green it's green it's green
green green Green definitely
[Music]
green I
I okay Green's alive green all green
standing
okay yeah oh that's still fine it's fine
yes mhm stay optimistic it's okay
mhm okay blue has to we wavering no no
no don't waver believe in the green okay
I
[Music]
believe it's green still green see how
far apart they are there's no way you
can you can snipe all of them mhm
Goodbye
Blue
no no I'm tole no no my knees are weak
no I can't feel my legs I have to I
can't feel my leg I have to I have to
dir for my head I I'm I have
to I need
alone wait did you go you did this I'll
be back I went all in I'm
broke I'm broke how are you doing are
you broke or are you fine I'm I'm at 700
that's pretty good should we can I ask
for a small loan of 10 coins oh just 10
10 yeah just 10 I just need
10 oh thank
you I'll I'll do you one
better more
cute 100 extra zero just for
you oh oh I am ever grateful thank you
but you will only spend it on green
right
I
[Music]
always how much do I owe you in return
what is the interest on this oh it's
just it's just
30% okay oh my that's
all I feel like
the the like the
percentages are they like accurate or is
there a way to numerically game the
system based on like the numbers
hold on how many times have we
got I think it has to do with confidence
it's all a brain game if you're really
confident and you believe I think you
can
win 99% of gamas quits before they win I
think you can do it oh the house always
wins does it is it actually rigged
against
us what color did you guys do are we
betting I'm betting I'm betting green I
went 500 on Green
500 that's how it goes we lost last time
we'll win this time is is counting
colors the same as counting cards am I
going to get thrown out of here um they
are very small and the B bookie the
bookie can barely see anything so it's
fine you're fine he's not going to be
able to
tell
okay mhm okay red is
out okay very good looking good so
far yes okay it's like a it's so green
it's like a hat it's
yeah an arrow pointing to the
Moon okay and the Moon is very high up
green star to the Moon green green no
green can still do this
5050 green to the Moon do we believe in
it we believe in
green
no it's rigged it's rig it's rigged they
hate us it's
rigged they hate us they hate us
specifically we're like 2/3 green and
they're attacking us for it okay I'm
going to go all in on this last one
I mean we're do we're
do a green
green Green is
do what about red no red is not enter a
number it is a number stupid could be
red though no it could be it's going to
be
green could be all in on red f it could
be oh it's 500
Max okay
okay can't go more than 500 that's
fine
500 how are we going to explain this to
sh and Nissa oh well if we make money we
won't have anything to explain right
true and if we don't if there's like
which won't happen then we can say that
another the team we're burglaring us and
yeah yeah
green
green please green please you don't
understand yep it's green
yep clearly there there can only be
one this time it's a arrow that points
downwards too pointing down because
because you're going down the other
colors my
red wait you went for red
I went all in R oh
[Music]
no no it's not fair it's not it's not
fair blue can't believe they would do
this to us oh
no I'm drowning in the fountain
yellow don't come in the
fountain for this up please
okay I don't have I don't have that much
money left I'm going to I think I'm
going to call it here it's going to be
green this time okay one last it's all
on you f I got I actually believe this
time we're actually
do I'm going all you say last oh how
much is that last time I was wrong this
time we're
do okay because it was yellow last time
it will absolutely be green this time
mhm Okie doie it's all probability
really
yeah I keep for getting my
head I K see we can even go upstairs to
the cannon if we go around here oh can
we tamper with the Cannons I think so
maybe we can talk to it make it so it's
always green we can talk to it very very
you know
enticingly Canon you have to make it
green this time make it green make it
make it green Canon green make it green
green you love green it's the only color
for
you your
love Color of Money color of nature you
love it color of success color of love
if if which is red which is the opposite
of green let's see how this
works color of leaves color of crops of
Life hurry niss is coming color of
everything to
you it's okay we're going to make it all
green green green green green green
green Green okay okay okay it's looking
good you want green that's what you
want listen to your heart I never
doubted the green I never doubted the
green I'm sorry green green green green
green Green yeah
[Music]
never never do I have a th coins oh my
God nice a thousand coins yay okay with
that Victory I think I'm going to go to
sleep oh my memories are coming back to
me it's almost like I have to sleep oh
memories of bedtime memories of bedtime
memories of my comfortable bed with a
pillow that is cool on both sides
M and a mattress that's made of
money s this of money what's my mattress
made of I'll sleep in my hat don't worry
about it never
mind yeah just flip it around and it's
like a sleeping bag sleeping bag
actually it's long enough for that you
look like a you look like a
caterpillar if you turn it around you
caterpillar a like a a pastry like a
cornet do you remember that scene in
Lucky Star where they're talking about
the chocolate which would you eat
it yeah
yeah good questions I accept that it's
like that I believe but it was really
fun thank you for hanging out oh Scarlet
wand Scarlet
one and green team red team oh yeah red
team full of money red is the opposite
of green so it makes sense if you think
about it yeah yeah it's like
complimentary callous so it makes a lot
of sense okay see you guys again for so
we can kill all the stains and destroy
the Dungeons and win and gambling good
night all the money my
M wait can we have like a slogan like a
battle war cry SC
cry Scarlet I don't know any good ones
though
Scarlet wand seek
Scarlet uh wait curiosity and
creativity creative
curious
[Music]
uh wait guys we the creative ones we
have to come up with
something this is a bad look maybe maybe
the other two oh we have to wait for the
others right that wouldn't be nice if we
just yeah that's why we have a lot of
good ideas but we're trying to be
inclusive okay bye on green on
[Applause]
green byebye goodbye everybody good
night good
[Music]
night look I have a
cave I have a cave I have a cave that
was fun I'm really tired I'm so tired I
have a c isn't it cute isn't that so
cute thank you very much for hanging out
with me I know it's not like the usual
time but I was really happy that I was
able to take part in this they they
obviously put in a lot of effort in
preparing it for us and I'm super happy
on that I got to play with everyone and
uh yeah I'll be back soon for I sleep
and uh yeah thank you very much it was
fun it was fun hanging out it was really
cute I think I think the the the the the
dungeon like the castle itself was
really impressive visually so that's
very nice and I learned how to increase
my Renta distance
so okay bye everyone Take Care thank you
very much I'll see you all some probably
tomorrow oh first I have to sleep well
it is technically tomorrow okay byebye
see you this way I want to go this
way look at Sparkles
it's shiny okay
bye Scarlet W that is secretly
green
bye bye bye bye-bye bye
bye bye-bye thank you for hanging out
bye
[Music]