[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
all right everyone welcome to Halloween
cup 2023.
[Music]
[Applause]
all right all right I'm gonna I'm gonna
do a little speech for you guys
it's my second year
all right all right thank you thank you
okay
um as you guys know oh wow this is the
second year of Holo ID card 2023 and I
would like to say thank you to all of
you guys who've been accepting to play
with us and trying all the games that
been setting for this year
um and also
um I would like to say thank you to
ollie and rainy for being the emcee
today
[Applause]
oh
for do a lot of practice so yeah it's
really helpful for me too and well
that's all I just want you guys to have
fun for today
today yay
yes so uh we'll be watching all of you
guys
will be commenting on every one of your
moves
secretly
yeah and after this what do we have
after this rainy
well we're gonna be having a captain
speech from each of the team
so if we can get the leaders to come up
here please
okay
what if I shift shift all right
let's go
[Music]
it will be it will probably be chaos
chaos
and
next we have risu
okay
um
[Music]
so yeah let's let's have fun today
oh
yeah I love our team leader who is risu
thank you I love you too I love birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
we saw the leaders and then it's now
time for the full introduction of each
team we can start with please
[Music]
Amelia from Amelia senpai
hello everybody Emily Watson
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
um
bae
up to you hey do you want to go first oh
okay what's up it's it's me it's it's
big we're red from uh yeah
[Music]
okay
hello everyone I'm Anya let's have fun
today
thank you
[Music]
all right
next would be a girl senpai
[Music]
foreign Generations
okay
[Music]
nice nice nice all right
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you and next it's time for Team
for TV to introduce himself
[Music]
okay
Spirit okay
[Music]
thank you
oh sorry
and next we have Kyla oh hello hi
everyone my name is
[Music]
and Kelly Mommy
let's party I'm energetic Yankee let's
go
real cool yeah thanks I know
next next next we have Kiara
um it's currently 6 A.M
[Music]
and I am gonna be at badminton and
soccer fighter
[Music]
we have Moana
from hololive English Council thank you
for not putting me on the soccer team
it's fun though
what are you participating in for now I
will be in capture the fort and also the
potato sackery
[Music]
okay we have soda Senpai dosa hi hello
hello uh
so why why is it
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yay next Lunas I'm fine
hi
and hi everybody
my name is
thank you thank you
[Music]
and next last but not least we have
coyote
[Music]
um
[Applause]
all right
nice wow
that's four that's all for team for TV
right yes
but you know other than like introducing
the members I kind of want to hear
something more don't you think yeah yeah
everybody come up with their own team
cheers
[Music]
yeah
okay
I'm ready I'm ready
[Music]
so after me I'm gonna start okay okay
okay okay
three two one
oh
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh hi
let's go
[Music]
um
that was so good yeah
let's go
[Music]
let's go let's go okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
two one see candy
oh my God
[Music]
oh my god
well then
see what do we do after this
is okay
okay then wow
[Music]
so the even today
um we're gonna play a lot of games
starting from capture the fort or we
call it bending on and after that we
move to the potato secrets and after
that we go tuck of war and then after
that we have badminton uh from the a
side and then badminton from the B side
and also after that we have soccer and
that's all yay
another is Andy
so that's all I hope you guys having fun
for today
um
now it's
it's time for you guys to uh I think
it's back to the interview
yes right team
okay okay
[Music]
thank you
you guys are so good thank you thank you
oh yes
so we will be participating here
is
yeah
okay
we will be watching closely no pressure
we're watching and you have to win for
us but no pressure
where do you watch it from
good question oh where should we get our
bleachers or there's some seats over
there but this is a nice view actually
okay
we can just walk around I guess
I'm sorry sorry
hello
it's interviewing time
what are you most afraid of of the other
team nothing
is there any special tactics that you're
you know secretly cooking
okay so it seems like they're so ready
for this game
oh awesome
what is your tactic kailashing we we
have
we're gonna pick you win we have secret
tactics that we cannot tell here
you guys will see for it yourselves
right yeah the audience the audience
seems like you guys have secret Secrets
I wish you guys the best of luck okay
thank you yeah
okay goodbye yes
so yeah I will tell fauna in advance
that I I've already I have already told
phone number
this is like three two one
um division
uh-huh the basically one person go to
left and three person go to right yeah
oh okay okay it's just like all
attacking instead
of this game but we believe that we have
remembered the route yes yes
I'll follow you yeah sure sure if if
there if there are mobs just just go
just just run away
accept it
I'm not the Cliffside
okay let's go ready ready I wanna watch
Percy win
yeah ready
how do you feel again in here I forgot Z
I want to see
okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh we start already
but it's okay
they are gamers
[Applause]
ah
foreign
I know
Super Choice
so they were like opening the doors
their strategy
there's strategy like we thought they
wouldn't really use the middle
okay
so
foreign
like I actually remembered the the the
way to the Middle with uh yeah
um
but we were like there's a lot of um
success
Hold On music changed
tactics
we
are interviewing the winner first yeah
oh that's right yeah yeah
okay
um
oh it's getting crazy
Club
yes
there's no NP no HP we can just hit him
don't hold back don't hold back to hit
him all right okay
oh
[Music]
I think the interview is taking longer
than the game itself
[Music]
oh whoopsies that's not what I wanted to
do next is me yes oh my God
on the right
yeah much bigger
tonight let's get the other side
please oh I went to the wrong place
[Music]
thank God for that that would have been
tough
let's go let's go
it's gonna be crazy
oh it's still okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
you guys are great
I'm ready whoa
oh what's up
it's bigger oh my God
the door is opening if you like press on
the on this
cool oh
um
I believe in you
yes
we need to restart
okay okay thank you thank you let's just
run for now I think okay just practice
warm up warming up warming up yes
[Music]
stuck
um
is very fast
okay
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
thank you
yeah
no problem
it's doing really great and I'll try to
keep it up no pressure no pressure
I mean at least as they're like first
and second our teams
what did you do
okay we're ready ready ready ready ready
[Music]
while watching
yeah we're watching for him
foreign
[Music]
because we did really make it clear
beforehand but after this after this
race in the other competitions if there
are connection issues uh I think to also
to make it fair for everybody uh we will
not be restarting uh the competition so
it will just continue yeah thank you so
much just wanted to keep everybody on
the same page thank you and good luck no
problem thank you thank you internet
yeah
okay ready
let's go
nice
[Music]
nice nice
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
one more time
you're doing great
let's go no okay
amazing
come on
[Music]
thank you
let's go
don't worry about it it's okay it's okay
for everyone it's okay you did your best
you guys were fast plus I mean okay we
had the two fastest people though let's
be real so it is
okay
good though you're amazing
I believe yeah
you know what someone in in chat said
three candies nuts oh my God
okay good it was it was oh my God I
shouldn't have read that
I don't know how to explain it in
Japanese man
that was good okay okay okay okay okay
okay
don't forget to hydrate guys
[Music]
what what is after this
thank you
[Applause]
um
I am a very nervous
thank you
wake up
I mean I won't be here
you won't be out there
just thinking about it as like making
making ramen
Ramen yes
oh yeah the other other person
[Music]
thank you yeah yeah let's go oh
no problem
for anyone who wants to watch can go up
so I think everybody's already a boy
oh yeah
oh
um
Hawaii
okay
[Music]
thank you okay
on Monday
I'm gonna do my best I hold my mouse
durability will stay but yeah it's okay
okay this okay let's go this is the time
where I think I hope my mouse can get
like double click what because hey
[Music]
no problem no problem okay wow
finger fingers
[Music]
ready
everybody's
let's go let's go
I don't know
I'm a [\h__\h] forward oh
um
let's go okay where am I okay so let's
go fly we can fly we can't fly yeah
I can't believe
me
[Applause]
no good job I'm not gonna I'm not gonna
lie um I actually thought we were losing
because when I was practicing ah we were
fighting I was red team
the winner go to this I'll explain it I
thought we were losing it okay
[Music]
that kitty cat I hear a mouse
um I thought we were losing actually
because during practice I was red team
so I thought I saw the red go down and
down and I was like oh no we're losing
uh you guys are catching up now it's
like two two one but I feel like you
guys have a chance to actually oh we can
do it we can yeah
for sure how do you feel how do you feel
on winning now
can you believe that you're win right
now um
welcome
I stopped I stopped we still won though
oh you'll be okay
you
[Music]
thank you
thank you we can do it we can win this
[Music]
oh yeah
Kiara and Kyla a bad news
is Kiara back
she was
[\h__\h] is kind of like went somewhere
again
you're a a
[Laughter]
you were so good I was watching you
while I was cooking you should have won
honestly
the fingers you're a legendary
oh yeah you go he also win one the
finger uh competition
yes yes
finger competition oh you can watch that
strap
s
you perfect the back I'll protect the
frogs
[Music]
Yeah ready ready
I'll try to stay calm because otherwise
actually if the clock already the ball
already fell to the ground you can't
actually yeah
we have yeah there's so much
so if you if you feel frustrated just
shout like a real sport
okay ready ready yeah
who has the best
okay okay ready ready guys okay
they could shoot anymore now okay there
we go
oh nice nice Kyla is always the best
backup oh
good job good job good defense
[Applause]
oh
okay ah it's gonna be out is it is
on the other side
don't worry you're doing great you're
doing great
don't worry don't worry don't worry
though don't worry
it's out it's out it's out oh
my God
because it's going towards the wrong
side yeah
oh you have to hit the
[Applause]
floor
for the first hits after the first hit
you can hit wherever you want
I'll take it okay
[Music]
okay
totally winnable
a bit come back
[Music]
that might go out is it out
let's go
again
[Music]
will there be an interview
oh my God please win let's go let's go
let's win this please
[Music]
I believe
it
wasn't ready
okay
wait
yeah
looking good hey okay okay okay okay
don't mind don't mind
do you pass in badminton in real life do
you pass to your teammate
we only can possibly do like one one
okay you cannot pass
ES
let's go away
cool
I'm enjoying this too much
winning feels good
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
we sweep
yeah okay
oh no
yeah they're so good
oh okay it's okay
oh no
all right soccer soccer congratulations
for goal yes go to go shoot yes don't
score an own goal yeah
is everyone playing soccer it's uh six
people
okay yes it's going to be
elephant okay
hmm
OS everyone everyone can shoot
okay shoot
got it
okay also you can uh you can also hit
the ball by your body without actually
clicking with the shoes oh okay
oh okay you can wait by your body
without using the shoes Yeah so
basically shoes is for shooting Aha and
you can like
um dribble dribble is this awesome yeah
dribble right right kind of kick it with
oh with foot okay but not shooting yes
got it okay
got it no problem no problem
the team go team okay we can do it
I believe
it's very tense
it's tied right now oh man yeah
so epic
so I don't have to do I do I just run
into the ball to dribble it or do I
click it
um
like if you if you if you're alone with
the ball you can actually just run over
it okay run toward it okay
foreign
difference and soccer is gonna make the
big difference yeah we are leading but
we still need to win the soccer ball
but the soccer is 20 minutes in total
right wow
and should I maybe try to stay in a
certain area like close to the goal or
so any any I think uh uh uh Kiara and
Kyla
are both great at uh striking right yeah
[Music]
um
much forward while the uh the others can
I think at least one person to stay back
and guard without being yeah somebody
has to stay around the goal like at
least in the area around the goal
otherwise
okay yeah before you'll be okay okay
second goalkeeper
translate in Japanese
like this is just
one that you can actually dribble the
ball without actually clicking oh really
yeah
yeah it helps a lot oh yeah
um
okay
and break after 10 minutes
foreign
[Music]
are we automatically running no no I
think you always have to press
yes my little finger gets tired from it
after a while but yeah because I'm
pressing it nothing's changing so it is
you can jump as well but but but it's
like balls
they sent it out pass it
to your friends
[Music]
don't worry
don't worry don't worry
it was close it's okay it's okay it's
okay
[Music]
okay sometimes it just disappears it is
how much
can she be that close Okay okay
he's just so close down
[Music]
Watson's a really good goalkeeper
we'll see
that joke
okay who is it who is it okay okay
go go go go go go go oh shoot that was
before
okay what does that mean don't worry
okay
right side okay go
there
that's the goal
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go
yeah
okay
okay okay
[Music]
go go go go go
go go
[Music]
what's that
I'll be just staying close too okay
please
oh yeah
the wind
let's go
Jason
[Music]
it's not fast enough
okay oh
ladies
[Music]
and take it to the left too again all
right
okay okay okay we're gonna take it to
the left again go go go go go go go take
it take it okay
is it
okay
[Music]
yeah oh no oh nice enough
okay
nice
stay close I need to stay closer to here
yeah I'm gonna go into the right side
oh
wait where's she gonna okay
come here
I feel like it always goes
okay hey wait hold on
okay
it came back
I don't know if I'm running or not am I
running I I don't know yeah yeah you
feel like you're running I didn't feel
like I am but I'm not holding control
I'm sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
confuse me
oh nice okay oh my goodness
okay
here we go
all right
okay
[Applause]
they're Betty Betty where's the Bowl
here it is let's go this
what the [\h__\h] nice nice
okay
okay let's go come on come on come on
yeah I did I didn't know soccer will be
this oh yeah okay okay
it works
yeah no definitely do that oh that was
that was upon eyes that was a blue night
yes
okay it's okay okay no problem
kick it
no oh okay
oh
it is intense
yeah maybe describe
[Applause]
yeah yeah
I wonder if maybe I should not defend it
I should strike instead no I think it's
good
you're good okay I feel like I'm doing a
bad job no you've been doing this
I don't think we need more defense
though okay because we can because we
can just kick the ball to the front we
don't need like that much of like you
know often we don't need much of the
attackers oh okay defensive yeah so if
we got the ball just kick it okay okay
somebody
yeah
then it might be hard it might be hard
to get points Yeah because sometimes
when the ball finally goes over to like
the goal side I feel like then often
there's like only coyote Senpai there
and nobody's helping yeah I should be
closer to the goal honestly okay
100 because they're winning so we we
really need to be aggressive I think
okay okay
[Music]
um
all right
okay
they were interviewing yeah I think I
need to be more in the session
[Music]
okay
nice nice
um
Empire
[Music]
[Laughter]
very classic
bad weather by the way I really hope I
don't DC oh don't worry it's over soon
just 10 more minutes okay
chill
stop stop
raining
I'm gonna kick them
I wanna I wanna make them stumble
yes and I have a guess
ask us if we have any strategy yeah okay
just just leave it to Lady Luck I guess
maybe there's a miracle comeback yeah
[Music]
um
okay
stronger aggressive everything stronger
let's go
okay
just take a deep breath don't worry
[Music]
okay nice nice
okay
all right get ready ladies here we go
all right
yeah she's really good
um Watson
where is she gonna where is she gonna go
okay
no no no no no no no
no I'm right over my head I wish I could
jump better
I don't know
from there I don't know if we can hear
from them I don't think the rules are
that realistic
it's better to try
um
[Music]
can we just follow her
yeah
careful oh okay okay
it's the goal three versus one okay
nope
[Music]
okay okay
I also still have to turn around every
time they're already looking in the
right direction
you get around the ball oh
man come on
I'm sorry
um
my aggressive the aggressive guy so loud
oh no oh no oh no Kelly Kelly protect me
I'm ready I'm ready
I might go sideways yeah but nah
nah she wants to go okay
it's gonna be tactical about it okay
okay go go go okay
yeah yeah yeah
yeah come on to me what's about amatori
don't we love each other
fun
day
all right nope
[Music]
over here
Watson's too good
[Music]
yeah
oh God oh God
okay okay okay okay
all right
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
all right
um
[Music]
that was close
I don't know what
are you doing
you can do this
so I'm about to come back
tell it protect me Cali all right okay
okay
[Music]
he wants to confuse us
okay
all right ladies we're here we're here
let's go let's go
okay okay
[Music]
laughs
if we can tie with them we just need to
tie with them yeah
I'll be good
no no no no no no no no no okay all
right it's fine it's fine
yeah defense
I'm here
[Music]
okay okay
defense
protect protection
defense defense
[Laughter]
okay
three minutes we can do it one goal per
minute
you never know you never know exactly if
you take it I'm gonna take it okay okay
okay okay
laughs
you'll be doing great absolutely great
okay go
oh my gosh oh my God
oh my God
steal it
oh you gotta steal it nope Callie go go
that was close that was close
extension no like 10 minutes oh
was was a good momentum it was a good
momentum
bolster does fly
it is it's fly still I'm gonna get a
ticket to the left all right there you
go
thank you
nope nope nope nope oh nice
nope nope nope nope nope nope
whatever happens this was a lot of fun
yeah
we killed it at the tug of war though
and the badminton yeah the badminton was
good though the score again the potato
yeah we should have won the potato sack
race but it is what it is
I have the best team me too
[Music]
okay sure
okay
[Applause]
my team is the best
[Music]
one more
we didn't even have penalty penalty
um
at least it was close it wasn't like
they completely destroyed us right yeah
yeah not not like Pokemon unite or
anything like that
um
there was literally do not get gas lit
into thinking that we didn't do well in
that tournament okay
it was great
even though I was watching yours it was
it was really awesome
the whole time
good thank you
[Music]
strong I mean it's a good amazing
we are in the hub yova and Cali also
like good
um what is it
it was awesome
look at our bodies we're all the same
not even wrong
[Music]
the games are just like also so much fun
I really enjoy all the games yeah
I think the map is open until uh
I think somebody says 20 something
something so if everybody wants to try
it by yourself if you want to ask
someone to play with you
definitely Kyla not asking anybody to
I'm still trying to get a friend to play
The Tackle for because I really love
that one my hand is crying
I'll play against you Kyla anytime yeah
you know what we have until uh Kiara we
have to play like two two versus one
like both of us versus Kyla what wait
what
if it's me only
I think I don't have the stamina no no
no
don't worry I can maybe do it alone
again
I will just die but yeah
um
good games
a game and that's done everyone
what's up
when did I look cool yes I was watching
from above
you should have been cheerleading where
are your pom-poms
my heart
you mean in front of your heart
how strong are you now though getting
punched like this yeah
she likes it you sure about that just
like back in the day
pink
[Laughter]
slaps
everybody get spanks
[Laughter]
[Music]
Emma did you play soccer in real life
before or what I have I have oh
that explains everything she was a
soccer player never had a prayer
[Music]
are you announcing your wedding with
someone
amen congratulations
[Laughter]
it was intense and well after all of
those intense game will be announcing
the winners the winner
yeah so first of all from the bending on
the capture the fort
the winner
with 40 points
and then we also have the sack race with
30 points yet again three can you win so
that brings us to a total of 70 points
[Music]
what's the next one the next one was tug
of war
in which it was a blue versus pink team
OMG oh my gosh
[Music]
for how many points
40 points yes
and then badminton again two matches
both won by Purity so 20 plus 20 so
another 40 points for party
so after three candy was leading pretty
we managed to catch up by 10 points and
then that's where soccer came in and
became the deal breaker
Watson too strong and we are happy to
announce that the winner of the whole ID
cup is the
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
that's all
right
I'm a loser
thank you
awarding
oh yes
I sent it please distribute everybody
[Applause]
oh God
yeah this is medal yes
let me see hey what if I just put on the
gold medal anyway
I have access to the gold but maybe I'm
gonna put on the gold no matter where it
is
[Music]
um
my medal now
let's go
thank you
we also got a yoga medal yeah
it's got gold
yeah the pink one is cuter anyway
[Music]
does everybody have their medals
heavy there's a dog show just like the
opening we will be asking for a few
words by each team captain starting from
the teams
[Music]
that was it that was really fun really
really fun and
um
can we do oh can we do the
um the the yellow together again let's
do it again let's do it again let's do
it again yeah yeah okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
everyone did
um everyone did their best doing the
games
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you for playing with us as well
thank you
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
and next we can we have a little bit of
some words from the captain of Timber TV
please foreign
[Music]
yeah
also potato we put a good fight yeah
[Music]
So yeah thank you so much everybody
thank you so much for inviting us so I
thought this year was really fun fun
thank you
next year again please
guys guys guys
okay do you want to do the cheater for
one last time
[Applause]
oh birthday
thank you thank you
[Applause]
lastly
a picture
everyone go into the podium please
[Music]
ladies
yay
three two one
[Music]
it's okay thank you
look look at me look at me okay okay uh
okay okay
[Music]
I don't
okay okay
[Music]
good time
wanna take separate team pictures you
guys can do it now in your own free time
it's fine okay
[Music]
ah nice hello hi it is
yes
where should we go for the picture
[Music]
one of the balloons the ships yeah
teach us how to fly in Minecraft wow yes
and what I can't get the
okay it's been updated to creative mode
my hands are a little strong
ER
light
to get into the uh
oh
sorry it's okay it's okay it's okay
all right
[Music]
um
it's so pretty
[Music]
are you taking
um
I'm flying all right let's go let's get
in the dragon in the dragon dragon's
mouth and [\h__\h] yeah there we go
dragon's eyebrows
yeah a dragon's head pool
foreign
yeah okay okay you you can watch the
screen on yeah I see yeah okay
so please make sure that I'm in the
middle so I can get like a better oh
okay
[Music]
can go in front
of us
too far right yeah
we can go a little bit
name
oh hi okay
this works this works this one's nice
this one is nice
okay okay got one okay two
um
everybody
everybody look up how um
perfect
perfect please
get my good side
okay okay I think it's done
okay I will send it
thank you
I want to see what's in this ship this
ship is cool oh yeah yeah
wow
and the other one I don't remember the
other one
wow I'm an explorer
wait I'm gonna send the pictures
[Music]
I wonder when the Japan
sports festival is
there should be an announcement about
that Japanese
yeah yeah I got it okay I need I need to
close my stream first okay wait was it
invitations
[Music]
okay so everybody
thank you so much for watching everybody
and thank you so much for
uh supporting Timber TV
foreign
[Music]
thank you so much hopefully we can
improve uh a lot of things if if we
actually have
um another cup next year so please
support everybody support hello ID
support hello Yen and also support whole
life uh members JP as well so thank you
so much
20 23
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]