every blueprint shows a Supply Closet
here but H guess that tipser wasn't
scamming me I guess they hat did
spontaneously relocate here 001 is
food oh theor hat okay thought it' be
foodless had is a food now pretty sure
it's not but I never know what the kids
are eating these days hang on is that
a it is that a nest made of plastic bags
oh my God I found it kp's research
division must be losing their minds when
they see H actually that does explain
the hallucination
reports wait a minute that sound I've
heard it before there's no way it'd be
from that project right I wonder if kfp
is so interested could hat means oh hat
tree I get it now no manufact address
rank a uniform budget it don't make
sense now they not buying hats they're
waiting for them to hatch we
just oh my God why is this so and the
recordings from Project Yi
v153 hatching process that's what this
is oh God I hate this
place un 001 file just flying away round
know it's it's strange why why are all
these files in such weird places K if
you really that
sloppy yeah probably actually know think
about it but what if someone wanted me
to find
these making so much noise they're going
to come up here and find me oh
man
hey
hey hey little
one I forgot about you too huh
I'm so
sorry just be a good girl and keep your
flame burning bright
okay everything's going to be just
fine you think a lost bird can still
find home even after forgetting the
way I hope so for both our sakes
[Music]