[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
Gather at the venue  To all of you,
let's start streaming!
Our first large-scale event,
Hololive Super Expo 2022, started
at 10 o'clock a while ago, and a large number of
customers have finally arrived.
Thank you very much to everyone.
Yesterday, the weather took a turn for the worse,
but it turned out to be a beautiful sunny day.  It's a great day for an event.
Well, it's me. My name is
Nana Noguchi and I'm
here today. Thank you very much.  I'm
sure
everyone is enjoying the atmosphere of the venue, and I
was able to enjoy the venue early, but I was already excited to see all the
talent's
costumes.
Sorry, I
often see the upper half of my body when I stream, so
sometimes my whole body comes out, but when I
thought that I could see her full body and in real life, I was like,
wow, that size.
Even though I thought about it, I got really excited, and I
also saw the area where the office was recreated, and I was already
looking at the whiteboard and saying things like medicine,
and that was
just visible from the tea ceremony stage.
However, everyone has already gone to that life-sized panel corner.
How about that
? Yes, there are a lot of
entertainers
hanging out there too, so I feel like I can't give up anymore.  I've been really excited
since this morning,
so I said yes.This
is Makuhari Messe, where various projects are going on.However, I'm
sure you've all been very excited since the morning.It's great to
see you all here.
Thank you, thank you,
and to all of you who have been watching the latest version,
thank you for being with us since this morning.It
's true.Everywhere you
look, it's all Hololive.It's so
detailed,
even the staff members are so passionate about it.
In this space,
we will be holding a kagami biraki ceremony to commemorate
your prosperity and the success
of Hololive Super Expo 2022.We will
hold a kagami biraki ceremony before each big event.
Everyone who is watching the broadcast, please join us. Let's celebrate
together the great success of these two wonderful days.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much. Let's get excited
.
First of all, I would like to introduce the people who will be
witnessing this event.
First of all,
Mr. Mikonamin, please
take the stage.
[Music]
Yes, it's okay. Everyone,
let's go at our own pace.
[Music]  This
is a character created by Miko Sakura, a 0th generation member of Hololive.
[Music] Take
your time. Yes,
everyone. Let's
proceed with the event safely.
Next up,
Subaru Cup.  He
's so cute when he's toddling around! He
came up with a light swish.
Marunouchi-san
is a character that was created during the activities of Hololive 2nd generation Subaru Ozora.
Next up is Ahn-kim.
Mr. is a character from Hololive 0 Toki Sora.  It
's a character that was born during our activities.
Yes, he's doing his best.
Next,
Mr. Udin, please talk to us. Brother,
slowly,
yes, Uri-san, Corona Ins.  This
is a character that was created during the activities of Crazy Onii-san, a 2nd generation member of Indonesia.And Mr.
Small Am, please take the stage.
[Music]
Mr. is a character that was
created during the activities of Hololive English Wreath Watson Amelia.Yes, you
are full of energy.And finally, the
organizer.  On behalf of the organizers, I
am Mototeru Tanigo, President and Representative Director of Cover Co., Ltd.
[Music] I will
be welcomed by a big doctor.
Thank you very much.
Well then, I would like to
represent the organizers of Kagami Biraki, President and
Representative Director of Cover Co., Ltd.
Motoaki Tanigo, the organizer representative, will give a greeting.
From now on, I
will call you Mr. Yago, so
please understand. Thank you very much.
Hello everyone.
Everyone gathered at the venue.
Thank you for the broadcast.  Dear viewers,
Thank you very much for coming to Hololive Super Expo 2022 today. I would like to
thank all the talents and partner companies for being able to hold this event safely today.
On behalf of everyone at the cooperative company and all the cover staff, I
would like to express my sincere gratitude to everyone who watched.
When Hololive started four years ago, we never
thought we would be able to hold such a big event.  We are
very happy to be able to hold an event for fans of Hololive and Follow Stars as Coronaine Productions. We will
continue to have our employees give up their time and collaborate with the recording company to
hold events that will please the fans.  If you have to  I
hope
you enjoy the 2-day Coro Live Super Expo 2022 from today.
Thank you very much.
Now,
let's move on to Kagami-biraki. The
fish used in Kagami-biraki yesterday
were provided by Mail Type Co.,
Ltd. Meiji Mainstream Stock  Thank you very much to the company.
Now, I would like
to perform the Kagami biraki ceremony. On
behalf of the organizers, I will be covering the Kagami biraki ceremony. Mr. Yagyo, President and Representative Director of
Co., Ltd.,
will officiate the Kagami biraki ceremony.
Please have fun with all the characters. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Lego. Now,
let's take a look at Kagami Biraki. I hope that
everyone involved in Hololive Super Expo 2022
has a great time.  We will hold Kagami Biraki in our hearts as we pray that the two-day event will be held safely and successfully,
and that
good health will spread from Makuhari Messe to all over the world.  If
you are watching online, please feel free to sing along in the comments.
Well then, after this, I
will call out to you, so if
you are watching the broadcast, please leave a comment.
As for everyone,
unfortunately I can't speak today, so I'd like to
ask you to shout out ``Yoisho'' from the bottom of your heart. I
hope you'll get excited with some applause as well. I hope
all the characters are okay too.
Is everyone okay too?  To
all the visitors, are you
ready?
OK, thank you very much. Now let's
go.
Thank you very much for the dream in the middle of the light.
[Music]
2 days long.
Ini.
Now, we will have a theater and have a Kagami Biraki ceremony.  We would like to
conclude this session. Thank you very much to everyone in attendance.
From now on, it will be time for the Goto session.
Now, members of the media,
please follow the instructions of the staff.
Please come to the moving area for the photo shoot.
[Music] We
are currently preparing for the photo session. We are looking at
time availability for individual requests. We
will respond to your request, so
please send us your request.
Please wait for a moment as we adjust our position.
[Music]
All of you who are visiting
will also be joining us from the PR department, but we
would also like to take this opportunity to take a commemorative photo with you.
Well then.  Are
you ready? Yes,
everyone who is consulting, please look at the center first.
3. Please smile.
[Music]
Ah, if there are any people who need individual eye contact, please
raise your hand and let us know.
Any
pose?  Do you
have any specifications?
Is it okay?
Yes, we're going to have a great time over the next two days. We
're currently holding an original session here.
Please raise your hand and
look at us.
Yes, please turn to this side.
Everyone, I would like to
ask you to look towards the right side as you look at me.
Yes, thank you.
[Music]
Yes,
that's the end of the photo session. If you
'd like, please look a little further back.  Is
that alright?
To all the speakers, please wave your hands to those on the left.
[Music]
Yes, everyone on the left. Let's get excited. Is it
about time?
Next,
there may be people on the right side watching the movie, so
please move your hands limply. Is
everyone okay?
Finally, please move to the center. Yes,
everyone watching the broadcast, please do so.
Please use the hashtag Connect Hololive Rain 1 and share your screenshots.With
that, we'll
conclude the photo session.Thank
you very much.Okay, that's all for now.Thank you
for your patience.This is the
end of this ceremony.
Thank you very much to all the speakers.
Please continue to enjoy Hololive Super
Expo 2022.
Thank you very much
[Music]
Weiss Schwarz
Hololive Production's booster
pack
won't stop Weiss Schwarz
Booster Pack
Hololive Production Now
on sale
[  Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, Chugai Kogyo
Contents for those who love anime.A cafe that collaborates with anime that
plans and develops anime goods and sells them on the Internet.  We
also have the latest information on Twitter
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
Everyone who came to Hora Live Third Festival, are you
having fun?
[Music]
I think
so.
[Music]
Our project is about to start.
So the
project we're going to do now is to
connect photos and make a picture
MC.  I'm Mel Yozora, who is in charge of this project, and
these are the three people who will be taking on the challenge of this project.In
order, please introduce yourself and the contents of the photos you have taken recently.Hello
hello
[Music]
Regulation of virtual robots.
It's Roboco. The
photos I took recently are a lot of Ai-neko's cha-cha. It
's
nice. [Music] It's so cute. I take pictures right away, like when she gets on the futon. It's so cute.
[Music]
Next time, Nenechi.  Please, yes,
this is Orange-san who came to the live show, and I
'm Momo Shizune, an idol Vtuber.The most recent photo I took is one I
remember of a hot pot called Mama.Recently  It's
cold,
so let's take a look at the last one, Button-chan. The
photos I've taken recently are hmmm.
When I looked back, all I saw were pictures of food.
Thank you.
[Laughter]
[Music]
So I'm going to connect these pictures together and the picture
story will
be displayed randomly. 4  It's a game
where you create a story on the spot based on a set of photos.
[Music]
It seems difficult, but I guess it's okay. It's difficult. The
person who can create the story with the most unusual ending will be the winner.
Well, first of all, let's try it first.  as  The person I'm
going to take
is Roboko-chan. OK, show me Japan. Roboko-
senpai.
Let's have some fun.
Good luck. Hmm. Good luck. Now, please
make the four photos that will be displayed into one story. Is
that okay? It's okay. What kind of photos should I
take?  I'm sure it's coming.
Then
start.
[Music]
That's where
my
future lies.
Wait for me, princess. I'm
having fun. You
said you're a princess anyway, so why
don't you wait for me to be a princess?
I'm going to go there on foot.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Before I knew it, it seemed like I'd made friends. There must be a lot of these kids out there. That doesn't
mean they have friends.
[Music] That's
delicious. I
wonder who you are.
Apparently he ate too many cookies and
became tiny. It's the
same problem he had before he became tiny. It's disgusting
. Ah, this person seems to have
eaten too many cookies and become a bit
sick.
[Music] It's starting around his
neck.  I was about to give him a
massage to get the cookie out,
but
the two of us were doing it.
[Music]
Before I knew it, I had
turned into a dog. Wow,
Cookie.
What's that all about?
I'm so happy to have met my husband now.
Wow
[Music] It
's still the beginning, so everyone is
like, ``It's hard to get into it.'' It's because I
don't understand it, right?
That's what I was saying.  I
guess it's like Megane-kun. [Music] [Laughs] How do you feel about it? It
was a good response. But as I was thinking about the story in episode 3, I realized that he was
n't acting like that sick man at all.  When I realized it was a massage, I
rushed forward, wondering what to do.I
wondered why they were trying to get air into my mouth when it tasted so good, so I
used acupressure to
push it out.Next
time,
Nenechi.Okay.  The
world is pretty amazing, too.
[Music]
Please, let's
start.
[Music]
I'm the man
in front of you in the middle of this intersection.
Today, I'm
going on a journey to find lunch on foot,
right?  Hey, I
wonder where my lunch is. I wonder where it is.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Where the hell did I put it
?
Where is it? I have lunch too. It's
been a while and my stomach and back are starting to stick together.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Wait, wait, lunch.
Hey, you're hungry.
Be my lunch.
[Music] Are you a
red panda?
Red. Is
there somewhere to
eat? Eating, eating.  I'm eating this
[Music] It looks
delicious
[Music] I
summarized this on my trip to find lunch.
I see. In the end, I was trying to eat panda.
[Music]  Up
to the
3rd one, yeah, it was definitely pretty. [Music] That's right. It would have been nice if the red panda came on the third one. That's
for sure.
[Music]
[Music] I
wonder what it is. It's
probably soothing.  It's a
good thing to have animal power. It's true that this and
that is not a flag.
My last
animal Let's try to predict the animals that might come.
[Music] It's
Button-chan, so I'll do my best.
work
New Researcher Because I
'm in a white room, I'm always busy showing off my work
,
but I can't say it's great to be here, but I'm living a pretty good
life.I
think
[Music] I've
seen something.  There's money inside the microscope. It's
a secret. I was told to keep it a secret,
but it seems that a new type of bacteria that turns people into zombies has been
discovered. The
higher ups told me to keep this a secret.
We can't do anything because we're being told
When I heard about it, I got a little worried. I
wondered if I could run a company like this.I thought it was a very good company, but
when people called me zombies, I didn't really
understand it, so I
ran away.  I
think it's true, but
if a biohazard was born in a laboratory,
I might be the first to die.I
handed my resignation to my boss and
quit the company.I'm
starting to feel black from today onwards.  I'm all free
After all,
Hall's Zabi is amazing. That's how I
became a backpacker and a person who travels all over the world. It's amazing. After all,
every day is boring.
That's what I thought
from the beginning, so this daily life is quite boring.  I get a good salary
and live a decent life.
[Music]
Freedom is the best thing for me, so I
don't know if there will be zombies, but I
'm thinking of living a leisurely life like this for a while.
End
[Laughs] I can't put
together all the great photos. [Music] [Music] It's a special festival, so it's going to end with a bad ending. [Music] It looks like there are still more pictures, so we can do one more round. Eh, the seniors are showing us a lot of good things.  I
want to see your seniors
[Music] It's
okay, Mel-chan, you
can do it. Show me your story.
Okay, let's do it.
We are black.
That's who we are. That's
what we are.
Inside the company.
I don't think it's possible that a woman named White is using white hair,
but black bullets are using black hair, and she has to
add black flowers and roses.I wonder if
White is competing with her.It's really impossible
.  [Laughs] I
wonder why it's white.
This is White, the traitor of the Black group.
This is the culprit behind everything. This is White's stag beetle, the
stag beetle,
this white thing that even Black is trying to crush.
This is a smooth floor.
As expected, we have to be black.
All kinds of colors have come out.
Blackdown is black, but this is
us.
Yes, it's
White. The white
woman turned into this lightning and now she's living in it.
Yes, she's been turned into an ability. That's right, she's
no longer a human. She's not a human anymore.
She's been made normal.  Okay, okay
We, the Black Team, will
continue to live in the darkness. There
have been quite a few white people.
[Music]
Pretending to be a black bullet, there has already been one
gray original from the beginning. There is no white problem.
Betray me.
Gray is gray, after all.
In the second round, I feel like I want to see everyone's world again
.
I want to do it first, okay.
Next time, it's Botan-chan. Are you
ready?
[Music]
What's this?
What's this? What's this?
This is an old inn at the foot of the mountain.This is a small inn that provides rooms for tourists who come to climb the mountain
without meals,
but it
was bustling with climbers every day.One
day, it was a
secret...  We need to increase the size of this inn soon.For
that purpose, we need to
add tools and
make the inn bigger.Now, we
are talking about the behind-the-scenes of the inn.  The
owner of the inn
called Shishido Kogyo and
decided to have the back of the inn renovated. He thought this would make it easier for
inn guests coming to the mountains to use the facility. [
Music]
Here I come!
[Music]
One day, a dog
came down from the top of the mountain
to the foot of the mountain and left something in his mouth.  It's
okay, that
[music] I wonder if
it was the dog that was caught by the tourist who climbed the mountain. It's neck is already there. Maybe it's the
person you're talking to?
Give the dog something to contact us.  I was doing
tension exercises at the inn
because I thought that if there was an incident that I was worried about, I had to act quickly.It
was an incident, after all.Please
help me.One day, a
very big
typhoon hit directly.  The
mountain was blown away, and the
inn
was all washed away by the typhoon, but
the dog had brought it all at that time, and the
tube he had in his mouth
was a long thing he had brought with him for long throws.I managed to
get it out on the ground, and somehow the tension
survived.  After all,
there are good things to be done to be kind to animals.
And I was
excited to rebuild the rope inn all over again. Ah, I
understand.
[Music]
It's okay next time, I'm at a dead end.
The dog was probably a messenger from the mountains
.
[Music]
Hey, he
left me there.
[Music]
OK
Yes,
I'm
23 years old. Yes, my
hobbies.
Fighting
Today, I'm
training hard to kick and
defeat my opponent.I'm training to
defeat this guy, and I'm sure I can defeat him tomorrow.It seems like
he's training me.  Grandmother
If it looks like it's going to be
dangerous, then we'll have to hold our guns and practice. Hey, we were supposed to fight here, but I guess
I've lost my mind again.
No, no, no, here, here,
here.  That must be right. I'm a
heartless 10. I've grown up and become like a person, but I'm
growing up. I'm a
grown 20.
[Music]  It
looks like the old lady and the old man
got lost.
Are you here?
Sweets.
I was
supposed to be bulky, but when I
noticed it,
Summer
Yoshi
turned into a cat-legged man. That's
weird. He might have a bit of a bad eye. Hey, please put on your
glasses.
Wow,
the world is so dazzling today too.
[Music]
[Music] We
need to create a story with animals in mind from the beginning.
Yeah, that's right. The
direct probability is that it's a dog and a cat. I'll go with that pattern.
Okay then, let's go to the final Nenechi story.
[Music]
Look, it wasn't there. Don't look anymore.
Hurry up and squeeze my dick.  Hey, I'm
really hungry.
Wait, I'm going to squeeze it right now. Wait a minute.
There's nothing there.
[Music] There
's something on the way down.
[Music]
If this continues, I'll fall.  I'm
imagining it
[Music]
Help me, sweet
potato
[Music]
One day,
hey, this is the newest powdered milk these days
[Music] The
first 50,000 yen
It's so colorful Let's
bathe it with our whole body Take
temporary preparations for our whole body
[Music]
This
[Music] It's
not about milk, it's about
infiltration
[Music]
But it was number one after all.  I'm glad I
predicted it.
Today's episode is
good, but there are two different animals.
Who are they
?
[Music]
From now on, it's night. I
want to decide on this picture story queen.
[Music]
Who is it? Who is it?  This
[Music] The
most amazing
story I created
was Nenechi's Hungry Lunch Man.
Yay, I
don't count this one. Yes,
everyone should give it a try. It
was fun.
[Music] Well
then, everyone.
Please continue to enjoy the cat's live third festival
[Music]
Good Day Tour Cherry
Swarkunz
[Music]
Hello, my name is Calliope Molly, and I'm bitter. Thank you very much. Don't let it
hit your skin. Good morning, hello,
good evening.  Thank you very much for your support today.
Hello everyone
[Music]
Hello everyone. I'm the
president of KFP and the manager of Kitchen Live English.
Chiara Takanashi is said to
be a shark.
[Music]
It's fun
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Laughter] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
I see, I see
Carrie
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Music
]
[Music  ]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
[
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Laughter]
[
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Laughter] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause]
[  Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
Dice Schwarz
Hololive Production's booster
pack
won't stop Weiss Schwarz
Booster Pack Holo
Live Production Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, I love anime  Nachugai Kogyo We
plan and develop anime goods that people want to enjoy content adventures and anime, and
sell them on the Internet.We collaborate with anime and have
done things in the past.For the latest information, please visit
Twitter
[Music]
Everyone coming to Hololive Super Expo 2022
[Music] I'm Kanata
Amane, a member of the 4th generation of Hololive, who will be the host of this program.
Thank you for your support.
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Laughs]
I'm here.  Introducing the performers. First of all, I
'm Kara, the
world's strongest idol Aten
Hunt
[Music]
And 3
[Music] I
'm Flare, who I don't know about from the first generation. I don't talk too much, so it's kind of
weird.  I
had a cough. Thank you.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I do
n't really understand Japanese, but
when I read the atmosphere, it
seemed easy to understand. Thank you.
This program will be presented by these four people.
Thank you for your support until the end.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Hololive Super Export 2022 Are you
enjoying it?
So, it's just the
four of us, but of course it's our first time together.  I
wonder if there's something we all have in common when we watch TV shows and talk.Everyone
in this world was
crazy.It's funny because there's only one person who is.
However, I do
n't see much in common, but
as we work together today,
I'd like to find out.So, it's time
to start planning a little bit today.Thank
you.
So, let's do a challenge for these four people.
[Music]
Okay, now I'm going to ask you all to try out Sam
while you're on your own and
compete to see how many challenges you can complete in 3 minutes. [
Music]
Complete the most challenges.  The
challenge holder is the one who completes the challenge.
Everyone
understands. Did you understand the rules?
Okay. Well, first of all, let's take a look at what kind of challenge there is.
Okay, let's
go. Check this out. Here we
go!
[Music]  ]
[Laughs]
Challenge to sort by talent debut
Maximum 10 seconds on the clock Make
3 other people laugh 3 tongue
twisters in a row without chewing
[Music] The
3 people who will disappear don't know
Trivia challenge This was great Catfish
My brother is a genius
Good luck!
[Laughs] We're
going to have you compete to see how many of these six things you can accomplish in three minutes.
How about you? Everyone, I think I'm
pretty good at it.  I know it
seems absurd, but I
always do the bus gag.
[Laughs] It
makes us laugh. It's
funny. It's
like that after my seniors. But hey,
are you all ready? Let's take
on the challenge right away.  Let's go.
[Music] Well
then, let's talk about who will take on the challenge. You
could decide by playing rock, paper, scissors, or
I'd be the candidate, but I'd
like to decide properly.
[Music] I'm
here. The closer you
get to the end, the more disadvantageous you are.
Hey,
[Music]
[Music] Are there any
earthquakes?
Even if it doesn't happen much, I
'm going to do it as much as I can. I
love you,
Flair-senpai's
challenge. Well then.
Start
[Music] My
body clock is exactly 10 seconds long. I guess I'm the one who started this one
myself. It
seems like I'll get the same start here, so I'm going to go.
[Music]  I
wonder if I can interrupt you with this? Hey, hey, hey, it's not coming soon. [Music] What do you think? Okay. [Music] [Applause] [Music] I'm still going. A tongue twister is a tongue twister. Please give me a tongue twister.
Grilled ribs, grilled ribs.  Grilled short ribs
[applause]
This is
strong, strong,
scene knowledge that the other three people don't know.Challenge:
Which is better, mushrooms or bamboo shoots
?Maybe not everyone knows this.  I
think everyone should know a little bit about this
[Music]
Do your best, do your best
[Laughs]
There are quite a
few. Hmm, hey.
Challenge to sort by talent debut. Yeah,
first name
Experience Straight
line
Choco-sensei
Um
[Music]  ]
Here, there are two challenges for Flare-senpai. I was
only able to do the first two.
Trivia I thought everyone didn't know. Which one I
like.  I
thought everyone didn't know about it, but I
did it.It's completely blank,
but I'm happy about it, and I don't want to make a fuss about
it.However, in the last three minutes, I'm getting quite anxious.  Well,
please think about it.
Well, next time, we'll do House for the last time. Well then,
at the head of the genius shop
[Music]
Do you have confidence, brother?
Not at all. You
talk a lot.
For those of you who don't want to go,
I'd like you to do it.Introducing Grandpa.Okay, then I'd
like a 10-second debut version.If you bring it first, you can do it.Iroha-
chan,
okay.[Music]Then, wow.
[Music]
Next is
Mameshi, please.
[Music]
huh?
Well, OK was
actually a
misspelling of all correct. That's so
funny.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Next,
uhm.
Mathematics right away, yes, 30 seconds. I'm
smart.
What's 7 and 7
?
Um,
791, right
? 10
[Music]
Second challenge
[Music] It
's starting. I've been
waiting quite a while [
Music]
[Music]
[  [Laughter]
I'll do my best.
3 times 3
times It's
Inu Nature Chin, but for now, yes.
[Laughs]
[Music]
First
place.
How was it, brother? It
was difficult, after all.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
Well, Heartsuma will be the one to decorate the last part, but
how about having confidence? Well,
you're also responsible for the management, right?
[Music]
[Music] Let's
start,
please. People of all ages,
men and women, young and old.
[Music]
Please challenge for 130 seconds.
[Music] You're
cool this time.
100%
[Music]
Please, please.
[Laughter]
[Music] Do you have any
trivia about apprentices other than yourself?
[Music]
Well, the green onions are ready. Do you know why they're no longer spicy?
That's it, stop it!
Listed in order of talent debut.  Please challenge me to change it. It's
terrible. I'm a little worried that I'll make a mistake. It
's easy.
[Music]
Erm
,
Gura-chan
[Music]
Wait for my brother's face.
That's a lie Wait a little longer
Surprisingly
[laughter] It's
difficult to do this when it comes to turns Well, it's not
good enough
[Music] I got
one shot to make three people laugh I never thought I'd
do it all That's
a lie
Wait a minute One shot to make three people laugh  Well, that's a
challenge.
Good luck,
Gorilla. I'm not a gorilla. I
want to go there for the first time in a while.
[Music]
[Laughter]
You
[Music] It
was interesting
[Music]  I
agree with you.
[Music]
[Laughter]
I did it too, but I thought it was
time for me to hang it on someone else.
[Music] No, we
were all just small fry.  Well
then,
[Music],
please
[Music] You're so
funny, you
seem to be good at it.
Let's get started.
[Music] I've
been battling an illness.
[Music]
This is
it.
[Music]
Here it
is.
[Applause] I'm
a little nervous about this.
Actually,
[Music]
First of all.  We've
found the finalist, let's move on to the next one.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Please give me more.
[Music]
Oh no, this is all that's left. But I'm sure
everyone will laugh.
[Music]
[Applause]
[  music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] Thank
God that it's over.
[Music] So out of all the cats, who has
completed the most challenges?
[Music] -
Thank you very much.  So,
to the challenge holder
[Music]
Please let me know how you feel now based on the results.
But you're smart after all. You
should do it.
[Laughs]
Thank you very
much.
Congratulations.
Thank you. Here's the main announcement.
[Music]
Weiss Schwarz Premium
Booster Hololive Production
is now on sale as part of the Hololive Super Expo 2022 goods. This includes Pro Live 0th
generation, Forox, and Solo Live
Indonesia.  Contains cards from
more than 50 talents, including Solo Live English talents. Be sure to
get at least 1 of them! You'll definitely get 1
of them
! At Card & Creative
Flag Out, Hakusho Cards will also be on display.
We are currently selling
card binders and
acrylic card stands.We also sell supply products that can be used with cards. [Music] We are selling card binders and acrylic card stands at the local booth.You
can store your favorite cards neatly.  It's
going to come off.
[Music] So, in
addition to the products I mentioned earlier, the
50+ sleeves,
deck holder set, acrylic holder, and
rubber mat that are included in the booster pack are on sale.
Everyone, please take a look.
[Music]
Yes.  then behind  Click
here to introduce the product
Holive Super Expo 2022
Training
Recognize it
Volume 1 to Volume 77
[Music]
[Applause]
More than 60 talents are
introducing the product
currently being broadcast on Hibiki Radio Station.
From Hololive Presents V's Sconro Plate
using the key visual
of the radio Acrylic star
[Music] - I
like it, it feels like this radio is being recorded.
Plate acrylic stand is 2,800 yenB
Nitabe The
products I introduced are
available at official merchandise stores and mail order.Please
buy them.
[Music] I'm
starting to get a little angry when I say "Please," but
this
program is also good.  So that's it for the cat people.Full
Live Super Expon 202
23 people.Now let's
go to the end of the show and say hello.Then we'll be talking to
Kanata Amane and Mr.
Red Foods.  It
was a play dish with a flare I didn't know.
[Applause]
[Music]
Bye
Wow, I
can see you all,
Hola Live  Hello to all of you who are coming to Super Expo 2022
and to
everyone who is watching this stream.This
is IKEA Lamy from Gokise, and yes,
this is Shishiro Button, who is coming to this live show.Makuhari
[Laughs]
Well then, in this program,
for those who can't come to the venue,
we at Shishikori would like to show you what the venue was like.
Today, I'm not a fan, but I'm
sending all my office information to the expo,
so it's got this kind of ah
[music]
feel to it.It
seems like they're going to a Buddhist altar over there.That's how it
feels.  I'm
in a state where I'm moving. Everyone, please go to Makuhari and look for something.
Yes, I'll go here.
So, first of all, today, I
see there is a tweet that was solicited in advance.  I'd like to introduce some of them.
So, will you be there? [Music] Thank you very much. [Music] A two-shot with Kanatan and Kanatan. Of course, that's not true, but I guess that's true.  I
guess they took the picture together using an app. I
guess it's Korori or Calorie.
Eh, it's
so cute. You can play like this,
actually. When I was
looking at the tweets, I
saw some people doing it with babbles and such. Well, let's see.  I'll
take a closer look at it later.Yes, let's take a look at it.Click
here for the next tweet.Yes,
what is this?If you look again, it's probably because there are
too many goods.When you
buy goods, what and how many pieces do you buy?  It
seems like they want it,
so please give it to them in advance. I
see. I wonder how much it costs. I think they
have about 4 sheets of A3 A4a paper. It seems like there's a
lot of excitement about the merchandise sales as well.
Thank you for buying it.
[Music]
So here's the next tweet.
Oh,
Mr. Showman, this is me,
Hollow Alternative
[laughter]  You
can actually take pictures of those carrots that appeared in the scene
with Senpai. It's not a horse-drawn carriage, but more like a cart. Let's
GO let's GO.
There's something like this
[Music]
Well then, let's take a look.Next, that
's Yukimi.Although I'm a
professional controller, I
definitely wanted to take a two-shot with Larry as a memento of today.I
didn't hide Lamy-chan from the unfamiliar operation.3
But it's okay. Anyway, it's still cool. Please
read it.
There's a purikura, right? You can
get some kind of stickers there. There's
all sorts of Horror Live's original items.
There's also others besides Rami-chan that you can get forements. I'm sure
there are various members.  I'll
probably check back later if someone tweets something about this,
so I decided to take a photo, so
thank you very much.  Let's
go see what's going on
here. It's a
deserted place. There's nothing here, so let's
take a look. I'm going to show you around the various places in Makuhari with my eyes wide open, and the staff member will take a moment to
put the camera in the storage room.  I'll probably be carrying various boosts with me,
so
if you're worried about being seen, please be careful.If you
cover your face, you'll
wander around,
so the staff will be visiting various places at the end.  I do
n't want to be seen right now, so please let me
go to the manager. If
you can do it with a face like this, I'd
be happy if you could do it, please.
Yes,
wait a minute.  I'm working on various articles today,
but
are there any booths that I'm curious about? Well, I
might have made a remark about the court [laughter], but I'm
just wondering about the booth staff.  I'm
going to ask you to go there and I'll explain it there.
There's a courthouse.
Everyone, please look forward to it. It's a
fun
place. Isn't it the same place
? Well, that courthouse is a booth with Marami and
Shishiro. Which one would you like to
participate in?  Well, let's
talk about that a little later. How do you feel about it? I heard the
divine voice of the Ama Ne staff, and the
broadcast will be connected soon, so let's
take a look.
[Music]
Looking at the comments on the stream, it's nice. Yeah, I
can also see the comments on the stream, so the
comments on the stream are also visible to Lamy and the others.
So, everyone who's watching, what's up? I'm ready. Let's go.
Amazing, amazing Sui-chan and Azuki-senpai are also
here.  This is it, it's changing smoothly. See you
there. It's amazing. I'm so tired. It's so exciting.
It's a huge monument.
Life Spikespo 2022 is huge. The
monument is really big. I'm standing here.  I
want to take a photo. That's
amazing. So if we wait, maybe we'll show up too.
There's a possibility. It's
amazing. This time, if the staff at the scene were
a little more persistent,
we might still be able to do this.  Because it's Gamers, I
thought it was a long way off, but it's even
further.The
staff's aggressive camera work,
but
it's really the booth.The venue
is huge, wide, wide.Makuhari
itself is a bit big, but Makuhari  The
message itself is still pretty
big.The
monument itself is probably huge.I
think that's probably true.When you actually see it, it's
amazing.There are people who think it's big.Everyone,
everyone
[Music] I wonder
if they can hear your voice.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well, that's all for now, and now we're in the 3rd season.
Well, I
guess I'm a little
drunk now.  Why do
n't you just wait a little longer? Once the 4th season comes, you'll already be able to wait. I'm sorry, but please wait a little longer. I'll
come.
So next time, there will
be more ways to enjoy it, like [music] [music] [music]  So,
6th graders,
thank you, thank you very much. Hey, what's
going on here? I have a feeling there's going to be a guest.
Who is that? Who is that? They've been
taken away. They've
come to the courthouse.  Is that
wrong? These are 2 of them, Danie-san and
Mikotania-san. They're so
cute. They
come here all the time for quite a few events.
After getting a taste of them, I feel like they've become a bit popular. They're
cute, too. I don't know if they'll be popular,
but I'm sure.  There were other characters this time as well,
which means I wonder if they'll
come or not.
From the court.
Why? My
brother's mascot character.
This is Ame-chan, right?
And finally, Anki
[Music]
Is this Hololive? It's
gotten so naughty
[Music]
Oh, you're
pretty aggressive. You just
won't jump.
[Music]
Everyone's posing like this.  I wonder if
there's a specific pose? It's refreshing Nico
Danie
Rico Danie is so cute, Udin-chan
[Music]
When I saw this at the scene, it was
okay to take pictures. It's okay to take pictures of this.  I heard that it's
okay, so
please take a picture if you like.
[Music] It's
cute.
Well, someday, my Daifuku will be
like this. You should feel like an old man. He doesn't have anything. Eh, that's
right.
[Music]
Maybe, like a smartphone.  There's a chance that you're watching the broadcast
.
Today, after I watched the broadcast a little bit, there
was a small child in attendance. He
was so loved.
Wow, I guess I'm happy that we're being recognized by a lot of people. I'm so happy.
Thank you very much. Thank you, everyone.
Well, we've been so excited from the beginning, but I wonder if it's
okay. So I'm looking forward to it. I hope I
can't think of anything after this.  Let's move on.
[Music]
[Laughter] You're
getting used to it, you're getting used to it, and then it explodes.
So, without further ado, let's
take a look at the booth.
So, first of all.
Let's go to the place where Lamy and Cecilon are curious.
[Laughs] I
think both the people watching the stream and the people in real life will be curious. Hey,
why do these two keep going to the courthouse?
[Music]
See you,
staff.  I
heard that the
fan club is going to be renewed.The
fan club has died.It's
right next to the entrance.Is
this really nice?
Just say it  It
looks like a Kanananda festival venue, and this is the
courthouse.
Yes, this is the place.
Members of Hololive are
appearing as the plaintiff and the defendant, respectively.
For those who came to the booth as the plaintiff and the defendant.  This
is an event where you become a member of the jury, listen to both sides, and make a fair judgment as to whether the person is guilty or not guilty.Whether it's the plaintiff or the defendant, it's on behalf of the person being sued.
[Music]  It's easy to get sued if you
come here and get sued. I'm
looking forward to seeing who gets sued, so please take a look. I
participated in it that day. I was
hooked. Now,
please be innocent. Please take a look inside.
Who are you doing this with right now?
It's your teacher, it's Choco-sensei. Which one is this? Which one is the
one who complained about the change with a slightly angry look on their face?
This is the
one who changed it. I wonder what this is probably telling them.  I
'm curious. She has a
really cute face and is angry, but now she
listens to both sides and
says, "I'm innocent." That button means that fate will part.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Please be innocent.  Thank you very much. I
hope everyone, including those who are currently on trial, enjoy it.
Oh, I see
. This is amazing. It looks like it's been made quite seriously.
Thank you for the surprise.
No, but I'm glad that so many people lined up. I'm
glad. Let's go to the next booth. The
next booth is
nextto Jean. I
can see something.
Over there is a
holo-fortune-telling
hall. You
can't even tell fortunes.  That's right. This is it.
Hololive members act as fortune tellers and
predict the fortunes of everyone who visits.
As you answer the questions, the fortune teller will tell you your personality.
Maybe he'll give you some advice to improve your future fortunes.This is
it.I wonder if it'll show up now.It seems like the
ghost side will
appear randomly, but there's a room.It's been quite a
few days.I wonder how many there are, maybe 1235 or 5.  It
's so random that you can't really tell who's going to come out with all kinds of follower faces.Who's
Poloporo?
PorupariI
can hear it
.
[Laughs]
In the case of a robot personality, it's called a fortune-telling house.  It seems like you have a
senior, but
if you don't have one, I think you'll come out the other way. Hey,
this person who's been separated from you will
become more honest. Which one are you? Which one are you? Are
you the
type who can't be honest? Ah, it's
okay.  I saw this person's
okay, I'm
sorry. I couldn't do it. I'm sorry. I'm
going to go in now. Yes, it's next. There
are a lot of questions like this. Is it
yes or
not? Who is it?  I wonder what it's like. I'm
so excited. I'm so excited. The various followers will tell me my fortune. [Music
]
Looks like it's going to be fun. [Music] Hey, I want you to do it. I want you to do it. You
made a choice, right? At home, it'll
come out again.  I guess that means the holo surface
will change, so the answer
will change, but the answer will also change.
Please everyone, local people, please play and
check it out.
[Music] Well
then, let's go to the next booth.
[Music]
Where's next? This is an error booth that is familiar to both of us.
Please explain this.
Yes, this is
Aogami High School, the setting of that story. It's a
wooden school building.  We have
prepared a variety of exhibits, including life-size panels of the characters from the play, and even the
latest information that can only be seen here.
There isn't.
Is there any latest information that you can't see here?Here we are at a booth where everyone can
become transfer students and enjoy the world of Hololive Error.Hello,
what's the latest information
here?  I know I said it, but
now it's just for the fun of those who are visiting the booth,
so
please everyone. It
was a one-one-one ship. It was amazing. You couldn't have been more
hospitable than a high school student.
All of the things that weren't popular are a little bit like that. It's
written here, but it
's that old school building in Cicillon. It's from the past. It's
amazing. The set is also amazing. It's
extremely hypnotic. Ah, everyone.
[Music] Is that the
notebook that was left behind?  There was something left there. I
left it there. I wonder if it's okay. There's a
wall that's really crumbling down, and I remember it. It's terrible. I
remember it, and I'm apologizing. There
's also a key. Oh, that's amazing.  I
can see something, so I wonder if this is a secret.Yes,
maybe this is the latest information.It
looks like an amazing notebook,but
[Music] I
wonder if it's something people who have been doing well can enjoy.It might be fun.This is
amazing.It
makes me feel nostalgic about the system.  But in Naru Shishiron, you
see, Kaname plays a character called Fukami C.
But Makoto's school building is also a
character that appears, so it
's nostalgic.  He's
not really smiling. No matter how you look at it, he's
having fun. Enjoying history. It
doesn't look like he's having a lot of fun, right
? This is a bit like what you're thinking right now.
Maybe it's information about these two. There
are new possibilities.
Yes, Miima is quite a mysterious person, so it's
amazing. It's amazing. The outside of this is quite elaborate.
This looks
like a hallway. Look, look, look, my
senior
took
it. I wonder
what's going to happen.  The
clothes of the present day and those of the past are very different. So, I wonder if
there is anything amazing about it. Hey
everyone, let's go to the next one. OK,
next time. It seems that
all the Hololive talent's
costumes are on display.
Well, what do you mean, it's all of us
? All of us were stripped of our costumes.The
staff told
us that we weren't going to go home today, we didn't have the strength,
so we're wearing idol costumes right now.It's
true.
Hey, Ramy and the others will be able to wear those clothes the day after tomorrow.
I see. I wonder if I'll be able to go home today. I'll take this train today and go home. It'll be a little noticeable. [Music] People will ask me if I'm Chihiro-san. They'll ask me that.  Dero: I
can't say it's different, so
it's different.
[Music]
Everyone's so friendly. It's amazing. From the beginning, we're
all in a group. We're going to the camera.
People who don't show up are a little careful.
As I said, everyone was very active.
Thank you for waving your hand. I'm
happy,
but
here it is.
Hololive Productions'
realistic reproduction of the costumes of all the talents was the most important thing. Yes, we paid attention to the
design of the costumes until the very end.  I heard that you can see the
hippie stabbed clothes on display right now.It's so
cool.It's so
outrageous.Well, you can see it
from a little further away.  I
thought I might be able to smell the smell of the hood, so I guess my senpai
has already taken off her clothes.  The
cat is
tall, and from the looks of it, the cat's
body lines are probably quite long.The
recall rate is high, and if you ask me, it's true.I'm
sure this is a robot contest senior.
Even Roboco-senpai was able to show me his legs and stuff,
and I was
like, Wow, he
made it all the way to the end. He
left me out.
[Laughs] I
mean, he usually wears things like this. I
want to take a closer look at this one. Yeah, I'm alone.  I think
it's a pretty fun corner even if you take a close look at Neko-senpai alone.
It's Kitten-senpai's sudden costume, so Neko-senpai is probably safe.
Well, she's
safe. I'm glad I can go home wearing the new one.  I
think she's wearing her usual clothes.
[Music] It's
amazing. All her parts are so
beautiful.
Even the way she stands is a bit
[ __ ]. I
think everyone is
paying close attention to it. Her waist is a little tight like this.
Azuki-senpai is so cute.If you
ask me the truth, everyone looks
a little different.Even
Mel-senpai, who I think is very particular about her poses,
can almost see her skin.
This doesn't work, it doesn't work.
[Music]
Good.
Hmm, good. If you
look at Hachama like this, the
design of the skirt is really cute. It's
quite detailed. It's so
small, I didn't notice it until I
looked at it properly.  I noticed that the
upper half of my body is often shown in broadcasts, so I
don't think I'm interested in looking at the lower half of my body, but I think it would
be fun to see a lot of different things.
[Music]  The tails are
all attached, right?
Well, the tails are
coming out, too. So, I have a spare tail
for today.
Ah, this senpai is cute too. The
new hot spring bomb is so cute. It's
behind Ayabe-senpai.  The Nosa ribbon isn't great.
This is amazing. The
three-dimensional effect is really amazing. Hey, it's also easy to see how tall he is. Yeah,
Choco-sensei's chest isn't that great.  I
have a senior who lives next to me, so it's
a bit unnecessary,
but if you look at this, you'll understand that it's
really impressive.What's the
height of the side end of this chest?It's
amazing that it had to be recreated like that.You
can almost see it.  I
can almost hear you saying that voice.Kismarisen
is
healthy.Well, it
's healthy.
Okay, I
couldn't see Luka-san.
[Music]
That means
Neko Labo. That
's nice. Everyone's watching. They
also
have EL and ID.
[Music]
Marin-senpai's 3rd generation is also there.
Mecha 6  There are some new students too,
and
when I look closely at Yama-chan, I
see how tall he is. It's amazing how small he is when lined up like this. Yeah, if you look at him, he's probably tall.
Oh, it's expensive because 3 people are relatively expensive at Nepo Lab.
That's right, that's
right. That's right. It's
cool. It
's a pirate. This is amazing. It
feels like the usual, usual, usual clothes.
[Music] Let's
take a closer look.  Don't lose your vocabulary.
This is great. The mace and other
weapons are included.
I'm going to fight. It's
so well designed. It's
amazing. It's
amazing.  I'm going to
watch it for a while, but if you're in Makuhari, I
definitely want you to see it.I really want you to see it.There are
costumes for all of Hololive Production's talents on display, so I
think it's going to be a lot of fun.
[Laughs] The
feathers are red.
Ah
[Music]
-
Come on. When they came, they
missed us and took them.
Oh, that's terrible. A little
later. A little later. A little later.
What's the matter?
Is it the same with my master? That's a bit devious.
Wow. If you look at it from the side, you'll see that.
But it's Ram-chan. What do you mean? It's Ram-chan who's
always looking at me. That's right.
Don't do that camera work.
[Laughs]  The
one next to her is Nene, she has an idol feel and
is so cute.  The
clothes you see are so fluffy and the skirts are so fluffy, so it's
really nice. [Music] The clothes have a lot of ribbons, so they look girly. They're really cute.
And the sides are white.
[Laughs]
Take them off.  Well, you made me take my clothes off. That's
amazing. I took my clothes off. It's okay. It's torn in
one place. There's one more place. That's why
. When I get back, I might have been drunk.  If I
don't look at it properly, even after looking at it, I can still feel the way he's standing. It's
amazing. Thank you. The balance of his body is really white. The way his legs are bent, the four-letter words for his body. But it's okay, cc.  I've got a spare, so
what's the situation? It's
not that oil, isn't it
? Isn't your chest a bit bigger than usual?
Well, I guess it's a bit
more of that. Omar seems to be holding it down a bit, so I see.
But it's over.
So,
when do I feel it, but then I don't know? Hmm, I
feel like it's already happened a little bit, so I'll do it again. It's
okay, it's a beckoning cat,
so it's okay. Well, I guess it's
because there are will castles next to it. Well, it's
a little bit. The
contrast is inevitable.  We lined up next to each other. They're
all so voluminous. Yeah,
wait, they're really
small, so I
can't mess them up anymore.
[Laughs]
Because they're
amazing, aren't they?
It's so fluffy. Your reproduction skills are amazing. I want you to show me a little bit. Reine-chan's this and this. The cart. The cart. It's amazing. The skirt and the chest. It looks like a flower. It's amazing. A little bit of this.  It would be helpful if you could lift it up. Oh,
this is this. This three-dimensional effect is
amazing. It's
amazing.
[Music] A
wonderful enemy.
Even my brother is wearing a skirt. It's
amazing.  They
're all so amazing! Look, this one
really feels like Reine-chan, too. It's so
expensive, you know. It's true. It gives off a really worn-out look. It gives off a zombie feeling. Wow, it's so cute.
[Music]
Nice! That's
amazing.
Ri  It's so cute.The
tail is there.The cat is a Korox.Iroha-chan.It's
amazing.There are enough for
everyone.There are enough of
them.There they
are.It's
amazing.  She's
pretty tall, I guess.
Chloe-chan and Lapu-Lapu-chan are
really
small. Maybe she's the older sister. It's
amazing. I was able to recreate that thing on Lapu-chan's neck. I'm
sure it's
not a chain though.  What should I say
?These are
n't handcuffs, but they're kind of big.
[Laughs]
Handcuffs around your neck.
Big, big,
big. What do you call that?  I
just don't get it, but it's amazing,
everyone, Chorui-chan is
just right. It's okay, it's
amazing, it's
amazing. When Holo
shows,
even newcomers get their costumes ripped off, and they
fight because they're fighting, so they
decorate it, so Hololive is tough. This
amazing side
killed them.  Maybe it's on display, so they're all
set up already.
It's really a fun booth with the costumes of the talent on display.
Everyone please take a look.
[Music]
Well, after this, I'm going to
go to the next one. It looks like I can go to the next booth, so I see.
Let's go. Let's go.
Next time, I guess
this is probably the
Hololive
Alternative
booth.  That's right, I saw the photo earlier. Are you going to
get some carrots? Let's
go over there for a second.
[Music]
Oh, wow, wow, wow, that's the Holo
Live Alternative booth.
This is the Nemaa Different World Creation Project's booth.  It
expresses the world of Hololance, which is the setting for the story of Hololive Alternative. I
see. Please come and see that space. This is a
booth specially designed for the event, so
please take a moment to enjoy it.
Have fun! The
girl was doing it right now. It's
Asora Senpai. [Music] It's a really big carrot. It's big. I hope you
enjoy it. You can't take pictures. Please be careful and
watch your skirt.
Good luck
[laughter]
Now that I think about it, Pecola-senpai, it's
amazing that she's carrying something so big. It must have been difficult. She
was carrying it with great force and seemed to be having fun.
But in the cat's
PV, she
was carrying boxes and boxes.  I'm a little curious about the future of Nitako and
Hololive Alternative.The
number of followers seems to have increased recently,
and I'm really curious about the progress of Hololive Alternative.
Yes, personally, I'm really
interested in alternatives,
so I get it, so it's a bit...
[Music]
That's it. I heard that there will
be a Hololive ID booth next. I guess
this is it. There are so many different booths. It's
amazing. There are so many different booths.  Yes, it's
amazing. It's starting to show up.
This is Kololive Indonesia's
bootstruck.
[Music]
Yeah. Looking back on the history of Hololive ID. It
's a history chart, and it's a
traditional Indonesian game.
Gardening It
means that you can experience Rec Engelik. Acting skills Yes. There are
many exhibits where you can enjoy the world view of Hol Live ID and the atmosphere of Indonesia.
Games What kind of game is
Engelic Engelic
What kind of game is Engelik Engelik?  I think it's the
one in the back. It's amazing.
This is
Engelic. I don't know how to play. How do I play? This is Engelic. Even so, I
'm playing by asking the monitor in front of me.  So yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.  It
's like, okay, I'm skipping to the
next one, and I'm going to skip to the next one,
and it's amazing, it's a sandy beach.  I
'm curious though. It looks like it's going to be
fun. It's amazing.
[Music]
It's so
cool. It's so amazing. The
temperature is amazing. It's really amazing. It
feels like an explosion. It's like this. It
's the Indonesian atmosphere. Yeah, yeah, that's it. It's
a little bit like that. It's always with JP.  I'm wondering
if I can experience a slightly different atmosphere.What's that? That's what I'm
curious about, that Lamy.This
time, there's that bento.The bento is
n't just Hololive's JP.
ID's
[Music]
Oh, that's right. It's pretty
much like a cat inside. It's
amazing that it has such an Indonesian feel. It
looked delicious, so I
want to eat it.
[Music]
Here it is.  The weapons held by Nema EL1 students are
being completely reproduced in seconds and are on display.Also, there's a
photo shoot where you can take pictures that will make you feel like you're in the DN member's cat distribution screen.
Apparently there's a pot too, so be sure to take
a photo of it.And it looks like something like that.Guru-chan's, that's that, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, it's typical of the University of Tokyo.They have figurines, right?  Please take a photo.
It's so cute. Don't
step on it. [Laughs] You're stepping on it.
Wow, that's amazing. That
thing in the back
is the mini 3D one. I wonder
if I can take a photo there.  I ca
n't take a
photo. I like the photo spot. From today on, you ca
n't even get a Hololive en. I want to see the amazing weapons. I want to see them. I want to see the weapons. Ahh, this is amazing. I wonder if this is Kari-chan's. Crab-chan and Hina-chan's obi are properly attached.  Hmm,
this is really scary, isn't it?
If you were forced to do this, you'd be pretty scared.
[Music] It looks like a
TV drama will be made. I wonder
what it's
like. I originally wrote that this book was amazing, right?  You
've ranked up. That's
amazing.
It's a pretty detailed weapon like this. I think I'm looking for one that also has things. It's
cute. It's
amazing. There
's also an Osami-chan one. It's quite a
shark. It's a doggy. When you think about it, it's
huge. When you look at it from this perspective, it's that small.  It
means you have this in your body, right? That's
amazing. It's so well made. [Music] So
cute.
There's also Abu-nee-chan.
Kiyora-chan's illustrations are so cute
.
Everyone's A is good Everyone's A is really good It's
not like I can write and become an artist. I can't do it. It's
cute. It's
cute
. I like it. I want to take a picture. I'll
put it in one of the en machines. I'll
put it in all at once.  Is
it just an illusion? You can become a member by taking a photo with me. I
like this 1:11 life-size figure. I
really want to see this. You might
want to see it here.  Only a little  I
can't see the cat's costume, so
I can see how the cat's height is, but the
figure feels even more realistic than the cat
.
[Laughs] She's so
cute. She's amazing. She
looks like my girlfriend.  You can do that!
Seriously,
instead of Touhou Boyfriend Zura, you
can do Horizontal Boyfriend Zura. Just
do it like this on one side of the heart. Only one side does this.  That's
nice
[Music]
If you share it on Twitter, I
think we'll all go see Foromega
again.Okay, okay.What are we going to do?  The
fact that we're in a booth means that we can be seen,
reflected, and
ah, that's amazing. The fog is
narrowing down. Yes, we're humidifying. It
means we're not taking any kind measures.
Everyone should take care of their throats.I
want to take a look at the
food as well.There were some people who had several bento boxes, but
this time they
are selling 5 types of bento boxes.I'm
sure there are a lot of people who bought 5 types of bento boxes.  I
think there are 1st,
2nd, 3rd, 4th, and
Hololive Indonesia lunch boxes.
Nepo Lab's 5th generation
has something called Blue Cracker Drink
[Music]
[Music] I've
really had lots of cookies and drinks
.
I see, it's very popular, thank you.
Everyone, there
might have been something like this too.
What's up with the prince?  Was it delicious? Please
share your company and information on Twitter. I
would be happy if you could give it to me.
Hey
everyone, I don't like it, but looking at the lunch box
makes me hungry. I ate lunch earlier,
so yeah.
And what you can see in the back is a
rest booth like this,
where you can eat that bento, etc.Everyone
likes it.
[Music]
[Music] [
Laughter] [
Music]
But I think I can hear your voice, so that's right. I'm eating my lunch right now. I've
been watching a lot of Bethel, so let's
all eat slowly. It was delicious. We all
look alike, and we're
eating heartily.
Oh, everyone's eating it. I wonder if it was delicious.
So, is it here?
Nami. [Laughs] [Music] It's everyone. Thank you for showing us. That's
amazing. They
come in droves.
Thank you.
[Music]
Fox jays are also here.
[Music]  [Music]
Isn't
it a festival where everyone has so much love?
[Music]
That's why this is
not the event stage.
[Music]
Speaking of broadcasts like this.
Shishiro Yes, it
's a call and
response that can only be seen at an event.This is Coleland. Thank you, everyone. Yes, everyone. Yes, I'd like to do a call and response with everyone who's watching this Meetel. I really
think so, but it's not like a shout-out.
Or can't we
all raise our hands? So what's the point?
Why do
n't we play rock, paper,
scissors? It's like if you beat Shishiro, something good will
happen today.
I think I'd like to play rock, paper, scissors with Shiron.Then,
Shushuron, I'm going to bring out the goo.I'm out.I'm going to bring out the goo.I'm going to
bring out the goo.I'm going to bring out the goo.It seems like I'm going to
bring out the goo, please.I'm going to bring out the goo.I'm begging you, I'm going to bring out the goo.I'm begging you,
so Tellamy will shout.So, leader, please put your hand out.
-'s Rock,
Paper, Scissors Po - Ah, everyone purges with a piano heart
[Music] Don't
trample on everyone's hearts, but
believe in the goo The person who made that par is this sea  The
person who read the secret and gave a punch has won,
so let's have another battle between the winner and Iko.It depends on you.Let's go
ahead and make it to the final round.Then
I'll
give you the signal, please.Okay, let's do it.  You're
doing this because you're heartbroken, but I'm heartbroken, but do you even think about it? At first, I was a goo. Rock, paper, scissors-chan, a goo person. A goo person or a savings person. Congratulations to the person in front of me. Congratulations.
Now, both times now, there are a lot of people on their own
. It
's true. Illian is there. You're lucky. Let's use the final boss Shishiru button. Let's make
full use of the final boss. See you then. I'll
give you a scissor.
[Music] The
white button is a scissor.  It seems like everyone is
giving a par by pretending to make a goo.
This is a psychological game. So let's move on.
At first it's a goo. It's a rock, paper,
scissors pawn. I did a good job of
making a punch at the end. Hey.  I
tried to make my heart hurt, so
congratulations, congratulations, everyone today.
Good things happen to everyone, both the winners and Aiko, and the losers. I'll
leave it as something that can't be helped.
Ah,
thank you everyone. So yeah.  It's
almost time for today's broadcast to
come to an end.However,
the booths that we weren't able to introduce today will
be introduced tomorrow as well, so please look forward to it!  I
want you to
see the office. I
certainly want you to see that. I
want you to see how busy that office is right now. I want you to see it.
Oh yeah, we're saying goodbye. I understand. It's
sad.
This Live Super Expo 2022.
Huh?  There's more to come, so let's
get excited from now on.
[Music]
Well then,
thank you everyone. The
reporters
were Shishiro Botan and Lamy Yuukihara.
[Music]
[
Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
Everyone who comes to this Live Third Festival
Enjoy Hololive Third Festival  Are you
having fun
? Our project is about to begin.
So, the project we're going to do now
is Hololive enemy press conference rehearsal. Yeah, I guess that's right, but it
's a little sudden, but it's a bit like Hololive.
To all the superstars who will be responsible for a little bit of the future, thank you very much for coming here today. Don't be too picky. I've warned all the superstars that
someday you'll be holding a press conference or
something like that.
Hey, today we're going to have a rehearsal for this press conference,
and we're going to have a rehearsal for this event.It
's on stage, but we're going to
do a rehearsal for the press conference.It's extravagant.It's the best thing I've
ever been asked.
I would like to ask you to introduce yourself and
ask me some questions that you are having trouble with. But what is that? Well, I would like to ask Mr. Fubuki for a
second. Hello everyone, I would like to ask you to introduce yourself to me and ask me some
questions. Hello everyone, I would like to ask you to introduce yourself to me and ask me some questions that you are having trouble with.  I'm
sure you think we're in trouble right now. I didn't expect you to send me a message like this. The three of us were together so suddenly. It's strange and that's what's bothering me the most. [Music] Please, please. Yes.  I
'm a comet, a vtuber who's burning the raw stone of tomorrow.The
most difficult question I've received so far is
something that made me laugh out loud recently.
[Music] I
often get asked questions like surveys, but
that's why I've been laughing so hard lately.
By the way, at
that time, I
laughed out loud
because I was laughing out loud. I don't laugh out loud anymore, so I wish you would stop. Please
stop it.  I'd like to say
no to the question.
Please say yes and thank me. Thank you for saying yes. I'm a
butler from the 4th generation of Hololive.
Tsunamaki is no good.
Yes, yes. What bothers me when people ask me this question is, after all, when is the next 3-day holiday? When is the next 3-day holiday?
[Laughs] That's
true.
[Music] Well,
okay, but please be careful about your health and
have fun streaming.
Thank you. Today's rehearsal
was just to answer some questions.  It's
boring, so each of the three of us is the Prime Minister of the Kakujiki White God Country, but they tried to do what they wanted. [Laughs] What's wrong with that? As the host, what do you think? [Laughs] Hoshi pretends to be that Prime Minister who is late.  I
would like you to hold a press conference.As the
Prime Minister, I would like you to answer questions as fluently as possible and
without hesitation.
If you're stuck like this, you wo
n't be able to get a sense of who you are, so
answer the questions fluently,
keep a cool face,
and
leave a famous quote.I've set the bar high for you.Okay, first of all, yes, I'm sure you've
made all the preparations.  I
would like to do my best,
risking my life. Mr. Watabe, who is often forced to risk his life on official programs,
thank you very much.
And everyone on the train.
Fubuki-san and Sui-chan are on the train.These
two journalists are a bit scary,
but
as long as time allows, please
ask some tough questions.Okay,
first of all,
Tsunamaki, the prime minister of the square-wrapped country.  Mr. Watame's press
conference begins.
Are there any reporters who have questions? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes,
what kind of country do you want to turn your country into now that you're inaugurated as prime minister?
Awesome.
Well,
what are we going to do?
After all, we know that the number of sheep will increase, so
food is not important after all.
Wait a minute.
Establishment By the way, does that country
have a lot of sheep? Well, they
almost look like sheep.  But, are
there a lot of sheep girls and boys?
That's
right.
By the way, what kind of law do you want to make
in that sheep country?
Lawyer:
Don't sleep, there are so many
[music]  Isn't it
true that when you count sheep, they go to sleep, but they don't? Isn't that right? After all, it's dangerous that they keep running all the time trying to get them to sleep.Are they the country's sheep?  That's right. The
Prime Minister says he's not a sheep. By the way, in one word,
what kind of country is this? Yes, yes, yes, but
what kind of place is
this?
To put it simply, it tastes good. Is
there a possibility that it will be eaten up when the Prime Minister changes?
Sorry.
[Laughs] Is
there anyone you would like to be your secretary? Or a minister, or someone you would like to consult with.  I do
n't have anything to do, but do you have any plans
? Eh, I'd like you to play Sui-chan.
By the way, the money is a bit negotiable, but I
'll buy it for how much money I like.
Then
500 yen a month, 500 yen,
no, no, no, I'll give you a little bit of a train. I
want to know your motto. I guess I'll have to try it, Prime Minister.
[Laughs] That's
amazing.
By the way, what is it that Victory wants to do now? I
want to do it.  I'd
like to have a second live performance.Prime
Minister: Yes, there
will be a live performance at this event, so
let's do our best here as well.
[Music]
Yeah, but let's talk about another minister.
Yeah, that's great. Let's do our best.
The same goes for this third festival. The
fashion is strong.
So it's almost
time for the press conference. The accounting is over.
[Laughs]
So I tried it.
What do you think? Both the person being
attacked and the person asking the question were in Europe, which was quite intense, but how was it for the two people asking the question? Well, it was interesting because you can ask anything you want.
Hey, no.  It was
interesting. Mr. Watame, who has been attacked so much, looks a bit like he's done it, but no... It's difficult. [Laughs] I know what you're saying, but it's contradictory. But you're too kind, and I think you're a bit like the prime minister. Dame-chan.  Hey
[Music]
Next,
I would like to ask Mr. Fubuki, the Prime Minister of Shirakami-kuni, but I don't think I can do it,
but he seems like a prime minister.
Now, the press conference by Prime Minister Shirakami of Shirakami Province will begin.
Please give me a message.
Is it a
message? I understand the message. Well,
my fellow citizens, let's
continue to push for good health today.
Is this the prime minister's recommendation?  Of course,
you guys are idols.What
are the people?
For the Prime Minister, the people are just
horses.The more
the people
flirt with each other, the more
power the Prime Minister gains.
What kind of people are there in the
people of Shirakami-goku? The people of Shirakami-goku are full of unique people.
Various attributes,
comics,
girls are okay, boys are okay,
ita. The
combination
is the Prime Minister's favorite combination.  That's right, the
Prime Minister's favorite combination is the thing he mentioned earlier
called Minori, and the
lovey-dovey cell phone of an older sister and a cute girl,
is that correct?  It
's also my boom.Do you
have any recommendations?Reporters, you have
n't taken the
course.[Music]Even if you take the course, that call over there is
still coming in.Yes, that reporter over there
is watching because of the pay.
Waki-tei is already justice,
justice, right? I heard that they also collect the idol's oppe mouse
pad.
It's from 10 a.m. to 10 p.m.
What does the Prime Minister do on his days off?  What
I try to do is play my favorite games and watch anime. It looks
fun. By the way,
what kind of work do you plan to do in the future?
Well, first of all, I heard that you're
thinking of dividing it into underground areas.  I
think there are various types of people who just want to become idols. I see. There are people who are adventurers,
there are people who are fantasy-type people, and
there are people who are okay with it. Well, I think there are people who want to be idols.
Which district will the Prime Minister be assigned to?In
that case,
of course you'll be in the idol district.Cool and
cute
idols.Are you really attracted to the job of Prime Minister
Sorry?The Prime Minister is right.Of
course you can do whatever you want after all.
[Music]
Hmm.
So, the
press conference is about to end.
By the way,
Tsunami.
Yes, where is that? I guess it's
an operation zone. I
wonder if it's okay. [Music]
What should we name the shop? A
Mr. Dame, who was assigned to the district, asked me
right away. I see. What should we do? What should we name the shop?
Bye. We
have a lot of side cups. It's
probably the one with a sign. It's okay. The
shop staff.  Doesn't it look like a castle or something? From
the looks of it, does
n't it look
like a pea castle? It's
fine, it's fine. Yes, it's
over, but what about that reporter this time
?  It's a form of acquisition.
Prime Minister Shirakami: I guess there
wasn't enough room for scale,
and we
ended up creating a country with two journalists. This is quite a feat. I was
thinking of putting out a little more rags, but it's not quite right.
Akagi's ideals are high.  That's a bit to be
expected, but what do you think of the Prime Minister?
Were you free at all? Well, you're
free now. It's a wonderful gathering
of games, anime, manga, and any genre that has released your desires.  I
heard that it wasn't going to become a country. It's a
completely happy island. I'm
sure everyone in the venue right now is
probably thinking that they've put us in the [Music] district.
Well,
in the Hololive district among idols.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. It was a wonderful press conference.
And finally, you were quite good as a reporter,
but what about you as the Prime Minister?
Sui-chan, okay. I feel like being a
reporter is my calling.
Even though I'm a mom, I feel like I have a strong defense, so I'm
really looking forward to it. I'm
going to solidify my skills. Now then, Prime
Minister Hoshimochi Koku Comet's press conference will begin.
[Music]
Hello everyone.
Thank you very much. Here's what's next.
Question time.  I'm thinking of taking the program, so if
anyone knows, please let me know.
[Music]
What's the appeal of the job of rating viewership? It's not so much an
appeal as it is supporting the people of Japan.
What kind of things do you want to do to do your best
? First of all, you lose your morning.
[Laughs]
Is that so? Isn't that okay
? Is there only night?
Does that mean that you live without sleeping? That means you
live at night 24 hours a day.  It's just that the sun doesn't rise.
No problem. Yes, that's the kind of country we are. Yes, that's
right.
What are you doing now?
On your days off, that's right.
In our country, we only come here at night, so I just
lie down.  I'm
sure you've put in a lot of effort since becoming Prime Minister, but have you
ever felt like you've failed? That sounds like a
joke.
Well, up until I became Prime Minister, this country was completely
destroyed.
It was the power of the chan who helped me get
started in the mornings, and it was the same for me, too.
Well, she wouldn't let me go to work before 3pm, and then I'd
be late because I had to work before 3pm.
And so on.
[Music] I
think that by doing it at night, everyone will be able to spend a more peaceful time.I see, I
see, I see.I see.I see.I see.It's
true, but it's understandable.My
physical health is fine if I only spend the night at night.
Well, it's true that health is important,
and I think that's what everyone is saying. Well, we're
currently developing the latest technology.  Looks
pretty cool  It
's rice that grows in the moonlight.It's
suspicious, but I'm curious.What
color is it?What color is it?It's
blue.It's blue.It's
rice, yes.Does it
mean you have no appetite?
How do you spend your nights?The
people of Japan
work for about 3 hours and sleep for about 3 hours.  Or doing something you like,
or taking a bath. That's
great.
By cutting it to 3 hours, you're actually more efficient.
[Music]
That's really good. It's scientific.
There is a basis for this, and it is said that it is better to work
in a short period of time instead of lazing around for a long time.Well, that's
right, a doctor has said that.Who
is this?
Koyori White Coat.That's
also the person who turned off the sun.  He's a bit younger,
but he's more of a doctor than a kid. That's
amazing. It
seems like it took a pretty huge budget, but I wonder if the
finances are okay. He was
doing it, so
by the way, if you
let a doctor do it in that white coat hut.
What are you going to make me do? That's
funny.Next, I
'll have you win the lottery.
[Laughs]
What kind of shops do you recommend here? Kao:
Are there any shops you recommend? In
fact, there certainly are.  Is there any money?
[Music] There's no
poisonous substance
[Laughter]
Well,
it's Hoshimachi Park after all.
What's there? Well,
our country has already given up the
super idol star
Machi Comet.  The
fact that there are scattered stars nearby
seems fun, right?
[Music] It
's an area where you can be chased by comets. That's
right. It
's a stage where comets sing. There are
plenty of greetings, and I see, there's
even a parade.  It's fun, but I'm
doing it alone, so it's very difficult. I'm doing it alone.
Accounting is over.
[Music]
This seems like a pretty fun development.
But at the end, Park came out and it
was a bit difficult for me to be managing it all by myself.It's
so black.Let's
increase it afterward.Yes,
everyone who has been in such wonderful health,
please give us your impressions one by one.First of all,
that part of the story.  Thank you.
Hmm, it was fun. I
don't get asked questions like this very often, so I
'm sure it's not like this. Isn't it like this reporter?
Don't you have a lot of fun?
Even with the first customers.  Please leave a comment
Please, thank you for watching.
Thank you. Why don't you become a butler too? Please become a
sheep when you live.
Thank you.
Since we are able to build a new country
, I would like to borrow the help of Coro Live.
Thank you very
much. I hope you will continue to support us. And
Prime Minister Fubuki's speech
? Well, my country is a utopia after all.
As expected, I'm thinking that the child will live in a utopia,
but it's not
okay to be too naughty, so in
that case, the death penalty is the death penalty.Ah, that's
beautiful.That's right,
Kitakami's arbitrary and deformed
sales.  I see. I see. I
see.
Survival rate
[Music]
Schwarz
Hololive Production's Booster
Pack Even the pack
doesn't stop Weiss Schwarz
Booster Pack Holo
Live Production Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, I love anime, Chugai Kogyo.I
plan and develop anime goods that I want to enjoy anime as a content adventure, and
sell them on the internet.I collaborate with anime
and do things in the past.For the latest information, check out
Twitter [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[  Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
'm sweating and tired of that pot.
Thank you very much for your help.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] -
[Applause]
Ok I'm going to
play an Indonesian game, and I'm going to show you my red hair, and I
'm going to have a great battle with Ramando Grasshopper.
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]  ]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Laughter] [Music] [Laughter] [
Music] [Laughter] [Music]
[Laughter]  I'm
sure I'm missing something like this, the
questions I hear  A senior
with a friend, the
purple of the hekamaki pick-up
[laughter]
Gita, even the ideals have been sweetened somehow [laugh] -
[music]
[laugh]
[laugh] [
music] [music] [music
]
[laugh]
[music]  ]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Laughter] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[  [laughter]
[music]
[Music]
And
Elia, who I really admire,
posted
it [laughing] OK.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[
Music] [Laughter] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music  ]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] Meow the
Enma Brick It's
in the gravelly troubles!
Hello, I'm talking to Akare-sama
[Music] [
Laughter]
[Laughter]  ]
[Music]
Mika is the girl who's sorry for that face, and the packet comer is
stupid.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter]
[Laughter] [Laughter]
[Laughter  ]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[  Music]
[Music] It's
Expo!
Let's get excited
[Music]
That's why everyone is
so
excited. Let's do our best today.
[Music]
Okay, I'm the master of ceremonies this time. I'm Matsuri-chan, an
all-live
idol.
[Music]  ]
Kai
[Music] The
true person in charge of purity among Hololive's 1st generation is
Akirose, also known as Aki.
Thank you. I'm watching you.
[Laughs] Yes,
everyone.
Comma through, let's go with this flow. The
leader will do a fair copy.
[Music]
Well, I'm Noel Shirokane.
Thank you very much.
[Applause]
[Music]
Here are the different corners of the festival where you can participate.
Later
memory quiz
Yes, I will explain this corner.The
plan is for a quiz to be held in which one person will ask the question and the other two will be the answerers.And from here on out.  I
think it would be easier to understand if I explain it a little bit along the lines of the actual process, so I'd like to explain it a little while pretending that
the festival is the person asking the question, and
when the question opens,
Noel is the answerer.
[Music]
Please give me an image.
Yes, first of all, it
looks like this, but an image will appear.Yes, that
image will be the first time you see it, so
please be careful.And at this timing, the
questioner, Matsuri, will think about the problem.Yes.  I see, I
think I'll make it.
Well, it could be anything,
like
how many carnivorous animals there are, but
don't say it out loud.I'll
think about the problem, and
while the performers are thinking about it, the two people who will be answering the question will ask each other.  The whole time
Noel was wondering what kind of questions would come up, and
just memorized the image.Okay,
yes, time
passes and the image disappears, so after the image disappears, the
festival
will put out the problem there.Yes, then.
The two of you are asked to
come up with an answer relying on their memory.It
's a later quiz where the questions come out later, like yes or no.Memory
skillsIt's difficult today.There are some people who are a little confident.It's
good to be confident,
though.  I'm thinking of changing the person giving the question for each question.Yes,
everyone can ask the question.By the
way, the
person giving the question will also announce the correct answer while the image is listening.
Therefore, the memorability of the questioner
is also important.I see, I have a pretty
good idea of whether it's okay or not,
but I feel like I'm going to ask a question that I don't understand, and
what kind of question it is, and it
becomes a quiz show that I don't understand.  Okay,
let's give it a try. OK, let's start the festival with the question givers as we explain.
[Music]
Now,
please give me a picture. It's a
rice ball. I
want to eat it.  Well, there
's not a lot of information,
so that's right.I'm going to
start thinking about the problem by the end of the year,
so please think about it carefully.Okay,
let's go.It looks
delicious.I'm hungry.Please look at the images when making the problem.  I'm
worried because it's so simple that I feel like I'll never
be able to answer it,
but
it seems difficult.Okay
, I've decided.Okay, let's do
this.I'm trying to
memorize it,
remember it, memorize it,
take a good look at it, but I'm trying to remember it.
If you watch it for a long time, you'll get
hungry. [Music] You're not hungry, you're getting hungry.
After all, the rice balls are delicious, they're delicious.
So, there was a problem at the festival, but it means that the two of you
memorized it perfectly.  I
think it's about time, but what do you think?
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's it.
Now, I would like to
present a problem from the festival.
By taking the time, I hope that the memory of both of us will be
refreshed.
What color was it?
[Music]
I guess you were just looking at the rice ball in the middle.The color of the table is,
after all, the body.
[Music] You do
n't have to memorize it.The
colors are pretty good.  There are a lot of things, but
yes,
everyone laughs.
How did the venue
create an effect here? How about that
[laughter] Did you
manage to answer? I wonder if you
understand.
Dear listeners, do you
understand? Did you memorize it properly?
Well then, it's time to go. Well, yes, I'd like to ask someone who is confident
. The people who will be working with me.
[Music] I
said, "I'm sure."
Coffee video
[Music] I
have it.
[Music]
Next, Mr. Noe.
Here, here.
Rodon: Dark Lone,
right? [Music] [Music] [Laughter] Well then, I see. Well then,
Matsuri-chan's
that one, ah, that's different. Hello, that senior. It's
different. Because brown is like this. Ah.  Mari:
That's
not bad.
Even if it's brown, I
didn't notice.
[Music] Let's
take a look.
Here's the correct answer.
[Music]
Okay, please check the image.
[Music] It
's black. I
thought it looked black.  But, it's brown.
That's because of my preconceptions. When I say that, I
have a preconceived notion that it's brown.
[Music]
Hey, I didn't follow suit. This is
frustrating.  I was
n't drawn to the color of the black nori on the rice ball.And that's it.The left side is
lit by the light, so it's quite bright,
so I think the image of black was a little too weak.However, the
correct answer was definitely black.Everyone
is a
listener.  It was difficult for everyone. I
see. I think I made some good questions. So, we've just
started, so yes, that's the first question
. Now, I'd like to move on to the next question.
Who wants to do it?
[Music]
Well, it's okay if you make up problems. Is it
true? Since you gave it to me, I feel like I have to do it as a junior. Now, I'd like you to proceed a little bit from here. I think that's okay
.
Well, first of all, that's it. I'd like you to
send me a picture. How do you
feel about it?
[Music] I
see, there's a
lot of praise for this. I'm sorry,
Nobita, but you have to
try a little harder.
I see, this is it, but I
'd like to go with this image. Now, I'm going to
create a problem, so I'll create a new one.
Eh, open this sticker. Everyone wants it now.
[Laughs]
As expected. I
want people to praise me unconditionally. I'm just alive.
Yo, on that forehead.
[Music] I'll
walk around town with this. I
see. It looks like I can do all kinds of things.
[Music]
Yeah, it looks like I
can do this. I
might not be able to remember it.
Difficult sentences are difficult, aren't they?
[Music]
Yeah.  I see,
there are a lot of different patterns. I
don't think the leader will memorize the problem before he makes it.
[Laughs] The
problem is probably serious, but it's
true. Yeah, I see. I'm
starting to feel motivated. OK
[Music] I'm
shaking. I gave
up. I
tried to erase the burned wood.
OK,
yes, it's
got a scary face.Okay
, that's okay.Okay, now for the image.I
hope everyone has memorized it.Now, it's
okay to ask questions and ask them.
But here I am, just a little while ago, learning Matsuri Senpai's
technique and getting a little nervous.I
only remember one thing that everyone can make.Okay, let's
go, okay?Then,
the question is, behind that
flower that was on the top left.
How many are there? It's a cherry blossom, but
how many are
behind the cherry blossom? The petals on the back of the cherry
blossom are red. You
're looking at it, you're looking at it quite a bit. Let's do our best.
[Music]
So, by the way,
in terms of numbers, what kind of numbers do you like?
Wait a minute.
By the way, what are you
talking about? Just one time. Just
forget what you said earlier and
try drawing a picture of cherry blossoms.  I
think it's good, I think
it's okay to use the cherry blossoms that know how to give up on the righteous path Um, I
don't know if it's a problem that can be solved with the addition of memory and intelligence, but I
see. I'll
buy it based on my knowledge. Yeah.  Let
's go. I didn't write about men and women.
[Music]
Hey, is it okay?
Yes, I'm feeling weak again today. So,
first of all
, Ah, I'm
Hinode-senpai. Are you confident? Well, these should fit. Glasses are cool. Glasses are cool.  A
question from my senior. Yes, Akira-senpai's
answer is ``I see.
Well, speaking of cherry blossoms, there are 5 cherry blossoms.'' Yup, it's
delicious, isn't it?
Yummy
[Music]
This is an illustration.
But it's a really mysterious technique, and it's like,
okay, that's in the middle, and there's a seed,
so Ematsuri-senpai looked at this answer and
was like, hmmmmm.Okay, let's
take a look at Matsuri-senpai's answer as well.Very
well.  It's done.
[Music] I
see. I see.
So I'm going to go with the leader's answer.
Well, I think I've got the leader right.
Here's the leader.
Delon: Yes, 5 pieces,
everyone.
[Music]  So it seems like
everyone might have made a mistake. Let's take
a look. Well,
can I have a picture?
[Music]
Well, in a nutshell
.
I remember the one from earlier at the festival that was very well done.  That's what I saw.The
letter 1 says, ``It
's wonderful.It's wonderful.''That's
why I
want to send it to you.Let's try a little harder on the podium.I
would like to give everyone a wonderful sticker.Next.
Who is it? Well, if it's in this order.
Well, I should open it. Let's go.
Please, please. Next
time, I would like to create a problem that will make everyone say VV. This
is an image.
[Music]
This is information.  It's a
huge gathering.
[Music]
[Music] I
see.
Okay, so I'm going to make up some questions.
But I
can't help but remember it. It's
certainly cute, and I've seen it many times, but this is it.  It's
hard to remember that so-and-so is here.
[Music] I
see.
[Music]
But when I look at it like this, I
think Hololive has really gotten bigger. It's amazing, it's
really
amazing.  -
Amount of information
People like school It
seems like it's getting more and more like that when you get to the grade level.
[Music] I
can do the questions. Can you
do it? I was able to do it. I told the
guy that everyone would be okay, so I
gave him that.
Now, I'd like to ask you a question.Yes,
what was that letter written at the top of this page?
[Music]
If I forget, I think I'll be looking at people a lot.
So,
spring, I
'll have to do a reverse meta-read, ask questions, and read the manual, etc. But then I'll
have to talk about what this event is all about, and then I'll write it in color.
Hey, is that that? I
don't know what it is. I don't know how to spell it in English
. I
wrote it down in my head. I
think that's what the administrator said. That's right, that's
it.  [
Music] I don't
think anyone can get this wrong.
I wonder if I should wear glasses.
My eyes are huge. There's
no way I can make a mistake.
[Laughs]  It
appeared.
Okay, so I guess it melted.
Okay, then I'd like to open Matsuri-chan and Nore-chan Phantom Thief at the
same time.
Don Do Don
Super Expo
200022 Ah, they're both the same
[Music]
Content
Wait,
Festival
[Music]
Say
[Laughs]
So, here's the correct answer. It
was Den Super Expo 2022.
But everyone was too senior in town, so I
thought about whether or not to include Ai, but I couldn't.
[Music] It's a
shame, so I'd like you to study a little more.
[Music]
Thank you for your support,
please. I mean, everyone, it's always a
dream.
[Music]
By the way, we were
able to perform live, we were able to do something that we were happy
about, we were able to plan things like this,
and everyone was great. Let's
end this on a wonderful note.
[Music] There's
still a
lot of fun to be had.  I hope
you enjoy it, so I'd like to end
by asking you how it was after trying it
out. I think I was able to hide the fact that my ability to retrieve memories was a bit weaker than I had expected.  I'm going to put it up and
do my best.
So
that's all for the corner you've been waiting for. Yes
, everyone, I hope you enjoyed it. Yes, I
had fun. What
are the highlights of each Third Festival Expo?
There are a lot of them, so
please enjoy them to the fullest.
So,
bye bye bye
[Music]
Weiss Schwarz
Hololive Production's booster
pack
won't stop Weiss Schwarz
Booster pack
Hololive Production Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, I love anime Chugai Kogyo Contents
Options  We
plan and develop anime goods and sell them on the internet.We have
collaborated with anime in the past.For the
latest information, please follow us on Twitter
[Music]
[Applause]