in this
Indonesia hai hai hai hai hai hai hai hai
Hi
Hello Eh Bro I'm the one Sorry have started to be
you but I am here right now as
risut Iman Doctor risus sit up Yes
so resto here as Doctor
resolution squirrel friends there is no  Doctor
Risus Sit Up will open a
free consultation service for guests who
will come today Yes. Are
you ready to find out
who will come to the
Thufail resolution Doppler clinic? Yes, are you?  are you
curious?
Are you the one they will consult
yestoday early Open eye and online
consultation of the doctor May suggest
kulliyesi tupai means the school
and I will In White suggest that will
ask me for Advan Iya seductor Reason
Yes outrigger Ouch I think it's time to
rest  the world
to have wav to help our first section
sorry sorry sorry I don't understand now
okay seating lets count our first
ah our first glance
cuy cuy
Jokowi
alright Let's read our first best
everybody  Uh okay
Hi
songket hello hello hello hello okay lamis
Strike ama Welcome finished having fun
consulting with Doctor resusi tupa where
you can consult about
everyday complaints from the strange
to the strangest before entering the
consultation session Please select the voice
you want to handle
complaints  you Press 1 to select
Rizzo's voice Press 2 to select Wizu's voice
Press 3 to select Ayunda's voice,
you are welcome
I
am I want number one OK
then thank you
thank you for choosing the Thursday service
I'm worried about that  will help you in
this consultation session without
taking too long. Please introduce
yourself and explain what you want to consult about,
please
hohohohoho hehehe Thank you, Doctor,
name issue, circle the map. I'm an
angel and now I want to
consult about Um.
How can I control the stability of
my voice?  when we sing because the
drl is more often unstable when
singing, listen more uh OK,
thank you Wow, that's
really
very interesting, so a a, without
further ado, A Doctor issue will
help,
so
the way is
em-plus there, we have to practice
breathing properly  but there are things that
we usually forget, namely m A where we
have to cut sentences when we
sing so to stabilize the voice
when singing a there are times when we have to
pay attention to
m Where we will cut
sentences when singing Yes That way
we can
feel the flow of the singing more
so comfortable, usually the afternoon is
Aa the main key so that singing is more
stable for tung tung,
this is very helpful.
Thank you, former daughter, I'm satisfied and
before the consultation time ends. Are
there any messages and words you want to
convey from our guest Lili Iveta
Hi there?  Of course there is one for the
cutest doctor  my prettiest Hihihi I'm embarrassed
doctor Ouch
OK then that's the message for the doctor
today's issue happy birthday to you bro
results uh doctor what do you mean Sorry who
OK thank you
yes I hope you'll be more successful in the
future Hopefully you'll be more beautiful and cute
and also hopefully there will be more boxes Hopefully there will be
more  those who love Sis Lis uh want a
doctor iso mawi Sumo Ayunda, I hope
many people love you and are always
blessed with health and abundant fortune
52 thank you, thank you for your words then
Thank you for your words when erysuprim a
in my heart  To my heart the deepest worry
is here hehehe in them I am
with you Thank you for
your time to consult
and
Maybe next time rise will open
another consultation service so see you again
in the next consultation session
OK thank you Doctor Heaven's issue
today doc thank you
Alright that's our first guest
then Are you satisfied with
today's session because we
are going to have a lot of
guests Yes because they are already queuing
friends so Are you curious
about the next button because the issue is
also curious
Hi
just a moment
then let's contact Dudi  dudi
dudi dudi  dudi dudi dudi dudi dudi hai hai hai hai Hi
dudi dudi dudi dudi okay okay let's aha
contact Om Aa Let's
contact our next guest pun
wall
dududududu
[Music]
cutu dududu hello hello hello hello
by klase we are connected Welcome
to the session  squirrel resuscitation doctor consultation
where you can consult
about everyday complaints from the
strange to the strangest before
entering the consultation session. Please select
the voice you want to
treat  your complaint Press 1 to
select the issue sound, press 2 to select the
wisu sound and press 3 to select the
Ayunda sound, welcome,
hello, hello,
hello, hello. Wait
a minute. Looks like we're having
a bit of a connection problem.  the
caller is ready to choose the
voice he wants
Hi selected
Hello Hello I want week3 uh OK
then thank you for choosing
our service I am Ayunda who will
help you in this consultation session
without lengthy papers  Please
introduce yourself and explain
what you want to consult about
after
he alo'oa doctor Ayunda my name is
Apple and I'm 18 years old forever.
He said that's how it used to be, I have a burden in
life, what's the future of this burden, what is it
called? I have to go to the gym first, he said,
but three about mager  to go to the gym
because it's such a burden,
uh, the problem with life is that my burden is. Hey,
I just finished teaching my friend at
that time and then he said he was angry Kyle.
My problem. Oh, even though I cook
normally, how come it's just rubber added?  chocolate
plus copy Then add honey and
apples, that's really normal, right?
So what's wrong with me like that? Oh,
okay then uncle, I'll
give you a little enlightenment about
your problem. So actually it's
not the cooking that's wrong. The apple that's wrong
is actually my friend's stomach.  Those of you
who don't seem to be strong enough to
handle super food from Apple
Hi, that's right Hut is real, right? Oh
yes, I'm ready. It's a shame I'm wrong, so
to overcome this, maybe in addition to the
food that
will be provided, maybe you can
give me digestive strengthening medicine.
Wow, that's very enlightening, Doctor
Ayunda is like that indeed.  once heard it,
my goodness  Thank you very much, Doctor Tray,
because my burden is reduced like
work, huh, Michael, then are
you satisfied with the answer to the
consultation this time, it is very strong, Mochtar
Ayunda, thank you very much, OK,
then before the consultation time
ends, do you have a message and the words you
want to convey?
from what Apple said it was the doctor's
birthday Nia Oh yes that's right
so I want to say happy Day eroh
Thank you for the time OK the grayer the mouth the more the clouds the
name the happier the smoother
the life goes on the clouds the name I hope
lots of good things happen to the doctor yeah
I hope more patients are helped
by presence  the doctor here has
thanked you very much then here are the
voices again songs please child
As for her name ayundari she likes
picnics right hahaha huhuhu I want to
sing happy birthday but Bro Turkey
anyway please go ahead please
need to get muddy
terer
mrut teteh
hahaha Wow
the song is very interesting Thank you  very touching love
Hello Piye hahaha
Thank you stupid water for inviting Eponk Yes I'm
sorry I gave it too See you next
time
much much
wow friends that was
our second caller  and I hope my advice
can be a little useful to help
their lives hah OK
then without further ado because we
have a lot of guests today then
we will move on to the third guest Wow, the
doctor is very busy this time.
OK then let's go
just welcome it without further ado,
Toni Tunik Eto said. Welcome to the
Doctor Resusi Squirrel consultation session where
you can consult about
everyday complaints from the strange
to the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to  choose a sound
resume press 2 For
that WOW issue press 3 to select
Ayunda's voice welcome
Hi
to track Well
[Music]
so the most dangerous zone what
numbers are there anyway
[Laughs]
Ah wrong guys this number 2
Thank you for choosing the service  If
you're
sad, I'm Vishnu who will help you
in this consultation session without
long words. Explain, introduce
yourself and explain what you want to
consult about,
hello, hello, you're free, hehehe. Today,
if you want to come, I'll be here. So if you were earlier
I'm back closest to Wadiah's acquaintance.
Yes, I'm HT, bro. If there's anyone there, it's
really like the cat entered
Deathbird. Unblurred. Google, look, there are
so many people, there are people whose
manhood attraction will be
hihihi, Ken Arok, consult me.
Hi, bananas, what do we eat?
Can you please refill the
question? Banana If you don't do
anything,
ah, a little hiat can make teeth, why
not? If it turns out the
rica-rica fish puzzle is painted to be a
smut Oh I see. That's it.  If you eat the chest, you will
appear, appear, there will be
a lot of it. Oh, how do you say it so that it
doesn't get dirty
? Hahaha, it's a hobby of eating. Is it magic that it bleeds like that?
Hahaha. Before you eat, wipe your
mouth first with a tissue, use it
like that, use it here, random luck, ah,
our elders are there.  Can you print PT Patria
really dry? Ouch, how do
you set it? What do you do? Edit it
first.
Usually, what are the covers
called, over over over making?  Yes,
that's the main thing, don't, don't be precise, the
Kidul blender, it failed, the catfish,
so that's the part that can be accepted,
hehehe. It's
still really lazy,
sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Thank you.
Hi, thank you, then, aa, father,
father, our father is the one we love
because I died and  good
[Music]
finished high haiwiki nyuci Thank you
if that's so thick Well we're going to get tired
We met there's something you want to say
Oh yes of course the final tekek is driven by
Rizal
Heroes V comparing fashion photos
Ok  rek doctor helicopter newsletter
paint
okay okay then because
because we were a little
unique before then we will move on to
sweeter guests Yes that will be the one that
will soothe your hearts so
then let's get started with the call
Sis, I'm sincere, you can consult a doctor
rization tupai where you can
consult about
everyday complaints from the strange to
the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to choose the result voice.
Press 2 to choose wadaw issue and
keep three to choose  voice  Ayunda
is welcome
OK Google the
third amp or not
Can you do that
Aa Then okay gecko ah before the
cement I want to give you a simple gift
cycle because it's the
doctor's birthday right I'll send it yes please
then no Aa I'll hunt
okay this and like this  and quickly die
alternately okay hahaha huhuhu cq40
simpei ama put down the gift Ah you
like that Is there anything you want to
consult about and please
introduce yourself first Ah
yes Introduce my name Ni  There's the
legendary Panca Doctor, so
I've had a complaint lately that I'm
confused about the many Tajung
Seizure characters. I mean it doesn't
really matter because their charm will
continue, actually I don't want to
prove them, but I'm
really tired. I need entertainment and in the end
I'm addicted and in the end  sim
like that I smile every day until I
think I'm crazy then I'm
dagdigdug Do I have
heart disease believe I'm shy and
all that kind of thing And I also what
is it called?  often hangs up
because it proves that the character is not
real. Is it a subtle method, that is, healthy or
what, can you give me advice like that,
doctor? Go up. Thank you, Miss Nia
Reza. Lion is in the light, it will help
paint a little to deal with your problem
because in my opinion it is a
normal thing.  especially if the character is
extraordinarily handsome, brothers, so in
my opinion,
Aa Mbak Nia is still a normal Ema,
because because I don't
lose my common sense, I just type, maybe
or bite a little  Oh yes or
what kind of convulsions to deal with
please
just call the nearest handler yes that's right
so
to deal with your convulsions which
might be a little out of bounds
maybe yes yes maybe it can be used Om
Aa certain time quickly yes people can be
charged a little normal toll like that Yes  so it's
still normal, but I'm on GSM and GSM
and I'm tired of him playing Sin on
them, they have to be on
GSM too, why am I Ha, they're
me, they have to be given a little love, Om,
I'm aware that  hahaha
Jember same
hah ah they seem to need
love too yeah Oh okay okay ah
thank you Doctor I finally got an enlightenment
lately I've been anxious
about the doctor Thank you for
opening up to love like this doctor
and have if Happy birthday so
Is there any  the words that Aa wants to
give before we end today's session,
ah, what, happy birthday,
tissue, I'm waiting for the original song
tonight, because Thank you
for talking about it, please invite
you too for this conservation.
Thank you, see you in the next session,
hi, hi.
Bye, it's there Hi, you're the one who missed it
Hello friends,
the energy to dispel the result is really extraordinary.
Looks like we have to learn
from our guest, namely Nia Reza Lion. Wait
a minute, I forgot to put the picture in
this, Jeng Ma'am, who is very beautiful,
then we'll continue
for a moment.  -Wait a minute, Vishnu, drink first,
look for money to wash e-tolls,
Hi,
Laila's fortune, wait a minute, drink first, OK, hi, hi,
hi,
our friends, Aa, call OK, welcome to the
consultation with the Squirrel Resolution Doctor,
where you can consult  about
everyday complaints from the odd
to the strangest before entering the
consultation session. Please select the vote
you want to handle
your complaint. Press 1 to select the
diesel vote. Press 2 to select the issue question.
Press 3 to select the swing vote. The
Constitutional Court Law is welcome.  OK, then
Thank you
for choosing our service, I am Ayunda
who will help you in
this consultation session. Without further
ado, please introduce yourself and
explain what you want to
consult on,
please, hello Doc, I'm Mika Matikah
from  nijisanji eh id eh eh Today I
want to consult if a
few days ago or from
a few weeks ago it seems like
I'm starting to feel like I'm afraid I'm starting to get
really scared by efforts like
those breeds or Dogs every time there's a
squirrel or something like that paypay which is like
a bit-  It's a bit onee-san, like that, it stirs my heart,
it's a little dagdigdug, it's a little bit. Sitting like that,
my pocket makes it hard to breathe, it's like
that, OK, so Oh, so the complaint
is shortness of breath.  because squirrels
make you afraid of squirrels,
Yes Nok. So, if you are
afraid of squirrels, please take the
nearest AHM trap so that the squirrels don't
come close, but
if the complaints continue, such as
shortness of breath, convulsions or
headaches, please take or prepare an
inhaler to help.  your breathing
Aa if the complaint
persists Please contact the doctor to
get GWS pills
resident I was going to ask for GWS pills but
how come now the doctor says
I prefer Manado dangdut Then
I will give you a prescription after this
to get the pills  GWS, is
that all the complaints
from Mbak Mega Melati
kw2 thank you very much uh ah
then before the consultation time
ends Are there any messages and words
you want to convey
FW be
happy Tanjung Bunga everything will
be Oh good everything-gummy okay
we
I just woke up checking things out gozaimasu
Thank you hu tweet for original
song Yale
close like Thank you for coming
then thank you for your words
and time see you again in the
next consultation session bio Thank you very much doc
uh  uh
Hi guys that's what silence is not easy called
they continue
this
no thank you very much He has a
complaint that he is afraid of cupai brother
is willing to be sad
so yeah like that
there have already given a prescription
what is the prescription for GWS pills
to the person concerned thank you Frances
ha ha I have  present at this session
once it's
checked you
hello so wait
a minute the issue of drinking first oh donlesi the
next si again the nation dudohno Shaykh
Indonesia nah ah the
donation is closed Dadi Sorry
your sandals are like that let's wait
a moment out Who else  what we'll
call if you're alone, drink
first for a while and then get thirsty
because the next G thing
will be very euy
Mecca really makes an RV resume
while you drink first okay Doctor resolution
squirrel will continue to listen to
your complaints for a while
6 first we grind
launchpad.net
Hi hehehe
[Laughs  ]
Indonesia
Hi sturisoma lizard medals
hahaha all kinds of soldiers to
prepare themselves and dress up their body
and soul for a moment
hehehe hehehe Hi
hehe he
hai
hahaha
hihihi hai  hai hai hai
Then let's
just keep going for a bit, have a drink first
then I'm told Edo Then let's Call the
next caller while every
cheating is a little first huhuhu
hai hahaha
eh as a doctor here it's very very
very
very Marvel's brothers and sisters just a moment
hai  hi hi hi hi eh
that's Hi Sone
sugiwa wed police here namiraatasya Yoga
Sony jutekin chicken curse nazoya
henneberg I go to the Noki drag  Mouse
Sultan is not bad Soyu should Let
It
Go kimono by issue please no temple
gokilun object new let's memeque go
keyboard by Los Angeles er Abby kudasai
Dodo
enilno the unique Sumatra robots
yuk
Cheese that Gus Azmi Ayo tuku by Master
kungkai Okta monoculture parents
Toxicity tada  Kimi
Shaykh sholeh Dewa Jikoshoukai tuh
online tweets kikasete kudasai
Hoi hello oh great tribe driver
odong-odong  odong-odong eosen let alone the
name escapes
ogoh-ogoh
[Music]
tokuno debt zooad his idol misoro
yuk decimal curse chicken ideas
di sono online yuk di Zenit critic the
writer nontongo.co song okadoc Talking
Tom Wita detect modem naide sukanya
Hello mobil Cane Tokyo  inoxx1 sing mugo
We once knew the machine
toison Hero the enemy
tried great kid Sifana solemn and muscular
times Heru new stylish  the demo is playing yoyo
Blazing, this oil is washed
kasyaira Dubai, enough weatherli tokidoki
stretchy banish
corrective twidash, visit you trade value bye
Kayla Yoi loading NATO skin Adit Angeles
sugoshita menu tanoshi activity
onestopgps rukutuk rezeki.com that's Joe's
name is den-o
Ih the bread is crying over  Cimone wata sietho
Faidah creature
appeal oh
my cellphone
[Music]
al-fath yo
Hello Ma
teenager
money
Yi  with markers
ngoday den-o cie
Nihongo Triangel
Woi horse
thank you thank you
Eto
Thai Gua only cikuda zainil tajwid
matching color code Heni Nata
world frog sign Ayu Jokowi
Hi
Nugraheni dotulong er that mag Marry
Edward
snowden still selfish Kidul flowy Avin issue
eh talk
What  do you want to start
[Music]
viewing messages
Twitter cheating
sorry ama Nihongo daiyo
Oh direka hai hai  Neng Come on, let's look at
Bonek 50 Teguh,
that's what we're cracking Eto'o chigga all
near the Times Tahai shop
Oh yes
small GT Kudasai Hi
maintain spotify
and edit you
hahaha
icostats half of this data type
Oh
yes just a moment Pi betel River freezes
So that's a bit like what  That's it for a moment,
yes, Egypt is a celebrity, so
Yes, bring me that. Hi
tujhko dead, the verdict is
Korean-boys, sudirmanto,
hi,
then come on, let's go  we ee
Indonesia
Hi believe
it's a bleach weh
Hi members of the Indonesian
machine friends movement Hi
tas kemenkeu
baby toh
Wetan Aas mbak Riri Sumo
fix
bye bye
launch Nga Nga hai
hai
the lounge
ndeso
hai hai
ndeso hai
hai yeah Wait a
minute ya diskor looking for education discord
PC almost  u hi hi hi
hi
OK Google
Rizky YouTube Ayu
nyuci
Unit
send to
Indonesia hi hi
KMU yang
hai hai
the best hai hai hai hai hai
hai
dream drifting away
Niken vietsub the
nih Hi that is
Hindu molish Minanda
Moscow and suryokusumo
Ichinose so seconds International
need nazoya Hai Nadekigoto mode now
we soto
Mito yusry crew by our prophet sae-hee
Hi  cow gokil woyla ichiu Wisnu Klego
kimono proof kill wae new way no kowe
Go Keyboard
Arabic rasae
[Music]
please oh gini that
anu goshimei arigatou gozaimasu ta kurai Okay
telogosewu appear safety sodachimasu
Ayunda the most nyuruh
soredewa Jikoshoukai Toure ya Minutes
each
site Hi
my name is ok www.neanime.org that's
it
nocciole likes using balloons Let
's go Strike high noh  cc.xpi The village
likes it as old as me metu
stick sinus demo raima sen m afternoon Oh
Solo  Jokowi's mini story Ido Ido
is active Taeyeon
souqy.aku Dino manggau gomuno Gaskins
anode eh oh
it's for us safe umaini seconds tea tuh
seasonic
forelock Surono Hi you are here mah
happy
hai hai
told to
swing swing swing
like
fall everything is good  it's just ayeuna,
Goblin color, weird
cat hahaha,
thanks for the
highlights, love that
[Laughs]
No teasing, OK, Kanina  rumaini
hoka-hoka message he stays Kutoarjo Mask
Hi anoa Merry code please Resto
curse me tea
atuh ih
please dia instatories cardboard for or
kroto isonia soundtrack rasae Hey died
via injection prayer account
Asok LED Gray
hahaha hehehe arigatou gozaimasu ta
thank you thank you bye  -bye
Yes t-shirt dosto songo-songo zagato
Android is the f*** Frozen seenit.io to
find the solution to the Swift Out
suchs Frozen
Khair
window process Hi
emytos were still
broken
under these in
Indonesia
hai hai
you explore Windows
say
Shoulders Tego
OK
so click restore dress
we stir
hahaha
topics fall Mega there i
Indonesia Hi
die we Zaini
Hi
Baby good love you
Cie
cie
Mbak  wes
understand
the fun of fiction fiction fiction
hahaha
[Music]
I
am destroyed man e Hi I am deh Ackerman
really ah YouTube
anti shoetique just ready for the
next color yes yes
okay  al-wadjan driver the next color let
go
Indonesia
Hi hehehe
hi Guides or girl live score
badges0 hai hai Hai
netok next
Easter
Oh Shaykh Sudais
Hi
watermelon
announcement first
Aceh MS King
okay
pray ready for the next color the day
the next next next yes  yes
okay okay sumbopu
[Music]
paint Okay Williams Timezone who made C
Okay Lex karwacot Dokter wis consultation
with kentut nothing to lose your problem
or how is for storing the consultation
with  animals for the goal for the
consultation cool out Boys just one two
is just
wait and just reach up Ayunda Ayunda Yes please please
please please one two or three
Aha
tripleasport I thank you so much for
your attention for choosing a mission he
invites who will help you  on the station
for the weekend introduce yourself and
explain to me about your problem
hohoho hihihi site Sands of
abstract NSP stroke Suzuki
Hello how much I
nice How much time you and stay out of
the okay okay hungry so
sincere and twice micro swirly serum Here
I  wanna fight each
hungry
so
OK So there are some reasons that we can feel
hungry during the stream but frankly
would likely it with its water Bridge
dry coldly bye over your solution
Yes very nice solution quickly et m opo ma
hias Sounds from around your stomach old
inslate  brother that comes out When your
stomach grumbling static uh Let great
things bright and it will keep your
stomach Farmer yes yes
Hotel next time Thank you very much for
asking for
each before each and the
anything you want to say
I
love you have a Wonderful wonderful  year
following  Muksin Happiness
Wooyoung Vodka Hah
m.ask.fm collabo can survive cake
year spicy hollywoodnya which you thank
you so much Pain message and also see
you again in the next next time okay
thank you bye bye
It's
very difficult to be concerned because each
slide On The Stream  Beethoven Hello
friday friday friday okay filter Yes I
put some 9 we blogsome times to the
sound of my dream link from links to
make some students May make your
Hi
enough Impressing Aa confide in another color  b
i would like to do something fresh Yes
alright won't give some ad-diin tebel
advice
Asikin magic Come on March
nubie in the
one I finished eh May on it will be
available
ane
Newbie smells Ona from today from the
day in the march of
seven seven seven seven fell Seven oh
oh Life Indonesia
official Twitter yes  sriwanto by each
sentence
from now on bikin-bikin get my message
and what are the match What are the
beach just friend OK,
use Indonesian first, here are
two special items, Bantul.com sarong,
makura, memories before bed and a
soft tail charm, a warming risk.  be
careful, so if you buy two
complete sets, you will get a
postcard signed
directly, yes, the postcard that will be
signed directly is cool, isn't it, Uh,
finished Ride
Saudi sad Ade Derulo The default
cardboard is for ipos cardi will get
Enon, it's great  complete set of your Wembley postcard
with Risou's signature yes,
that's right, but understand. What kind of issues are
things are the single detail has to say
Yes dakimakura
khayna my heart iah trading guys version
brush on First
Hi
enternet Yes already kilo rice site Merry
cute match
choose this season  destroyed bytes art lots of
memes body Enno so
acem it's a it's yours Is The Kitchen by
once a kitchen emoh
u-seal risus Heart warming love-child
time  it's amazing axindo will be you
should Yes you have to buy it please yes
and heavy books
you will get a message via narrow buzurg
pos cardboard size by me like me trush me
in the wild Madly
Shining very much very much amazing I
will tear my eyes  my my heart to Shine
your cardboard hahaha
power you waiting for it's beautiful
make cake AHM Indonesia official
Twitter rhinoware retweet Allah Laila
Indonesia
by Nabi Indonesia and similar without
first Yosh with match her
iku slang
Ayu right good  zergling Is there and use a
r i ri f a n i question you can ask us
tour reactions about story about
everything is already there in the
description of may
ab-100
selfishly if you have a question
it's in the description Store add Link
provided by Federal live Indo
syaa so cash is
far away wow
Sis written by Magic is it all
just appears morley story from the day
for men see you can free our radiation
every night very good very very he loved
the most Ayunda back in the beach So I
love I need your
November 2 can be Edward, so it will be sold on
Tokopedia, also attending, you guys, keep
following the updates, yes, it will be updated
and will be sold on Tokopedia, so just
decorate it, just buy the
brush products, it's very easy
Yes you for your face brush, please one
time offer one time for next year  it
would be like this anymore Yes it's his own
time Chaeri
[Musik]
Farmer in asleep without getting out Put
down You're everywhere Yes bytes very
nice cover everybody
is someone Miss out [ __ ] Please
by Sherina
Hai thank you so much for Listening to
me that talk about the bottle here
it by our market leader huhu huhu huhu huhu
huhu
Huhuhu Okay show clothes Habib everybody
from YouTuber body and stomach
flu
in let's move on to the
next caller then
uh
painting Android the now yours yours
You're
this or not  mainin
bile information ask
Kwan
Hai he's
reluctant How much but OK so sung-hwan
next color of
access OK
initial konco turu wis consultation without
anything will send to your problem How
your first  before starting the
consultation please wait for the
consultation the world with just one
Epic yourself
chest cover quixley under topics Ayunda
voice
Hai yarn review Quiz
uk.eng TubeMote Fulham Ilmi
gua baseball is really funny right uizuhu will
help you on the station without further
Ado
introduce and  explaining to me
about job
weh gemling kekinian famous for liking the
vinglish formula sorry boy soundtrack
song The Monkey Iya ama found Sorry the
f*** out [ __ ]
solving problems
early childhood
eh so for away  er Years Eve Marry a
sleeping schedule Soul each have Once
eam I Can't Fight Shadow Fight season
hebei achoy
Painful that Begins because you have a
wedding adjusted with Straight am
sleeping schedule Why don't we just move
the sun
www.hayy.net  hubei new fhx-b trust
myself in the same
Chaeri
magic awf tweet-tweet
stick shooting schedule on
daiam see you snort acuy amen
amen I'll do How much
sleep like Ours
techsem our sleep Oh  yeah come on wes cannot
sleep you show me about each other on
time and incomplete
kwangsan good grandfather cover gecko
Iphone4 wayame doctor it
soffice.net mp3new year through our
Sweet Nothing republican however it's
pretty long time everything is because of
the two
[Music]
mp3we  are like in yourself to get moving
the sun much
for help
on
How You're looking for at the help of
schedule planning you
Yes crisye paint happy
birthday giveaway
Hai Evil stronger stronger
yris  knoppix Armstrong Lex by missing
value in Germany
ezuke
OK
thank you for that feel happy song
keyboard
[Musik]
khsusu
song about taxi yuk Lex Happy birthday
Angela
oh yes uyuj Crowe that the kitchen
y95dan it Benz
OH no the world we live real real real
real  real
kwe bikinin lux Willy uyesh welcome okay that's
it Kyu Won
Hong Okay Arif Rich
served two
two
cheated or clothes sleep now
[Music]
joyes Gauss our our next
turyyan
and good morning
and nice race
omong
I will check out then please
please please I have some other people's Yes I
Hi
MB huhuhu bener
badges0
Happy
[Music]
beautiful morning on ration 300i
story hah
this Hehehe
Hahaha happy Okay and something that I
would like  the sea hobbiri Gotta go to
Marry Marry heartwarming a message from
someone so let me play the video Firza
OK
building without
clear birthday talk
Om etong can pocong
Hi  KYT diffusion
Hi
just sub huhuhu ghosts Jusuf
Habibie numbers 13 yes guys Subhanallah
Hi thank you so much good thank you so
much for giving me I'm very high
Performing a message for my birthday hai
Hi
asoy that was
mechs
mp3when message from
yachh It means a lot to me take you so
much I
[Music]
I
definitely you the cabbage glue Virzha
Cover Girl
various yess
of course you
Hi hehehe
Jonggol wait  want Once
ampere most for the next couple dudu
[Music]
Nesya cassava default
refworld next Wow Iyos
dodongo
hihihi.com isi homicides Kidul first
cassava kid credit
instead of glass Hahaha
again jammed
hahaha
as before before we go to die Cut then
Let's be there, still a noob  etusi
motorbike taxi driver
lecture competition don't
know
can
video ah
Hi
little monkey
ancur having to the nervous one that was born
[Music]
kefir Er
hai hai
yo
and shake the rice
yeah  Goyang Shining Ajeng
toy Spotted monkey nexcare relaxation truck
tsabina choandry likes
[Music]
ddu-du-ddu-du
Star drink first if that's the case hehehe while
waiting let's drink first
hello Mama Teh Oh I think Hahaha I
think what was that in Scorpio?
lagging lagging again for a moment
smos wow I'm worried hi hi bro I'm
home comment hihihi
shark Pondok Karya Kho
Minggu looks like he's hooked ondekigoto  take a
shower later Roro Kidul
No
Taiyou the wallaby tribe has finished
being touched by the crazy crew for the baby
Ideology that's Vishnu Hulk Hulk Mother
WA number new let's go keyboard saw Nabiku
cultivating
fall nayamigoto that's still
that mermaid in solemn that's got
yumichika lizard read
Losta Masta Christmas
Indonesia excited
eat jobelist Can I
make
Yes Newbie doesn't die
deck know how confused hi bro I
like it I need it full this is shocked
because
[Music]
is the magazine  the progress is full Step Two
ynwa motorbike Indonesia
is the soul of one keigo Freemason is the
law Hooke lives
ichfa
Ashlee monokai sustech come Bakauheni
cursed ethos there is left Thomas
Tisna that is the temperature of wushu style whether it is
sitting iTune first playnow patitos
qq7 specifically for medical there
is a photo of that please papaya kunaon
Disney
is enough, is Toyota Little the engine of
his friends Ouch baby East Oku the world
likes
guys Nasa told me right miss you baby
baby baby
baby baby baby
Ouch  baby talk soto ayam TV
post
yes about
Ben10 Ma'am don't have download model
look iyo
iyo Well that's mechset.ini politics
waterfall ngebet
hahihu luya
Ouch Hello Baby
if you remember meeting
that Hi Bro cucak that prayer sounds blasphemous
Inalum this is hocane Messi he's Otoy  Ali,
are you still
holding back the districts Oh no season Decorate Dumadi
notes Yovie chandracom.net
choiheechu Hi
strange things in Indonesia
Kadek's charm  city Moscow color country
asobru stadium
Hanoi roughly
Hi during wa taala XP home rattan Jono
method top
how bye
[Music] there
should be us air BoBoiBoy
Come on Papa zeiss uh
Hi bicycle Usada papain next uh How
other things that you mind by amroe
expecting sunexpress  simple hohoho Edo
Icut DC Just Nyosor guys
come on tuwai porn Saturday night Central
Indonesia needs Made nandomo kita Dimas
eh hi already  nurmaini I told you to go to the
UN circuit, we say Idol big
two Lee sunkyu technology bailive you
please no Kriwul Kliwon let's play Come on and
okay okay bye the
clamped officer Come on Google
Hi, I like the object with the chin corner
to fall in love again May wish to
the museum
Baitul Dewa  mice like that Unaya
michikaze horse tae-hee
[Music]
hmm that's Hai
old Hi like it
or not NTT country
nah Yaumul masturbation HP tuh ih through like
Ashoka  Coker doesn't drink the village head's excise. It's
great, isn't it just pretentious, it doesn't type,
if you want to use skill no. D, it's grass jelly, the
rule of Describe Musim Mas, you're slime
Saint, elementary school ring, the
filming of the ring is a bit up to
March
10 kaladawa, please your image is big,
hai hahaha og Atoz year  that's a chihuahua
that's a pyramid
[Music]
Mocil's love is
coming I was the one WHO Hi ugly
hey hey
crisis go gisi mermaid flea Disney
should
hoi dog residents of
kyoc a
Hey who
Happy birthday birthday happy birthday
[Music]
it's
on the snack label
Asta curabhaya Rune actually nganu Simi it's
finished
Shaikh
Smash Dewa etouch jogodayuh masteng
contributed uh uh
Hi
everyone Come on, support
tazyin
next power more prepared for my heart
for myself  first OK Let's
Get Rich the next Corp
Hi Miss
eh ugly
Ica ugly
Ami Ami Bear Facebooke
kutamindo more Mas
this ticks you Oh yes bye background
music of Thank you
tega White
Hi
next Galur please susu
[Music]
Hai
taza fit
Hi
Uh hello I love you
hello hello funny
Indonesian hahaha
not washed years still alive Corry
sushi to play where you can
consult with consult
about everyday complaints from the
strange to the most  strange before
entering the consultation session Please select the
voice you want to
handle your complaint Press 1 to
select the issue voice press 2 to select the
issue wayaw press 3 to select the voice
Ayunda is welcome
G2
hi-tech Jokowi the pen is breastfed  Cut
the color, how popular this is,
thank you for choosing our service,
I am Vishnu, who will help you with the
dishes, this consultation without
long words, enlighten
yourself and explain about the things you want to
consult about
at that time, Papakuan, they admit it. Hoi that
was hou Yi
Subhanallah
we Wow
bleake please
Hi  Here, I'm going to tell you a story about timer
expense, come on, your timer is going
this long, all of these are units,
most of them are
chasing points at Simping time,
so Royal, what should I do?  I have to have to have to
do it. Then it runs out
when I go to Simping or next to
Lyrella, right?
I think it's a matter of knowing what I have to do,
called Choi. You need
oil onions that can control the oil
from start to finish so that Abian
Athaya's activities can be organized so that PHO  the
heavy one is responsible for
handling all activities Oi yes but the
doctor is not the handler the doctor is the vegetable
bye bye bye
ih this afternoon therefore you need a
very
experienced handler ih if you want to resign you
can be an oil onion  wushu can be Mr.
oli yes oh how much does it cost per week
per week only with
divorce Aa love and affection every
time uh
10 gadgets then Is flip satisfied
with the answer so ouigo need to
stop from this feature Nia
Just looking for an opportunity that's another war  I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm
ready, hahaha
hihihi, it's better to have background
[Music]
when I'm crying a lot, I'm just playing with
clove, you're
like that, oh, I'm like that. Before the consultation
ends, what are your messages and words
that you want to achieve?
Oh yes, so please listen  listen
Because these are words from the heart Oh yes okay
Wih senpai Happy birthday wish you a
long life oli shell wish the
best for senpai and English
yo yo hi hi
Hi
disappear
ready prayer mat hehehe Eh that's all yeah
hi high-end Hi
yes saza Huh what a guest  that one
Hi Edo MS Lembangdi
reshuffle Doctor consultation session where you can
consult about
everyday complaints from the strangest to the
strangest rubbish before entering the
consultation session Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint Press 1 to select the voice  diesel
press 2 to select the wisu voice and
press 3 to select the Ayunda voice,
welcome
you are sincere. Thank you, it seems like
our caller nature this time is very
enthusiastic, you are so, I am
Ayunda who will help you in
this consultation session. Without further
ado, please introduce yourself and
explain.  about the things I want to
consult about
my anal my name is noble
today
your doctor came to help me
Abdullah which I have been experiencing for a long time anyway
so the same is available is that I have been
on my back a lot lately
wanting to sleep
watching TV
Hey Hyun Joong is funny hehehe I
really thank you for waiting for me
OK then Thank you very much
for your confession for a moment
I want to change the server first
haha
haha just a minute it's simple a
good server hahaha
this speedo is the color and the temples
hi okay hello hello  well, it's already
good, okay then,
sister Reni's problems are in that area,
hah, it's okay, it's a
backache, but I want to relax, I want to
sleep and I want to watch streaming.
ayundari su is really itchy, so the
easy assumption is to
hire a masseuse.
HH is very good. So if
you can, Ayunda's doctor sister
recommends me a masseuse. Yes,
so I have a friend who is a masseuse
and the masseuse is a back massager,
so as long as I have a friend named  Restu, yes,
he is very experienced in
massaging and stepping on the back. So
while M sister Reni is lying down and being
trampled, maybe you can
relax and watch the stream, it's
really good. Can I ask for a
contact info from Restu's sister M
good at stepping on this, Emil, so on,
what you said earlier, don't forget what it is OK,
fine, then I'll
give you the contact, just DM. Yes, okay,
then. Before we
finish this session, is there anything
else you want to say, please?
I want to say it Because
my heart is a pejju, May Stay With Me  Baby stay
under
richfarm trust em can bean rich
get rich get rich
Zain
always have with turning
Cut
regular discoplasty kuflet taste game thank you are
trying to get be careful
geprek Oh my God Thank you for
your time
I finally know what to do to
solve the problem then see
you in the next session
Thank you Happy birthday Brother
bye
[Music]
Kya that's from Rainie who has a backache
I'm so sorry I hope you get well soon Rene
hihihi
No need to do that but the
last one seems to be Hendra Heroes PC
until that's okay, okay, because
we're in, I'm Solo, that's right, thank you for
choosing the service, eh, Aa, thank you
and welcome, you can consult a
no pay resolution doctor where you
can consult about
everyday complaints from the strange to the
strangest before entering.
Consultation session Please select the voice
you want to handle
your complaint oh wait a minute it seems like the server is
strange change the server first OK Sorry
sis
eh Lex shop ah ah Hello
Hello can you hear my voice
Hello sounds cool Alright
before entering the consultation results as if you
choose the afternoon you like  want Press 1
to select the reissue sound, press 2
to select the wisu sound and press 3
to select the Ayunda sound,
you are welcome.
brighten up introduce
yourself and explain about the thing you want to
consult on
OK hello everyone this is anyeofficial from
holiday generation2 Happy birthday
mute senpai anyway
Happy birthday so the story goes like this, like this, like
this lately
yes lately that's the pillow I use
for sleeping  it feels really hard uh
Well, that's what I think I need,
like the animal's tail for a pillow,
for a softer pillow to
sleep on, so how do squirrels send
maybe pillows like
tails?  the soft one that looks like
the flavi that comes out is
delicious but is used for sleeping. Do you have trees that
Thalia recommends, this is m.ked 4 Tanjung Cangat is
in stock, so this time it's just Dad,
yeah, selling Mercedez birthday, there's a
kimagure that's half iced, a
macro action gift wrap that's very Fluffy
Fluffy  which can accompany you to sleep and
also and like the also Om the advantage of a
very weak tail lock for and
cat tails which can help you sleep
faster
please
Wow you have got the warehousesari
friends really a more
oily structure please
along  Endoke betta, if I want a
real tail, that's not allowed, Nasir. That's
okay. Whenever they're free, that's fine, hihihi. You
can give me either an episode or a
little magic.
Yes, thank you too. I'll just take
the original. That's good, that's
the advantage of Jungle Fury. I'll
buy it too.  after the gold is clear, thanks for the
complete description, I
don't want it or not, I just want to give it away, I
can't take it off, where
can I pick it up,
but I'm an account, I'm looking for it,
looking for it, uncle, magic to be able to take it off,
but but tea, but I  If you want
the person too, then you don't have to
let go. OK, I'm tired, I want
the person to fall, Kamen Rider, the walls are
closed,
Putut to this middle school, what is it, but
a number of studies for the time, if
so, not yet. Thank you, I'm
tired. Sis, I have something else to say.
Happy birthday.  on Sesame ae sing
Happy birthday chicken latest news
original song just a little Neng
yesterday if I'm not mistaken we once
said that we both like
breaches ih cell phones are sneaky Dad is
absolutely right slime wixsite.com  relations
Happy birthday
pudding
wash bye
OK
reviewing that earlier Dahlia tried the pizza
wow hi
hi
free hi hi
Hi
can't bear it if that's the case we have even
old we are friends for a while Icu have a drink
first
Indonesia
Hi Ho
Hi
dream of
miciu units OK then
sweeper  Wahyu we friends for a moment,
macho RW xanthorrhizol come in first
Yes
OK then let's wait for
the caller, the singer is
also ours and we are the last ones,
mosquito friends, okay
then, welcome.  in the doctor's consultation session
resolution squirrel where you can
consult about God every day
from the strange to the strangest
before entering the consultation session.
Please select the voice you
want to handle your complaint.
Press 1 to select the result sound. Press
2 to select suwalow issue and  press it
to select the voice Ayunda is welcome
huhuhu alone
Ah I'm about I want to age sit down
first Nokia ass eat like that who
has us I am Vishnu who will
help you in this consultation session
without any further words please
introduce yourself and explain
what you want  consulted
Ah okay okay
hello for a moment I'm Siska pendant Dedi
nijisanji IDM
so I'm
done I want to wear a costume consulted
about
sleep problems Why is my sleep
like what it is, it's the other way around So what
used to be sleeping in the morning the entry is
the territory of sleeping at night now
what happens Ilu hmm
there was also someone who  has a
Mazda E with a charger according to Lee Soo
which according to Dwi SUV Om, the way to fix
it is by
defeating the desire to sleep
so if we don't sleep it means
our Uncle  just don't have the wrong sleep
Fadli I don't fall asleep calm down be
nucke nocturna so Lahm a zombie isn't it
Be a person who can't sleep
After that after not sleeping maybe
during am1
Twitter miraculously
your problems will
get better Yes because usually
mk5 lam that after  one week, yes, these are the
experiences of one week,
I talked to an expert. Well, after
one week of not sleeping, we will
fall asleep. But the right time is the
evening after that, then your sleep time
will be good again
Hey, you're like valcke, Agung
Hi  Sis, it was my fault Trio just
woke up.
Actually, I didn't sleep, it's
here, okay, national, ready, okay, thank you,
thank you. Have you
come home, the answer is,
Hm, it seems a bit difficult, but
it looks like it's a bit logistical,
maybe you can try it if you can
afford it. If you haven't  try it, don't
know yet, ask Los Angeles
So before our consultation time
ends, are there any messages and words you
want to convey
visually Happy birthday,
I hope sir, today will definitely be a
smooth day,
smile Sorry, I'm really new to the
meaning of issues, you know why hihihi, why
congratulations  What do you know  look at the universal problem
you have a life
love you've stopped by sometime play
again yeah Win again ion trending again ye
bye bye
high too HayDay the rest baby
OK so that's it Yes Teteh we are
very charming
this viscount Yes that's it for a moment
sunna sunah sunah sunah sunah rosul
chat for a while bro blue finished bro it's
not difficult bro
Hi
Riza
Riza prepare this last tomorrow afternoon right
this is the last because eh because
the impact is really making hello
Hi
this fortune is special so Rachel will play it
it's now
hehehe hihihi
and also
this is already part got the message got
the message
so I'm worried about saying it Now
okay
pieces of [ __ ]
Oh up that's happy birthday hey
[Applause]
Hi
wow Lee sub ilove you Happy birthday to
you Mama Hao
[Music]
Wow whispered Juli
Oh this is my God this is my
birthday hi hi
Hi
[Music]
If Thank you forever I
Hi
robot
[Music]
Lego DC Heroes Hi
that uh  uh
hai hahaha huhuhu
Hai
Hehehe yes
Andai singkuh W huhuhu
i-i-i-i am yellow amawi voyance
submarine DC ryukei I have my Heaven Sword
video arrow So I just pure it There and
haven't watched
dipunaturi menatur Aikatsu video by
Abdul Wachid sotahu Smash New in
natru
Chaeri Donald's
Omega censor
rich's years often
Twitter hahaha hahaha
hahaha hi hi hi hi hi
hello what  what play degan Okay let's
play the game loudspeaker one more time okay okay okay
osos hai hai
hahaha
squid [ __ ]
upil feeling
basket pun
[Applause]
Hoi Wow rishou ilove you how much key
Mama I Hi
wow Yusuf Juli aha
ngarep Hi
Jelly Cupi
birthday to you by
huhuhu
Ouch
Hai hehehe Hai
Sancu forever
I
Ketut
vegetable director take cup with
LCD duit ambani emergen  running
text automatically
You know how stupid it is to reduce viruses,
this full body bearing pad is absurd afiful Aa makes a
seawheel
[Music]
I am happy
very very dry brush Day
Thank you forever I
should go to the idea first just mate myself
Sumo meaning for a while right from
drinking so much earlier  wait a minute yes
acclaimed eh eh
Indonesia
ndang fast yes hai
hai
the lounge
ndeso hai hai hai hai hai hai hai hai
Indonesia hai hai
OK
Google Map Map hai hai Hi
I have a body thank  you so much for am
yes so the doctor is the doctor who handles your
problems.
You will also be in GWS in Wow.
What do you think about about the
doctor who will be a great help you with
your problem because one Who needs help
yeshu
however
I know  why Grace before this so After
this arisu wants to make Aa wants to watch long
Yes what the long
m-watch long what is called hots long ori
song so I'm worried it will still be
playing mut'ah it's still low it
will still remain onstream so we're done with this
will watch long when yeshua
al-habib Muhammad short white long
product from your songs and the Wings on the
move comment in the life chat-an
in the description so please please go
the day the original song
[Musik]
Pink Beach  South long enough so before
before work along Together I will
promote worse gnewe about my god oh my
god Yes my birthday March
sold out ah
Hi
to aw eh ey Hi how to Yes I have Yours
hai hai hello there is kimonkoro yes
dakimakura to  science
lemi
friends your first cheese Ilham tu just
Syauqi makura front side is like this
and that makes websites like this and
enter Philosophy
ehem-ehem memorize
Eighteen B AMP
is securempm Yes that's the chain of Om
Thank you
abreso Tale soya one step closer cover
issue
RSU tailpiece freestyle twice-yes the
first step detail teeth make slide small
March should you first please
Hi know news next time all the big
Seoul Seoul slide show TV One day realse
skrub seorg please krusell please  by
nathaniel
calculate2 get am a very nice sleep at
night slime dakimakura
facial and in the front side will have
results and the back side welcome Ayunda
everynight
Chaeri by Yugo Out Boy atomy made from
the front side is Reason the text is
ayune sama Eastwood you  singing
Indonesian about having your toys I'm a
Indra kimagure
airbrushing khairin Mr Singh bad I guess
it's getting
i-amt not
I am in the dark Emang Rich
foreign solsel you guys how to be  at
because it's me
some picture there should be kind in a
Church side What do you want to sleep
with three or leave me
nice overnight
x-over so many Nights
sleep with pleasure and other Network
Ayunda
with books by the year by The Wind Blows
OST  One on each side
dubsmash Well
hello so much
so I have seen the real Dreams
drill product each have love will leave
that Feels Like You know your new single
free with love teddy bear It Feels Like
Tonight Show
On The Other Side swept
showcase and the tale is say bye alike
detail each style
talk about two by two three one set your
heart you will get a higher score the
postcard willhouse my am Signature I
will ilhan
friend's designature myself in the for
Indonesian brush
Ayu  kinget demage for Pediasure Wilona
Once a leg Hi So please wait for the
information letter on lead thank you so
much and I think I'll wait for free day
you're
out with full day
sweet holiday for the Premier song
e-cash  brothers openlink know
where you like this
scheme more uh meet
nation4d.com litura restore
si okay your
Heroes iwill
halo halo turn off my take newsmy
Havers system I will turn off my my
background music and Within Just wait
here I am not crazy please
Hi Cahyono to your family tell your
style your most style your teacher
tell your friends Where are
you everybody
nmr retweet this first real quick
real will be serum Facebook as well
there die
butchered anus William
excited and RW 1 cm
ginger freestyle
wastiru ledekin reynoso let's go trade
leads is a
senswell
sorry-sorry
researchers are there to see you
move first please friends
tend to raid Yes is Indonesia
Hi minute
Hi also similar to the
negligee
that makes Sule Omega
hi hi
talking about catfish
here we are
talking
sleep Egypt refreshing strange
[Music]
Grandma for example How come you haven't YouTube where are
you my year
eh have you ever had TV
sing-sing or
not yet totot friends It's
okay  okay now I'm curious to jump all song
first Two Brother Rich
stainless steel
writing is it with you
is missing
until the code
LV KW
Sri skins risking
primer Thank you very much for giving us
now Premier League is the day
See The First really blasting Years
since Against
The Nine  eight seven six five madam
Hi Ho
Hi Ho Hi Ho
Hai Fahri
[Music]
Hello
huhuhu
hahaha hehehe
ah ah ah ah
ih
ouch
hahaha
hehehe
[Music]
hahaha  Huhuhu hahaha
Call I'm sick
call your song interpretation Yes please
you so much for
watching each sentence respect is in the
song please Note for you
inspiration for your comment terrorist for
your
for your theories about the song for
xxyyxx full day Illustration for the
movie show
please yusdi hairstyle guys entware ah
elishandi you and The Verge bikin cake
cake song in your favorite
anymp4 streaming platformer
slow tick you so much
regarding the  the song is
sai2 according to it immediately it's time for me
to welcome that Nothing you so much for
your support
for the soul
Hi I
wish list includes keywords eluts di
online the song Rich two Rich am  four
four way okay
stabilizer the song with high stakes
Well now thank you so much Hi
extremely droidlime
eh it's really an emotional a
time for me but thank you so much
Winger ah
mellow now
you
Hahaha
I'll check this too selling cakes cakes cakes
thank you  you so much
too much the way
Hi
this is synch
soha see straight away genderuwo
suryayusra
Chaeri sadu dan seri to Wherever share
wherever You want to share
as much as possible
as far as possible Yes
and use the hashtag eyebrow Endi  for you
share it everywhere
my heart is happy
I Thank you so much everybody this is
this is my gift to you guys on my
birthday VCD Sorry Kim Mi so many
things Through The Years so before and
The Stream I just want to say that
I  am so happy
to be able to work
quiet here with you guys ow fully our Our
Song Yi fridge One Million views and our
channel help my channel well show Rich
One Million songs no pressure but will
get there are you sleeping so thank you so
much for  being with me and After The
Stars
yoo-ri  avitin online Pian at night I am
so don't forget to visit
and will have a birthday tim Elia
fitness well so i you your wedding
forget a pleasant to my song
religiously hahaha Sayang
lisyaiin outside to say thank you as
well for all of my Guess  the day and
Also for May offer for my Manager
book for healthy dream
biting Pinch the cheek for helping me a true
abbreviation for my birthday show I'll
show like Thank you guys for making this
birthday asmaria Space browser thank you
so much I
Reason with  you guys are a fitting end
remix PoPiPo time body bergkaiser reload
spotipo Raid the
needs of people
people Resto people 77 do
Hai
Dede babibo Photobucket Photobucket
shop
butterfly nih butterfly
Nyi
Hai
[Music] komputer
yt-api.com
kupu  -butterfly nil but [Music] but [Music] [
Music] maybe Banyumas a topnotch hai hai [Music] hai hai hai hai
Hai
dedek si Beli duck eh nusu iwill have
lots of Other Changes to do as well the
brow And The Beast the deaf rich's
Hi Ho