[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
thank you
Katy King
oh hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello
I don't hear any sound wait I think
probably only if I'm in the game
should there be sound
I don't hear anything wait a second
keep getting
this is oh I think I heard something
what did I
this is a very special
uh well at least you can hear me for now
don't worry I'll fix it this is a very
special one time only
sure
one time only actually rise up free
suddenly hear it very loudly
okay nice
yeah
um I feel like rides are free Alchemist
of the end and the secret key just came
out
uh I'm not really sponsored but I was
given a key
so thank you very much for providing the
key go away take more games
oh my God
ah
uh yeah literally came out like in the
past couple hours
[Music]
and I as you may know I played
um I didn't rise of one and two on my
channel before
foreign
[Music]
I got so many other things going on at
the moment
so I have to sit
some well
maybe priorities so to say oh it's
pretty loud in my ears
whoa is it a okay volume for you guys
though
thanks for the membership guys
um
[Music]
a bit loud okay you joined membership
during the rise of one playthrough so
might as well use this today thank you
yeah well ryza
um was like
oh quite a journey for us
we played one and two on my channel and
it took a long time
but we always had like some really chill
times back then
it was very
fun and relaxing and cute lots of cute
yeah
I really enjoyed the previous games
so I'm curious how this new and
most likely last one right
uh ryza game would go and I was like
already really surprised when they
decided to do ryza 2 because I didn't
expect it at all
uh and then you know after right at two
it was like all right all right rise is
like really popular now
so I guess possibly that could be a
third one but no way have they ever done
like free
in a row of the same game
of the same like series
have they ever
[Music]
what what yes yes they have
free
Iris that's the way Iris well that's a
really old one isn't it
always almost always comes in freeze
yeah but I feel like the previous ones
like Liddy and swell and Sophie
all those more recent ones that I played
they never had free or even two
did it just kind of like change
maybe where did I put my oh here's my
water okay
yeah yeah they used to always be free
hmm yeah well Sophie I am getting a
second one now
okay so it really seems like they're
moving on from Riser after this you
would think but now they also announced
an anime which is really cool
[Music]
videos
yeah
there were always trilogies
in a shared world but with different
protagonists
oh
so even the eye is one for example did
that one have different protagonists
then
is it a first for it to have the same
protagonist three times in a row
[Music]
I spin up with Plata as the emcee yo I
would absolutely love that
um
iris is different protagonist oh
I was was the first trip
who's right who's wrong motion you're
supposed to know
without other people say no Iris are
different from
right that's the first of the same okay
okay I got one guide again for a moment
[Music]
you haven't even seen baby Plata what do
you mean
is there an official baby Plata what
what
do you mean
[Music]
I mean I think I would have liked to see
like
was it Monaco or Claudia
as uh uh like bigger Focus maybe but I
see why they go back to rhiza
it's cloudy all right it's not is it
Claudia
wait on it
even to this day I just don't know what
I'm talking about
hi there
maybe if I get absolutely
Enchanted
there could be a chance where we
continue to play it but I don't know
generally I don't have the time for it I
think
but we'll see
okay
you recommend the prologue move video
does it have like some
some copyrighted music
if not then we can watch it
might be interesting for everybody else
just to recap okay
you can view the summary of the previous
games with blah blue blue this section
contains a lot of content related to the
story of the previous games we want yeah
yeah for you guys and for I guess
reminding myself to if it was Claudia or
Monica
miruka
[Music]
um
I remember too
[Music]
foreign
I gotta oh
my god oh I think I absolutely blasted
that uh boss away
the dragon I absolutely destroyed I
think
remember
wow
that's why we met um the other girl
right
didn't we
kilogram
s
foreign
[Music]
I don't think I was using Rose bombs yet
thou Caiman rise up to when I finally
figured out
there's a song that I don't wanna play
probably because I'm scared where's my
mouse
can I if I skip does it skip um just
these like ending credits and then move
on to ryza 2 I wonder
danger skips everything okay maybe milta
and uh
how does keyboard work
okay
because I was able to recognize the
important things that are hidden in a
simple and ordinary days
oh it's already ending okay
should be fine probably
audio jungle
three years later
three years IRL it wasn't for years
right for a moment that sounded so
realistic
red red
okay
you and me and our backstory
unbelievably
[Music]
eggs
all right so fee never turned out to be
an evil mastermind right but I thought
they were gonna be
today
[Applause]
[Music]
oh I love them all
except this one
foreign
[Music]
somebody
is
not gonna be back right
ample with his eye bags
same TBH
[Music]
is
we did so much for this little
[Music]
foreign
numbers
this is a really good like
explanation
good recap
um
[Music]
our adventure in the Royal Capital came
to an end
so sad oh I was so sad here I was like
suddenly so emotional oh I remember oh
Treasures I gained on our great
adventure close to my heart
we've had a lot of Adventures there was
anxiety and regret but also a ton of fun
to be had
oh
the bonds I have with everyone will
always be there no matter how far apart
we are these bonds will never be broken
foreign
[Music]
oh man
wow wow
okay now I'm so hyped let's go
let's see I don't know how this is the
first time I'm playing it with keyboard
last time I was using controller but my
controllers of course is always not
working on PC so oh we're gonna try
how how do I start a new game
oh there we go
was not enter
I like this loading screen where fries
are walking just like she also walks
she's saying the same thing again
yeah yeah
yeah
guys are lynched out
foreign
what is it this time
oh
cute fluffy
Stout is not real in German no
he didn't Naruto run
see oh excuse me sir who are you
I mean I know the one on the left but
yeah
continue
[Music]
the payment to hire the other guy
hold on guys
the crash that we couldn't play before
the mean guy
[Music]
hey y'all
whatever
[Music]
how to fight let's go
who
[Music]
okay tutorial because I really need that
at least that now for using my keyboard
comment begins when you come in contact
with a monster in the field
uh the goal and balance to defeat all
the enemies the once their HP reaches
zero you'll win duh
uh conversively uh conversely if the HP
of all allies participating in the
battle we're just there with the players
defeated
the comic progresses in real time oh the
white gosh on the right side is the wait
time gauge when it accumulates enough
for one round you can take action
is this new noise is the same as last
time
you don't say
you die if you were killed
it's looking the same
okay
press left Mouse click to perform a
normal attack if done correctly you can
hit up three times in a row done
correctly
okay at the rat temps perform a triple
hit hold dead skin well so what's the
right time
one and well if I would like to do a
triple one two three oh
how do I know it's the right time
I don't know
I just smash
oh I really just mashed Okay so
smash okay nice nice nice nice
[Music]
you can gain AP action points from
normal attacks and one day p is
accumulated you can activate skills AP
can also be gained from normal attacks
by allies
your day is still timing
I mean if you press too late then it's
over but so you just have to mash it
um
okay
I'm gonna attack too can I
just read throwing up
[Laughter]
you leave me no time okay let's do it
again hi
press red while stick to block while
blocking you will take less damage but
you're waiting time gosh stops
[Music]
I wonder what they were saying
don't worry oh wow
when the guys above the enemy reaches
its maximum it will attack if you block
at the right moment you will perform
Precision guard and receive myself hey I
wonder if it matters to like if I just
have the block uh like the whole time
if I block less and if I just like put
it up in the very right moment
[Music]
you can time it to the hit to do less
damage
now it does matter okay
[Music]
your turn will never come if you keep
blocking oh wow wait this seems new
okay
[Music]
we're gonna do it again
oh oh I guess I could skip
wait which one is that
there we go okay use S and right Mouse
click while holding space to activate
skills activate
what three I have to hold free things
s
right Mouse click and space
[Music]
whoops
how am I supposed to remember that
there's so many keys on the keyboard uh
why couldn't it just happen like one
okay
uh
s
after attacking one
after that
[Music]
I tried doing it
I understand
[Music]
yes
hold space
then as should I hold space while
already attacking normally
hold space and press s or right click
just hold space
[Music]
ah what what it went away so fast what
are even my skills
what what
[Music]
okay ah
huh
might be easier on controller
um
what
and now I can't open skills anymore
well come on
[Music]
because it became okay
I did something
let me try again
wait I want to do the right click one
[Music]
eh
hey why couldn't she only do it once
because maybe it doesn't like the space
after all
hmm
one attack one and then skill only hit
one left okay
oh
okay it will take some time to figure
this out I think let me try again
timing the timing yo
just pressing it
in the end I'm kind of okay just
pressing it at the same time
[Music]
this seems like
uh you might want to use a controller
for this I feel like controller would
probably be easier to use
um
but I mean I did it right but
uh yeah I did it so I can skip this now
right
[Music]
why doesn't it Autumn I didn't when is
it not automatically move on to the next
thing did I do it wrong
[Music]
I think I knew it laughs
yeah I didn't do it right
it wants me to do both
[Music]
oh well we'll do that another time
oh
I can do that that's fine I'll be fine
I'll be fine actually
will also increase tactics level the
higher the level the higher the combo
count for normal attacks and the more
experienced gained
this concludes truth oh [\h__\h]
all right uh
how do I block again
what
I don't understand
attack attack
I'm so confused
and I did a chain didn't I
said
I did a good block now too I think
[Music]
[\h__\h]
is it a bad block
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I can do what I can do
it it's a different system though than
before oh look at her flexing
[Music]
you need to hold space without attacking
foreign
[Music]
is very German it's also not really a
name
cute her face is cute
I'll check for the subtitles after this
dialogue
[Music]
how about this
is
okay
even the NPCs are kind of cool
oh
spooky
cool
Alchemist Bridge
honorable alchemistry
what whatever
can't reach into the code with the key
in die hands what
what
gangemari
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
before
walking more dialogue
foreign
I remember her
[Music]
please
thin tree
Lance
damn what a treat
I don't know if I complain ah whatever
it's not one of those
[Music]
I was just told I can't play the ending
theme
this is the opening theme right
worst case I'll cut it out of the VOD
but I think we should be fun
[Music]
do we have to start from the beginning
again learning all the beginners recipes
again
probably
wow that's a beautiful key
[Music]
first it was free now it's a key
so has she been a character before too
that I'm forgetting about
[Music]
can speak for the recipes
Monica
[Music]
what is it about these scenes where the
whole group is there to make me so
emotional
don't leave
the bed Monica
oh man
same place again we keep on coming back
here
[Music]
oh
phew
almost
this is also
uh are the where the dialogues like this
in ryza 2 also completely voice acted
finally a text box
they were was I just listening to them
or was I reading them anyway
out loud
might as well try the series you should
only story stuff ah okay okay okay only
the important stuff
foreign
thank you
you can press a button when you see a
little word
but sorry I just looked at my phone
while I was reading your thing because
my brother wrote me something on
WhatsApp
what was she saying oh it's careful and
doesn't get stranded in the lake I hope
I have some fishermen watching over the
ocean just in case
um
ah
a young man who took up the sword and
works for the village used to be just a
scruffy henchman to boss but perhaps
inspired by his growth but to step up on
his own
okay lumbar
yeah that's cool
especially foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
wrestling Stout a young Alchemist on
gurkenland AKA cucumber Island full of
brightness and bigger once an ordinary
Village girl she grew up to be an
alchemist after partying with free hell
yeah she lost her enthusiasm and spent
her days as a shell of herself
but so she was depressed so espresso but
now changed to continue his research on
maintain to maintain cucumber Island
should we read the towel one two
wait I never knew his last name
he's a novice scholar was being a
student in the Royal capital in addition
to the experience came during his
journey as well as his education he is
continuing to deepen his knowledge and
understanding every day facing the
biggest unknowns of his life on the
Clark Isles tells heart is racing oh
with his friends he uses his knowledge
to solve the mysteries on the island
[Music]
foreign
in case I missed it or forgot who she is
in the middle of the game
thank you
oh those looks great
she did an ooVoo face oh
now
I want to play the whole game what the
hell
no no not yet we'll we'll see we'll see
me too
[Music]
the circuit art of combining multiple
objects to mix it's not so secret
anymore
we all we all are able to play the games
a forgotten technique required talent to
handle which I don't have
I need to ask you guys how to do it
[Music]
and I thought an experienced
professional Alchemist shall never be
out of ingredients Riser what are you
doing you should know better by now
rise I'm not lifting a finger Bulls
neither though
those trees look funny oh yeah the world
wielding let's go
[Music]
pal has joined my party
what about bulls
there he is
doing my party let's read the heir to
the bronen family a family in ryza and
her friend's hometown of how about
and her friends used to be on bad terms
with him no I remember but they have no
reconciled let him becoming a sincere
young man he did not join the adventure
ryza and her friends had in the capital
which made him feel somewhat reserved
with them now working on the
self-discipline in order to stand
alongside his friends well damn
[Music]
surprised they added him to the party
okay press space while moving toward a
slightly higher step to climb up okay
cool oh wait she really really climbs
uh quests show ex show Quest objectives
oh oh it shows me what I gotta pick up
I'm getting the case where the event
will occur occur occur which monsters to
defeat what materials to collect and
where to report the quest once the
target for that location is achieved the
quest will continue nicer
Target icons are displayed on the area
map as well as on the mini map and field
screen quests that have not yet been
activated are marked with a question
mark and when the quest is in progress
this will change to exclamation mark on
the screen you can check it via help
oh photo mode yeah okay I don't need to
know about that now
wow wow can I swim I want to swim let's
go
[Music]
mini map
oh well okay hey here the keyboard
controls really don't bother me
um actually pretty easy to use
I'm not even sponsored and I'm saying
that
[Music]
wow
field welcome to the Westfield weather
yes
oh I remember this place you remember
guys remember
she runs really fast wait how do I run
did that tell me how how do I run
look at her cute
oh but her boob is reset weirdly do you
see that
[Music]
oh yeah
whoa oh my God
[Music]
let's go Sonic oh
exploration landmarks
there are special landmarks in the field
discovering landmarks increases the
amount of information displayed on the
area map is useful for exploration
[Music]
I'm guessing this Hideout was one oh
fire outside interesting
can I go inside
wait what was this was the entrance
proceed
[Music]
I have nothing to do
I am free
[Music]
sounds like some whole life
Yen members
okay
nice
looks pretty yeah let's go collect some
stuff where where go to the pixie Forest
I guess follow this way because on the
mini map it's showing around that area
what is this
sign on the menu oh Vines is that what
it's showing me oh sorry
whoa
that didn't even take nine seconds
get it
get it oh oh I probably need like a
white can I go
oh that was seven seconds left
seven seconds so it doesn't even take
seven seconds either
oh
which means if they have this kind of
thing then they also probably have the
one where we go on all fours remember
what's this why am I here
can you hang on to that no
yeah honestly I didn't want to say it
but her chest looks bigger I might just
be the jacket I don't know
she's probably uh what How old is she
probably still growing
oh
I wish I wish I wish I wish right now
this looks like to me you know what this
looks like
I feel like I'm playing one of those
anime MMORPGs
oh my God I wish it was that right now
holy [\h__\h]
I wish it was an anime with my more
Pidgey
[Music]
let's go
she's 21 in this game oh 17. in 120 and
two
yeah
get get it can I not
I wanna punch it
fun she's all grown up yeah for real she
can even drink alcohol now I mean she
could have already drunken alcohol if
she was European which I mean look at
her name I guess she is European
is her world in Europe
where is it
gather medicinal ingredients gather
edibles
uh-huh
how many
[Music]
oh how many how many donuts oh
isn't the Beehive an edible
you broke
fresh berries there we go oh I just had
to get one I'll get more though
oh I like the way they break like glass
huh
I'm only with me but the other one was
fine with a stick
stick bunk
and this one is okay with stick bunk
again
oh well look for a place to crouch I
wanna is there one close by
no
[Music]
um
I want more though oh sorry
[Music]
I want more
I need more ingredients you pick them
flowers where's the flower on fire
special flour which can resist fire
what's up
special one
[\h__\h] sorry
[Music]
you don't need to stop anymore to get
you mean
you mean I have an endless inventory is
that we what are you saying to me
no way
foreign
I still will get the full inventory I
guess that would be like too like yeah
overpowered or
what do you mean I don't have to stand
for it so I can do it while running let
me see let me see let me see I mean
if I have to punch them probably have to
stand up
more ingredients
oh wait I owe them I automatically went
back somehow my unconscious
let me back all right all right are we
going in
Carlos though
well there must be a tattoo in the house
right
okay okay okay okay okay
let's try to understand this from the
get-go I can do this
I see a bear behind you oh
there was a 10 in the background but can
I talk to it that's the question let her
cook yes let me cook synthesis is the
art of creating new items from multiple
ingredients for the power of alchemy
a recipe is required for synthesis the
more recipes you gain the more items you
can make
lesson size grass beans
okay are these like uh Health items
when you select the recipe the material
Loops will be displayed ingredients are
put into material Loops to synthesize is
this the same system as ryza 2 because I
feel like didn't they change a little
bit from one to two but this looks kind
of familiar I think
[Music]
I think it's the same okay
do I remember this at all it's been like
over a year I think
each material Loop has a specific type
of ingredient that can be used there are
also elements fire ice cold air I think
I remember that oh boy
ingredients also have elements and when
an ingredient with the same element as
those in the material Loop is used the
element balance will be accumulated uh
okay sure I read that if I understood
that is another story but will be fun
with a certain number of element values
are accumulated the material Loop will
be leveled up and become more effective
accumulating element values in the
material Loop and making them effective
is the first step in synthesis
uh-huh
sure sure the material Loop in which
ingredients can be can be added from the
beginning is called a core ingredient
Loop
uh-huh
the core ingredient Loop is a material
Loop into which ingredients must be
added
aha
first put the ingredients into all the
core ingredient loops
oh thank God I'm currently not planning
on making this into the series
uh
try it out uh what what do I do
I
remember this oh
they put it on top of here that's cool
and then
okay it looks a bit different but like
the in favor it's the same
and then I can I can probably already
make it no not yet
wait what what what how do I open this
again
[\h__\h] how do I how do I open the the like
previous dialogue again
wasn't there a way of doing that because
I accidentally did it several times
I want to read back
um
press up it doesn't work
oh let's put the item from here you can
add ingredients until the quantity
reaches zero
okay this is a trade Loop which is an
important material Loop to transfer the
traits of the ingredient to the
synthesized item
when you accumulate element values in
the trade Loop and leveled it up you
will be able to transfer trades transfer
trades allows you to transfer the trades
of the ingredients to the item you are
synthesizing uh-huh and I I mean that
assumes seems logical
I think you told me that twice now in
other words unlocking trade Loops adding
material oh there's a typo materials
with traits
and transferring towards I'm I'm
tester I improved breeder
transferring trades will allow you to
make more powerful items
what
[Music]
hi ball let's go I'm so proud you never
noticed that but I did
ESL
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't don't bully her for that man
can I synthesize a croissant now we have
the basics of synthesis let's take a
look of the at the steps of synthesis
again okay number one add ingredients to
all corn ingredient loops
number two adding green is to trade
loops and other material Loops to boost
number three start synthesis when the
number of inputs reaches zero or when
space is pressed aha
this is the basic flow of synthesis now
let's start synthesizing freely press
space to start emphasizing immediately
why must it be such a difficult word
synthesize freely oh my God freedom
how about this one
[Music]
can I look down
quality
okay I would want to add the highest
quality one right I have two with 51.
this one has like a quality trait though
yeah
what's that mean
no but still like this would give more
quality even though this has a quality
trait
prioritize quality or traits
but this one has a quality trait
I'll just go for this one
ah Quality Sales for more
[Music]
oh do I really want to use everything I
could already like finish now but
I mean
let's add some flour
flower can we go let's do it
uh let's add let's add healing increases
item heal amount by up to 15 percent
well I can do more I can do all of them
not really oh yeah yeah that was
something was like they're locked and
then I can later unlock them if I I like
reuse them and then re-synthesize them
and raise the quality by doing that
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I
remember I remember but for now the one
trade we actually need is already there
so we could be good
um
I remember
something
and I eat the maoam
one of those chewy candies I want this
for strawberry
quantity one mm-hmm
I remember I'm cooking
cute look at her
hair haircuts
[Music]
I really hope that even after rise up
Rave
um
that they would maybe not every game but
maybe in some games they would consider
to continuously use this concept artist
I just love his art style his or her I
don't know
so much
Liza you're going to move on
because like before even before they
kept reusing the same artist over and
over and over again for many games
um
I'm following that artist
I really love his art style yeah he
designed the new Miku racing Miku and
gave her also marvelous assets hmm
the artist that Drew me was from
previous
um athletic games
[Music]
social
oh
my God does she have migraines
oh y'all look at her
fancy earring it goes behind the ear
cool
um
you remember the recipe is this how
we're going to Speed Run oh
we're just gonna make whatever came to
our mind
thank you for reminding us I guess
I wonder is it the key are we gonna make
the key right away wait we're not even
actually doing it
foreign this is the key where's the
toilet
Chihuahua
okay man
no not at all
kiwawa
they did that because of me pretty sure
okay
super treats in rare cases you can
obtain materials with powerful traits
called super trades ah the ones with the
Plus
super trucks can be transferred to items
during synthesis by using materials with
super traits as the base ingredients
however it only works once you unlock
the super traits slot material
Edward here it said special trade slot
however
suit trades can only be transferred from
raw ingredients an item that inherited
super traits from A past surfaces cannot
transfer them in a future one
was that a thing too previously I feel
like it was maybe
if you want to transfer a super trait
use a material of the desired super
trace it has the best ingredients
[Laughter]
um
still
[Music]
um
that's kind of a title but not the one I
could talk to
[Music]
she said the thing one more
why did you say anything but shut up I
want to hear Reza
no no
time
no why are you getting mixed up in this
I'm not talking to you I don't want to
hear your tattoos
I only want to hear about my own tattoos
[Music]
what the hell we need more tattoos
nothing
oh
time is passing
I'm just looking for tattoos
[Music]
okay uh where are we going to the city
we gotta go on the boat
[Music]
Kyle
why does this one not talk to me what
the hell
that's like
so hurtful
it was getting all excited already cat
whoa
interesting cat
[Music]
wow
wait for another angle oh
it has a really cute pattern wow
remember that big ass cheese I think
they had it previously too
my paper let's go
you can pet the cat 10 out of 10.
I agree
probably can pet some dogs as well if we
wanna
[Music]
hmm
oh man did they like I mean they must
have like remodeled the city to like
improve Graphics right I mean they can
just like reuse everything right
he also looks nice
wait
I didn't realize because items from them
too if you do it for the first time
I'm just gonna completely ignore her
using things as normal yeah but it looks
nice I mean but it's probably just uh
what do you call this effect again this
blurry effect
makes it look so nice
motion blur a bloom bloom yeah I think
what I mean is the bloom
I gotta like compare screenshots it must
have at least one
done some touch-ups
can I jump down
[Music]
I don't think that was possible in ryza
too
yo I mean you could swim but could you
really jump down here I don't think so
whoa whoa cool how do I get back up a
little bit
a bit what
um
I I didn't
is it the consequences of my own actions
I can't go here okay
for a prompt
um
[Music]
why would we hurt the turtle
don't worry guys
you're not getting soft locked by
jumping into the water thank God okay
let's go on to the quest lady
foreign
character almost like more of an NPC I
really like her design too
she's like etchan
like a fantasy version of vegan
are the medicines ready
oh yeah I guess here you can have
although
eh I should have that's the thing right
when you that's what I did in previous
games for quests I always make a
shittier object
and I didn't do it this time damn it
um
this is my favorite sad character
[Music]
oh
something dropped
and uh
did you see
cameraman what are you doing
what's this I mean
I do not understand the focus at all
oh
maybe same
can I make a joke maybe it's the same
cameraman from
orifice
oh ah I'm roasting everyone on all sides
wait wait can I just check who's Reza
again ah thank you okay thank you thank
you thank you for so much I almost
forgot
[Music]
I just had to check who I was really
quickly
[Music]
not enough shots of random people in the
town
heart of the island is Nani
power reactor on the man-made Island a
few years ago ryza fix it allowing its
stable operation for a while so that was
in ryza one right
well aboard tonight oh
Dusty ah
that thing yeah I totally remember that
the flotation device
a device that floats the man-made island
is actually a relic of all times using
Advanced Alchemy to float on like
um
[Music]
why is that though is broken
I granted for this one to level 50. damn
man that was annoying I think
go towel
foreign
[Music]
don't worry
Claudia Monica
[Music]
you are not Monica
in order
Claudia balance she is a bright and
successful businesswoman and and the
daughter of the Balance factory she has
taken a small denture and turned it into
a high-profile growing company a person
of business and a close friend of ryza
through their Journey no matter how far
apart they are and despite not spending
much time together there's a bond that
them there that will never change
ah
for real
true
don't make me cry it's too real
um
[Music]
wait I need explanation for that why is
there no glossary for that fast horse
is that like literally speaking
was it a figure of speech
what what about horses
Uma
um
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
Buy sell coin exchange or deliver
huh
I will not tell you what happened
gold coin exchange allows you to
exchange gold coins
which are very rarely found in a field
oh for Valium items with the liver you
can earn rewards by giving them
specified giving items specified in
quests to people who are going to start
okay
I'm so excited is there any tattoos in
here
wow pretty flower can I get some
materials in here
and another crazy dream besides the
corona one that I would like some
explanation from you guys anyone who can
explain my dream to me
um I was on like
an ice cliff
but like
it's not quite a cliff it was like a
really steep
uh Mountain Ice Mountain
and um
I me and some other people we suddenly
started oh wait there's something here
we we suddenly started uh
dancing to a Beyonce's song
quiet while the father left behind I got
an achievement
oh many things I've written in The
Travelers Memoirs some of them also
point to certain places where you may
encounter treasures and Powerful enemies
uh okay I might read that later
eh yeah we started dancing to Beyonce so
we really like we were doing the same
routine and routine and we all got down
like kind of on the floor and then we
well while we were dancing pretty much
in the beginning immediately
uh we all like fell down the cliff
it was like I don't know 100 meters fall
and we crashed on the ice on the ground
people were watching us by the way and
cheering for us we crashed
on the icy ground and Ice wander
and
people were like oh no oh my God what a
disaster
I did not take falling damage no
surprisingly but I still acted as if
that was like just really really
problematic and and you know
which Beyonce said I have to like I
think it was
um
an old one the one that she does with ah
it's not and it goes like
[Music]
that's where we fell down that part
I think that's the part where we fell
down
and uh yeah we didn't die though but it
was kind of weird like man because the
ice and when I fell and landed some more
ice crashed on my head too
and yeah it was just um kind of
dangerous so uh
don't dance uh to Beyonce on an ice
cliff
it's that simple
[Music]
well
oh wait somebody actually took it
serious thank you
jumping off point slippery slope
nervousness dance might be in relation
to Fest probably a projected fear of
what could have gone wrong
who knows
maybe we'll never know
[Music]
I can't even reach
don't tell me how to live my life
I should go ice climbing with Beyonce oh
my God I don't even
I don't even know her
and then let's go uh wait so there's a
pink and a blue pointer now
oh mother
which one do I go to also oh climbing
what's up here
it's just the same stuff I get outside
tunnel no
it's so sad
[Music]
title
why is there so many tattoos they're
teasing me
where do I go
coconut
how do I scroll in
I'm scrolling but it doesn't zoom in how
do I zoom in
I have that right there wait good there
we go no we don't go
oh no there we go
is this where I am
where am I at here am I okay I'll just
continue going up
foreign
[Music]
thank you wow where did you get those
from what
yo there's so many
no I don't want to talk to you you don't
give me anything
only the animals are worth talking to
me
clean water
scrap paper oh another cat
so many
cute we kind of stole that from her I
feel like that was gonna be her dinner
is that okay
is that really okay
[Music]
I think she was planning on eating that
oil tree fruit which looks exactly like
an avocado suspiciously
okay I'm gonna go for a swim
wow hey that's so nice
ah okay this time we have to go up by
the ladder
oh
there's a little standing Point here
[Music]
there's avocado oil so oil tree is
correct
why not just say avocado
oil
okay one Quest run over here which I
think is the main quest
a
right that's so nice
no problemo leave it to me
okay gladly I want some action
local Alchemist picks up the trash only
talks of animals and swims in the
fountain debts totally not me
there
[Music]
pink one as well
it's even further ahead
[Music]
of the power of taru that has been
bestowed upon me
should I shall Crush
however you say it in fancy English I
don't know how do I get up there
oh
wow she can climb
thank you
I gotta pick up everything guys you know
how it is
[Music]
okay one more no
there we go
oh no
it just disappeared in the void like a
ghost cat
AKA like Kelly's cat
oh wait don't scare the cat don't scare
the cat
as a loot Goblin myself I approve you
call yourself a loot Goblin
you
a dog but I mean that's really realistic
like normally if you run
that fast next to a cat she will
probably get chocolate
[Music]
actually it was so funny last night I
was laying in bed in bed
and uh I had like one of my hands on on
my cat just cuddling petting with her
and she was sleeping
and then I just I I blew some air out of
my nose like
like that
and she got so spooked from it like she
was like she was like for one second she
like was break dancing
and then in the next second she just
kind of got blasted
jumped away
but not it looked like she was like
like
explosioned away from me
and she just fell off the bed like that
she was so shook
[Laughter]
uh I felt so bad I got some scratches on
my hand because of that
normally she seems sleeps pretty uh
height but in this case
I don't know something about me blowing
my nose
gave her the biggest spook of the
century
oh more thank you thank you
imagine that green explosion oh we don't
talk about that it's terrifying
Game of Thrones man
okay where is that Quest Ayah here
when I sneeze my cat always zooms away
they're all the same cute
you can collide with the NPCs now it was
not possible in one with the walking
episode is that good or bad
um
I don't remember that don't worry
it's good
foreign
you can learn new recipes for synthesis
and skills useful for Alchemy the skill
tree contains a large number of skills
which can be learned from skill any
skill you like
yeah
learning skills require sp sp can be
obtained for synthesizing or completing
quests oh unexplained
it's forcing me to learn this one
now you have learned to unexplained
recipe once you have learned the skill
you will be able to learn adjacent
skills
aim to master all skills to become a
top-notch Alchemist
Ry system
yeah I like it I like it
should be awesome
what did she not give me like any new
Quest I just gave her something
why did I go here
okay
I guess we're gonna slay some enemies
now
oh
let's go Gotta Get towel to work again
I should make Onyx blades
is it like a weapon for the boss dude
or is it like a weapon like a bomb
it looks like the weapon that boss would
use
well
[Music]
I'm so strong
whoa
is it okay for me to fail all those
trees I kind of feel bad
damn she's so powerful
[Music]
I want to pick up everything
I can't help it I'm gonna have like a
huge inventory again and then I'll be
like I don't know what to use and I have
all the shitty materials
in there forever and ever
oh well
oh wait what where are we going
there should be some enemies
up
here
okay yes the game lets me go here
I want to do it while running
oh I'm both wait I should go back to my
house once
I have 300
materials apparently so if I go back it
will just leave it there right
wait I need the ax
I also think I have like too many things
how do I leave it
does it just leave it automatically
no I have friends in space
oh
wait just update
no okay and how do I know how much I
have
how do I check my
uh
[Music]
wait
uh f is Quest tab is menu
oh cute
[Music]
container
empty 9756.
what does that mean I have space for a
9700 more items
[Music]
it becomes limited later
ah ah basket basket basket basket basket
where's my basket
basketball
[Music]
oh because we're in tutorial mode
okay
mother
[Music]
um
well then
while we are still oh okay for this one
I need an ax
while we're still unlimited we shall
collect
everything
[Music]
see how fast I can pick up these items
at least the ones that I can pick up
with e
these ones I kind of need to like aim
wait wait
unlimited power oh wait nothing worked
really smoothly
okay
this is fun I like speeding through it
just saves a lot of time
hmm she's Sonic okay which which enemies
are we gonna fight not these ones that
we just saw right
we need the ones on the beach
yeah Bank means like a sand bank right
like a beach
um
if he gets those ones what
is this
quiet notes on entering the forest wait
I'm going to a forest
come here
good question where am I going
okay let me try to
take down one of those that we just saw
maybe it was them oh oh the pig Arrow
I I forgot to follow the Pink Arrow
okay then we continue moving
moving
ah
yeah no it is here
I didn't realize
okay how do I find
uh someone with a super cute between
main characters if you want a Tuesday no
no no no no no that's okay
um
it wants me to do it press X to switch
to aggressive mode while on aggressive
mode your Alice will use skills and
items aha
okay yeah do that
C to switch to support mode
x x and C why not just one and we switch
between
let's come closer tutorial thank you
okay
[Music]
well something with s in space right
oh
I don't know
one button is it too much to ask
Monday night don't even want to try I'm
sorry
I'm sorry I will try the other NPCs
they start at level 20. oh yeah it seems
so
foreign
games too
you coming for me
because
[Music]
thank you
why don't you attack
holy [\h__\h]
I did not look at the HP at all because
I thought hey we're in the beginning of
the game like why would anyone die
oh wait looks look she's like really
dirty
is it because she took a lot of damage
or is it just
the rain
he looks pretty fun
all wrapped up
[Music]
interesting yeah
hmm
there's a button to do poses what which
button is it maybe he'll uh uh uh
tab
I don't have healing items though
uh
I can't eat any of this can I
can eat the berries like straight can I
oh okay we will just have to survive
we're done live
the fighting anyway
which way does it go this way
[Music]
no wait I don't understand uh
maybe go to The Hideout
s
wait a second we gotta like kill
ourselves don't get healed just by going
home I wonder
oh look she's like so wet oh she's still
dripping
[Music]
wow
are we healed now where do I see
um
tardy
oh yeah they got healed
why does she have a flag on her uh stick
wow wow wow wow wow okay we should make
some healing items let me just
synthesize some stuff uh
but how do I
I want
uh r r ah what you still telling me
something well select all press I didn't
realize it was telling me something I
was just like trying to move
press uh the middle thingy to select
ingredients and press left just add to
it and use all the ad materials for easy
synthesis select all for using all sorts
of ingredients
[Music]
ah the usual bumping me with all kinds
of information
in the beginning
uh where is I guess you can just make
grass beans for now because I guess
that's all I can make right now
oh critical but if I put this in here
[Music]
because it's not in the trade one does
that mean it will not have a chance to
take the the critical plus I don't
remember
[Music]
you need green ones oh
oh
okay
[Music]
choose this one oh now we have two can I
get rid of the other one that I chose
confused
foreign
[Music]
I put in there
um
select
oh no
they're a way of
[Music]
Escape we just go a few steps back okay
assistant stand and then you
use one and then
[Music]
I have to take this oh well okay
oh bonus strong blessing
stupid classic
but healing's also no no no no no okay
okay wait I guess I'll just why can I
only do the three I want to do four like
last time
this one only took up one
and why is it locked
[Music]
I could do uh
an old tree fruit too
[Music]
I need more green
it says times one and now I've got two
and it's still unlocked
[Music]
um
oh it's unlocked now
[Music]
I don't want that one
I want
do we have something better
I don't know
I'll just go I'll go for this one
Whatever it's not necessarily better
and now we add blue one in here
no no no I can still continue we can put
something in here it's been recovery m
um
so I just need to in order to get the HP
Recovery M I just have to fill it up
with free green ones
is that how that worked again
I already hit the cap huh I did
and now I hit the cab
oh wow oh wow okay okay I got the
healing
at least
I will make another one
or maybe we should make a make a bomb
let's try to make a bomb can I make a
bomb
where did I get Crimson where from well
okay
powerful
yeah
[Music]
then we need some sand ideally something
that already has two oh this is perfect
this one's perfect
[Music]
we have one with two no we don't have
one with two
but we saved on the other ones
let's get another one
we have two more quantities
five damage this one's already filled up
fire damage M oh
I think I can do this
now we're done but that's pretty look at
that good fire bomb spicy meatball yummy
now she's alcheming
no I'm cooking
exhausting explosion vitamins and
lowered guard as in clickburn s been
decent for beginner
now we can add which one do we want
flat increases with your normal sense
waiting time when using item but also
increases power and heal a month by 10
Max
because when he'll write with few
targets
I know I'll go for powerful oh I can't
get any of them anyway all right
bomb
[Music]
um
a recipe morph can occur when the
element values of the material Loop
shown with the recipe are met when a
recipe morph occurs a different item
will be synthesized oh
[Music]
huh
I understand
either sympathize with recipe more about
displayed on the recipe list so they can
be synthesized without my spring morph
next time
no it's like tree right
then yeah I remember I remember it
brings you to a new item yeah
uh okay
[Music]
we need two electricity
I'll have a single one
okay
[Music]
so what if I don't have one
will I fail
I mean it still seems I just won't get
the effect I guess
they want even more electricity I don't
have any what about this one no
[Music]
you can use other trees you won't get
color points for it
you just don't get the effects yeah oh
well I guess as long as we
uh can chop some wood whatever
[Music]
yeah okay this is fine for now
and just think that would cut his ax
right
[Music]
whatever
you can
um
[Music]
hi hi hi
oh
look it's
Claudia once you have created your own
Gathering tool you can equip it in the
item section of the ah yeah you can only
like bring a certain amount right
oh yeah yeah yeah I remember
can we do another one that we might need
the hammer
[Music]
seems like we can make it
I don't remember using or needing a
hammer
but
[Music]
thank you
bunk stick I'll add one more
Master crushing
okay
we need two for Gathering up as
um I don't really need trade slots for
these let's not for now I prefer to go
up to Gathering up M Maybe
[Music]
come on
I feel like do I have a free a triple no
let's just let's get it up to Gathering
up and M I mean
oh
can't go up to L but close enough what
is ADD gases [\h__\h]
what is that what's that dude
I mean why not
come on yeah getting up and we got that
one
[Music]
whoa it doesn't matter I can't get them
adds element to Garrett material or
that means the hammer counts as a gas
and synth for when you use the Hammers
oh as an ingredient
[Music]
anything else I can make I can make bone
armor
[Music]
and I remember the neutralizes
should I make a boom armor
foreign
[Music]
bones s what's that
beats armor
[Music]
I love the BDM too
well I have to do this one otherwise I
can't move on
[Music]
firm bones and quality thank
you I think Eva Philip the HP will go to
firm bones m
or you can probably eventually change
the soundtrack
um
two older ones didn't we do that in the
last game we were able to change it to
older Atelier games be gem
it's in OB GM
Persona call
can't do oh I'm sufficient okay okay so
we might as well fill up the HP
okay well
I'll get that
um
I don't have that
yeah okay I'm good I'm good I'm good I'm
good
yeah I think I'm good it's okay to stop
there right
wow
if you have the DLC oh I don't think I
got the code but I don't think it
includes any DLC
pretty lady in the summer dress thank
you it's my new hairstyle looks good
with the hat doesn't it actually in the
DLC I think ryza can get one of the one
of like a hat that I have
I was like oh we matching
[Music]
so can I like wear this is this like one
of those armor items
we need time I want to make an Oni time
needs two
point I'll make I don't know what that
means but I'll make I'll make it fall
soon
enhanced skills
we'll be able to fill that one up
[Music]
um
there's fire I don't have I don't have a
sharp only
can make Japanese
[Music]
wow here pretty thank you time to
accessorize it I don't really know what
this is going to be used for but oh I'm
done
Warriors off
sharp only enhanced skills three percent
HP regen on turn Xs
you can't
yes only a chestnut is wait it's only a
real thing
I know uni is like isn't that some
Japanese seafood why Japanese I think
it's the name Japanese name for some
seafood that's what I thought that was
originally
it's urgent isn't it but here it doesn't
look like an urchin at all
just really an urchin in the game
sea urchin yeah
okay let me see
[Music]
um
items
you're nice
and um
can I put on like some armor or
something
equipment oh yeah oh yeah yeah they have
like a couple of uh these slots oh and
only charm is something you can put on
there oh but wait before I give it to
you how do I go to
ah there we go equipment
ah but was there a thing with blank you
know you can only put certain armor or
you should only put certain armor on
certain people or does it not matter
I can put that ball no armor on her it
would suit someone else better maybe
I'll just give this stuff to her first
20 death
that's good huh
why tile change weapons in every game
does he
does he let me look at the skill tree
what can I make what can I learn
do I learn the next thing this one oh
uh a trial craft uh-huh wait that sounds
new I know craft bombs were a thing
before but I don't remember a trial
craft
his breath Haze you
wanna know what that is but we'll
probably need it
or Trio
I learned an island
so much fun guys
[Music]
playing probably have something fun on
my private time
[Music]
but I only got like shitty items so far
let's report to the Elder
um
[Music]
Mr rise of playing for us well you can
always watch The Bod of an old one
yeah the scene that could have yeah
yeah for it to be playing something on
my steam deck in bed finally because I
haven't really been making use of the
steam deck my brother was impressed
though that I have one
[Music]
no no no no
Let's help him out with a senior
struggles when we're talking for cat
oh wait can I let me see let me see let
me see
that's right they have already like some
kind of
uh variations of their outfits well
where would I do that party
no no no
how do I do
you know at her room ah okay next time
we come back
okay dokie
my desk uh
NPC running
from the rain
[Music]
so realistic
I like that detail
s yeah
[Music]
foreign
and now it's been so long it's been like
over a year over maybe even two years
since I played that
game
I would have to like get a
uh a recap of what the hell I was doing
um
come on I don't know where my pizza is
[Music]
awesome
is there anything that I needed my ex
for right now
lb lb
how do I switch my
yeah I can do like a big swing
quiet peculiar power of Arbor ruins
all
right
yeah
oh he's got
he's got I mean okay
he's standing in the bench
but he's got an umbrella
there's one good thing and one not so
good thing here
we're carrying the umbrella
also I like her design
[Music]
let's follow them
oh she went inside the house where are
you going
run run faster why is she running so
slow I can run much faster oh sorry
please continue
just checking out where you're going um
it's not stalking I'm just trying to
figure out if the NPCs have an actual
route
that makes sense oh no not going in
there
[Music]
oh oh she's running it's a really far
place
ah oh my God the cat is under the bench
sorry cap on the bench
yeah other cat that one doesn't give a
[\h__\h] about the rain
I did give a [\h__\h] about me though
oh oh
foreign
[Music]
away from each other
I'm getting distracted I'm just testing
out the game as I should
as a game journalist
anyway back to business
it's been a while sorry
foreign
[Music]
I was just checking
my Discord stuff on my phone because uh
I saw on my desktop that I've got like a
million messages and then while I'm
checking on my phone it's just it
decides to just suddenly update and
close itself okay thank you for nothing
but
I actually
now obtained uh Ultimate Edition code
kind of late but
I wonder if it Stacks I want to see oh
my God
does anyone know if that kind of like
Stacks if I already am playing the game
with one cold and I get an ultimate code
afterwards
is it just do I have to install another
game
your redeem is unlock the list I mean
that would be ideal oh we should try
after this dialogue safe and then leave
the game once download
[Music]
um okay okay nice
oh there's some cool stuff
even additional area
wait I really like that outfit okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
there's no swimsuits on the graphic that
they sent me
foreign
[Music]
I think that happens with the previous
game too okay okay we have to prepare
some stuff but
is there all the safe
table
t
is it auto safe
in the room
okay uh what we can teleport
am I living in the pixie Forest is that
where I live
here
yes
so dark
okay wasn't it like a book or so
or out of the table right
right here
oh wait
first we'll see what there is without
DLC
oh nothing
I thought you could take up even without
the DLC you could take up the jacket or
so
nothing nothing okay wow that will be
like a really clear difference nice
okay
nice huh okay now I can close the game
right I'll just go I'm gonna I'm just
gonna close it
[Music]
Maybe
it might need like installation time I
wonder did I properly save I'm just
gonna check
[Music]
yeah okay
two hours Playtime closing
now game activate
a product
insert the kill you
activating
uh-huh
Ultimate Edition
oh it's updating really fast oh
okay okay 63 76 percent
96 percent
my library still says it's uh
not the ultimate edition I don't know if
it would change to that let's see
let's see that was fast
so supposedly
what we get
is
this
uh costumes at Endless Summer slash
costume safaris Travelers
recipes fashion pack Alchemy Mysteries
I wonder if that's some overpowered
stuff
uh recipe SpongeBob out of Adventure
additional area Raska Island and gust
extra bgm pack
uh season pass Bono's costume set Goss
collaboration set of two
oh this is the lyrics Edition custom set
back to Summer which is where she can
take off her jacket it seems like
another look jam-packed keypad game
[Music]
let's see if it works
oh was that an Autism let's save a
second time
[Music]
left outfit looks like mermaid
left on the right side you mean
oh
[Music]
um
no I wasn't it wasn't there uh
[Music]
uh what was it
was that
here I already forgot
oh that's so much
ryza has the most stuff all right let's
see so this is default
wow isn't this like a placa outfit it's
not the one that I like though I mean
it's fine though she's she's cute in it
I mean look
because there doesn't seem to be a oh
it doesn't seem to be a a
zooming function in there
[Music]
I mean I'm gonna be honest I don't think
it really suits her hmm
suits this but
um
[Music]
it's wobbly cute I like that she gets a
tail
huge bunny ears
okay
changing room how about
uh
this was basically oh wait so this is uh
also from another character isn't it it
looks a bit familiar but I'm not sure
who
damn those flies
damn
oh cool cool
cape
is it a new one what is it ramizel
outfit and Sophie too
oh
wow
pretty good I like this one more
I like the cape
[Music]
damn damn girl
not bad not bad
[Music]
yeah yeah that's pretty good that's
pretty good all right all right what's
next
[Music]
I like it
I mean I don't remember how the swimsuit
looked in the previous game but I think
I like this one more
can I say one thing about these shoes
that she's wearing I'm gonna expose
Kelly now
I don't know if she ever mentioned this
on stream though
but Kelly wouldn't mind I'm sure you
know Cali normally she was like always
wearing some stylish kicks you know
like really stylish cool kicks
um in the recent times when I met her
when we went to yakinikul and so on
cheers
I think do you call them Birkenstocks
look very similar to these ones but it's
literally just like yeah
she was wearing
yeah like legit fat sandals
I mean she was just getting really comfy
and I even
um once witnessed her manager
Jay chat roasting her on them like Kelly
what's up with you recently what's with
those shoes what are those
[Music]
you know it's totally fine she can
totally rock those Birkenstocks too
being comfy and all that
but it's just such a big change she used
to always wear the stylish stylish kicks
ever
hahaha
they're called Jesus sandals it's a
major death
it's so funny you know it was like I was
also confused I was like
and I thought maybe just this one day to
be comfy but then
the next day she was wearing them again
she has this face right now
but honestly like
I also cannot put much effort anymore
into my looks these days like I just
can't care enough they're orthopedic and
so comfy yeah go Cali read those healthy
shoes let's go
yeah sometimes you just want to relax
exactly so if you clip this
I clipped this but Cali would probably
beat me up no you'll have to clip it but
include the part where I'm saying it's
okay Kelly you know we want to be
confident I want you to be comfy you
know you know I totally get you you know
just
yo anyway this swimsuit is sick I really
like it it's cute
at the design I'm not even being first
yet I just really like the design but
also
damn Riser damn
metal designs again
hmm
okay
[Music]
so this is the old outfit with Adam
jacket right and this is the
this is the
uh ryza 2 outfit without a jacket this
is random one this is ryzer too right it
was the other way around I'm pretty sure
this is ryza one
um
foreign
[Music]
I love this color variation
I love it so much
this one makes me feel like she's about
to enter a casino and play poker
laughs
looks like an apple
and this is so cute I like the red a lot
my chest game
[Music]
um
and I think Ryan's at two design might
be maybe my favorite I'm not sure though
[Music]
I can't decide
maybe this one for now
Rising Two Jackal is pretty it really is
okay
[Music]
um towel let me see what you got again
it feels I don't know kind of nerdy his
uh swimsuits always
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God is he wearing cracks
oh my God I can't
can't
well I prefer the red one too
actually I really prefer both of them
over the green one
so I guess this is just kind of his
image
[Music]
and then oh
my God
oh
um
barely different
[Music]
um
I
I need to look at this
I can switch right
[Music]
set main character
how do I there we go
Oh I thought yeah you can't run around
with them
what was that dude I'm selling the main
character
oh
oh God
[Music]
I mean
um
I just I I I I I I feel very
uncomfortable looking
um
it's been in Speedos I think
personal preference
I
I mean you're rocking it you're totally
rocking it
but I just feel so uncomfortable looking
at men and Speedos
is that supposed to be like goggles no
it's a necklace
um
don't look
[Music]
um
oh he's gonna kill blue butts too
[Music]
does he have nipples though I think we
already know after the games they don't
have nipples his
his belly button is like uh a mole
his belly button looks like a mole
[Music]
maybe it is a mole but look at us
twinning oh cute
[Music]
she could be less as always
thank you examination time
anyway we're gonna we're gonna change
this up up
sorry I'm confused
changing room close
[Music]
this one has some red in it it might be
the most matching with us actually the
default one
look at this
nicer
it doesn't reflect on here though that's
kind of sad
all right guys
let's continue
prepare ingots where do I get a certain
gods or do I have to make the ingots
this is something I pick up or is it
something I
I have to synthesize
[Music]
it's a sympathizing thing
okay okay but I kind of I want to go out
real quick
because I can't hold back uh which way
which way
oh
um I wanna find some something to Bunk
with my hammer and something to Bunk
with my ex
foreign
really quickly going with me guys
[Music]
no that's just normal and how do I
switch the weapon
or for example here right so
I can't use this one
um gaboritos are
ah
[Music]
so with this one
I can get some soft sand here oh can I
get a different material
[Music]
if I use oh if the staff I get would
the ax we don't know
and I can use the X on the stone tool
and get something else too I like that
yeah yeah yeah I remember nectar rock
that was a thing in in Riser too as well
[Music]
foreign
that's cool
now
depending on what you need what about
this one oh that's new too
eroded Stone
probably gonna get something different
with a hammer as well
all right
while stuff you gather it with hand
you could play too much after I want to
switch from my phone oh yeah because I I
did turn on that setting I mean I'm not
paid to do this
unfortunately but uh they did give me
two game codes man noise uh uh let me
try again
Hammer doesn't work right yeah okay
not sponsored butt Ed it's like
uh what's the word
opposite okay
what's the word
it's just home run the log yeah skill
no that's not what I mean not endorsed
ironic that's also not what I mean but
it's more into that direction what the
[\h__\h] is an oxymoron an oxymoron I call
me a [\h__\h] contrary that's the word I'm
looking for
why you guys find these difficult words
at me
a contradiction yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
or
ah
okay I need to practice this anyway
yes
I'm doing it she's cooking
[Music]
contradictionary phase like adult child
well guys did you honestly assume that I
would understand the meaning of that
I'm just looking for the easy word
hey
you're overestimating me
this is fine this is fun guys
[Applause]
how come we have not met a puny before
spoonie dangerous we will see
it
yeah
let's go
I'm a practice oh but he's not coming
for me okay
pony pony
Pony
Monday
okay we're gonna go back now
and follow the quest
wait how do I go back
the most iconic anime yeah
good material for plushie oh yeah I mean
they totally already have merchandise
like that
[Music]
looking forward to all the other colored
punies golden one black one
red one
[Music]
oh you know
life guys there's puddles after the rain
and they look actually pretty good
they're reflective
oh
guys
maybe the waters reflective from the
water y'all
why am I so excited about this
is
[Music]
they make a splish splash sound too
good job
dab Castle good job
[Music]
I cannot make Ingot why
Stone
I know half Stone what
[Music]
um
what
what color
[Music]
s
okay ah oh I don't have
anything I see
but I have some stuff that's spicy
doesn't really matter it's just for a
quest to anyway
[Music]
right
but I do get like more SP if I make a
good item right I guess
[Music]
okay okay
oh one more
um
one more
Maybe
trade slot
okay
how about critical
enhanced finisher
and the last one doesn't count anyway I
think
[Music]
free units hey
this is the perfect like
off day chill in bed feel good kind of
game
so honestly I think
I think I'm personally even though for a
while I was also thinking yeah it would
be fun to stream it too
but I think it'll be great for me to
have this
as a game to play offline
new voice active Verizon no no still the
same still the same
just play privately I get it thank you
yeah it's just so cozy
but if I need help
you guys gotta help me
maybe maybe if I like make a lot of
progress and I go I come to oh okay how
about that if you guys are interested I
don't know maybe that's also weird but
maybe if some really dramatic boss fight
is coming up or so
I could I could stream dad or if I'm
struggling or need help
I have a stream dad but I don't know if
you want to like jump in randomly
um
Twitter post yeah
stream the final no I cannot actually do
that I think
if I understood correctly I'm not
supposed to
[Music]
um
show the ending
[Music]
don't include ending ending song or
ending movie
I mean I don't know where the ending
starts for them
but oh well
oh
guys
I have
um
and interesting we're gonna still
continue playing after there by the way
I'm just chilling right now I have an
interesting proposition is that the
right word
proposal but that's that's not what I
mean preposition
it seems like if you want
because you guys were telling me
about it and I didn't even know about it
until like yesterday or so
proposition okay
um
it seems like I asked about it we uh I
have permission to play
the open Beta of Diablo 4 on the weekend
if you want I could switch it out with
one Fire Emblem stream
I don't know how to get into the open
beta but if anyone can then I can too
should we do it should we take a look
because it's only on the weekend
[Music]
yeah okay then we might wanna
oh
[Music]
you just download it okay
cool cool
what
curious
okay I made ingot
synthesize two Onyx lights oh whoa whoa
whoa whoa okay I need to angle for that
huh do I get to keep the unexplanes
what do you mean Kyla has it is Kyla
playing a two on the weekend
what it means you can help if I need
help
she already played it
[Music]
did she play a close beta
was there already an open battle back
then
hmm
was it closed or open it was closed was
that sponsored
there was a buy-in open by that weekend
last weekend oh
she played the clothes
interesting I mean I think it'll be fun
I'll figure it out on my own
is there an online mode for Diablo 4 too
[Music]
electricity I don't have allergies at
nine demons
[Music]
what do I have to fill it up
and look down
oh it's online it's like MMO now what
always wait do you see people running
around
is there servers
oh soft animal
s
[Music]
instead well that's so cool I'm looking
forward to it not a full MMO apparently
but not a hoodoo
I don't know if I want to do that
[Music]
are these for me or are these for the
quest person
Clans and World bosses Coolio
[Music]
as a social aspect of one oh
it's for the class person okay then I'll
just can I already like
am I done how do I know I'm done again
I'll just give her the shittiest Onyx
blade ever
Tony
only made one though gotta make another
one foreign
[Music]
and there's no like minimum quality yet
so
just take this
Time Savage
cucumber Island uh oh yeah
[Music]
wait
oh can I not like go there how do I go
okay
I was hoping there would be a whole live
clan in Diablo you mean like members
playing together
um
I wanna let me see how much I will enjoy
it
I did my best
totally believe me trust me
what were you expecting
yeah I really like this
come on
look at those matches
so cute
I have to wait for a spot okay okay
it's like a dog reacting to their owner
saying let's go for a walk walk walk
funny stuff
Return to razza House
I always keep on pressing thinking that
will bring me to where I want to go
walking treaties
Brilliance my cats don't really react to
any specific word like that
unfortunately what are those
tomato pumpkins or something like that
but what was I supposed to do in here I
returned
turn to rise a house
is it a specific spot outside
oh
what it says return to Reza house
[Music]
you mean return to the beach
wait what
oh my parents house
whoa
foreign
I'm just gonna
run
uh yeah
don't talk at the same time
oh I'll just go here
foreign
[Music]
you're so right oh my God
she's so cute look at her oh my God
but I need my Patty fix hi
this is so sweet helping her family
[Music]
yeah
looks like a Tales of NPC
[Music]
s
sympathize a light and sturdy whoa
Oh no you're not supposed to say that
game
[Music]
all right hoes
all right let's make a hole
[Music]
okay
what is that a light and sturdy okay how
is that like a trait oh no it's
literally just a name a light and sturdy
hole
hahaha
okay
can I use that too as a tool or is it
nothing I can use a broken hole oh
broken hole
I want to make jokes but I'm I don't I
can't even like make a joke about it
can't even say that's me
laughs
[Music]
I don't have to put much effort into
this one either right
um
that was my brand name
my band name oh your bad name
light and sturdy hoe or broken hole
[Music]
all right yeah
that's why your dad can I make it good
all right anime look look it's
dirty
issue
a mother in distress reportable deliver
the whole to Mom yeah
Alchemist Uber delivery
coming right up
there you go
please enjoy
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you it is isn't it
[Music]
foreign
wow it's my room
not here
well wish my bed looks comfy
[Music]
I don't know what time is it now
uh
Mommy
[Music]
yes
I feel like I could with some assets
totally make myself look like her
checkout Island
[Music]
I like the big gem right now the violin
is really nice
piano damn
this might be my favorite until now
so far
oh
now the guitar is starting oh
my God oh my hands full
foreign
[Music]
not all at once
take a sorting ticket
oh damn we're really busy
why everyone has a problem at the same
time
if it was going to take up to 100
minutes right now
[Applause]
and where's tomorrow
I think I'll do it on Sunday though
Sunday's still fine right how long does
it go
foreign
[Music]
how can we not
um
this way
I'm following the air bro
I'll wait this way no what this way
this way
reunion
I'm so ready
reunion time
[Music]
don't know let's get the cat off again
some some of them I've noticed though
they don't run away when I run
this one doesn't
[Music]
oh by the way thank you for the
reminders for the post office I ended up
not going because I realized I can still
go until like Monday
[Laughter]
the deadline is Monday though
so I really gotta go thanks for
reminding me though
you can remind me on Monday again if you
want
but actually like when I tell people to
remind me of something
I end up just remembering it by myself
but if I don't tell anyone then I don't
remember
so
you guys have the same thing by any
chance
[Music]
no nipples guy
yeah the instrumental note
[Music]
oh man that reunion feels yeah
guys just be like hey
[Music]
foreign
mm-hmm
[Music]
let's go
whoa
where is the arrow and where's the
string but okay she's cool I love her
but if only it was real
air
noise
when swimming fish by the water
Riverside how do I fish ah I need a I
probably need a rub yeah
[Music]
foreign
yeah we're gonna check out the outfits
for Claudia too when we get back
I agree
[Music]
not really
foreign
[Music]
I don't care about the OG gang I want
Patty
foreign
[Music]
thank you
and like Claudia's new outfit
[Music]
s
either
wait wait wrong boat or am I good
[Music]
ah we're good
yeah I gotta check out the costumes give
me a second
the roof always look so
broken
DLC content
you too I guess I'll look at yours too
for real they want to see the DLC
okay let's go
she's become sentient sentient yeah
[Music]
I can see that sloppy
it's like a museum
foreign
[Music]
okay now to the important things no not
yet
hello
nanny is
[Music]
social
GK
changing room
wait okay I guess I'll look at you uh
oh wow
how conveniently those flowers cover up
the chico bee
oh I like it though I'm trying to like
us
uh he looks like a
high school student who goes to
like the graduation vacation or whatever
you call that spring break whatever
well
[Music]
it's very dense though
oh wow
[Music]
you're gonna stay red because we're all
red right now actually
how do I go
oh there we go
now we look at the oh no
look at Claudia my sweetheart
so this is default
there's a swimsuit oh
I like it can we look at it for a second
[Music]
oh I really like the design
I'm interested
oh
yeah it's good
10 out of 10 swimsuit
I mean liking
it
[Music]
oh okay that's that's kind of like brown
red
oh wow
this is so safe so she looks like an elf
wow
I don't like this one that much but
since we're all currently trying to be
red
for that
[Music]
um
yeah looks good when we're together wow
actually looks really mature her like
brownish red
nah nice synthesize a bump okay that is
how we celebrate long time reunion all
right all right I already synthesized
the bomb recently though
okay let's make a better one
[Music]
we need two here
my green ones are
all just one okay
the word guard is
a fire too no there we go there we go
easy peasy can I make a better one than
before we still want the fire damage and
don't win
yeah I bet that's gonna be all I can do
it doesn't
it might not actually be better
wait traits wait I need a trade I can
still do a trade
[Music]
all right all right all right
okay
not too bad
[Music]
I think I want to prioritize the
critical
don't you agree
it's been a while let's make a bump yeah
yeah let's immediately make this I tell
you go up in flames
hello
[Music]
beautiful
quit always good right yeah I agree
honest creative synthesis can be
equipped and used in combat or during
exploration you can equip items for each
character from Battle preparation in the
main menu equipped items are called core
items the item won't be fully effective
if the item is higher level oh then the
character's dexterity
oh for example here it's like 36. oh
okay okay keep the item level in mind
while equipping I think that was a thing
before I do
um
cc is earned by using skills during
combat if you have 10 plus AP you can
use CC even when it's not your turn oh
yeah yeah you need CC for the items yeah
CC points can only be used during the
battle in which they were earned so be
sure to use your items proactively
however if an items level is higher than
its characteristics dexterity the item
will not be fully effective equip wisely
be sure to take the items level into
account before equipping it
well so I should probably like put it in
do I put the the bombs I don't put in
there but
there let me check for example
cute
ah okay that's where I pulled it let's
bring a bomb and another bomb and the
healing item I will give just because it
kind of feels nice
Monica
and ah I feel like I don't want to make
another
healing items
I still can only do wait maybe I can
learn a new one
we have 404 uh ever we have error SP
nice
and
where would I go for more healing items
ah medical powder that sounds like
something Medical
necessary
50 SP that's really cheap
[Music]
not really what I'm looking for also
these are really expensive
yeah I can't afford them anyway I can't
this one also too expensive yeah
all right I gotta make more stuff
[Music]
getting the SP up is useful yeah I guess
so was there that
SP percent up I didn't see
I'll aim for that
um okay grass beans
again
[Music]
and
could I get a trade slot
[Music]
just once this one to go up do I have
another green one only have these ones
damn I need to get more of these green
thingies
video
I don't have
okay I guess we'll stay with the S
ick it's fun
[Music]
yeah four green I don't have that many
okay no no no I guess I'll fill up this
one
actually
um
[Music]
a button
I'm good
[Music]
I guess I'll add one of these
do I have a double somewhere
yes I do
amazing
[Music]
they probably make no sense but you
can't
it's better than nothing
[Music]
what else should I make should I make
some like
armor stuff
for the others
[Music]
I'll come here I should try to make some
of these things as well
poison cure sounds useful
um
no need for now
I only have one cotton
[Music]
where did I get the cotton from I want
more where that came from
element value
add General Goods
[Music]
I'll fill this one up
anything else that makes sense no
damn it
[Music]
from a cat I got the cotton from a cat
damn you paid attention
[Music]
um
I don't even get the train so sure
[Music]
I think
well an unexplained that is
surely one of their weapons isn't that
but for the one that for the guy who
isn't even with us anymore is that
I'll make
and
aren't these the base weapons that
everybody already has
you probably need them to synthesize the
best next the next best item right
hey
Stray Cats hmm
[Music]
I'll make some flour
oh scrap paper for the bag okay okay
add fire
[Music]
yes
level up
and then some of the Wings
can I add more
I have two more slots
[Music]
can't fill up that one okay
so I think I'll fill this one up
[Music]
did you make it to the post office or I
just said like a half an hour ago or so
that I decided not to go today but thank
you for reminding me turns out I have
some more time so I'll go on on Monday
[Music]
oh am I not done
oh wait I have to eat
uh it's one of the basic ones that I
have to add
[Music]
I don't have the the right thing but oh
well
critical
[Music]
attractive
you guys are welcome to remind me again
yeah
and yes I do have alarms on my phone but
I can't like the alarm is just you know
they go like wait what we want they
don't tell me what am I we want we
willing for
[Music]
so you know
let me try to just
synthesize everything I can right now
foreign
[Music]
what else what else should I add I'm
making a red neutralizer
[Music]
um
quality
and a traits lunch
trade slots true
and gum powder maybe no I probably can't
fill that one up
let's fill this one up
small Blackboard to Note reminders that
you check every morning I tried doing
that before with like white boards
but I ended up never using that kind of
stuff so I gave up
um
and notes I mean I write down all my
on my tangents in my notes on my phone
but when it comes to like to-do lists I
don't really check those
somehow
I mean it would make a lot of sense if I
just would check them I know
I know I just I'm alone
I also always wake up for my alarm I
just don't look at the name of the alarm
I just turn it off and I wake up
oh wait maybe I should do that one first
one first oh okay
[Music]
let's add Stone
I'm not the only one yeah
[Music]
they're all double loss
quality and another charade slot
might just add another trade spot
[Music]
oh is it smarter
I don't believe the saying that if you
forgot something it wasn't it probably
wasn't important enough people always
say that but I don't agree with that
at all
or sheep
you can't
a Half Men meme it's not a meme
generally
[Music]
um in German
like it's a saying that everybody says
[Music]
like my mom would say that to me
everybody says that to one another
it's pretty common this is just a meme
for you guys
it's like common saying here
whoa wait I can make a fishing rod
whoa
I'm a catcher's net I remember
[Music]
yeah cause I made the Alchemy fibers
they say it in my country too there you
go
fishing game of the year
it's also common in Spanish aha
similar
um
Master fishing master fishing
I should fill that up shouldn't I
whatever
[Music]
and Friends
capable fishing interesting
wait I don't have to fill up this one
right
it's only the ones that I like spiky
right that I have to fill up
[Music]
trade slot for a fishing rod I don't
know about that
[Music]
wait I feel I should fill up this one
what the hell am I doing
I'll give it a train slot just because
why not
okay
I am
I'm finito
[Music]
is there something that helps me with
fishing
no I don't think so
I'll give it quality though
[Music]
it's a poke stick
I'm gonna poke the fish to death with
this hey
and I guess we can also make a net
before we go
more adventuring
[Music]
I wanna be the very best
oh no
I can't fill it up
that's okay
it's gonna be fine I can still like
eventually improve all these items right
when the game tells me how to do it
like no one ever was
butt getting a vanity
she's so funny
add or
I don't understand but sure why not
[Music]
pleasure support increases supporter
level
oh yeah The Voice
no Ash like for real oh yeah right they
move on to like a new thing right I saw
I saw
so a lot about that on Twitter today I
don't really does anyone actively watch
Pokemon here
[Music]
no healing taste for me though
because I made really shitty flower
[Music]
I'm going to recovery
not anymore but it's nostalgic I will
miss ashbycon Team Rocket hmm I think
you know after so many years I think
it's good that they move on does anyone
like disagreeing with that anyone who's
like no they should have gone on forever
with the same characters
same age forever forever
I mean for us adults I think it's nice
but if you're a child and you just got
to know Pokemon then it might be kind of
like hey I just got started I just
started watching this
it's feeling full good does that give
more healing
again
it's good to move on New Generation new
character yeah I think that's good kids
need new stuff
[Music]
spend his time to move on for a long
time
the season where they soft reset Ash's
age and procession progression after
that it was okay now it's fine they're
moving on
um
[Music]
I don't know where to check it's okay
I'll miss tea Market oh does that mean
they will also have
like a new team
new villains will they be as dorky and
as stupid as the previous ones we will
see they probably will
know
foreign
[Music]
I wonder how Japanese Bros think about
it
normalize the word graduation again
a lot right recently maybe this way I'm
like I'm like getting you guys to like
become immune to it it's good
it's shock therapy
tomorrow
[Music]
that's not how it works that is exactly
how it works decent since it's what what
the word decentralizing
spicy
oh it's not Central
desensitizing it doesn't say that you
don't get it
I'm gonna make a craft now I'm gonna
craft the crabs
holy macaroni exploding spots perfect no
no
one okay I'll make it another time
fries
[Music]
you need just one here
you need
well I have a double
oh
what is surprise
[Music]
it's constantly mentioning it makes us
more word about it
continuously tease graduation without
being specific champions in downward
spiral
foreign
[Music]
explosion delays the target's turn oh
I like dirt
so I'll try to fill this one up
and surprise
press L we only have two left maybe go
up to UNI Spike m
yeah I'll do that that should be easy
oh we couldn't get the quality up but
raising the quality
for a bomb does that make sense like
what would I do that for
doesn't it just matter if like for a
quest item they want a certain quality
or I guess maybe for more getting more
SP
but just for personal use
it will get more effective
it does more damage oh oh okay
hmm
done
[Music]
okay
soon enough I will make myself a rose
bomb again
that day will surely come
[Music]
I don't have any traits right
yeah okay that's fine
um can I ask someone who played this
game before uh like this one
specifically for items that you use in
battle like uh
bombs or healing items when you use them
once
do they I feel like in the previous
maybe in Rise of one or so or a
different athlete game I feel like they
recharged you didn't run out of them but
then in another game I feel like you did
run out of them so how is it they stay
[Music]
did they disappear in Riser too
oh they stay nice
okay
Unlimited
[Music]
okay atoms and he's still look I'm so
equipped
I can start cooking now also have 800 8
X where's the SP one
increase the quantity I know
yeah this one I should get this one
and speaking during yeah okay and next
one I want the quantity one maybe
fill up my inventory please
oh learn recipes
[Music]
okay
we'd be cooking
all right so two sphere grid
oh wait then I wanted to uh what was I
gonna do wait I wanna switch something
out here
um
ah
let me check real quick bomb
[Music]
which one heals more
recovery s
s
this one has higher quality and it has
feeling full um
[Music]
not sure
which one would heal more
[Music]
cute look at her so cute
one by one the guys are all replaced
like you guys you know exactly how it
goes in the kiwawa jrpg playthrough
biscuit heals more
laughs
she does have nice legs so yeah she's
very elegant I like her
okay
[Music]
where are we going
crack aisles oh it's so far we're
skipping like so many areas
where we go
can I even
can I even go like this I don't think I
can I have to like go there by boat
normally first right
probably
[Music]
what I have to walk
what
[Music]
that is really an adventure okay so
we're going this way
oh my God
[Music]
so is me
um
yeah
we do be walking but we do be sprinting
so it's okay
I got even more materials but
let's see where we can use them oh wait
butterfly can I so can I
[Music]
just work
she said she said she got it but she
really didn't
have to actually aim for it Seven Stars
the net is so tiny there's gonna be
bigger Nets right surely
[Music]
foreign
on my stream and make an opinion there
Sophie I didn't stream unfortunately but
I think I enjoyed Sophie quite a lot too
they're both really good
is better for a newcomer
foreign
[Music]
guys
okay put me first I can do this I can do
it I know how to fight
excuse item you need to accumulate CC
for normal attacks and skills if you
have enough CC you can use the multiple
core items at once Quantum so never
consumes ah so don't hesitate to use
them yeah let's go
oh thank you for the CC press s to
select an item
oh
but isn't S also for something for
fighting um
vulnerable oh it shows me
which this enemy is vulnerable for it I
think they did that last game too
oh yeah
all of them if I want to
so why not let's go
oh nice
noise yes
can press left click or as well holding
shift to use the switch skill to swap
with the rear character switch skills
can be even performed during normal
attacks because I don't know what that
means
[Music]
am I gonna actually use that
let's click while holding shift
[Music]
oh
uh okay that's how you switch while also
attacking
chain skill text after after shift skill
uh you want me to continue
[Music]
that's two
if you have a p try a skill chain to
inflict even more damage
oh God okay
uh
thank you
what
uh
[Music]
I will not do this
never play the game without this
I don't think I did it the way they want
me to do it
actually orders may be proposed by an
ally when the condition is
yeah
I think this was also
a thing
feel physical damage okay
cheap two conditions yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I love these kind of cutscenes it makes
me feel so powerful utilize switch shows
and action orders with your allies to
swing the tide of battling your favor
this concludes a tutorial oh I just
realized I probably have to relearn all
of the controls
when I play
on my steam deck
I think I might just start a new save so
it tells me everything again in the
tutorial
uh sorry that was a mistakes
[Music]
it would be easier might be good might
be good
feels more intuitive alright alright
yeah I was thinking something
that it would be easier on the
controller and steam deck is like a
controller so
you can consume 1080p to use a quick
action which will let you take your turn
immediately regardless of your wait time
but when you do this you can only use
items you can check it with your help
okay
I will relearn all of this as well
on my private time
a blue pony
[Music]
look at that oh
come on
[Music]
physical damage though there we go there
we go go girl
oh
[\h__\h]
I messed up
part-time Warrior by the way I'll make
you make fun of me
this is obviously the work of a
part-time Warrior
[Music]
okay I wanna see it
oh okay these two can get something
let's Punk
mushroom powder
oh this one doesn't work
this almost doesn't work
I want more mushroom stuff okay
um
by the way I'm gonna cook after the
stream I'm gonna cook something with
fish this time it's really rare I think
maybe only the second time or so that
I'm cooking something with fish from
hello
[Music]
I know it just felt like I should
probably choose
every once in a while it's healthy right
yeah some kind of like just White meat
fish
oh
thank you hey I don't like that as long
as I like grilled yeah
yeah I figured this stuff out already
I got it all check it out
[Music]
interesting why fish is my favorite
I don't know I don't know I forgot I can
tell you on my typical kiwawa's kitchen
after tweet
what am I doing here why am I wasting my
time here
[Music]
how have you been rice
oh I was not lonely at all
foreign
[Music]
memberships
I don't know I just feel you know uh
kind of sad because
I'm thinking of football Senpai
struggled
so long
to get her check mark and then she
didn't even have it for that long and
they're taking it away from her
doesn't she deserve better Fortune food
nice
Pokey she fought so hard
[Music]
foreign
I highly agree
uh but it for me it stopped being
convenient already like I don't know a
month ago when they started doing this
thing with the blue stuff
that's when my verified tab became
absolutely useless
yeah it is what it is
so I don't know I mean I'm not gonna
like I don't think
personally buy it myself
um whatever that is subscription
but maybe um
purchase them for us
they'll all be fake yeah
yeah
so true
okay since I'm gonna start the game a
new afterwards
I guess I don't have to
for damage effort into all of this at
the moment into leveling Etc
exactly exactly draconia
and parent
oh that one's glowing gold
[Music]
wait
hold up plus yeah I don't really know
[Music]
yeah I don't really know not much about
that
[Music]
okay apparently
uh what
social media
I think
I mean
yeah
not really finding new friends exactly
yeah that's the thing already existing
fans it will be great
foreign
but there's no way of like
getting like a lot of exposure or so out
of it right so
I think we'll continue using Twitter
anyway
ancient pillar nice though all right
where do we go
this way
we think you're hoping will appear in
that rise anime hey I don't know it's
just a first season right so I'm really
no
but I'm actually really interested in
watching it because already the trailer
when I watched it
um there's something about actually a
rhizo that just makes me so emotional I
don't know
I want to watch it
I don't wanna walk
foreign
sentimental no yeah they know how to
pull my Heartstrings
oh so many punies
Pony pony oh she
cute I
don't have the sheepsis Kawaii
it immediately like fails to see me
[Music]
emotional a fight make you emotional
wait Claudio's dying somebody else
Claudia oh my God
so when I use items off
battle outside of battle how does that
use up the items
they don't disappear right but there's
like a
maximum of how many I I can use right
oh there you go I feel like
that's it
[Music]
that sheep had a personal issue with
Claudia because she she likes to eat
sheep
strange silk
I used my CC Young
but they reset every battle right
she she point the wall
[Music]
Monica
you which way am I going
this way
see you again
I like her silk
my mouse moving the home screen
when I sneeze
thank you I'm sneezing a lot today huh
it's all the same
foreign
[Music]
I remember this place I remember every
place man it's all the same places I
hope they have some new places too
though
it's nice also too real see these old
slices nostalgia
not bad
I will see a new place soon okay
foreign
[Music]
even more different materials
to call his unconnected areas of loading
screens and rice I want to collected
them all so you can run for them
seamlessly oh
I didn't even like really realize that
I guess that's terrific now cool
they did that very well then
it's so seamless that I didn't even
realize
if you could not like
that's really cool
small crystals
that's a pretty butterfly
yes
look different than the other ones but
it's still the same Seven Stars One
bamboozle
open world atal here
[Music]
to make Natalia Emma more pretty
Wednesday Wednesday
I'm waiting for coming huh
Emma morpg
I really hope they let me play it
maybe even spawns at me
yeah blue protocol
waiting aimlessly but it's getting
closer
there was actually online but it doesn't
exist anymore
we don't talk about it
oh
sayaka
that's the worst
okay I will stop collecting everything
now
unless I see something new
nice Dodge
powerful powerful powerful things
[Music]
no I know I know and let's
make this one
where is why so far so far we gotta go
so far
you can really Speed Run for this in
theory
I want to watch an Atelier speedrun
there are actually speedrunners right
during Risa and her friend's Adventures
there are times when random quests are
giving an addition to main quests such
as helping others these are called
random quests random quests varying
content and some are initiated by party
characters not appear on the list of
quests but they are indicated by a quest
second at the Target point on the map
and field screen quests that have not
been ordered yet
our Mark of a question mark
a little explanation mark icon is
displayed for questions
okay thank you
[Music]
oh it's just a light thingy
defeat the group of monsters hunt tiny
devil okay oh I should have hit them
I wanna watch that
why don't you both go for me
[Music]
there's already a five hour run of Rise
of free up
if it's your first time playing it you
should just enjoy
without trying to speed run
[Music]
what happened just now
yeah surely that can be even shorter too
yeah yeah what did I give me im's lost
item
um
oh
poor
um
sick on the sofa go get well soon wait
more
[Music]
hey I did that
got some cool items for it too
foreign
[Music]
I guess if someone else can do it in
five hours I could
why did they use a bug or what how can
you play it in five hours when you're
playing blind probably at that point but
that means I could too
how the [\h__\h] what
I think of it that's incredible
I've been playing for four hours
skip ah all the talking
well again
oh an hour left oh I guess I'll finish
it today
[Music]
true true
they're making me recap so much I
already watched a recap on the main
screen girl
no need for recapping anymore
[Music]
oh it's those guys where am I going
where am I going
to do it no
no no no no
ain't nobody got time for that I am on a
mission I need to finish the game in
under one hour
top price of speedrunner
so but again
money
[Music]
hmm
oh that's all the places we went to
before but like connected in one View
s
[Music]
foreign
should I I can't teleport back here
right
if I go back once and empty my my basket
I mean
what are you
something to fight no
it's just decoration can't even milk you
sorry
I can't teleport back here now all right
then I guess I shall do so nice Camp
though
[Music]
okay
yeah gold
foreign
[Music]
oh
man Liza
sorry
foreign
[Music]
where the main Mount was alpacas
and there was like different variations
too I think I think it was eating
eternal
that's one of the reasons why I loved it
so much
[Music]
foreign
Chloe damn
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
before
I did
[Music]
powerful
what does that mean is that good or bad
it's probably bad
making fun of me
um
or not
[Music]
cute little story as a reward for coming
back a little bit nice and what did I
come here for I had to empty my basket
it does that automatically right or do I
have to like
go here
no probably not
although I don't want to check my
again
okay it's the same
[Music]
hmm
oh yeah yeah I saw the Luna uh piano
sponsorship thing
cool
I mean I don't play piano or anything
like that but
where can I go
[Music]
no way I didn't call that's that's where
right no
order
guys guys how do I
go
foreign
am I running the right way
no
no no no no no
wow
[Music]
foreign
I really didn't find anything
yeah I was rushing but
[Music]
at least like in the beginning when you
enter a new area would be nice
for Dragons eh
I don't remember seeing dragons before
foreign
[Music]
please
foreign
it was totally on purpose
[Music]
all according to keikaku
yeah
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
oh this is cute
is that not a landmark
[Music]
narwhal grasshopper
hmm
a diary wow
[Music]
what's that
exploration zip lines
oh it's so peaceful here
should I use a zipline
[Music]
oh sorry
I thought that was the zipline what is
this
little
that was your Universal graduation
congratulations
wow a chapter in your life clothes
beautiful
yes we're not using it
more graduations
nobody panicking though if it's not
related to me
double standards
oh sunset
wow so beautiful
oh it's becoming so Orange
just like me
oh real for real
[Music]
Donuts go this way probably
so I I'm not gonna you may have noticed
I'm not too like
um
careful about Gathering everything now
because well I'm gonna restart anyway
and
hopefully I'll be able to show you guys
more
of the game
this way but I'm not gonna play that
much longer
waiting for a good point to end it for
today
and then we gotta read some superchatos
[Music]
okay first thing in this game needs
absolutely no skill
noise you just need a nice fishing rod
wait we're dirty right there buddy oh oh
it just stops there for real
I missed my opportunity
I think I saw for a moment it shows e
should do something to interact with it
God damn it
but it didn't work when I pressed it
oh I think I have arrived Twitter
[Music]
oh maybe ah you know I probably have to
activate the zip line on the other on
the other end too
enable in in order to be able to use it
right probably
foreign
don't seem they keep on saying let's go
further let's go further there's like
nothing really to
not a good spot to stop at
whatever
I want to live in here
man this Lighthouse sure is tall it
would cut a pretty wait probably wait
lent you don't mean to
I mean we came all the way here right
let's go up
oh come on you better not forget why we
came here in the first place
[Music]
what
is that like a special dungeon
[Music]
foreign
that's where they hide the goat milk
[Music]
those flowers
more treasure there's no enemies here
there's just Treasures
[Music]
maybe at the very top there's a little
enemy
oh
nice view
look at us all red the view is
incredible
little detours are a big part of any
Adventure coming up it was a good idea
right
I gotta admit
this was a good idea lent I can't
imagine missing this View
oh
hey what's that over there
hmm wait a minute is that a pirate ship
or are my eyes playing tricks on me
you find out too why would there be a
pirate ship here
[Music]
um
well I see another little detour now
you're getting it now you're cooking
was there no more item out there so
would I have not seen the pirate ship if
I didn't go up all the way up here
okay
huh YouTube acting up sorry
yeah and don't be like that
sorry
YouTube please
Stay With Me
[Music]
U.S was dying
Europe was fine well another reason for
you guys to move to Europe or visit
Europe
I should be Europe Ambassador
where do I go here
oh nice climb
[Music]
sorry I'm just rushing now I wanna find
something
[Music]
foreign
only the second one though
[Music]
the water looks milky I like it
oh
random Quest trigger
and there's a quest for not only
killing some enemies but also Gathering
items that's cool
that's not it which one
over there that one I can go eat them
even faster
[Music]
can I jump I can't jump oh there's
another one
can I switch dolphins
mine's out of gas nah
yeah they're like on a set spot in the
map
if you want to roam around the water a
bit more freely
um
speaking of armor I have a Oh dolphin
gone I have a
a little something from her
let's just say a souvenir
you know how I took T-shirts from
some I mean I was given T-shirts from
some whole life Japan members
well well well
around the uh beginning somewhere in the
first one or two weeks
of the previous trip
um
[Music]
Cutlery I needed a spoon specifically
and
I guess I asked Ahmed if she has one I
don't really remember how we got to this
point but yeah she gave me one and I
have since not given it back to her what
the hell is that
[Music]
and she didn't ask for it even though so
I just took it home with me
I have a I'm a spoon now what is this
it's a pony shrine
serious
[Music]
steal it
she never asked
to have it back
she gave it to me in the beginning
borrowed it to me
I guess she didn't need it anymore after
that but now I have a Memento Memento
memento
from AMA as well
the Amber spoon
that's that feeling
I need a dolphin
One of a Kind Idol merch
I'm always asking about it in a stream
eh
she cried because she lost her favorites
from just kidding hey hey I was about to
believe it the first part was kind of
believable
what's this
what is this
but I guess go ahead the signs on the
map are about this thing
um
probably not able to do anything with it
yet what is this shadow
is there something above I can't really
look
for grappling
[Music]
and this area is definitely new right
all of this
is very new to me
and I guess
I would be exploring a lot hi thank you
if I wasn't
if I didn't know that would just make a
new save file anyway
that would take so much time and this is
already taking a lot of time even though
I'm rushing and just ignoring most of
the things
damn
yeah
a reason for it to take a trip to
recover the lost spoon of Amelia Watson
her life depends on it where do I go up
[Music]
get back her spoon
spoon the Wawa what are you talking
about
money huh on the map there's like a
weird thing going on here
wait where can I go up
let me up uh here maybe
males back
no comments
yeah I don't think she needs it let's be
real
but now she has something on me she's
like she could be like you're still my
spoon you owe me this
how could I say no
what is the reason for your trip um I'm
bringing back a spoon next time I go to
America
I know what to say to the immigration
guy I have a clear goal in mind okay
okay
I am here to spoon I mean no I mean uh
bring her the spoon oh
[Music]
that that's my goal
do I have to fight that thing
is
you know
am I like gonna struggle
I'm
I'm uh fail here huh
um is there any Landmark here
I can save so I can
yeah
did it save anything where am I now
oh so this should be a landmark there's
a there is a landmark here no no
it might even be friendly
doubt it
whoa
this is the landmark
fancy tree
I do have some bombs
well I don't know it doesn't feel like
I don't think I'm strong enough
this Fountain I don't know what it is
but when I'm close to it I feel power
flowing for me
does it heal us
vinyl power
ful
oh wow what
felt the power from the fountain gets
stronger for a second
[Music]
what's this
I wasn't there it wasn't there until a
moment ago it appeared here after the
Flash
I can't say for sure but it may be a
gift from this fountain
amazing maybe it's sympathized with our
power
sympathized
hey guys they're the same kind of light
is that a gift from the fronted Hill
let's get it
what
[Music]
that's right uni
it's just flowers
spring princess
line okay so I found that so now I could
go back and Save
in the Atelier and then a sapling brand
that's the stuff phone that has on her
head
oh
okay so I'll go back once
let me just check I have the landmark
okay okay
oh
I watched that whole uh birthday stream
of hers and then I didn't chat because I
was on the wrong phone
but I also watched like her whole
afterwards reveal thingy as well
rare for me to watch like full streams
from other members I just like Peak
every once in a while
let's see
yeah but I was actually watching while
cooking
so it was nice I have something to watch
[Music]
hmm
oh saving
oh yeah I was asking for slaps I was
asking not for me but for you guys for
those saplings actually
[Music]
free streams from fauna
free
I watched two I think
maybe it was free
[Music]
okay Clark Isles uh
what it was it here
yeah
so let's see if we will get absolutely
heated destroyed blasted
don't know
or if we stand any chance at all
do the show
I haven't even tried to fight a single
one of those small mobs
hello let's be friends
oh
doesn't move yet
now we got invited
no need to check it out no no
ah finally yeah this is a kind of like
progress I want within the stream we
understand what the key is for now
[Music]
oh I'm gonna unlock the
oh
oh that's it okay
oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
I am gonna fail
Ure
[Music]
looks way too strong
oh
that's so intimidating combat specials
special to certain enemies May begin to
try charging a special attack during a
fight once it's fully discharged this
attack will deal massive damage to your
team but you can cancel the attack if
you're able to stun the enemy before it
finishes charging
you can check it via help
okay by the way if I want Claudia to use
a healing item
I have to switch to her right how do I
switch to her
what was the button again to switch
somebody remember
[Music]
I already messed up
nah I have no chance look how much
damage he already did
I do a lot of damage too does he have
more than one health bar I wonder
goodbye
oh there none of them are effective but
whatever blast them go go go go
okay
this girl
can I stop him
is he gonna one hit us
can I stop him from doing that he's
almost dead
[Music]
yeah there's no there's a weight period
yeah okay here we go
I guess I'll do it alone
um
please tell me he doesn't have a second
and take
it
oh
[Applause]
yeah okay good yo
oh my God it's so rough alone please no
no no
hello
I feel like it's manageable
um but I think I want to put a healing
item in
one of my slots
but if he has a second how far does
someone know
if he has a second helper then I don't
know then it would be really hard
I really would have to level and craft
something better
[Music]
reload to save
why I didn't really lose anything
particular
ah if I waited the bumps until he starts
charging really
[Music]
hey I only lost like two islands or so
it doesn't matter
um he doesn't I mean he doesn't have a
second just the first one okay then I
think we can Brute Forces it's not even
that much of a Brute Force like
it's manageable
[Music]
and that will be the end of the game
totally
that's when the game ends all right all
right all right come on I can do this I
can do this
go kiwawa go
otherwise
is there a big a quick scoop skip skip
button
ah
space
ah I don't remember I don't remember
okay okay I didn't fumble now I fumbled
with this uh first time of the [\h__\h]
ah easy peasy yeah let's go
so should I not use the bums yet really
really
nice maybe like not all of them it's
them
[Music]
um
let me use it to heal someone can I
decide who to heal
oh this Hill's just myself
does it just heal me
[Music]
um
does somebody know
oh
[Music]
somehow it automatically selects the
bomb when I use the biscuit
oh well okay let's see if we survived
foreign
okay so now
it's charging now
now I can use it man
no
um I wanna
sorry I wanna use the craft beans
oh
[Music]
okay
okay easy easy
what kind of warrior you are let's go
what
is it Peasy Lemon Squeeze
is
wow
first try totally
just a little taste of how the fights
will be in the future
foreign
[Music]
what
what was that just now
[Music]
Lord Lord oh
Google
is that a door to that world
[Music]
foreign
not only
[Music]
foreign
civilization that is said to have
existed long ago little of the
literature remains and most information
about them have been passed down orally
their name appears often related related
to Alchemy
foreign
a kingdom that prospered for Alchemy in
the old days it had Advanced Alchemy and
built gates to the underworld to plan
the resources from the underworld but it
fell into decline after the Battle of
Felucia
hmm
me trying to learn Korean writing
excuse me
call of the universe is a symbol of
skill and exploration handed down to
Alchemists only the name remains but no
specifics are known
huh
explain more please
[Music]
foreign
Nittany
um
this will be such a great Cliffhanger to
stop at oh okay it's living its own life
its best life
happy key
what
their reactions
foreign
[Music]
I feel like it's just skinned itself
snake
[Music]
he was pregnant
oh
let her cook
she's cooking
oh my God
oh
was that a good or bad idea
America
is
exactly Claudia
I don't know
sorry guys even the characters are
giving up for today
it's over
what a cliffhanger
it's a cliffhanger
slow motion running
turn to the islands with a hill
foreign
[Music]
wow
I feel so accomplished anyway
um
should I end it here I guess it makes
sense to end it here
[Music]
this was
takanashikiwawa with
actually Horizon free Alchemist of the
end and the secret key
it rhymes
it was fun so far and I feel like
they're definitely improvements
[Music]
not saying that improvements were even
necessary
you guys shut up I'm talking here
thank you for the Memphis
[Music]
yeah I'm gonna be reading some Super
Chat tools
oh
yeah nice nice memberships
we don't want you to end yeah I mean
it's kind of sad it's not like me or to
start a game and then not finish it
um
so I'm sorry about that but you know
there's reasons and such as time but
also other things
such as monetization and more things
that I will not mention but
now we have plenty of other games and uh
so much to do if you never finish the
previous of course I did
of course I did
look at my channel I think there's
playlists for my other Riser game
playthroughs so if you're curious feel
free to watch those
um yeah
you know every once in a while I'll play
this
if I run out of uh if I'm done with
Queen's Gambit I think
I want to watch Queen's Gambit
right now kind of hooked
[Music]
um you can backseat me for Twitter sure
yeah I finished both the first and the
second one and I think for now and
that's fine to have that on my channel
um I mean I feel kind of bad about
[Music]
nah I feel kind of bad about it man
hmm
it would be a nice conclusion but it's
okay
maybe we can watch the anime together if
you guys want
it's just the first
uh
game though is this the first anime the
first Atelier anime they're making
gotta say damn they like accomplished so
much
or friesa that's really great oh this is
the second one
[Music]
right there was escan launch I watched
that one too
that's the one at the little game
that really triggered me because I think
I ran out of time or something there was
like a
time issue and I guess you know without
you guys helping me telling me how to
play the game properly I just I guess
was doing some things wrong
[Music]
family minute man that's I'm so glad
that's not a thing and Rise Up
um
I still understand how you run out of
time and Escalade well I kind of did
[Music]
I don't remember well but I just know I
wasn't able to finish the game
[Music]
I hated it in Aisha
the most forgiving one about the time
limit may have been like that but still
thank you for more memberships thank you
[Music]
eska
is
[Music]
foreign
reason for the one in Aisha oh
is there I never played that one
[Music]
for whole you got stuck in a near
tutorial two you weren't a gamer yeah
yeah yeah yeah damn yeah remember I mean
you weren't there but I told you guys
about it
I know I was able to clear the near
automata uh tutorial but I gotta say
it's it's rough for someone who plays it
for the first time
you know on their own yeah it's not that
easy
for real
anyway so tomorrow I play five lemon on
Sunday I guess we'll dabble into Diablo
4 probably
not 100 promised just yet but I'll look
into it I actually haven't seen like a
single teaser whatsoever
about the game
I'm kind of interested nonetheless
tonight
in the tutorial before there's any
ability to say for now yeah yeah yeah
that's another problem no safe oh my God
did Nero automata copy that from Metroid
Prime huh
not being able to save for such a long
time and really triggering me
apparently if you do the diable for
better someone can come to your house
and do your core chores while you play
the game
what
what are you talking about
[Music]
um
sounds like
[\h__\h]
oh
I wonder if there's a deeper meaning to
that
maybe killing gpus
I mean kill like forever kill
momentarily
[Music]
oh the cute time
huh
[Music]
what
TPU kill
[Music]
for the 80s I don't have a 30 80s right
it was breaking for the 80s specifically
those
well I don't have that right
so I'm probably fine right
[Music]
man you scare me what it's like a virus
then
legit kills your GPU forever
uh refund please
[Music]
Kyla was lagging
okay well I'm kind of worried about this
and that but we'll test it out okay
let's go to office
oh man I'm kind of exhausted kind of
tired today no energy today I'm sorry
about that
[\h__\h]
uh chat
maybe yesterday I used it all up
In My Memory stream
why am I so big
[Music]
here we go that's more realistic ah okay
um
did I leave the bgm like this
kind of nice
I'll leave it
yeah I'm glad you guys enjoyed the
member stream hey
really happy thank you guys
I ended up just eating something from my
Frieza some uh what was that a lentil
potato
or gratin that I did a long time ago
always good to have something in your
freezer past kiwawa thank you very much
for thinking of future kiwawa
lentils yummy I want to cook more of
lentils
uh where did I
leave off last time
[Music]
uh
I finished some superchators
I read them or I didn't
I didn't today
and my freezer is big enough don't worry
I'm living alone so honestly what I'm
not happy with is my um
my my my my my my my my my my what's it
called dishwasher
collab okay
I have one more hour till quitting time
it's a weird but slow Friday at the
office with only me in the department
well that's perfect that's perfect for
watching my stream
anyway Here Comes
this one I'm so happy that we did the
Stream
and we were able to bond so much I'm so
happy man I hope I can meet Gooby Diva
again
soon soon soon sometime
you know
near near future would be nice
it was a fun stream I'm glad I was able
to play a
um off collab only game with her
yeah metric Prime next week
good Austria when oh actually like we
were even talking a little bit about
that he
but I don't know when but you know
she's very open to the idea of it so I'm
quite I'm so happy
[Music]
about getting me in the middle of
[\h__\h] nowhere
[Music]
yeah goodbye
Austria when she should join
oh
She's Gotta meet my cats
it has to
okay so these super chattel shouldn't be
too long
um
[Music]
yeah I think she will love my cats but
doesn't she you know
it's pretty like much struggles a lot
with her own cats a cat
to cat
like she told me
quite a lot about her cat
and she doesn't seem
very happy with her
I think it's a good I'm not sure
yeah apparently he she is a monster
um
it's like she tells me these horror
stories about her cat and I'm like
how
such a troublemaker yeah
Gremlin cat
um
she hasn't mentioned it in a while
I don't know she doesn't seem to have
such a big bond to her cat like I do
um
I feel like
I don't know what's going wrong there is
that just
is a cat born like this and unfixable
[Music]
no cat can for real Bill evil monster
cat
[Music]
um the time her cat left her head just
on display
what you mean uh another animal's hat a
cat head or what
yeah maybe
hopefully her cat will chill out after a
while
[Music]
damn such an aggressive cut
she was a cat taking some leftover meat
out of the mouth or teeth of a crocodile
shows like that cat from hell but
I don't know
I feel like
[Music]
that would probably mean that that cat
had some kind of traumatic experience in
life uh until that point
and I would never
assume that it's the cat's fault
[Music]
but for real lying damn she's gonna love
my cats I think if she has so many
struggles with her own
[Laughter]
they're good noodles at heart yes
normally when cut getting engineering
will become more common yeah I've been
waiting for that too on my cats but I
guess they're still pretty young
[Music]
you can give her advice I tried actually
so
there was this time during our stay in
uh Japan
where we were we just like the whole
group
we were just walking away from lunch
was actually off of the ramen that we
had and you know we're going to go to
our dance lesson
and uh eventually we reached
um like a corner where there was like
um a street corner where there was a a
bread
store
and we still had some time I guess a
little bit some a little bit of time
before the dance lesson would start
I'm gonna check out the the store so you
guys just go ahead
so
see I guess like
we I want to draw this
I kind of want to draw this on the paint
screen
[Music]
let me cook
wait which one is the
diamond
[Music]
welcome perfect perfect
two ice creams in a row
Okay so
[Music]
um
well
straight corner here
and so
you know
the team we go over here and then we
were about to walk that way but Emma
says oh she wants to go
look into the bread store
and it had like Windows here it had
Windows here
so we just she says I'll just go go
ahead
don't wait for me it's okay I'm just
gonna check it out real quick you guys
go ahead
and
so
she walks this way but we were like over
here
[Music]
one two
wait a second
[Music]
I feel like somebody no we were probably
I guess we must have been four
confused okay let's just say we were
four here and then I'mma went that way
[Music]
okay bye bye but I didn't feel like
moving on so we just kind of stood there
and I started you know conversation with
gura and so on and we started talking
about Kito katos katos
so we all started exchanging our stories
about our pets yeah Kelly was telling
them about hers but it was telling about
the hers I was telling about mine also
where we were showing like some pictures
this and that we're talking and talking
and talking
[Music]
the whole time about cats on this street
corner right
and after I swear 20 minutes
after 20 minutes
you know
still no am I coming back we found that
you know she would eventually get out of
the store and then go the same way where
we would go
um but now I was getting like suspicious
I'm like
wait a second guys you keep on talking I
just want to see is she actually still
in the store so I walk around the corner
and they follow me and we look inside
and we stare people inside the store
like staring back and like well what are
these guys looking at are we staring I'm
just like hit
I mean it's gone I'm just not in here
I mean it's not here we waited for 20
minutes even though she said go on but
we've wanted to like I don't know
to wait for her
I want to wait for her
and wait five minutes for her to get
some bread
but even after 20 minutes she just
disappeared
hmm so we were like okay I guess you
know maybe she went somewhere else so we
just
went to the dance lesson Place straight
um
and then
once we arrive
can I make this bigger
not much bigger
[Music]
I'll just make
new
[Music]
eventually
the group
of
four I guess
reaches the dance lesson place
and who's standing here
I'm like ah man we were
we're waiting for you and she's also
like confused like why am I here before
you guys I told you guys to go ahead and
I'm like hey I wanted to wait for you
[Music]
yeah so she told us she never even went
into the bread place
and then she just went around like a
different corner
to reach there before us
she didn't even go into the bread place
even though she said she was gone and we
just waited there for 20 minutes talking
about cats
foreign and she had no idea
hmm
that's funny to me
but yeah I'm a I lost Army
um because she gets lost a lot in Japan
and like stations and so on
gotta be careful
yeah
at least you got to talk about cats yeah
it was actually quite fun
everybody was telling their cat stories
explained me
all of her cat problems
[Music]
it's fun
I guess she was just window shopping and
then ended up not buying anything and
just went to the place a different path
um
yeah I wanted to look out for her
Mission failed
all right let's read some super chats
Cruzan
fate in the bucket but now I am Freebird
so do I get back to work or should I
just hop back into the fryer
for now you can enjoy your free bird
status yeah thank you for being a member
for such a long time
eventually
what did I say I'm Gonna Make You guys
become
what did I say
what do you guys are gonna become
[Music]
did I say ashes or
oh aren't you being oh yeah but then we
also had the idea recently to turn you
guys into a burger
hmm
well we still got time maybe we'll get
even more ideas until then but the RGB
bird is already ready
um
ah another reborn one thank you
[Music]
return would you want to become RGB bird
or return to food status
it's kind of a downgrade unless you're
really committed to the bit
I remember who was that who
was some member who was so eager to
become food was always sending super
chats about it
[Music]
I feel like that person hasn't been
around for a long time
no I'm not thinking of yakaru
Felix yeah
Sal yeah where'd it feel like so go
[Music]
where did he go
has anyone seen Felix Style
I lost my chicken
[Music]
the team got eaten no
no please investigate someone
[Music]
has him on Discord or Twitter
have you seen my chicken
please invest again and report back to
me
I want conclusion
about everyone who leaves me
he's at the bread store are you sure
I've been waiting for 20 minutes outside
the bread store and no one's coming out
[Music]
it's a long time ago
hmm
I don't even remember but I I don't know
I don't remember when the last time was
but I remember the
super chats hmm
I remember everything
come back you don't need to bring back
milk I don't like milk like that
um
walking into a Popeyes no [\h__\h] way
thank you
for everybody who is still here
hmm
yeah
thank you
Flappy boy thank you for the words of
the chat
[Music]
uh thanks tencho it's so considered of
you to schedule a high tier stream like
the samitol Eco lab for CET friendly
hours
this way even the less flexible eel
Champions like me can catch alive from
time to time and sleep is welcome
yeah that was at like evening time jsd
really late
should have been decent for European
members to watch you're welcome
that's as good as I could make it for
European members at that time
[Music]
thank you king of the property oh you're
back to egg
I'll go back to
go back to Eric
don't you know the hit song
of uh what is her name
Winehouse Amy Winehouse
[Music]
anyway where was I ah you're welcome
Flappy boy thank you Sean for watching
I'm glad I could make a lot of people
happy with that collab it was fun I was
happy too I feel like we made ourselves
happier than we made you guys happy
I feel like we had even more fun with
that than you guys as I said like there
were so many
interactions that you guys couldn't even
see
like
the way we looked at each other gave us
very special looks
just doesn't come across the same way on
stream hmm
[Music]
I literally threw up man
that was fun
Flappy boy thank you
smokeless powder Richard thank you for
two oranges thank you
[Music]
never heard of the supper's Ready song
no never
the society thanks for the pinky
Hi boss I hope you enjoyed for foof
before the stream oh yeah that was
really yummy ah I didn't even tell you
guys I think
before that uh Cemetery stream
you know what we did
I reserved for us a place that
um you know I asked
I asked for that okay okay okay so we
did Ramen we did a lot of other things
what is there still one thing that you
haven't eaten yet because on the day
before or so I think we had Teppanyaki
so Teppanyaki also checked off the list
I wanted to make sure that she had all
the good stuff
experience at least once
and turns out she hasn't had Shabu Shabu
yet at that point so I reserved a nice
shabu-shabu for us
which wasn't a really calm quiet room we
had like our own room
it was really nice it was really elegant
the
waitresses the ladies that were working
there they were all dressed in like a
really traditional
kimono
[Music]
um
and then yeah we had Chapo Shabu
actually me and Guna ate way more than
Ina in this case
and I was there too
it was really good oh oh I was like so
emotionally moved
because like we got
um a really good
uh meat course so shopping is like you
know you've there's like a hot pot in
front of you in built into the table or
sometimes not built into which is on top
and you throw in like veggies and meat
really thin sliced meat and they serve
it to you raw first and you then put it
in yourself and then take it out
yourself and then you combine it with
like some sauces
hmm
[Music]
so damn
the meats that we got was incredible
you know I've been to a lot of Shabu
shabu's but that was the best shopping
meat ever
it wasn't so much in terms of like
quantity but the quality was insane so I
was like really sad when I finished my
meat but um you know I didn't want to
order any more it was okay
so you know what's kind of full already
for some reason she didn't eat so much I
she offered
to eat like two out of I think four or
five
of her meat slices
so they were already so little
they really didn't
serve much meat there but it was as I
said high quality wagyu shabu-shabu meat
and I'm like no way I cannot take that
from you that's really cool good quality
meat you should eat it yourself so I
turned it down once but like 10 minutes
later she offers it again
I'm like yeah
so me and kuna ended up sharing the rest
of India's meat
damn
we also had to eat a lot of the veggies
though because uh you know I was really
not hungry surprisingly
but the problem is like it felt like
there was 50 of the veggies was uh uh uh
mushrooms all kinds of mushrooms I
couldn't eat those
I said please at least eat the mushrooms
oh and then the cool thing was
afterwards we could choose
um what we wanted to do with the
remaining water and you know
often shopping places do that you get
the option to add like rice or udon
noodles
um
I think we added noodles and
if I'm thinking of a different occasion
and then mixing up things but I feel
like Ina got the rice option and Maya
may have been something else I'm not
sure anymore
um
yeah so then we finished it with the
noodles and then we got a dessert too
the desserts were nice too
like a really special dessert I just
went for like a safe option some I think
it was use Yuzu ice cream Yuzu is like a
Japanese citrus fruit
and grow went for
I don't even know what it's called
it's like a sea fruit a Japanese
traditional dessert but it was like a
see-through jelly
that you dip into a black liquid which
is I think black sugar liquid
you dip it into it
and it's like really long thin
see-through transparent jelly noodles
it's not noodles though
but it's in the shape of long noodles
I tried because I never tried that
before I tried hers
it's not cognac no
um
[Music]
I think I have a picture of it even but
I don't know I won't share but it seems
to be a relatively common traditional
dessert
no they were not green they were
see-through like completely transparent
no it's not tofu let me look it up maybe
I'll find something uh Japanese
transparent jelly
District clear Georgia
um no
no
I'm not similar
I guess just a different shape Maybe
[Music]
um
this ah amitsu
I think maybe it does although there
were no no beans
[Music]
I think it was called like the sauce or
something like coodle
[Music]
wanna be more chief
long thin noodles
let me add that to my description
[Music]
looks yummy It looks interesting that's
for sure
okay I'm really not sure I can't find it
right now I'm not sure anymore but
she enjoyed it I tried it I didn't like
it like that much
I forgot what Ina had though she had
something different too
um
zucchini
but these ones are really thin she had
like really
wide flat ones oh now I found the
picture that looks like it
oh oh let me show you
this is accurate
oh
this something like this
no
kuzukini
find explanation is made from Kudzu
powder Kudzu has been called Japanese
Aero root ah
also dessert originally been killed but
you can find it anywhere in Japan now
the dish consists of transparent
gelatinos noodles that are extremely
refreshing to eat which is why it's very
popular in summer there are two simple
ingredients in it water and cuts of
starch which acts as a thickener
mm-hmm
[Music]
cool rides I think it's good for her
that she's trying things like that
she's never eaten before
oh
starch is dissolved in water shaped in a
mold heated set and thinly sliced into
noodle shapes
[Music]
well
interesting desserts
in Japan
[Music]
oh
Kitty
[Music]
sauce
yeah it was a no and then that's it
[Music]
um
syrup made with water sugar and kokuto
kokuto is black sugar from Okinawa it
has a rich Smoky caramel taste like
taste hints of Maple and licorice yeah
yeah that's what it was similar to brown
sugar cocoa is great for creating deep
and bold caramel flavors unlike brown
sugar that consists of adding molasses
to refined white sugar Coco dough is
made by slowly boiling down natural
sugarcane juice
wow
interesting
[Music]
oh by the way the cruiser route for the
kuzukiri is obtained from 30 to 50 year
old Vine roots in the mountainous areas
of Japan
sounds rough
the route is prepared for a long and
delicate process where a small amount is
extracted into starch what a small one
only
because zucchini does not have much
flavor however this is appreciated for
its simply smooth texture and it's
delicate translucent translucent
appearance
[Music]
interesting
sounds like a hassle to harvest yeah
I don't know it was
I don't know how expensive it was I mean
it wasn't crazy expensive I feel like it
was part of the
um menu anyway like not part of the
course
[Music]
I'm getting hungry well I don't think
that dessert is very filling at all
it's a big luxury to eat this
but even you know I don't think you
should should feel regretful in my
opinion this better Japanese desserts
I wonder how many picked you as the
messiest room
wait what how that yeah there's like
some kind of questionnaire but either
asking like
yeah
how how would you guys know
is it like
depending on the information we gave on
stream before and they already set
what's the correct answer
I think
I think I know the answer
I mean my rooms can get very messy too
but I think there is some more messy
ones
yay
serving now the quiz
well don't disappoint me guys
I'm telling you
believe me
[Music]
you're investigative reporting helped
inform my answer to the messy room Quest
hmm
I can tell you also
Amish place was
like
not as clean as the Japanese members
places that I've seen
but
I wouldn't say like you know dirty or
messy or
yours no no no not at all and Kelly's
place I mean I've seen many of her
places
her places are very cluttered but clean
a cluttered ends like she has a lot of
stuff and shelves endless things
everywhere
[Music]
but pretty clean
who else could I
think that's it
is that all the places I've seen so far
from people
in Ian
I think so
[Music]
yeah that's it that's it
I think I saw I've seen a base bathroom
before
when she sent me a bathroom mirror
selfie
what was that about
that was like in the very beginning
hmm
[Music]
oh was that on my birthday stream ah
okay okay let's continue
um where was I
um
the social artist especially the pinky
Hi boss I hope you enjoyed for before
the stream uh yeah yeah I'll catch the
VOD but I'm happy you and God were able
to do a one-on-one collab for the first
time in over a year according to a
channel the last Samosa Outlets Club
yeah I guess that one just left scars
and made me associate pain
together with Gouda
no that's not at all what it is but you
know
I mean it's not like we didn't have
collabs I guess we just didn't have one
along collapse people take that like way
too serious like I'm trying to make
connections
and have like different collaboration
partners because there's so many people
that I hadn't collabed with at that
point and by now I mean I've collabed
with a lot of members but they're still
members I haven't collabed with and you
know recently mutola Senpai there were a
lot of fans who were happy to see that
for the first time
[Music]
variety is nice
who is the most hated printer
that was a phrased wrong wasn't it who
hates printers the most is probably the
actual question
um I will tell you I know who
they're possibly
painting it but I have to say though
I have been struggling a lot with my
printer too [\h__\h] my printer
I changed like the other day I was
trying to print something
a couple days ago and uh
it didn't work out at first it was
continuously the paper was getting stuck
inside for no reason I kept on like
dragging pulling it out and then putting
it back in but the same thing happened
over and over and over and over and over
again and then it seemed like it showed
me a sign I think that was saying that
there was almost no black ink left when
it was when after it managed to finally
print one page and then get stuck again
so I actually had some fresh ink for the
printer already
so I
put it in and then it still didn't fix
anything it still didn't work after that
so I had to give up it just didn't work
no matter what I did the paper always
got stuck inside and I opened it up and
there wasn't anything inside I don't
understand
the printers man
oh
I don't want to go all the way to those
stupid print shop
to get my [\h__\h]
man
I bought a printer so I could do that
here
yeah printers are a scam I agree so you
can put me up pretty high
when it comes to printers but yeah
apparently in her debut stream said that
she hates printers
but I might hate printers even more
if you own the printer then chances are
you hate your printer
[Music]
this is a bird thing
Maybe
doing
so much for printers sponsorship that
was never happening anyway
[Music]
yours broke down recently
that was bound to happen [\h__\h] printers
what
printer ink is such a scam
[Music]
agreed
I'd say it came in clutch oh nice well
at least it worked for once for you
Epson printers well [\h__\h] up some
printers then
no no I don't think anyone can be
neutral towards their printer nobody can
be neutral towards their printer
no you can only hate printers at least
your home printer at work for some
reason at work they often just work
I worked in my old workplace we had a
big ass like company size printer
I mean it did have its problems every
now and then as well
but I mean General functions were most
of the time functioning but this doesn't
count
that doesn't count
home printers all suck
[Music]
they are made to wear compared to the
home ones
not fair
business printers get maintenance yeah
that too
and they're just set up properly from
the first moments they get installed
[Music]
okay I'm so tired sorry guys I can't
banter months today anyway thank you for
the pinky Optimus Prime
baby because only one of you is used to
handling a chest
ah that one chess game with the chain
wrapped around it
yeah I don't think
it's anything to do with that
she was just she had the wrong strategy
and even on the second try
hahaha
you could not win
[Music]
thank you
for watching hope you enjoyed the Stream
soon
please thank you for the pinky
now that kfp is open for business I
would like two number nines number nine
large six foot X clip double seven two
number 45s one of cheese and large soda
thank you
coming right up but what do you mean now
that cave is open for business
always been open for business
it's been a while though
thank you
please leave a review
after you've eaten it is
you
that was the
Cemetery collab superchatos
I'm gonna read the Torah ones next
[Music]
I'm so tired why do I have no energy
today
[Music]
look we look so cute together
oh I know
[Music]
Violet ever got induction
Nathan cotton thank you for the rest of
the chat super excited to see my enoshi
and my Japan while she's singing
together hope you girls are fun what oh
yeah I guess it always wasn't your title
home Baker huh
it's really surprising there's quite a
handful of people who have TOA and
kiwawa as Oshi yeah always has been I
guess so I never paid attention
only paid attention to the kfp
well I'm very glad
that there's some of you guys
who I made very happy with that um
thank you
that sounds weird
he screams a lot for tour during Fest
how do you know did you guys doing oh
blind meeting
um
what's up with that what do you two have
in common I don't know like I was
wondering too
ah it wasn't a video call
um
sweet well did you also scream just as
loud for me
I hope so
any inside information please
he did okay
I believe
[Music]
you better
we have to put it did you guys record it
the all the calls you could record all
the calls
oh Nani
we screened hell allowed for you I was
afraid we're gonna get kicked out of our
place you came on right before quiet
that was the end of the year ah nice
lucky
thank you guys that's so sweet
I want to see the footage
so cute
I want to now I want to see it now you
told me I want to see it now
[Music]
anyway thank you Nathan mwah next one is
chocolate Insomniac thank you also for a
recipe chat I already know this is going
to be legendary collab between Phoenix
and attention
thank you yeah had fun talking to her we
barely got to sing the songs that we
decided on singing beforehand because we
were just so busy talking
and we had a little bit of a
time limit because it was after that
that I went to do the thing that I told
you about yesterday
um
it was right after
I mean well not right after I still had
like plenty of time
hmm
until at Senpai gave me like some advice
and so on I asked her do I look alright
and oh she like gave me advice so like I
I brought out some clothes because I was
in pajamas during the collab but I was
like I'm going to this place afterwards
I want to look good you know I want to
make a good impression so I showed her
my clothes and she gave me her opinion
on which one would look good and which
one would fit well
yeah I mean it was like mostly my
decision in the end but
she was staying for a while
um
yeah
then I told Inya and the other girls
whoever was there whoever wanted to see
it wasn't bad feel free to say hello and
Ina came over so yeah
[Music]
thank you chocolate Insomniac um
what where is the love Pokemon with
someone
but thank you for welcoming her nicely
on my channel thank you
[Music]
okay
sounds weird you sound weird
[Music]
no
that's all I can do with my energy right
now
I'm hungry and no energy
[Music]
um
GD thanks for the pinky it's always a
treat when you do karaoke doing that
that's in between it's just the icing on
the cake thank you
glad you enjoyed it thanks
so much for this that's okay it's been
so much fun thank you I had a lot of fun
too thank you for watching even though
we spoke Japanese
mainly I tried translating in between
what I feel like it became a bit awkward
for towards Empire when I did that so
I tried to tune it down a little bit it
was difficult you want to make your
guests happy but you also want to make
your viewers happy
um
[Music]
thank you
soon guys thank you everybody I guess
through today we weren't able to
monetize so I saved
some I gave myself like a buffer I guess
stalling
[Music]
people the people actually think I knew
all those rock bands because I was
basically just reading off chat
[Music]
um
um okay I'm like dead I don't know I'm
sorry guys hmm
let's have fun tomorrow find them and
thank you guys for watching me play
Adele
um I had fun I'm gonna play more take
I'll take my time but I'll report back
for you guys
I'll have to start from zero again I
guess
[Music]
I mean I don't have to but
it would make sense
[Music]
oh to learn the controls
hey I'm still I'm abandoning the stream
before 10 p.m what's up with that damn
nice damn I didn't expect that today
[Music]
almost six hours
that's not that long
but I think it was a good cutoff point
I was able to Shell
a good beginning of the story
like a good good appetizer I would say
makes you hungry for more so we should
get the game
not sponsored though not really
oh I'm so hungry and dead
[Music]
you intrigued nice
are you curious no
I'm gonna miss your wife wouldn't get a
game yourself and play it yourself
[Music]
stay between this dream which one
Japanese or English
Twitter
[Music]
what's nice to see Rise Against women
yeah it felt very nostalgic
[Music]
they were tweeted fan of me as ryza too
wow
what do you mean you wonder who won't be
the lucky kfb to get codes I don't even
have any quotes for you guys
what do you mean
sorry guys no clothes for you guys this
time
or are you referencing or hinting till
back in the day because I guess I had
codes for you guys um in brands are one
or two
might be reference
and never offered codes
[Music]
yeah I got coats for myself
oh
[Music]
oh sorry no cold
but apparently the game is on sale right
now anyway like a release sale
is that right somebody said that in the
chat before today
no
somebody said so
otherwise I mean they do a lot of sales
don't they so every once in a while
to do a sale you can just wait for that
oh no did I get one guide
I don't have the energy to get one guide
I'm gonna go now
foreign
[Music]
thank you for watching
um hungry
[Music]
thank you I'll be done soon bye bye see
you tomorrow
[Music]
foreign