whoa
[Music]
pineapple
mine
[Music]
in the chat
8-bit drama
did pineapple
about retrospective
and I can't find it
where is it
it's not on YouTube yet is it
I know when I found the pineapple one I
found it let's hear it
gonna listen to it now
[Music]
he's got summer Vibes in the back of his
oh
yeah I know you can hear it it's my song
it's got a beach behind him
[Music]
but I'm a big advocate for pineapple
people
oh oh yeah wait did he just do that
[Music]
do you know what I mean
can he do that it sounded like it came
from him too
[Music]
thank you
pineapple fried Kiana
[Music]
he needs to play retrospective though
he's gonna love it
[Music]
he's just vibing
I love I love I love you guys picking up
the pfk
[Music]
oh
nice
is he gonna do it again
I know that was that no it was just my
instrumentals Maybe
[Music]
some kind of tropical sound
why would there be a muscles on my cheek
hahaha
[Music]
okay
good night
[Music]
was this one today I guess so
[Laughter]
bro I'm happy with that one man oh my
goodness once I figured out that it
wasn't just like a straight beat it was
the uh
I was like oh oh ah a brain cell just
freaking went off in my head and now I
could play it right oh my God thank you
Dominic once again for the new subject
to me most red loving rock on very much
appreciate the prime support
that was 8-bit drama yeah but he's gotta
do uh retrospective
he's got to do retrospective look he's
gonna love it that's like drum song
Let's Go
[Music]
you can have the sound back
hello
[Music]
Sparks spunks
Chihuahua
pfk
baby
[Music]
spoken anyway
let's go this one today I don't know
what did I do last time
I don't know uh was it this one maybe it
was this one man
how you doing guys oh my God I'm kind of
stressed out because I just came from
Toronto I literally just came out of the
airplane
I was just in Toronto and now I'm back
in Austria I just got off the airplane
okay
[Laughter]
I'm stressed out I just quickly had a
little pre-dinner
now I'm streaming from the airplane
excuse me I'm right now in the airplane
is there anyone in the chat who's
actually also at the convention right
now
because I think it's still very much
going on
yes me
me ah I was
hey
yes a group of us hello hello group of
you
I'm there spiritually
um I came home after your panel oh
that's fast you just went there for me
wow
oh thank you Brucey
no no no I said Toronto I want to go
about to run this so far honestly so
understandable like I don't think it
makes sense to fly over a continent just
for like an hour of kiwawa don't feel
bad I will come back to Korea hopefully
one day
and uh Europe maybe one day too
[Music]
so guys we're gonna play holla Miami a
little bit and then read super shorts
not for honestly none of this is gonna
be too long because you know it's
already you can see my my time up there
it's already 9 P.M
because my day was occupied with
the anime convention panel appearance
with Wayne that was so fun no no I want
to tell you maybe a little bit about it
when I can
um so fun it's been a while since last
time
feels like it's been a while
oh no don't rip my sleep schedule it's
it's already ripped so
uh oh we can deal on Hogwarts Legacy
30 off
should I buy it now
what other weekend deals have we got
human fall flat
sea of stars
some publisher sales
there's a Pax video game exhibition
September one two four oh
now
is that the
is that like supposed to the West says
West is that supposed to be like uh
something that makes out for the lack of
the what's it called the big thing that
we don't do anymore apparently the big
gaming thing
eh
E3 e Fria that's what I mean Pax
westerns is in Seattle I thought that's
La
Pax kind of took over from if you're
here okay okay that's so like sad that
they don't do it anymore that's so lame
it was nice to have something bundled up
but okay okay okay Ministry okay you do
you you do you
oh
was that you free with the oh was that
you free
with the guy that I'm huh
what I'm thinking of isn't there another
thing that's like similar to E3
hey
what that with the guy that's like funny
I'm as as vague as ever
maybe it's game awards yeah
[Laughter]
yeah yes yes no I don't know G of Kaylee
I mean the guy who's like I don't know
I Google G of Kaylee
him
yeah he seems familiar
so he does which one games
he was at Gamescom but he does
game awards okay are we still doing Game
Awards
I'm asking you guys so many questions
I'm in a talking mood right now
yeah okay hey at least something
g off oh is it job
see off
it's a job
it's Jeff oh
what a weird way to write Jeff
I don't think that sounds like a
non-existing name I feel like that could
be a name
G oh
g off
funny okay let me
I'm going one two
one two three let's play Hotline in
Miami
loud
for sure oh
loud kind of even though it shouldn't be
so loud
um
ah beautiful Oh What A vibe
What A vibe
it's allowed the loud so loud
wow I have I guess my overall audio
really loud right now
I'm gonna go back and replay the
tutorial I don't need
no gamer skills hello I had some issues
in the beginning maybe but not
afterwards
is it good now
we can still turn it down later if it
gets too loud
um so yeah let's play a little bit it's
not gonna be a long stream
um because it's late already but at
least I'm streaming better than nothing
mascara
what is this ah
are we still in Pilots huh
what
is this
this is where I I don't understand is
this what I'm supposed to choose
what does it say skip intro
what intro
intro
why is it asking me now about the intro
pick the last one act two oh yeah but it
looks looks like see this looks like I
don't know I didn't do it yet you know
what I mean
I'm in act two
oh
where
high scored zero best time unknown
now here I got something
huh
oh now it's quiet why is it so quiet now
that's loud though okay music up
is that music is that sfx
and that what about what about maybe a
bit louder
it's very different from the menu what
the hell
okay
ah hello
oh dear you scare me
um
oh
you need an invitation to get in
I'm here to see petraf tell him
detective Pardo sent me I didn't think
so
that it's a quiet still yeah I'll raise
it for you
here we go
if you don't have an invitation you
better leave
well well can I shoot you
I can I can punch him
oh what
was I supposed to do that
uh oh
oh I'm Reviving him I'm Reviving him
did I instantly regret my actions oh
money he died
eh
kind of funny that I tried to revive him
though
do they not see me it's like four stairs
they should still see me I think help
somebody call an ambulance oh we're
actually oh
there's been an accident and they're
gonna kill me is there anyone here oh
uh I don't remember how to fight
come here come here
[Laughter]
you can come here okay
he's gotta go he's gotta come closer to
me a little bit more
okay don't scream so much already
I can see me
wait maybe I can't um
how do I pick up weapons again
and I pick up weapons again right click
it didn't work the I was trying to
pick it up
isn't working
oh he can't candles weapons stuff oh my
God
yep
[Music]
well
that's a bad position
Maybe
[Music]
yo
okay okay okay okay
he was taking so much time what
ah
okay
what the
laughs
ah
[Music]
try to understand aren't they gonna see
me no okay
basically same pattern they have two
non-gun people and yeah
like take a break from hinting I don't
understand man
I don't understand what is he right
click after two hits
okay I'll try to it's weird like I'm
like am I pressing the wrong thing but
then it works though partially
oh
you can't get on him
or is he done and now I can't pick that
up either can I only pick up when I'm on
their body only non-level weapons
he's done or what
[Music]
okay we're playing baseball now is this
in their position they're done for now
what are they gonna come back to life
okay
ah
okay that seems my character doesn't
want to kill that is so out of character
okay now we shouldn't go over there
because I can't really see what I'm
hitting there
we should go this way
okay uh come here guys
I should have known
uh standing through to Minot God damn it
I forgot
ah
let's make a starting Twitter
also that the pineapple pizza let me
just say
oh yeah I know it doesn't look so good
it wasn't even that good it's so hard to
find decent delivery pizza
like if you want like proper Italians
quality good pizza you won't get that
delivery most of the time
we have begun already where are you
yeah no the pineapple was fine
yeah but overall like the crust was like
[Music]
yeah okay uh yeah okay
your first con even though I mostly
happy okay you know what's funny uh the
oh the staff oh God
the staff introduced uh me and Wayne app
or before
um the panel started and we were
listening in and I we were muted though
but I was laughing so hard because
um MC was good but like I don't want to
roast him anything but he just didn't
really know us I think that was very
noticeable because he's he said pfk and
it got me laughing so hard I think I saw
I was I was seeing the camera feed and I
think I saw a kfp smiling too
um
ah
who else is there
that's probably the only person left
now I know BFK BFK
but I heard that
um something uh something about pfk
being yeah actually a thing and Cube
Cube
quebecue
kid is that how you say it Quebec cubic
I feel like it was something that I was
uh I wasn't expecting
right
okay okay okay okay
Quebec cubic cab okay back
whatever
uh yeah why is KFC called pfk there KFC
is called KFC everywhere why not in
oh hell
came back
thank you
ah
man
uh pulley fruit Kentucky what the
just call it KFC like in other countries
where language is not English it's also
just KFC
like I don't see a reason why you would
make it
pfk
no in France it's also KFC I think I'm
pretty sure so it makes no sense to me
they have to translate it say la
they try really hard to keep their
connection to French
[Music]
come here come here
uh French Canadians they're like that
really hi
okay
oh
did you just break it the teeth is that
broken did he break that thing
wow okay
foreign
okay
he unloaded it wow okay
interesting guy
just like me for real for real no
oh
I'm still warming up okay
uh
I'm scared I'm scared okay
one more
oh my God come on
again odena my name he still pronounced
my name pretty decently I think
takanashikiara but in his name he said
Renee
pavolio Renee he said that that was
funny to me too
the emcee I'm talking about the emcee
talking about emceito of the convention
panel what's quite funny
shift IRS shift was a thing shift
thank you
okay
are also completing in French they were
nice though like MC and staff everybody
was nice actually the
the one of the staff who was like mostly
taking care of everything
he was at first wearing a miss or Modi
t-shirt
almost t-shirt
ow what the
yeah and I recognize that even though
our camera feed is pretty bad quality
yeah I see I know I know
and then later he changed into another
shirt I'm like oh where the shirt is
that is that my AFP ring or shirt let's
go
he has a whole shirt collection it seems
yeah he had the kfp ringer shirt on I
don't want to assume anything but one of
the staff might be biased in the kfp
if your ring is my sleep shirt it's so
comfy right it has a really soft fabric
yeah a real one and then you know I was
watching when people were coming into
the panel room it was
one of the smaller rooms but I was
honestly happy because I was really
worried that we couldn't even fill this
room
it was like lengthy but never kind of a
never room
um
but yeah they were coming in and I saw
already in the beginning so many people
with orange shirts or quinoa shirts
it was the biggest room in the con the
con isn't that big oh yeah yeah I I
guess must have been kind of a smaller
convention
yeah and I saw like Wawa cosplayers and
I saw two pecora cosplayers one casual
one and one um default one I'm pretty
sure
and I think I saw
some more cosplayers brain hordes can't
remember now
and then they were like three separate
people with fresh pineapples
and they they kept they showed it to me
in the feet they showed it off to me
good job bringing pineapples I did
honestly not expect any to see any
pineapples
one two three yeah maybe that was
coordinated one two I see one two one
two three people bringing pineapples
right
fresh pineapples and I was saying to the
oh nice and that's the right way to do
it I guess I was saying to the audience
like hey you guys should
um make sure to use that pineapple
afterwards to make pineapple pizza and I
thought that was really funny the way I
said it but I didn't hear any laughter
but to be quite honest with you
I think our audio feedback from the
audience sadly was not really existent
I don't know if they laughed at all but
I looked at their faces and nobody
looked like they were laughing so they
seemed pretty unimpressed with pineapple
pizza or the idea of pineapple pizza
uh we groaned and laughed really
hmm
do they do Canadians hate pineapple
pizza even more than other people
hi come here come here
once you come here can't you see me
oh
okay I I was able to take care of that
one so now we just have to go to the
store
they invented
well again then pineapple should be your
new national anthem and you should be
all celebrating my my idea about eating
pineapple pizza after the convention
hell
oh
that was difficult
[Applause]
what if I go around
hey how am I supposed to do about those
guys
I'm what
okay
okay that was wait oh let's should we
wait for those guys too
oh my God I found the strategy
okay waiting by the door for you guys
can I what is this lethal is this I
wonder that's considered lethal
I can use that one huh
okay any more gun guys maybe we can go
to that room
or that one I don't see anyone in the
Halls at least I'm not better stay like
that
my reach is not very much
okay good good good good
the fact that he doesn't realize that
his friends just got bonked through the
door kind of dumb I guess I can throw
them on how do I throw it again
throw it again how do I lock on again
right oh yeah true right because
I'm getting rid of the ammo that's so
funny
oh yeah and then like this
tell me that throwing doesn't knock him
down completely and then I don't want to
delete it
five percent is an Ontario invention
whoa
well then even more reason for me to
love Canada
um Canada Oh Canada
people are the nicest
Oh Canada are we gonna do this I'm gonna
still try to not throw it oh
[Music]
great great
I'll get another one
[Music]
scream is my weapon
I'm trying to scare people with my
scream you know like an animal that were
the absolutely
laughs
oh sent a really cute group picture by
the staff
like by our staff
ah
I got a Cave Creek picture which one is
you guys
you have to tell me oh my god look good
they're all orange
they're all orange oh a lot of them even
bought the Toronto
um convention only t-shirt
yeah and they got the maze they didn't
they don't have the other cute Kiwa
cosplayer though that I saw the other
one did they not find her this time
hey cute who is who I need a list of
names
I need names gonna show retweet it it's
not a tweet they just sent me the
picture I don't know if they'll tweet it
too if it's like because apparently I
don't know who took the actual picture
actually
maybe they'll upload them that shirt is
too good you think so you like the
T-shirt
um
my folder
aha Mamma Mia what is that
massage chair it must be a massage chair
but that part looks kind of freaky
okay let's do our best on other side
same thing I think oh oh we can door
that MF
if we do it right yeah
okay
oh
oh oh wet easy easy easy easy
foreign
oh suddenly very brutal I've
like lethal then why is he doing
that like that was
exaggerated wait there's more
you know
is he done
okay oh there's a there's a person
sitting in the sauna that's a sauna cool
it's realized
are we killing them both
goodbye
that's not fair
where's the scripted
I'm writing a book about the mask Maniac
it's like this pirate told me I could
talk to you about it
are you a friend of yours
I should be sweating too because I'm
really nervous another very good friend
I take it sending you here of all places
no I reckon you're right about that
this book you're writing it must be very
important to you risking your life to
come talk to me you sure got balls
well what is it you want to know you get
two questions then you get the out
of here all right the police claims the
masked murderers were a part of a
vigilante movement
are you of the same opinion no
I don't think they were Vigilantes they
were much too organized they knew our
exact locations and are insight into our
inner workings I don't know what they
were a part of but it was no group of
Vigilantes what is vigilante
why do you think they targeted the
Russian mafia specifically what where
are they after
I can't tell you what they were after
but like Batman oh
they effectively destroyed a whole
organization and then they were gone and
they knew what they were doing and they
seemed to be trained very well
we caught a couple of them alive and
tried to break them
none of them talked not a single one all
right no more questions
okay so did you see already I was to
punch this guy holy
it's quartz
oh thank God okay
oh
I was so stressed out just now oh Mamma
Mia
[Music]
my water bottle
along with other 3D women and let's go
[Music]
I wanna breath from that oh damn
Funk
same just got it today let's go Kiara
3d water bottle
B for dangerous
what a day
what kind of voice would he have I don't
know
what is something happen
no well yeah that guy Patrol
you know what he looks like a little bit
I'm only saying this because I'm
currently watching
which is so random
um
uh once it called again
um home it's on Disney plus right now
but it used to be on normal TV home in
German it's which I think is a really
cute name
home not renovation home
Home Improvement
Improvement he looks like a l l l n l
the a l l what's his name yeah Allen
Allen no not Tim Allen it looks like the
other guy the the guy
who is with him on the TV show
but he has a bit more beard I guess than
that
Al Borland yeah
I I used to watch why am I watching that
because I used to watch it as a child on
TV randomly and uh I was really young
really really young and now I found it
on Disney plus so I'm like you know what
I'll give it a chance I want to see how
this hits when I'm an adult
and it's honestly kind of cute and funny
and it's like not that bad as an adult
too
and I'm listening to it the first time
in in English I used to watch it on
German
yeah blast from the past
it's actually so cute and and and now I
can understand it better like my brain
is more involved now
yeah in German the name is
uh listen to who's hammering
[Music]
who's using the hammer basically
what a translation yeah that's a
translation I blame it on myself
foreign
listen to who's banging listen to who's
bonking uh it doesn't get better somehow
in German it doesn't have this
it doesn't sound weird when German
[Music]
hey
oh man anyway it's kind of cute I like
watching it right now it has many
seasons so I guess I'll watch it for a
while the neighbor the neighbor is
always like that mystery because you
could never see his face
but actually in certain angles you do
see quite a lot of his face anyway I
don't know why they always
hide it yeah Wilson Wilson
and I think the mom like as a child she
always just seemed like a typical
annoying mom who's just like all she is
is a mom and I don't know she seemed
annoying when I was a child but now as
an adult when I watch it now she's
really Charming I like her
you guys should give it a try too
he wouldn't see me I almost got beaten
up just trying to get in
oh you actually went there you didn't
figure you would
man sometimes I wonder why I hang out
with you when did you become such a
douchebag
well I did tell you to write about the
Miami mutilator instead didn't uh a much
more sophisticated case really and you
wouldn't have to talk to the mom people
will have forgotten about those
Vigilantes by the time your books are
you will just wanted growing up me too
me too dad and like full house and I was
really young
besides I bought you beard right and you
didn't really get hurt did you let's
call it even her
thanks for the beer and all everybody
who still owe me one
already don't forget I'm putting my job
on one if anyone finds out I'm giving
New Leads then it'll be it for me
they'll decide for incompetence or
misconduct before that happens so I'm
surprised they haven't fired you already
card let's get out of here okay
yeah I should get some sleep too you
want to ride you know that kind of
douchebag voice that I'm trying to make
right now I feel like it's the male
equivalent of a valley girl voice
let's go let's go oh my God
it looks good
Surfer Dude voice
recently I know you may have noticed
I've been saying a lot of Nara and garu
and so on it's it's the Australian
influence in my brain right now that I'm
not doing Valley Girl voice when I'm
doing that I'm just doing an accent okay
it doesn't mean I'm doing valley girl in
that moment yeah new jeans with the New
Zealand and the Australian influence oh
my God
talking to them they just I just watched
them and they it stuck with me it's so
stuck
right now it's so stuck in my brain
um
[Laughter]
I'll take my chances on the bus
okay oh
now we play the the blonde guy
bye bye
you sound like a Jewish style douche
talk while constantly biting a bottom
lip with your top teeth
what how can you even talk when you do
that
so we're going somewhere special tonight
eh
yeah my friend Jack told me about this
place down on Northwest 184th Street a
real hold the whole building's
occupied occupied by junkies and low
laughs
[Music]
you mark anyway his sister's been
hanging out with these wasn't
been home for weeks it hasn't been he
figured we'd get her home and teach her
friends at lesson plan we're doing art
schools for your friends now are we
isn't that pretty much what we did last
time I didn't hear any complaints back
then we can't Patrol the streets looking
for scumbags we'd be in jail in no time
yeah but I didn't sign up to be no hero
rescuing woman and that's not my
thing I just want some action
so you got any better ideas
oh should we just stay here or should
you stay here and argue all night
I'm sure as hell ain't staying wait is
there two ducks oh I just realized
there's two ducks oh but not Ducks
swamps whatever
[Music]
is that a duck noise it sounds like a
bird noise
[Music]
jump up
how cute uh ain't staying here I'm ready
to roll
come on I'll come along with you but if
anything happened to the girl it's not
my problem got it oh now I'm what zebra
what am I
oh my God I'm so many people at once
sixteen moving up
oh okay we can do Corey who has the roll
Dodge yeah
or we can do Tony killing punches no
weapons
didn't I have fun with that uh decently
last time I'll try it again
[Music]
those are some bloody punches and the
music
[Music]
either aim
oh I should not say anything throughout
the whole stream And We Just Vibe to the
music honestly
[Music]
come here
come here come here
it's actually really loud is it
maybe a little bit less here
foreign
guys
I'm here
please
okay
[Music]
nothing here this is a big place
oh she's dumbing Daft Punk oh I love
that funk
I love this kind of music too yeah
was that my punch
[Music]
this makes me nervous
okay good so far pretty good pretty good
oh he's smoking doesn't use that as a
weapon
would you like to come back to the door
sir
foreign
[Music]
can't get to the other room huh okay
then I'm gonna go
what a bob okay he went inside
[Music]
okay
it's actually pretty easy so far first
trying everything
[Music]
oh what's he doing
okay first try I don't even I didn't
even go that slow
foreign
[Music]
I was really occupied in the past couple
of weeks with album finishing and I
don't know what Elena was doing but she
seemed kind of preoccupied too
um so when staff was like starting to a
dog oh no
so fast
that was like starting to try to get
like an idea out of us of like what do
you want to do
I I just I wasn't really able to really
think of anything interesting or new
so I was just like oh let's sing again I
guess and have many games and then staff
came up with the mini game with a new
game that we didn't really do before so
that's cool what we did oh okay I did it
okay
like a convention game what we did was
goodbye
that's a heart attack man
[Music]
what we did was like a lyric game
in three different difficulties although
I thought the hard one was easier than
the medium one partially for me
uh
[Music]
so in the easy level they would show
um one song for me and one song for
dinner
um like only Snippets of lyrics
[Music]
the first song uh dance so obviously
easy since we just still had it in our
brains right
what do I do about that dude
[Music]
let me go back up
nah that's the only path I can go to
though
I can go that way again
[Music]
okay at least I I got him to come over
here
oh and dog is
dog is it can I get them
nah the dog is so difficult again
yeah so they would show like Snippets of
horridori dance and we had to fill the
gaps and if we didn't know we had we
were able to ask like the audience
but on the easy level we weren't the
least important supposed to ask the
audience but it was going really nicely
in the beginning and then
soon after I already scrambled
surprisingly
[Music]
um but then Lena also was you know in
the second
um lyric example okay
struggling so it wasn't just me it
wasn't just me and that at least gave us
an opportunity to interact a little bit
more
with
um
with the audience
yeah bye
yeah
have to bait out the dog because I feel
like it's too late when I wait until he
passes by
[Music]
e
did you see me
see me
[Music]
no one else is coming okay you know
well that was not the punch that I
expected
[Music]
uh okay no no gun guys all right should
I risk it
[Laughter]
I didn't see
it
oh my God I thought he had no guns
I need longer arms I need Luffy arms
fluffy is the one with the long arms
right
thank you
yeah so hopefully dance was the first
song So we had like six questions uh
free per person about the lyrics
and then uh the next song was um heart
Challenger by Kiara and Elena quickly
knew like she got the first question and
she had no issues and then then it was
my turn for my own song
[Music]
oh and I I was struggling
even though it was such a
hmm familiar part of the song it was the
make me fake me and I was struggling was
it made me make me well later I remember
the fake me okay I remembered it I
remembered it eventually it just took me
a moment
's favorite of yours yeah she did say
she's singing a lot and that I think she
did say also
at the spot that
your favorite yeah our oldest smoking
ones actually gun carrying
[Music]
oh guys come over here hi
oh no one saves me hi
[Music]
hi oh my God okay I'll go from here
um
hi hi
[Music]
I don't want to come over
anyway then it was
the one I got was really simple it was
actually
almost too simple because it was
something I could have guessed just
because of the context of the line and
the Rhythm
[Music]
um so that was easy too
uh and then
oh we're all stitching struggle
I think she really only struggled with
that
with one horror 39 actually that Subaru
was singing
yeah yeah so we were guessing a few
songs and then at the end the hard level
was suspect the hard level
lyrics to guess was suspect but we know
suspects so well we sang it so many
times
so honestly it wasn't really a challenge
we immediately got the answers like we
looked for one second at the lyrics at
the screen and we immediately knew it
so that really wasn't much of a
challenge
I don't know I I hope it was
uh let me actually ask the few Canadian
uh Bros who were here were there was it
okay was it fun because I wasn't sure we
had to kind of rush through it
eventually I noticed that you know our
time was we were running low I thought
the game wouldn't take so much time but
we were rushing through it
so I felt like maybe they're not
enjoying it I don't know it was a lot of
fun really
[Music]
yes okay okay if you say so it was nice
some awkwardness we didn't really feel
awkward
to be honest I noticed that we made some
some audience members feel a bit awkward
because when we were asking for help
they were like a little bit shy
I don't feel awkward though
not really
um
I just felt nervous because I noticed
that the time was running out and we
were supposed to sing four songs to each
and that usually takes like 20 minutes
um like maybe 18.
add a girl I thought I bought some
raising her hands to say the line to
help us stay the line but she was just
raising her hand to say um
who sang the line which was also a hint
that Reina wanted so it's okay but she
was cute I I complimented her on her
accent and I saw the whole audience
laughing like she said like five words
and I was like oh my God your accent was
beautiful and everybody laughed
I'm just being honest
that's pretty
[Music]
pretty accent what did I do don't shoot
maybe I should go outside still my
mother
I just want to bait uh I want to bait
both of them come here
how how do you know
nothing
hello am I actually like too far
yeah he must have seen me then let's go
here
it's right there
[Music]
oh my God I can't risk it too much
come on
okay that was difficult
okay now maybe
Ah that's rough that's rough that's
rough it's rough I can't just run into
that room from Below
because they there's so many guns
wielders
and the smoker has a gun
[Music]
yeah
come up again please
[Music]
yeah I wanted to go after him but number
one oh
laughs
[Music]
um yeah
okay uh
is there something here
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
the outside is cleared now I can go in
there maybe
I got stuck in the door
no place no
ah
oh man
anyway yeah we sang some songs and Dana
told me that she wanted to sing
um
uh I was gonna say that and illusion
nice and I thought actually illusion
Knight and tgw have a similar Vibe and I
knew you guys might want to hear that
one so I chose I chose the tgw to sing
it first and then also pineapple of
course we just released the envy and I
think it's hype and people in the
audience can scream
the feet
he's kind of dead the audio fade
but I was just hoping where where was
everybody screaming pineapple
my hands still heard from the Clapping
along
I'm sure they yelled it I hope so I gave
really clear instructions and I tried my
best to
um like within the song instead of
singing right before pineapple I I gave
instructions like so around
[Music]
well you know stuff like that I
implemented it
seems like a rock as a live performance
I think so they were yes we did awesome
yeah they yelled it out good hopefully
you were also wow proudly showing off
your pineapples
[Music]
why why did he have a gun
I'm sorry if there was more
but I think they were free
no doggone
not there he comes
[Music]
let's wait for him
come on yeah okay
right
oh bgm dead
and they were aiming for more
I saw also so many highlight highlights
pen lights it was uh kind of weird like
normally normally at conventions like
this the people who sit in the very
front are like the most hype and the
further you go back in terms of seats
the less hype the people are
what
um but for some reason there was like
this specific section in the in the
venue
yeah you got the pineapple hits
different when you're holding an action
pineapple
there was a specific section in the
middle that was like extra hype they had
uh like the whole middle section had pen
lights
and they were really she like so
cheerful
[Music]
gang
but everybody seemed to enjoy it so I'm
happy everybody was like clapping a
little bit yeah and I did away why did
the wave again it's been a long time but
I did the wave
[Music]
yay of course I did yeah but I did it
from front to back this time and then
back to front and they look nice they
look beautiful
[Music]
really nice
signature wave
it's not a wobble panel but by the way
it's exactly
you know need some I think it's really
nice to have some audience interaction
because they love that kind of stuff
they eat that up hello
hello hello hello
oh my God
how close are you guys making me making
me come to you please
okay I'm gonna run again
yeah that was see that's them what can I
do
[Music]
um
I was gonna go back quickly I was just
gonna haunt him but it's difficult
somehow
Tony math will rock
um I guess so because a lot of these
guys are keeping their distance
hell
um but I'm I I am dedicated to this now
oh we got the gun guy quicker this time
I guess they just switched oh
I really enjoyed the panel really
thank you actually like we even went
over time I was worried we could even
fill the time properly but we even went
overtime for like 10 minutes or so
it was fun I wish we could have done
even longer I always feel so bad because
like panels are so short and you guys
pay money to get there
wish we could do it longer too
[Music]
we're bunching
ah
man
I'm just trying to speed for the
beginning love from Toronto left back
Morano thank you
[Music]
okay ready to go dog still coming
talk you want to go faster
cool hi
[Music]
okay cool cool cool cool cool
[Applause]
why don't you see me
why don't you okay
[Music]
now you're counting the days until you
can see me again in Toronto I mean maybe
I don't know that will
adopt that they will get the same guests
again one year later
um I don't know if you guys have any
other big conventions in Toronto
even this one you guys told me it was
kind of small
don't you have a bigger one in Toronto
come back to Orlando
wait which one was Orlando when was I in
Orlando
[Music]
oh that sounds big
conventional I would love to with anime
North let's go anymore well you know
it's not on me
um
the
they like to recommend me you know
especially to
like also Korean conventions they're
like how about koala she's uh
she's she's studying Korean you know
yeah
hey
maybe I could run now I'll I'll try
oh I couldn't turn around fast enough
that would have been nice
[Music]
oh
didn't see me huh no he saw me
[Music]
now we should have a whole life
convention
but not in Japan we should have one
overseas that would be nice
for Ian and ID members
that's what I want to see
[Music]
masturbate
I am the master beta dog
timing of the dogs is so difficult
[Music]
huh I just heard something disconnect
what was done
what is that you guys hear me right
[Music]
clip it I've said it before
okay doll come here
[Music]
windows
so this one sees me even though he's
turning his back on me but the other
ones are looking at mine what's going on
the other ones that are looking in my
direction they don't they don't even
notice me okay
let's try to bait them through this door
somehow
[Music]
oh oh dog
um hi yes okay okay okay this just gotta
work what the what's happening
well Windows want some attention
[Music]
I had to risk it I had to
we'll be stuck for ow it's lagging
we'll be stuck forever on this level
[Music]
yeah
thank you
shotguns are evil it's lagging because
of all of the shitty Windows what's what
are you trying to disconnect and connect
what is it well I'm not even moving
anything
what's your problem
and let me disconnect some things
completely
is this
it's nothing
okay now stop stop Windows stop
okay
and I was having a moment yeah oh so I
got like disconnected I don't know if it
was me or if wayna's connection was
kicking me out but I got disconnected
several times from weiner
so weird I never have uh stay unstable
Connection in these situations but
during the panel
only during the panel during the game
section thankfully not during the
singing section I got disconnected like
three times I was like what's going on
I'm scared that this happens when I sing
I was always back pretty fast though
yeah
[Music]
the world
okay
but yeah it was fun and everybody seemed
so nice and we got to
um talk to some Toronto fans so okay
Canada Canada fans but also some people
came from America even
that was really sweet
and it really relieved me I honestly
really thought that we would not be able
to or I would not be able to fill the
venue
[Music]
but we did and people were even standing
in the back I mean it was a relatively
small
um van like um room
yeah but like I don't really see cat
Canadian super chats much so I basically
judged it by
what currency I see a lot you know
uh
yeah I'm Canadian thank you
[Music]
quinoa merchandise someone you can watch
sure
when even the staff wears your
merchandise that made me happy like the
MC had probably no idea who we were but
um the staff the staff knew who we were
I wonder if the staff guys like uh
a common kfp chatter
[Music]
he didn't say any recognizable kfp name
or so I don't know
I was wearing your first uh
pull my shirt
yeah you know in the beginning when the
first people were coming in I could
still like hello
I could still kind of like
[Music]
see like oh okay this person is wearing
that shirt this person is wearing that
shirt but after a while like everything
was just because of the camera quality
and the streaming quality was just
getting more and more blurry like a mess
of Love of colors but
the door disarmed him yeah nice okay
well I don't think we can continue There
realistically speak unless I well I'll
try to yeah yeah okay
those two I don't think I can taunt that
well
um
if I run past here they will not react
to me right
hey Canadian
so we want to see more Canadians to
protect wow
you weren't there it's free
kilometers away
yeah
your guys's continent is kind of big huh
anybody you
[Music]
hello no
okay I run I run I run okay okay
[Music]
please tell me that above you there's no
one with a gun
oh okay nice jilliance
bank I remember you yeah one of the
Canadians
um this door doesn't open
is
wait wait wait I gotta be careful I'm
like so far I can't up now
foreign
[Music]
I'm really trying hard you know
you get so far and then you gotta do all
this over again oh
oh I'm focused
yeah it's just difficult with this mask
this this map specifically
trying my best to bait them
you know
should I let me get this one
[Music]
and
at least I have like a pattern of what
to do first
[Music]
Oh Canada Remember the Time Canadian
select some Cali so hard yes
yes I remember
[Music]
I'm still having a fun though I just
gotta I feel bad for you guys when I
have to do this over and over and over
again
foreign
you see me I know you see me
oh I took in my moldens to realize
I wasn't just some tiger plushie
I'm real come here
[Music]
okay
let's bait some more come here come here
hello no
[Music]
all right
came really close to me
oh yeah
as long as the funny sounds keep coming
you're having fun okay oh second dog
oh thank God thank God
okay his his daddy
you should have kept them on a leash
this wouldn't have happened huh
all right all right
[Music]
keep your dog go on the leash
done
and I've gone Knife Guy
this one I'll keep for later let's do
the corner oh now the closer one has a
gun that might be a good thing honestly
hi
just gotta hope that the top ones don't
have a gun like they seem to sometimes
switch the weapons out depending on the
reload
so this might be good
um
no can he still have the gun
[Music]
if I walk over when he's doing the this
this turn or I try again to bake
hi oh yeah
[Music]
okay now these are two up there are
difficult though because there's like so
much space where they can just I have to
bait them somehow
[Music]
I guess from that side this may be
better I don't know let me try this
silence first
I don't think he'll he'll oh okay
[Music]
yeah come here get come up here again
okay
okay but this one has a gun I'm pretty
sure that one has a gun and he will see
me even if he faces that way that's the
last one though
uh
yeah I know he has because he shot me
before
[Music]
well
I just wanted to move the door away and
hide around the corner
wow this is so difficult
ah
Maji Musa
[Music]
oh my God
now
I wanted to be
assertive and aggressive
I definitely am
oh man
[Music]
yeah I just need the last one this is
the last one
he's making me trouble
[Music]
why
a dog
he did oh he wasn't okay
[Music]
from here it doesn't see me
let's try to bait him oh okay that's
good maybe so we don't have to like do
this all at the very end okay okay okay
okay now I think now I think I can do it
that was a good baitanji
another dog coming
[Music]
let's go dog
yes okay now
look at the rainbow item rainbow
[Music]
what rainbow item I don't really how do
you mean this world thing
let's go I'll Focus I don't want to
up again
oh baby a double
[Music]
um
yeah I can't use guns
okay though
I like this challenge so no one's out
there anymore right I can go freely over
here
[Music]
now don't forget there's someone with a
gun up there probably
and I can't
[Music]
oh
next one next one please
one after another okay and next one oh
okay I gotta go to the dog okay
I have the routine and but no poutine
[Music]
sounds so disgusting but Elena told me
reminded me I guess because I surely
heard it before it is just a like like
fried fried french fries not fried
french fries with something
fries of gravy see that's not so bad I
honestly had that like yesterday
[Music]
because I made um
oven oven
uh baked roasted chicken I made roasted
chicken legs
uh limbs
[Music]
uh we'll be out with some fries because
it was supposed to be mashed potatoes
but like I'm not gonna spend an hour
making mashed potatoes when it's in the
end the same potatoes
but it uh I made a lot of like
actually I guess it wasn't really gravy
it was more like balsamico sauce but it
was really good it was a kind of a
sweet-ish
I die dog
come here guys
I don't got all day
hey
why don't they see me
this is just like in the great Wanderer
[Music]
witness me ah not like that
witnessing me witness me before I kill
you
not the other way around
no man
we're getting so good at this though
[Music]
I'm here oh thank you
what
my hips are just the wrong timing I
guess
[Music]
you little
I live by fry I live again I will die
shiny and Chrome on the Fury Road for
immortan piano wow you are a little bit
too much into this you make me sound
like I'm the leader of a cult
hey
but okay I like the motivation keep it
up keep it up
I don't like that
come on come on no not again sorry sorry
yeah
that's how it's supposed to go
I'm so sorry guys
I'm so sorry
man
[Music]
no more
a very German
Austrian classic way of swearing
[Music]
sites no more
you
yeah but they're into
all right
all right is this what I'm gonna be
doing all streams this level
oh
I just
[Music]
yeah
just wearing like an Austrian sailor not
just any sailor
[Music]
Kiana order can I change it don't I have
to redo the whole level
[Music]
I'm landlocked through but I can be a
sailor on a lake too okay there's some
big lakes in Austria beautiful
lakes okay surrounded by beautiful
mountains
[Music]
of course we have sailors
this was the door
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah I just wanted to try and stepping
one foot out of that door
[Music]
backed up to slow
foreign
logical solid arguments extra lie
otherwise I have to press like rewind or
eject or
you is a rewind
[Music]
okay oh man yeah
but we were so close literally so we
were we had it
who the needs a roll Dodge
I don't even know
I don't know who needs that you don't
[Music]
um
the last guy
I know I don't want to be in zebra
[Music]
oh he heard it but the others don't care
what
[Music]
somebody explained that to me
oh this whole room
oh my God
[Music]
well I don't know I don't even know
anymore how to use a gun I don't know
how to use a gun anymore
I really don't
I want to use melee weapons
pull the trigger point and shoot
you know
love me some tone joke
[Music]
okay
I saw you coming
whoa
whoa okay okay okay let's switch to the
shotgun that's a shotgun right
um I'm gonna go through I suppose
checking checking oh okay
okay
room empty then
[Music]
uh
okay
somebody there
guns are just ranged
rolling on their corpse yeah it's like
teabagging but move a little bit more
Style
doing something actually cool
um
okay okay okay I thought he would join
him
[Music]
okay shut his brain that oh
why at the very end this is like so
classic man of course it's Gotta Be The
End where's my weapon
okay I'll take this one
I'll take it I'll take it
timing with it no
no
[Music]
I didn't think so many would
come here oh my God
oh
are we done no
this shot must work now yeah okay I only
had one left that's right man ah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
oh
[Music]
you were doing better with Tony no I got
it into the groove
you have to consider that
I don't know I'll get there I'm fine
[Music]
okay see I'm fine I'm fine I'm just fine
ah wait wasn't this the room that would
end does it end early if I find the
right person
why is it not I don't know
[Music]
no okay
no okay I guess I gotta kill everybody
as per usual
fun
what's left up there huh
what else was I in what else was there
anything else I wanted to say about
about Canada Oh Canada
I'm just happy how it went it was fun
I should have picked up a new gun
oh well
and yeah I don't think I am at any event
soon
but
um yeah let's see if you have time to
visit no of course not I did it from
home in in one way it's um of course
like oh oh
it's really convenient to be able to be
at any convention all over the world
comfortably from home but at the same
time
it's also you know oh out of ammo
also
like sad because I don't actually get to
go to the places except for honestly
dokomi was actually
cool because they ah again
they did
pay me to
actually
oh
to go to Germany I mean Germany is not
so far but still you know they paid for
accommodation and stuff no and for my
staff not only for me
yeah but that was the only time I think
I I thought hey why does the knife miss
the dog is it just timing or am I doing
or is it just immune
hmm
[Music]
does it fly over his hair like it oh
can't no too low on the ground then why
does he not just aim lower it's not that
difficult
[Music]
okay
why did you run
why do you run away
oh dog
okay
yeah this this is honestly obviously so
much easier mom mommy yeah
but I'm proud of how far we came in
doing it my way
very proud can I get him from here
[Music]
I was so focused ah man
I feel like I'm doing great today I'm
just not
being treated fairly by the game
[Music]
it was still it was still
don't blame me
I can't read too
the person present calls me
[Music]
yeah I'm doing good I won't let you tell
me otherwise
[Music]
dum dum dum
okay
[Music]
oh yeah you better go away because my
shotgun is so loud it's gonna call all
of these over here isn't it
[Music]
oh
okay now I'm pretty much done with my
ammo so give me a break please thank you
oh we could get the shot now
yay okay
okay
all right I'm I'm red oh they're
dangerous I almost just walked over
there
[Music]
why is that one shiny yes I guess I
guess shiny it's just like some weird
dirt on the ground
smooth sailing from here yeah
[Music]
oh
where is he where did he go I can't see
him
oh
he's so far
going to the middle yeah let's go to the
middle
stay in the middle
thank you
okay that's good
[Music]
um also actually I'm surprised that was
the first uh panel I ever did with Lena
I don't know why we haven't been invited
to do a Duo panel before
shot until the dark and got some peeps
how much more oh
if
oh
get her oh oh There ah
no scope baby oh that's what they call
no scope let's go
as a Canadian Cafe America I'm not
complaining oh my God they're like the
perfect person to oh
to see us at the convention
you are this is literally for you
hey back
whoa take it easy there I'm just here to
get you your brother Santas we're not
going to harm you my brother
he's killed all my friends
look we've got a car waiting outside to
drop the gun it's time to go we'll drop
you off at your brothers
come with you are you insane you
murdered my friends you're not taking me
anywhere now leave me the alone or
I swear fine you have it your way and
we're out of here all right what if I
should turn now can I
I failed a mission let's I guess not do
it I guess
lady doesn't want to be rescued by mass
murderer zebra okay I don't honestly
understand it but to each their own
if she thinks she's better off without
me okay go rot in hell I suppose
ah finally we did we're done with that
level
yeah yeah D plus wow Improvement
oh we got the Alex and Ash mask okay
get on anytime soon this isn't a good
time to be messing around sorry I was
having fun with your mask
excuse me
[Music]
if a cop came by sauce like this
uh it ain't gonna go faster with you
bitching okay besides I've been telling
you to get the van fixed for weeks now
all right I still don't see why that
would be my job it's not my van
just do it you're the only one
of us who ain't busy with work all day
take it down to any about The Chop Shop
he owes me one
fine just get the car running and I'll
do it tomorrow okay
there that should do it they start try
setting up and let's get the hell out of
here
you know what I would have liked to do
at the convention though I made a great
we didn't get to do a meet and greet
this time
so it felt like kind of incomplete I
wanted to meet all of you guys
[Music]
[Applause]
man would have liked to talk to you guys
it's been a while
hmm
I think I think our team probably
suggested it I think we always suggest
it
yeah but you know there's reasons why
conventions might not want to do it you
know so that's fine it's just sad I
wanted to talk to you
[Music]
when was the last wow I mean agreed I
don't remember
last year I don't even know if we had
one this year
oh yeah
what's the matter you look a little
nervous
well boss
something you need to say just say it
look we've known each other uh for a
long time now but you've done a lot for
me
no need to be polite out to the point uh
cut to the point I can't read this font
sometimes
all right I want out I don't know what
accents I'm supposed to do who
is this guy
what kind of voice would you think he
would do and my Boston oh when was Anime
Boston
they're Russians
Russian I'm getting to God for this
but it also sounds entirely and when I
speak like this oh I'm failing too
soft
too strong too soft for what
shooting people putting my ass on the
line I've had the feeling I'm not gonna
last much longer for a while now
I've been having these dreams
well something something
like Nico and Roman yeah I know
somewhere there
is she also rushing them
dreams huh you want that you're out but
first you have to take care of some
business for me okay what business
nothing being a chop shop downtown
Northwest 42nd Ave there with the
Colombians now won't give us our cut no
more don't worry they're just what who
Looms nothing you can't handle
it didn't about
yes though you're afraid to come back a
French now no not French was nice thing
about today oh my God
thank you hello did you have fun at the
convention
yay
don't you afraid to come back anytime
you change your mind as a party gift
grab a sample and now I'm definitely the
footage
Japanese food energy
of our new product here it might spice
up this new boring lifestyle you've
chosen you know I'm French now now that
was kind of on purpose because you guys
told me
maybe I should do a hafu accent
part Japanese import something
about Japanese and part Italian I wonder
how that would sound wow what a car
which one's mine this one
I want the other one I mean
accent shifting
can't control it so
we have no mask we just we just
ourselves but there's a freaking
skateboard what
and there's a lot of people walking
around there you expect me to just walk
in there and shoot oh my God
is there skateboard
what am I supposed to do with this
huh why are you why wouldn't why
wouldn't I keep the gun
it's got like a silencer this gun
doesn't it oh
okay let me out again
this one
oh
window okay okay wow
well it's 12 anyways oh I didn't
miss so far did I
mean
oh okay I missed once
um gotta be careful I'm careful go
careful
um
this one he's got a gun I know it you
can't fool me
if you oh
he's so he's running so fast I'm sure
yeah yeah he wants to get to me
shots for me
huh okay
and then I I should probably change
weapon that's okay though
shot into the nothingness I shoot into
the happiness
okay
window
oh
okay it takes like one shot to go
through the window
Ah that's unfortunate oh windows windows
are made
oh
[Music]
should better go back to Linux
I'm stupid I'm stupid
[Music]
ah
at least finally we have a freaking
silencer that's like the first time no
okay
yes
I missed one shot though didn't I
[Music]
does Austria have a Navy I don't know do
we
huh
actually I don't know
maybe not we have like a military though
we probably don't have a Navy
okay
for what oceans again though we have
lakes okay but and we might want to help
other countries but you know
Wonderland and you're in the country
yeah rub it into my face William
Sandy Golden Beach okay
man
this guy is too far for me honestly I I
should go from the other side
remember I only got two animals left ah
one
I meant one
which one gets it
[Music]
if someone yeah get something else gotta
get something else
what about this one but they will hear
these ones so
I will be heard
it's okay so
it's gonna be okay
[Music]
um
okay I think one left yes
locally here let's go oh left side
oh am I shooting people oh
oh that was I was very focused on the
on the cars excuse me
[Music]
one of them got a chain muscle cars are
they I don't know they don't really look
like muscle cars to me but what do I
know I'm only a certified muscle car
expert so what do I know should I try
shooting through the window there
see this time it actually got through
immediately and I got even the kill
ER
oh keep on coming keep them coming makes
it easier for me all right now I want
this one again
I wanted it I want him again
what the oh we got the back one did
it just get the bag like somebody in the
back
there we go
hmm
oh let's go
am I focused on him let's go from the
top
three shots free shots
oh what is that I'm like
what's with the all the way man there we
go
sniper Joe
six shotgun shots I'm scared to go
around the corner
um
okay oh okay hello
hmm
oh
there's still someone here
oh my God
wow
he was like oh look in the door
last one
yeah yeah where do we go
there
shot
are we leaving already that was kind of
short
the music I know
in my door and my car next what
honey
you
[Laughter]
okay
ah this is gonna yeah upset everybody oh
my God okay
[Music]
oh oh
so what
oh
[Music]
give me that give me that push
oh is that what are they doing with that
car
it's like connected to some shaky thing
what are they doing do you do you know
guys any car
mechanic experts
I'm getting a job done you think they're
spray painting it oh okay but what's
this like connection though
ah this is like a the color connection
and this is like a sprayer thingy
a compressor oh
[Music]
okay well that was easy actually I would
have liked a few more to join from the
bottom but okay okay okay
um
I really want to know if there's someone
left down here but I can't see that far
all right I'll go here okay don't walk
in by accident again
oh dog coming
I don't know what to shoot first ah okay
let's let's ah wait no
foreign
we dive together how romantic I
am okay calm down is this your cousin
tell him to get down
okay
my God
violence
is not the right option for dogs okay
[Music]
I don't know why we are supporting them
to be violent whoa nice oh I got them
from that room good night
oh
baby
oh they're coming uh
[Laughter]
once you run because I didn't I only had
one shot left and I was gonna miss it
hot probably
hmm
but he went like and I I was real I was
like with my feet I was running
hmm
and I keep running running and running
running and running running and I'm
running one and running running and
running running and running okay wait
in this context there's no disrespect
I want to sing Black Eyed Peas
Mommy
I shouldn't have wasted so much time
Oh I thought it was already dead should
have wasted so much time in in that one
level because my concentration is
already like leaving me
[Music]
okay
this doggo
seven time killing that's is that that
Panda's age right
oh
okay let me get the shotgun
for now
after I said ah Penta is five oh
what's seven
SEPTA
I don't hear that one much it's a rare
one I'm just too too good
no one heard that what if I shoot it and
I would have liked the color explosion
that would have been nice
hmm
blind sauce rice but no I'm not flying
Jaws
[Applause]
My Bullets go far baby
they're going to places are they going
for me oh yes they are okay okay I'm
ready
okay
now
amazing wow thank you
do we gotta go to bottom path
oh okay he saw me which is fine that's
fine I might want to get a different
weapon oh that's empty oh
free and these are all empty
[Music]
pretty okay
membership let's go
okay this room
it's really bonked the dog with the door
can you
I'm so sorry
[Music]
that they're not dead though I know
okay
all that went uh somewhat well so I'm
happy with that
that was also pretty well
hmm
efficient yeah
good run good run right out the window
and Destroy evidence
throw it out
no one will ever find it right right
right right I hope so
I want to try to get some of them
through the window at least a dog
would be nice but he is making such big
circles
okay well at least a good bait right
oh oh
okay okay
man I'm lucky
um
I apologize is there something I could
talk about I'm trying to focus on the
games I can't think of anything
um sure there's like talking topics
no wait what
um
sorry I keep on forgetting I saw someone
reminding me and I liked the comment uh
the the Tweet but um problem was I was I
think already lying in bed or so
how's it planning going for the
anniversary
um
good I guess I think I'm doing like only
two and a half uh challenges so to say
um but they're they're not going fine I
think
wait crucial moment crucial crucial
streaming on the weekend the coming
weekend of
maybe maybe I don't know if I can
difficult maybe in maybe a short one on
evening but I definitely wow that the
Rhythm definitely don't have time on for
a full like super long
seven eight hours
stream
thank you
ah come on guys oh
that's not fair
today we had this the famous triangle
going
door MVP
you see is that the next book will be it
will definitely be like please don't
expect too much from me next week uh
it'll be a a week of
um
well me doing stuff but you guys only
seeing it later problem
haunted creation weekend
oh oh I went swimming the other day
again right and um like two or three
days ago
and I tried you know I bought myself the
like a swimming swimming goggles
um
and I tried to
[Music]
oh I tried to improve my swimming
because I read that
you're not when you do the normal like
froggy style swimming
whatever you call it
um
when you move both arms like
simultaneously that one
dad you automatically like a lot of
people will keep their head above the
water all the time normally and that's
actually not good for your back they say
so you should actually like have your
your head pointing downwards into the
water so that's why I bought the goggles
and I was trying to do that but oh my
God it's so difficult I saw people do it
in in the pool
I saw people
um
uh do the
show
that swimming style properly I guess how
it's supposed to be done
and I I tried to mimic it but like I
every time I try to go into
into the water to get some uh no out of
the water I guess to get some air I
Can't Get Enough air and and uh it's
like too fast people do it so fast
that's not like the the right speed for
me
like the way they do it
the breaths they take are like I guess
really short and
I don't know
it looks difficult and it is difficult
and and then and the water like kept on
going to my mouth and my nose and
everything was going up and down up and
down on the water over water
and I just felt so stupid
um being the only one seemingly not
knowing what the they're doing
yeah
yeah yeah I tried that or like at least
holding my breath doing it but
I don't know no matter how I tried it
just seemed very inefficient and just
didn't work out so well
okay dogs really don't get affected by
that at home
doggo
uh-oh
no I'm so done yet
props for trying I draw I'm not
still I want to learn the one properly
where you don't move your arms
simultaneously where you go like one arm
in a circle the other arm in the circle
I don't know what it's called man
freestyle I guess yeah
I tried that uh oops I forgot about you
I tried that swimming style
um
backwards though
I could do the arm movement backwards
which is also a legit swimming style as
far as I know
the backstroke yeah I was kind I think I
was doing I think I was doing it
correctly I think I think so
no
yeah I'm bad at this today today's not
my day
today is now my day
nice shot though nice shot
nice double shot
so done with this stuff
okay
Bring it on Bring It On who's coming
hmm
anyone else
you remember my first Hotline Miami
streamed that was something else
[Music]
um
yeah anyway so swimming was rough but I
didn't do my best and then and then you
know what I freaking forgot my swimsuit
there
I can't believe it I was I knew when I
left I was like hmm I feel like I'm
missing something I feel like
I feel like I'm missing something what
is it and then hours later I realized
my swimsuit
I want if I can get it back because it's
my favorite one
um it's like kind of the one I bought
for swimming as a workout because
um it covers a lot of my body so that I
don't have to you know put sunscreen if
I have to do that
like you know I just I'm
not to do a workout so it's like a it's
one of those Speedo
brand swimsuits but the whole back is
also covered oh YouTube we're back oh I
was just talking about my swimsuit I was
describing my swimsuit you telling me
you didn't get that
you're telling me you missed my swimsuit
description
that's too bad really
got it in the shower
um
like I went into the shower and I saw
okay okay uh these people are getting
really naked these girls these ladies
so they're they're taking off their
clothes to shower okay so I took my
swimsuit off and I hung it up
and then I forgot about it I didn't
forget about my towel but I forgot about
my freaking swimsuit
ah
well yeah I like that swimsuit because
it's it's like my swimming swimsuit not
my vacation swimsuit it's my swimming
swim soon
I want it back I wonder if I can get a
bag
wow this room can we bait them all
they don't see me over the table
[Music]
let's go
dude
okay
oh can we do it finally
let's go and I think only this room left
and then there's some guy ooh taking
cash out of a safe down there
oh
wait wait
[Music]
I wouldn't think theft is common in
Austria well no
that that one made me nervous
okay and now do we kill him or do we
talk to him
okay all right can I take the money get
the bag I got the bag
[Music]
yeah yeah I wanna I wanna call them do
you have my swimsuit or did you throw it
away
otherwise I gotta buy a new one I guess
I don't wanna go swimming before I have
so many swimsuits man and bikinis
but I don't wanna
where's my car
that's not the way
[Music]
I know it's not the one
the way use the cash to buy more
swimsuits
uh
huh this arrow goes there this arrow
goes dead what
Where's My Car huh
up
oh yeah
what was it with the skateboard though
what
was that about in the end oh God this
guy's so freaky looking man
Mama performs the concert in her
swimsuit and loses it no no no it's
don't worry it's not the swim the whole
life summer swimsuit it's my swimming
swimsuit oh it's been so fun
I just feel more comfortable in that
swimsuit because yeah it covers
basically everything except my arms and
my legs it even covers like my neck
pretty much
and there's like
um a zip that I pull all the way up with
like a string
like a surfer wet so it's kind of like
that yeah I was looking for like a
swimsuit that covers as much as possible
so that I use less sunscreen and then I
don't look so naked yet not quite a
turtleneck but
the the color is definitely
covered good for actually yeah yeah it
like literally it looks like like what
somebody would wear who's serious about
swimming
Olympic stats
no it's not like a Japanese school
mizugi no no
sounds almost like a scuba diver suit
yeah I look like a swimmer in it
[Music]
how would he speak whoa who the hell
yeah who the hell are you
well they're both so bald
thought you could get delay huh
get away I just woke you who are you
you're freaking me out man
it's your lucky day today kid this bag
which is safe this bag here just saved
you left I'm getting out of here you
should probably do the same now out of
my way
out of my mind
[Music]
we leave this mess behind
well yeah
oh a b c d yeah we improved we keep on
improving let's go
uh is this story because I think I
actually will have to cut it off soon if
I want to read some supercharge
hi honey oh welcome home I made your
dinner it's in the fridge
I'll eat it later I'm not that hungry
right now
oh you had a rough day
I quit my job
you quit your job just like that and
your boss just let you know
can you do something about the door it's
like bothering me it goes like
look I'm standing here because it's
comfortable okay so speaking of which
I've got Surplus for you but what what
is that
you'll see tomorrow okay I am feeling a
bit too tired right now I'm gonna head
straight for bed are you gonna stay up
for a while
I'm just gonna finish this shower
um you know the Kardashians are like
so so funny
I wish I was one of them oh
is this like golden stuff that I stole
look at my guns is it a cat
oh really fluffy thick one Cavite oh my
God oh my gosh
[Laughter]
you know I'm alive wait I'm gonna be
done I'm a lifeguard I'm gonna also
trained swim instructor assistant taught
many how to swim happy you finally want
to put your head into the water after we
had the swim cap debate a month ago I
still won't wear the swim cap though but
everybody was so serious at the pool
like a lot of them were wearing swim
caps and everything
yo people were so serious
people had their water bottles on the
side of the pool
that's how serious they were
and they were so fast swimmers I really
wish somebody could have taught me how
to do the freestyle I'm too shy to ask
man they're all like and also focused on
getting their workout in
you're allowed in the pool without a
swim cup yeah I saw a couple yeah as
long the only thing they asked you to do
is shower
beforehand hmm
I'm losing so much money oh don't worry
about it
somebody behind me is picking it all up
the chickens are picking it up
you listen oh
you're listening to well Miami radio
bringing you fresh new music each day
what do you like whenever you like
that's our motto it's a beautiful day
today the Sun's shining and the sky is
clear you can't go wrong with weather
like this yes that's for sure later
today we'll be premiering a hot new
single from takanasi Kiana pineapple
from her newest album point of view
we interrupted the broadcast for an
emergency weather report a tropical
storm is heading towards Florida coming
from the Atlantic it's estimated to
reach Miami by 7 PM we caution all
residents tubes
funky chicken
dinner nice
where are we going
I'm going away far away anyway it
doesn't matter to me
are you sure do you even know where
you're heading
without directions a lot of people wind
up going round in circles
and there's Roblox and looks too
promising
I didn't ask you for your opinion
what if I told you that this is this
road leads to Nowhere or rather that
you're heading for a bookmark and uh
oopsie you're closing in on it closing
in faster
but you already know that don't you
have no idea what you're booking about
we'll see you soon enough
by the bunk did you forget to bring your
girlfriend
no that was on purpose I don't want her
I'm not sharing this with her she's
better off of me anyway without me
anyway I mean
me Mary
it's like a Marco Polo
[Music]
oh man oh man no
no
hi honey I'm so sorry about this you
would have done the same thing if you
were Me Love
bye honey
she took the money
I guess in my dream I proved that
I would have done the same thing so
what now
he's just shaking his head okay
what age scene execution execution
now we have to stop here can I just
close the game or how does this work
I was reminded by the radio
funny thing
the MC you know I told the the panel
people beforehand that they should try
because I've seen this happened before
when people go in like a lot of people
will just sit like if there's a path in
the middle they'll just sit like closer
to the path they won't go all the way in
a lot of them and then people will be in
like two
um
so I don't know lazy shy or not don't
want to be bothered
uh to go like through and fill up all
the empty scenes so I told them
beforehand oh called out did they call
you out but I told them so that you know
and everybody can get a freaking seat uh
to maybe make sure to tell them to sit
uh closer to the walls first not closer
to the path go inside fill all the
scenes you know and because I said that
they were making an effort to fill the
seeds properly and then he was like this
MC guy he was like doing almost like an
auction he was like uh we've got we've
got uh two seats in the front row
[Music]
another God
yeah it was like an auction it's funny
can't walk around outside this one it
was like the seats were like two rows
in the middle there was a path and on
the sides it was just walls so I thought
you know you gotta be smart with
um
getting everybody to their seats in this
situation yeah
you're missing out on that character and
I don't have time unless it's just
another little bit of a story I can do
it but if it's like more fighting
my day is short today unfortunately
oh we'll play more next time
yeah I thought that that might be
a full level
because it just announced that I was
moving on to the next scene so
ah sorry today is short because no time
it is one of these but at least I'm
screaming at least you know I could have
said that's it that's all I'm doing
today my job here is done I'm just doing
convention
[Music]
but it was a fun day combined with the
convention kind of felt like a short
thing though
[Music]
probably because I got up so late
tomorrow Monday oh you know what you
know what you know what we'll do it
before I forget it I'll upload
if you want I'll upload the wallpaper
now
a song playing in the menu's paper for
meditating you want to meditate now you
feel like meditate I guess after playing
Hotline Miami you need some meditation
[Music]
it's good for your heart after so many
screams
oh my God
the violence is a meditation no
for nothing
if you guys want to stay for super drag
reading you're always welcome it won't
be too long this time I just gotta
wait never mind about the wallpaper my
brain is too Port right now to actually
find out where it is
let's go here
into my girl's room
[Music]
I don't think I'll keep this music on
though this one I don't like this one so
much on long term
oh I'll do the one paper after the
stream I promise I promise I promise
[Music]
it's kind of gloomy
um what should we have instead
thank you for your stream thank you for
watching even though it was short thank
you
and thank you also to everybody who came
to watch right after the convention
[Music]
this is my GTA music that I downloaded
just in case
it is also kind of like like I don't
know it feels dragging
oh yeah
oh
I love music like this like those and
um those tracks where they use like a
little bit of anime phrases like
um I don't know
you sound like these
[Music]
one's so cute
bubbly just like me
bubble
okay super chance last time
um ah I had to cut it off in the middle
of one
[Music]
um
yeah the Baldur's Gate ones I think if I
know where guys
[Music]
oh do I was just 71
no 56
ah okay
oh this is so cute
[Music]
thanks guys
for reminding me
hey hey
oh
wow why why must it be why must it be so
much of a gap
foreign
[Music]
vibes from this
hey
[Music]
guys
I don't want next week to start because
I'm feeling like I still have so many
things that I've been ignoring so many
obligations
too late it is next week no not yet in
my world my country
not yet
[Music]
it's just annoying things man you know
40 minutes oh hey Carlos you're here so
then listen to me reading your super
chat then
but can I ask
Ed your profile picture
what is that because it reminds me a
little bit of some German TV show mascot
the mouse
but it has like something in its face
oh
for cheetah from chainsaw man okay
that's not what I thought it was at all
[Music]
wait let me Google that okay okay but
this thing
pochita from chainsaw man doesn't it
look like
um
the mouse from descendo Mouse instead of
a chainsaw in its face
can you look up everybody can you look
this up really quickly
oh my God this is like
somebody tried to mutilate this innocent
children's TV show Mouse
by ramming a chainsaw into its face
[Laughter]
it looks exactly like it oh it's just
missing the ears
the color is the same
[Music]
and the eyes
anyway okay hi
hi I don't do soup as often but I wanted
to thank you seriously for all the
amazing content you're delivering the
contest album holiday when still
streaming for us daily I truly do feel
appreciate your hard work and I'm proud
of you might watch the anime
oh my God I love you oh thank you
you're so sweet
thank you I'm happy to be your Aussie
thank you for supporting me
[Music]
happy to hear from you don't worry about
not doing super chat often that's
totally fine but thank you for being
generous
and sharing some of your wealth with me
thank you
hope you'll continue supporting me
[Music]
me too
um so
satisfying
shonkers just like it's so easy to make
her purr you just have to look at her or
touch her and then she immediately purrs
smoothie is a you know only only when
she's really in the mood
but when they pair it makes me so happy
because then I I know that they're happy
to
meow you're so sweet
it's just so satisfying to hear
sometimes I pick up smoothie and you
know she doesn't really like being
carried or picked up but there's a
certain position when like when I hold
her like that she will set uh she will
like
be okay with being carried a little bit
and then she starts purring while I'm
carrying her sometimes and that really
surprises me
yeah over my shoulder yeah
mine don't like being picked up either
yeah I think you told me before man
why why
[Music]
I need it I need to get another kitten
and raise it and fix whatever I did that
made my cats not like being
um
held or or or like being on my on my lap
for example because chunkers and
smoothie day like being on my lap or
wherever on my body when they were
kittens they would sit on me
[Music]
and then they stopped and I was hoping
they would just do it again later when
they got older but so far no
[Music]
I don't have a name and I I'm saying I
would love to have another cat but I
don't think I would do it anytime soon
realistically because I I feel like it's
already like I got my hands full of
these cats because they're so needy and
I'm so needy too towards them
hey yeah I already have yeah my hands
full with them
[Music]
and even though I cuddle them like so
much per day each day and give them so
much attention I still feel like I'm not
giving them enough attention I still
feel like I need to show them more that
I love them I need to make sure they
know every freaking day
um
and and also a lot it's difficult to
maintain like some fairness a good
balance so that tonkers doesn't get
jealous it's movie this movie doesn't
really get jealous I think but I think
jonkers has potential to get jealous so
I need to balance it too
love everybody the same way
ah
I need them to absorb my love
thank God my cat is a Loof oh she
doesn't like notice anything
[Music]
we know you love them equally do I I do
I do but my hands often go towards
moving naturally because she's just
softer you know I can't help it but but
that's moving it eludes me more often
just yeah
she's a bit more like she does whatever
she wants what chunkers she won't always
be my by my side
she'll like be kind of weird about it
sometimes
no but she'll always be there so
I love my cat so much they cut the life
can get complicated yes yes yes yes
they give me so much happiness though
like even when I'm on an idol meeting
and I'm on an idle meeting they just
like Zoom around my my feet my legs they
like rub against my legs and um
and then chakras will just sit right
next to me on the height of my butt and
look at me and I'm like are you sure you
want to be so close
and she just chooses to sit right for me
I don't know she's she's just so she
needs to be close to me at all times
[Music]
sometimes they watch me when I shower
which is cute
they will stay and they will stay in the
same room
while I shower
sometimes they don't care sometimes they
leave but sometimes they stay when I
shower
[Music]
and when I eat breakfast on my break on
my on my big dinner table they will sit
on the table and watch it watch me and
wait for me
I'm so sweet I love them
guarding me guarding me from fires
anyways second time thank you
certainly thank you soon
thank you for the pink for the rest of
the chat I want to say you did amazing
in Splash party I really love the live
version of totally dance and the usakan
performance was so great you make MC
sections so much fun too you've worked
so hard this summer I'm proud of you
also chocolate
thank you I did work hard
[Music]
I gave myself extra work too by making
an album
[Music]
pineapple uh chorus dance
shorts I will upload it one of the
coming days where I'm not streaming
I still have to figure out my schedule
for next week I don't really know I
think I'll make a schedule but I'm like
right now I'm like really not aware of
when I can stream
but I have this dance shorts and and I
also have like still some other uh
videos from chegey
in my
backlog that I could upload
um
[Music]
stream tomorrow or not I don't know I
want to take the day off but
[Music]
um
wait what
[Music]
what is this
where would I fly to
oh
you know you know I told you guys I'll
be doing like one challenge that's kind
of like flying related
and in my schedule for next week I I
blocked out like like a whole day
with like flying day
um and I was like what did I plan to fly
to another country
where am I going I forgot about it just
now I was like where am I going this
time why did I forget about it
where am I going no okay I'm not going
anywhere not really
[Music]
um
yeah I think I can at least stream on
Tuesday tomorrow
depends on how I feel
um
I think tomorrow will be mostly like me
trying to get my together and plan
some things yeah
I think that will be at least like free
streams okay
at least three
[Music]
tomorrow is Labor Day oh
uh I don't think is it a worldwide
holiday
[Music]
no need to commit to streaming I'll I'll
put it in as a maybe
hmm
[Music]
American U.S on Labor Day so on Labor
Day you don't do labor that's kind of
like
contradicting
shouldn't you be laboring on Labor Day
yeah
call it free day not Labor Day and Thai
Labor Day
[Music]
babies cannot be born tomorrow what
well surely there's someone working in
the hospital right
[Music]
oh going in labor oh my God you're funny
wait it took me a moment
going to labor oh it didn't even take me
uh
we're in the chat to figure it out
ah
you're making a joke right
it's illegal to be born tomorrow you're
just gonna
it'll be shushed if you were
accidentally born tomorrow they will
like
fake the paperwork and make your
birthday tomorrow instead
foreign
[Music]
why'd you have to choose Labor
Day Labor Day doesn't mean that you
should go in labor today it means no
labor today
apparently
back inside of you
oh sorry misunderstanding I thought it
meant I have to go out today
[Music]
is Kiana okay no
no
okay Mundo thank you that was such an
unrelated tangent but thank you Buddha
breakfast
[Music]
uh Nathan cotton thank you for the pinky
would you eat us to make you stronger
too I'd happily sacrifice my neck
I don't want your neck I don't think
there's any meat on your neck
[Music]
can I can you sacrifice your your tummy
I'll take your tummy
and then I'll blow on it like
[Music]
you're like a baby okay baby yeah
raspberry I had raspberry pancakes today
again
hmm
[Music]
it's a delicacy in Asian countries
chicken neck I'm so sorry but
you guys have so many Delicacies over
there that sound just no like like a big
no to me
no thank you
chicken necks are good nah hell no no
why why you no
chicken nuggets instead
[Music]
The Leftovers of chicken we can use to
feed more chickens
[Music]
she cannot excuse me
what are McDonald's chicken oh chicken
nuggets made of
as of August 1st 2016 2016 the
ingredients within the United States
are as follows white boneless chicken
uh water salt seasonings
yeah well I mean I guess they just
probably use the whole chicken and mash
it up I guess but
um
ah make chicken nuggets chicken
McNuggets are made of parts of chicken
breasts tenderloins and rib meat
it says so here there's no chicken neck
in there
music is rotting your brain
okay okay okay okay
okay okay no no no no no no no no
no no no
another
there's another source that says
contrary to popular belief McDonald's
chicken nuggets are made from 100
chicken breast meat
no well you know what with a company
that big I kind of believe it because
they surely get like checks a lot from
whatever like hygienic hygiene check
company or so
don't you think that they have to keep
up all like those especially when it
comes to food they can see what they do
no
look at chicken nuggets getting made
suddenly revolting
foreign
here's some Persona jazz
this is also brain melting I think
though
pink slime
and in Europe they have to be one of
those what do you mean what is that
so in Europe they have to be chicken
breasts okay it seems like something is
like banned um
honest
do I Wanna Know
oh I'm Googling something
[Music]
um
what
what I don't understand
ammonia treated lean beef trimmings
ah
edible meat parts that stick to the Bone
but can't be stripped by a knife are
recovered by mechanical Mains and turned
into a substance that can be for burgers
and plop chicken products at lower cost
oh my God I'm so sorry to all the
vegetarians in here right now
all this talk is like probably like even
to me like getting more into the details
is disgusting to me too
yeah
I wonder if like fauna has me muted on
Twitter because of all the food that I
cook uh posting on Twitter
sometimes I wonder if fauna might have
me muted
I gotta ask her sometime if it makes her
feel uncomfortable to just even see
pictures of meat
I wonder like I mean I I could
understand
she doesn't care I think so
fun has never replied to Kiara
coincidence I think not
hmm mysterious
she said she wants to fight you what
what about what meat
uh
I will lose
I'll honestly lose
anyway uh technical King
Brendan kitchen
um RV last dungeon
I don't know it depends are we last we
have to ask for permission for
um each game
if we want to use some kind of mod
and some Publishers or developers
outright uh say no reject it directly
others are I think more open it depends
on the mods too and then we have to also
ask the mod Creator yeah
generally
uh doing Moonlight thanks for Pinky and
when you just sent gave me flashbacks
about a certain girlfriend I haven't
seen in a while but since the game is
uninstalled I guess she's been suffering
in the void anyway you're amazing oh are
you referencing
um a certain game
I don't know what I said though I think
I remember saying something that could
remind you of that though but I don't
know what it was
what did I say
about NPCs being alive only for yeah
yeah
above that theory and it's terrifying
it's just terrifying
it's it's kind of um
it also reminds me of this Charmed
episode actually they did several
episodes like this
um let me tell you because I think the
concept is funny
um in in a couple of episodes two
episodes of three even they bring up
this like Doll House that of their own
house like a dollhouse version of their
own house that they have kept for
generations and
um in some episodes they get like stuck
in there that get like teleported in
miniature into that house and the other
sisters don't notice it and they look
for them and oh my God where is she and
eventually they get trapped in there all
of them and yeah they have to make their
way out but when they're in there their
powers also grow smaller or Shrink
smaller
so they had that and also there was
um there was an episode where
um they got that was pretty early on
they got stuck in a painting
because when you would look at the
painting uh uh this was when Bruce still
was around she would look at the
painting really closely because that was
kind of a job and then and she noticed
something was moving in the painting and
then eventually she kind of got like
sucked into it and the guy in the
painting was like actually like I don't
know he was in like some kind of haunted
painting for years for centuries uh
apparently so he claimed
and and there was like fire traps and
everything going on and they were trying
to yeah Dodge them this and that you
remember huh yeah
and there were a lot of these kind of
funny Concepts
yeah
those are neat focal points for episode
what is that main focal point
they get stuck in things so often
I wouldn't say it's an easy time
point of focus oh okay
now honestly it's amazing that they kept
on coming up with all these ideas for
like eight seasons wow
sometimes they would repeat them though
that was just like usually they would
come up with new demons for every
episode there was this one demon though
that they kept on bringing even
in season or the second to last season
it kind of pissed me off
he wasn't the first season and then
still kept on showing up it's like a
demon that
um
is is able to like pretty much kill you
um by using your own fears against you
and all he has to do is like show up in
front of you then like use his magic
Focus to get you dreaming about your
biggest fears and you're like paralyzed
in that moment and you can only Escape
if you fight your fears but but
basically what happens to you in this
dream of yours ends up happening in IRL
yeah and so if somebody has a fear of
drowning then the IRL they end up
drowning out of nowhere
uh stuff like that
you mean the actor was him I don't know
barbas yeah Barbers was the demon name
what what what's what's what what
yeah plenty quicker
yeah why are you guys bringing up a
Freddy Krueger
ready
terrifying why'd you make me
look that up
you why why what
does he do the same thing
it just kills you in your dreams oh you
no because Barbara's he doesn't join you
in your dream it just makes you do that
and then watches you suffer and they
brought him back so many times because
apparently he was just especially
efficient and especially strong
man
[Music]
he's a classic well I've heard of the
name before before yeah
but
that doesn't really look like something
I would voluntarily pick up to watch
it was such a jump every time for real
for real
and around the last season they they
just wanted like some kind of demon that
people already knew I guess
remember you you one person remember
when they were like in this like
avoids having a conference between good
and evil and
it was like a like a court scene in the
void and they had barbance there who was
obviously biased to speak up against the
charm sisters
proving why they are actually bad and to
be stripped of their powers making an
argument for the evil side but yeah it's
just like wait you revived this
character for this uh come on yeah they
kept on bringing him up because maybe he
was the only demon actor that felt like
um that felt up to the task and the the
pay
that they were giving him maybe the pay
was low and he was the only one who
accepted
man
Captain coming back
what is this from uh Charmed I'm talking
about Charmed
I want to talk so much about Chad but
you know the cool thing is
angels they oh my God they all love
charms
and and and and and
so they they are here for me when I want
to talk about it I was like I was
venting to them about season eight and
the ending and all that and then I cried
about it because I knew they would know
what I'm talking about and and they were
so
so up for it
uh let's go they get me they get me and
now I'm getting
um money to watch Wheel of Time because
she really likes these kind of fantasy
shows too we talked about
um Game of Thrones and we talked about
houses of dragons Etc yeah we're talking
about all the shows and and and yeah I
told her to watch
um like she asked me if I if she should
watch rings of power and I I told her
rings of power while you know even I
must say I wasn't like
like visually it's great
uh and if you don't care about you know
the story being like accurate
then whatever you might enjoy it but
even then even with all these points
there's still some iffy Parts but still
uh I don't know I feel like you know if
you just want something fantasy to watch
something in the world roughly up Lord
of the Rings then watch it that's what I
told her because that's what made me
happy enough to watch it too and she
said yeah yeah that's all I want you
know I didn't read anything either
and same for
um Wheel of Time I guess but I must say
like
yeah okay apparently both shows are not
accurate to the book
but I would say wait of time
did a decent job at being like its own
good thing you know what I mean
while rings of power was a bit like what
the
in certain points
I've been loving season one so far I
don't even remember if how much I liked
season one but season two the first
three episodes that are out now
are really good
and I need you guys to watch it so I can
talk about it
they're really good
and I loved when those evil people
showed up
because the design of their outfits is
crazy
and
um sorry maybe spoiler
um but you know there's this one really
evil guy I don't know is he deaf or so
the one that was going up against Rand
in the first season at the end
but he was like up there with like this
these uh two other ladies they they were
like the top three people apparently
um
and and
the middle one on the real frown she was
a lady and she had like her outfit her
headdress and everything it was like
covering her face and she looks really
mysterious I'm I'm excited to see her
face
at some point
I know the costume design is kind of
cool
it's covering their faces partially you
see only a little bit so you can sneak
into their faces you want us to organize
our own watch alongs he's not just watch
it on your own time whenever I don't
care
you think she'll be good I can uh 99
percent
telling you that she's cute
what this what this shot scene Sean Sean
Chan is that is that what they're called
they're messed up what do you mean
oh yeah yeah yeah oh my God if you
Google that the first picture that comes
up at least for me is those free people
and they look like they look so
threatening and freaky to me but I love
the like outfit designs and the color
theme
[Music]
damn but what's with the freaky young
girl that has like they they actually
make all all of their almost like a lot
of their female servants they make them
wear this like weird pacifier
I don't understand I don't like it
but yeah
the I don't know it's just really cool
the throne is so cool and and the outfit
wow I love the colors
man oh what is this oh yeah yeah
that's the that's the other one though
oh my God
yeah oh the nails though the nails I
hated the nails the nails freaked me out
like this leader Empress whatever of
evil
um her nails she's got like
two meter long nails that she like uses
like a whip to give commands
like she would look at something and she
would like whip twice with her
fingernails and then they know what to
do
so weird
they always
their fingernails
Nails you can see it in the screenshots
too the fingernails but they added this
sound effect like like a real whip like
I'm like wow wow then they are putting
so much focus on the fingernails
uh whipping fingernails
you know normally when you have
fingernails that long they should really
hurt
I think
they must be so annoying too
oh man okay I'm excited for more
I wonder is the next episodes coming
next week I wonder
okay I'm tanging into tangenting too
much but I wanted to talk to you guys
man
any Disney plus favorites ah
yeah I don't know I feel like I got
Disney plus to watch one show
specifically and then I was done and
then I was like what the do I watch
now the rest on Disney plus doesn't
really interest me
um
they only got some like some cute
sitcoms and that's pretty much it oh I
might have even only gotten it for
Family Guy
why does why does Disney Plus have
family guy anyway I would think that
Disney plus is trying to have family
friendly shows maybe they just read
Family Guy and they were like okay it
sounds family friendly let's add it
Disney owns box still I feel like it's
it's damaging their image
got family in the title oh yeah yeah
that must be family friendly they also
own Hulu well then why don't they have
all the Hulu shows on Disney plus yet
huh
[Music]
it's on Hulu in the US instead which
Disney also owned
and yeah okay yeah
I don't have to go to bed at midnight
okay
fine
that should be on Disney plus
there are other Hulu things on other
services in Canada
okay
um
why was I
oh okay I think I was here
um
you are great in this summer concerts
I'm glad you were getting chances to
dance and perform and that told his
first song was a big success yeah let's
go
Let's Go endless
I didn't know you were from New Zealand
let's go
thank you
for your sake I hope one day we get a
kiwi
holotomy kiwi bird told me
would be cute but um I say that but I
actually want to keep the numbers of
birds down I don't know why can't they
just like I don't know add other animals
like there's so many animals out there
that they haven't put into uh
a concept yet
why keep on adding Birds but okay
birds are very versatile I guess so
koala
YouTuber would be cute
yes
spider drop bear now
crocodile
[Music]
um
elephant
yeah okay see there's still so many
animals that we could do
pineapple YouTuber that's just me
that's just me though
[Music]
oh a snake between lisp so if somebody
wants to be a YouTuber who has a list
they should just get themselves a snake
design yeah that would be funny making
your traits into your design
implementing it
if Horton gets to nine members you can
be like the opening of Splash party
oh that's too many no
five is good five is good anyway thank
you endless
love for you sweet support
with message I appreciate it
[Music]
is
your performance was amazing last night
and heartily danced with such a hit to
think that it got 1 million views and
also on live performance as well in just
a week yeah
you girls were on a fire on fire a
standing ovation wouldn't be enough to
congratulate just how good you were oh
my God thank you but you know you guys
oh you guys are so sweet but more and
more it makes me think Whole30 dance
should have been a little bit longer
um
like maybe three minutes
no more than three minutes it's okay at
least three minutes
would have been nice would have been
nice
it's just too short
next one can be longer yes it must be
uh-huh
you could literally add another
verse and chorus to it
but you know it's perfectly loopable no
no
I was so close to asking the Toronto
people to do oratory dance
for us to stand up and show us their
moves
had to hold back
well thank you Francisco thank you for
supporting holotoni let's go I think you
guys are definitely
um helping to
how to stay
um
thanks to you it will be I think very
very very
possible and likely than totally will
get to do more stuff in the future
because you guys supported it so much
I think there will be more to come yeah
so thank you for that
now I don't know
I would say you know it's it's
definitely a good argument that it did
so well
I don't think that
it's
would be
you know anything but positively
influencing
the management
hey
let's go
downstairs
sorry but I just remembered since now I
think I'd like to ask her for advice on
how to teach the timkins how to use or
how bird in combat
they're small size is getting in the way
or maybe we should stick to Ariel dagger
combat only
shouldn't be using Albert and also Elder
Kiana doesn't know how to use a halberd
aggers generally sound good for you guys
I think yeah you already have one don't
you
what's an aerial dagger where's how is
that you mean just like throwing daggers
now I guess a mixture of throwing
daggers and just normal you know you can
do whatever one you want with the dagger
it's just a dagger I mean for me it's a
dagger for your size it's maybe even
more than a dagger but it still looks
kind of like a dagger
I don't know is it a dagger
cloud of daggers
why can't we just use guns because you
know if you're together with alter Kiara
it just makes no sense if you're using a
gun
people don't use guns in that universe
and that's
alternate
timeline
they're still sticking with
you know knives and
the toothpick hasn't Pike that's a
little bit too small
you're not that tiny
but I thought you came here
yeah but she's not here all the time you
guys
alternate chickens are there
waiting for her return whenever she's
here
can we use spares well yeah but like
small skill or skewer yeah yeah
can I use this as a mace
um excuse me did you just rip out your
arm or your leg
can you put it back
I just remembered I
I had a weird dream about a chicken last
night I just remembered
it was weird
that was so weird and also I was
carrying this movie around outside in
the street over my shoulder
and suddenly there was a chicken also oh
I just remember something was on fire
the building was on fire oh and my old
smile Edge or she
did um suddenly open the meet and greet
even though she's been retired for like
I don't know 15 years or so
I was so happy and I was like in her
presence in the same room
I was like oh my God I can't believe
she's here
we're so happy to see my old ocean
yeah because she was the first one to
graduate from her group her Idol group
it's mileage
and the first one it was like pretty
early after debut
and it was kind of sad because they were
doing so well and they had such Perfect
Chemistry
and I feel like they were like legendary
they were building something up that was
gonna last for a long time but then she
left and soon after another there were
four members
and they just fell apart
it was so unexpected
yeah now they're anger me and Judah mu
and uh there is I think now uh no OG
member in there anymore
and even their second generation members
are basically only like maybe one or two
or one one no even the last one I think
graduated recently so it's like really
not the same group anymore yeah
yeah they had so much potential uh it
was so um
unfortunate
I would like to live in the timeline
where they continued to stay together
for a few years longer
man it's so sad
cherish what you have while you have it
guys
that is what we must learn
from these situations
well
and so true
nah it's so sad though ah
carp up some things for the pinky
can't wait for the next week Wawa thanks
for thanks again for great stream today
and loved your performance at the
concert thank you the next week it was
this week right
was a fun week I tried to stream uh as
much as I could while combining you know
album promotion and all that I tried to
make the you know the first half of the
week kind of special
[Music]
I want to sing I wanna do more um album
karaoke but I can't just do another
album kind of okay maybe I'll do a
members only POV album karaoke
I just want to sing all the songs again
ah
but yeah
um it was a fun week yeah
finally the album is out it was really
exciting really exciting week but uh
kind of exhausting too mentally
So yeah thank you everybody for joining
me on that trip and thank you Evans owl
okay
um
[Music]
uh uh I'll try to do one more
and
[Music]
it's only to the side of my favorite
song
still didn't find one you know yesterday
I spent like an hour or more probably
one and a half hours even
um watching I looked up on and sorted it
by newest I looked up uh point of view
um and then I saw uh two
I think two full album reviews
and one pineapple review
and I don't know I just get really
curious so I watched them and the album
reviews they were so positive they were
um they were all like really
really sweet and especially this one guy
I sent it to Moni as well there's one
guy I had to comment because he was so
he was so so so hyped and excited and he
was like getting up during the Great
wandera
and
um like he already enjoyed pineapple and
then love brush but then with tgw he was
going crazy over it and he was like oh
this is the best this is it this is it
oh my God
but then but then comes red perspective
and he gets hit even harder and ah
yeah he was so cute
up and was dancing
he's so cute
[Music]
man
I'm happy that you know there's a song
in there for everybody
pineapple pizza
yummy yummy
what was his name uh if you look up
and
um
point of view album review
and then maybe sword find newest like by
uploads oh wait
[Music]
now now I no wait wait just just type in
a point of view
and then sword by
uploads
yeah
and Dylon
and I don't know what they were free
album reviews I watched all of them
that one was a pineapple okay no it was
two it was two
album reviews
yeah
and there's a new one now
I guess I gotta watch that one too
[Music]
yeah the channel is science senpai
yes
already in the form
yeah everybody's got their own point of
view they're sharing their point of view
funny
[Music]
I can't find it
okay if you really want to see it
[Music]
uh let me show you
he is so cute
makes me so happy
okay
um
big announcement Hollow cure uh stream
what do you mean please no
what is your problem
[Music]
I will read this
he's loving it right
you use it
it won't take long okay Patsy thanks for
two pinkies he can't something big just
happened and I want to share it with you
on kfp today I became a homeowner wait I
feel like I read this
my payment's all cleared and I have the
keys to my own apartment I'm looking
forward to all the new challenges that
await me oh my God it's also nearly my
birthday I'm sending this early to
account for your backlog but my birthday
is on oh my God
it's early you calculated correctly it's
tomorrow
oh
12th of September oh now it's today oh
my god oh hi hi cats chunky monkey
chunky monkey is saying happy birthday
two
say happy birthday to Patsy
see see
come on at least per
at least
you heard it right my payment oh wait no
month I thought it was still for me but
oh yeah okay it is midnight so okay it's
tomorrow okay oh it's up it's after all
uh tomorrow
she was yeah she was purring annoyingly
it'll be my third birthday with kfb and
it won't be the last if possible can you
sing me Happy Birthday I will I will if
you request it like that
um I won't think it's for everybody
because then I have to sing it a million
times you know but if it's a red one and
you ask for it
I still have chunky wonky on my
lap this is very good
hmm
I don't know if I can think of rhymes
[Music]
here's me and conquered
celebrating you
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your
pants too happy
you travel the world
from Germany to Japan
were you in America too
[Music]
I love you happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you or you were
everywhere
in your pants too
here since the beginning
here until the end
so dedicated
[Music]
try the chicken yeah
well there must be an end somewhere come
on
yes yes yes yes
hmm Pepsi thank you for being here for
so long and what
yeah I know you travel a lot
to see the Wawa and also you hear even
though you are one of those crazy
Australians who want to watch me live
I don't know how you do it but you do it
and I thank you for it so much
thanks mate bloody hellmate man you're
the best mate thank you to us again the
dedicated loyalist Aussie gang
you crazy
crikey man
thank you honestly means so much to me
thank you always being we're rabba
forever whenever my chicken will gather
whenever my Aussie chicken scabper
no country is too far
um
no country
uh they fear uh
um
and they are always near oh
whatever where wherever my Aussie
chicken scaven no country is too no
country do they fear yes they're always
near oh
Banger thank you Patsy happy birthday
and congratulations on the on the
homeowning noise
a connection
wait what when my birthday I said I need
now I need to pay more taxes
what is it your birthday I don't
understand
what I understand oh
I've been getting patches recently what
why did Tales of Symphonia switch
recently get patches that's so weird
um
with walk along s with red Super Chat
I'm celebrating my 13 th 39th birthday
oh normally I don't care for birthdays
but I figured this birthday was one
worth celebrating can you guess why
oh yes Miku ah
I just want to show some love to a very
special burp and a very special day
thank you so much WoW
I appreciate it well
I hope you did
something fun on that day and you know
what if it's your 39th birthday this
year you should you should go to some
like vocalo and concert or something I
hear
um yeah they do some cool stuff out
there there's just like Expo right in
Japan
Vocaloid related Expo and I think it
already happened now recently actually
but that sounds fun if you like Vocaloid
that much
yeah it just happened yeah I paid
attention to Vocaloid way more in the
early days
um I don't really keep up with it
anymore
I am magical midnight Expo that's the
one that I'm thinking of
oh yeah yes they also go to other
countries too
huh
wish I could have maybe next year maybe
another time maybe you now this year you
need to start planning so you can go to
it next year
I have a friend who always goes there
even when it's overseas
huh
there's Twisters on the planet yes I
hope you can make it work I hope you can
make your Vocaloid dreams come true
congratulations happy birthday
happy birthday to you I know that's not
the lyrics but
an oldie but Goldie
mwah dances with vocalists thank you
congratulations
oh I've heard of that one
but
I wouldn't go there I think if anything
rather than fantasy Basel I would just
go to like Comic Cons and you know it
works it worked out because I saw
Joffrey
at a Comic Con and spontaneously went to
meet and greet him and get a signature
so even though it wasn't planned at all
still can't believe that his autographed
picture is still
um right by my door entrance thingy
um on top of my my shoe shelf case
thingy
so I've gotten comments quite often from
people who go who enter my
apartment like my sister and she was
like what the
it's just straw free and I'm like yeah
yeah I'm at Joffrey
and I told him I told him
I told him to sign it as a takanasikiara
ah
Risa I haven't seen you in a few days
where were you girl
I was I was thinking of you yesterday or
so
and I was playing Baldur's Gate because
I found a weapon
that would be perfect for your bard
and Wisa it's so crazy oh my God I I've
I'm still so far from the cop I played
like 15 20 hours or so and I'm still so
far from the goblin Temple
I mean I could go there but I'm just I I
was trying to do other things anyway and
I didn't think I could do so many things
still oh my God
it's it's crazy how deep I got like
literally I I went so deep
did you find
because you spend a lot of time playing
on your own but did you ever find the
book
the Act One the special book where you
have to find the stone that fills in the
book to open it
do you know what I'm talking about
because if not then you missed out on
something cool
yeah
okay I heard from people that I like
they spent hours and hours playing so
much of this game and they still see new
things in my stream because I
I am like looking EV in every corner at
every I'm looking at even the the
most normal looking thing like books
that are blending into the scenery I'm
like opening them and reading this all
these books that give me a little side
quests that you wouldn't expect is crazy
but yeah there's a special book there's
a really special book it's basically
um the Necronomicon
and it's like really interesting that
whole Arc
and if I do a second flavor I want to be
more pharaoh isn't wouldn't that be your
third playful because you're doing one
with collab and one right now on your
own and then that would be your third
one
economicon
a second alone yeah
yeah honestly because you you if you
play alone anyway you can take all the
time you have in the world
my God there's so much I
I'm I'm also working on Carla's uh
sidequest
like her her story I guess every
character has their own
proper quest line I guess
so working on that is pretty cool too
hmm
oh yeah right maybe in your third play
for you could try playing as dark urge
to change it up a bit more
yeah things are heating up
that's so fun
yeah I was fighting like a big ass
teleporting spider
um I was like really scary had like 150
HP or so
and it's babies I was fighting it's
babies
you know anyway really cool
I killed a lot of big enemies
Giants
proud
dropped some gravity on them no I had
gravity drop on them
I guess
I wanna I wanna stream another solo
Baldur's Gate next week
collab next week but I feel like I won't
catch up to them anyway if I keep going
at this pace
won't catch up to our collab anyway so
um
yeah the tea house I want did you go to
the Tea House narissa
I was like aiming for the tea house last
time but then this one Village there was
just so much there on the ground I
couldn't get to the Tea House you did
okay I want to go to the tea house next
time
I don't know what there is but people
kept on saying Tea House Tea House Tea
House
don't smell it
[Applause]
[Music]
ah that will probably if things keep on
going like this I'll probably take up a
whole stream anyway
I need to get out of that underground
like I shouldn't be there right now I
think I'm I'm there a little bit too
early
foreign
[Music]
con huh
fun
Sir with a projector and big speakers oh
man Polo's amazing oh my God sounds like
fun you know
like a good time special convention
that's the one I was talking about
during holocaire
Wicked Tunes
Barbie movie you like that too yay thank
you
thank you oh my God I'm sure kiwawa's
Angels also love the Barbie movie
um
[Music]
I guess so yeah
wait what what do you mean John Cena is
related to Tina Fey and Emmy Amy Perler
their names are different
what do you mean
what it says here to be fair John Cena
is an amazing comedy actor and then in
Brackets see sisters with Tina Fey and
I'm Amy
what do you mean their sister what does
that mean
am I interpreting it wrong
oh it's a movie
see I knew something was wrong there
and
sisters
wait if it has Amy and it's a comedy
movie
want to watch it oh wait I might have
watched it toy strange sisters reunite
and throw a feral party to bid goodbye
to the family at home before the parents
sell it
um how new is this 2015.
no wait maybe I didn't see it I have to
check I have to watch a trailer
looks funny
is he like the dad or so in this movie
like he could play the Dead
um
will narissa visit Austria before the
Visa changes oh wait ah you mean wait
you remind me yeah that wasn't there
like something about European visas
changing
like anybody needs something because
until now like a lot of countries
like
America for example you can just enter
Austria without anything but yeah I
heard of that next year
I mean it shouldn't be too difficult
like if it's like a Visa like how I had
to get one in in Indonesia in Indonesia
I didn't have to apply for it beforehand
I just went there
and I paid a little bit of money in
there in cash and then they stamped my
passport if it's like that then it's not
difficult
um
yeah I don't know I've I've seen that
but
probably not too difficult for most
countries then to get our Visa I don't I
can't imagine them making it overly
complicated
because we do have so much tourism
obviously
yeah
it'll probably just be a simple thing
like where you sign up and you tell them
when you're coming and then it's fine
yeah but I maybe you have to pay a
little bit of a fee but I also have to
pay America fee when I go there although
I noticed it's like
um
like like once in
a year or two like there is actually
quite a big time frame that it covers I
just have to sign up again but I don't
have to pay again but that's nice
yeah it's what we have to do when we
visit America already so it's only fair
if we turn it around and you guys have
to sign up for something too when you
come to us
for years we've been paying you guys to
go to your place okay so now we turn it
around you oh me money
basically narissa you owe me money I
paid your country yeah several times
money to visit Yo and you guys are
probably not even aware of that and you
think it's a given that you can just
enter Europe for free those times are
over you're paying me money now directly
I will give you my bank account and if
you want that Visa you better send me
money directly
uh the quinoa attacks
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes my bank
account is the right account to pay that
yes
don't mind do you
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
not the Super chance
so what do you mean do you want to go
into the usual room um
some new candidates for the usual room
huh what usual from Wisconsin is
still there
I just don't have to over yes later
already right now it's very much still
there here
there you go giant Yahweh hands are
sending you to the usual room you know
it's even even worse now then if you say
there's the usual room then where did I
send you well to the void that's even
worse
yeah who knows stop
goodbye
hello darkness my old friend
I am here to come to see you again I
don't know the lyrics
ah
what uh
bottom thank you for Pinky Super Chat
action Violet
Empire
Scarlett thanks for the pinky high
tension I just tried to make kinotori in
Minecraft last month what do you mean
like the sounds
and I'm happy that you like it on
Twitter that time oh yeah I think I
remember something like that by the way
I saw some comments of my video said
that there's if there's a chance you may
sing it again with the video Source next
time
uh
uh wait
a habetic
what do I look up on YouTube
Hino totally Minecraft and your name
[Music]
this is insane
this is how do you even make this like
is there like something that automates
the process or are you actually like
doing all of this by hand because of yes
and that's absolutely insane
you guys did like you can even see the
blocks I think there you need to look at
this
it's by hand that's not
so cool
oh my
with the video though is like prop like
edited right like those lyrics you
didn't like find some way in Minecraft
to put lyrics like that
[Music]
how in how how insane do you have to be
to make this
my God
[Music]
this allow me to say again to make it
clear this is made in Minecraft
[Applause]
it sounds so proper it sounds like an
8-bit uh remix of hinotori
what do you mean you can make the lyrics
show up like this in a game
how
yeah those are not note blocks Minecraft
note blocks music by hand and the lyrics
by particles what the
what the
okay wait I will finish the super
chats from that stream and then I'll
sing it for you okay because I don't
know how many oh wait here's it says 150
to 200 hours
that doesn't even sound like enough oh
wait it does say
um
all right okay and that doesn't sound
like enough it sounds like this looks
like something that would take you 500
hours honestly
I don't know wait I guess wait 150 hours
it's like about as much time as I spend
on Fire Emblem maybe more I guess a
little bit more
um what the
no no I feel like it takes even more
yeah for just four minutes yeah okay
wait okay wait Scarlet wait until the
end random collusion thanks for the
pinky
all right let's play this in the
background
[Music]
uh for the red I mean random position
hooray
for everything yay hooray what did I do
uh odd announcement thank you random
collusion for
[Applause]
ever
for spreading positivity hooray hey
what's up
as I also like to say
Jacob 47.
let's go our first album congratulations
thank you yeah first album
ah
yeah I'm so proud I'm so proud after
three years I
I finished off the third year by
releasing an album it was
it was
just a journey
um
yeah
checking that off of my bucket list
let's go thank you
but I have a double Zone thank you for
the pinky oh my God I had no idea oh
this is such a surprise this is a dream
come true for me
yeah um I honestly don't know how other
members can even like not talk about
their projects when they do stuff like
this behind the scenes like how can you
keep quiet I I am incapable of keeping
quiet about it I need to talk about it
and I think you know it's interesting to
have the behind the scenes because like
when you actually release it you won't
remember half of them or more than half
of these things that you would have
talked about anyway
so yeah
yeah I like to share things when they're
still in my brain basically
yeah thank you for for acting surprise
like I told you to Chase
[Music]
Mexico
and Beyond excited for your album it's
been something I've been looking forward
to for a long time I love your music so
much thank you for your hard work wow
one more awesome money another one from
the RC Squad oh God actually I didn't
even like think of you as an Australian
I'm so sorry
I didn't I didn't even realize
oh my God
thank you
are you Australia
mate
it's really amazed
good to know this is trillions man we
have this connection we have the special
connection don't we
um
yeah yeah I love your art because
I like your name too
thank you thank you for the support
you adopted us office you're also one of
them oh my God
I'm adopting the horses am I adopting
you or are you guys adopting me
um you guys are adopting me
know
from the Aussie Squad thanks for the
pinky I'll take your entire stock Stream
Point of View thank you
ah
I I am so happy you guys are so excited
about it thank you
for the pinky you can't stop me from
buying the physical and digital copies
come with you thank you I'm really
grateful to everybody who's getting both
the physical and the digital thank you
I hope you will enjoy the extra track
that comes with the physical one and
it's just a really special Memoir to
have right
[Music]
there's no breaks on this type train
foreign
[Laughter]
versatile emojis
[Music]
co-workers listen to it thank you I
wonder is there like can you guys try
can you do me one more favor
I think there's many like
um radio stations where you can request
a song can you guys try requesting songs
at your
um radio stations I I think
if we start getting pineapple or sleep
talking or whatever into
radio stations from normal people like
not just Anime radios or whatever
I think you know people could
get interested maybe yeah
and then they listen to it on the on the
in the car
that would be so cool
can you guys try that and maybe if you
even get even if you even like um manage
to catch it when it actually plays on
the radio
I I I I I want to maybe hear that too I
don't know I guess it will just be my
song but I want to hear them announce my
song and next
we have
am I pronouncing not right
yeah I don't know Japanese
a new song is released from an album
point of view uh the song is called
sleep talking enjoy
talking
[Music]
they're all syndicated so cover would
have it was a mean
don't they sound like that
take a nasty take kanashi
Kate
take a Nash
key okay
here we have however they wanna
scuffle my name I don't give a
um show me what you got bring it on baby
two heads Samantha
Nashville Kiana
uh
Rockstar we have
um it's been pulled tomato cheese or
yellow ostrich
YouTuber tanakisha Korea
sounds weird
um we are
um
Dragon Days requested oh sleep talking
yeah so let's listen to it let's go
apparently the fandom is called p f
crowded I got that right pfk we're pfk
now yeah you know you know we're pfk now
yeah I know what would be so cool to get
it on some radio stations and I think
requests would help get the ball rolling
I don't know how else to do it to get
their attention
[Music]
um
Yum Yum Yum Yum anyway
thanks for the pinky finally you long
worked and from us awaited first album
you mean not awaited Surprise album This
is a milestone server to new heights you
deserve it uh so exciting and proud for
you thank you
but you have to work
on your acting skills yeah you forgot
the script
you have not awaited this album nobody
knew about this album until I announced
it
don't you understand I think I made it
clear enough for you
yeah it came out of the blue out of
nowhere right right you were so
surprised like oh my god wow bamboozle
I thought you were working on
some fear to play
you announced it and connect the world
eh
well
don't hit me with logic
what
shut up
but didn't I say like I'm working on one
I didn't give you a date or anything
could have been in half a year
let's move it calm down I'm like almost
done
I know for my destination lucky profit
thank you
okay I was saying this but not too loud
because it's late and because I screamed
a lot
foreign
[Music]
myself
this gives me total Vibes holy this
could be a polo song
straight from the game
[Music]
don't break I will never give up don't
break
[Music]
foreign
could you tell me please
[Music]
[Applause]
never seen it
to me
[Music]
please
just telling me to stop streaming
so I'm gonna go
did you hear
[Music]
y'all
okay so thanks for the Minecraft Tino
Tony
and thanks for watching guys short
stream I mean even now we've reached
four hours so
Columbia
oh there she is oh
you just went to the toilet you little
get out of here
but it's a little bit wet
gonna touch you
go away
yeah uh I will go
um I'll upload the membership wallpaper
okay
foreign
[Music]
I think
um you scare yourself with it I think
um
if I make a schedule I make it tomorrow
after I get up I don't want to do it now
bye-bye
thank you love you guys thanks Canada
especially today
[Music]
thank you
I have good news by the way
okay maybe just this once I keep it to
myself until more close to the actual
thing
[Music]
I'll try to keep it to myself then
keep your secrets
[Music]
thank you
laughs
[Music]
um