[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n e
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
h
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
k
k oh hi hi hi
a lot a little bit more war
cries
darling attention please yes yes yes yes
attention please she's asking you pay
attention pay attention yes for your
attention attention given I Sor guys
little bit of delay because of setting
up but we are here and we are so ready
to destroy each other
[Music]
yeah yeah we're playing worms ex yeah
you don't know how to play the game
right yeah me and first
timers good luck me and waya will not
hold your feathers wait wait wait wait
wait wait no you've got to tell us you
got to get tell us generally how to play
we'll try we'll like we'll try to
sabotage
us we are maybe we should be on the same
team I've played before doesn't doesn't
mean I I remember anything one thing I
can definitely do is extend the time for
each turn I I think that is round time
20 seconds so that you have more time to
figure out what to do maybe maybe just
this once I'll do unlimited but yeah oh
just all right all right aim for is this
what I'm sorry you can't see my screen
what is like Teamsters buffins team gav
taste
that's just
team yeah and then uh yeah it's been a
while for me too but the numbers I
suppose is the numbers of units you have
so I'm pushing you all up to
six okay rounds to win I don't know
let's do two why is it on one isn't that
really low rounds to win Round Guys chat
what should be rounds to
win one day and then can play
again round it is one round one okay one
one round is it not just one cycle of
each of
us those numbers just one for this
for yeah yeah let's let's just do one
round to win run run round is the whole
game okay until somebody is the only one
left standing I guess okay uh turn time
my round time round time turn time ah
turn time wait I think turn time turn
time is infinite yeah no round time is
infinite but turn time I cannot do
infinite 90 seconds is the maximum
Ladies sorry okay and warm heal yeah t
so real time infinite means no sudden
death or what no just that yeah I guess
so I guess so that would probably mean
that yeah what's going on wait a minute
I was just trying to figure out what
things
spontaneous
combustion let's go you figure it out
um we want we want sudden death of
course we want it so 20 or what yeah I'm
I'm bringing it down to like yeah 20
probably all right all
right um okay so just to get you a
general idea we all have worms on this
field it's one screen we're all seeing
roughly the same thing
and then you can choose in your turn you
can choose a weapon I think you can also
switch the worm that you have selected
but I don't remember how but it
automatically selects one worm and then
you can like get a weapon and then shoot
sometimes you already have a weapon
sometimes it's around you uh and you can
pick it up go there pick it up but like
you have I think if you start walking
and then stop walking uh I think you
can't continue walking uh eventually
like there's a limited uh distance that
you can
walk and like D and D yeah uh you'll see
and and yeah but you pick up a weapon
and then you aim for someone you want to
take out all the other teams and
eventually the terrain will be destroyed
too and there's a chance that you'll
self-destruct because you're destroying
the Earth that you're standing on for
example yeah you'll see and there's
really really op weapons here and there
so let's try to find let's just do it
cuz none nothing of what you said made
any sense yeah I guess so okay we'll do
it as we go press ready uh yeah okay
maybe it's one of those games Nissa
where you don't have to know what's
happening you just press the buttons and
hope yeah no not necessarily
no but the first round learning learning
by doing would be best I think okay so
let's start by okay we still
start oh my God they talk try like
walking around I think 3 2 1
now uh wait who am I you can jump too so
you could jump trying how do I jump who
am I space probably I forgot no it's not
space no it's not face it's something
else oh is it face well then no walking
for now we'll figure it out chat will
tell us but yeah try to go to that gun
good I remember cuz it can't be it can
be space l or enter enter they're
saying wait is it everybody's turn right
I'm so are we just watching one person
how do I
go there go there you go okay how do I
how do I aim it oh oh
okay if you look around with the mouse
uh you can see that there's also area at
the bottom and on the left and so on
isn't it great to something sorry I'm
sorry I didn't know it was you I didn't
know who was
who I didn't know who was mine either uh
no it's aa oh it is enter jumping is
enter but I don't know what this how do
I switch the chat how do I switch the
worm that I'm
on you can switch Yeah you can but so um
no oh I guess you don't well I don't
know what to do down here do I have a
weapon from the GetGo I don't remember
either nobody know weapon switch what's
how do I ah okay wait I do have a few
things okay it will be so great M oopsie
oh it is no it's already really great
where' you get that uh okay so once you
have a weapon in your hand you can press
W and S to go aim higher or lower
um so let's try this how do I oops
ah yeah right click is to choose the
weapon how do I fire
it how do I fire it again I'm
getting uh space bar okay you got to for
some weapons you have to press space bar
longer to charge it up all right we're
remembering everything step by step
learning by step
guys it's good that we don't remember
well Raina because they have a
disadvantage
already yeah I after all after that I
feel a lot more
confident and then what's how right
click was it yeah right click you can
choose the weapons you can scroll feel
I'm pretty good okay um wait which one
are you at now oh here oh I'm going to
shoot oh wait that's not me whatever
shoot
yeah didn't do much damage though I
guess hey leave my team bad intentions
alone just scared okay how do I move how
do I oh this is how I move a crate has
landed somewhere apparent oh this map is
huge oh [\h__\h] how can I take this tank
and you have to jump oh okay how do you
can but I'm not sure if you can go far
from there did I I do it go okay uh now
how do I enter uh maybe oh oh it says
right there wait but it's it's E I could
see it was blocked oh nice you can yeah
Mak a big
explosion wait this kind of sucks can I
leave not too strategic stay
committed okay no no no there's what's
in here
what is that I got a a battery a phone
battery okay I'll go back in the tank
we'll see if that will prove
useful I mean there's I don't I don't
want to shoot myself you could I mean I
could sacrifice it can I get how's this
not killing you okay okay hold on hold
on oh no that won't work oh okay okay oh
it's facing the H yeah it doesn't face
that far down I guess I guess it does
not you also try shooting
yeah I'll do a test I'll just do a test
okay yeah sure sure nice
holes tip over the mountain yo next time
try with your right Mouse click uh to
see all the weapons you already have at
hand and then you can just choose one of
those look at that that would have been
nice to know my that's good okay you
don't need heal yes it's
okay oh oh don't oh this just be free oh
hold g dog I wish I could see where it's
going to hit question
mark yeah you you can only really see
where it's
aiming oh what yeah you aim too close to
the stone I guess and it just like
explodes
itself not
be ha well well well oh oh wait what it
switched turn oh no oh no looking at
another worm right now yeah I thought I
was going to be next to
narissa well who's red again not that it
matters but else you're standing so
nicely on the
cliff
so I think no leave me alone baseball
bat could work oh my is that or a helmet
it looks like Ste
it does look like
hair you're
rude that was pretty
em hom
on how do you use items what right click
right click right click scroll through
them and just okay choose one that
they're withholding this information
Nissa no I told you where the hell did
you get a baseball at I told you right
click I'm for telling you
oh
nice wow good punch good although I
don't just like I think it's still at
100 HP yeah Jee
dang
intense wow look at that more crates
let's go oh it's going it's going to
fall into the ocean no not quiet not Qui
oh I see wait where am I who am I
remember right click for choice of
weapons you're right you're right right
click for choice of weapons all right I
got and then space to charge and weapon
you have to press space longer to charge
it or if it's like a I guess you just
also continue uh okay okay go home run
are you serious oh there we go I thought
that was a shotgun so you I guess you
also have to closer yeah get closer oh
my yeah for some weapons you get a few
more shots than one but that was I guess
two oh you did 50 damage nice I see I
see let's
go
what explosion of the machine I guess
because you damaged
it I'm not sure what's happening but
worms are jumping off the cliff that was
good I'm going to pretend that was
calculated yeah you planned it
all oh wa you might you might want to
jump down there yeah come down kill some
people destroy them look somebody's at
the edge of the
cliff not me okay she's learning she's
learning from the best how do I how do I
use it itace ah space careful now okay
but uh get a bit closer get a bit closer
perhaps no no no you should smack the
other one you should smack the other one
oh oh oh he only fell down there oh you
following there's a bunch of people now
down here okay they got 40 damage
welcome to the cheese house
okay
oh oh 69 is your HP
huh like my subscribers right
now I I I will just go one more time and
Trust the mighty baseball B although the
dist distance is pretty far you going to
hit a home run not poor poor what are
you say
blue why are you all targeting me it's
just you were there look
[Music]
at
there where are you going to go way in
there I don't know where you go I do you
have maybe like a teleportation device
or something like
that
sometimes uh there's oh there's a tort
on the bottom uh bottom yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah you girls can look at the
weapons now to to
study I'm going to
teleport here
oh yeah so one strategy is also to just
stay as high as possible because
eventually if you're on the bottom
levels you're going to die I'm on it oh
yeah yeah are you yeah where am I here I
am wait how do you people down here for
some reason oh shoot oh oh dang it oh no
oh I I've trapped myself oh
dear why why is enter jump oh there oh
no I wasn't trapped okay hey you hey bud
that's where's that bat I don't have a
bat please I'm just on my phone looking
for seats Clos I have a
bat will you hit the rock that will
happen uh maybe could wait what ah I
don't get it you did it right you did it
right it just like bounced off of the
skull off did it bounce off the loot
thing yeah maybe also the loot thing I
guess so now that's
silly to keep us in track it's okay you
still do damage game of luck Nissa the
game of oh dear R oh dear revenge is
near no narissa we should stick together
narissa and M
I think we should stick together narissa
we're both beginners here I don't know I
don't I don't I don't know if you want
to H me against the loot thing that's
fine oh it's good to pick that up first
yeah it's good that you learned we
go take me out huh
awkward back we just keep attacking each
other and you keep on coming back to
each other
too mhm oh oh and all right you guys
have to take each other out smell that
cheese do my ourselves
here yeah I guess I'll I'll continue
this whole nice position I just yeah I
just want to make sure I actually
hit
yeah uh did it oh still 100 this isn't
no it's
like a while have that chance why does
it take so
long just it needs to calculate all the
other collateral damage you know I
see
um R join
us I don't know what I should do yeah go
down go down to them what's that want to
join the
party yeah we're having a lot of fun
down here yeah they're going to G up on
you actually unless you do Fight
Club it's a party over here oh I'm stuck
no I thought I was stuck too nice oh how
oh you just kicked me out of my tank
how' you do that yeah it's it's yeah not
in a good position there oh my goodness
there so many one spot what if what if I
do baseball bat here everybody just
continues to use the baseball bat wait
can I give recommendation oh okay you
did not that was not what I was going to
recommend
but that hurt we need to be more
experimental alone
I it's okay I'll try something else next
time something more inter recommend you
hit narissa
but I guess
not gamble nice the heel landed right
where you needed it if I oh maybe I
should teleport no two of you are blue
no what's in here can I go in here yeah
de there's
a is that I don't I don't I don't think
I can get in there oh I can things for
me oh you got another heal I think
what's this thingy why is it fire that's
kind of scary I think you could maybe if
someone's in there if you shoot the
house it will maybe blow up the person
inside too thank you for telling me out
there over there other side other side
run run I'm I'm out of here no thank you
no thank you okay okay um I guess I'll
teleport cuz no one's over here let's
see teleport where are we going wait
that's why is it so slow hello okay I'll
go uh uh I guess I'll go I know I oh my
gosh why do I have to drag my mouth so
much you going down there too
p i could join that party or I could uh
yeah I'm going to I'm to oh yeah you
could be yeah you could go there sure
join me I'll destroy you sure I welcome
it try me okay who's next go wild oh
artillery backup okay let's use aissa
where at the bottom you got to work
yourself up let's go that's Bruce why is
there fate Monument How what what one is
the
teleporter
parachute teleport
okay oh what you doing you want to join
me on that ledge no join the fighting
pit want to join go to the figh the blue
yeah oh not a bad
idea I think it's got to be red to land
oh a little bit higher it was red for a
minute there you go there you go little
hard
that's a good spot that's a really good
spot first there's a foot monument and
here's a shoe Monument a this is like
the feet
map people aha uhuh uh um
okay do you think that the rest of the
body is like too high for the worms to
see or comprehend so they just think
there's giant feet oh
probably yeah possible the rest is just
out of sight how does this work does
this work I don't know how it
works oh my God you want to you want to
join the pit
no oh air strike
wowed you killed purple light oh who
died that's
me you messed me up
I won't forget that got to be creative
with those
weapons you s up you encouraged us to
make a Fight Club yeah she's setting us
up Nissa she is me so well I did set
this collab up so I guess
so okay can you make the jump come why
you stuck the pole the pole use use a
weapon that can do you know damage from
like away like I just
did my
good
um what should I do double tap enter oh
you can scroll oh you got a little
chicken on your
head double back space yeah for back
flip apparently oh okay I can
try oh that's
cute oh there we go
there we go oh cute and then I can try
to um I think you
shouldn't
yeah I think you shouldn't try anything
oh the Sheep interesting what does it
explodes at the end right it explodes at
the
end I think you can you set it off with
space huh oh are you going to kill it
you let it run and then it sets off
whenever you press space boring I see
bro why did we do this well well for
reasons was that a me was it a
message yes she's coming for you it's
just me here or is coming for you oh
scrolling is nice okay okay let's see um
what could I parachute jetpack just so
you guys know if you sent the Sheep it
doesn't go on forever eventually it will
also explode on its own so don't wait
too
long I don't know how these I don't know
what these will do which one like I
don't know what do you what do you want
to do do you want to teleport or do you
want to use a weapon from the distance I
I only have one teleport left so I don't
want to use it I guess the the bunker
Buster in the third row is what I used
to drop an air bomb air strike which one
which one third thir from the bot
the second from Strike no the bunker
Buster because air strike for me wasn't
available but the air strike would work
too and then there's a jetpack with
which you can fly away uh it's on the
bottom um row okay I'm going to hang out
there I'm going
to I'll use I'll use oh I can't use that
okay I'll use this I guess oh I don't
have much time why is it like this oh my
goodness
choose a good why is it
so okay I'm going to do here
oh okay me I taught you how to do this
thank
you oh oh
oh what what did you choose the air
strike or the bunker Buster the bunk oh
the bunker Buster it goes in the bunker
I see it goes down one it didn't let me
use the air strike yeah I think you need
to still like collect the air strike in
a box in a crate possibly I
see what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
whoa yeah that happens a lot in worms
what I didn't even mean to attack
anything what are you going to do yeah
not sure she's sending a message you're
sending a message you would sacrifice
your own soldiers to win is what you're
telling us that's terrifying what
the I want to get both of
you no you don't oh but it's I don't
this is probably going to go very wrong
just try it it'll be fine it'll be
fine I don't know if it'll be fine might
not be oh no oh no oh no oh oh it places
it right where you are okay good to know
oh but I did two damage yay oh to myself
too you you really messed me
up rip car yeah that nice orange
car who's going to get it
first neither of
us apparently I don't want to go down
there either oh my God
where is this way apparently you can tab
to switch worms how wait how do I move
okay mind which one which one that is
true I'm going to ride scroll
why I can't zoom
in Chad why can I not zoom in but I know
she's in the middle
there oh help
me hi there you're mildly annoying
what's where are we let's try that is
such a crazy thing to say right that is
an insane thing to hear in the year 2024
it keeps on so much so much you're
starting to
me hello come on scroll back
in okay I think it was just bugging
around now it's fixed it's me hey hey
buddy hi what happened the rocket League
car I'm just I'm not going to I'm just
going to use this yeah where the car
like that oh my God shotgun oh my God I
am
innocent bring her down I don't think
you're mess up you're going to point a
gun at the roast chicken just like that
oh wait I think you hit yourself too
yeah a little bit recoil recoil yeah
OU and we haven't even done anything oh
you can get the
crate yeah nice I don't want a bazooka
how do I put the Bazooka down I think
you can still switch with right click
and then
scroll right click
scroll oh oh oh you don't want a
bazooka oh hey now oh
my she's
aggressive oh my let's go you know you
killed one of my Soldiers the car you
kill one of mine so we're we just took
it even I do not recall I
recall she has good memory just
Ving yeah R is like R is she's doing we
only have have 3 minutes
left oh [\h__\h] okay uh well we're learning
we're still learning this is a tutorial
this a trial run yeah
yeah uh uh
oh dang oh she's got going to
do no hey I think you a little more a
little more to the left it doesn't start
here I want to see if it starts there or
if it end drink milk tea you guys are
terrible help okay now hold up I should
have been
protected a three minutes until the
water rises it doesn't end immediately
you just might want to go up water rises
yeah
yeah oh that's why you said we should
aim to be higher I see you smell
likee I see I oh byebye God man down
worm
down you're
brutal I'm just here
super it's okay naturally
brutal it's okay me and way have a
packed for the second game no no no I do
not want that I want to get out of here
what so I have a jetpack right I'm going
to use that how
do how do I do this I'm out of here I'm
out of here oh space space to yeah and
then less space go down again hey you oh
shoot oh
no yeah oh hey oh I'm oh I'm going to
wait uh leave me alone don't why you
kill her oh wait oh you're right I had
time I have time to do that yeah you're
so right
okay um let's see
uh oh wait how do I how do I get rid of
this wait please I do not want the jetp
pack anymore
I get out of you can only use one thing
per turn so oh should I just chill here
for like seconds press space
again oh no oh you're right oh there
there you go there you go oh you can
still you can all right can
you oh look at look at him is terrified
what the heck that is not what I
wanted why isn't this working you're
running out of time
terrified why is it not getting her you
missed the head I think you aimed for
the for the chicken on top that's not
fair but that doesn't that some S I
think I think it went through her
head of her
head well that is good good deceive
tactics okay let's use a new color for
this lip piece wait you going to end wa
I keep on saying
wa W are you going to end it down there
end
it um you know how to it's just you and
me here I'm just listen and I I've been
just chilling I haven't done anything
you're leaving her
behind how he leaving me what I'm going
to be
alone
no just going to have a lonely death in
the water
I mean I'm going to die it wasn't wasted
time just now a little bit later yeah
you've extended your life warranty yeah
slightly a crate has landed down
there L rain it I'm feeling some
favorite child syndrome me
too I'm observing
[Music]
it theese I don't think you should do
that
I think you should do that yeah I don't
know what's going to happen honestly
know how to think don't say that but
don't worry you will just probably be
pushed to the other
side what the
heck hi there that was the fire a party
over here party
[Music]
island1 got you
yeah you
oh we're back to this okay okay we keep
on
[Music]
Switching yeah it's probably
over or is it over over for is it Gavin
oh there we go
gav goodbye it was a nice time chilling
with you here fighting for life and
death could this make a difference what
is it I wonder m
wow look at that Water Rising in 24
seconds here I am
uh let's see what am I to do I don't
have a single one down there do I try I
try to hit you from here I don't know
that's not going to work no that's I
don't think so you don't think that will
work Ian what else is there for me to do
uh you can choose like a a distant
weapon
or something that goes something that
travels
in do I have the air strike now I might
have it yeah you got to go for a rain a
I do all her people oh boy all my
people oh it's a good spot I technically
you know I've been Ving a good spot
where I I am in every spot okay no no no
where where the big G and royalty are
it's just so three no are you over there
wait where I can't where are you right
there right there no no
no yeah seea food
poisoning hoko is on top where are you H
oh I'm inside am I sa inside I think you
might be
fine I will test it if I'm wrong no
you're not going to be safe you're not
going to be safe I'm not going to be
safe you're running out of time you're
right 9 seconds Drop It Like It's Hot
sorry okay four three you could go for
three of them and you go for
me oh
[\h__\h] I'm sorry see how risk so fake I
didn't want to risk it for myself this
is
targeted no targeted
harassment I'm everywhere you can take
revenge soon no but at least fr is on
high ground oh the water is rising oh
yeah oh my God they going to get they're
going to get my baby chimal is going to
die
no oh oh hey now
dramatic hey now wait oh hey now hey he
doing she's doing the right thing this
is not what dreams are made of we oh
just joining my body kind of that was
that was a good shot mhm now I'm really
chees that
HT
oh time to get this cheese rolling oh
not what do we have not good not good
teport this is intense why isn't the
water I want to see you
drown what
that's a
very I want to go there let me
join oh oh you're
teleporting yes okay and
then look how oh well that's all I got
to do no I should have used a jetpack
why does have
a what
should she
still that's
crazy bazooka ah what you got I'm going
to no bazooka go for
uhoh she's taking out her biggest rival
in the
game cheese that was you're starting to
gr me right in
the she's all done my
baby your baby my baby drowned
let's go wait that's so sad oh dear wait
no no no no no no not what I want uh
let's see I'm going to oh you're in
there wait where where why is it doing
this hello can't see him why you hiding
my cat by the way I named in I named the
thing out from yeah your cat a yeah
that's my cat the one who just drowned
oh okay Den it feels really bad wao
good use I
guess at least you hit this time Miss
yeah at least I did I thought that' do
more damage you're totally going to kill
me when you get the chance
there come on you can still win this
bazooka you can still win this
W oh sheep she good good idea how do I
use it you send it you press space and
then you yeah they press space again
when you want to have it explode oh oh
yeah oh
no
way that works too yeah that's
how wow it went the wrong way yeah it
bounces off oh dear the water's getting
higher my dude's going to
die
a have more time just
oh this is also air strike
is
O give it a go let's see
it why I have one guy left I feel bad
all right let's try this I am far from
and
then what I choose you but I have to
shoot it from here is that going to work
okay let's
see I am the CH is it not that you can
select
multiple it's like homing Miss lightning
I get it I don't get it oh you have to
shoot high up in the air oh we're
learning we're learning we're
learning oh my
goodness oh
my oh my I see I see what beautiful eyes
you have you're
leaving where you
going oh
oh oh what's she doing hey now hey now
oh she still have one of those huh all
right you didn't go far
enough getting
roasted I'm roasted baby I died one
HP get
them
egg they dropped an egg oh thank
goodness it's time to get you out of
there Bruce I got you I'm going to use
my last teleport to help you
okay where should I take you
though to the egg shoot where did you go
no the egg how about we go uh we about
the protein let's go
here you you smell God was what's oh bad
choice oh no gate open start is about to
die
too I love that song Or was is
it we're going to list the colors you'll
need for you have to get higher
um where are we at who's who are we
dealing with she's got the Bazooka oh
there Nissa can claim the lies of those
two guys down there but there's gav you
know I don't think I could I don't know
you walk down
uh you do
like you don't need to follow my advice
oh no she's coming down
I is coming down is it's over for
me open star
no welcome to the cheese house oh okay
one um what with these guys and
cheese I think Kiara's guys just like
cheese
why does that make me so sad what are
they fighting for are you
okay what are they fighting for hi hi
cheese
apparently oh banana no maybe
not make someone slip and break their
head The
Recoil well well it's you'll be fine it
it'll be it'll be good it's a worthy
sacrifice oh yeah oh
we're just
places sweet dreams are made of cheese
wait can we change he with tab
apparently I don't know if that really
works because there's an item to switch
uh a different worm also on the botom
tell you to do such a
thing goodbye
oh that was not cool
down I have one left imagine Rissa just
winning because she's at the highest
spot even though she just has one
worm
choosing kill one for
sure yeah just the ones for sure yes I'm
really cheesed off it'll be a nice
change oh that hurts me that is not cool
that is not cool oh that is Oh that's oh
that's well reaction double hit let's
go oh no
wa oh how quickly they
[Music]
fall you going to stay up there
huh where it's safe and dry oh even
higher you're going to oh my goodness
I have one worm left there's I have
nothing to live for
like I don't know what y'all want from
me like what am I supposed to do
crackers it's understandable oh dear no
way she wins like that right no way it's
not going to
happen all right what you got what you
oh my gosh
really that's what we're doing no no not
when you're right next to me I can use
something else done mm uhhuh
uhhuh that uh-huh okay that will
probably have too much recoil or so as
well no it probably won't does bazooka
have recoil probably I don't think I
don't think bazooka would cause recoil
what would be good here just a
bazooka n you're you're fine fine you go
for it you're you're good you're good
maybe I'll try to punch you into the
water or you're just going to get her
over to rain s
here why yeah why not finish rain off
what the heck was that Holy
grenade
what whoo What did I
say huh wow oh okay no there's no
surviving that
okay then I'll take the L
say that's a beautiful hole really I
think it's oh my God it's so hard to
there's I'm going to go to Rissa
Rissa you won't um you won't attack the
25 ha little dude right no of course not
I don't have anything left so what what
could I even do at this point
don't believe her don't trust
her dear when you close to you do things
you never thought you would
do I I can use that what's this uh blow
torch parachute ninja rope
jetpack if I
use you a grenade get up there oh I
don't think so you don't think so you
could try it though but I feel like it
might backf on
you
here a homing missile wait where's
that oh this you can do anything here
don't wor about it oh my gosh what is
with this okay yeah it's so
uh bro okay you can try the Homing
missile okay aim up I'm assuming like
this aim up yeah seems so seems so she's
doing the job that we want her to do
let's go wo
[Music]
oh what the
heck how
you you hate me I see you hate
me you did so well you hate me it's
War babies just started drowning a it's
okay it was just tutorial hey
Nissa I'm more invested in the
adventures OFA that's oh she
miss bro
why she missed we
Landing okay it's all that's there's
another one there
okay you've got two left I think I think
waa might win this no because they're on
the same level the next time the water
rises it's kind of yeah they will die
yeah s but now I know how to use this
so okay all right all
right okay
okay I was
thinking what the car I think the car
stopped me yeah it's the
car [\h__\h] car
oh no I have to charge it and turns I
think I had to charge it that's the
problem they don't
end somebody call medic
uhoh I'm going to drown hi we should we
should just leave it to fate you can
kill me but you're going to
drown I mean I might not you're going to
drown it's possible I W drown okay if
you if you press tab during the first 10
seconds you know before you you like
start your turn for real for real then
you can switch your worm
apparently just for next time please
move
me please
oh oh that didn't kill you shotgun
weak I'm
sorry oh my God this
is there we go I
can't I think that means m
will win because I'm going to
drown pretty sure I'm going to
drown
yeah oh oh
oh M first timer M see you don't need
experience crown for my
collection yay
congratulations huz huzzah look at you
go oh see there's Awards too yay party
animal what does that even mean I don't
know she likes to party oh Raina was
very accurate with her
shots good job okay now that we've
learned how to play it I'm going to make
each uh turn time
shorter okay like not that have to go ID
me have to go to
ID go idle me go idle me okay she has to
celebrate her win that's what she's
doing she's partying so narissa what
will be your strategy for next time I
have no
idea let's go round round time is I
think the round time is good uh turn
time is shorter yeah good round time is
good I think yeah it was fine an hourish
it was fine I think
it's we can it's just we can end it a
little bit like we can do
15 for round time littleit yeah let I
let the water start Rising earlier I
like that the stress o
yeah try enabling all weapons they said
I don't know what that means I don't
know what that means will that be
confusing they
are they look all enabled ah you mean
from the getg go to have everybody have
one
or is that like I think that would
be I don't know do we want to try a
different map too oh yeah yeah we could
we could change the map I think rather
than having a lot of weapons from the
get-go I think changing the thing will
be nice yeah yeah oh Wormhole oh wow no
good guy
feet aw it smelled so
nice
what I was admiring the quality of the
sculptures oh was that this looks
beautiful o and we can have different
schemes there's like beginner
intermediate and so on I don't know
let's beginner beginner oh yeah wait
that just changes the turn time and
stuff hold all right all right okay well
now you have to Ed walls or roof they
said maybe because
ah I see I guess if it's walls then you
canot well I mean it's fine no let's
take the
desert hello hello hello welcome back so
we've shortened uh everything a little
bit you have to you have to re-edit the
round time yeah yeah I did oh yeah there
you go we've shortened it all a little
bit M from now and you'll have 60
seconds to do your turn instead of 90
seconds and the whole
time until the water rises is a little
bit shorter now
too
so let's this is the real one no more
tutorial destruction go oh wait ah wait
don't don't press ready we have to
change our colors there's some oh the
same color oopsie how do you change your
color click on the the color
Square it doesn't you're around I think
only the host can do it I oh okay I'll
change your colors You Make Me Blue you
want to be blue
yeah okay so that you know who you
really are green let me let me green
okay
yeah ear M red okay M red okay good wait
it would have been would have been good
if I made it accurate
to the the colors on on the screen uh oh
on the screen actually let me do that if
you don't mind way will be
purple uh Willow be like ready M
yellow and whist stays
Blue okay let's
ready
ready let's go let's go no
mercy oh
oh oh oh welcome to the wild
w wo time to get this wheel of cheese
rolling
let's see where I am tap didn't work to
switch oh
wow wow okay oh my god
wow wait I'm
red
[Music]
yeah
okay I from the
cheese oh nice a little bit collateral
damage there good good good good good
good start good good walks away OU OU
you want a Band-Aid I can I can heal you
back to
health just come here to me just come
closer to
me what the heck why is it why is n set
up so
well not well oh dear maybe she's in
trouble she's set up too
well we have to change it good job first
step go s i mean she did it super she
did it
wow ready it's me all right let's see
what what what can we do thing doesn't
work the time thing what can we do here
I'm sorry the tab oh I I tried it too it
doesn't work weird I'm going to start oh
I can't start with that oh
no let's see can I start with will this
work oh wait I can't use that either
what the heck can I use Nobody's around
me like an air strike or so or
teleportation or you can if you use aack
then you can still
attack I think I'll hang out here can I
just can I just
chill probably yeah chill yeah I think
so yeah I mean could throw a grenade I
guess I'm running out of time though
there might not be enough time okay move
it the best moves are with 5 seconds
left m
m just Panic moves I I I can't get over
there it's okay I'm going I'll hang out
it's all good mhm a skip rope is to skip
the turn
uhhuh feel you wouldn't want to do that
really our got to make use of your
turns that's okay I it's beautiful and
we haven't even done
it you're
plotting okay wait you guys were saying
that WIA has set up so well but she's
also set up really well for air strikes
up there she's easy to be hit by yeah
yeah no one has air strikes right now
though oh soon soon soon soon soon
soon soon soon
soon yeah I don't really know what I'm
supposed to do right now
I don't know either I think it's you
know at the start of the battle you're
just like huh what do I do
just me Anda we both have ours so
grouped
together
[Music]
yeah
strange you
know yeah I I could grab a box a box
take your time speed will come later
take your time speed will come
later very fitting what'd you get what'd
you get what' you get what you get let
me clean my see sheep for example could
have been a good choice you can just
send it running down it'll come back and
just I think he's kind of stuck you
know oh oh no no that will fall down oh
there is something down there oh oh
Roger's going to get
it
maybe
hold oh I switched oh it seems like I
switched maybe I did maybe I didn't
um what is a tasty worm
lick worm do we want to taste it out
test it out let's test it do you want a
taste of the tasty worm lick I don't
think it's very ethical to test it on
somebody
else I'm just testing on worms it's okay
might
what is that what oh what the
heck I was like oh that was not useful
but then it was useful
H nice
interesting
interesting I I don't know about that
one oh o o o o o You're mildly annoying
mildly annoying
I have a constant talk of cheese batter
making me hungry sorry I don't even like
cheese that much you don't I don't not
that much nice punch not enough to talk
about it all the time oh Fire Punch
you're starting to gra me okay you are
in the den of bruus and boggy and
jewels it's my turn hello I don't like
this atmosphere
jazz
hands are you going to hurt me with the
jazz hands h
no you going to stay down there or
leave
shotgun you going to shoot me you know
what I might not be able to it's just
you're already kind of low I don't know
will this actually hit you it might not
I would start from where I'm standing
actually wait would it still hit her
though wouldn't it be too far away
you know I'll the first shot on rainy
yep it missed as I predicted so what I
get the second shot because you're right
more certain to
hit of course it
is there we
go time it was
smart now I'm really
chees let's be mature guys o
watermelons watermelons yeah anybody
care for a crate ooh spicy crate I want
the
crate okay let's use a new color for
this little piece over here are you
selling a l don't show your fear are you
selling a l there I don't know what she
selling he lotes please
one no Bagel how oh she going to
teleport on the
high wait but wait but wait
yeah we saw that me and way we saw it
coming I wanted to know what it did oh
okay there was a a mine right at the top
I see it was like a button you could
claim yeah looked like it could maybe
pick it up yeah let's try this oh my
goodness don't rob me over please how
does this
work I think it digs downwards
why well oh that is
gruesome yeah okay just one
[Music]
time okay okay did not do much but it
was
fun
to wa the right too you're mildly
annoying yeah oh he deserves it please
end
him okay
Into the Dead is inside huh I'm going to
turn you into a there is someone
[Music]
there someone speaking French where am I
sir oh here I am hello there's not chimo
the cat no chimo the
[Music]
cat why do you hate cats hello I know
the game you're just going to baseball
cat a cat
basb P cat to the Sea like that jeez
heartless all right let's
go a
meow can we have a moment a meow moment
of of
Silence
whoa what'd you get what'd you get
what'd you get I actually didn't look so
I'm not
sure um
purple purple light I will remember your
name purple light purple light the name
of the the cat
killer I know I didn't even know it was
a
cat cuz it's based on my cat's name
oh you named you named your yeah I named
all my worms she's the only one who went
through that trouble I see it oh I'm I'm
sorry I I you're in my may have I may
not have done that had I
known you're forgiven it's okay what's
going on Jo smell bad or something send
to
War what you got you're running out of
time do something anything it's okay
what am I supposed to
do you could have you could have shot me
and it won't kill
you you want an instant
kill that's so sweet you don't want me
to
suffer oh what are we
doing oh you're standing all together
but that's I'm I'm there
too sacrifices must be made there
there's a lot of people in the middle
there but this goes kind of down right
well we'll see if you hit it directly on
someone it won't
ow
ohed that's predy damage for something
like that it's kind of soft I think
that's why it's better to use it on
multiple people like in an
[Music]
area L too short to be save by cactus
that goddamn
Cactus oh well you go for somebody
else two at once my goodness good one
again she can't this 5 HP in a dream St
great she's going low low low low low
lowow let's
see wait why can't I move H oh there we
go I feel like I'm the chosen one in
this situation hello uhhuh I feel the
eyes and the stare and and the punch
incoming oh no oh okay down there okay
oh my God there's no to the pit of worms
I hope no one
drops a big bomb there that would be a
really good
spot
unfortunate I I think somebody should do
that somebody who's not down there but
everybody's
there I mean sacrifices sometimes need
to be made Thea soon won't be there
anymore she only has 5 HP there anyway
oh there we go I I made the suggestion
and I suffer from it wow
I'm let's be mature about it guys it's
for
entertainment wait who
died I don't know a grave huh well well
well who died why are they droing it
they say it's for me but they're putting
it where I can't reach it yeah oh oh
[Music]
I am situated very
high
H it's a nice spot to be in
but but you could be even higher how do
I
select I'd be very grateful what what
what am
I okay I wasted it cuz I didn't know how
to use it I was going to select a
different Worm but oh no
how does the parachute work again I you
just fall
[Music]
down oh oh there you go you
highe go up go up why is it not going up
oh there we go I I press the wrong
button okay we get that
and oh she she gone wait what I don't
know
where where you
going I just want to go
somewhere I
see
okay okay well
um I'm going to royalty I'm going to get
the hell out of here are you why don't
you like us why why would you do that
what about bird how do I move again I
forgot you're mildly how do I Mo w w we
both forget bird brain one more might
call
it bro stay away from
me
territory H oh yeah assorting
dominance can we can I change weapon no
no uh I I think you can
yeah oh no I wasn't going to say
anything you okay then I
see people what they deserve we
learn it's me this
way not like
that like that yeah enter twice you turn
around and then those back backli wow
needle how's she do it oh my goodness
why you learn to jump like that
oh over the
bird are you going for
me nah you smell like cheese the crate
first of
course pleas
please move me move me no why I'm
sorry I'm sorry no not a second shot no
have you're ready for me don't Don't aim
for my hands aim for my face mie look
I'm going to stare right at you after
doing that let's use a new color for
this little piece here she's so
edgy how come how come these worms are
so edgy you didn't even choose them did
you theas are really edgy
yeah look at that hair
you join the Ed you're flying away oh
There She Goes
oh bro why couldn't I see
[\h__\h] you're going for the top
[Music]
again this game has it out for
Nissa no top of the tower for not now I
just want to be
[Music]
there I feel like I want to try to how
do you double jump
again uh double double enter double back
yeah double enter watch
it just me uh what you trying to do
stuck what are you trying to do just
gain some distance first me face me like
a man uhoh me like a
man okay there we go and
now maybe sometimes sacrifices have to
be made oh but I'm there too man all
right have to be made I'm there
sometimes sacrifices have to be made not
fry there we go that's the
one where you put the arrow is kind of
the middle I need to
remember the middle okay
she's still in me she gets a
heal she stuck she's stuck yeah can't do
anything oh she got to leave this gives
me Fallout Vibes
bro
ma'am oh my get
good
good can you not destroy the
sign well but then she's wasting her hit
but there's no one else
there maybe take a step back and then
get out and then just walk under the
sign oh can I yeah I think
so oh I can oh but you still get stuck
there arms are not very bright you see
they cannot walk around
it well yeah that is good
choice oh oh oh oh the time
Oh I thought it was going to be a
missile you were teleporting oh
silly what 2 minutes until water
rises uhoh uhoh all the all the people
down here all the worms down in the
middle all the worms that are dying
we'll have to run for their life now or
climb for their
life uh-oh where are
who's
oh hey let's be up here
together I think
so how do I oh man I want to go there
too
now you can still attack I
know uh-oh maybe the other way oh
because you could have sent her into the
ocean
probably oh but this is fine too that's
close to the ocean
ton it's
okay beat her with her own ton just look
at that little oh helicopter
wow but still hard to
reach we I heard you got bad
intentions apparently I do what are they
I don't
know World worms destruction
you'll be the last wor I'm standing is
that your
wish I hope for you that you can make
your wish come true she going she going
to beat her oh she going to punch her
she punch T punch me t
t wa gets beaten with her own Tong doog
that was
rough sorry I haven't had the
opportunity to hit anyone
yet time to get this rolling
[Music]
okay no no no
no I need to I need to go
bye got to get out of here hey you got
to go up to the top of
the yeah oh no she doesn't want
to uh okay oh
oh oh my my
turn wow
I think my turn was ending so I had to
make it
explode at least I hit more yellow than
red danger sheep well rainy you could
totally kill that big G guy yeah yeah
he's so we D Bru take revenge on the
toners oh yeah you can hit you could get
multiple Birds yeah oh wait that's kind
of close to
yourself oh that was close fine that was
close
about she got me oh let's go we die
together how
romantic mhm it's like Romeo and Juliet
wao that is oh no people are going to
drown oh dear got to get out of here oh
my my dude down there I didn't realize
he's there oh de sa oh he's done for no
it's over for him no if he knew you were
saying that he would be crying um I'm
going to what am I going to do I'm going
to I'm going to use
this bird of a Feather die together I
feel like ja die I don't think that's
how it
goes He I'm going to sacrifice ja hands
should I sacrifice J I don't have to I
could I could go for these guys yes yes
yes yes they feel too safe up there top
of the tower oh you're up there that's
me never mind also good idea though I
feel like I'd kill more if I go here
though I'm going to try here and just
hope ja's hand doesn't get they die
anyway from the water yeah oh they die
sooner now yeah uh-oh yum yum not doing
so that was not very much oh that
sucked okay okay I feel like uh tatang
was kind of protected by the big
armor good again good one yeah good luck
ja's hands maybe the water wasn't the
real
danger crate Landing right in front of
you right there I don't think I want to
be there purple light goodbye to you
tat unless buff tatong unless strongest
unless what you going to do I don't know
what to do man I mean purple will die
anyway outp will die I think you don't
have to yeah get out as long as you can
get out of
there yeah get some ele whoa oh careful
you can still use it yeah yummy careful
careful careful oh this has just become
I'm surrounded by Nissa
I would love to be surrounded by free n
is done
for yeah maybe not this
game oh that's fine but she can say if
there's so many narissa she can become
a choir
choir choir oh yeah she can make her own
musical too that' be beautiful murder
let's go imagine a quartet I'm just Nur
goodbye purple oh purple lights lives
for a a tiny bit long dies yeah nobody
dies okay he's definitely done
[Music]
for
n I'm still not so close to death but
I'm so far from
everybody
yeah you can teleport yeah still got all
my teleports but see feels like
everywhere is pretty Danger
dangerous I'm just like asking to be
like killed I think I think to the left
have to do I think to the left is a good
spot to do whatever you're planning can
I craft this
no oh no purple light's
dying I know this is karma it's karma
for purple light for
kicking kicking my cat yeah I don't know
how this
works oh have you gone soft
no okay I see I see now how it works but
it's too late uh you can kind of like I
think work your way through
the ground with that by purple light he
deserved
that YY YY
W
oh oh okay okay I thought you were going
to just drive off the
cliff me too
actually please send me to ja hands
please send me thank goodness ja hands
I'm getting you out of here what's
hoko hoko is my other cat oh I didn't
know the name uh but wait
Hoku is that
Indonesian yeah Indonesian what does it
mean oh it's just a name oh I
missed
yay oh no my God illusion is just like
you know taking a bath taking a little
is taking a
bath nissa's just up here I know is
winning right now yeah all I would say
that uh yeah yeah have the most alive
mhm I guess and you've got The High
Ground mostly and The High
Ground sheep oh oh okay sheep whatever
oh goodbye sheep goodbye
sheep that is so sad
[Music]
I have new weapons available let's go
maybe it is something to escape well you
well do you want to get it
no wait I want to get that
but yeah it's scary oh I miss
pressed I miss don't having a bad
I wanted to jump but he's fine can you
escape oh no can I
escape space I
want wait we were just both like [\h__\h]
this we don't have a chance to live
these could turn the war painful we
choose our own death yeah like a Samurai
game really wants you to suffer I refuse
to die by their
hands what do I got we have to
go when we
decide bro BS away oh okay oh yeah
beautiful
beautiful you're
fineac oh no no wait no we are the
experienced Birds we have to show them
who's boss wa okay so let's start by
loading
up we played this game before why are we
losing I'll see what I can do we should
have had a packed I don't have I don't
have enough bad intentions yeah that's
the problem true okay that's that's the
reason Nissa ised by her bad intentions
she's trying to hurt me she's going to
hurt she's trying to hurt me she
look at her you sound you sound so funny
look at this she even paused watch she's
watching me as like oh my goodness oh my
oh just one worm she's she has it out
for
you like a happy little water the lead
of boards have
changed my goodness
M at the bottom now but I guess you
you're sharing B on how many people you
have
left
um oh
no oh oh oh I see what you're
Grady I see what you're doing well will
I [\h__\h] it up this time well we'll see
only one way to find out you got it oh
you you got it oh you don't got oh I
guess you
[Applause]
did The Holy Hand Grenade was
wasted
rip no wait to do something about them
no go for the lower ones they're so
nicely together come on they're play so
nicely
there bazooka might be good for this I
don't know
well we'll we'll
try uh I don't know wait what about
grenade what does the grenade do try it
just got to pray that it lands well oh
oh
[Laughter]
yeah we're we're the same oh dear we're
the same bakas ready all right never
give us power to get out of
here listen never thrown a grade grenade
before
okay where should I go I'll CH over here
we're giving them the win so that they
feel better about themselves how sweet
how
considerate you need to win m is joining
the Rissa Haven can someone take that
egg I want to know what it does I don't
think you can take it can you maybe it's
what egg maybe it's for like collections
outside of this game
general not helpful now there's a egg
like on top of the
sign on top of the sign oh that's my
corpse what do you mean yeah oh my go
you return to
egg yeah oh you found a nice place
there hey yo she's she she's hidden in
the tower
[Music]
crackers oh I still have a
Teleport oh where are you going to
move I a Nissa stay away from
me don't worry I'm going to stay up here
oh you can see what it looks like when
you're in there
a
okay back to oh my goodness that would
be the perfect time for someone to bomb
the top of it am I right
no well me and Kiara there why are you
asking for that you basically have the
chance of a double kill you're just
hoping that it will only land on me and
not on
you I mean I could no never mind Jo them
no I don't want to
I'm gonna move yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'm gonna go to leave qu alone
here like yeah a little bit more oh
yeah Love's too short to be alone wow
Love's too short to be alone sweet uh-oh
oh Jews it's over oh Jewels
no another one drowning in the waters of
sharks shark food uh what do I got let's
see
uhuh what's this
one y jet pack you can do anything so
don't worry missile I don't know if it's
going to work H you want to fly or you
want to shoot whether or not you Tred to
no I want oh oh oh no do you think I'll
reach that high uh I think
so we can find out oh wait a shoot come
on
there we go all right I hope she messes
it up no she will not mess it up ah she
knows
no let's see how it goes no just don't
fall into the water
waa Flawless sprinkly water why
why I think I only have one worm left
do slow down the well
okay so let's start by holding up a 1in
brush with ceran blue Roger what are you
going to do
Roger uh I don't
know how do I
undo anything how do I just
move
go yeah oh it do be like that a lot of
the
time yeah where it's just full of um I
didn't mean for that to happen
um wait
don't look at that gate open start just
standing at the Ed Health though awful
shame if someone just pushed pushed him
off the I'm
sorry homing missile you don't have a
homing missile w i don't
oh you should focus on the people on top
okay for you but I don't know if I still
know how how it works oh wait maybe here
wait where did n's go in the
to oh up
okay
woohoo oh wait so R also here oh no
goodness oh now I have two wies here
yeah now look at you I'm sorting
everybody to where they belong
oh oh no no no no w
you got lucky oh my God want be here
alone she that was all on purpose of
course no wa I took you out
completely you killed her I'm sorry I
even
l no no
no okay yes yes yes yes I could take out
two people yeah leave them
alone they're right there almost dead
avenge me even though she did nothing to
me how could you it's fing so
beautifully you might still win don't
you have one in the tower
oh yeah one in the
tower okay your I'm probably still going
to go out next um y
bye-bye oh God byebye Jules okay Gavin
Gavin is barely
breathing he I feel like the moment I
move I'm going to drown I think you're
just going to drown it's not your turn
it's okay it's okay how do I use a
honing missile I don't see
it do you have do you have it in your
how would I not have a Hony everyone
else gets one why wouldn't
I yeah yeah yeah you have it oh there we
go yeah oh Nissa you win you win Nissa
but make sure to go up with W yeah yeah
yeah little bit away from the boat yeah
win should
work you had to charge it sorry
oh we we we learned by doing I to so
[\h__\h] up good
job let's go okay can you do something
about this get you you're in there do
you I don't even know where you are
you're hidden I don't even know where I
am she's like I don't know if I should
go up there under the roof like around
the first uh Bell have yeah she got she
got inside the yeah yeah but I can't do
you have a bunker Buster no I don't
no I mean can she get I could have
bunker Buster her but you are on top for
the tower so I couldn't I'm like I want
to go to the top of the tower but
narissa you might have something that
could get me oh maybe maybe can you
craft it we're running out of time but
there's a crafting window I don't really
know how to work either I don't think I
can I can't uh I'm just going to [\h__\h]
come on man um I'm going
just I mean you could also get me here
so might as well might as well yeah just
get higher just get high higher yeah
might as well quickly oh I messed it up
oh I messed it up oh dear oh it's over
it's over for me I messed it up I
pressed the wrong but no it's not over
yet maybe she has
nothing where is how how deep in the
tower is Nissa she's just like below the
roof I think um what you
got do you have a good question what are
you going to do I'm just looking at the
tower right now um I know no 50 HP
honestly you might still survive a shot
unless you fall into the
water I don't know she what does she
have she doesn't know
either oh oh what what be careful be
careful oh there she
is I don't know what I've got I don't
even oh oh she she got something
interesting that oh what's that what's
that oh oh what is she going to do what
is it what is it what she going do no oh
I are
you if you learn she still Liv was time
I'm an idiot is what I am I don't know I
love you as an idiot it's entertaining
I'm so stupid same same girl apparently
I have to charge it I feel like we were
all something happen she's still going
to win though we were all doing the
tutorial higher than me no oh we're like
about we're actually about like the same
you're a
little or do I teleport to the
top a I mean that's a very good question
I feel like I'm going to fall off if I
teleport to the top yeah maybe cuz I'll
teleport no no with a jet pack maybe
sign or the top I want to
okay my gosh why is this so weird skill
issues oh my my mouse okay here all
right here cunning
o bro we're going to list the colors
you'll need for this oh my oh what do
you have left that could help
you that oh what's that you trying to
teleport she's going to teleport next to
me I I think it's a weapon I don't think
so or is it oh it's a Teleport she has a
teleporter out oh she has a teleporter
out well but then you're kind of asking
to be pushed down next turn yeah I
know it's easy now oh my you can even
use a baseball bat so that you don't get
like by The Recoil shot you don't get
the AOE you'll get shot first my God
don't do
that oh my
God be real be real you're going be
freaking for
real gets two
win yeah look at movie
go I'm scared of her she's a buying to
be reckoned
with honestly wow wow w i that's pretty
good considering howow my damage was you
were in the lead the
longest yeah true but even in the
previous uh round uh whoever was in the
lead did not end up winning so true yeah
it could Anything could happen in this
game pretty much damn
wow did you that
was yeah I did I did this game's yeah
now that I understand the game is so
scary maybe I'm just like I might also
just you know you won every time what do
you mean I know so now might be uh you
know what's the word delusional that's
not the word but even when I feel like
it's almost more funny when you still
don't really know what you're doing cuz
we keep on blowing ourselves
up it's pretty
funny like even me and waya we kept on
like especially in this round we blew
ourselves up too much I just don't like
the water I just don't like the water oh
creeps up on
you so that was worms I I don't know the
early birds did we get the worm I think
we got the worm I I think so I got
definitely got the worm she got the worm
I eat worms I'm
in are you going to roast them or grill
them or boil them what are you going to
do I'm going to sell them sell I I buy
fisherman give me I'm hungry
they're only for fish what are you a are
you a fisherman I'm a bird I mean
fish is a fisherman yeah I am a
fisherman that be $3,000 yeah 3,000 so
much WoW I'll eventually pay them back
wow you can ask
you I believe you thank well that was
fun sorry it couldn't be the original
game but I think a lot of people
preferred this game anyway so I think it
good I like it yeah we're spreading the
violence fting us I'm glad to have you
my sweet Birds I love you all so much
yay bird of I'm glad we could play
together yeah yes me too I love birds
they're so cute they're so sweet you
know I was I was saying um this is
a an atsumi atsumi uh Gathering of birds
that speak English really well but
actually Rie and Super S by they both
speak really good English too so maybe
sometime we can have a six people six
people work yeah yeah oh my gosh it'll
be big there'll be a lot of screaming
cuz we already played it be fun we
played this game with subu before and
she screamed her heart
out I remember that that was fun let's
does yeah definitely thank you so much
for being here guys all of their
channels of course yall are subscribed
but they're in the description in case
you're not subscribed you have to in
case you want to unsubscribe no oh my
God no don't unsubscribe no that's so
sad but yeah support the birds support
the birds yeah support the birds so they
can get more worms yeah please I'm going
to go back to sleep so I can later play
Fallout you too I want to sleep yay yeah
I want to sleep but no stream for me
today well rest well everybody and do
you know what we say in
[Applause]
[Music]
German and in German we
say byee lovely lovely
[Music]