​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's Aq-tan!​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​What's she looking for?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mother's Day!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gratitude!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mother's Day?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Marine's Internal​ ​​
​​ ​Relationship Chart​ ​​
​​​ ​Mother​ ​​
​​​ ​Daughter​ ​​
​​​ ​So she's looking for...​ ​​
​​​ ​a Mother's Day gift?​ ​​
​​​ ​As in, a gift for me?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aw, shucks. 😊​ ​​
​​​ ​Loves Minato Aqua so much,​ ​​
​​ ​she's deluded herself into thinking​ ​​
​​ ​she's her mother.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mommy's so pleased.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep, yep, carnations are the go-to.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I'd prefer to be surprised.​ ​​
​​​ ​Last resort!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way, sketchy books?!​ ​​
​​​ ​How naughty.​ ​​
​​​ ​Spaghetti! 💦​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't understand adult fiction!​ ​​
​​​ ​She panics while​ ​​
​​ ​checking the books out,​ ​​
​​​ ​only to be denied with,​ ​​
​​​ ​"Miss, these are for adults..."​ ​​
​​​ ​I-I am an adult,​ ​​
​​ ​she says, indignant.​ ​​
​​​ ​But she can't hide the embarrassment.​ ​​
​​ ​It's written all over her face.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's willing to go so far for me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Squee! ♡​ ​​
​​​ ​Mom, check it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​You mustn't look at her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait! Not that store!​ ​​
​​​ ​Grapefruit​ ​​
​​​ ​Exploitative Work​ ​​
​​​ ​Shochu​ ​​
​​​ ​Soda​ ​​
​​​ ​It's only got stuff I hate!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are they haters?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew. Thank goodness.​ ​​
​​​ ​What are you doing?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, I can explain. 💦​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm watching over​ ​​
​​ ​my baby's first errand... 💦​ ​​
​​​ ​Hah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Unhand me!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am her mother!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, a gift catalog.​ ​​
​​​ ​That is fine, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's fine, but it'd feel a little distant.​ ​​
​​​ ​All good for family​ ​​
​​ ​who don't meet often,​ ​​
​​​ ​but we see each other all the time.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd like something that feels​ ​​
​​ ​a bit more personal.​ ​​
​​​ ​That said...​ ​​
​​​ ​Any gift that Aq-tan chooses for me,​ ​​
​​​ ​I would rate...​ ​​
​​​ ​a ninety-five. ♠​ ​​
​​​ ​How bored are you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ack! Aq-tan!​ ​​
​​​ ​You've been following me all this time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Busted...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll take it now, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​What you just bought for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​My Mother's Day...​ ​​
​​​ ​P-​ ​​
​​​ ​re-​ ​​
​​​ ​se-​ ​​
​​​ ​n-​ ​​
​​​ ​t!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not for you, Captain.​ ​​
​​​ ​Marine = Mother​ ​​
​​​ ​No way...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ur... Urk...​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaaaargh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah...​ ​​
​​​ ​M-M-Marine i-is...​ ​​
​​​ ​y-y-y-your m-m-m-mother...​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, I got this for you instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​You should've said so sooner!​ ​​
​​​ ​Happy ending!​ ​​
​​​ ​A heartfelt gift!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you enjoyed this,​ ​​
​​ ​please subscribe for more!​ ​​