e
oh
hello oh
y why do you guys have clothes I'm so
sleep I got not sleepy way yeah you get
like 150 coins in the beginning and one
shirt costs 50
coins so expens I have Z
coins well the 50 points that's nothing
look at the other prices those are way
more crazy this is the cheapest
shirt yeah or you can get like a little
fart Emoji thing no oh yeah so I'm going
to click on ready okay well uh is it
everyone's first time playing the game
yeah should we introduce ourselves or no
yes
okay
starting
from the player
order okay yeah okay we can we can
introduce ourselves while doing the
volume check then
yeah true
okay I'm not a cat I'm
hello hello hello
yeah sounds
good next one the one who says sounds
good
oh thanks for having
me did you just wake
up oh no I'm just sick she's
sick she sounds a little bit like
Mar oh my
God sounds like okay and next uh uh my
lovely this running bird
uh which one
uh yeah why why did you need to think so
long about that CU you both are running
I was choosing kiaha okay hi
Kik um I'm the kiaha I uh love ID girls
and I love am so this is like the best
party ever let's go let's
go so fucking loud let go let's
go
y next the one this yellow
bird wait who's yellow yellow bird oh
yellow
bird um how to how to
introdu um the the my soul you
go done
okay good day man my name
is from hly fight third
generation my
soul let's go have you had Brey
yet Brey done Brey nice
Brey nice Brey okay next uh Amy let's go
hello Watson
[Music]
[Applause]
detective we have a detective we have a
detective and we have a secret agent
very nice I'm
I'm barely a
secely misunderstanding of why is here
oh oh oh should we should we talk about
it should we tell him's going to tell
him funny who's going to tell
him wait can can we talk about it yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I I I reacted with an
emoji to the the invite of this CU I was
like oh shoot that sounds like a cool
game so I put a little POG a little cie
POG re and uh I wasn't expecting to join
but I'm here and I'm happy to be here
anyways we're happy the New Year we're
happy the New
[Music]
Year sign up but she's still here even
though she didn't sign
up she didn't sign up for this it was
really
funny yeah it was really funny cuz I was
like uh react if you want join and I was
like I mean pged so I was like let's
go yeah yeah makes sense makes sense
yeah okay uh this
is
H re I'm R
yay last but not least our sweepy sleepy
bird
oh did you just forget about me
Zetta
wow oh that's how it is okay
we how
even thought you
introdu okay
attention please thank you for your
attention miss
you now the real last but not
least hello it's Ana from Hol Live ID
second
generation
[Music]
yay wait um how do you change your color
can you change your color I think need
to
change yeah you look good perfect I mean
okay yeah it looks it looks good enough
okay yeah you're good
okay okay s
we don't have much time I'm thinking we
can do um you don't maybe one
uh games yeah want to classic
games and then we can try other stuff
like um the hide and seek or The Killing
Spree one I think
okay there's many different
modesa Sensei yes
is this um is this game like a certain
impostor game this call oh yeah yeah
something similar but
duck okay and Goose du but quack yes
wait which one go which one is the
Imposter the duck or the goose I think
the duck is the okay the goose is the
crew
mate I haven't very much I haven't
played either one du in the
tile I haven't play either so yeah I
haven't played either I couldn't up my
alarm also this is also going to be my
first
time sorry just in case I overslept
um yeah okay let's play I think
everyone's first time playing anyway so
let's play what could go wrong right let
what could go wrong oh okay three 2
[Music]
oh wait is this like proximity I think
it might
be
uh-uh wait is this proximity it is right
I I'm going to be honest chat I don't
understand
hello oh if you click on the test oh
navigates you to the it gives you likey
oh you're
righty
[Music]
let's see oh I can't go here I oh this
is so bad I don't know the directions me
too why does this why are you following
me cuz I don't know where to go fine
bye bye Zeta you hate me that much you
forgot about me first first you forgot
about me and now you you don't want me
to leave okay sure bye bye thought you
were H TP you you you hate me that much
okay no I
don't fine
fine can you oh my gosh you got walk
using your
cursor I don't
know H did you know that you can walk
using your cursor
using using your mouse I know oh you
know you guys know am I the only one who
didn't know okay I don't know even but I
mean it's not nice yeah it's it it's not
really
nice just use W
ASD yeah I'm I'm using W ASD
too there's
a
oh we doing
stuffs I think
we understand yes we need to
double yes
yeah okay
[Music]
okay
what
I
[Music]
what oh we were
lovers we
were was no
one okay okay we need the wait did no
one kill yet no one seem to kill just
trying to see what
yeah I think we can make the T long yeah
that was that was the task
longer I thought we would have more I
was looking for dead bodies cuz was I
was the vulture I'm supposed to eat dead
bodies but there were no dead bodies oh
my God what the
that um we do have um four versus four
right no cuz like two do and then two
two other people on the duck
side that's what I saw wait was there
four people I think the rolls for the um
the duck side is only two so oh wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait like a bow on the
victory I I was I was a vulture which is
not the duck yeah duck but a duck are
you guys supposed to help the ducks like
you're eating dead bodies that means
people won't find the dead no the
vulture is kind of doing their own thing
they just they don't even have to do
tasks but they also don't kill they just
eat corpses and if they get to eat
Corpses
they're just in for the they're just in
for the win yeah just for the food yeah
just I me dodo as well it's like jest if
they get out they win alone yeah I
thought that was supposed to be a skill
to help like the duck so that no dead
the um cuz when you're a duck you get
these like unlock this and that like
sabotage unlock blah blah blah do I but
yeah I've been trying to work that out
but I didn't get it yeah I didn't really
understand have to kill someone if you
want to sabotage oh so it's like
oh knowled I will bring Alis sen pie I
was searching for you we were
lovers you know you know what's crazy
the lovers role they didn't tell us who
the who the other partner is yeah yeah
don't know so we have to look by
ourselves just came out where's my
lover where's my lover
TR one more time okay um my task I I I
set the task list to be larger so I
think it should be fine everyone okay
let's go press ready ready up please I
am ready okay again
so I was thinking of um a
um in
gnosia like um not really not really the
imposters but they help the imposters
you
know I was thinking about
that so not really not an imposter but
not really the Villager
either I was thinking about that for um
kiaa rooll what was it game um everyone
is something actually
right yeah maybe oh yeah everyone is
something where are the
tasks I don't
know
yummy sorry sorry what hello no no no we
we were at the dinner table and we
didn't know that it means like a
mergency
go okay
skip
sorry wait we can't skip we have to
vot okay this is literally a skip ad
moment oh now we can skip
ad the
loed what what what does that mean what
does that mean I don't know what that
means everyone is safe everyone is
sa yeah I was pressing skip my cursor
doesn't show in
OBS so you guys can see oh my gosh where
do what do
I
please
what do how do I task
oh the yellow a guys where's the
entrance throw
bath yeah I think yeah I think I I'll
just have to wait right
I'll just have to wait um I want to go
oh I can go from this side I
think
what guys guys guys W happen the
theut yeah yeah you and Ollie went
upstairs right I went right and then I
saw it upstairs not upstairs the room
beside it uh
ohes okay so with me wait can you self
report this where can you self report in
this game yeah I don't know I don't know
I think it's either reported or Ollie
and
Kyla H but it wasn't KY because she just
got into the
room okay then but I don't
but how the hell do
we you just pressed the name I think I
just yeah I think I pressed the
name what oh my God
what wo
wo I think we don't know what we're
doing yeah
same
[Music]
oh it's
ready
hi hi
hi okay
um good
luck and you look sus
too
sure are you oh are you my
lover are you my lover are you my lover
are you my
lover no way are you my are you my
[Music]
lover don't we hate each other today
though I mean you hate no no no no
no a very popular Trope from hate to
love oh my gosh enemies to
lovers enemies to lovers stro no we are
friends to enemies to lovers okay okay B
we can do task together okay
okay hello rain rain it don't do you
know that we we became enemies to
lovers wait what yeah we went from
enemies to love you can kill anyone
right why are you guys why are you
screaming that I can kill anyone you can
kill anyone right just kill all of us
this M is so
only but sh kill me kill me kill me kill
can kill anyone right I think no a Sher
I I only I only kill
Ducks
oh I think it's KY she keeps ssing
everyone then can I kill Kyla yeah just
kill
mebody
don't kill me go let's go
murder do this the
murder I got
distracted
um
what what do I
um trust me I said I
trust
don't no one trust me before so you self
report it no one trust you self
report was staying lowy the entire
time did you actually report or because
I was Canadian so like I self report I
didn't report uh it's Auto
report I had kill the Canadian bre don't
kill the
Canadian I literally said that I I saw
wa and rainy together before that
happened and but no one me did you
yes I don't remember you saying it yeah
I don't remember you saying
it together so communic wait who who who
was the who was the who got the L roll
oh yeah I no not me wait what the what
the love was it was it you no I I'm
lovers with
you spicy so we got it
correct oh my go sorry my alarm keeps
ringing on okay so turn it off
girl a lot more faster than I'm trying I
have an alarm I set an alarm every five
minutes uh I'll turn it off okay so are
we ready how about we switch it up with
different rules okay okay yeah
M let's
see rise and grind Gamers I
think uh I think I think I think I you
think we can do assassin so basically
it's uh you can kill during meetings by
correctly guessing a role or die trying
that's
youry yeah during
meetings
M let's go let's go let's
go go I
likeing you scare me
woman guing around I'm
ready how that
uh okay let's go safe safe
safe okay so I opened the Wii and my
goodness there's so
many she she's just
fping
Canadian and then celebrity detective
engineer oh my gosh I'm I'm reading the
wey
oh
my body
outo oh okay the first time I
was
OMG it
counts oh God okay um I need to go
to
on the
grounds wait
no not the
grounds he you killed all the
rats
um was that what did you
say h did did you just say something
about
killing I said kill the
I just killed the
rats why is that a task because I I got
a
Tas self reports us might be
self-report no no no can can can you
explain okay where was the body where
was the body where was the body uh the
body is in the laboratory in the top
right labat
wow well me me and Ella we were we were
in the kitchen I'm in the kitchen me and
Zeta were very very far we were in The
West Wing yeah we were
inng it it was me no don't skip it was
me I self
don't oh it was you actually it was
me that's very sus that's a very size
what if she's
not what she
a um probably a
doo that very fast no so who who killed
he it wasn't me I killed yo
you're kidding you guys leave me so
easily I was like oh how do I make
myself like if I want to be kicked out
as a doo bird then I should just make
people think that I'm the sussy one so I
just say that's too s i i voted
Waton I also
voted she was
quiet how many times did dies s by got
the duck the go the the duck the duck
I'm voting you
next whatever happens we're voting her
out
first okay let's ready I'm
ready shopping
[Music]
clo
are
we are we are we yo yo yo yo are what
are you
me yes I am
Canadian oh a what are you oh are are
you
lovers I'm looking for my girl friend
wifeu wifeu your
[Music]
wifeu
[Applause]
[Music]
canadiano oh this is
still how do I do
this
[Music]
a hi hi hi hi hi
oh are you guys did you find did you
find your wife food Dan
it what what is
happening um
[Music]
so
from here from here is it sa I think we
need to fix the sabotage yeah true
sabotage
sabotage uh did you guys got it yes got
it oh I got it I got
it okay everybody have to do it I think
everybody has to do
it I did it I do it already wait wait
wait I think what h
what it's done it's done okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay I want to be with we byai
what what what why do you want to be
with Senai why that's and I want to eat
the body that's kind of ss
oh oh
okay dust Dusty dust you wa why you just
standing here about me yeah why why am I
standing here I was doing this task with
the the skull oh what T there's so much
dusting it's just a dusting there's so
much dusting oh
okay fun fun
fun
hi oh I love this
taskell I love this task cleaning the
it's putting the oh you're cleaning no
no I'm putting the pouring the water in
oh yeah you're putting the water and
then it's going to be it's going to be
wild here later yeah when it fills up
uh-oh
oh no no two people
gone show
people is
this piano room I'm voting re Senpai no
matter what room why it's re Senpai I
mean she became she
became I gu
reent because she's always
it nah this just my luck that makes
sense but are we voting I I vot I voted
me something but
I oh no oh
no what if she isn't
it no no no longer wanted that's so sad
that's so sad
no
how do I do
[Music]
this she's following
me
nice oh
[Music]
see I'm
innocent I kept low profile never
[Music]
TR Rea only died cuz she was a lover
with me I was killed and Rea died with
me so romantic this so
Roman wait that's not true I murdered
you
K yeah you did you did but waya died
with me because you murdered
me yeah so you guys know
that
and okay let's do something
really
stupid let's
go stupid stupid stupid something stupid
something something stupid something Dum
something
what
about what
w I heard oh how about a detective round
I
hope detective do detective you can
investigate players to see if they have
killed that round maybe too op maybe too
op okay never mind to op to
op okay I can we we can go with st walk
ER basically you can track one player
that's my turn
okay again you scare me
woman I'm ready by the way
ready
[Music]
okay
ah oh
God
[Music]
okay
hello we do our
stuffs yeah do the stuff and then why we
why we walk we doing task no you're the
one following
me no you're following
me you're
following very sauce okay
fine where where where do you want I
don't think what where do I want to go
go right why why do you want to follow
me you go right I go I go left okay you
go left I go right what you're the one
who follow me who's following
me I I would like to deduct a few
things I thinkla might be a stalker so
she's not a duck what okay I'm I'm the
stalker Ollie and it's kind of
useless oh never mind call her
useless what no no I'm saying the
stalker roll is kind of useless cuz I
like I don't get much from it I feel
like does it like do you win if you
successfully stalk someone what does it
do Molly why are you blaming me I'm fing
you no no no protecting you was trying
to call no I was trying to
like
never yeah nice
[Music]
deduction wait everyone is safe
for what does dodo do
again what does doo do
again
[Music]
interesting she's
gone
[Music]
No don't touch me don't touch me
what wait wait wait wait wait wait what
wait what what's going
on minute I what I was cleaning a
picture and Raina ran past me and I
heard her and then I was done cing the
picture I was going in the same
direction Olie was going with me and we
both saw the body kind of at the same
time I was like what the what what what
well for sure it's not aelia
inp de Z is also dead oh you guys
are what why why would
who where was everybody where was
everybody where were you
huh you tell me right nowson tell me
where you
were I was with
ol she was with me I was with ol I was a
vol no no before that I was the
whole going on what's
Happening oh shit no stop you messed up
big
time you guys messed up big time
[Music]
why you are so close you were so close
but you were telling the truth no fight
I knew you were the do do you were so
fast sorry wait what do do again
needs to get voted but all I got the
people right
the
yeah yeah but I still wanted to win so I
voted for
myself I see crazy that is so
sad and you didn't win I'm so mad for
you let
okay is kind of
unnecessary mhm okay the stalker
roll um yeah yeah this one instead of so
I'm exchanging the lover duck to um
Hitman duck and bodyguard Goose so The
Bodyguard gets a bonus for protecting a
player wow but the Hitman gets a bonus
for killing them I don't know what the
bonus entails though how to
the
same I feel like the discussion time I
feel like the discussion time is a
little bit too
short yeah to be honest okay okay okay
okay agree discussion time that was 30
seconds how about um how about uh 45
45 okay yeah what from 30 to 45 from 30
to yeah the options are only 30 45 60 oh
okay okay 16 yeah can okay 6 okay let's
go
16 okay okay I need to write this down
mhm let's go okay so let's go instead of
mimic I'm using the detective so
detective can investigate players to see
if they have killed that round okay mhm
okay we can try that one okay let's go
okay what bye-bye byee bye
bye
[Music]
um
what
oh
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
what wow that's so fast that was fast
that's so fast wa
is it self report is is is it like
automatically reporting no um I report
it it was at West
Wing it went to West Wing West Wing can
you actually see the map oh you can yeah
you can see the
map hallway I didn't see anyone it
wasn't Wawa Wawa is safe thank you it
was why do you know that was pretty fast
I'm safe too it pretty fast last time
the last time I saw someone mhm In The
West Wing is actually
Ru yeah because
wasaa and then I don't I don't think
it's
Ru from
hwayi you're from
[Applause]
hwayi stud library and then yeah it's
it's it's a long way from from hallway
to West Wing who are you guys voting for
um I'm I'm skipping me I'm skipping
you're very
Qui only kind of
s is
it she still she's still safe oh okay
okay okay okay wait if if I have if I
have to protect this by does that mean
she's automatically not dark or is there
like a possibility
that
hi I need to hi hello goodbye hi bye
please I need to be with
you please marry
me what the
[Laughter]
fuck okay you know I'm going
okay humping the
pillow
nice what it looks like it looks like
one it looks like I'm Hing a
bow where's where's the lights I don't
know
oh no
boss what the heck we're trying to fix
the light I think oh oh oh it's fixed
nice nice almost a stack kill I see I
see how it is I think Ollie might be
dodo
again what is she's saying stuff she's
she's yapping in purpose that girl girl
she's yapping in
purple I
again what do sheing
about no idea no idea wait can we say
our
roles like the others I mean if it's
it's it's a good one yeah sure okay what
are you Ana is the the protect the
protecting one oh wait wait
wait come wait wait wait do
not I think it's Wawa
why because actually
there's
food food
oh
oh I was about to report that cuz I I'm
the medium I can't see it I see wa going
around and there's a corpse around where
waa left yeah I was with
Senpai wait yeah the whole time don't no
don't stick it on me I'm the medium I
can see the dead bodies I was about to
go back to the dining room to report
because I just looked at my medium thing
medium it CH me it shows me uh like uh
there's a countdown every once in a
while I can press shift and then I see
how many ghosts there are and for the
longest time it was just one from the
last round and now I just after my task
refreshed and I saw two so I was in the
studio doing the the base or something
string connection and then just around
the corner is a dining room where you
can report right so I don't know where
the body is but I went to the dining
room to report you going back and forth
that was I no no I saw you going back
and forth as well so don't stick it on
me now you you two were together and you
were probably thinking oh we can stick
on W if I kill someone no I'm the med oh
my God I S God why
is wait be killed again actually I
wait how how good did I just explain how
the medium Works only you got the wrong
person it's going to be bad okay okay
I'm not sure
yeah I'm hungry I swear me
too the of the dinner why would you do
that why would you
you she no we sa okay yeah you
better oh no we're separated and I
forgot about doing T what am I
doing huh excuse me
hello what the throw out
trash
um I think it might be
raining I think it might be
raining yeah I think it's raining though
cuz Ki KI was trying so hard to defend
herself I don't think I don't think it's
her then that that just eliminates the
other
no these ducks are too
clever I don't have the
heart me me and Senai we were on me
it was so funny seeing run away from
rain she didn't say anything yeah we
figed out a little bit too
late cuz like meai we were wait you were
dead I'm sorry
gooes
ohing okay okay I think
uh how about out we try since it's been
our help but we try different uh mode
yes sure we can
try okay what about this hoot and
secot H and SE the owl must with NPC to
complete task to win the game spotters
and snipers work together to identify
and kill the owl to win I don't know how
many owls there is that sounds much
anxiety
what about Goan go Goan might be like
better like hide and
seek the
tag okay want to try
G okay let's can complete to reduce the
timer or choose to hide oh okay okay
there's a similar mode in um in uh Among
Us I mean we can try everybody runs
really fast we can try try the other
otes too after this yeah something I
think we can try the goose hunt first
and then we try a different one after
this yeah okay okay should be a quick
round let's
go go who's the
kill you know what at least I won once
today as an imposter duck is who's the
duck not me oh hello so you're not the
duck I'm not theck
dog are you the
dog oh
no do we have to do tasks I think we
have
to no ol task I think
I inter
it's not that
buddy no no no don't don't come close
this isn't by no not me
no what's her it's
her no it's her
we need to do the
task man what the
heck oh God oh God oh
God
hello no no
theask I was doing my
task who's left how I was doing my
taskit we can still do the task yeah we
can still do the task we can still do do
we have to do the task like that that's
so hard I think so yes yes yes no way
you have to because it
will
so oh my God what getting the DU I don't
know the task is too much the task is
Tas is too much the task is too much
okay for this game yeah yeah also I
spawned where arisu spawned in the
beginning so I
was
no what are the odds of spawning with
the killer man oh we can't adjust the
task it's like set I know it wasn't time
so the moment Ru immediately came to
chase us I was like oh no don't don't
come close to
me Z is like what what Z was like what
not me no I was isn't talking
about I thought he was I thought he was
Zeta but then Zeta
died why I did nothing thing okay um
there's this one called Trick and
Treat so villagers complete tasks to
call meetings and then vot out the
monster to win so it's like we're wolf
right the monster wins when everyone's
been converted to a throw I don't know
what a throw is like vampire I I
love okay basically we do task call
meeting vote out the SS
one ready ready ready
ready I'm
ready oh God no don't come near me don't
don't don't come near
me okay how do we stop people that's
that's the true question that needs to
be asked cuz I want to stabby stabby you
know this is the book you're looking for
the art of finding
things
[Music]
what's a th hi I don't know I don't know
English
Kyla it's
Kyla is it
Kyla
oh
no
no how do you how I guess I'll just into
Z how do you how do you do this what I
don't know how
[Music]
to oh my God what the what
the I don't know um was the studio
restraining Theos oh my
God I have haven't seen anyone I haven't
seen anyone but wa wa but she was just I
don't think I wa or anywhere
e
immediately
Goodbye Oh
no have an intervention about
bullying I
no I guess that makes sense you get
bitten by werewolf
you hi you buy you got turned into
one you
know that was a perfectly cut gasp from
Zeta did you guys hear that
[Music]
oh it was so hard to figure out I didn't
know what I was doing but I guess I
won thank you my little vampire babies
you're
welcome convered all of them well not
all of them but most of
them
wow that was fun that was
fun wait so what can the th
do kill the
other conver the vampires turn into like
zombies so they're kind of like yeah
like
zombies but even when I clicked like the
Turning thingy it didn't happen
immediately it takes a while I guess
until they turn
into oh did it happen immediately for
for the others for the ones for the fs
who converted other normal people you
know what I
mean I don't know let's play let's let's
play one
more last one whoever becomes the
vampire good luck just try pushing
everything
okay okay
okay you can't stop those zombies right
how do you how do you oh
space it was space
Spanky
what SP
[Laughter]
what
uhoh SP
what oh my God that sounds scary oh my
God no rain are you you're noted
right wait no no no no no I'm sorry what
oh this is yeah this is
emergency uhoh
yo what the
fuck okay I don't think it's raining
what I don't think it's Ana either yeah
I don't think it's raining so it's
either Ru or waa G I
vote I had enough being
voted Le I understand it's okay I
wouldn't vote you either bullying is not
okay I'm I'm I'm gonna be a bully today
and vote ru
shit I going cuz you were you were
talking about spanking
something that's that's my
job
again no oh no I wanted that no
rain
oops yeah kiar sounded like she wasn't
trying she wasn't trying so hard to
defend
herself which was which was
s which was s
see see you got to trust me I'm always
Hest I don't know why it gave me vampire
again I told
you wa why spicy time I tried to stop
but it didn't work for some reason
spicy
why W you talking about then what was
that it's because I need to fluff the
pillow oh I had to do
that out for
blood one more
please please do do we still want to do
the previous one or a new one try a new
one new one okay what about this taste
like chicken
social deduction Battle Royale protect
your team's chicken and kill everyone
else what do you mean social deduction I
don't know
deduction duck the duck duck is this
like
[Music]
PVP I Battle
Royale yeah I think it's like it's like
Battle Royale I think you're supposed to
protect yourself one one man for their
own okay okay protect your chicken ready
[Music]
up ready ready
ready nice ready ready protect the
chicken prot protect the
chicken you're a chick who's not ready
let's see everyone's ready everyone's
ready right why can't I start the game
try again try again are you ready I'm
ready I'm ready I'm
ready are you ready wait
maybe here okay up
again
ah maybe we need a minimum amount of
people to
stop
maybe then maybe which want which one to
play then we okay we can try the um we
can try this one this one hoot and seek
maybe okay yeah let's go okay okay let's
try whatever this
is let's go let's go have to take down M
even though she's not
here
represent I can't start either I wonder
why that's so
weird ready and then ready maybe we can
I I I'm ready and ready already um yeah
me too I just did it I also
did
um
weird let me try again sorry let me try
again no
problem maybe if the room is restarted
worst case I think the only like you can
ready um if it's like classic my button
lit up when it was classic but other
molds I don't think like
[Music]
can what you guys want to try
draft sure so draft draft is like the
like classic but like you can pick your
rules
now that's so
nice let's
go I don't know how to okay so
let's oh you get a GTAA oh you get a
Guta
oh what what
[Music]
this you get to choose first okay you
need to win the Goa there's a vulture
why would you choose vulture out of all
things I um I mean I'm I'm picking I'm
picking whatever this wa can we see what
the what the duck the goose the duck
also chooses them duck yeah I think we
can choose we can choose everything like
we can see
[Music]
everyone's
eat living the life of Goa to the does
show a fake one maybe for the maybe it
shows fake one it doesn't show people's
names or what player they are yeah yeah
it doesn't show
like I guess technically we can just
like guess which one is
which W A lot of people pick random I
didn't ni sh reading I was reading
sheriff
sheriff damn it I wanted to be
Sheriff then K Sheriff no
no
okay hello
hello don't kill don't kill me please no
I'm going to do my task what are you are
you waiting to kill
me no you see I'm uh I will only kill if
someone else is
dead
okay wait how do
what yeah how how does this one work
wait what how does this one work oh no
someone's dead someone's dead someone's
dead some on us stay with
me okay don't worry I got you you can do
the barbecue I'll I'll be on the lookout
okay why how do you do
this I'm not sure it's the one with the
lid right yeah it's the one with the lid
and like you try to light up for fire I
guess the doors are
opened how how how
did how do I do
this
help
oh this is the box but then it's not
it's not doing
anything oh there we
go how do you do I to be angry about it
um you just you just use it like how you
vot with um
uhoh
hi oh I didn't even see a body so I
don't know why it
uh I actually don't know is it where was
the body where's the body I don't know I
didn't see it I think it's selfreported
I'm the sheriff so I can't oh you're the
sheriff so the what role wait so um
where were
you and I was in the hallway by the
laboratory okay I think Zeta Zeta came
from above from the hallway and said hi
was it you Zeta H yeah it was it though
yeah Ollie you hurt her right you hurt
the high
right two people did West Wing no way
you came to the kitchen there's only
there's only no I was in the wng from
the kitchen I was in the
wng I came in no you said hi to
us well one thing for serious not Ana
because I was with her the whole time
yeah I was with Ollie the whole time so
it's definitely not wait who wait who
who who tell me tell me tell me
I the loop IED
myself
no goodbye Zeta goodbye
Zeta well
that
what did I tell
you
me you should have not killed me I
actually don't remember saying hi
what I don't remember saying
hi not kill
me you my
helper didn't you hear hi didn't you
hear someone saying hi maybe it's no but
I did saw Zeta oh you didn't see Zeta I
heard a
hi I mean I said hi to
everybody she was singing where you dead
Ru I was dead yeah you were dead yeah I
killed my
helper yeah it wasn't you then if you
were dead cuz it was right before the
the body was found I heard
[Music]
yeah that was fun though the
was can we do it again yeah the drop the
Dr yeah let's do it let's do it again
let's
Go's
go I swear to God someone said hi Chad
you heard you
heard I didn't hear a
hi no CU you were the one who
she was in front of my
eyes why would you
pick that's so freaked up who picked
vter he's sick sick being what does fure
do
again
bodies I like this
one then you're a party you win then
that's use it
wow Z
dang what does
party detective nice oh detective it
looks
like Batman
Batman we will never
[Music]
know
cute
[Music]
okay so
what my room they won't kill me
because a why why are you following
me
hello we go to the
studio
are they okay kind of sze if you ask
me
what
H wait what
but isn't
this
what
hi hi hi
hi can you stay with me
okay yeah dinner oh
okay okay how do I oh I go to the D
dining room and sered
dinner there's a task that lets you serf
dinner H was together oh hello no h
wasn't together
hi okay I'm done
[Music]
okay oh God this oh my
God
a h together H
together wait for me guys wait for
mea H H is waiting I need to where's
Kyla Kyla was going to the upper side I
think without saying anything which I
thought was sus by the way even though I
said hi to her I said hi to her but she
didn't answer me with high back which
was say
back thank
[Music]
you I here I need the two of you there
you go Kyla where is
Kyla
hi sure
sure
oh she's spanking spanking you I have a
task over here so I'm going to do
thisas wor I'm watching I'm watching
yeah my task was over here you can
continue
yours I need reass
hiy reassemble pain oh wait I got to do
this one okay oh I got to do this one
the bath
oh I hate this one the the plunging I
don't understand how it works I've never
gotten this one
before how do it work what was that
s fire fire let's get
fire fire
fire uh
fire the kind of going to lie do we all
have to do it
coming it's
raining oh this how do
I oh
god oh are we
good what is this
blue is it indicating that someone's
dead
[Music]
no how do I go
there
oh
okay I we switch party party
party party
[Music]
party I lost sight of every thought you
were dead
no I'm still alive and
well I think went this way okay okay so
it's definitely not Holo right it's not
H it's not Hol
all I
saw wait
what what the fuck you wear a
vter she she was following you just in
case you died yeah I was hoping I was
hoping either of you guys would get
eaten or something so that
I it was hard cuz everyone was together
the whole
time yeah I I think having only one
imposter is hard it's so difficult yeah
it's really
diff there need to like yo let's be
together yeah there needs to be
too not making it better
though I'm ol accompany two of you yeah
a a
moment okay I actually you know what's
crazy I actually didn't know that party
was an imposter I thought party was just
like uh like the G just like just like a
just like a usess rooll I was like it it
only says something like you can give
someone high pitch sound during meetings
I was like sounds
cool what so you high pitch voice also
kill neutral Ro yeah I mean you can also
kill so I guess it will be hard for
villagers to like discuss with each
other because of the loud sound
maybe
I my R like if I'm not alone if I have
like at least I guess if I have at least
two people with me I can't get killed so
that's why I keep asking people people
to accompany me I was waiting for
someone to get
Le H was together the whole time it was
so difficult okay okay I think we could
possibly end it here maybe
yeah I want to play again sometime yeah
play play again some yeah this is so fun
it was so much fun thank you for making
the time to play together
than thank
you it was a lot of fun yeah thank you
thank you thank you I'm so excited to
see all of you in Japan soon for
FES then we can party
party party for
party
take care of everybody take care
[Music]
everybody good AO
good good byee
byebye
bye
[Applause]
by