[Music]
hello hello hello hello
Mary Mary among us Mary among
us
among welcome everybody to the uh
Christmas or Holan holid day Among Us
stream we have gathered here today with
so many lovely cute girls and we're
going to have fun choking and stabbing
each other
right sounds kind of
fun let's go awesome well we're going to
um do it without proximity chat by the
way guys uh because you know we have
some first timers here I think it's
Advent girls's first time among using
here first timers
that's we're not such yeah we'll find
out how they act when when they're
impostor we can't tell yet like for
others maybe we already know a tell but
for these newbies we don't know what is
their tell maybe that's maybe you could
tell us would you be so kind in your
introduction to tell me what your tell
is
please nah you got to find that out that
information is classified need a little
cash money up front first try well okay
then let's start with introductions
let's start with the only one who's a
real astronaut here
Amy uh hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play let's go let's go can
we maybe there's some new viewers at
this point who don't understand why is
am able to wear her own clothes in the
game and why am I wearing P
clothes am do you want to explain H yes
we have H we had a collab with Among Us
where you could get a few uh Hol live
outfits and items in the Among Us shop
but I don't think it's available anymore
it's kind of a
time too bad if you missed out me and we
are p right
now I thought this was a keyboard slam
you guys are actually you guys are in a
room okay oh yeah wow okay I thought you
just slammed the keyboard
here keyboard slam I know that's what it
looks like code looking like a slam Oh
no you're giving them hints you're
giving and slam welcome to the slam jam
please join
than fer who is C spam who that is
all right well I guess that's
[Laughter]
Mor have spam color
too yummy what a Spam color that was
amazing nice box oh while we're at
Callie's uh you know bullying her for
her name Callie please introduce
yourself so we know that's really you
all right oh yeah if you insist me it's
me Mory Kai hold life English is
hardworking Shinigami Des
uh I'm in a place with very terrible
internet so I can't stream my POV but
I'm very excited to be here with all of
these lovely ladies as the sheriff
completing my tasks and making sure that
we win the day let's go yes he wouldn't
kill anybody and she is now known
as calm
SP I
guess but yeah I'm so happy you're
joining even though you can't like
stream properly thank you so much the
dead beats they trained me well I wanted
to show off my new skills that the dead
beats yeah
with members fairly recently oh we got
to watch out she's good at the
game thanks the dead be didn't you just
ask us how you kill people in this
game okay I guess that didn't help at
all that you played it recently it was
unhelpful well okay moving on to fun of
where is she where is she I can't find
her I'm in hiding you can't vote me as
the impostor if I'm hiding right
there is from H live English promise
hello hello I'm here does it feel does
it feel like normal now like it still
feels weird to me to hear that
introduction
promise yeah so fresh still it is it is
still pretty fresh but I like it I think
it's boat yeah not boats I feel like
everyone's been traumatized by boats
recent
what's with this current Trend in the
whole life English of watching school
days what's going
on last
why about the tree there's a family St
[Music]
the why like it there's a staircase did
you know there's a staircase I know
there's a stair I know
Nowa I have no idea what these girls are
talking about good I'm so
confused it's too cursed nice that
everybody is having fun school days and
all that it's fun a jolly season it is
great piece of Cinema yeah all right
Iris our number one Christmas lover
hello yes you're number one Christmas
lover here hiis it's Iris from H live
English promise
your uh I love this game but I I I
really suck at being imposter but yeah
so so yosu yeah but I'll do my best are
you really bad at it I don't remember I
I was horrible at imposter last time I
played this I screwed up she gets
imposter maybe you just need a better
mate to work with cuz you're dumb d m oh
[\h__\h] faceit of a poopy
head I think there's no what you talking
about the lobby will fall apart it's no
problem let's take our
time
okay by the way have you guys speaking
of Iris have you guys all seen the
yesterday and today's episodes of the
Holo Ian Advent calendar cuz Irish was
very involved in them I was very
involved in them
yes and they were both in 3D
oh out into space yep so Iris why did
you do it uh oh it's cuz you know we
needed some light to bring up the
Christmas spirit you know mhm what
better light than actual fire right yeah
oh that makes sense and you know it was
my whole plan so that I I could become
the Christmas tree in order to become
the Christmas tree you needed to burn
the actual Christmas tree
first about burning Christmas trees
that's kind
of it is the master plan it's pretty
late
yes
very it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire like the fire fire like the
fire fire fire like fire okay uh
everybody's uh joining in again in the
lobby I think I'm coming I got my name I
freed C spam he doesn't exist
anym she's real no more C spam I'm sad
is going to hide the code if I have
streamer mode
on yes yes it's hidden for me it does
hidden people self introduction please
Hi H bomu I'm clu sparkling Gem of Hall
life English Advent and today I'm a
space Rock but that doesn't mean you're
allowed to Stellar Stellar me out of the
ship so I am not sace I am nice
wow okay that was pretty good you give
me nice us
no no that doesn't work here doesn't
work
here a man so you have to prove yourself
prove the truth you can't fool us people
you're sus dang already you're already
sus already why are you
doing I think I think it's her yeah I
think it's good guess ISO it's
definitely okay let's move on to FCO
please I'm H I'm H
I'm together
we your voice okay
moo sometimes I become a dragon
sometimes you know but as long as you
know I'm not Chihuahua I'm not Hua I'm
there we go yeah and together we make
the best crew mate you know G dogs a
good crew mate not kind unfair it's kind
of unfair oh yeah if you imposter it's
two two of you
[Music]
guys I think I think we should vote them
out right away every
time kind
of well let's not do that but indeed as
a crew mate they might be very helpful
cuz it's two brains for one I guess I
guess who who's on the keyboard who's
controlling contr I'm the legs you're
the brains I'm also the the pointer
finger yeah nice looking forward to
the that'll be nice to see one one day
they will play separately but today is
not the
day isn't this game on mobile and maybe
somebody could play on mobile
I on the work I is connect really
doesn't work on this
side well okay and then
please an imposter hi
darling adish diva is Raven Coss cute
I'm an impostor today because I'm
pretending to to be money I guess
so yourself oh my God fake it till you
make
it we're we're a nice couple n so aren't
we how ironic be running away from
you I don't want your child
narissa even if honey Works made a song
about our child I don't want
it okay okay and
then
please this is
oronia from H live English Pro what Hol
live English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I almost never get it so
you can trust me I believe her trust her
100 TR yes I trust her 100% I trust
everyone 100 what are the chances that
say the truth I look so kind pretty high
none of none of us will get imposter
probably yeah probably none of us yeah
that's how it works how many how many
imposters are we doing I set it to
two we're
nuty I don't know should I two I don't
know
might good two is good
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what the common
tasks were that's
suspicious why you you don't remember
yeah oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been too long add rolls
or something right like you can do stuff
now or
something like roll
roll oh yeah wasn't there something
besides crew mate now like um uh
like the Imposter like the Spy or
something like
that's SCI keep them on that's fun okay
yeah I don't know how does that work
though I don't I've never played the
beginning yeah there's four rolls there
I don't know you girls can probably see
them in the settings uh on the on the
computer here there's scientist who can
access a portable vitals panel so they
can check at any point of time if
there's somebody dead so they always see
the status of the crew and then there's
an engineer who can use the vents even
though they're not an impostor but then
you might be sus you have to be like I'm
not the impostor I just vent because I
can oh that's pretty cool really and
then the guardian angel uh is the ghost
of the very first one of us that
dies uh is that how it work works the
first person that dies yeah something
like that the garden it says the ghost
of the first Dead crew mate they can
temporarily shield and protect other
living crewmates oh yeah so I guess if
you're the first one that dies you
become the guardian angel and then you
can protect somebody else so that don't
die yeah if you do it properly and well
timed you'll be able to prevent
imposters from killing their victims
sounds amazing me throwing so that I can
become the guardian
angel
a already are yes
no and then there's a shape shifter who
can who can change the appearance and
disguise themselves as other crew
mates why would you do that though that
just confuses everyone just makes the
Imposter or they're make the Imposter
harder to find too because then you know
the Imposter can say I'm the engineer
and oh no I'm the shap you know like
please I promise I'm not a murderer it
doesn't say that sh
but why would why would why would a crew
mate do this I don't know why would went
off but I like the other ones yeah
should I should I keep them or should I
I think shap shifter is
impos oh it is okay yeah it just doesn't
say so so wait does only one impostor is
only one imposter The Shape Shifter is
that how it works oh I can set how many
there will be I can say is that how it
works I can say want two or I can say we
I want one or zero I can set it in the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too that we have one for sure
oh default is good right it's probably
B okay okay default then let's keep the
rolls then let's go we're going straight
tood
before
we before we go um can we have the
visual tasks off because if we have it
on it might be too easy visual tasks
off
true very good okay and before we start
I'm Tak I organized this thing the logos
and the thumbnails are commissioned by
me so no
problem
don't kill me because I I paid for this
okay don't kill
[Music]
me byebye byebye
byebye will somebody forget no they old
mut [\h__\h] it's PR usual oh this is the
first time I'm on this map hi guys by
the way hi uh oh let's go let's get used
to this map I think now still everybody
will use the excuse that oh I'm new to
this I don't I don't know the tasks here
oh what what do you do here oh that's it
nice we
LIF nice oh three
times oh I'm finally doing my workout
with my new arms finally I'll I'll be
get rid of them what is
this what the [\h__\h]
what oh it's a fris spe that you have
what is that why do I
what what was that what was that why did
I have an animal and what the [\h__\h] was
going
on what the [\h__\h] was that I'm genuinely
confused uh what is this oh we just yeah
turn it on turn it on turn it
on yeah nice new map so far I like being
on the beach getting ready for the mes
not wearing my swimsuit yet though oh
wait how do you get to the oh you got to
go
below no
no I miss you the only real you guys KS
the only real astronaut you know what
that means we don't have a chance of
getting back to our own
Planet unbelievable so who saw Watson I
didn't see her at all I did I didn't see
her I all oh I see who who reported just
now me I did tell us about where you did
tell us about it where was the body so I
was going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms I went on and I went down
uh the the little zipline and then in
the storage room Amy was dead
room we around the Buro
yeah
saw right so F was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senpai was around and then crony
Senpai went down before the Senpai was
there too yeah yeah Moco was chasing me
around
I don't know what's going on I have
mushroom problem yeah I had like a meat
problem I don't know like I suddenly
turned into like a a lighter pink and
there was like a chunk of meat chasing
me was
that something new the puff and then
they CH into people or something like
that what does that do is that just an
effect to freak you out or does it do
something I know I don't know I think it
I think the the the mushroom like if you
touch it or something um it hides the
the people so you can just like kill
them and run away and they would be able
swaps my skin or something like
that it why you know that hot yeah yeah
my skin got swapped as well yeah me too
swaps the skin we came a wizard and then
I had a little worm next to me for a
moment and then poof it was gone and the
light was back
on but it was weird I I don't know what
what goes on in this map I don't know I
feel like I trusted cron s and now I
feel like I don't trust
crony I will say I passed by and I was
actually running away from crony cuz it
felt like she was chasing me I didn't
see you where were you you wait you
[Applause]
me
there she
Burn by
everybody okay goodbye what the [\h__\h]
that was brutal I don't know the fact
that she had like her own like
um oh oops oops oops I knew that would
happen to someone well that kind of
sounded like iris is not the Imposter
right uh wait how do you get can you go
up too from
here
use o
cute that's fun well that reminds me of
like when I was a child they had this
kind of stuff um where you it's like a
little little chair
ah I had a
feeling wa now I can tell you my story
uh where I had a chair uh it goes like
kind of straight like kind of like a
chair and it hangs on like something
like this and then it go it's kind of
like a zip line but not not exactly the
same thing like this one you know what I
mean did they find me oh they found
someone else didn't
they I think people found
we what wait the left couple died I just
saw Nissa like 5 seconds ago though
Nissa is in the South part a lab in the
hallway I don't know this
map um wait how do I look at oh I saw
narissa around like next to the
greenhouse when I Wasing
she's above the green
house I saw her walking around I didn't
see anyone near her I didn't see anyone
else yeah I only saw Nissa when we went
up to Communications and that was the
last time I saw
her you L she didn't see anyone except
the and I think she would scared us I
ran away instantly cuz I will be honest
I don't trust anyone who voted for crony
in the last round what seems like the
imposters were trying to get her out
because they wait wait
wa's
dead tell us before huh huh something
important when we're going to start yeah
to kill her oh yeah no to kill me yeah I
did tell them that they did
only us really oh that's true there's
two imposters still but crony could have
been an impostor though honestly like I
don't know
you guys turn off it doesn't say who oh
it doesn't say oh I wouldn't put it
behind her if she self-recorded because
look at her look at her um her icon like
she why why are you so suspicious of her
for no reason I don't know I feel like
you wouldn't be this suspicious unless
you were the impostor and you're sure
not I swear to God I'm not I I I I said
out right that I saw like narissa pass
by just 5 seconds ago before her death I
didn't
ITA I didn't see you though uh no I was
pass I passed by her when she was going
greenhouse and I I'm currently at the
meeting room I went the opposite
direction that's why I was like stuck
that beo and Irish Senai are suspicious
I think so too wait why I swear what
were you
doing I was walking around I was in the
L the L wait where's my the lab and then
Nissa was on like thep 10 seconds I'm vo
biu I
I don't have
enough swear it's not me it's not me
that's not enough right to kick her out
it
[Music]
is we get
him I thought we won yeah Tombstone guys
I told you excuse me you didn't even
notice I was dead
guys literally pass me and biu killed me
immediately good team self report good
team you two that was pretty
funny
tomb I was surprised well you know what
we learned from that because C was
pretty quiet SU the quiet The Quiet Ones
that's not theet fooled me Cy fooled me
too guess that's a strategy H I was just
confused cuz like my voting was super
rushed I was like wait wa wait why am I
suspicious all of a sudden everyone just
literally just the Spiderman everybody
pointing at each other no one in there
peer pressure peer we don't have to vote
if you don't know we don't have to
vote like
Iris out that was so weird I thought it
needed to be like majority vote to even
get anyone off I thought too I enough to
kill
me it was only a little bit of us left
so two was enough yeah people had
already
died we're strong at this H we're good
pretty good doing our tasks wen't you
the ones who
guys I guess we're S no matter what
can't be
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to be you know can we
turn extended voting time oh
sure yeah uh it's currently 90 seconds
should we do
120 at least yeah at least 120 120 is
the
max okay good yeah Chad says apparently
we can vote or skip the vote if you're
not confident like who it is
pretty
confident talking certainty there pretty
confident voting out all yeah I was
pretty
confident well now you now you know then
you maybe cannot trust your
confidence yeah true
enough all right then let's start
another
round even though this is really fun
here thank you cron for finding
see you on the other side bye bye see
you guys bye damn it oh oh but I'm
something cool oh the vents the people
going to sus me if I do that the
vents what is this pizza is that
pineapple no it's gold what do you
do
done what this a that's a vent what that
doesn't look like a vent oh I burned the
things or what oh I can make m
a marus
[Music]
marshmallows what what oh you can't even
take it away too early okay so you have
to wait until it's the right color and
then you can eat
it have you guys even seen this map yet
cuz to me I've only saw it saw it seen
it in like the advertisement the one
trailer and that's
it first time yeah maybe it's time for
another
amus memb only stream haven't done that
in a
while I love the slapping
sound uh yeah whatever this
was we hi hi
hi we're in the males
almost
uh
oh what's this ah it's emergency button
oh it's it's like a horn like a like a
seashell horn what the [\h__\h] is this
purple stuff oh it's dangerous
mushrooms this is actually so
difficult I always thought this about
this game this many
good nice nice 20 out 20 out of out of
20 I can't talk I need to go to this
right
side we need to remember the people who
we
meet why do I
scream why do I scream also that didn't
really what did that do to me I just
changed ah
maybe changing bodies is that just in
order to confuse people like that so
that they're not sure if they saw you or
not ah what did that do what does that
do much's
confusion
oh
no not again come on yeah come
on what all right I'll break it down for
you oh please what I did all my tasks
you guys could see me I think some of
you saw me watering things in the the
mushroom place I moved some storage
around roasted some marshmallows went up
to do my tasks in the communication room
and what do I find Watson dead middle of
the floor I didn't see anyone leave
though was anyone near Communications
recently where
isun you take a little like a what is it
a wire zipline
zipline I'm far for a little bit but we
didn't see much I just laders yeah I was
just in the jungle
area yeah I know there was there's like
oh oh okay these white white things are
okay yeah the line go up and down but
yeah I wasn't there yet um in the bottom
right
um there was a lot of shape shifting I
don't know who is who yeah there what
happened with that the mushroom is that
the mushroom stuff working on everybody
everybody got a skin shift right yeah
it's so that we don't know who is who
and then we can't prove like oh that
person was there or whatever but we all
look different like not like each other
right so it's not shape shifting yeah no
it's just the mushroom power m
is that doing it or is that oh by the
way I just want to say idea I haven't
used it yet but I am the engine pass by
a mushroom it does it
okay I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter just saying I didn't use it
yet I wonder recently was anyone around
upper engine Lookout or mining pit
because the impostor may have tried to
escape by going down the ladders I will
check it out I was walking that way but
I didn't see
anyone okay I've been down over in the
left area for the whole time doing my
tasks so I haven't even gone over there
Yeta I haven't been up there yet I have
tasks and communication like I was going
to go up I'm currently passing I was
passing by the greenhouse I was going to
go up but and then you didn't see
anybody run past no I didn't hard to
tell still at least hard to
tell yeah but people was kind of
quiet just saying actually bi boo passed
by me and didn't kill me so
me this is the first time I'm doing Tas
I can tell you I've been doing water
with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing and and I video game I
shot
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I do have t up
there okay we'll see we'll see evidence
inclusion but keep your eyes open
yeah maybe don't don't go alone don't go
around alone guys go with a
buddy we don't need a
buddy
together
m
[Music]
m okay wait I I never end up going where
or like reaching the point where I want
to go who's following me
cron so
she just likes me so much did you guys
see the ad K the video like went up like
uh six 6 hours
ago it's another Community reference
what the [\h__\h] is this oh Community the
sitcom the second one and I basically I
I chose the people like I chose Iris
because um like originally that that
uh character that she's
playing is like
sings like
really well and
like impressively so what the [\h__\h] is
this oh no please don't come kill me oh
this so I needed someone who can
uh sing really well so I was like I I do
you want to do you want to you know sing
for me be the tree be the Christmas tree
and then I wanted someone with like a
little bit of a a cool and like
questionable attitude so that's why I
went for crony for the other
one I knew she was innocent was the only
one she was a little bit suspicious
though she was I passed her going down
the ladders from communication to the
lower part
she Me Maybe one of the communication
where'd you find her so I was going up
the ladder to the communication and I
didn't really see her body but um I saw
the the vent which is the plant kind of
opening up and then closing so they
vent yeah they vented to wherever it is
from
Communications oh does anyone know where
where the vents from Communications
connect they can go anywhere right I all
the vents can only usually I don't know
in Old Maps usually vents only connect
to certain other vents I should have
checked and then I could have told you
but too bad no
idea I I can kind of say I think crony
is not self-reporting at least because
like I feel like I was I was running
around with her a little bit alone she
could have I saw you yeah and she didn't
and then I saw CI running around I think
we were alone for a little bit but she
may have been on cool down as well but
she yeah she was coming down from that
she was she was coming down from that
area yeah I told you I cross PS with her
oh okay but yeah and Cory said someone
[Music]
vented where were you a good question
yeah we were at the beach the beach
we're just kind of going around but we
don't really understand I don't know
what's going on in the map here we just
if you hit tab it'll show you where you
are oh tab yeah hit tab the map will pop
up there's also the map icon on the top
the map
icon yeah the top right a there's a
settings I see a map but I don't
understand it it has a lot of marks on
it yeah a lot of marks that is that is
it exclamation
marks h a lot of marks on ites it have
some x's on
it curious curious question you want to
Marks I mean I I don't see so many marks
on my map yeah what does an impostor see
maybe does a previous impostor want to
tell us what they saw like Callie yeah
call I saw some x's with circles on time
and i' click them
[Music]
sabotage a lot of marks on the
screen marks
I'm do you have anything to say to
defend yourself we're just doing with us
there wouldn't be so many marks on the
screen
would what happen
to goodbye do it I couldn't
[Music]
the I hope we don't regret that see you
later
okay oh that was funny because like
normally you can use it as an excuse
that you're not so familiar with the map
but in this case it was kind of um their
[Applause]
demise wait how do you what how the [\h__\h]
do you enter that a
from I think am I the only one who's
getting Shook at by this stuff I think
we need a
we need a a compilation of me getting
jump
scar oh com's
disabled wait where are my tasks didn't
I have oh this is a task uh what what
ah you sort it
out oh I hope foku will sort it out uh
whose fault was it that we found out
that they're the impostor
if they're imposters then actually we
have three Impostors not two whenever
they're
imposters yeah we need to fix this the
clums cuz I don't see where my tasks
are that's a
huge
okay does the other side also have to
activate it but what if what if no one's
there did I do my job oh hi Mory oh wait
you're doing that one and nobody's doing
the one up there I have to go
there all is it fixed oh it's fixed I
think yeah oh yeah here like this I
don't finish my
sandwiches cuz I don't know where let's
go I think I had to do this one too what
is
this what am I trying to find oh nothing
it's on the task
ah who who is dead cellie
wait I just saw her like yeah I saw her
too saw her too I feel like saw her body
right underneath the the
ladder the the left
ladder you can check the map you can
check the map and see exactly where the
green house like close to the greenhous
yeah wasn't she just with me at around
like yeah I saw everyone
Communications I was getting some stuff
done there and the and also the lookout
and then I went down and I saw her she
moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around there I'm in
the lookout right now I'm in the mining
pit I was around I think when everyone
was
around yeah we all went to
Communications home yeah everyone like
uh everyone
except uh who was it like R Rissa
and uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other
coms
um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you were
being just um you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stack killed but you
moved away from the the radio like where
everyone was trying to fix it oh that's
well you needed to go do the other thing
right to fix it I was the first one
there in the radio and I tried to put in
the code but I think you have to put in
a second
code yeah also I had two tasks that I
did in
Communications okay I did them cuz I was
I was in Lookout I was putting the code
in I think I was the first who arrived
and then nothing was happening so I what
I thought I would go to the other one
and I saw cie was like doing the code at
that point as well so she was like she
already arrived and then I left her
alone there and I was about to go up to
the other communication thingy but then
uh it was already fixed so then I went
back and I saw I think I saw crony again
or so but I didn't see FAA and I didn't
see Iris at all I saw youa I saw all of
you guys I don't know I know I saw all
of you guys the communications I was I
was
alone for a while and she didn't kill me
yeah I saw Nissa go down go down I
didn't I was going to the green down
where are you right now um I ended up in
the lookout because I got lost and I was
very
confused aren't we
all I'm a little suspicious of crony cuz
she didn't vote for Fu Moko she we have
no time running out of I don't know if
I'm enough to vote [\h__\h] yeah I don't
know I I I don't know either I'm going
to
skip you going to
skip skipping no
we good luck crew
mates skipping at that point I mean we
all had like no idea I guess but
skipping at that point feels
like you just want to you know continue
uh this
because it's going well right now
because the non- imposters have no
idea it's like going to your advantage I
shouldn't look at the map the whole time
cuz I don't see dead bodies at
all and this I feel like everybody gets
killed in this area it's really
bad yeah we should do a task win that's
the thing we should we have to do a task
f
oh wait that that that path is
uh what the [\h__\h] is
this what the I thought someone was
punching me don't kill me uh wait I need
to why did I do that I have to go up
here PA
paa could have killed me there couldn't
she but she
didn't oh
maybe I should use my venting skill
honestly and see who else was
venting should I be doing that where are
the
vents punch punch punch punch punch
punch
hello [\h__\h] late uh is this a vent no
wait the vents are this weird flower
thingies okay let's
see
[Music]
um cool is where and when you're in the
vent you and there's somebody running
around you should be able to see that
right it doesn't like hide it from you
right oh [\h__\h] didn't see
anybody are people all dead no I surely
HT give me emergency what is
okay I'm scared I think it's
her
uh hello hello hello I think Nissa is
trying to kill me ah you are so I can't
believe you I was not I checked
everyone's vitals and I decided to go
back to the meting area can and I saw
her and I got a little scared so I ran
back but then she chilled so I thought
it was cool but then she hit the
emergency meeting button much my
surprise no the thing is there's a
little bit of a backstory I was running
around and the only there's a back story
yeah my task what do you mean
backstory I was running around I was you
know I I I was running around crony
alone she didn't kill me I was running
around fauna alone she didn't kill me
and both of those I kind of fought were
sus and then I found you and you kind of
followed me and now I think if it's not
cron if it's not FAA follow you what do
you mean I ran into you and then I ran
back to the meeting area you are so fake
K I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either yeah even though she
could have and as I was doing tasks I
could have killed crony too and I didn't
which I would have if I had the
opportunity to if I
were tell me everybody tell me Iris uh
and tell tell me fauna what are the
remaining tasks that you have I'm done
with tasks and I was with Iris yeah I
saw yeah B was sorry if you felt like I
was chasing you IR I was kind of scared
I was kind of scared you were like stick
to me like little time yeah I have I
have a task to do at the dock okay and
then I have one at the cafeteria then do
it and then we win yes task win let's go
guys we have to do it yeah also I think
people who are done with the tasks can
um follow just wait in the meeting area
or follow yeah I mean we have to do the
tests we can't just wait in the meeting
area no no no like people who are done
with the task can follow can I add on I
do think I do think Marissa's a little
bit you and me Let's Stay Together if
I'm dead soon staying with you no we're
stay together whether you want or not
we're staying together
now I'll actually tag along with you
guys if that's okay just to see if one
of you okay I'll feel safer there wait
then maybe you twoo are the
imposters no I'm done with my tasks as
the thing so I to kill me it is kind of
scary oh my God I didn't kill you when
you were around yeah what the oh you two
didn't kill each other because you're
both
te oh my God you come with me and IR why
youing it on the blue women yeah let's
just all stay together and we'll see
what the blue women do oh my God we
follow Iris does anyone else
have I'm done I'm all done oh yeah we
should follow Iris we should pressure
her follow let's follow Iris yeah yeah
you can totally follow me okay nice hey
who voted for
me me you little sh TR you wait am I
okay okay good you better you little
[\h__\h] love you k please don't kill me
okay what
wait I'm not I'm not the
one so Iris has to do tasks right move
move your
butt yeah yeah yeah
yeah so there wait someone stayed behind
didn't they okay okay two of two of
these people or maybe just one is an
imposter
is it possible for us to get new tasks
even though I'm like done now what is
she
doing
y task win who was it
what excuse me I was it was on my desk
what who was the impost impost though
Iris I wonder who it was it was Iris and
Iris
themselves doing so good put us on the
SP doing I'm sorry I was suspicious of
you
fauna I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
Iris didn't kill
FAA why didn't you kill me together for
so long I wanted to keep a someone on my
side and because crony was susing fun in
the beginning I was like maybe I should
keep her on my side and kill cron
instead and like I I saw that Iris was
uh going into the same room as uh Nissa
was so I was kind of waiting outside the
room to see I saw I saw I was like oh no
I think she sus I was trying to kill I
was trying to kill you actually um I
when you were inside the lab I was I was
following you and I was going to kill
you but then I noticed you were moving
weirdly and you were like running away
and then Marissa came comes in right
away I like oh never mind I can't kill
you
here gave up went back I think I was
playing a little bit too cautiously but
um so difficult there's only there's
only me that's I side I was I was
worried like it was still pretty good
yeah still impressive yeah I can't I
can't believe you suspected
me
iing
all well it ends well hopefully when
we're together alone in the mes nothing
I won't kill you don't
worry Don't Drown me in the ocean please
we're missing mo mo
yeah oh sorry I was the let me just I'm
here
sorry um I don't want to like you know
make any hard rules because you know you
just kill whoever is conveniently there
but please do not kill am right away
next
rounde being a
ghost no no no we need our we need our
space on out to do her job yeah kill me
first I love being the
ghost no pressure yeah no
pressure okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed uh the votes uh you
can't see who
voted hard for me to try to vote
someone boy let's go
go see you later
bye why am I always the crew mate huh in
all my Among Us streams I'm like never
something
interesting it's not fair it's just not
fair but whatever I do always say that
it's less stressful less pressure so I
guess I appreciate
it but one day it will happen the thing
is even as a crewmate I'm not even that
uh useful I do my tasks yeah but oh wait
that's the wrong thing um but I don't
really like I have a hard time adding
anything to the conversation to the
discussions I feel like it's hard for me
like they often always talk so much at
once and it's hard for me to hear any
anything you know that makes sense out
of that and then my brain is so empty
and I I have no
idea wait I was literally when I was
walking down here while I was talking I
was thinking about the mushrooms and
they're like I was like they're about to
come they're about to come and I still I
still got
surprised but yeah I feel like I can't
really help his brain empty and and even
though like in hindsight when I think
about it for
example for
example what is is this a
puzzle for for example now that I know
it was F and Iris I can say oh I guess
they were pretty
quiet no okay thank God now I was
shocked it was am again hello oh for a
moment I thought you were dead again
am oh no
no well
hope is dead I just saw her alive like
less than 30 seconds ago must have just
happened I just found it in the meeting
room but I was up in the drop ship if
you look at the map and then I went down
and I found her body there and biu was
up there and fauna was up there and biu
looked like she came from down below so
I'm a little sus Australia are you
because I knew no one would kill you so
I thought it' be
safe like the story but fun was
following the B of life so I'm kind of
SED to fly I was just making sure no
funny business was going on who was
around I I was alive like less than 30
seconds before she was found dead like I
it felt like like 10 seconds before so
I'm I'm like What's Happening that was a
really fast I only passed by in that
area it was like bioo and fauna and
that's it a say in that area
specifically did you see anyone like
coming from that direction
I
saw storage room and then I was using
the
zipline and like B wasn't taking the zip
line up with me
yet oh Well B would you like to defend
yourself
what I was following Amy because I no
one was going to kill Amy so I thought
Amy was the safest bed but Amy I saw you
didn't she not following her but coming
from a different direction I was
following this entire time you did not
follow you the entire time I was running
away from you so I didn't always see you
I was following you the entire do you
want to kill her why are you following
her this
is this
is T I've done one task so far it was
asteroids I haven't done the rest
because asid I was following yeah the
asteroids the video game didn't you do
asteroids in the last one to yeah what
is the asteroids one like
[Music]
maybe she has her I went straight to
Communications I mean I will
do going to skip
for time to I don't want to die
yet by the way Iris I don't know if you
know but you mut oh it's because she's
dead oh never
[Laughter]
mind but she is dead I just wanted to
make sure she joins the conversation you
know if I is or F Su one of them out if
I
go byebye people This
Is
We I didn't even vote for her I voted I
just I didn't vote for you people it
wasn't me oh thank you I just
byebye me
bye-bye we it
bye oh I don't know I thought I F found
that explanation to make
sense and now I want to be more sus of
people cuz I've been so
careful uhoh
oh oh no this place you can get killed
so
easily uh
oh
ah yeah oh crony and Fa I here
not
uh down
here again they are fast it's father I
watched her kill oh [\h__\h]
no I knew
it dead she's dead the switch
the get a shape
shifter no that makes it so much worse I
went I know it's not bi boo because I
went down because I saw bi boo pass us
we were both waiting to get into the
kitchen because last round Fu Moko and I
were frying fish together right so as I
was waiting I went to get bi boo cuz I
was like Advent together strong and when
I came it was right in front of the
kitchen it was right in front of the
kitchen is where is where the death just
happened and I saw someone running up to
the Splash Zone so where was everybody
and don't lie wait you found which which
of the two bodies
didat I don't I don't know where I don't
know where then I have something to add
I was just up at the very top in the
communications and there was crony and
there was fauna first there was fauna
and me and everything was cool then
crony joined I left and now fa is dead
okay can you confirm this crony um after
I was uh doing the ladder task I went
down to the zip line again after that
was done so I didn't really see you saw
Kiara up there yeah I saw Kiara and
fauna up there and then after I was done
with the ladder I went down the zip line
and I couldn't see anything else aside
from that maybe someone vent I'm not
really sure CU it's kind of a short
you I mean
know I going to give my alibi really
quick and I saw bio and we were alone
and she didn't come after me or anything
but I was in the Splash Zone in the
beginning I collected shells and then I
left okay where were you though at the
time of the
murder I went up to storage just
happened I reported it immediately yeah
I I know I went to Splash Zone and I
collected the shells and then I saw bi
Boo and she didn't hurt me and then I
went back to storage okay and then crony
and kiata were over in Communications
yeah so Watson where were you I was at
the laboratory laborat I I am sus of am
because Iris was around me fa and Amy
yeah I am too what and now so now I'm Su
it seems trying to vot someone off no cu
the last the last murder the everyone
who was present we know that it wasn't
fa now and obviously iris is dead so
it's only you were bio but I know where
bi was the time of the murder forgetting
that the first round I reported the body
and both bio and fer were with me and
none of them said that they B even said
that she was following me the whole time
but she didn't see me kill anyone
huh CR trust me trust
me I trust you I
trust who are we voting
for selfreported
[Laughter]
is yes oh my God impostor
gone
bye-bye says no I don't know kiar is
really suspicious right oh sorry okay
see you later what wait was she about to
say it kiar was really suspicious of or
k is
suspicious what would what would she say
if she was saying K is really suspicious
of any like anybody besides crony and
not I wasn't ious of anybody besides
cron so oh wait there's someone
here
hi okay H I think I did a good thing
there I feel like I actually contributed
to us winning possibly winning the game
so I'm pretty happy with my observations
of my
find of finding um should I stay with
her where did she go
didn't she go
down what am I saying why do I not end
my
sentences where did where did nura go
what is
this oh I pull it out oh can we eat
those are these like space veggies what
the [\h__\h] I'm a wizard I'm a wizard in a
box it's getting dangerous anyway
because um we don't have many people
left so we have
to we have to clear the tasks Let's
Go
part suspiciously quiet oh hello Watson
and be
boo what the [\h__\h] is
this uh people didn't do anything just
now
no now bye I'm scared ah reactor [\h__\h] uh
reactor where the [\h__\h] is it down there
okay okay let's go we can do
this people
B is this the B
tax why is it so
slow you and me people you and me let's
go we saved the world people we saved
the world then it's certainly not us cuz
we literally just did this together uh
the Imposter can do it too
but we saved the world we're
heroes
ah this task still
exists why have there been no deaths
guys or are we just not finding
them what are we looking
at oh oh people
no we stop I I wanted to check if anyone
and REE is dead oh yeah I didn't I was
wondering
too I I think Kiara is safe yeah cuz we
just did the emergency thing together
yeah and then am joined right when we
finished it I really think I ran away
both of you guys are I thought both of
you guys were the impostor and you were
going to kill me
no I do you I really because the first
death was Iris and me FAA and Iris were
the ones that were closest to each other
and yeah well that's and now I'm scared
I know it's not Kiara because Kiara
didn't kill me or anything so yeah okay
I still have three tasks left by the way
but wait so why did why did you just
call him meeting because I was wondering
if anyone you because we're about to
finish our tasks and you don't want want
us to finish our cast it was too quiet
and I was scared if anyone was going to
die and I thought like might as well
chat and right Kelly what were you doing
I went down to mushrooms mhm and what
what's the last task you did the Sorting
the mushrooms into the jars and the
crystals okay KY has been quiet yeah she
has I mean ask me any questions you want
but if you talk too much you get sussed
out too so just ask me any questions and
I'll tell
you what's the last task you did
um I don't remember I was in
the shot I can't ask chat too cuz I
can't even look at chat um I know this
sounds suspicious but yeah I don't
remember I'm gonna I'm going to vote for
am I think yeah you're the Imposter
you're just you called the Mee him cuz
we're so close to finishing our tasks
that you're scared no [\h__\h] the I'm
scared of
dying aren't we all I mean I saw cie and
she didn't kill me and I was running
away from you guys cuz I thought you
guys were going to kill me so H that's
my defense yeah okay we
can okay oh you guys if you guys vote
for me you're wrong just so you know
uhoh I'm going to vote for
Kelly okay
or KY what she seems the most sus cuz I
saw you I saw K and B together and you
guys didn't die so unless you're both
the impostor no we're not uhhuh that's
exactly what an imposter would
say well you think everyone if there was
two imposters alive we would lose by now
so there's only oh okay true so one of
the previous was well crony I guess was
the one that got knocked out right so
wouldn't that be heard yeah huh I don't
know I don't know I know I say we just
Skip and continue doing our tasks unless
you guys are if I was the Imposter i'
try to vote one of you guys out right
now and then I'd probably
win I'm going to skip you guys are wrong
regret your decision I love you I'll
miss you yeah right no she's
burning are we winning please what
right how many more oh sorry sorry how
many what how many
what
M it's it's h can we do I guess we can't
H [\h__\h] she's going [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh it's not this it's not this it's
not this it's not
this let's freaking
[Music]
go wacky it wasn't me my
god
well that was wild
I
again that's her tell she was quiet oh
you turned into Faun I see see we
thought Kell some was quiet too but you
[\h__\h] I'm so sorry am how do I ever
redeem myself to you it's too late it's
too
late can't even believe me I it wasy
too I'm not a real Amy
goling I tried to protect her and now
I'm the one that killed
her I can't trust anymore yeah I can't
trust T I'm sorry I can't believe I got
imposter twice believe me I won't get it
why is every good at lying I don't I've
been watching professional Japanese
Among Us players
recently yeah everybody's just Poker
Face the whole time had practice
that's warned you guys you didn't listen
to
me damn it
and I still didn't get impostor a single
time
man maybe next time we still got more we
still got more time right yeah yeah
there's a little more time then let's go
next
round oh I saw I saw way the ghosts uh
were going in their own channel did you
have
fun yes yeah yes recommend it it was fun
I don't know why CR crony was probably
too guilty to join the dead voice ch
oh wait there's a dead voice chat I
didn't even know dead voice chat I was
like why isn't she joining I was like
probably cuz she feels guilty oh no I
don't feel guilty at
all at
all you don't feel any shame I think
crony just randomly get voted off too
cuz I don't even remember like everybody
yeah I got
voted
was for
that new yeah cuz I told you yeah I told
you to believe me see oh it was actually
good what I did thank God she was right
you were so right I was right easy way
to tell easy way to tell if if cie is
imposter she's quiet when she's imposter
all
right imposter so I don't know bye you
are the Imp
wait
why it's like I'm cursed is my account
cursed it's always like this and then
other people get it all the time what
the [\h__\h] is this
oh oh wait I can swipe like this
okay there's so many tasks
[Music]
here ah the stick is ah you don't clean
you this you just pick up the stick and
then you get the
marshmallow I don't like
marshmallows I'll get it for sure
eventually not today unless this is a
short round I did ask the girls
beforehand like how long they want to go
and generally like 2 hours seems to be
the max for
some so we can go up to 2 hours I am
also not tired um I actually did a
really stupid thing in terms of my wait
it's down there terms of my sleep
schedule you don't even want to
know I around like 8 no 8:00 p.m. I was
was like just taking a break after my
stream and I was getting kind of
tired so I was
like I I I want to chill a little bit
and watch Netflix or so but I know if I
sit on my bed I will fall asleep and I
knew it I really knew it but I did it
anyway and then I fell asleep and I was
like well you know what maybe I can
sleep until like was this
oh maybe I can sleep until I don't know
3 4 5 a.m. and then I'll be good for the
collab but then I couldn't sleep as long
as I wanted to so I just I slept I think
4 hours so it was just a really long
nap and then it was so stormy that I
couldn't sleep again so it wasn't about
smoothie it was most mostly about the
weather being really
loud I didn't even see I didn't even see
I didn't really see I didn't [\h__\h] wait I
didn't even really see wait she was just
there wait wait what what
happened wait who did I see no no no no
it wasn't me I was where were you where
were you when you pressed
it who pressed it wait I pressed it I
was oh my God I was so in my tangent oh
my God I went up to the top right to the
communications and I was just Tangen
thing and doing a task and suddenly I
see a dead body but on the same spot I
think I saw at least one more person
maybe another maybe two people I think
so it's Kiara Iris fuok and then I just
came into the room and I saw Callie
outside I just the moment went up the
ladder all of a
sudden lost
Communications we went with almost the
same time and then I was trying to go in
the way to the mushroom door but I got
rid of the mushrooms
but uh maybe you killed by
accident maybe it's just by being silly
uh-huh wait
what wait I mean you were there right
when I reported right no I I just walked
into the room like after cie she was
already in there like alive and you guys
were all doing the power thing or
whatever and I was also starting to do
the power thing putting in the code but
then you guys finished it and then
somebody reported Call's body so I
didn't even see it wait so you're saying
besides me there was Callie and you I
were like went inside the communications
the
there on the other side of the mushroom
wall so I don't think they could kill
her on the other side of the mushroom
wall but I don't know yeah I just went
up the ladder was how it went and then
all of a sudden report there might there
was one other person in there but it was
hard to see cuz everybody was bunched up
I think I saw purple yeah purple was
Call's dead body no no purple is be boo
oh that purple we do have something to
report yeah
we
heard okay you are and the m and we were
thinking maybe this being Sil that's
good thing that
we I heard that thought was saying it to
someone else and now trying can we have
someone who hasn't talk talk please me
me me yes so um I was at Communications
I saw a bunch of people there and I was
trying to like uh do my task and like I
was still on the task when it happened
so I didn't really see anything oh so
you were also in
Communications there so many there okay
wait you were there even now when when I
reported you were still there crony um
yeah yeah oh so you were one of the
other people I saw then where I wasn't
sure who am I seeing oh [\h__\h] I voted for
f well I remember this I will remember
this but oh shoot you
guys I was just it as a
joke I don't remember this well I I also
think like the the statement from am I
didn't take it as that but like
especially with what happened now with
Amy being there I didn't even consider I
already forgot am was saying uh at that
time so that wasn't even is she going to
kill
me that wasn't even my
concern what the feet what wait wait
what
yeah there was like a crowd of people at
communication wait did did
you people
gosh
yeah wow see The Quiet Ones it's always
the quiet on I knew hasn't said anything
but I was ctive last round that's I
asked you to
talk we're both innocent sorry I
thought I thought it was too B
seding for susing am right because of
her statement but it wasn't am oh
yeah I said that on
purpose being silly the two imposters
would of course vote for
fuo I you guys I'm sorry oh my God this
is what happened okay next we we got to
go
next don't give it to the blue
people it to the people
no don't worry I was muted oh [\h__\h] wait
[\h__\h] now I'm nervous now I don't know
what
to okay uh [\h__\h]
me oh the do are they going to be
helpful or are they going to be
[\h__\h] okay acting like I'm doing tasks
acting like I'm doing tasks acting like
I'm doing the
tasks I am totally oh I've never been
here I'm totally doing the task and I'm
not scared at
[Music]
all CL sabotage let's go okay I want to
be useful I feel like Fu will like mess
this
up
wait should I try to kill
Iris I'm coming for you where did she go
where where did she
go where
she sh sh sh sh sh [\h__\h] I should have
done it right
away she must be here where are
we [\h__\h] I'm going to mess it up I'm
going to mess it up what did I say up
what
ah I'm going to be the one messing it up
KY I I I ran up because of the
communications thing was down and she
was right there in Communications in
front of the the thingy I don't think it
was I was at the other I was with but I
didn't see her body I was down by the
dock I was in the
labs me I'm oh yeah I just met crony in
the labs
yeah Iris and I are doing the other task
the power thing didn't kill each other I
think we're
[Applause]
safe up some lift what narissa F where
were you I was down by the dock I I
figured that you probably all were going
there and I wanted to keep doing my
tasks so I just went down and I was
doing a sand castle and then I was
checking since yeah don't the um I
passed I passed the Tex yeah they
disappear but if you pass you can still
do them oh okay yeah so I was checking
manually okay yeah or if you just still
like remember where they were before it
went down
yeah
well
reactor
reactor what task what were you doing at
the reactor we're doing our task we're
just trying
to doesn't want to use the map I don't
like the map I like finding the little
yellow mark on the the screen is
oh now you know now
know emping
yellow I actually haven't done that yet
the yellow there's a yellow is so cute
it's a little Among
Us uh
theow marshmallows
yeah so in conclusive but what task were
you
doing yeah the marshmallows are nowhere
near the reactor so
that was before yeah but what were you
doing today huh we doing a bunch of what
were you doing what we doing in the
reactor yeah what were we doing in the
reactor
[Laughter]
find for now I'll give you guys the
benefit of the doubt than you please
don't kill us
again
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] they were so close to being
ejected and they were as I said as I
expected they were very sus in their
behavior okay now I need to I just
realized I need to know in case they ask
me um like I need to I need to know a
task I need to know a task just in
case okay the this is the numbers task
why am I doing this right
now 5 6
86 okay see but like this I'm getting a
good reputation thanks to
this oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] yeah I think I'm already
making allies though because I had
several opportunities to kill someone
and I didn't do it can I kill Iris if
she's she just went down
there you
[\h__\h] you almost left me alone in this
wide wide
world [\h__\h] the pressure is
insane just looking for someone to kill
oh iris is there again and
a
uh [\h__\h] let's I'm totally I'm doing the
trash
task
okay I'm doing trash T it's like the I I
find people and then they're just kind
of too far away next time I see someone
I want to kill
them [\h__\h] so nervous I'm so nervous
sabotage what was that what did I just
sabotage [\h__\h] where is
everybody I guess now they're going to
CS unless you're someone like narissa
then you just ignore the problems in
this
world I I should go up to comms at this
point
[\h__\h]
I'm oh I'm
here it was K it
wasar Kar killed don't believe her do
you see I saw people kill am I am medic
I am medic I can see people's w
yeah and I can see you kill am is that
how it works I am I can see people's vs
I have three battery charges every round
to see how many people are alive this is
the first time I have medic I saw Kiara
k no this is hard for me because I had
just I had just seen bi Boo and but I
did not see kiata and I was going down
and she didn't follow me so she might
have realized she was alone with a but
uh bioo also when she killed me
self-reported and then immediately this
is literally the first time I've gotten
scientist and I have this is the first
time I play it so how would I know that
I have three charges of scientist to
check
vitals where is the body first time in a
while uh the body is up the by
communication okay I
[Music]
saw watch it you probably just looked up
some guide about those no I didn't this
is the first time I have whatever
scientist whatever I can check people
well I was I was so often alone with
others and I didn't kill them so why
would I you know can somebody vouch for
me cuz I think I was Al alone together
with a lot of
people come on
oh I was alone with for a while but I
was not alone with Kiara yeah I saw k
for like a split
second saw alone and I saw crony times I
think alone and I saw narissa like maybe
one or two times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or FAA was going to kill me cuz like
they were just kind of walking around so
I stuck around one of them to make sure
I didn't get killed um it would kind of
check out if Kiara was the instantly I
saw I believe I really time okay who
sorry
goodbye forever thanks forever uh what
was it I I love you or I'm than you
forever
well somebody's not voting oh yeah I
just accepted that you guys are voting
me me out but I guess you'll you'll no
you're running down the
clock it's so sad I I was always is with
you
guys so sad love
you goodbye goodbye I will go up like a
phoenix and I will rise like a
phoenix
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I thought I didn't see people
there I didn't see
people I was low stressed because we
hadn't didn't have a kill for a long
time
oopsie let's haunt her how do you do
this
H oh what is this what does this
do I know what that
does oh they could hear my voice
probably if there was a microphone or
whatever yeah F's probably
panicking ah see this is exactly what I
thought like I if if if I was going to
be questioned I would panic I can't lie
like the
others I
can't but fuok was really quiet in that
round Waring
day in that discussion they were
probably like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] no no
don't don't vote the other impostor out
what are we going to
do I'll try to help of sabot aging at
least yeah I should just stay crew mate
forever join the ghost oh they're
currently not uh in a voice chat like
separately they only did that for one
round pretty
much oh B I think fuk is like probably
too nervous to do anything right now
like
kills did you enjoy being an imposter no
no no I
didn't
but they're not fixing the
clums or maybe now they are and the only
one who isn't here is f
seemingly
[\h__\h] and I even killed my one and only
my love Amelia
Watson I'm such a
fake I am the impostor my love is the
impostor yeah there's so much pressure I
was feeling doy
doie let's close everything cuz why
not let me do the I want to do the
reactor where is
fumo oh
here ky following oh even I can't see
fuoka anymore after that foka cron is
like behind you
oh Iris oh she's just checking
probably
hello oh no I I cuz I I I believe it's F
what like when we were going to when
comms were down we were going up I see I
see like um many of us were going up I
think it was like I think I saw hear
them defend themselves I also saw I was
also with crony and narissa alone none
of us killed each other um and we were
all going up to comms but then I see
fuok coming down from comms ignoring the
fact that comms is do the bottom one
first right we just TR to do the C and
at the top if you were at the top you
would do the top one right we're just
counting we're focusing on our task so
bad the task on the map when comms are
down yeah yeah you can but if you walk
around you can find them
what we did last time
too ear that's why I decided I think
so talking at once and I can't get
anything that's how we play
among me AAS you did this time what's
what's a task you did what's the task
you
diden why' you you you come came back
down from comms even though Comm is
sabotage way back down to the greenhouse
the greenhouse is
pretty green Greenhouse is
[Music]
[Laughter]
pretty we're the cutest
puppies
wow look at the Little Liars look at the
Little
Liars they literally I think me and are
the worst Liars in this
grp you can't put us
[Music]
together I don't know I'm to scared I
don't want this to end then I have to
defend myself my for my life don't um
delay your death it's I have to in
face Sor excuse me
byebye puppies
[Laughter]
y that was really good susing out Iris
that was
impressive from the reactor too even the
last round when when we almost voted
them out cuz they didn't know what they
were doing at the
reactor that made me 80% sure and then I
saw them going down from com oh yeah
yeah why say we're crew mate will do the
ex
yes I'm so sorry it's
okay you were just trying to survive I
understand think out of this whole group
of people me and foku are like the worst
Liars so it wasn't a good
combination I my your B my we were so
bad I
was makes me
laugh I love too you you see see I I had
The Good The Good Life I know I did the
marshmallows and then she goes oh we did
that last
[Laughter]
time oh my god well at least I finally
got imposter do we don't want to do one
more round
yeah hide and seek for the last
theek hide andek hide and
seek hide andek sounds fun it's like
hide-and seek like how you'd really
think hideand-seek
would think we have to mute for
hideand-seek wasn't there an actual
setting for hide and seek though yeah
there there is there is computer uh you
might have to make a new room though
maybe um if you can't change it in the
settings um on the computer yeah then
you might have to make a new room is it
yeah no I don't think you can change it
here okay then I'll make a new one okay
okay
okay okay it's kind of like it's pretty
much like playing tag yeah
cute um any preferred
map let's do the original the OG oh yeah
yeah let's do
[Music]
OG
nice I'll send you the link in the group
uh the the in the group mhm okay there
you go yeah this one's chaotic but
really funny thank you never done with
before oh it's fine and it's a short
game too so okay let's go
perfect man this is scary this one this
is like the only time I actually want to
be imposter hide and
seek I never want to be a moner ever
don't have the move for this same we
don't have to move for this you no I
don't think
so give accident I guess we can mute if
we're
done uh yeah we don't have to
right wait we can we can hide in vents
oh is there only
one oh is this like
zombies we can hide really do tasks the
timer goes down
quicker do we have 3 minutes to
hide minutes to hide she's in the med
Bay over engine she's coming for what
wait
what oh man is she green that
was who knows what color I might
be
everybody's clumping
together where is she right
now my
God is
that wait how does this
work no do your best can hear the music
come close to you when she's close by
that's
scary crony where's
crony oh that's fun that's so quick too
that was so short another W another W
want to be
[Music]
imposible for both the impostor and the
the the the crew
mates can we increase his speed for both
crew mates yeah to but also I I uh I
think I have to make a new Lobby because
I don't think I can change the amount of
uh Seekers oh there's only
one yeah I it's fine to leave it on one
we just need to speed up so we're all
running really
fast okay
Maxum
W let's go this is how it should be jeez
oh boy we
got yumy let's
go wait do I get to go that fast too I
think so oh I
hope I'm going to be Unleashed for my CH
might F why are there okay oh God where
do I go H don't forget we have to do
task task Tas there's task I don't see
them I see tasks but I don't know what I
really want to finish those
sorry it's all
[Music]
good why do I have
no scared I'm scared I'm scared I hear I
hear the base we got to win we got to
win this I can't find you
guys's everyone so
fast taskas
[Music]
task not her I'm going on a vacation
with
[Music]
her yell I'm not even near you
Terri you
know like a horror game us set it on
[Laughter]
the terrifying screams
[Music]
here
louder louder and louder yeah it's so
cha going to get in
trouble the moment you hear the guitar
you're
like oh she
[Music]
coming my eyes are spinning 20 seconds
more
[Music]
seconds [\h__\h] oh you're going to be even
faster in the final round I'm alive okay
should I do T
I need you to run around like I this
chicken she get one more minute come
after you don't stand still because it's
going to show your later on it shows do
you guys know where I am show your
location it shows my location yeah
there's a there's a red DT uh that
indicates where the I have it on me
I as hell what I shouldn't have bies I
see dead bodies I see dead
[Music]
people [\h__\h] does she see me from the map
too she gets closer oh go oh God
[Music]
God that was so close
that was impressive IR that was really I
don't know how I just didn't really see
her on the screen that often so thank
God everybody was so
fast that was close though teleporting
across the
map the ghost couldn't even keep
[Music]
track nothing is scary who is it this
time let's go who is it
cross
go she going have fun run run
run does doing tasks do anything
like early Tas win if we do if we finish
them all yeah we could get lucky I was
being very proactive with the Tas hide
hide and seek you got to
hide not
why can't I oh
no got to go got to go got to go I was
about to get in the thing I'm
sorry
nice oh no what color you guys on you
guys damn
it I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth it it I know right I feel you just
of easy
bait gck you ran past she R
fast she's going on going to the
cafeteria wait can we tell
her it might be a little
unfair oh okay I felt that was the wrong
direction okay you know what
a let's do our
task I'm too scared to move around at
this point I die whenever I use do Tas
is
just in
4k she only has only three
left what is the danger me there ah come
on guys one more one more
minute St good hiding spot though she's
going at a good Pace very good Pace oh
[Laughter]
30 30 seconds 35 seconds that was
amazing keep going
keep that was a really good hiding spot
yeah that was a nice hiding
spot I it so loudly all time oh no
whoopsy
slippery everybody's so
fast one is there
overtime so fast I
can't you got to
survive
I'm no pressure oh
man just go just go just go you have 30
seconds you can do
it what you do you're Phoenix to her no
the
B we have 10 seconds 10 seconds second
easy easy she won't get you she won't
she won't get you oh
no 2
how many seconds left one literally
one a
millisecond
though that was the clutchest ever what
yeah can't escape time at the end of the
day butar is really slippery yeah really
slippery oh my God that was exciting
I mean ex I'm I'm pretty exhausted from
that but we can do another one if you
want I'm down for one
more actually you know wait wait oh no
before Oh I want to I want to speed so
fast yeah it's fast oh good okay never
mind this what you wanted how do you
kill people the whole time um there's a
kill button so don't you worry okay oh
my God no way I don't want to be here no
the monster she has awakened she has
awakened I'm coming for you nobody's
using my hiding spot right oh that's a
good idea don't use my hiding spot might
go use it no that wasn't your hiding
spot that Rampage there were two people
there I only saw one
person
overlapped does the music get louder for
me too I feel like it does it I don't
know it gets louder oh when you're near
someone really even for
impostor you little [\h__\h] get out of
there get out of there you little
[\h__\h] what's going on scary
no
[Music]
where
she
[\h__\h] where are
they hiding
[Music]
spot oh no that's okay that's the stack
dead bodies I still got time I still got
time
oh I saw someone where is
she that hiding
spun I
again stop being
so oh my God that was no I have found
anyone in like agent you passed by
somebody
[Music]
a someone's here no oh
[\h__\h] where are
you hello I'm all
[Music]
alone no hints no
oh there was some button popping up
there the use
button
[Music]
yeah even see you that's
lame you I saw you that's all that
matters oh
no oh one more one
more
[Music]
run no no no no one minute there's still
one more
minute they're literally right there run
run you can throw it through a loop just
run just
run keep go in a circle go in a
circle
wow doie
doie that was again pretty clutch I
would say get
the out foring after
Mama Mia that was wow that was fun that
was fun that was merry I'm too excited
to say anything so let's start with the
with the goodbyes from anybody but me
um please no oh yeah this is really fun
I'm glad we could get together and have
like a little Christmas Among Us
celebration the perfect holiday SE
holiday game right for real
just red with toy and some blood when I
think of Christmas I think of Among Us
viol and
ornament it it's pretty festive the
colors this makes me want to play this
makes me want to play on Project winter
yeah yeah I know
C well thank you I'm sorry you died so
often
[Music]
I'm but that's okay it was still fun
Callie what about you you had some good
good kills today that was fun it was
nice getting to dust off the old Scythe
for once and get back in the game for a
little bit that was
nice yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun way
really in a fun way yeah in a fun way I
guess that's about it we should argue
more often yeah yeah let's do it let's
do it no no I can't maybe not yeah no
we're just stay TIY but within among us
we can argue as much as we want right
and then outside of Among Us you know
we're different people among us changes
us but only what happens among us stay
Among
Us stays Among
Us
all right and Fa please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules
science science Bill what sence lying
science science Rules end statement next
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think Kiara knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it
don't worry about
it'll it's a
okay Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs Christmas
yes yeah no this was fun I'm glad I was
able to lie better this time yeah yeah
you need some good lying we need to
learn from
Iris never suspected everyone everyone
was great I love how bad fok was at L
yeah
you you can tell it's their first time
you can tell it's their first time my
first time it was the same as me when I
played for the first time worry is
always like that it's great I love it
thank you very much that F they were so
lucky cuz like in that one round they
were about to be voted off and I thought
I was going to be alone but then somehow
somehow they
survived they
survived Bo I couldn't save you C so
it's okay we couldn't save each other
even if we wanted
to well thank you Iris and then
people what about you I was happy to be
able to kill people I wish I was able to
kill more people but I satisfied with
the amount of people I was able to kill
this
time thank you for your service that's
the spirit that's the Christmas spirit
let's go let's
go it was it was solid solid reing good
job again I'm so
sorry it's okay
betail was it what stays in Among Us
stays Among Us don't wor exactly
exactly well we learn a lot of things
today we really good at lying right no
that was
it yeah and uh we have fun we we yelled
a bit screamed a bit and we did a lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we had
fun so true let's play more yeah when I
saw I was imposter with F I knew I knew
that you weren't going to be good at
lying we have to do
face
are too sweet yeah it's all good true
it's funny
goodg I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together Ki
[Music]
welcome I'm sad I had to be the impostor
I don't like it brings me no
joy murdering me what you mean no oh but
you were so good though you were good at
it with CR was over right away me that's
true yeah you guys blue women women are
SC women blue
women say it it's the blue people the
the avatars I always say it
mhm yes thank you you I'm glad you had a
good time let let's continue this in the
males you
peacefully the other Blue Woman
Quon yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice U because I never get
imposter yeah I never get these rules go
yeah and thank you for organizing this
it was a lot of
fun I love among
us I guess you know there was all sorts
of drama but like we said earlier what
happens Among Us stays Among
Us wow
beautiful well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh the it's out of my hands out
of my power now but please check back on
it next week we'll all tweet about it
when it is finally up uh so stay tuned
stay excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with us viewers I say to you
viewers thank you for spending it with
us and thank you to the girls for
spending it also with us thank you for
getting together at this
time Merry Christmas
everyone
[Music]
H
H had a lot of fun that was really great
and I hope everybody has a nice nice
holiday season some cookies
yeah Yum Yum Yum Yum okay I have some
protein milk in my fridge o very
Christmasy leave it out
for maybe Santa will come to to drink
your
milk oh protect your milk
right I don't think that's gonna make
Iris like Santa
anymore does is not a lot Santa is iris
is literally the tree now okay I'm the
tree but I'm not yet don't let Santa
drink the protein milk we can't let him
get any stronger than no no muscles for
Santa no give him the power no PO the
cookies oh wait isn't like in some
countries Santa drinks beer or people
give beer to Santa really or something
sounds German Santa gets drunk I don't
know I think so drunk Santa lot and then
he yeah oh no oh
no it just makes it worse that doesn't
really sound like something I would want
to tell my children over yeah okay with
that I think some people already gone
like fle is gone already so I guess
let's go
everybody
happy holidays and to all a good evening
bye merry Chas mermas Christmas great
Christmas last Christmas peace you my
[Music]
cat
that