[Music]
do
okay i am ready now i am ready my
minecraft window is like all over the
place but i'm gonna
sweet uh
yeah i'm also all over the place because
i don't i came here i was kind of lost
but i don't know where to buy the
tickets so i guess like whatever maybe
we just bet on the horses in our head
then at least we don't lose money
exactly let's do this
are you guys ready for the festival
are we
here and i had like no idea so so much
was being built because just i think ian
and id was not really notified of like
the process of this until a few hours
ago
i think um
i think i don't know like i know a
little bit at least about like the
building but it's not like i wanna i
can't participate anyway so
yeah at the end of the day i'm just like
you know let's go to the festival
hello
it's more than i expected it's even
bigger than last year i think um
you know oh my gosh i'm wearing pants
i'm gonna take it off okay nice
oh i was like
skin of your new outfit no
yes you're still wearing the sports
festival you know i changed my clothes
because people keep telling me i never
changed my clothes so i did just for the
festival and then here you are with the
sports festival off
i didn't realize well that's a little
bit embarrassing but okay no problem no
problem no problem
where is the
there's a lot of people here but i don't
know where evil the horse betting place
is and where the horse
ticket buying places i don't know where
any of that is yeah it's not here right
this is we're doing some horror stuff
we're yeah this is the horror house do
you want to go to the whorehouse later
yeah we can do everything
yeah enjoy the festival let's go oh my
gosh there's music
what oh they must have built some kind
of like tune in here yeah just follow
where everybody else goes but currently
everybody's here everybody's here i know
right probably didn't start yet
maybe yeah ipm they start
uh okay okay okay yeah the horse bidding
place i don't think we need to do that
maybe when the horse bidding starts you
can like follow everybody
oh there's like an
english explanation for this chicken
game chicken shooting game oh this is
ollie's
ah that's why it's english nice very
nice shoot as many chickens
before the chicken
falls into the lava
oh
no
[Laughter]
don't
this is not rust okay this is minecraft
shoe it says shoe as many chickens
funny aren't you yeah i'm pretty funny
aren't i
i didn't even make a connection because
i'm a phoenix
exactly
yeah i was just um what if it's a water
situation you know like what if
what if um
[Music]
where do we go oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's supposed to be
like um carousel
a merry-go-round oh my gosh what is that
why why is the horse like that
it's so oh my gosh it is like a
merry-go-round kind of thing but it's a
pig get a cow and uh it's just not
twirling it's not going around but
betting to your right oh really oh okay
let's see let's look
i think
i think the thing is like
until it starts oh can we really steal
that betting ticket ah how to buy how to
buy how to buy
what to buy
i've ate eight diamonds give me one
ticket please what do i bet on how do i
fit how does this work i don't even know
[Music]
hmm
what is this
musk
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh where's this booth
you can get diamonds here in case you
don't have any oh apparently okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
i will bet on
uh
what first race runner
ah
first race runner is
tokoyami oh yeah who whose horses
i think it's on the uh the list is the
complete list is on the thingy
[Music]
i think like they're in the they're in
the public vc um
if you want to vet one
oh
wait i think
how do i open here
ah oh no that was oba yashki
join join me obviously okay
you get like one slip every single time
that i'll put each like diamond so ah
betting slips back if you win okay next
yes yes
how much
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello
[Laughter]
okay love messages
you are my everything
you
will you um spend the rest of your life
with me
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
it's
thank
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you okay
thank you
[Music]
i just don't know where to go
now let's everybody i guess
i got diamond from choco sensei i didn't
bring diamond but uh if you want you can
you can try out her booth
oh no no it's okay it's okay i already
bet it's better oh okay okay okay
where do we go next though everybody's
still here so i guess we're safe yeah i
think let's just wait
which voice chat is the
horse race i um
i'm not sure if they want everyone to be
together for that but
uh maybe
oh a lot of people are number three
um find that one
yes yes yes you hear their screams
maybe
where is the location though
that's what i want to know yeah
but they're all still
these are still
chilling
[Music]
but maybe they're chilling because
they're talking in the vc wait who's in
the vc i don't know
oh
i think like after the horse race it's
gonna be like a free thing yeah yeah
yeah yeah and then we can do whatever
yeah then we can do whatever we want
maybe it's like right behind this thing
here everybody's in like three chat do
you wanna go to three chat
or i don't know it's up to you
yeah
i don't know
maybe eavesdrop a little bit of what
they're talking about
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
foreign
um
okay
[Music]
all right
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
quack
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
foreign
hello
welcome back i think they said something
like uh believe the voice shot except if
you're a racer so that's why i came back
okay okay
okay okay okay
i don't know
i translated a little bit for my chat
while i was muted oh yeah i was like um
i was like how do i mute because there's
so many windows
but yeah basically it's like starting
from now they're gonna
they're gonna like test drive
before the real deal
okay this is test testing rounds yeah
really oh they get a testing round
that's pretty nice of them
yes yes yes what did you bet on by the
way first round subaru right
the second round i don't have enough
diamonds
in some meaning you went all in for sure
yeah guys i went all in for savaru let's
go oh
sweet
well i bet for i think uh second one
mikko and third one pickle ah nice nice
nice but uh maybe third round is later
right i
think
i think fourth round fourth round is
later okay okay
because i guess the yeah the winners and
second place riders of the first 40
rounds will be in the fourth round
anything
it's my favorite foods
tonkatsu party make it clear i think
that was a bundle yeah
winning and tonkatsu's stuff louie
really likes her puns
pun birds pumpers
there's so much violence here they're
like infected by rust
i know
um
yeah too much rust hello
oh my god are you gonna play on the day
where like
supposedly everyone fights for
like death yeah that's what i'm asking
like i asked a bunch of people if
they're gonna come but um i don't know
um i haven't seen the answers yet maybe
after the stream
i just i didn't i didn't know when
exactly that would happen anyway so for
now i just scheduled a stream for 31st
but i think that day there won't be any
fighting yet because the reset is on the
second so probably on the first
is where the fight happens whatever oh
really
i don't think i really would want to be
part of that anyway
yeah maybe i would want to like sightsee
but not not much
but i want to at least like watch it you
know so i'm not like behind
yeah
it's so easy to feel me like you're
missing out so i'm just gonna you know i
will watch
yeah
oh oh they are they're introducing them
yes yes
[Music]
horse is called tokuyami kayo
they're sharing horses though because
like for example mio's horse will be
used by bulldog senpai too ah so this is
just like the sponsor of the house diago
apparently
[Music]
are they all listening to the
introductions now no
maybe
it's just the writers and the organizers
i think right now together
okay it's it's like
i don't know what to do this time in
this festival like
yeah
there's like uh i have i have no clue
where to be and where to go i think it's
just like what right now is the horse
race
[Laughter]
of course yes we got
same time let's go
i'm betting all in for subaru senpai
guys
to show that follow tori um
bond yeah wait so if i bet two diamonds
on salvador senpai and let's say she
wins yeah i doubt no
hey don't be like that
but how much would i get back
[Music]
four maybe i don't know
is it double or
i don't know
because they never really said the
multiplayer oh it's army
i don't know i bet one i mean
i got i got my diamond from choco
sensei's booth
what did you have to do for that
um
she uh we have to give her a love
a love message
yeah
love message that's why um yeah i was
telling you you know if you want to give
give it a try
ooh
look at that okay
is this a test problem now yeah i think
it's a test round now i think
oh wasn't what i'm saying but how do you
do it oh shoot only with octopus right
yeah i have lots of fun
see
no that was
oh monthly go go oh they returned oh
i fell i fell backwards
sort of goal really for real
but she went back okay that's obviously
a test run yeah
okay i'll kill coke
okay okay okay hopefully with that one
test round she realized how to yeah she
has potential she needs some confidence
you know
confidence yeah have confidence i'm
going to eat i'll be up here cook the
chicken
where are you oh i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm
gonna go with you
fine
oh really sorry i i'm i'm kind of
capturing the audio differently from
usual so i'm i'm confused too
yeah i think like my my bgm is also kind
of low
but
it's fine
it's better to have the bgm little
rather than too loud if it's too loud
you can't hear anybody
what's up is so fast though
oh oh oh so what is that doing bad
either go
go go go go go go go go
oh she kind of like
got hooked on the fence for a moment but
she's still going fast she go and she's
going
somewhere far behind
oh the spider webs yeah bye
they did nothing to want to visit bye
and wait enough around is she doing
maybe a few maybe multiple laps maybe
maybe yeah yeah two laps they said
awesome
i'm impressed by somebody
oh my god
how many lives is this oh yes left
yes she got sick she got second let's go
her horse is really cool though it's
like red and black
she probably had a [\h__\h] horse though
yeah
i think yeah i think it's about like the
stats of the horse
yeah yeah
i must have carried watermelon senpai
perhaps or it was her own gamer skill
who knows who knows who knows
it's a teamwork between like the person
and the horse right
yeah
yeah they have to trust and love each
other they have different colors that's
so cool it's just like power rangers or
something
i don't think i've ever
seen that kind of armor how did they do
that this is like maybe like with dye
i don't know maybe they die leather yeah
they dye the leather maybe because you
can right
i never tried that in minecraft but it's
also been way too long i forgot so many
things
oh
look at them riding by the audience
it's so cool
nice
so cool oh yeah
applaud eight eight eight is
[Music]
wow go go next go next connects connect
go next let's go
i didn't vet for anything
ah well then you can lean back or you
couldn't bet um without you know
oh
let's see who's up next uh bhutan senpai
with uma uma uma
senpai with yogurt
[Music]
i don't know like for me on the screen
number two
they start announcing the rankings in my
place
oh yeah oh i'm i'm reading a different
list
let me see if i can throw watermelon
senpai
a watermelon
sandpaper okay yeah she slurped it nice
she slurped it yeah
watermelon
right now but she's cheering all her
date isn't that oh that's so cute
[Music]
that's isn't that fitting
oh
spicy
[Music]
what did eena give you
uh
okay
what's happening down there i don't know
bedding maybe
eh let me see it i don't know because um
maybe they're just checking maybe maybe
maybe maybe before before the next round
they're like six though
zeta is here
oh
oh everybody who
betters on what bet on what am i saying
buy is uh they get a return of ten times
the bets that they
oh
ten times we're rich
not bad
nice you you're going i guess
uh i wonder can do i get a return for
betting on second place
they didn't say anything on second flip
oh no they're now gonna prepare for the
second race okay i guess the only first
place
everybody who bets on the first place
gets
diamonds really
really what about
second come on
can we at least get like five times
oh
it's okay i'm glassy shibo senpai was
like second so i'm proud i'm proud of
getting
betting for her
let's go
yeah for riding a horse the first time
yeah first time rider
at least like i feel like riding a horse
in minecraft is a million times easier
than rust and
i pressed space to jump i just fell off
the horse in the hospital i know
i was running away from a bear and then
i pressed face because i wanted to jump
no did the bear kill you in the end yeah
yeah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] horse
where are you why you leave her to die
like that
yeah and then you know what like i got
myself a horse and then i
left her like overnight because i wanted
to sleep and then in the morning she's
gone maybe she died so weak
oh that's weird i also had like
something weird happen like i found
inna's horse somewhere
um standing randomly without cover
without food so i was like okay i'm
gonna like protect it so i took it to my
place and i built like a feeder and
everything for it and it was perfect it
should have been fine it had food inside
too a lot of food and then i i'm gone
for like three minutes i come back and
it's the horse is just gone just gone
yeah
which
it shouldn't there's no there was no
reason no explanation for it
the food was still left in the in the
feeder
it got spirited away
and there was no one that could have i
don't think anybody took it to be honest
yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's why i was like you know even
though i have a horse like maybe i'll
just
not use it
you know
just not use it and then maybe it's
better to you know
use somebody's taxi if i see someone and
then if they have a car i'm gonna like
hey um use the hot air balloon the other
day oh when i logged on the water the
hot air balloon was like right in front
of my house was that you or somebody
else no
no no no no no i left it far far away
because then when i wanted to use it to
go back to
well my house then of the field somebody
took the fuel a certain somebody oh my
god
okay
anyway
but but hot air balloon um the the
controls are really difficult but once
you've got it it's it's actually a quite
a good
like way of getting around
okay okay yeah okay it's hard to shoot
you
from like down there so no one can get
can you shoot somebody from up there
though
from up yeah i don't try i didn't try
but
we're for try perhaps
oh okay i mean yeah that's something to
definitely try for next time i think
yeah
why are there two riders in there
i don't know another one
[Music]
a white one let's see
no oh and then overpower
number two
polka with yago
[Laughter]
oops i wanted to give you a flower but
it fell
i got it oh you got it nice i'm taking
your flower because my joke was so good
it's a token of appreciation
yes
which means you are the bridge basically
the whole life what the name
nice
name
where is majida not participating today
number five
is
who are you are you rooting for who
today
in this year this race no in this race
in this race
see one time i was actually fast enough
to say something sweet in this one i'm
i'm both i'm rooting for because empire
no nico
okay okay
i'm gonna root for
masjid
oh
okay
well i mean the horse name says it might
say hi let's go
[Music]
let's go
it's because it's the
mickelson clyde
fighter
don't let me down
yeah
might say let's go
yeah i'm going to root for my eye
if subaru
oh my
god oh my gosh
let's go
second time
ah come on
cut yes
are they are they rigged did someone put
like butter or oil on the on the feet
yeah but man she's so fast
[Music]
two laps
interesting interesting okay i didn't
even use the chance to do a second lap
but i think they did one yeah it's like
yeah
[Music]
what really
let's go go go go go go go go go go go
go go
nice jump nice jump now don't fall off
now yeah this is your chance go go oh
yeah go around
come on
i'm watching over
you watching
her house is so motivated let's go
actually she got a safe distance from
puerto rico no problem here
oh my god oh wish you still won i think
wow wow
omg
wow
[Music]
she came in third or third third true
third nice not bad either no fan not bad
yeah i feel like my day high is um also
pretty good he has pretty good stats
[Music]
will not be in the third race though no
who am i supposed to root for
let's see let's let's see the list of um
participants later i can tell you it's
[Laughter]
[Music]
senpai did i say i keep on saying send
by [\h__\h] sake
number one you know
do i get it now
maybe
she's she seems to be working
number two jaguar
thank you
okay number tiny this
this one
no wonder is chicano
i don't think there's time to keep
everybody there
wow they came up with like a cheer yeah
cute
all right
are we doing this now what wait is there
time
is there time
here let me check in the voice chat
that she's in i really love to sense
with her care on a stick wait i don't
have carrots i can't ride so sad she's
not in any voice chat okay
[Music]
maybe
maybe later or is it now uh i think they
will announce
the third race is
because
wait seven times
for oh
[Music]
how is it
what is going on
[Music]
i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna keep it whatever it's
only two diamonds in the end whatever
who cares i'll try again at the very end
because
i'm gonna
bet all in
all in as an in my heart
um for kyle luma69 because that shows my
support for the fellow hulatori which is
louis and kyla i guess
oh by the way i have 690 subs nice
thank you for your six nine teeth stumps
yeah
what what
what a bae
[Music]
what are we waiting for right now
um what is for the third round
yes
you start but
i don't think we're starting it
well
what's this one i think i want to touch
the bed around here oh sorry sorry i
keep on pressing e to open things
it's right click right
that's right click
[Laughter]
sorry
should i play really okay okay okay i'll
just i'll just give it to her here hi uh
oh [\h__\h]
uh what was he cute
okay
what's she gonna do
oh no oh yeah i think i might be getting
my winnings oh what a nice nice
and maybe should i try the the first
returning the first one as well
[Music]
what about this one
arigato
[Music]
what
if if
if i don't get anything back for that
that's good that's good to just just
wondering just wondering
[Music]
she's thinking
hard
a long time i think
oh i guess not
maybe not
[Music]
nothing for second place only first
place
but different
even
if the horse even if it gets number one
though the horse that got number one in
the second round only got seven times
the return while in the first round the
number one horse got ten times
why what
what
why because maybe like they already know
the power like oh this is the most
powerful horse or something no it
depends on how on the other people bets
on the vets
if there's a lot of people betting on ah
i got you this kind of stuff works i
don't know i forgot
oh my gosh crony's burning wait so the
lower
the odds are the lower the return is
the that means the
more people
bet for that person or the less people
that
i don't know
you're the big brain people yes okay
that's correct oh okay
so seven times it was lower because more
people bet for mikko senpai than people
bet for vata senpai uh-huh i see
so like uh the more underrated someone
is the bigger the payout will be
everybody's all lined up now
oh okay miss
with her horse
i love noel senpai's face
why does she have that color
what is that was she wearing i said i
was wondering too wait did the quota
simply end up like having the mask style
if she ends up doing it i really want to
visit it do you know
i don't know about it oh
we can check it out if she does that
[Music]
if i knew that this was happening i
would have liked to participate in the
race i like riding horses
yeah
horse riding is fun we have to make an
enid
focused uh festival event yeah
we should yeah i feel like we need to
make because i know like japan like
makes a lot of events too which is great
but i think it would be nice if we also
make our event i feel like it would make
everything fruitful especially because i
did
i never was on the server finding but i
saw and i heard that you guys are really
good at building stuff so oh we have our
people
yeah we'll leave it all you guys and
we'll just be mental support for
building we'll just give you the
materials and you guys build it yeah
i mean i'm not the one that's good at
building it um
uh kyla's like really crazy about
grinding and i think like the person who
built the most on the whole id cup was
um
ali muna and
kyla was sponsoring one of the prizes
like we were doing like this
uh
climbing thing like climbing like a
pole and then on the top there's like
prizes and the prizes are like
netherride swords and then you know
netherride shoes and stuff like that
no
yeah
nice id is pretty crazy like not me like
i'm just like super casual but the
people in that are kind of
crazy
yeah yeah i mean i just saw like clips
of
kaela's collection of elijah's and stuff
like that
oh this this elytra i'm using it's
kyla's by the way
i'm not surprised yeah we were like
working on something that's why i was in
a deserted island remember when i logged
in earlier
yes
nine oh shoot oh trial trial trail race
oh my god rogue sent by so fast
whoa
what the what
what
[Music]
so fast she disappeared
yeah wait that's really fast what the
heck is that
damn
yeah everybody unity has their roles you
know kyla kayla grimes and smoona builds
and me i'm i'm in charge of writing
fiction you know i'm i'm the librarian
and they're like
aryan yeah
the librarian
oh we're starting oh we're starting for
real
where are you
i had to go a little bit further because
when i'm back that far i couldn't see
the like the beginning of the race oh
okay okay oh cause you don't have zoom
in
no i'm using zoom but still i wouldn't
see them
okay then yeah weird
like they're too far my my loading
thingy is too low okay okay
go go
i keep on hearing those
hey but i don't see them did you hear
that too
the sound of the flying thing is when
you don't sleep
oh phantom
and i keep hearing like weird sounds but
i don't know i can't really pinpoint
what it's oh my god where's kai let's
how you're so high up
[Music]
there what is she doing
oh
she's flexing
stop let's go oh
well this time it's a bit more balanced
not an obvious first place right away
the the first third ones
are all very close
i'm gonna zoom in
content
oh [\h__\h] so what's up it just went past
it as if there was nothing there oh
where the hell is it but
oh here here
i'm louis
come on
where is the nose again
[Music]
but once again had no troubles with that
part i'm like an announcer am i doing a
good job you are
i i will also announce our wedding soon
don't worry
aren't you married um
i guess i don't know i don't know i
guess so hey louie
i'm louis cam right now
go go go
she tried she tried
she tried
damn wait first was
christmas who i i didn't even look
probably told somebody
commentary
[Music]
but thankfully kaiduma 69 is not in the
last race yeah
so no one gets that [\h__\h] horse
[Laughter]
no i'm going to turn that into basashi
right away
paso
so it's kind of sad she's here all the
time she's not even watching the race
what's she doing
she's up there i wanted to get up there
but it's so hard it's just one pixel
wait what did you do again to get that
one diamond
i don't know she's just really rich uh
the economy id server is a little bit
messed up
look six
oh yeah she's telling me to
just because
ah so many voice chats
it's so hard to find okay
let's see
oh my god please
yes
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
i love you
[Applause]
no no no why would i do that
well you stole my diamond so i stole
your admiral
fine
it's okay it's kind of like we're
trading lunch you know when it's like oh
you want to swap lunch
you can have my emerald
i have your time
yeah
wait uh are you currently betting for
the last race right oh okay okay
are they bidding
yeah the horses are
uh
i might bet for number one because toast
empire was on number one and one with
that one
but also
ah vatami's horse is not in there and
she got number one
but it's not in there the other one that
one was
oh oh yeah miku sample right
[Music]
i know wait they're choose ah those are
the available
oh let me see let me see they wrote it
here right yeah what's it say oh last
race
last race
and do we have
yeah we have okay i'm just gonna bet on
number one
that's gonna take a while
okay um are you gonna go now if you're
going tell me i'm gonna go too
ah
i'll stay here the line is long yeah
okay okay okay okay
you're loyal to number one huh
like how i'm loyal too much
no no no i never bet on that one before
oh really oh oh what am i saying five
okay
ah everybody who bought a ticket please
go away yeah yeah i didn't buy a ticket
yet yeah okay
oh
is saying anya stole her
ticket or diamonds
delicious
the tears of your dangerous game here
they're gonna let out the anger and
frustrations in
in rest later
aggression
aggression in my minecraft summer
festival more likely than you think
is
oh by the way what
fireworks didn't they say
i wasn't that happy
45 minutes
down
[Music]
the line is long
it's freaking long
is a minecraft head like she also has
like the blue thing on the left side
right reminds me of my
reminds me of my own head
my like my default yeah that's right
yeah
so i was like huh it's me no it's kind
of fun
i got sticky key
oh
why are you not turning it off turn it
off
but you can you can't squat if you don't
turn on sticky keys
i just have to do it slowly which is
more challenging anyway isn't it
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
you can't do that if you don't if you
have sticky keys on
[Music]
yes i'm here i'm right behind you
when did you wake up today um i wake up
at like noon
like it was just a normal time for a
whole life member yeah
i usually wake up a little bit earlier
but yeah i just felt like waking up at
noon
i woke up at
at nine oh i was supposed to have a
recording at 9 30
was waiting and stand by for half an
hour oh yeah i was told to come back in
like one and a half hours because
something went wrong and got delayed oh
yeah
yeah then we recorded for an hour and a
little bit yeah and then and now i'm
here nice okay
you're failing you're feeling refreshed
though right no sleepy no
uh
right now i'm okay but i'm sad i could
have slept longer uh
it's a it's a love arrow kiara will you
accept it
watch me
wait wait wait wait almost
nice no thank you feels just like when
you're in love i think that's the
feeling yeah it's like
a little bit of a heartache
what are they lining up for they're
lining up to bed for the last round guys
okay let's lighten up two then number
one
oh that's perfect combination
number one the horse strong because
one in the third race and one of them
isn't by strong because one in the first
range
nice choice
they need a second stall
no i don't think they have enough stuff
yeah one more employee please
you have a lot of employees can you
right you can't like uh land them
for the festival
yeah yeah
true right
unbelievable i'm not waiting for so long
here out in the blazing sun
please do some water at least
so much sunny i know it's different
remember like because last year i think
it was like night time but somehow it's
day time it keeps day you know when is
night time are we never gonna have any
night time
i think they turned it off yeah
they also turned off the spawning of
enemies
ooh
okay
yeah but are we gonna have fireworks too
maybe they're gonna like put on that
time for that one
yeah they should
they should
okay they have to they have to
daytime fireworks so cool
fireworks no i think it was always dark
[Music]
mm-hmm
nothing
how are you doing
you flirting with someone else no no
you're flirting with fauna and soda
simply i was trying to get food
ah
i have food too okay give me
yes
eat my food only
did i get it
i think so potato no i didn't get it i
think somebody stole it
no we need to we need to stay in the
secluded place but maybe after we bet
yeah
after we bend oh
oh
where is she
oh okay well
uh number four number four
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
foreign
okay
hello i'm back
[Music]
did you bet
how much did you bet
one i only have one
ah i bet ten on number one oh look down
how nice i am wow they're doing it so
properly
[Music]
nice they're in line so cool
in charge of like the line
you know in like conventions they always
like uh do have that sign like this is
the last point of queue and then
whenever someone behinds them behind
them like queues they you know
we transfer the sign
i wish we could have that
i thought the like if they're standing
on the side now somebody says i caught a
line did i know because like i was i
thought i was standing in a line in the
middle here and then suddenly i was in
the front so i was like okay
i think um
oh the line is so long
it's so long
it's gonna take ages maybe i should just
stand in line for fun i know me too
no no no don't make it longer than it is
yeah no it's just like to discourage
others from betting so not so less
people a little bit for number one you
want that return right we can play
something while we're waiting oh true
true true true
a fishing game
you can fish
oh yes um push the button to start the
game was to say
item fishing game
the center hopper
aim to get the items
into harbor there's there's hoppers in
the water
i gotta try it out oh
okay i guess i'm gonna try to i don't
know how it works though
where's the center item
the center push the button to start the
game
there's a cat in there
what
trying to get the fish someone rescue
the cat
wait
i need to oh
fish but like what
oh oh i get it
it's so hard
i don't even know what i'm doing
[Music]
the center however do you mean this one
or that one
can i can i put the cat in the hopper
wait i thought the music was for you
but no there's nothing in the chest yeah
there's nothing in the chest okay let's
return it oops
okay
i'll try
i don't know i forgot how to okay there
we go no no what are you supposed to aim
at
uh like like you move the items to the
hopper
[Music]
how did i i'm not oh i moved something i
guess i'm not a good fisher you know i
don't know much fishing experience
i fish things that move
i feel like i did something oh
i got an iron
nice
i got something yeah
okay okay
yeah what is this
slots
oh yeah that looks interesting it's a
crude
no money oh my god
you can
lend money
what the
get three gold blogs to get a prize cute
cute uh throw golden glass
no i got this i got three gold ingots
from choco sensei
oh
i didn't bring any gold i brought
emeralds oh man
what's this ah a ghost place
should we go for the uh can we don't
know if they're busy do they need like
an employee announced will be made when
it reopens it's not all right don't say
it's closed
yeah okay okay okay
what about this thing
huh
let's shoot the chicken yeah should have
seen the chicken before the chicken
floats lava take bow and arrow and
barrel stand behind the button press the
emerald bun start shooting game as if
you hear belle please return bow and
arrow put your high score in the tube
what's the side of the game okay want to
try
how many i can take just a stack of
arrows i guess
um yeah i guess so give back the rest
check up our armstrong button hide the
button okay it's over here
press the emerald button start shooting
you need to
right click
all right
[Music]
oh
i didn't get that one though more please
are there out of chickens
only one came down
yeah i think like this chance was like
really low because like they hatched the
egg and then sometimes it becomes a
chicken sometimes it doesn't right
at least i didn't shoot it let me try
one more time
oh there you go that's more
[Music]
and let me try let me try
what's your high score on two i don't
know i don't even know if i hit that one
correctly
if if if that was hit i think you will
get um
the chicken
it ends automatically ah
oh
it keeps going if you actually get
everything
go get them
no
[Music]
ah but you i think you missed one of
them
yeah that's one the last one i saw you
so three
yeah i didn't i only shot once
so that's one
yeah two you hit two you hit two
something's a bit broken here
oh
what
hello
[Music]
huh
oh my god come on
i like the idea of this but it
[Music]
chance of the
hatching is really low i guess what
that's great i hit all of them but there
was only one
ah
[Music]
what is that
what's on the scoreboard no one yet
high school well i'll write down two
i missed
more who what this one i wonder
this chicken one it's ollie
are you all right oh yeah two
but it was it was
two out it's how are you supposed to
like hit him when they're like
don't get salty it's my middle name
yeah
yeah oh i missed that one but got the
last one
yeah just two
all right two two out of three good
stuff good stuff
okay wait where is it
huh i forgot okay
okay
okay i'll return and i'll return it
later
two out of three
way
how is that how does that work that's
fascinating
nice nice nice size yes okay what next
go next
okay go next
what is this library by the way
write your memories all
let's oh this for later maybe
maybe at the end of the day
what's this
[Music]
yeah
they look like they actually look like
it
oh
the tree
that is so smart
isn't that it's me yeah yeah yeah yeah
memorable vlog
oh there's like names
happy potato
crazy kebab
sushi kebabs
[Music]
please press the button okay we can
order
what should i order what should i order
what should i order
and your favorite
my favorite but there's no quinoa kebabs
i would go for the subaru then um okay
okay
oh zora kebab
wait do you have to pay money
what
i thought it was gonna be free
i don't think it's free
oh i got it i
yummy
thank you but i'll give it back to you
because i have already i got another one
you have to eat lena yeah i'll eat the
rain
emma oh i do have emma rounds
i can play this one
i have which i'll give you one too this
is yours that you were supposed to win
from choco center
and i have 64 more
button push gatcha emma wrote one play
where do i put them
okie mochi ah you don't even have to put
them in
but i will what was that what did i get
something is this this one oh
cool
let's go i will i want more okay one two
oh
cool okay two emeralds i owe it two
emeralds one more
taco
you got it you go too
where do i put in my diamond
where do i put in my emerald
oh just like
but okay
oh
what did i get
invisibility potion
i got that one too
okay i only have one so
why do you put the row in the hopper in
the hopper
that's a dropper
and it's full
that's what you can get here because
hmm
i want to keep on the ride on the rail
on the ramp
oh this one yeah the hopper it's a
hopper
ah
there we go
it goes in the you just put it in there
okay i got three but i want to do more
all right
i will i'll give a six so i'll do three
more
okay
there you go another fire resistant
nice
i don't need that
tree
go go away tree sapling no fauna
saplings more fire resistance
yeah
and one more
oh wait
secret is living things
oh really oh yeah i got one living thing
i got a tadpole
what
weird
oh i think i got everything that i
needed yeah
nice
wait we still haven't seen you
[Music]
oh oh okay okay oh she accidentally set
it off i think
when do we go next where do we go oh i
can go like this
look at this what is this
is this where the sounds are coming from
yeah oh my gosh i think this is like
what pagoda simply made right i could be
wrong what look this is the mask the
mass shop is like here
oh eat
oh you have to ah that's how you oh
i see
wait what
oh i see i'm in cali and gouda
what did you um i accidentally somebody
did it but i i got monster senpai mask
oh
how do you take it one person won't
drive i said well i'm using okay
but but
somebody whose was it i don't know how
to ask
is is can you say senpai in france
in the chat no i don't think so
but just just write the
like in the minecraft chat
yeah how should i ask um
okay okay
close eye step
oh this is a game you can play with two
people elena oh yes yes
oh
someone guides you to the melon and you
might die
yeah this is the
yeah
okay let's see
oh but i have two so many items where do
i put them kara do you want to try one
see who you get
i want but how do you have to have to
pay no i think it's free but only you
get you get only one try
um i technically didn't try but i got
somebody else's mask so
ah
[Music]
where do i push
that that thing in there yeah
okay wait they're doing it right now
anya got something
oh mikosepa has hatsuma's head i think
[Music]
i wanna try i wanna i wanna try pulling
because technically this is not what i'm
following oh my god i'm for booking some
point well uh
i know your date is now a focus empire
oh my god
oh my gosh and then you're wearing the
sports uniform so technically if you
take off like your cape and shield
i am her maybe the [\h__\h] senpai i
talked to like i looked at in minecraft
maybe that wasn't even public senpai oh
[Music]
okay
okay let me see if i
who did she get i wanna play this but
where's space to put my [\h__\h] maybe here
okay okay
oh no
okay i'm gonna put on my mask
yeah everybody's head is there
well what are the odds how the [\h__\h] did
you get me
is it cheat
did you ask someone did you did you
exchange
[Music]
oh my gosh yeah maybe maybe we can also
punky
oh visa
she didn't say anything i thought
i thought that was you
oh crony
oh my gosh i almost followed zetta
instead because i saw your head running
off
you can switch heads with zetta
get hurt
ahead okay is this ah
oh george
kiara
okay when i want to want to go see the
race the final race
[Music]
god fox
god fox yeah the fox god
ready
maybe i can find focus senpai
hey where's my friend bye
hey there for rookie senpai with eop
mask
i am
[Music]
so cute
she talks in the eof language now yes
pagi
cause that what she's always says
oh my god
mask
i want to talk to her about tunic but i
don't know how to start the conversation
yeah monster senpai is flying with
luna's infamous right now
oh
oh she took off her head oh wow you guys
are twins now
twinning
what's so naughty
cute
oh man i wish i didn't take out my
sports festival outfit
don't need no folks
tunic no
okay
i said i said something
oh i'm so proud okay back to brainerd
elena one and only just plain just
raining
this test round right yeah
oh
it wasn't bad
it's going pretty fast yeah
but usually i think usually it's like
the result is always different you know
like somebody who goes like super fast
at like the practice you know yeah
so far it has been kind of different
okay
let's see
[Music]
go
go go power reindeer
i'm counting on you
[Music]
uh commentary has a comeback now
oh yeah
yeah yeah commentator
chihuahua
good
i think we'll see in a moment
[Music]
yeah we will see
oh i guess fawn also bet on vatami
senpai
[Music]
is
interviewing currently i guess
number two
oh my god
[Music]
i am the bgm uncle oh
oh god we have no idea senpai yes
[Music]
who's writing a super senpai
is
[Music]
eh you didn't even do that on purpose
did you
no
lucky
yes
i like how she added
wait did somebody get fake suicide
[Music]
and this time we have one more number
six
ah she lost her old minecraft account ah
that was the only other name available
uh-huh i see
ah
this is i stole her face
what is it a watercolor oh no she has to
use another person's face now
number one what does it find
will she really become number one
what will happen
this is the last round last round guys
the best horses oh oh number four they
have the order wrong but and um because
she's last
because she's announcing
go go tell us
two rounds no armor no swords wait is
she talking about oh they're doing
something else somewhere else right i'm
gonna give her
chicken
because if i got the chicken ah
mozzarella
god and god
oh nice
this is a really
special interaction and special the gods
are friendly with one another
because she's looking
[Applause]
um
let's see what else i can give her a
watermelon
[Music]
man if only i'm wearing my sports
festival
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
choose zombie
the gods are watching above us yeah we
are so lucky
the gods are watching
do you like game of thrones
no i haven't watched it i'm sorry i know
you like it
[Laughter]
i know you because after this is done
i'm gonna watch the new episode of the
spin-off because
like this night the new episode came out
yeah you've been talking about it a lot
so i was like huh she likes it really
yeah she really likes it huh
no i don't know yet to be honest the
first episode um came out last week and
it was very
violent like
pretty bad
no not violent but there was so much
blood that it was like too much to be
honest but that's just game of thrones
style i guess so yeah
yeah
oh no
anya is cute where were you when anya
was killed
you know
where were you when i used to
start excited
oh my gosh
no
japanese members probably don't
understand no
it's called they got the horse tickets
oh
he wants everybody who bought a ticket
to write down how many you got
[Music]
there's no
there's no there's no actual text
channel though
yeah there is there's the horse ticket
no kaika
[Music]
can you ride for me because i don't see
it
oh it's in the micro holo derby
you're not in it
oh i didn't join that one can you write
for me
kiara is what
uh number one ten tickets
thank you
what's up there oh they're so excited
what are they doing are they wrestling
i want to check out what they're doing
later
[Music]
dunk
wait guys how do you ride a pig
um you have to like put the saddle oh my
god put the saddle and then but you have
to
be holding uh the carrot on a fishing
rod
it's an item you combine the fishing rod
with the carrot
that's uh only then you will be able to
drive with it
yeah i didn't know you could put a
saddle on a pig
yeah i used to do that a lot
not in the hole or sober like back then
yeah it's it's really funny but not very
fast you know i guess
oh my god
senpai oh okay
i ain't done all day
crony come picky
yeah yeah perfect cronie
oh cronichiwat
where's crony
come on horsey what you waiting for
oh flair senpai is kind of the senpai
so confusing i can't even like look at
their head
anymore
i have to look at their their actual
name oh yeah
bae looks like she's an image that got
censored mozart wait where where is she
just like because there's so much going
on in her outfit oh
like that yes like censored
too spicy for minecraft
[Music]
everybody's like betting like um
50 like my god you guys are so rich
and here i'm like
[Laughter]
well you know in the end this is it's
just a game it's just a game
yeah that's called if you want to gamble
more then you can do it on the rest it's
you know
i guess so it tried right yeah i tried
like twice
how did it go it went well it went well
but it was like the lowest thing
oh
but at least you know the server like i
remember like last year it was a little
bit laggy
but
yeah today seems to be
totally fine when i first logged in i
was like should i turn on my shaders
apparently no
oh you got your shaders on yep fancy
it was more laggy but i think they
improved the server
didn't they do something um
i heard they did something no before i
think like they expanded it
my keyboard died i feel like i've been
having a problem with like my usb hub
oh yeah
where were you when laying aboard was
dead he's dead
i'm such a meme lord well funny well
okay it's connected again yeah it's my
usb hub it's not really my keyboard it's
also happening to my tablet specifically
indonesian memes
oh there's a lot
of indonesian names
oh indonesian memes
well guys what are some good indonesian
memes um usually there's a me there's a
really annoying meme when when i talk
when i talk and
i don't know where i forgot where the
meme came from i think it's from like a
person for example like they're they're
asking for direction in like another
language that's not english but then the
person
uh responded to them like
it means like i can't speak english you
know
yeah it's like a meme but then like
people started using it in chat
when i'm speaking english and i'm like
shut up shut the [\h__\h] up
i like
yeah these days
uh these days you are yeah it's it's
mostly like taken from like tv or like
some you know something like that so
it's like really not very contextual
[Music]
i don't know i'm not very like
what was that how about you
how about you guys
i don't know you you tell me of um memes
from
memes from where you are
austrian memes
specifically german ones i only german
beans i can i can pick up one right now
and i'm really um questioning myself why
that is the only one i can think of um
it's like um
you walk into a room yes where there is
um
uh
wait what was the word
yeah
oh yeah uh like a lot of straw
a lot of wood and you're like oh
oh why is there you know what the horses
eat or or what they lie on uh straw and
they're like oh what why is there so
much straw in here oh yeah but that's um
but that's um
[Laughter]
yeah my few german speaking people in my
chat are like no
no what what is it um
no no it's not it's not it's not
children safe or uh
friendly
oh it's not family friendly okay okay
okay okay
yeah and then somebody's like oh
basically the whole isen means yeah you
know like indonesian memes like internet
memes are so nonsensical so you know
eisen from bleach like
oh yeah basically like this guy with
glasses and then like it's a caption of
his face and then like
it means
[Music]
it's like
ah it's like a really weird play on
words
uh you know how this the saying it's
like you know when you when you think of
it and then you usually like say another
statement right for example like oh when
you think of it this is expensive or
something
but they make it so nonsensical like
when you think of it why are you
thinking about it or like the more i go
this way the more it goes that way
something like that it's so
and then
you know it's just like really really
nonsensical i really don't know how to
explain it to you i feel like
the recent state of like indonesian
memes is just
we laugh the more absurd it is the more
we laugh at it
i
understand everything yeah yes
same
i probably would need to see it yeah
like yeah see what you're talking about
then yeah i don't even know that
character from bleach yeah
i don't think it really makes a
difference
the more it goes here the more it goes
there
uncle 26 times multiplicator if they win
jaguar five times only
yeah
we're kind of like in the past modern
era of indonesian memes yeah
like nothing makes sense and exactly
because it doesn't make sense that's why
it's really popular my god
oh my gahashida is 13 times
multiplicator
that was the one that
is that yours
no i'm majid
yeah
oh my god
is five times multiplicator
[Music]
i guess what is it what about number one
number one
[Music]
did they ever say
you know
they didn't yet they didn't yet but the
fact that 26 times is for uncle means
people don't believe in alcohol oh my
god
wasn't it senpai on uncle
i think it was not just him oh yes it's
not a senpai on unko
she must go against all us that should
like motivate her even more
[Music]
i mean if i had more diamonds i would
have liked bet on people you know yeah
yes yes yes yes yes
they're definitely missing they're still
calculating one two i think so because
they were like yo you are betting
oh there's fake sweetie
what
must kill fake sushi
kill all the fakers
[Music]
oh maybe it's robuco senpai
yago five times
oh no
somebody
wow so like just for today the names we
say homono really is necessary
hold on i've lost you know five times
oh
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
not bad
and
we're missing two
five times yeah what the heck
is mine
arduino
free
only why is mine so low the lowest is
i'm the og match the high fan everybody
else go away
yeah well well let's see if we might
have some surprises here
yeah we have okay i bet all in from
majde haya just so you guys know
[Music]
i bet 10 on number one
unko muscle power
[Music]
mastery mushroom
mushroom
[Music]
yeah i bet all in i bet all in for much
the high eyes
one diamond
because
technically it's all in right
i spent all the diamonds i have left
you're all in doesn't mean very much
right now hey
hey
what
um what'd you say wait
um
you know like on top of your name
there's you say homonos like i had to
take i had to make a double take
yeah it's crony
so we say crony
oh oh mikko is leading
oh
it wasn't by following up subaru is kind
of third
yeah but who knows we might have some
surprises in spider webs
oh miko's taking some time
also last time she went there easily i
think she went for recently but miegle
got a big lead now
oh
where is my
oh no
go go go go
[Music]
no i was doing a third round or was she
really that slow questions
what
was she around behind so far really
[Music]
damn she's taking a sweet time
what was her horse called
uncle and horse
must be
taken apart afterwards
so put it in the recycler
[Music]
wait
oh
kuro is wearing
who said
that
[Music]
congratulations what there was like a
viewing thing oh sorry excuse me excuse
me it's like i'm viewing it
i think this this is also for viewing
everything's from feelings
looking at the camera
[Music]
we can go play nowaday now until the
fireworks yes
let's go play oh who's distributing what
oh those are just tickets
let's go play i can't even look at these
people's heads anymore i need to
i want to play the lava thingy oh yeah
yeah yeah let's do it let's do it let's
do it
oh my gosh gets the horse oh
what oh
the first person the first gets the
horse or what
oh i hope they will
have a
a
beautiful life
cherish like the color of the horses
where are you so cute oh um
[Music]
i'm behind the stand behind by the beds
do you care to join me where are you
what wait which bands um
right behind the watching stand like
there's a newly built uh watching stand
made out of um oh there you go there you
are
hi
[Music]
yeah where's she going
i want to try this one too
okay
oh i haven't returned the bow from ollie
game
oil
i think you can just use that one
yeah i guess so i have like seven arrows
but i'm just going to use five
are you supposed to stand on the
what on the you're supposed to sit here
but what is the cow there
yeah
can't go
i think like you hit the you hit this
and said you hit the the card instead
fireworks at 55 no actually fireworks is
soon do you wanna wait for fireworks
first whoa but then i think i can
squeeze in one game but it's just here
you have to be on the on the truck right
on the minecart maybe just on top of the
gonna be on top of the car i don't think
so
i think you have to like
ride it
is it okay if we kill it
i'll kill the minecart
uh oh yeah yeah true
you will be free kyle
oh sorry sorry sorry i'm really bad at
doing stuff like that uh uh wait uh i
have my inventory so oh
uh
okay
uh uh um i'll get it for you
no i got it i got it
oh you mean the meat
yeah
[Music]
okay five shots that's the phantom you
say you keep hearing a phantom there's a
phantom in the mine cart
it's like how do you shoot them
it's in the cart
i have no idea
okay
[Music]
gonna get dizzy with this
oh okay
i mean i got the card off the ship
oh wait i wasn't using my five shots i
was using like an endless uh oops and i
don't know how how often i even shot but
oh well um i think i broke the game
so we mustang
summit mustang i broke the game because
i shot the cart instead of the beef uh
what do you call this place
oh my mustang
[Music]
last time
somebody my sorry somebody my sorry i'm
so sorry i'm so sorry i'm sorry sorry
sorry
let's uh watch fireworks together
yes
[Music]
where
i know ah i think there's a
you could go up to the carousel to watch
that ah you want to go yeah sure sure
sure
doesn't even have to be the very top but
let's see what's up at the top uh huh
oh it's a bit dangerous here though
there's no like oreos wait wait where
are you
on top of the
oh hanabi sugar
where is the fireworks gonna be
uh we will see it
i think um that stage is where the
fireworks go off maybe
which stage
uh if you look to the right
[Music]
the white blue thing
and the seating oh there are
there's actual seating there maybe we
should be there yeah maybe
hmm
okay
what if i like
youtube
oh yeah they're all they're all going
there now so i think that's where it is
i see like the things we're like
probably gonna get out of yeah
okay
where do you want to watch
next to you
next to me
oh boy nothing
[Music]
fireflower is fireworks right
okay
yes we are at the stage in my already do
you want to like go at the back so you
can like look up better or the first um
there's so many people there i wanna be
alone with anyone okay okay okay
let's let's let's look at the corner at
the corner
oh is he how's the corner cozy corner
exactly
yes
gather in front of the stage wait so
like here like in front in front
what's in front
what the seating is for
ah in france like what's in front of
like here
thing up there that's when the fire
flowers will go off eh
two minutes two minutes wait so on top
or what
oh my god oh my god
control yourself
don't die with the light bro
huh
so where on top how do i get off the
stage
there's a
some stairs in the front of it awesome
stairs really
i am seated correctly
you are but why why are they telling us
to go up some
are you confused
yeah
believe believe in your
correctness believe in your correctness
okay
we have to set an example you know
okay also there's people behind us too
so yeah so maybe it is behind they sit
in front but maybe this this is in front
yeah i think so
now they're taking
seats
[Music]
right now it's going to be so weird
because we're we're just
nothing in the masters
[Music]
just trying to see who all those heads
are
yeah no
oh
no
so how senpai is wearing coyotes head
and it fits her her clothes really well
because they're pink
i'm just looking for if somebody got my
head but apparently not
oh
[Music]
is
wow
incredible
[Music]
dangerous dangerous
it hurts
i wanna i wanna check
i wanna check from the top from the top
of where we were supposed to be
[Music]
yeah
i'm just gonna take like a lot of you
know
p.o base
[Music]
so beautiful
oh
[Music]
oh my gosh part of the senpai
yes okay we got it
oh
is it i think it's calming down
holy [\h__\h]
oh it's calming down
it looks so pretty from the stage
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't know what sound that is
stuck under the stage
sounds really weird what is it
or pigeons pigeons
shoulders
oh
[Applause]
oh it's done
[Music]
let me party party
on yelp
[Laughter]
are you gonna eat it are you gonna eat
the fireworks yummy
oh
my god violence in front of my eyes
they did a great job building all of
this damn
nice
yeah gunpowder well spent
i'm really i'm really lacking gunpowder
in minecraft i wish they would give me
some
you should start killing the creepers
then i think uh nah [\h__\h]
[Music]
nobody fixed the other thing i think
yeah yeah
i want to play this yeah
but how
oh my god
let me find the chest
melon attack game player close eyes
navigator guide to melon ah
i found chests but they're for building
oh but this chest literally in front of
the thing um i don't know if um
no no but there's um
isn't there like a lot of axes in there
hmm
i found some chests where there's some
space
or
stuff also an ender chest after this you
will have free time
oh yay
nicer
oh my god
let me put my my important things
in here
first of all only using okay
i'm gonna take off my
mask because it's a little it's getting
a little bit suffocating
mask oh
yeah
finally
some fresh air that don't need that
oh
and what about the horror game is it
hope open yeah
but you want to try the melon first
right
yeah let's just do that one first
because now they're already lining up
for that
for the [\h__\h] house
okay i'm gonna put my stuff away we can
do once you lead me and once i lead you
okay
uh the lava is really hot
axis in chest
oh
what is the x for oh here we go
is there anything to fight i thought you
just no you you you the watermelon
attack the watermelon
oh
okay okay
oh it's okay i put everything away i'm
coming
wait
wait i thought it was an empty chest and
what is is there no um
chest where you can put your stuff
i didn't see one over there
hmm
you must have forgot oh the navigator is
up here oh
ah
supposed to be up here
okay no one's doing it right now so i'm
gonna go okay
i close eyes you tell me where to go
okay uh if you go straight three steps
how far do you go
[Music]
uh one two three okay um take one step
take two steps
one two
oh
turn left
here and take one step
one
turn left again
take one
step one okay take three steps
one two three oh that was three more
steps
one two three okay turn slightly right
take two steps
slightly here
one two turn slightly left again and two
steps
[Music]
one two
and then take two more steps
one more step i think
one
okay one more one more
i feel it's hot around me
oh one more sorry
oh
why do you keep like making it shorter
one more step i'm scared but no i'm not
scared
as long as you're leading me
more yeah one just one
okay turn right
more
try walking one step
yeah
okay take three steps
okay oh my god okay slightly left left
left not slightly just very left very
left
very left yes
later later uh more more more left
more oh yeah and then take one step
one
one more step please
one oh pop up okay um and then turn
right
right uh more please
more
um
too much too much slightly to the left
please okay
and then try one step
one
no
wait
um okay uh so go slightly to the left
and then one step
okay uh one more step one more tiny step
same direction
okay turn slightly right slightly and
then take one step please
yes and then two more steps please
[Music]
okay uh take one more step the same
direction
one okay and then turn right
i thought you know your voice it makes
me
it's so sweet it makes me feel so safe
okay then you better be safe um slightly
more right please
okay and then um go straight one step
um
okay uh turn slightly right just
slightly
slightly to the right
and then okay try two steps
one
two okay slightly to the left again
just one step try one step
okay uh three steps
one
two
three this reminds me okay turn slightly
round left and then hit
slightly left here yeah and hit
was hitting left or right
left left
why
okay maybe turn a little bit to the left
again and then hit it you're right in
front of the melon
the left here
really and then okay left maybe aim
lower maybe or i don't really know
when can i see if i have the axe
selected just just yeah you have the axe
selected
um
[Music]
did it work yeah it's working it's
glowing but do you have to destroy it or
what
not sure
[Music]
can i look
i don't know if you can look i have to
hit longer
ah and then you place a new one there
nice
thank you dana
okay
i was actually relaxing
really relaxing guiding you to
watermelon in a lava surrounded area
can i put it on top of that though
a spreadshift maybe
no it opens the chest i guess i have to
like
put one here first and then
i don't know i don't know i don't know
routes hold shift it smudge it yeah you
you hold shift while you put it
but now if i destroy it i'll just get
another like pack of melons right really
wait uh okay hold shift
crouch hold shift
yeah no no so it's like you get the
watermelon and it's kind of like the
same thing maybe as if you want to put a
sign on top of a chest
so in order so you don't open the chest
you press shift while you put it
[Music]
let me let me let me try
i'm too stupid right now
i'll just do it like
oh my god
let me save the day
okay and then she's gonna put it
yes that's how you do it so you crouch
if you crouch while putting it like it
won't make you open the chest
oh i think cronie is standing there
ready to do the yeah and she can go
first it's okay
that was suspenseful
yeah
riveting
but it was actually kind of relaxing for
me to be honest really
my eyes and letting it happen
actually not that bad and the bloop
bloop sounds yeah and the lava we're
also relaxing like as actually it
sounded like as if i'm in the middle of
a jacuzzi ah i mean if you think about
it that way
you know hot water right
yeah
just a bit more extra hot for the
phoenix
plus
my stuff
my bucket
my happiness bucket
fireworks the baked potato this i bring
back i wonder if the other game was
fixed too i'm sorry i broke it
um yeah it should be
oh
i'm so cookie
oh you put your mouse back on
yeah where are you
who is the the first
um whole life member whose stream you
watched
me
i forgot who the first is it's
definitely like somebody
but um
oh there's a cow
[Music]
no wait it has to be it has to be like
from a cliff i think like a memorable
thing actually is about like matsuri
senpai it was a clip about her like the
band-aid one where she put her band-aid
over her
i think that's the first one you saw
yeah
oh there is myosin by me
or
from black hair to white hair yes
i feel like in uh
maybe you should stand in line to assert
dominance
okay wait how how do i put my stuff
though do you want to hold my stuff
if you go i don't i don't know if i have
enough space but if you go all the way
over there straight ah straight there's
some chests of like building materials i
put my stuff in there
okay
oh under chest i haven't under my under
chest is full
why do i have heads why do i have miko
stamp ahead and fond of sarah's head
[Music]
is burning
oh
lava
bird
no she didn't put herself away no
oh no
oh no oh no no
she's just
she's burning again
oh okay
don't die don't die don't die if you die
don't don't die here
[Music]
whose stuff is this
uh
where
in the chest
no in my inventory i'm i think like i'm
i'm holding some stuff that are not mine
like this fauna head and uh don't worry
about it if it's just the heads then
don't worry about it
if they want a new one they can just go
get one again right
true no worries okay i'll put the head
in the ender chest though because
it would be sad if i lose them
oh my god
this is really cool i like the idea of
this damn who built this one do we know
i don't know i don't think so
it's chat no
it's chat now
it might only be one of the chat boy
hmm
i can put mine back don't forget the
elytra oh shoot you're right
the elytra
[Music]
oh i become
guava
like this maybe
let's put the electron in the under
chest
and swap it with something else
okay i have a torch but i don't really
mind it is fine
come on come on
okay i'm lying there's like roni is
still playing very slowly
trying he's playing slowly all right
then
we're we fast i feel like we did it
pretty fast
hmm
but there you know cronie and mummy are
on a date with like three girls from the
6th gen
yeah they're communicating probably in
very broken english and broken japanese
right now
wow taking three girls
so spicy
yellow who's guiding her
a lot of people basically like
um it's mume because she's the one
looking down and robokunsan is not part
of the group i think so okay then
yeah i think it's women then they
shouldn't have problems communicating
wait no no
is in their voice chat now oh all right
but maybe like only one person is
guiding because if there's multiple
people guiding it's very um
[Music]
you can't have multiple people guiding
it's supposed to be a game where you
test the bond of two people not three or
four five
exactly oh i'll take the x
[Music]
maybe
we can do two at once
what if somebody accidentally pushes
someone though
yeah and then you just wait behind i'm
like oh didn't you just wait a little
bit for five minutes later crony needs
some time yeah
we can try
moana
[Music]
i don't know
trust me okay go nah no wait i don't i
don't i don't want to accidentally kill
chris okay
because we're that fast fred she's
almost there though oh it's almost there
wait i'll be right back
okay
it's harder with more people guiding
really are they doing that is that what
they're doing
[Music]
there's like four people up here
no
god by the crooney time is ticking but
take your time because your time
your time is your time
time is time is no problem for you it is
time
[Music]
just just joking
not very funny
okay wait i'm kind of curious where
crony how corny is doing actually let me
she's so slow and now she's facing the
[\h__\h] lava
we're all right all right
go crony
come on can we confuse them even further
by helping them
be like the fifth sixth person to guide
her joining in the voice
hey cronie
[Laughter]
what if i were to um sneak up behind you
and slowly push your head
okay then
what if i were to make that a reality
don't make them let your dreams be
dreams
[Music]
she's mad okay
i trolled them for a second oh god
what what what did you what did you say
what you know
i just said left left straight but i
don't know
what happened with ioha
oh
[Music]
what happened to video how she burned
death
was it my fault
i hope not
sorry i don't think so
yeah i don't know where she was
she burst off geez what
oh no
brother you don't have to go few major
oh my god kroy's so close though
been there for like 10 minutes
come on come on go crony
go crony
go crony go
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's back on track though yeah
so why is she looking at right here yeah
she's always looking in the wrong
direction
[Music]
and was i also always looking like
sideways no
no i think i pretty much told you to
like turn so that if you turn then
you'll be turning your head right right
[Music]
like me this is what this is how people
feel i think when uh when we do like
mario kart tournaments like they can
only watch so they're like oh my god
brody has trust trust issues i think she
has trust issues with like her um her
girlfriends
oh
oh but she's she's closer though maybe
they're like just leading her in a less
conventional way
so yeah definitely
dad is saying that we were really good
at it
yes
let's see how it will be the other way
around though oh
well it just means like if you're doing
well it just means that i am a very good
guide right
are you are you are you as good of a god
as i am
[Music]
i can be a
i can be a different kind of guy
sure
[Music]
this is an idol from
my my favorite island work
you probably expected something else but
i'm just nerding out
yeah one last thing okay
go go
hit it
you're doing it
maybe she needs to like walk further or
maybe
ah yeah a lot closer longer
[Music]
mind watermelon
watermelon
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna go down so i
can yeah
apply some pressure
oh my gosh she's literally in front of
it
yeah it was it was kind of like when i
was doing it
like when knowing you were doing it
i wanna like what are they doing
[Music]
you have to hold it
yeah you gotta hold the button down
[Music]
wow
oh brony
i'm back
who would you would you say i don't know
it was mummy guiding her so i'm
wondering like where's the problem
they're speaking english also they broke
band block
what the heck
oh my god okay we just start okay we
just start
she's already there like yeah she's
literally already there okay let's let's
let's start
i'm gonna close my eyes
am i hitting
am i uh facing the right direction
you're looking straight right now yeah
so yes let's go like baby steps okay
yeah one uh three steps straight
how far is this
very good another three steps straight
i'm gonna do a speed run
turn left
is this enough
oh only your head moves interesting yeah
um do one tiny step
no
a little bit more left
yeah one more tiny step
uh-huh uh a little bit more left
a little more left
yeah tiny step
i'll be careful uh louis is passing by
okay no problem now's crony passing by
which just wait wait okay okay
go croning don't run it okay okay um a
tiny tiny bit left
like this
yeah and straight straight
another one
one straight
yeah
okay one more
one more
a little bit more left
this right yeah straight okay one
two
three one more one more
a little bit more left a little bit more
left here
yeah and straight straight one two two
three three
four four
beautiful five five
six six
seven seven
eight eight
nine nine
oh one more
okay i turned right
how much
oh quite a [\h__\h] a nice nice uh
was 90 degrees 16 90
how much turn right now a bit more a bit
more
okay make a step
one tiny step here
okay a bit more right okay
um a bit more
okay and one baby baby step
bubble bubble step more right all right
another baby step
more more right i guess
okay
i want another baby step yes
okay let's um
yeah more right more more more more more
more more okay step baby yes
yeah okay that's good um one more step
one more step
one more step one
one more step okay
and
90 degrees left what the fudge okay
is this just a good put them on the left
yeah yeah enough yeah
yeah and then well one step
how is it another one
and
a good amount of right please to the
right this
yeah and in the step
amazing
step please
step
yes one more one more okay yeah another
one
it's so fast like what the hell were
they doing before another one
uh-huh another one another one
yeah
okay
more step more step one more more one
two
one more
one more one more
and then to the right side to the right
side how much
quite a bit more put it more
yeah well yes a bit more a bit more
beautiful
please step ahead about one two step
a little bit more right a little right
more more more
yeah yeah
step one baby step baby step baby yeah
yeah a bit more to the right uh-huh
okay baby step
uh-huh
uh now
a baby step baby step
okay uh one step one step
two steps
three steps
four steps
uh-huh well uh three more steps
huh beautiful turn left
left
a bit more a bit more a bit more and
um step big step
yeah
now hit it uh do i need to aim lower or
nothing you're good but just uh hit
stronger like longer
yeah you did it i did it yay
and then and then
do i
i'll take the take one melon i guess
yeah do you know how to place it i think
so
here we go
chad you have to time how long my try
took then how long crony stride took and
how long might it's right let's go
oh she's doing one of those empire i
think nice
nice
you're really you're you're a really
good guy i acknowledged it
and really it yeah it does actually
sound pretty relaxing like the blue blue
blue and then like the guys like turn
left it's actually relaxing yeah i get
it i get it
okay let's play another game
what do you want to play what what
speaks to you
what speaks to me um
aside from the face oh look that's so
cute
yeah
it's really look takoyaki stand or not
baby
oh yes
what does that mean
it's always so nice to see how like they
come up with these creative solutions i
love it yeah no i'm going to take your
eyes oh yeah we're going to take oh do
you want to go to the horror house
[Music]
they did say something in the chat that
like when it's um open again
like when there's space again they let
us know
oh [\h__\h]
do i go to the is there is there a chat
room for a whorehouse
uh
is there
[Music]
can we enter with two people does it
have to be
low
solo
and they're gonna have a long shift
today yeah
relatively long so
damn oh
cute
a real luna
i watched do not stand by playing uh
rust a little bit the other day oh
really
yeah
very cute destination very cute
looking at sumaru senpai doing her thing
oh
oh are we like registered i wonder can
we go
um i'm gonna take all my stuff
oh yeah you don't you didn't take it
back or was it did you
oh no not yet
okay okay
[Music]
this
squashy wait please
yes
squishy away please oh my gosh i'm so
close to like holding
i'm so close to like holding h to like
put all the stuff in the inventory is
there like um oh oh yeah this is like a
minecraft equivalent of that
ah [\h__\h] right i have no gold [\h__\h]
i need gold oh yeah i have gold what
four well four i wanna play the slot
missy i'll show you sure sure hold on
excuse me
my diamonds oh i put them in the ender
chest i think
[Music]
is this broken though is it supposed to
be like this like
this is normal this is just what the
last person ended up with
what is up
[Music]
they're giving out like uh tickets with
like numbers to
like say it again
oh yeah so you know when's your turn
okay
uh we're supposed to get one two
i might take a while
[Music]
oh
yay i think i got it oh i'm back i'm
almost back soon
number 10 weight number 10. and number
10. i started to hire mascara really
i think so
[Music]
i got number 10. i think that counts for
those of us okay
okay i wanna play slot machine
cloud machine
i'm hungry
hungry
for my real real life
number two
okay so professionally
[Music]
yes
thank you
okay i just throw it in there and i can
slide
with the
kiwky
one more hi
oh here we go
ah
what are the rewards or three gold vlogs
okay i'm gonna try i'm gonna try
yeah yeah
okay
i like the sound it's so
loud so dramatic so industrial oh
come on come on come on
now i can gamble more oh you're a
diamond out of toilet oh my god i could
have used that for horse bedding
only one two i got two
oh can i can i do one yes this is here
here take it
thank you
nice
oh no
i already lost
there's like so many more
like games and they're also so
professional compared to last year it's
so cool right the stall that they came
up with
damn they all got so much better at
minecraft um respect you know i feel
like even if the festival is over you
can still play
a yokata review what's this
entrance
safe locker what's this
huh here we go free play
is it like a [\h__\h] house but it looks
happier
what is this
maybe
a trap house or something
oh dear because it says like a safe
locker it says
yeah
please put your stuff after please go in
after you have uh you know
put your stuff away yeah i'm putting it
in now does it have space for all of our
stuff
not mine certainly
[Music]
okay i'll go in fast
oh what is this it'll be fast okay
you'll be fast okay okay okay
bumpy speed
whatever it is that waits in there i'll
be fast hmm
i still have hot wings and my shield
there we go
i shouldn't have brought so much stuff
but i was stressed out okay
oh i forgot to return the axe
okay you can do that
what do we have please touch
reassuring so safe
business oh was it supposed to bounce
ah
because i
ain't gonna shop
i don't think i'm supposed to be here
oh
[Music]
glitched under the base of this
thing that they built here i think i
have to drown myself because i don't
know how to get out
okay
killing myself right now
okay that was weird
[Music]
well no problem for phoenix
dying once dying twice styling dying a
million times
in style
phoenix
die now buy water oh what's that
what is the fire
yay
let's go
one more
what the hell was the problem what did i
do
[Music]
you know the the the like beside the
takoyaki stall they have a ringworm
stand so cute
oh
who built this thing i want to
write an inquiry
[Music]
and the scaffolding leads up to nothing
because it's blocked i have to destroy
it oh
i want
something's free
oh my
my keyboard is dead and i'm stuck at
jumping
i'm stuck at the jumping position
because my keyboard's dead
i'm stuck
oh my god stop
oh thank you
something's broken
i'm gonna give i'm gonna play with
pumpkin pie
yes
block of redstone
yeah my keyboard got stuck yeah i think
i need to check the connection of my usb
hub it's been really annoying these days
i wasn't crouching and the first time i
went on it i was also jumping but it
didn't work i don't recommend you dana
to try this one because um you get stuck
in a place that you can't get out of
unless you break something i don't want
to break anything
oh wait can you come out
can you go um yeah i will come out by
[Music]
taking my life
my birthday
okay
yeah
i i give up i guess
i keep laughing i won't know what this
was
yeah maybe like a trap house
ah
yeah
oh oh well i need a gun okay unless you
want to try do you want to try
oh but i'm i'm i'm afraid i'm gonna
break something though
hmm it's already broken you can't break
anything more
do you think i look good with mikuty
head
i looked at your headphones
i was like why aren't you standing next
to me
yeah somehow i have mikochi and fauna
head in my inventory
time to play some pranks on mikochi go
go
yes
i've done though here oh my god i
thought it was real caleb and why is her
shirt red
what is this what is this
that's like a shooting gallery
ah or is it like the hammer thingy oh
yeah
or i guess it's like but there's no
hammer function so you shoot yeah yeah i
guess
[Music]
what
for for the slot machine i can use it on
the slot machine
oh
that's a bit worse
i'll take the gold
give me the gold give me
okay
oh
blazing rod
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna check i'm gonna
try
chocolate oh
nice one just wait there
stay stay stay stay there
and then we'll give you
something
it just takes a little while
did you get it
i don't know
i think you did i heard oh a blaze rod
yeah
okay i'm gonna shoot from here
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
i got totem of undying
but i got the fireworks doesn't that
mean that ah is that venus yeah it was
mine i think
i was like i was in the max green
it's not like at the same time oh i'm so
confused
me a maximum i know i got it now i got
it nice there you go
three
can i really get all these
like precious things for free
i guess so
[Music]
[Laughter]
just like went there oh oh someone oh a
couple people in there maybe they can
figure out what's broken
well maybe
let me kill
myself your slot machine let's go
someone's like it's id economy so it's
cheap
oh
oh shhh
you must have been really lucky there
yeah you got it i've got a blade problem
well you brought me good luck i think i
sucked away all your luck
[Music]
and i still haven't even brought in the
third person right for the wakayashi
yeah i guess so i don't
oh i don't think i can wait that long
do you have to go soon
no i just don't feel so well to be
honest oh no we should rest yeah i also
have i also haven't been like feeling
well especially them like the past week
so yeah i totally um i think i get it
yeah
but um i mean if you if you want to go
now it's um it's all right
are you i mean you want to like go
around a little bit first like maybe
check out the stuff that yeah if we've
missed something nice yeah just the
stuff that doesn't need like um lines
yeah
and oh don't forget to write your
console before you leave
so the snare
[Music]
and this is just the back side of
something oh that one too that one
that's the stuff that was the one where
kyle i was fighting
[Music]
oh where's that one
well look at them chilling they're
chilling
[Music]
oh
nice chair solutions
these
i want to
drink
some nice stuff
[Music]
what's this
oh menu draft beer
milk lambies sushi
water yakisoba water kebab
ringo malpine
chloe melon
what's ahoy mo i don't know
hoimo there's um and then luikinokosu
oh
[Music]
the server
yes i think so because it's her shop
yes yes
[Music]
oh they're like please
oh
next is number three dang we're number
ten
yeah i don't i don't think it's
happening in the next one hour and yeah
or even
like since since number two is called
it's been what 20 minutes or so yeah i
guess so
pretty long
so so popular damn
yeah
yeah but it is it's like amusement parks
like you know when you go to amusement
park yeah sometimes you have to wait for
like two hours or something just yeah
or even more
yeah gotta get the fastpass
yeah fast pass please
fastpass please
yeah
where is my queen where's my kinopo
i'm waiting
oh is that a oh that's fun
what's that
an obstacle course
am i allowed to like rob this place
oh they don't know
it's ahoy mo like emo like potato
ah
i see oh there we go
thank you
ah nice you want to try the other single
course thank you louie
yes of course i do
there's no chest here too there's a lot
of people trying it here
but also much stuff in here
yep
how about just not dying i mean dying
here is a
not so high chance because there's no
lava it's just lava blocks
i have a totem of the undying which i
guess i'll waste right here
i'm gonna just like
put the important stuff
in my under chests
but even okay you die it just drops
there on the floor
true
[Music]
no time no no i haven't seen anyone die
here before
i mean i mean you could be the first
i don't take too much damage
yes
oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
okay
i didn't take any damage what the hell
what
how do i find it
i'm like focusing on like the stuff from
the festival
i don't want to lose them so i'm going
to put them
what is this yo this place is so popular
now
yeah
there's a lot
oh my my elytra i guess
why am i not taking damage
i mean now i was crouching but
do i not do not exist here right now
you're on top of the bed right now just
like staying quiet
yeah you're on top of the bed on on my
side
interesting
[Laughter]
i think
uh must be some kind of
land because i i ran through the
obstacle course two times already
oh and i never took damage but i fell
down
oh cool
like your body is here but your soul is
somewhere else yeah yeah yeah that
freaks me out elena i follow you
okay let's see i'm your i'm your angel
i'll protect you okay
those are all please
[Laughter]
[Music]
and they're watching over
yeah you're just like here i love her so
sad
yeah open for me no one else opened the
door for me
thank you
i'm standing behind the door oh no
the pressure plate won't break for me a
straw projection
i'm dead
no okay i opened for you i open for you
there we go
[Music]
okay
you can't see me but you can feel me
yeah i might i guess so
wow
such a supernatural experience i'm gonna
eat
because what if i hit people wait can
you feel it when i hit you here right
no no i guess not it didn't even
register okay my dad my game is
completely dead i guess
you want to try relogging
nah it's okay
but you have to ride you have to ride
the console and before you go home
[Music]
yeah yeah i will
what is this this is climbing thingy
warrior fighting ah
oh my god
mao 69 arena i have no idea where she is
okay wait let me let me let me quickly
let's see if a relog fixes this oh my
god it's so hard the timing
what did i do
oh okay she re-logged she's relonging
okay you're here see me okay yes i see
you
see me
yes
i am
i'm real i'm real
i'm real yeah i just wanted to make sure
you
listen by scaring me she was about to
hit you know
she was about to be on an intentional
target
i'm gonna um
give back my ticket unless you want to
keep it and go later
[Music]
i don't know
i also don't know
um or do you want to give me the ticket
yeah that's what i'm doing and then
yeah and then i guess if i end up not
going then i'll return the ticket to
them
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
yes yes yes okay okay
okay
but yeah that's where is that writing
thingy yeah yeah yeah let's look for it
let's look for it
i wonder if you can like run the
obakeowski like after this festival is
done because that's what i'm afraid of
like it seems like though that they need
someone to supervise it yeah that's why
they need them to be in voice chat and
that's why it was close during the horse
race yeah maybe maybe
maybe okay it's okay i don't really i
don't really like obagi anyway
scary okay okay okay
yeah where's the console place
we saw it but i forgot
[Music]
i was the one with the books right
oh i don't even remember anymore
but honestly you know i think um
[Music]
is is is everybody else still streaming
because i feel like i also want to
stop streaming oh i think
they left good and they just left now
yeah
i feel like i might wanna
you know do a bucky ascii but maybe like
maybe off stream i could record oh my
god somebody's on fire
master senpai
on fire
do you think we can ride the carousel
though wait can we
i want to try i want to try i want to
try they all have saddles so i don't
know this is work maybe you mount them
you can't can't go on the peep just like
a cat oh my gosh oh my god
[Music]
i wish like we could have like something
that two people can ride in minecraft it
would be so nice
we're riding it right now but how do we
how do we safely get off that's why
there's water at the bottom i think i
guess so
cute
yeah carol look this way i wanna take a
picture
okay hello hello
yeah i was gonna say like i think if you
like uh use the
uh the the one next to me we can take
like a good picture
because they're right next to each other
can you get off safely
well it was i didn't die i mean
technically it's safe yeah
safe i'm coming
swim swim swim swim swim
yeah only a boat in minecraft i think
i should make it
why i wonder
i noticed that this season this season
this year there's no such thing as like
a love tunnel i think like moona made
that one last time oh yeah
yeah
yes
yeah we ended up going like the six of
us last year
kara looked this way
okay i think i think i took a good i
took a pretty good picture i think i
kind of don't know but you know
i took several this place is not safe
this is what's the word
[\h__\h] hazard
oh my god
[Laughter]
wait how do i come down oh uh shift
wow i literally didn't fall
what
yeah i didn't fall i left
i'm up here
okay guys
yeah i'm pretty impressive aren't i okay
i'm gonna go down
i wanna take one last picture
the pig is down okay
oh yeah yeah yeah on this stage there's
no more firework now but maybe here we
can pick it here you can take it okay
i don't i'm not wearing the mask anymore
yeah i'm not wearing the mask i don't
think i'm not wearing the mask but wait
uh i'm gonna move let me put away
oh
okay
i don't know i'm holding the horse
bedding paper
oh [\h__\h] sorry
okay
i'm gonna take a picture hold on
i'm going to crouch
[Music]
stickies
okay
yeah i took i took i took pictures
already okay
so beautiful
beautiful story skye
[Music]
thank you everybody for watching thank
you you still want to like ride the
console are you up i can ride the
console for you you can type it i can
look back
yeah no i'm i'm good but i had fun thank
you for being my date today yeah thank
you i had a lot of fun
like so much holy [\h__\h] the games are
incredible yeah it's so amazing
i didn't realize at all that this was
like there's so many people were
building so much stuff yeah
it's very very very lively
yeah
someday we will go to
vegetable in japan together yeah i want
to hey
you can watch fireworks
and guys i i see you soon okay and
schedule is out and the
secret collab partner on friday by the
way is amer not much of a secret just
wanted to sketch all the time
we're gonna play an fps game probably
[Music]
a kiss to end the date so spicy
[Applause]
i'm gonna watch uh the second episode of
house of the dragon now and then fall
asleep and have a second breakfast
okay
i'm gonna i'm gonna continue streaming
i'm gonna like take a break for one
minute and then i'm probably going to
continue streaming but i think i'm going
soon
okay i want to ride the console for you
too
yes
tell them uh
10 out of 10 on yelp by kiwawa 10k 1010
yelp let's go
uh very very
tediy moments
uh
much
love
and
uh kiara is killed
four times three three times no kiara is
chad you better take notes because i
might forget
my i can't i can you know my brain is
not working correctly because the very
cute girl is right in front of my eyes
oh no what do i do
i'm gonna do you once do you want the
the thingy uh the keychain oh yeah
yeah of course i do i'm gonna make it
into a keychain i need to figure out how
cause like i
i made the
the pixel thing the iron beads thing oh
yeah view looks exactly like you look
right now but i don't know how to make
it into a keychain i'll figure it out
and then i'll send it to you
[Music]
my gift to you okay i'll be looking
forward to it
yeah i wish you a lovely evening nina
okay beautiful lady look at her look at
her rocking the stage dancing and dance
no stay on stage be an idol
i don't know
okay okay i'll stay here i'll stay here
i'll stay here
my idol man
whenever kiara gets offline i'm going to
like take like a break for like one
minute and then i'm gonna come back okay
guys
so if there's like a now loading screen
the stream's not ending
you know okay yes yeah continue watching
later yeah
we're in germany
[Music]
fun moments
i'm also gonna
go for one minute be right back
[Music]
do
and
okay i am back
i am back i think
i am back oh we are just gonna be like
uh
i'm i'm going to go for the console
place
i'm gonna look for like where we uh
where i don't know there was like a
board where we can like you know
tell us our impressions
and everything but i can't really find
it anymore
where is it
a very successful date
nice
yeah um kimawa was um the one who
invited me this year and um
it's well
i mean i'm glad when diamond royal
fighting le mans 16.
closed captioning not available
[Music]
okay
i'm really curious what kind of game
this is
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what kindness
okay the idea economy is so messed up
you know
diamonds everywhere like cor you know
the club
what the hell
guys
where's their frog
the frog
[Music]
he was lit i don't have it
good dog
oh my god
so stupid
stupid frog
oh my
god
so stupid
stupid
stupid frog
god
oh man
i'm gonna
i'm gonna i don't know i'm gonna turn
into fauna to cope
with my sorrows
[Music]
so sad
um
bring mikko head
you know they said it's like only for
the festival day
so i wonder if they're gonna like wipe
it off or something
i've never seen like an animal that's
stupid
it's not even moving
it's not even me
okay
um
let's see
anya and zeta
where is ania and zetta
are they like uh vc i'm gonna i'm gonna
check
they're in the vc i might want to um
join them but if not then
i don't know
[Music]
i wonder if it's okay to join their um
wait i'm gonna find them first though
i think it's gonna be weird if i like
joined them but i'm not
here
zetta tried to swim in lava where is she
[Music]
here
oh diamond block kind of important huh
okay
let me
anya
what [\h__\h] doing
[Music]
maybe
what's this
oh
ah
okay okay i don't understand
oh my god
oh do i have to like jump
oh is fawn ahead gone
oh my god
oops
rip on ahead
it's gone forever i forgot i was still
wearing it
rip on ahead
it's okay i think it's only for like the
festival anyways
hmm
yeah i kind of don't know
how
hello
[Music]
today sorry no it's okay
um
no problem so
today so many many members
very heavy
[Music]
you know how you make this
yeah i
yes
[Music]
thank you
yes
and make it
nice yeah okay
come back and let's go
jump
on it
[Music]
i try again
okay please
[Music]
foreign
sorry
[Music]
yes
oh
amazing
wow you can make two by yourself
eat
[Music]
hold on
try again try again
one push
please one push oh
i got infinity ball
if anything oh
[Applause]
nice
nice nice infinity people nice
i forgot i lost my phone ahead
my god
no
i think it's the distance
[Music]
thank you
no problem
congratulations
oh you got something
oh
the stairs
come on come on come on come on come on
[Music]
oh
no arrow
[Music]
okay my arrow gone
oh no
oh
both are hard
[Music]
too dangerous please be careful
yes
[Music]
how
oh
[Music]
if you
wow okay yeah
that's cool
okay
[Music]
let's try
ah
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
so
no
so close
oh my god
[Music]
um
i got that wrong
oh my god i got that wrong let's go
let's go
fry again
[Music]
what
this trampoline is so
very difficult
yes so difficult so difficult yeah
[Music]
okay
yes i will go
i'm gonna watch
ah
too fast
oh first yeah
[Music]
oh my god
what's that thing like
let's go
oh my god let's go
please push
concentrations
so congratulations
thank you
yeah
no
man
[Laughter]
they're so annoying
they're not even like questioning it
anymore
oh my god
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god
is so heavy today
there was like 30 people oops
i died
oh oh my god oh my god
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
um
play minecraft okay
yeah yeah
yeah
literally
let's go
yes yes yes yes and he got
[Music]
oh
yes
what kind of jump i don't know i rotate
it i rotate it like
i rotate it a lot it's fine
yeah what am i riding what am i gonna
write
oh
[Music]
is there like a room is there like a
place where we can like uh write a zen
tai teki uh review of the festival
or just this one i'm not sure
because i thought i saw one but maybe
it's just for this maybe was there one
last year because like this is like my
first summer festival by the way if you
didn't know
i
don't know um my item should be here
yeah let's go
is that okay
[Music]
um i last time i checked it was still at
fifth
yeah i don't think horror is like
i don't think we're like
getting there soon i don't know is that
that long yeah i'm actually 10 but i
lost my ticket i wonder if i can go with
you guys
yeah yeah
[Music]
thank you okay
all right
it's still number five i don't think
they're gonna be like finished for you
another
so-and-so hour i might just stop the
stream and like like record record
yeah i mean i'll still be streaming so
like if people want to see
us yeah yeah oh yeah yeah if you're
gonna be streaming that's okay yeah i'm
gonna be streaming um
number oh it's at the sixth number so
that means like three more three more
more with this one actually not so bad
mm-hmm i'm gonna i'm so bad i'm gonna
take a walk i'm gonna take a walk alone
for a little bit i'll call i'll get back
to you i'll just i'll just stay here in
defense
yeah if it's gonna be our turn i'm gonna
i'm gonna um chat yeah just check me all
right thank you
all right
see you later thank you
oops
why is there a creeper
um ah couldn't they write your memories
of today in the book
put your books in the barrel below where
we'll read them
take a book from the barrel below
[Music]
hmm
did i accidentally take something that's
not rightfully mine
this is
put your books in the barrel below
is this empty
ah so the right one is empty
the right one is empty the left is
already
filled
yeah see this is close
like for example this one is not empty
see yeah okay i got you
this one is not filled
okay
um
[Music]
i'm gonna write it
is
oh i can i guess i can ride it at the
cafe or something
oh man hold on
i can't walk
because if if i write in japanese it's
if i write in japanese i become unable
to walk oh god
oh no
oh no how do i change language what do i
type again
[Music]
uh what do i type to ah there we go
key
okay
y'all just right here
[Music]
okay
ah that's right
[Music]
okay
and then
oh oh we played the
[Music]
um
we played the
what do you call it like the
melon
attack
the melon attack game
[Music]
attack i don't know maybe maybe later
maybe later
it's not our
[Music]
it's not our turn yet right
still like to yeah
trust me
let me check let me check actually
[Music]
axis ingest melon attack game
okay yeah it is the metal attack game
yes yes yes yes
um
yeah it's called mountain attack game
oh
wait hold on
challenge that we oh
did you do the melon attack game and
zetta yeah i did oh yeah i did
you want to do that it's like two people
how do i do the old game
it's like um you close your eyes and
then there's gonna be um someone who's
gonna be
sorry i accidentally picked up the
gotcha i don't know how to i don't know
i don't know how to do
this um which one the the mask
i mean technically like stream's over
right
like
yeah yeah and also i got zen lost as
well so yeah i burnt my phone ahead i
feel so bad
no yeah i also got sandler so i was
thinking of like
dude
whatever this lever yeah
[Music]
oh
is
the outfit that's like similar to mine
oh yes oh yeah
yes
nine
yeah
they're talking to everyone right yes
yes yes i've gotten a chance to go
inside
[Music]
oh no
i'm gonna go to the toilet oh no oh no
my usb hub is
yeah i can stop walking guys
i'll be back i don't even see you
anymore we're just raining find rain in
the game
oh you're here
[Music]
okay
nice
[Music]
hi
oh
yeah i do
did you try a moon assembly's place yes
i did
did you
it took the kyle and it should be like
near kyla's place but i don't know i'm
not really sure about the exact location
of the place
what do we do here
[Music]
in
um
[Music]
oh my god
okay
hi
it's iris
grandma hold it up
let's go nice new recipes unlocked
dang
let's go
yes yes yes yes hey
[Laughter]
i don't know how how many times can you
try like you've got a system usually
there's
me too
you don't really need stuff
oh yeah
[Music]
i just want to look at the beautiful
fireworks you know
oh that's it
i do have a house in jail what do you
get
i forgot where it is
what do you think i did i do have a
house and jp server but i i don't think
i remember
i'll search you don't have a house in
the id no not that i do
um i got given a house actually by ollie
i think was it
but i don't remember
i don't remember where
oh
the library
[Music]
[Laughter]
as wrists
yeah
hell yeah is it that's head is cursed so
she can't wear masks so sad yeah i'm
kind of so sad
so sad
[Music]
[Applause]
it was taking too long
yeah food
anyone food uh my
oh this is throttling flesh can you can
you get rid of flesh
[Music]
what
i took his glass bottle
okay open your flight of senpai
when you're flying senpai
thank you
i need food oh i'm gonna go slot please
lots again okay okay oh you're gonna
oh yeah you can do it with um what was
it again emeralds
do i have
food please
[Music]
is
what
[Music]
uh oh should we join
maybe oh
wait
what um
what is um oh the one with let's send by
polka senpai i i think um let me ask
yeah oh yeah cause it looks like
shirakin
it looks like she's like a chat instead
of her house chat
[Music]
okay okay
okay we need to go to the vc okay
hello
okay
[Music]
in these books okay okay
um which one is the empty one this one
is filth
my cursed head
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
um
yeah please please wait
um um um
this one wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
okay
nice
this is so cool
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Laughter]
please come
[Music]
let's go
oh
this is so dark thing so cool right
yeah it's so cool we're falling
wait so do i do i proceed
[Music]
okay
anthony
[Music]
um
to like hide the screen but then it will
crash and set
[Music]
the one obvious issue that
i don't know how to solve
[Music]
yes
okay
[Music]
hmm it will crash if i hide the screen
if i
hide the screen so i'll do this instead
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
i'm glad you're here
[Music]
switch on
it's like a puzzle
why is there no pgm in my game
oh oh oh
[Music]
let's go
what if i don't ditch the door what
happens
i'm sorry
[Music]
oh
yeah maybe the wind ah yeah let's go
let's go
um
[Music]
hello
you know this hits hard i also forgot
where my house is
oh no what is this oh i can't go
i can't go past yeah i can't go forward
okay
but
god your scream scared me sorry what's
funny
scream
you want to open this one
yeah let's open this one maybe maybe
because it's the dark because maybe it's
the way oh no
it's dark oh it's all right it's like
empty end look
oh my god
no there's something yeah yeah there's
some name
oh my god oh my god did you guys see
that yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah well
what's up what about this what's this
oh
what go further you can actually go over
there
yeah
i'm stuck you can go first
i think someone can't
hello hello
hello
hmm
[Music]
a wind there was a gust of wind look a
gust of wind helped us
i wonder what it could be for your
imagination
oh my god a gust of wind helped me
how do you go down
oh my god
oh my god my neighbor is loud
sorry
[Music]
how to talk
hello
[Music]
is
yeah okay
[Music]
yeah
yeah it's just like in front of our
house so it's like
um should we open the door
yes yes
yes my house will come
yeah my house now welcome my house
is
[Music]
you know
oh
[Music]
goodbye
hello
[Laughter]
good so good
oh so nice
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
very nice
[Music]
okay
it's so cool it's so cool
that wasn't that wasn't above just that
there was like there was like uh a cart
in front of me but there wasn't no one
so
yeah i wasn't advancing that was not a
bug review review
[Music]
i'll go put my mess okay okay um i'll
turn off my vgms
me too
medium
i was like oh my god drama people freak
off
the card that was advancing and
yeah
in front of me i was like oh god jama
people
stuff
[Music]
it's so cool though
for real yeah i don't think it was worth
waiting that long it was worth it i know
it was worth it
uh maybe anya uh do you have how many
like how many brown girls
can i have one
yes yes sweet
i can give you one here here i think i
have it now because i have one extra
okay uh
um
what if we picked like to keep the doll
because like that's probably a choice
based
something right i don't know i think um
i think you kind of have to because
maybe mikko senpai is waiting
yeah because i was thinking like like
hell no i don't want to waste i don't
want to like kill kill mary yeah but i
think the horrors won't happen if you
don't any marry you know
[Music]
yeah
slam dunk mary
slim dunk slam dunk
that that was too good i'm gonna include
that yeah me too bored
slam dunk mary hell yeah oh i haven't i
missed the
god quote
write my name
yeah i'll read my name no i have no more
space unfortunately can i can i even why
the board my but my board is not
highlighted you know the
oh yeah my board is also not highlighted
i think like three of us
all the boards are not
oh you can take it off
take it off okay okay how do i use the
glowing sack oh is that does it or do
you have my board perhaps oh yeah i have
your board yeah um how do i use a glow
insect right um i have no idea right
click the ink
click on it and put the glow ink sign
click on now
all right
oh yeah it's empty
um oh no um i didn't use the goddamn it
raining
let's let's let's do that again um
ah
oh um
zetta do you have my board um
[Applause]
oh thank you thank you thank you thank
you okay cool okay i have to um no yes
yes yes yes yes
so um do you put the board first or what
i'll put you write the board first and
then you apply the glow insect to the
written board oh shoot
oh you're right okay what the hell i'm
hungry
eat
okay
um
the curse of marrying
making me sorry
that is
okay thank you done
and then i do this right and then i do
this okay there you go
nice
cool
uh that was oh
oh god wait i i i messed up i messed up
and uh
um um i i messed up the how did he write
mary is it's not m-a-r-e no it's
m-e-r-r-y yeah yeah yeah yeah
um let let's do that again
let's do that again there's a shop here
what
what can we get
okay
we should be good
and then i do this nice yay
oh cool me taka this is merry slam dunk
yeah yes
slam dunk mary go to corey this time
this is my country mary
yes thank you for your wisdom today
mm-hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
game
you should try this rainy
oh i tried it
oh that was so much fun now it's so much
fun
oh if you kept the doll then mary will
say to be with you together and kill you
oh that's why i ripped osama oh oh
[Music]
yeah
yeah there's only us the horror people
and also us here
yes who are online right now should we
end the
stream here then shall we
yeah the fun here yeah
[Music]
thank you so
take much
ah that was really fun
i'm glad that i actually streamed the
horror
the horror house
i play i got to talk a little bit with
people i've never talked to before like
uh kazama
uh i've never actually talked to her
before
so it's nice
and
you know i feel like this festival is
like a really good um opportunity to
to socialize with people you oh my god
[Music]
you'll normally socialize with but the
haunted house is so
cool gonna put your book away yeah i
kind of don't want to submit it
i don't like i don't um
i don't think i have anything good to
say
yeah so i'm gonna um
i'm just gonna
erase and then return it yes
they kept going crazy yeah like um
going with kiara is really really really
fun i'm glad she asked me during the
thingy
i'm very v that made me very very happy
actually because um you know uh
i don't know sometimes i
i think like you know a lot of people
like hanging out with me but
would i be like somebody's first choice
you know to go places sometimes like
sometimes i uh feel like that you know
so when she actually picks me
she picked me like you know do you want
to go together to the festival it's so
it's actually nice you know
food
try kebab stand
[Music]
no i'm dying i'm dying i was dying as
well i think like mary made me like
super starving or here
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
or here here here or here
uh louis cafe
[Music]
you can
there's like food
okay i don't think they need food
anymore because they're like they're
like ignore me
yeah i feel like in the horror house you
know
of course like it's all like fun and
games but i really really really i was
really impressed with like how they
tried to like um
they try to like be in character and
like do it seriously
it's just
i i felt that it was this is really
amazing you know
so you know i also tried my best to like
get into like the the whole haunted
house
role play thing it's because it's also
cool
it's so like yeah i i really really
appreciate like the wow it's so good
yeah
how was your day with kiara um it was
fun uh we went to the horse racing place
uh we bet for stuff i didn't have any
diamonds so i got my diamond bedding
from choco sensei uh she was also
opening a stall in which uh you know we
have to give her a love message and
she'll give us like diamond and gold
so all of my stuff like my diamond that
i used to bet i
get it i got it from choko sensei and
then the gold ingot i used for slot
machine she also gave me some and then
yeah the slog machine gave me diamonds
which i could have oh my god what
oh what
oh sweet saying senpai
is there
oh my god mikko senpai is hush in my
head
that's so cool look at that she has like
the
mary skin that's so cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
scared me
that's kidding me
but are they still working
are they still working
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
yeah let's go
wait wait um one two three one two three
one three one three yes thank you
okay
thank you
[Music]
oh no
cute really it feels like uh
you know
really feels like you know uh the
bad
thing
in like this disneyland like where
there's like a mascot
merito assassin
[Laughter]
soon
like theme park ah i'm so happy i got
shushing with mary
so happy
it's so cool
[Music]
would be so cool
merry fence
merito
rainey
uh maybe like make this last um
kiara
toys
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
i
me
hey
okay
nice ah what a good memory i think it's
also a good time to stop playing guys
because i think
there's only uh anya and then shiraken
and then
watami senpai and then hatsama i think
yeah
maybe the people who hasn't really
gotten the chance to go
um thanks for the extra content thank
you i'm glad i streamed it
man but like the whorehouse i'm so glad
i went
like for
real
for real so cool
why is there eofy head out here
why is there eof head
what i'm gonna use iris head
um maybe tomorrow we will be gone
okay
yes
okay okay okay okay okay
you know guys thank you yeah i wonder
what's there in like a kyla place
but yeah that's it guys for today um no
free talk
[Music]
foreign
my goodness super chat will be read
another time and
tomorrow i don't know what stream i
still haven't made a schedule
but yeah
i'm feeling pretty much better so i will
um
i will be streaming normally
yes uh this week and remember my
birthday is coming soon so i have um a
lot of stuff prepared for you guys so i
hope you guys will like it pretty
nervous but i hope you know
yes yes yes yes okay guys um bye-bye
[Laughter]
well what does iris say when it's like
closing time
wait
what did i get hit with
i'm hungry
oh my god
oh my god i'm gonna die
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die oh my god
i'm gonna die disconnect
bye guys bye i'm gonna die
[Music]
do
you