[Music]
so
hey
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
bye
[Music]
it's kind of loud for me
too
oh you're sure
maybe this is so cute
this mouse is something supposed to be a
a crocodile or alligators paw
do you call it a paw
kitty camp
alligators and crocodiles are not the
same thing right
but i i always want to say crocodile
looks like a crocodile to me
[Music]
a clown
i think it looks more like a paw than
like a claw
[Music]
wouldn't them
wouldn't the nails that stand out of it
when the nails that poke out of it be
the claw but the hand itself would be
the paw
[Music]
alligators are north american elegance
have alligators have a different nose a
mouth
crocodiles are bigger have a different
facial structure yeah
i think i mean i think i've seen a
difference before
um
[Music]
which was the country where you might
just randomly
ran across an alligator or crocodile
which was that australia
[Music]
i think in canada you run across a bear
and in australia you run across wait a
florida
does it not happen in australia they run
across other things i suppose
florida oh my god wait that's so scary
do they
hit but like not in the city right
more on like does florida have a
countryside i suppose yes
[Music]
alligators are near where i am they're
known for american south they're in
australia too
[Music]
florida has both
ah you mean originally it was alligators
but now it's crocodiles and alligators
running around they show up in backyards
i feel like i've seen that before
that's quite a problem an issue
oh no
yeah florida seems like a funny place to
be in i've heard
some things about florida
damn
[Music]
including pools oh my god
they're crazy do they just attack humans
i mean i'm sure they eat human flesh but
if they're like roaming over florida
maybe they're kind of polite and nice
huh
need to hunt it down eh
wait shall we chickens do the job
do you think we have a chance
[Music]
florida man
do i know did i know the florida man
they're chill if you leave them alone
they'll attack your dog oh no
maybe there's like a
maybe in florida there's like a
percentage compared to other places in
america that in florida less people have
a dog either because their dog might
have been eaten by a alligator or
because they thought it would happen so
they stayed away from uh getting a pet
to begin with
is there such a thing
that's just my imagination
[Music]
you aren't wrong really
oh my god
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
not unheard
of oh
damn
that's so scary
i don't think i could live in the
country like or in a city or in a place
like that where suddenly
suddenly
suddenly really dangerous animals show
up
man
like bears and crocodiles and anacondas
or whatever i'm eating chips because i
feel kind of hungry um
even though
i had breakfast
but that's a couple hours ago i guess
[Music]
yeah australia um
but i suppose in like sydney or whatever
that doesn't happen
except for spiders that are as huge as
huge as your face
uh with legs as long as my body
that probably even happens in cities
like sydney
huge [\h__\h] spiders i heard about the
what was their hunter spiders or so oh
god please not
[Music]
in in austria
we don't even have like
any like poisonous spiders that just
roam around randomly in a zoo or
something like that maybe
but like
just like that no
there's literally like nothing
that you can meet randomly
that will kill you or
poison you or whatever
[Music]
so pretty safe in that regards
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay we're gonna play this game today i
i got the idea
from abe
she played this game like
a year ago or something like that
but it looks pretty cute
it's like two to six hours depending on
how much you do
um wait how do i get out of this
okay it's so cute
it's about
it's very story-driven
um it should be done with one stream but
yeah it's about this i think i guess
this is pat
this is pat he lives in new york city
and uh it is
he has a um
a problem because uh something about a
conspiracy
that is trying to take a family down the
biggest family
in new york city but turns out it is his
own family
so i guess pat probably tries to help to
make that not happen
[Music]
why he's so sad because yeah he's
worried man
they're going after his family oh no
oh
yeah it always looked very cute to me
the first time i saw him i play it i
didn't really watch any of it i just
glanced at it but um but i saw what it
looks like and i was like oh that's so
cute i want to play that at some point
so uh i think there will be a lot of
reading um
but we will see
let's start it's so cute
oh
he's so cute i can't
it's so oh
the style of the game is already killing
me is so adorable oh
animations are so cute
[Laughter]
oh pat what's up
no company please thank you
really what if i annoy you
oh no i'm blowing glass no i'm going to
espanol no uploads at all not even one
humbler
[Music]
really
hey i'm trying to lay low here so can
you remove them please
i'm so cute
okay okay
you got me
i'll come clean
i'm sorry for being so rude before i'm
just a little on edge
normally i wouldn't tell anyone this but
you've got your soulful eyes i can
totally see the entirety off
so i feel safe of you stranger
you see usually i love coming to john
johny's on my birthday like this
staying in the hotel floating in the
pool i'm guessing he's an italian living
in new york city eating two bagels at
the continental breakfast eating two
soaps in the complimentary complimentary
bath basket
but this year i've got a problem
real big problem oh
look at him
[Music]
how was i able to play this and not
freak out about his cuteness
oh my god
real
big a problem the venues i'm pretty sure
the family is finally trying to rub me
out for squealing squealing
or stealing
i didn't mean to squeal
honest i just see a pair of earnest eyes
and the secret she start flowing out of
my snoot
i'm doing it right now oh he means like
talking
oh what
snitching and mafia speak rounding up oh
ah
it's okay baby you can join kfp
oh cheese and crackers
what am i going to do i don't want to be
rubbed out
on tony even taught me i have to meet
him upstairs here at the at age shop for
the event
i didn't think i don't know but i heard
him talking to big mama on the phone the
whole family is gonna come to really
show me how it's done
what am i going to do mamma mia i don't
want to sleep with the fishes i have a
shellfish allergy
and my ass backs up when i get too
waterlogged oh no
wait a sec
you're interested in me right yes you
wanted to sit with me for breakfast and
everything do you think you could help
me
since we're such great balls you could
go out and talk to my family around
alligator new york city
find out information about the event
look at his hands
[Music]
and the way he looks up
oh my god
i'm in love i'm in love i am so in love
and this is so cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah this is a great idea together
maybe we can collect enough info to
save me you want to save me right right
great i'll text you if i need any help
how about you go out there and start do
you have a watch
oh you do great
i'll text a little before 10 am since it
can take 50 minutes or so to get back
here on the trolley
trolley
so make sure you check your watch a
bunch
sure
if you happen to get stuck doing some
weird game like activities while
investigating it could take time there's
a time limit
will the time run out
oh
does he have your number well i guess
now he does
he's so cute
i wonder
i might wonder if he's like like yeah he
seems really young
i want to protect him
a soft time limit
don't worry too much about it okay
nada hodol
oh
right before time runs out yeah that was
uh i put it in the title because it was
in the description of the game
that you gotta save his family before
time runs out
oh
[Laughter]
oh no i don't know if i'm good with time
limited games oh the oh oh i don't want
is there a bad ending
i hope not i don't want this sad i don't
want this boy to have a sad ending
i want him in tears
oh god i want to save his family
no
before crony runs out yeah
you got this oh
i hope there's only happy endings
wait oh sorry did i read that time i
don't have because i'm going to have a
murder done on me
how do you know don't panic like that
it's okay
i'm okay
you don't look okay
yeah yeah
because mafia i thought italian is
fitting
thank you for the super chat i'm gonna
have to play all endings now we're not
gonna do all of them i think but um
we'll see maybe this is the situation
where
like in hirotamata i i was i said i'm
only gonna do one but i then i ended up
doing more and more because it was so
interesting to me
hmm
i think of the beach pad remember what
dr duplessnew told you
anyways thank you so much for helping
out an alligator like me i really feel
better just looking at your super kind
invisible face
and be careful out there the last thing
we need is two people sleeping with the
fishes
we need to find a double bed in this
economy
what
see you later friends stay safe
yeah hide under the table if you're that
scared about being murdered whether you
hide under the table
what's visible what did i say
all right oh should we talk to him too
does the time stand still when i talk to
someone does someone know that have you
guys played this game anyone here
[Music]
i hope it stays still
takes time to read everything hell hello
stamp guest if you're looking to leave
the restroom you'll have to use the exit
error up there in the corner of the
screen
oh
we provide all of our patrons with an
extra-narrow and complementary pillow
mints
feel free to use both outside the vowel
mhm feel free
wait did you guys give me an answer
time doesn't stand still
if you travel during activity ah
that's when time passes
what time
time only moves forward and you do mini
games or change places aha
major action pass the time it's more of
turns okay
once as much as you wish just don't mix
the two up since that arrow is vintage
and known to contain harmful materials
such as leaf paint asbestos and a
combination of red poisons and cilantro
silk cilantro what
please feel free to visit us again at
john johny's and have a journey of a day
he looks funny
okay i can't go sideways on the outside
okay
let's see
[Music]
land around the gator
oh i used to say that a lot when i was
younger see you later alligator this
week click and drag up and down
is that a loading symbol the loading
symbol is so cute okay let's talk to you
it's like mickey oh mikey i bob you got
the minute for perhaps three minutes i
ain't above asking for five
oh card game oh no i saw you walking out
of john johnny's over there and i said
to myself mickey you gotta talk to that
mysterious stranger
a vision in pinstripe stays i ain't
trying to fluff you up for nothing but
you look like an alligator of
exceptional taste as well as one who
might like to dabble in high stakes of
games of chance and intrigue if you feel
me no no no no unless it's what was that
one that i can't play the blackjack was
blackjack
that's one i can play
no don't actually feel me i got a skin
condition
your skin's probably pretty rough anyway
as an alligator i don't know if i want
to touch that
they call me slick for a reason and
according to my dog it ain't going away
unless i start using that topical cream
at night
i love this
but i ain't gonna list gotta listen to
some jabroni with a smarty certificate
you know what i'm saying
all my smarts come from the street which
is also where i got this skin condition
and i'm
and my impolite lower back to
tattoo
oh
i don't know should we so directly be
asking about that
do i have to like
because i have a pen do i have to circle
it
oh
there's mickey but everyone calls me the
old king of guards well that one guy did
before he yelled at the fence to stop
stealing his emo passwords then his
pants fell down
and then he fell down then he fell down
it's an open mantle
but i have it on good authority from the
paramedics that he only called three or
five other people that saw bada bing
bada boom bada bing bing boom the old
card king at your service oh
the event
can i make mistakes in this game
oh
you know about the event well looky here
bub
bump it's a real secret of area dig
ain't nobody's supposed to be going and
telling pat about it my lips are sealed
just like they're sealed when i wake up
after night of nose only raving
i thought you would say like just just
like when you ate a [\h__\h] sail for
dinner
[Laughter]
a little bit too direct i suppose
that person's name but is it also just
like
something you say like dude ah okay
pat
so aren't we gonna play cards
you're talking about pat alligator yeah
i know that dude pretty well he's my
second cousin
one time when he was when we was kids
when we was kids those guys kind of
locked out the ccd after recess and
missed juice and cookie time what now
we only had one granola bar between us
and good old pat gave me the bigger
house oh
i'll always
remember that no i ain't crying and just
spit my own eyes on the display of my
straight toughness
oh
maybe don't just maybe if you play a
little game with mickey here my lips
might loosen up you think you can keep
an eye on this flurry of fingers and
find the queen oh god if it's only three
cards and you're gonna move them around
okay
free card mickey i'll play
mickey's running a street scam oh thank
you for telling me so directly
keep an eye on the queen queen and pick
the correct card to foil his plans
[Music]
just gotta keep my eye on the clean all
right get your peepers peeled because
these hands are about to become a
hurricane you guys look at it too okay
which one i don't even know what the
queen looks like see here huh
keep your eye okay on this one this one
the middle oh god
where's he gonna go where's he gonna go
i don't know oh my god
stop blinking
it's always in the middle dude he's so
funny
he's so funny
he's
you little [\h__\h]
well i guess we'll never know who won
who knows when trying to win blows or
some junk
did i pay for this i hope not i won
what do you mean i won
yeah you got a family member oh jeez
this is a wonderful game oh my god
anyways about the event well you ain't
heard it from me but i hear it's gonna
be a real fair to remember the whole
family has been talking about it for
months wait are you part of the family
that's really gonna get his if you know
what i'm saying
[Music]
i'm a bit confused i thought we were
saving his family but is his own family
going against him
but when we're saving his family
for sure
let me bring my
huge teacup over here so i can drink
easier okay the key to fam or are there
like two families
or is the family not even a real family
just a mafia club
[Music]
interesting anyways thanks for playing
let me know if you need any of my city
smarts while you're without your rookie
try not lick any trolley handrails
there was this an aromatology copay he's
not a real cake and alligator pants you
feel me
oh
pat's worried about his family wanting
to get rid of him yeah i got that i got
death
it's really ain't here yet so why don't
you
go check out the hurricane mikey got
banned for his slick fingers coming up
the machines and causing
a epidermis epidemic oh no but that
ain't mean you gotta suffer the same
fate all
wait where don't go
can i move whoa what
hotel
brodega alligator store can go to the
side no wait what
ah arcade he said okay it was right here
i thought it was not so close
unknown
um hello
hello
is this by any chance your first time in
the alleged new york city
i mean in the city city not on alligator
long island or something
[Music]
i'm sorry if that's weird i'm just fine
yeah i feel like i could text you some
tips
the scene is really big and has a lot of
colorful secrets that i wouldn't want
you to miss on your first visit
it is okay if i help you out from time
to time
yes
i'm great
i'll be sure to text you again soon
don't forget to enjoy yourself
alrighty
even though it was a text message i
still wanted to talk
um
this person looks fancy
it's a girl
i think joanie hey there we are for a
real challenge
i haven't seen you here before stranger
alligator new york city is a big place
but we tend to have regulars you know
like rocco and bonnie over there those
still are here every day but you i'd
remember such a visible face like yours
well i know i'm very pretty and stunning
i look at me being a real jerk i don't
mean to be giving you a hard time or
nothing i've just been a little frazzled
since last night i had a dream that i
was a ski ball
ski ball what's the ski ball
and some sticky finger kid kept throwing
me into the 10 point hole
go for the 50 things i tried to yell but
being a ball and all the ding-dong
couldn't hear me
i woke up in a cold sweat in my kitchen
systematically throwing individual
oranges from the window into my
neighbor's terrarium the vitamin c would
have helped me shake it off but all i
had for breakfast was black coffee and
the half camel of leftover candy
stickers
i would get the same questions okay i
wonder if we ever get other questions
or if it's always those
the name's joanie do i have to remember
all these people or bologna if you're my
fourth grade bully come back to fight me
you're not right
sam
anyway i work here at adelaide's arcade
sweeping floors and keeping all the
games running smooth as babies blow me
behind
oh
wait i just i think my my game just
froze for a second
this game is full of american things cat
i won't get oh no
oh
i used to work as a greaser in the shop
downtown but i love to be closer to my
gaming hobby they let me keep the
leather jacket though you gamer
and the company hairstyle oh that was a
hairstyle from the company not a hold on
the event
maybe we'll meet some
look i know you're here spying for pat
for whatever reason and that's fine but
i can't tell you family secrets you feel
me to give up in for that heart you'd
have to really impress me
hmm
cat
that's my cousin and also the most
genuine doof i know so you better be
nice then you're here i wouldn't want to
have to pop you one um
stop me in my field language
this yeah that has a rock and roll
hairstyle
kiana doesn't get most english language
terms anyway so it shouldn't matter
excuse me that you phrase that as if i
don't speak english at all
punch you is popular oh my god it's very
violent this game
uh i'm told i got a mean left hook and a
moderately insulting right hook
and a cake that could benefit from some
anger management courses
i tried to sign it up for some uh
calming huh i tried to sign up for it
for some calming hot yoga at the yanka
but it didn't go over well you ever get
kicked by your own leg
no
i
don't think i ever got kicked by my own
leg my my leg doesn't have its own life
thankfully
i'm learning new yorkie and let's go
oh yeah
remind me of drinking my tea before it
gets cold
it ain't great bud is that a new york
thing too picking your own leg yucca
[Laughter]
it ain't great
all right let's talk to the other people
so what do you think you can roll the
ball oh we're gonna play like oh game
time i'm talking pickle pinball i know
pinball i know
played on on windows xp back in the day
the old penny b as i like to call it
against the advice of both my friends
family and the supportive therapist i
see on first day
got the highest score on liz and wins
and tear eight months running but i'm
always looking for a real pinhead to pit
my skills against
someone you think i have to take on a
pinball lizard like me of course pinball
i can handle
um
special
one second i want to change
my chat to light mode i know i know i
know
i know
shocking
i didn't mean to make a joke i take this
very seriously
wow there's like a lot of
mini games in this game cool
i'll i'll play but
[Music]
first time after many years when the
ball is in play
i take the blunt punch and
control the flippers by clicking
r and l or use left and right okay
uh
okay
oh five thousand points to get her
respect can i do it only once
wait what uh where's the plunge thingy
oh my god what
where's the point at this one
oh my god oh god oh god
are you is this rigged
is this red
maybe it's not
oh my god i'll never get five thousand
okay wait maybe we can
[Music]
we're so close
wait no let me do it again i didn't get
5 000.
well i got a family member bench
i was really unlucky now
yeah
hey it's been a long time since i've
seen moves like that in front of liz and
wizards here he had that ball hitting
all the do what's and who's it so fast i
could barely keep up it's been a real
honor to hang with another student of
pinballs do i get another chance
i found a puzzle piece i thought i
needed five thousand i only got four
thousand seven hundred huh
huh
about the event she's actually telling
me anyway
now this might just be a rumor but word
on the street there's going to be some
sick games here not pinball per se but
you know you take what you can
get sorry
anyway that's all i can really say i'd
better get back on the grind trying to
beat my last high score
thanks for showing me your supple wrist
pinheads
catch you later okay
so for this the time will pass i suppose
uh let's talk to this person here behind
a train player you had a train move
um
yeah the train over remake was possible
but if you ask me nothing beats the part
and the original red train leaps into
the air and the harness holding the
action rings if you stay after the
credits you see the footage when he
falls into the camera guy and a makeup
artist holding two coffees okay he
doesn't really want to talk to me what
about this guy oh god
what a armstrong laptop are you doing at
the back of the arcade i'm not a raptor
little girl
i know what you have to that's right i
thought you picked us by looking at you
you want cold heart plus
where you found the right alligator and
i've got a job that will pay for both of
our retirements and employee-made
stuffies
you might see a humble claw machine but
this is a vault and we're gonna break in
she's so excited
but we can't just walk in look there's
countermeasures
sometimes no more the security guard
comes by and says i'm not allowed to put
my clawing chair into the aisle
without the boost i'm not tall enough to
wipe the claws
[Music]
she said it's a fire hazard but most of
the machines are here
you see behind here that's one ailing
power strip juicing up every one of
those babies
where
one wrong movement pinball and bump
huh
[Music]
oh yeah her shirt says anime
you haven't heard of me honestly i'm not
surprised
hey youtube we're back okay
her shirt says anime yeah
i'll leave no fingerprints and johnny
law doesn't have a clue or johnny booyah
from my geography class at least that's
what he said when i asked him to the
spring fling
pat
that is a patsy but not my party that's
for sure he's related to some of my
dad's friends
one time at that show pat pulled the
fire alarm because he thought someone
was trying to set him on fire
it turns out he just had a one piece of
pizza in his pocket
no one could find him for almost an hour
until the firefighters pulled him out of
the concert hall's crawl space he was
covered in spiders and had eaten the
pizza but was otherwise unharmed
physically anyway that guy's pretty
weird
i'd love to tell you about the event i
really would but it's our first time on
the job together mac you haven't yet
earned my umbrella trust
[Music]
wait i wonder the card game dude
did we win his trust
if i would have not clicked on the queen
but on the other cards and only left the
queen on the table or something like
that i wonder if we would have won like
properly
okay let me play this
maybe we could come to a mutually
beneficial agreement
the climb machine is a two-man operation
really
i mean i guess we can play it together i
won that game it said so but it also
said i won that under the pinwheel game
even though i didn't get to 5000.
it's a they're they're defining winning
pretty weirdly like the card burned up
and and the pinball machine i didn't get
5 000.
[Music]
you guys trying to kill you
[Laughter]
nice nice
[Music]
i need someone who's not gonna rock me
out for additional process when plush
comes to shove you feel me
what do you say old timer one last claw
machine score the big one hmm
claw machine
but that's cute what
grab the prizes as she advises of course
i'll play
follow sweet gelding's instructions to
get the perfect claw machine prize click
left and right to control it okay
for money
inside the vault is a treasure trove of
prices
i've had my eye on a couple of choice
goods but i need an accomplice with
nerves of steel and hands of steel
a top battery where you can push the
buttons and see and see the prices uh
so what do you say
so cute
okay quesadilla okay i tried
let's get some cute loots for our cutest
dudes first you should warm up your
tricky ditches
grab me any browser catches your eye go
on old timer show me what you got
is this difficult
is this a difficult one that looks like
doraemon
there's a can and sweets and what is
that
and the taco dart scene
and what is that it's a
something like a game one i don't know
and some cute dolls and a diamond
and a snack
okay um
how many times can i push one side and
listen
oh damn it
oh it seems so okay go
what two
oh
okay i didn't want that one but okay i
have the price let's check this out
maybe it's worth some money
i had a crystal face it was before my
astronaut face and after my pony face
you've got some chaps i respect that but
now the real job begins how will you
interact when the pressure's on this
time you follow my weight get me an
apple apple
where's the apple
that apple okay
uh so interestingly um it goes pretty
deep like even if i want to like get
this one it would get the bottom one so
it shouldn't this one shouldn't be so
hard
okay although it's very much on the
bottom left and i can't i'm not sure if
i can reach that
because the the arm doesn't go any
further left
well let's try
oh
okay wow
you got one what is it the apple of
course
an apple day keeps my spelling detail
away
he had to stay home four days in a row
after me and stacy did pop the polo you
did some red delicious fruits caught
those bang windows huh
you're really good at this
are we doing more
first try yeah but it's finally time for
the big score
i can see it in your eyes you're ready
to get the ultimate prize kept me the
doll from the best most awesome video
game franchise of all time final friend
city a doll there's a couple of those
here's the dreamy one all the spiky hair
this one
this is it the big one
sparky does does she mean this dude
i
i suppose this dude he's in here twice
i don't think i want to go for this one
i think i'd go for the bottom one i
don't feel like we can oh it's a cloud
reference ah final fantasy i don't think
if we press the button above this it
will go all the way to the bottom i
think
so
i guess for this now i have five tracks
because i did the other one first try
ah
that's kind of on the way
wait i wasn't even going for that when i
was going for the head one holy [\h__\h]
it just went sideways what the hell i'm
amazing
i'm amazed
i hacked i hacked the game
oh pro gamer mover what the [\h__\h] that
nobody saw that one coming
you're welcome to uh steal that
technique from me
try to copy it but you're not such a
gamer as i am so i don't know if you can
really
rock my technique
did you get it the ultimate price
his hair is almost as prickly as his
social intelligence woman
i don't get it because i don't play it
this is exactly what i wanted
oh holy [\h__\h] we [\h__\h] first tried it
twice
[Laughter]
natural talent man
claude
i'll tell you what you need to know
juventus a secret eh i'm okay they're
not a rat a little [\h__\h]
let's try the classic double cross what
did i get you those things for
[Music]
that's the calling card of a sweetheart
master criminal your little [\h__\h]
well [\h__\h]
okay
[\h__\h]
little [\h__\h]
there's someone behind here too
i'm i'm talking with the most obvious
one
at the end
alrighty
my mom is always on my case like already
go outside and talk to other alligators
or already stop hiding behind various
types of curtains in and outside our
home
okay let's talk to you
[Music]
rocco my little william was gonna come
here this place is a dump
bunny
it didn't have to come rocco
no way the only thing worse than being
in a dump is not being invited to the
dump to begin with
like you're too dressy for the other
trash which is unnervingly close to an
entry from my dream journal last week
oh i wonder if we if we take more like
several times with someone if dad does
something
else
take a shot bronco
hold your horses bonnie i'm lining up my
steak you gotta be delicate with these
things
oh is this a game two
oh i've been holding my horses i've been
cradling my horses i've enveloped my
horses in the safety of a tender
meaningful embrace all night waiting for
you to take this shot rocco
how come you never hold me like that
oh yeah yeah oh yeah some private info
that we're getting here
so i want to play with you guys
if a grown man can't come to our
children's arcades and wind by hitting
things unwind with a stick and yelling
squares what kind of alligator country
are we living in
let me play with you
there's just two rules if you want to
rack up the game with me be cool shoot
pool and stay in school that's free
rules
[Music]
if you're not even allowed to say heck
in here then i i'm i'm the one who [\h__\h]
who should leave because uh
as we've seen i swear a little bit too
much
damn you're
right hey what did i just stay
let me [\h__\h] play
ah that's the third game i lost in a row
you're too good at this bomb
i know
come on what's your secret
muscle hustle and wrestle
russell
my holistic dentist after he screams in
my mouth to soft jazz
we hand up the pool hall downtown
um
interesting
[Laughter]
she almost admitted she has an affair
with her dentist i suppose
just lining up my shot are we not gonna
like play with them i'm comfortable with
myself okay i think no i think that's
not happening all right what if i talk
to you again
oh can you be okay i guess we're leaving
now what is this by the way
ah just the settings okay hmm
well i guess we did everything we could
do here
[Music]
not everyone has a minigame okay but
that one was so obvious
what
uh what what did i do for him hey pop
you're just in time the trolley got here
a minute ago
it's rollie what the [\h__\h] is a trolley
why don't you go check out the city
bring mikey a hot dog maybe or some
protective handware i'm gross oh oh oh
mama mia out is this the trolley
but let me talk to her
oh there
i think i may have left my scrapbooking
scissors at home on accident
cute oh straw
it's a tram okay oh i found my scissors
it must have been your approach that
gave me good luck stranger where are
they
i've been trying to get outside the home
more since i had the new baby oh
nana is watching you today so here i am
out in the world
it's a little nerve-wracking to be away
from the nursery after those moms to be
honest
i already miss all the new baby smells
like poop
and throw up well
not all the smells real no more things
come out of babies and use the street
fragrance of the cute little heads
well
even that stuff is a little cute
maria it's wonderful to meet you i feel
like we're reading a book here
i love this who's so cute
i was heading to the local yaka i'm
gonna say it anyway before i run into
you i'm taking a class here today i'm
scrapbooking but i'm a little early
scrapbooking huh
interesting hobby
i meant to wait here in the lovely
weather until their class and mom yoga
and self-defense ends
we pray shop
oh my god do you know pat
do you mean myself
[Music]
she means your baby who's also called
plant oh i'm so proud of him it's his
birthday today did you know he's so
funny with how he trips himself to hotel
stay every year today he's just oh wait
no
it is
maybe this is mom
oh yes here fans of the third leg hole
yeah that's funny
he just loves the continental breakfast
and those three tiny soaps
you're the mom
i still get concerned he eats too many
of those i love the way she dances all
the time oh my god
seth shouldn't be coming out the snoot
of a boy that ain't i i see where he got
his cuteness from
event
if antisexual i'm taking this class
today
sense
she doesn't look like she has any any
intentions of getting rid of his son of
her son
hmm and so since you're one of those
friends maybe you could have a mom out
you see i'm trying to put together a
family tree to bring tonight as a
surprise but i don't have everyone's
pictures it's so hard for all of us to
get together in one place these days i
don't think anyone would like me to use
their photos from the early 2000s
we all made some questionable wardrobe
decisions back then
since you're already going around town
would you mind snapping some pictures of
the family once you get
once you get and bring back i'll put it
in the family tree maybe if you get the
moment something good will happen okay
oh i see you already have one there uh
would you like to put it in here you can
have mine as well don't want anyone
feeling lonely
okay
is that like um
some kind of like collection that i that
i get like extra
extra ending or extra points or extra
rewards for it
i don't think it's
necessary for the main
game or so i wonder it's like a
collector thing like if i meet every npc
in the game
she doesn't seem evil at all what the
hell
let's see how much you
obs
oh but yes the
oh that was not youtube that was obs
apparently today is just not too
very smooth
i don't know i don't know what's going
on
what is happening
uh we're playing family history mystery
how can i play this already i don't even
have the pictures click and drag the
alligator portraits into position on
family streak come back anytime ah okay
okay so this is like a
different kind of game
uh
oh
well how do i know where exactly it goes
you're the mom but
who says there isn't grandparents and
grand grandparents and so on
put you here oh no incorrect
where's pat by the way do i not have a
picture of pat
she must be one of the youngest
oh it doesn't stick anywhere
i'm guessing she should be one of the
lowest cause she's so young
she can't have a child
or maybe here
no
it doesn't stick anywhere thank you
thank you for the blessings
okay i don't think i can know anything
here right now
it's upside down
oh
oh that is interesting then she would be
one it really isn't really upside down
oh
so the youngest go to the top
well let me try all the top ones
shouldn't she in one of the top spots
ah i got one tween
mod on age appropriate anime
she's modding an animal forum no
and you're the moms and maybe you're
here or maybe you're here or maybe
you're here
or maybe you're
here
maybe you're here
or maybe you could also be
here
you could possibly also be oh here that
didn't take me that many tries 48 church
rummage sale cashier okay but that
really helps having the mom's position
this person said
of them said they're the cousin
but i don't think i can unless i place
it randomly on every single one here
not sure if i can figure it out
a cousin
sister cousin
my cousin would be uh
the
daughter
or bro or son of the
brother or sister of pat's parent right
mickey said he was the second cousin
second
god damn it i don't know
i don't know
no
here no
here here
wait
wait i want this is so unsatisfying i
wanted to find its place now
damn it
what about here no
one here no
here no here no here no
here no here oh i found it johnny
pinball wizard and now you uh are you
even related to everyone what do they
say about this dude
i'll find it i'll find your spot
oh i found it it's like mikey annoying
people okay nice brute force singing
yeah
nice
thanks again dear come back can you come
you're welcome
[Music]
uh oh yeah
hey it's me pat oh that was pat
that's me it's me pat
the alligator the one with the hat
hello pat
understand can you come back
someone came over to my table and
threatened me
well
they gave me a clue and told me to have
a nice turn
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway we didn't go on the tram oh no
yeah so you really can't do everything
in that short term so maybe it is really
impossible to meet everyone
i met your mom i'm not surprised you're
so cute
don't bop me
oh i need to get to you my new friend
sorry i saw your shadow over me i fought
some kind of restaurant assassin was
descending from the rafters to take me
out i know there's no raptors here but
assassins are tricky they can improvise
didn't you have
didn't you have the air when you were in
elementary school you know there dude
assassins really exist
what kind of world are you living in pat
come to me come with me to my world it's
better join the whole life crocodile
youtuber no alligator v2 ball
at least i think that's the acronym i
was absent a lot due to my nut but you
have a shellfish and a knot allergy what
are you not allergic to
you don't know
[Music]
it was tough times were bad at willy's
peanut butter factory elementary school
[Music]
anyway did you find out anything from
the family
well yeah i know they sound nice but
they might just be fluffing you up
i think you're just way too worried
about
what
[Music]
what oh
you guys are joking right
yeah i was like for real like worried
that
chad you got me worried for a moment
i thought you meant indonesia
whole live indonesia
well yeah i know they sound nice they
might just be fluffing you up
[Music]
god damn it
and you're not bothering you breadwell
to throw you off the trail sorry i've
actually just been sitting here
mainlining complimentary bread rolls the
whole time you were gone
[Music]
now they were having auditions you know
that
you know they were having auditions like
a while ago
[Music]
i need to
i need to eat more snackles
he's not the only one wearing clothes
[Laughter]
don't do this to me i already have i
already have a reputation of leaking
things even though i don't
that's not weird right i don't i didn't
leak what did i leak
at one time with ina
that one time with ina
where
i said she's drawing something but she's
always drawing something
[Laughter]
that didn't that didn't leak anything
what other time was there i mean i might
have teased something so you that you
only understand once it has happened
and i do that i do that knowingly
that
whatever i say only seems like it was
something after i've said after it's
been revealed
[Music]
oh my god inaudible
so i think that reputation is kind of
[\h__\h]
yeah it's mostly my own my own um
projects
oh yeah right right right the vr thing
people say i like that even though it
was already in the description
of the stream
and and i had permission to
to ask about it
so
but okay nobody cares for that and we
just gotta spread the reputation that uh
even though there are no actual facts
that prove it that i am someone who
leaks [\h__\h] and can't be trusted
[Music]
i was bitten by a vampire well that was
on purpose obvious
[Music]
and that was my own project
and that was my way of teasing something
that would come soon
[Music]
so anyway
maybe we should go to my hotel room i
think it'd be a little safe right there
unless low low low emoji with bread
let's go
okay
he's so cute the way he walks is so cute
someone stop him he's too cute harass
him officer oh cute
my safe place oh
it's a it's a is a it's a it's a it's a
thing in in the shape of a house
find a coat to pass a boat
help pat back into his hotel room help
pad with his outdated website help pat
remember his room code
okay
thanks for protecting me it really helps
to have someone walk me to my room the
wallpaper here is a little intense no
it's fine
kind of makes me feel like something is
staring at me
is that a hint there's a clique out
there
what am i gonna do my heart can't take
10 more hours of waiting
what's the event what did i scroll the
beans on oh no
cheese and crackers
oh man he's so
how do i help you remember
he's a nervous wreck yeah
since i was so worried about getting
super murdered today
the way he walks is so cute
i did the smart thing and got a special
lock for my hotel room door just a
little something i picked up at the
hardware store i was worried i'd get so
nervous that i'd forget the log's
passcode so i saved it on my website
alligator.fun
i even made a button you can click for
it
gee i'm really glad now i took those
only specific button making classes at
my local community center
okay here's a website guys does the
website exist really
of course it exists
oh my god it looks like a website i
would create when i was a child
oh yeah
oh my god
yeah really [\h__\h] shitty website
we of course with a counter with a
counter of how many
uh people have visited the website to
look extra cool
and then get the counter up yourself
an inspirational bling blingy yes yes i
was about to say bling bling messages
but this one is not sparkling
and don't click pad only lemon bar
poppers yeah nine one six one nine
if you're not that you're breaking the
law
he asked me to check it out
nine one six one nine that should be the
code how about being bad i look at him
so good we will we were under constant
i love this website this is so nostalgic
i love this
91619 okay i got it i got it
i got it 91619
i got it boy
i got it talk to me ah there we are
okay
oh here we are
this is for sure in my room you can tell
by the unobtrusive lock guys and so
can you go to my website grab the code
so we can unlock it yeah i already went
there don't worry about it i really want
to go inside and see if there are any
more of those three mints left
okay
nine
one six
one nine i remember
you did it thank you so much
this game makes me happy
is that the first sign what's going on
how are you gonna help me i like things
i always say the same thing i don't like
pink either what do i push now one uh
[\h__\h] no nine one six one nine
close it close it close it
hey oh my gosh
oh
hello my word this is quite the mess who
are you too and why have you opened my
door oh wrong door
but same clothes excuse me
who am i i'm bad this is my hotel room
my insult is long because my family is
trying to rub me out
but this is my door well i haven't
started luck because my family is trying
to rub me out but how come you have the
same code
but if that's true when my password
still worked
then
it's your luck
they are
so adorable
[Music]
and the music
oh my god
mama mia
is your law code 916
and our families are both trying to kill
us
so long stranger perhaps in another life
we would have been the total best
friends
[Laughter]
have had a voice
like ships in the night mr pat anyway
don't tell anyone what you've seen her
well i come for you endlessly
he's so cute he's so cute
he's so cute
i sure was a string of unlikely
coincidences yeah kind of man i was
weird
oh i hope that guy's room is okay that
stuff kind of smelled like what
[Music]
let's go to your real room shall we
man hotel rooms be confusing like that
oh wait that looks completely different
pat how could you have made that mistake
this is my actual room they're so
similar
i love this guy
oh my god
i still remember nine one six one nine
[Music]
come on in
i do i do feel like i won by playing
this game
oh my god
how is this not like how did this game
not get an award or something it
deserves a [\h__\h]
award oh
oh my god imagine i couldn't get my
skate
oh i'm so glad we made it inside now i
can really try to relax a little
okay
what are those
wolves on this shirt
that long nose
he's diarrhea
[Music]
sorry to distract you from the invest
engage now text you again when it gets
closer to 4 pm so don't forget to check
your watch oh you if you text me anyway
you know in case you get distracted
doing a collection of menial tasks from
rata formatted in an enjoyable matter
what does that mean
literally stats
something like that
i got a family member badge oh
jesus now
he's cute he's so cute
oh i thought i could investigate your
room do we this person is sitting looks
so funny oh hello
welcome wait
okay we'll talk to you
there's something so nice about sitting
by yourself in a restaurant with a good
book
[Music]
more i don't like dining alone it's
serene sharing a meal of just me myself
and i the kind of serenity that involves
not having to hear anyone else
it's nice oh wait same person what the
[\h__\h] it's a time loop it's [\h__\h] time
look oh
how did i get that
was that just daryl did he have that i
got a puzzle piece
what
puzzle piece is 2 out of 48. what when
did i get the first one
i remember getting the first one okay i
guess we're going outside
that that looks like the mouth of a
alligator but i guess it's just the the
little thing of a building
okay are we taking i wanna talk to this
guy
yo you never eat john johnny's here the
fruits are right but that bottomless
chocolate bowl was a disaster i picked
that thing up and bam chowder pants the
rest of the day
child advance is my nickname at work but
from an unrelated childhood centered
incident listen can we stop talking
about it i'm still feeling pretty
sensitive about the whole thing
not a hurdle okay
yeah that's probably on purpose it's
funny cute how do i enter the
the tram can i not oh let me talk to you
about buff boy
[Music]
oh my you're back already
why hello again there did you manage to
take any family photos no not really
no no i'm good i'm good i'm good no i'm
good i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good
i'm good thank you but dungeon
she's so cute though the way she offers
it to me
oh that's all right right there maybe
enough of time
wait let me talk to you
oh hello i didn't see you there fifth
william before
boy that side flower looks as tasty as
ever i'll come here most days to stare
at her
but usually leave when someone calls the
alligator police or slip and fall down
in the rather overall fashion
wait what
can i not go like anywhere else i don't
believe it
oh ella let me talk to you let me talk
to ya
or am i supposed to go into the arcade
again
oh wait oh you told me to look at the
flower okay look i got a puzzle piece
bottom right ah sorry didn't get it
oh
where should we go
welcome to the beautiful city mayor
whibley finn i wonder if we can meet him
booming bug economy see the alligator
new york city alligator opera get a
pagaya three hot thousand fridays [\h__\h]
it's not a friday today let's go to
downtown
hello
oh we're in the trap looks he looks
funny
he's so excited about his music wait
could i have talked to him that was too
fast
what's what's the matter with you are
drunk
george
the breeze the practicing quartet what a
perfect day to be alive elegant
even though it gets noisy sometimes i
love living in the city it's so full of
life and good burger joints oh burger
i wanna eat the burger
i'm so content he looks content i sell
bug you saw a bug
bugs bugs for sale more than one even
unlike what the sign implies
fork knife soon
soon
or spoon
you're lacking one leather
yeah sell books here
no not for painting for eating we're
alligators and weed bugs which is
something you know because you exist
here canonically
yeah anyway get bug buying a good buying
kiddo i ain't got all day because i
gotta sell bugs to feed my family with
different bugs which i buy with an
alligator clearance scene
most people call me papooli but my real
name is morty maguiles jr and the fruit
and the health
on account of my grandfather being
perfectly bisected by a wheat fresher
during the great depression oh [\h__\h]
that's so brutal
miraculously he survived who survived
but his life wasn't without his problems
such as how it was hard to see him when
he turned directly to the side
[Music]
was the last time we ever saw him and
also when those basement sounds started
up
but look at me rambling here to youth
about sellers screams and the like
my man lost her dimension
that's a good way to put it
he's a panicking paper mario life
problems yeah
it's brilliant right oh my god i'm
thinking it's a masterpiece
and didn't you say bad that's my
grandson's name oh grand grand mama
it's also the name of the nurse that
comes to the massage that comes to
massage the kinks out of my tail on
tuesdays whoa
did you meet pat or pat you'll have to
speak up i'm hard of hearing due to a
condition where i stop listening my
sentence and think about the war
[Laughter]
understandable
event i'm not quite sure what you're
talking about i have selected memory
disorder you see
and then i forget about things i don't
really want to go to
[Music]
this game it's gonna kill me
perhaps you could jog this old man's
memory oh man memory if you could help
me out with a favor you see the only
photo i've left of my dear late wife
martha has also been the victim of also
been the victim
also
of a weed for insurance you guys need to
be more careful with the refreshers
don't get close to them do you not learn
do not learn from the incidents
i can't seem to put it back together
oh the picture was
went for the refresher or your wife
martha
oh yeah i didn't
i would give anything to see marvel's
sweet smiley and if marvel was still
alive wouldn't he take a picture another
one
care to help this old softy gaze upon
his lost loved ones of course
of course
click a block just like oh yeah i
understand i understand understand
okay that's what i thought
oh these kind of games make me uh
nostalgic they remind me of when we
played alice
yeah oh yeah
um pretty close but i think we gotta get
the hand down and ah the hair
ah
[Music]
yeah now we have
the hand where i wanted it but i messed
up some other things that were already
in place
[Music]
oh
no
wait
[Music]
so close wait a second
make that one oh oh wait that one too oh
[\h__\h] i forgot about that one on the
bottom right
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
shut it looks like you're it not very
good shut up
i am
what kind of message is that
no no no no no no keep sliding
sounds kind of passive aggressive to me
man
uh wait no oh
i can i can handle this i just kind of
forgot about one piece
just too much
wait i can do this i'll need your help
um
[\h__\h]
i'm in a pickle
i'm in a pickle can i restart
i don't want to move those two anymore
[Music]
maybe maybe
i guess the bottom right will be the
empty one at the end
oh god oh what did i do
ah [\h__\h] i know this is the
is this the bottom right piece
[Music]
it was better before
wait i feel like i'm getting closer
ah
[Music]
can we switch them
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's just mess it all up maybe if we're
lucky we'll eventually get to the get
everything into the right place
[Music]
damn it man
um
ah
[Music]
yeah no
no yeah
no
are you serious
ah
i felt i feel like i feel like it's
getting cool
wait a second i feel like i'm kind of
close again
[Laughter]
this has to go here and then
[Music]
shut up
ah the first time already
[Music]
ah
no
i can do this
oops my fingers slipped
but do i still get the point
yeah
i'll dance and that's my [\h__\h]
i'll level into your mouth i'll always
remember the sound of a sweet voice
i just solved it wait there's another
one
oh dear it seems you've seen the other
side down with my secret wife could you
put this one back together too
it looks even easier it looks even
easier
if not for me then for creepy old good
grandpas everywhere
um sure um
god this is like
monster level
[Music]
what's it
this this is a way more difficult
picture
i don't even know what the original
looks like
[Music]
what
oh god no
i think i think i'll need to
accidentally
click something again i'll i think my my
greasy finger must slip again
no there's no way i'll solve this
this one belongs together
oh
wait i mean
[Music]
but this maybe also belongs to that one
yeah
no but that one probably goes to the
left side
are you gonna help me with this one or
not
oh
that one belongs together
no way man dude
[Music]
yo my fingers are feeling kind of greasy
here
[Music]
i'm so gracie i'm so sweaty oh oh
oh no whoopsie
oh that is intimidating
i win
sorry
you got a family member bench
oh dirty good old dirty it's been here
since i've looked up on my sweet curly
hair your sweet curly hair and your man
breaking arms
thank you so much for your help stranger
thanks to you i'm reunited with my lost
loves my book with them yeah mother
passed years ago but dirty is just in
witness protection you know from all the
men breaking
want a firecracker or gal
one
cold days i can still feel the fat of
broken body pain she left me
i bet i mean tonight's eventful i can
tell you it's on my pat it's past my
bedtime you young folk love staying up
late
me i'm in bed by six nightly after a
modest dinner of soft bug puddings and
four to seven episodes of soft flutes on
public broadcast anyway you know thanks
again for helping me out or should i say
helping free out
don't tell my grandkids
well can i get some bugs to go please
oh man oh man there's a lot going on
here let's try to talk to this dude
sleepy pants
can we wake you up
this is a man i'm so totally asleep
right now i love being asleep
i'm not gonna wake up what about these
people
what it's what do you call this kind of
musical group people
hello
[Music]
hey
you're not you're not in sync a quartet
oh a barbershop quartet
oh hello
[Music]
we're the downtown court i will sing you
a song it's not a very short one but it
also went long
we'll sing in the morning and we'll sing
it past noon
we've had a lot of noise complaints and
we'll be gone soon
hit the solo maurice
[Music]
maurice
okay
that is a simple introduction
we're we're pets on the uncles he's our
darling nephew all except for louise
who's just part of the crew
hey
lewis oh baby i'm not related to pat no
nothing like that i'm just a guy that
know that takes part in the show oh oh
[Music]
the story doesn't quite enter my brain
right now because i'm singing everything
well dude pull it back
sorry
the event
we can't tell you much but we sing like
a bird eh
it don't you didn't tell me anything
if you can help us if our act will tell
you all that we heard yes of course
i'll play do i have to sing
how to only get a quartet to hit their
solos when the scrolling bar shows the
singer's background point the spotlight
ah fun okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
louise isn't related oh i remember that
thank you
let's first warm up our vocal chords all
right keep an eye on the scrolling bar
at the bottom okay
since the shine the spotlight at the
singer with the matching background
okay
when the groovy disco pattern appears
shine the spotlight at the disco ball
will all sing together uh okay
are the gentlemen already my strong
oh god what how what
what what
what
[Music]
oh
well it took me a moment holy [\h__\h] yeah
we have no lives left
[Music]
okay okay okay
oh
if i do it again it will take 30 minutes
i'll do it
[Music]
i failed
oh no
okay
this time i'll rock it
[Music]
am i doing it right i think i'm doing
right yeah rocket
rocking elegant what
what do you mean
[Music]
how much time did we have
can i afford another time
i don't remember how much time we had he
said like 4 p.m but i don't know what
time it is
it
i wonder if i can do it again
no i want to do it again
a 30 seconds
[Music]
oh
okay should be fine okay aim for the
face okay okay okay okay okay
okay we start with the ball
[Music]
[Applause]
say that felt pretty good what do you
think fellas
not enough petrie's time patricia men's
more solo time
okay one more time for patrice oh round
two oh god okay patrice let's go
patrice
i'm your biggest fan
[Music]
the denise is singing real really
interestingly
[Music]
sorry about the knees sorry i was trying
my best okay
well to my ears that sounded
i feel like i could have had more timber
[Music]
i'm gonna prove it
okay okay last time okay okay this time
he's gonna be in the focus probably
give it all you got all right
here's a mustache
mustache man deserves spotlights
[Music]
are you guys cheering for them we need
to cheer for them
this movement
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice finishing pose
win
finally
oh we got a family member badge oh jeez
oh from him too
shouldn't it be four i only got three
come on man
all right sorry oh there we go
i thought so
you helped us with our song and to
improve our content now what we're gonna
tell you is rebooked at the event thanks
for all your help now we'll see you in a
wink unless we get arrested then please
bring us from the clink
all right they're gonna be at the event
maybe it's just gonna wait a second
i think i understand
i think i just
understood what the ending will be
they're not planning to kill pat it's a
birthday party didn't they say it's his
birthday or am i going crazy they're
planning a birthday party but it's a
surprise birthday party
so that's why they don't want to uh tell
me or him
what
wait a second did i how did i figure
that out it usually takes me much much
longer to figure out things
what
that's steven that's why they have i
mean them having music there
oh my god i saw fruit
i feel very intelligent right now okay
maybe there's a puzzle piece somewhere
able boy
that was obvious no it was not
no it was not
oh
so you go to the hill
oh you hear about joining the resistance
resistance
what resistance resisting birthdays
no i like birthdays
looking forward to my own again this
year
i shall
oh
my tea is cold or like lukewarm
[Music]
oh well
come to the front door but don't let the
feds tell you the password is the only
thing we're fighting for
just this absolute which is also the
name of my favorite marx leaning scub
band yes i said favorite there are more
than one
oh
it's not a face is it more not a snipper
is that a face now
no no i'm taking you seriously of course
there are two as a matter of fact the
first symbol was about putting a potato
in the tailpipe of a cricket alligator
governor when he tried to join their
mailing list
no gmos
as no governors may opt in
okay
he's so small
i'm monia but you can call me by my
online handle for safety which is kpop
angel85
you're into k-pop
i didn't think you would be into k-pop
you don't okay not a little but
i can have other interests besides the
cause
sure okay sorry about that true
it's almost like angel what the [\h__\h]
do you mean hat pad or do you mean bad
pet
no no you probably mean hat pad bat bats
is my high schooler neighbor that used
to pick me up for dsa meetings on
fridays until he got grounded he'd
apparently broken his name 99's favorite
set of extremely fragile and large-eyed
porcelain deer with something
the club
well it's not important we'll spring him
eventually yes dad i mean legally
for intruding anyway hot pad isn't okay
dude i barely know the guy but he still
made me a punch proof vest to where the
to protest protests out of dr soda
bottle caps he's a stand-up alligator
ally gator
he maybe drinks too much soda though
doesn't he know what the government
government puts in that stuff what is it
what is it what's disabled in there
i tell you what the cia agent that
watches my cell phone would probably
delete my tumblr in vengeance
he's he got i gotta give him a tinfoil
hat man he's one of us
that's where i keep all my pictures of
that one who's that i want a famous kpop
artist or what
which
i have four events to go this week oh
you're really popular
really active
like tomorrow the meet is gone on monday
at the soup kitchen then it's on taco
tuesday
at the women's shelter
it's just everywhere going for food huh
wednesday doesn't have a funny name but
everyone does get those cupcakes with
this white squiggle as an extra to
allocate a food bank
thank you
are you like
if you're talking about tonight though
you might as well go act like a cop
somewhere else officer pinstripes i
don't ride out my comrades my main my
mind is bolted up so tight uh the count
of monte cristo has spent years trying
to escape from me once planning his
vengeance against those who wronged him
it kind of seems a little bit too nebula
here
we just finished reading that book in my
tuesday lit class pretty baller to be
honest stevie h
wait no i guess he really says tbh who
does that that's like saying lol or lol
i love revenge and breakfast
no no do you have a game for me
like putting on eyeliner or styling your
hair so that you can't see your eyes
listen i'm not trying to give you
credible path or something i'm just a
little stressed out
not to go all first well props on you
bobs but i have a dying design due to be
scanned by tomorrow afternoon with signs
magazine
if i miss the deadline i won't it won't
get printed in time for the indie comics
annual people of bangs convention
there's a annual people banks convention
i need to go there all anime people have
bangs sorry this magazine okay i'll go
again
do you know how long it takes us to
staple a stack of these signs
at least two full episodes listening to
gator crater a true crime broadcast
about the world's most blown up
alligators
yes dad i also have lg for two over god
no shut up
if you could help me put some of these
pictures together maybe i could give you
this straight dope about that dope bass
super lit
so are you ready to join the resistance
of course
these characters are so funny
make paper word salad because your voice
is valid smells like zine spirit
oh teen spirit
mona's scene needs to cover three topics
evenly choose a clip to add to the scene
then click the page to glue it in place
be careful some clips cover two topics
at once
okay
i don't know if i understand that
so check it pin straps i've already done
all the hard scene stuff like picking
the clips and cutting everything with
semi-straight lines i needed to pick a
good selection and glue them in place
sadly ever since the thickening of 2017
i'm not allowed to use glue myself
or glue sticks or rubber cement or large
stickers or small stickers so you're
going to have to be that hero that takes
the pics all right i'll do it for you
i'm good with glue i have i have quite a
training with glue behind myself
this scene encompasses of course the
three most important most scenic things
possible i'm talking about social issues
in the comics and k-pop chiada pop
obviously these three topics go together
like peanut butter jelly and the fruit
comparable thing that escapes me in this
movie
but that doesn't mean we can lean into
any one more than the other my scene has
to be balanced so people will think i'm
biased that means no page space for any
one thing more than the other okay okay
so pick up and pick and get ready to
stick carefully in dough
i have a limited selection of content
and glue is forever just ask my hamster
your hamster what did you do with your
hamster
rip and valhalla be the third
did you
kill your hamster with glow
when you're done last time if it's ready
to scan so get fasting
i don't know if i understand what we're
doing
the cover is really important it has to
portray the essence of what's going on
inside it's sort of like choosing what
ironically humorous t-shirt to sport at
rush hashanah that will really unsettle
your extended family uh
what can i no no
[Music]
everything should be on it
local indie comics kpop
what was the third thing that would
covering what about this one is kpop
and
what
in the comics
i don't know
yeah a bit
maybe
what are we covering k-pop and any comic
swallows the third thing
this thing can you play fenstry maybe
can i social issues
uh
maybe this one is the most even
is this does this look even to you i
feel like this looks even
maybe
it also looks very emo
very itchy
although this one catches the eye more
fake yet i think
what would you guys say
where are the social problems covered
here though
[Music]
maybe it doesn't have to be so balanced
on the on the cover
i'll go with this
okay
eat it with leave in this will get him
cancelled for sure
for
toxic
don't forget to balance the topics i
wouldn't want anyone to accuse me of
political bias or standing bias
okay
[Music]
we'll put that
there
i actually made this one myself
no one watches the ferrex machine in the
school library at lunch time on tater
tot day
okay okay so we have the social issues
um
that's the kpop
or the x top what the [\h__\h]
i think that's the k-pop exxon was my
favorite before he got that haircut is
that a hint to um
a certain big
big group
a boy band now it just looks like a
local weirdo beardo giovanni from my
homeroom hopefully he smells less like
chemical burns
okay so we got the k-pop what was the
other thing a [\h__\h]
what's the other thing that's k-pop
again so i guess this one do you really
want someone
who eats a sad lunch for another term in
office what that's social issues again
wasn't there one more topic i forgot was
the first topic now i forgot the other
one
damn it can i switch it out but then now
it's not balanced
but maybe we have to balance it on the
other page then
i guess this one
this one kind of mondo bumps me out
so we had social issues twice and one
80 comics okay and okay social issues
twice and kpop once
i didn't play this very thing cool bangs
okay
so now we need we need uh in comics in
the comics this is any comics no that's
k-pop what about this
isn't that also k-pop
joshua ranson it doesn't sound like a
k-pop name though
[Music]
costuming
whatever i guess it just it just
shouldn't be k-pop
i don't know what i'm doing
hmm this one's really exclusive i can't
believe we got it
yeah
last inside page is a hard hitter you
have to really leave them wanting more
like really actually more like maybe
they'll give you a couple more bucks to
pick up a few of their comrades okay
okay so this has to be uh comics and
this is loyster phil's willpower
no no no
balance the budget what that's also
social issues
there is nothing about comics about
indie comics
that's k-pop that's social issues
that's social issues too
huh
i guess i'll go for kpop now
this is [\h__\h] rigged
is this
rng actually have this poster so
whatever blah blah maybe now what the
[\h__\h] this is social issues
this
is maybe indie comics or this one this
one
this is a comic come on
[Laughter]
this was last minute submission from my
friend's cousin mina
you can read the rest on her blog it's
got called the tour de force by someone
whose twitter icon was the best ship
from a popular tv show okay i need more
though
oh there's a comic
almost there just pass on the back cover
and we'll be done oh god and then we
balance it
wait it's korean
no that is about k-pop it's a it's a
it's a indie comic book about k-pop look
at this this is social issues
this is also k-pop
but social issues too
wow
i guess it's both
or everything
go with this
i know this is just a comic but this is
sort of what i imagined your life is
really like like i sit there and i
imagine it every day every day
did i fail
dull
i feel like i failed
i said fair and balanced but you're
clearly favoring one topic on the other
hand well you kind of gave me bad orange
[Music]
don't really have to listen to all of
this
again
uh
okay
cup is really important okay yeah yeah
okay we got the same colors i wonder if
the color was bad
okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's go with this cover
no wait
no wait it clearly says an indie comic
singing book design but
[\h__\h] what
well maybe we can balance it out
okay okay we have a big
uh oh god i don't know
i
[Music]
k-pop social issues
let's go this one
again
and then
this is a comic
so let's go with this one because we got
so many k-pop ones
and then
now we only have k-pop and social issues
again
[Music]
i'll go with k-pop remember we have so
much versus issues comic and k-pop only
one page so this this is uh this is
balanced it's all things should be
and then
now this page
we either have this cable page or this
i guess also kpop page
isn't this pope
k-pop yeah
joshua ransom it's either about the
whole group or just about joshua ransom
but i feel like uh an interview is
pretty cool
i'll go with the interview
okay
now now that was a lot of k-pop so
social issues
social issues and kpop
but how did the the cover count i wonder
okay social issues
social issues
that's a comic right
let's or or this one yeah let's go with
this one again
that's obvious to me
and then
past the back cover
ah what are we missing now
and now i think we can do social issues
again because i didn't have one
in a while but well i mean that's an
ugly back cover but i guess the looks of
it doesn't matter the quality probably
doesn't matter
okay let's see what happens
please please say it's okay
so here's your plus k-pop oh [\h__\h]
again
[Music]
plus k-pop
soldiers have three k-pop small comments
have won
can we skip this i don't know is it bad
to skip in
i mean there is apparently like if you
complete everything in the game is six
hours but if you don't it's two hours
but you can still complete the game
of these are double themed yeah i guess
so
time passes yeah
okay
but he'll send me a message if i if the
time passes too much right
[Music]
i'll still go with this one because i
feel like generally there's a lack of
indie comics
themes
i feel like we were close
social issues
comic
and uh kpop
uh
interview
um
i don't know
this one again
are you guys counting
and
comic
[Laughter]
and now okay we're last page again
what i do here
to comic to social 2k pump
someone said two comic 2k love one
social
free comic one kpop one three coming two
social two three coming two kpop 2
socials so far
okay so we need something that combines
kpop and social
this looks like k-pop and social
media whiplash and k-pop please say yes
please say us please say us please say
us
please say yes please please please
please oh
yes this is perfect let's jump into the
editor for approval
which is your dad
ah
sure whatever
where'd status monk
looks like we're all set to scan and
sent to printers
cute
okay oh geez
let's move on
family badge family members two of them
well how are they related to
pats again
they're not gonna read all this
i wanna go
[Music]
just wanted to make sure you know about
this cool local place called nana roos
antiques i know what you're thinking and
takes off for grandmas and you're right
the whole shop is run by a grandma
wellington and nanaru there's a great
local legend about the place that is
super haunted by like five billion
ghosts
what's really haunting though is the
price is ruffle
just a little shopping humor from me to
you i'm not really rolling on the floor
anyway another room is uh as much of a
car shark as she's a deal shark so be
careful but if you have time definitely
check out our colorful shop it's tons of
fun it's right there
let's go let's go
entering shop
ruffle
wow
there's a lot of people here
who's that small one jumping
diamond alice
hey hey look at me
do you want to hear my pop it's called
shiny tiny little thing here it is shiny
tiny money little thing what are you and
then it said i'm shiny got your money
little thing did you like it
i wrote it
um in my head because i can't write on
papers yet except for my name
but papa didn't like it when i write it
on grammar her english is about as good
as mine
[Music]
i'm gonna eat the whole
world what's in my pocket
now
doesn't come to babysit me anymore
understandable it's a secret i'm not
supposed to tell anybody your body
papa's not the fact that grandma would
be really mad even more in my turn when
i write it but on your butt but
[Music]
i don't want to eat pancakes that's not
my special plate because it doesn't
taste as pancake and you know how it is
don't put the smaller ones under the
bigger ones even i don't like that so
will you take me to pink i says
i was thinking today i wish i had
someone to uh cook meal pancakes every
morning man i'll play stacking pancakes
easy stack the bank is on alice's
special plate you can only stack a
pancake on an empty plate or on top of a
larger pancake uh-huh
[Laughter]
sounds manageable
um the a
so you only want it on your a-plane but
okay
but sometimes i guess i'll have to move
something around in order to
stack it properly okay i'm gonna know
that i am stacked badly on my special
point stack them carefully a big one
can't go in the little one you ready
i'll try this is yours okay okay
let's do uh
this is the smallest and we're starting
with the smallest you're kidding me
[Music]
i think
[\h__\h]
can i move to it once
ah
and put it back there too okay
[\h__\h]
i need to get to the lowest one
[Music]
oh i feel like i [\h__\h] up already
ah
damn it
hey it's difficult that's interesting
though okay
[Music]
itadakimasu
oh my gosh
[Music]
is it even more than before oh god
wait the [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah
damn it
okay okay okay easy hi
uh wait yeah that had to be okay easy
easy
easy there you go this is fun i like the
scam
come on get my skin
sounds kind of funny though is it going
even faster now
okay no problem oh [\h__\h] that's tiny
[Music]
[Applause]
that's actually confusing can you
try to wait a minute
um
oh god
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] wait a second
oh look the same size now
[Music]
um
no
ah
okay we finally got the bottom part
gonna place that in now okay
um wait um
[Music]
ah
i'll wait
that i know the other one is bigger i
think
okay okay this one and then
this one
and then
i think i got it this one this one
okay
there we go whoa you're eating a lot of
pancakes girl at least you're not eating
that many humans
if you ate that amount of humans we
would all die
[Music]
first try
oh
i always feel very accomplished after
eating a lot indeed maybe i'm gonna lay
here a little while there's gonna be
cake
and i wanna eat it so i
[Music]
after all that sugar in those pancakes i
don't know if you can really sleep but
that was adorable let's talk to that
lady
[Music]
you're late i've been waiting here for
an hour
what do you mean you do not work here
well it's not is that a ouija board
it's not as if you can fault me for
thinking so what with the drab wardrobe
and pathetic sunken eyes everything here
has the clear stink of death upon it oh
except for me of course i'm merely a
poor poor woman in deep mourning not at
all involved in mysterious circumstances
the police cannot explain
peace out yeah never seen that on the
ouija board before
ouija board
wait what does that remind me of ouija
board i saw that a meme video
what's oh yeah what's a what's up
what's the weight you
what was that people asking about ouija
boards ah people spelling wheezy boards
incorrectly
that was the meme video i saw
i'm really a lonely widow left behind
for the great beyond by my beloved light
husband horus oh horace always such a
wonderful wisp of a man
yeah wiggy board
luigi board
vegan
what is that the vegan board
[Applause]
he forever remained regal kind and
absurdly wealthy now in his absence i
find myself trying to take comfort in
the
met official arts
oh if only i could hear sweet strange
voice once more is that going to be the
minigame
pat you mean the one with the ridiculous
hat yes i am aware of him a terrible
stain on the bloodline that purpley
fellow
incredible all sorts of nonsensical
cousins for myself and my dear children
once removed at the very least though
it's of little comfort to me especially
when i see someone like patrick rolled
over a coffee table at the holidays
that's his most poisoned
he thought he saw the spiders man or
whatever nonsense
[Music]
oh i can't even imagine attending the
event on chapel road i've only my poor
there dear husband had been less
poisoned
i wouldn't there's a typo there
have to suffer such horrific indignities
will no one think of me and my feelings
can't sleep so i want you playing said
good choice but i hope you can sleep
soon too i have a i have a i have an
advice for you should try melatonin i've
been trying it too and it works it works
it works
it does work
don't use it every day
though only one really necessary
your questions grow tired some don't you
say you're riding up the vapors what are
you the lead detective investigating the
mysterious circumstances around my elite
husband's untimely demise
um
this lady is very very sus
how dare you i've had no rest for the
past week whenever i close my eyes i'm
visited by horace suspector reaching out
to me perhaps trying to send me
information about some secret treasure
he wanted me to inherit on top of the
rest of his racist state
it's illegal in my country what
really
i can literally buy it in the
supermarket here
will nothing stop his ceaseless haunting
if you could only find it in your heart
to help this poor widow i can give you
the information you seek
how do i help you
just use the spirit board to contact
horace and please find out when my
dearly husband once you want to know
what
oh what kind of evidence he has
you know you it would be better if you
wouldn't ask him at all wouldn't it for
you for you
hmm okay
follower goes for the eye of the plunge
jet it he could get tricky
the faster you move the more suspicious
the widow got
it
[Music]
okay
well i've never used a ouija board
before
magical insider to the dearly departed i
have my suspicions proof to me you can
contact my beloved late husband or i
shall out you as a charlatan to the
entire mean ladies bridge club
okay where's the ghost where's the first
one ah okay
slowly
was that good
it does seem like my [\h__\h] is perhaps it
really could be him round two okay okay
okay
not too fast not so fast where's you
and there he is
suspicion oh
there we go
nice
the mini games in this game are really
cool and fun man
could contact with the astral be
possible tell us more
like say if you know the circumstances
around your own death
i wonder if your nose man that's so sad
this like they should make a side game
about oh he's fast he's zooming
[Music]
a side game about his story what the
[\h__\h] i can't find him i saw him for like
a second
ah
finally finally
no don't disappear
no
should i can't go to
fast
goku
dude i'm trying to help you don't make
me lose this
finally oh my god
no i disappeared again
where'd he go
really
[Music]
i got that badge oh i got the ghost
badge too
it is almost too much to be believed
indeed my very foundations are ruffled
he loves me my horse said he loves me
even in this afterlife what a prince
among ghosts what a special speck to my
horse isn't so gullible
gumbo
thank you terry you've given an old poor
an old widow a reason to smile again
and also an airtight alibi
with a [\h__\h] she killed her husband
oh i must go tell the children at once
and also hide some sensitive items in
the toilet press
i know what gullible means i know no
i simply don't have any more time to
discuss the event with you today
farewell my medium
you're you're dangerous i don't want to
see you again
no more no more
all right what about you
i am still being a porcelain doll but i
came to life because of the magic of
this shop at least that's what i tell my
ex-wife so i can come sit here all day
i've got a good butt groove going in
this shelf
[Music]
you have a wife
and she
believes you that you're
okay
we haven't talked to nana yet
welcome to nano rose where if there's
ooze on your shoes it's just cause of
the booze
it's all dead it's all get out in
in here sweetheart so mine to ectoplasm
what
so you're interested in buying some
antiques from me today dollface we just
got in a huge new shipment of designer
grandma place never meant to be eaten on
as well as a bunch of confusing teddy
bears from the 70s with realistic
plastic faces i can get your real deal
on one of those if that's your fancy is
that you fancy i know kids are into
weird stuff these days
yes sir i i see you over there i'll be
with you in a minute
well shugo pie as the sign may have
alerted you i'm the only one and only
nana rule herself
only the finest antique goods and the
finest antique store owners
go on honey tell me i'm looking good for
my age
[Music]
i mean yes
you look just fine
ally stop harassing the customers
my sweet sweet patrick he's my absolute
shortest grandson
shortest as in tall
oh
[Music]
thank you for watching
why it feels like only yesterday he
would run about the shop squealing about
ghosts trying to eat his kidneys and
hiding in humorously oversized vases
love the voices thank you i'm doing my
best
gotta do them justice you know those
characters
as you know pro as you can probably tell
by my expression that actually was
yesterday that boy might not be playing
with a full deck
be careful with that vase it's expensive
ah so pat's inviting his little friends
to the event isn't that cute he's such a
darling little boy
i'll be closing the shop early to get
over there on time tonight gotta strain
all the ghosts out my wake before the
shindig you know those things tend to
hit your ride
yes sir i feel later for [\h__\h] sake
do you have a game for me too
sorry pumpkin looks like i have to stop
yapping about the event and take care of
a customer unless you defeat me in a
round of cards it cards
what do you say sweetheart i think you
can out all the old makeup is an old
made a game card game
i hope it's not a real card game
because i really i really don't know
card games
on your turn click to take one of
nanaru's cards then she'll take one from
you any matching pairs will be removed
oh wait should take one of your
animation pairs will be removed play a
left holding the old maid loses
[Music]
ah okay so i i i'm hoping for her
to take my old maid card
right okay
okay that's called old maid
okay that's that's that's an easy enough
card game yeah
which one is the old mate though do you
have it right now
house rules uh the younger player goes
first are you there at all you're spaced
out for a second sorry sorry okay i hope
i don't take the old maid
oh paris will is that good
is that good that i'm getting rid of
cards
i'll get you next turn i know it i find
so many pairs they should call me the
matchmaker okay so i suppose it's good i
her fingers are so cute the way she
takes the card
that's a pair for you okay
is
[Music]
only three left
oh
[\h__\h] now does chanel where i placed her
or is she not that smart
no
take the middle one yes she's so stupid
well i'll
no i wonder where she edited though i'll
choose the left one again hopefully yes
okay
[Applause]
wait then i'm out of cards though
and i win right
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
fun fun fun fun
i told her it was the bus
well my stars and gardens you really
beat me fair and square
i did
okay i can add that to the the
very few card games that i can actually
play blackjack
and this one
you know if you see my older sister
constance around you should try to
coerce her into playing around with a
doll like you
she also plays cards i think she'd get a
real kick out of it just don't stare at
her kind she's get a little feisty about
that so about the event make sure you
get there at any sharp if you get to
darling
what does that mean you might miss the
big surprise i'm sure to knock pat's
socks off can i be late
is it possible to be late or does the
game just force me to get there
uh if the time is up
i basically know
that that
basically can know the game
ending now
um i cannot be linked
darling wasting time ah i'll go left
it forces me
i'm forced
okay
wait does he wear socks is he
one of the shoes wearing alligators or
the nonshutters
a little something
well something will get knocked off the
boy we'll make sure of it
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's almost four and i could really
use your help oh
oh thank you for the red super chat
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you i should be able to
get to the super chat rating today
it's almost four and i could really use
your help do you know anything about
shoes
and the wearing of their
i know a thing or two
perfect could you come meet me at my
hotel room do i have to like uh
uh do his shoelaces
that's cute i remember
having to ask someone to do my shoelaces
all the time
just make sure you aren't fooled by any
shifty characters or college-aged
canvassers in cargo shorts
i already gave all my dollar bills to
that guy pretending to be the statue
outside the fourth street
i'm on my way
okay
are you so cute man
he's so cute oh this one's cute
wait maybe there's a puzzle piece in
there [\h__\h] i should have clicked around
more
i'm backpack
pat you don't have to worry about it
oh who the hell are you you're quite the
character
[Music]
good good evening to you fellow traveler
have you come to imbibe some ales after
your long journey as well and go so
pictures you'll find this novelty wine
based on the uh popular side what the
[\h__\h] uh nice suit i like dabbling in a
little bit of cosplay myself oh just
last year at uh alligator comic con yeah
uh yeah the rest is a character of my
own creation there is great wizard of
the door for
my brother mickey
help me put it together
no he didn't get it a bit slimy huh
here he has a nice haircut man
out there known as the terror of the
east side and most mag magics the
happening card game circles magic the
cavalry one reference i actually get
because i used to play magic the
gathering when i was like a child with
my family we played it together and i
always i was lost obviously
on campus i have known as a terror of
the ap biolab or the one with that
haircut yeah you were known here as the
one with the haircut i found a puzzle
piece
[Music]
finally finally yeah it makes me so
happy to know a reference i usually
never do
it's very unusual
how's your family so based
yeah
yeah yeah card games card games i
enjoyed playing magic
back then
[Music]
we didn't really play board games but we
did play magic and and some games on
computers yeah world of warcraft
like all the other families play board
games with their kids and we play magic
and
computer games
[Laughter]
fat is my second cousin as well as
my second favorite person to play
dungeons and dragons live
uh the first being my internet friend
carl whose dad got rich bite bite coin
uh-huh okay i understand bite coin
mining
that's a bart so you know pretty party
useless uh great singing voice though
he can really whale on that juice harp
yeah yeah it's a party
what am i not supposed to say
okay this is the point where it gets
really obvious
everything about playing magic on the
stream against who is there like
shadowverse is there like a steam online
version
[Music]
then i wouldn't mind getting back into
it but like i haven't played it for like
i don't know 10 years or something
or more probably more than 10 years
um
magic arena oh maybe i heard of that
[Music]
a
what color did you play again oh i
mostly went with like white
and blue i think
maybe sometimes green but mostly white
and blue i wanted like the the the
bright looking beautiful cards
like angels and [\h__\h]
toys
[Music]
chloe mentioned mtg in a stream recently
oh really
uh
so you played control i played nothing i
played i played uh being a stupid child
who doesn't know how to play a card game
properly and always gets beaten up by
blue white bird decks now
blue white flies
chloe thought mtg was mad but it was
short for meeting oh wait that's funny
why can't mean can mean both
ah fubuki likes mtg too really
[Music]
i wonder if my mom still has cards from
back in the day
i feel like those old cards are they
worth something now
i wonder if there were something now oh
[Music]
ah foreign
asking about the game
[Music]
i'm hungry
i said if it's you flair i'll do
anything
there's a meme in japanese language that
when you say
i'll do anything for you
it's like a meme like if you say that in
japanese and one of the japanese girls
streams if they say it the whole chat
will be like
you just said anything right
anything right right right right the
whole chat will say that
and now a few a few of my japanese
viewers are saying it
any anything you said anything didn't
you
okay next up do you have a game for me
you little uh uh bad uh uh weird shaped
friend
you were leaving already ah well safe
travels my vital traverser of the mortal
plane
perhaps we'll meet again in another
realm or on an internet forum for role
playing
i like to i want to role playing
on the internet for him
when i was younger too
i like this dude
bob
you're standing right there now
hello esteemed guest mr pat asked me to
inform you to come straight to his hotel
room upon the raffle he also asked me to
warn you to knock first in case he was
wearing pants
in case he was wearing pants but not to
say the second part out loud oops kind
of forget what i just said then come
with me i'll walk you to mr pat's room
at once okay
he's such a gentleman
his posture is so perfect
where's the lock
huh
ah okay okay okay okay okay that wasn't
his though uh no that's not gonna be no
no no no
please don't tell the internet we've had
a biohazardous incident again
[Laughter]
no problem i'll keep it secret
and safe
yeah one of you more about the robot no
it's nothing nothing weird just like uh
kind of like i don't know like fantasy
style like i would always make up like a
cute elf character
um
or ah there were some some themes like
uh i don't know vampire schools or so
and i would i would make up a cute
vampire character and
we would choose like pictures random
anime pictures from the internet to show
off how cute our character is so i would
i would google cute anime girl
and i would choose the cutest picture or
cute anime elf girl
and that one feel like that's me
[Music]
princess
um i've lost my family and um i'm a
warrior i can use magic
um
and and uh yeah yeah i'm traveling alone
alright so i also have a i have a
companion a bird so yeah stuff like that
yeah kawaii anime vampire elf no
watermark in school uniforms kawaii
school uniform anime girl google go
google search go
they never really lasted long it was on
uh there there's this there's just
there there was this anime
german german anime
forum it still exists now but they have
i don't know if they still have the
section but there was this section where
people would open up like rpg
[Music]
sessions kind of like a forum though and
then then it would either be like open
and and you can join with whatever you
make up or you can um
they make a list of what they need for
their story like what character they
need and then you would apply for it
some are really exclusive
somewhere really exclusive yeah yeah
yeah
you have to
write like
an audition almost
[Laughter]
um you know what i'm talking about
yeah it was so cringe now that i think
back uh it's so cringe
but i did that in my as my past time
sometimes i made up my own
uh and had other people join my own and
of course it was cringey [\h__\h] like
vampire schools because back then i was
watching vampire night and uh i was
really inspired by vampire night it was
my favorite anime for a while
really edgy
i think back fondly of that yeah i guess
me too it was fun it never really
got very far like after a few pages
usually people would disappear
and and move on to other rpgs for some
reason
your vampire night man
oh and i also another one that i liked
during that time was uh
um
what was it called something like my my
kaijo is made summer
my my my my school something president
or so is it made or something like that
i really love that one too
i actually read the manga for that one
and for vampire night two that's one of
the two of the few mangas that i
actually did read
kaiju are made of summer yeah yeah yeah
yeah another cringy super cute jojo
i was so into that kind of
um
tacky shoujo
mangas
back then now not anymore
um
[Music]
knock knock
no oran high school host club i never
got into
i think that was too many boys
welcome back i was just trying on some
uh nothing it wasn't embarrassing
i i wasn't doing anything actually so
have you talked to more of my family
found out any secret plans yeah i know
exactly what is going on can i tell you
you think they're for me no no no you're
totally wrong about that
i would definitely know if they were
doing that plus it sounds a little
far-fetched don't you think he looks
kind of happy though
yeah
i wish someone i have never had do you
guys have you guys ever had someone for
your surprise a birthday party i've
never had that before
[Music]
i would have to tell someone to throw me
a surprise birthday party but then i i
would know it's it is one
i feel like nowadays it would be kind of
difficult to throw me a surprise
birthday party because like
i would probably find out in some way no
no no no no no oh it seems to be a
really unrealistic thing
one time when i was eight
that would require friends oh come on
apparently it's like a thing that only
exists within movies and netflix
hmm
oh everyone says no
[Music]
i feel like it would be cute you know
cause like people when people get
sorry when people get older a lot of
people are like i don't want to
celebrate my birthday anymore right
i feel like when you stop celebrating it
it's easy to surprise one of the parties
so that's when it would be nice to have
a surprise birthday party
um
maybe someone will do that for me one
day
happens sometimes i've been planning in
a i've been in a planning process but
never had one done for me oh man
[Music]
hmm
i guess
now if you already planned something on
your own why would anyone
afford for your own birthday why would
anyone say okay let's do a surprise
birthday party even though they're
already planning one for themselves
anyway anyway anyway
yeah wink wink wink link
i don't think i could do a surprise
birthday party with the whole life when
to like celebrate a birthday so much
work goes into it i'm already planning
merchandise for my birthday in june
june's my birthday right
7th of june or 6th of july
wait no it's 6th of july i was
the 6th of july or 7th of june
july
of course yeah of course
[Music]
just might forget this is my second
birthday after all i never
the last one was the first one was last
year and um
of course i would forget it
i'm not so used to it yet
don't don't imply
don't think too much
into it
anyway um um
you can't pull one over oh no pat on his
birthday that's what i always say well i
say it sometimes like once a year he's
so cute by the way they're definitely
putting together a systematic plan to
end my mother into small life
no bad why the [\h__\h]
you know when i read the description of
the game i really thought it was about
you know getting him killed and the
conspiracy and protecting him is so cute
[Music]
not a hodo
this is why people say you leak stuff
what what does that what does that have
to do with anything with anything
there's nothing to do with anything
there was six favorite seven is also my
employee number huh
[Music]
who hurt you pat yeah
maybe if you talk to a few more people
you'll find that something we can really
use in the meantime though i actually
call called you back here because i
needed your help you think i'm having a
problem i surely need a problem okay so
you want to wear shoes but you're not
even gonna
like put on pants
but i figured if i did tonight maybe i'd
have better look like hot putting it out
of the event to safety if i need to the
issue isn't my usual shoeless pencils
nature but the drawer is where i
actually keep all my things last week my
nana roo gifted me an antique armor from
her shop as an early birthday present
it's being spacious practical and so
super haunted that it's leaving a weird
stain on the parquet flooring just by
existing
i haven't been able to find any of my
shoes and whenever i open a drawer weird
stuff happens yeah why don't you see it
for yourself
soul-searching find a pair of pat's
favorite shoes by clicking on the
suspicious drawers be careful if pat
gets too scared he'll give up on shoes
forever after each round the contents of
the drawers will shuffle around spooky
doesn't sound spooky at all
help me find my shoes please suspicious
drawers
yeah
close close it close it
[\h__\h]
i don't think there was any way of me
knowing where would it where it would be
oh [\h__\h]
i'm amazing i'm amazing i felt it
some something was guiding me to success
yoho
we made it there
i have nice shoes too by the way
wait more you need more pairs of shoes
[Laughter]
[Music]
nothing in there
stop all my luck ah i found a different
shoe
hey what about the other was that not
supposed to be was that not considered a
shoe when i'm looking i'm looking for
two different pairs of shoes now
[Music]
did it reset
oh no
that's the most terrifying thing i've
seen all day
oh no it's the hands yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i didn't get reset what if i open this
one again
[\h__\h]
i opened so many now
[Laughter]
[Music]
can you reset the anxiety please
wait which one did i not open almost
everything did i open top right
[Music]
how are there
i feel like i accept exactly didn't open
two yet
a memory game
[\h__\h] no no no
i'm so sorry
[Music]
that's my first time opening them
bottom middle
which one
this one maybe this one the one below
wait did you he didn't okay he didn't
mean it literally that he's never gonna
wear shoes again okay okay okay man we
started out so well
[Music]
i did so well in the beginning
oh no
i'm so scared
okay brown
shoe different shoe so wait so now i'm
have to look for that one
because
that over
overpowers the brown shoe
[Music]
it's the
wait so there's three pairs of shoes in
there at the same time
damn it now i'm looking for that one
okay wait so
red shoe
uh
what's the brown one in here
and the blue one
what's over here or here i think
ah okay okay okay okay that one is okay
so now that those two get replaced with
a ghost or or something scary i suppose
wait what do you mean find another oh oh
i i do have to ah
okay
okay okay around two okay it doesn't
matter which one okay okay okay so now i
suppose
they're mixed and again
okay
um
[Music]
i'm not surprised anymore
ah
the eyes
sour run okay we're looking for this one
now top left easy to remember
[Laughter]
bottom row second from the right is a
brown shoe
oh no she did it third round
okay
[Music]
it's ridiculous
[Laughter]
i'm just going road to row [\h__\h]
[Music]
slipper
i want to find your slipper now
um
[Music]
i got you buddy yeah your shoes
oh you're so happy they're so colorful
too i can't believe you found all three
pairs of the shoes that i own every shoe
kind of
every kind of shoe is represented here
brown sneaky and tropical
you know looking at them now it's kind
of giving me performance anxiety
actually maybe i should just go bear
flipper like i usually do
now i want to say you wear them because
like you're standing on your tippy toes
i want to see you stand normally when
you're wearing the shoes
i'm really curious
thank you guys thank you
such a fun game
sorry i'm so nervous i'm i'm not
thinking straight i'm sorry i mean to
come back here for nothing but i really
appreciate that you did oh teaser
i'm so glad we met today you're the best
spell i've had in a long time i only
liked me well that's mutual
really
you get back out there and dig up more
dirt and i'll text you just before
the event i see you later investigator
see you later
alligator
honey cutie pie man i can't believe it
unknown
you again
again your friendly city guide here and
i was wondering have you been finding
any puzzle pieces around not many no
i thought so you can find uh a lot of
fun things you might not expect in the
city by clicking around puzzle pieces
secret
bottles to look at interestingly shaped
sewer rats it's a real menagerie
maybe if you find enough pieces you'll
be able to do something good with them i
like unluck something or make a small
blanket for a family of chili squirrels
you know we've gotta save the squirrels
they're leasus
uh the world is bright so have lots of
fun looking around
thank y'all
look at him
[Music]
he's so cute
his mannerisms ah he's looking at us
[Music]
okay i guess let's go out
we don't have that much time left if i
understand correctly
did you know that's how they sell say
hello no not quite like that
italiano at least that's what i said on
the back of my christmas rice's box
today see
there is a lot of different alligators
from all over the world here in
alligator new york city that's why they
call it a melting pot not because of
that strange smell the sidewall gives
off in hot weather as i originally
thought if you want to meet any
interesting people during your stay
maybe you should take a start you should
start on the trolley since everyone uses
i already went with that one
you never know who you might strike up
conversation with there yo who might
throw a bag of hair at you and then run
away
that's the big city for you and full of
surprises
ciao bella
all right
and then let's go somewhere else now oh
but should we like work on our puzzle
on our another puzzle but the thing yeah
then let me let me do some family foods
i don't think we'll be able to complete
it
um realistically speaking
but i wanna i have a ocd a little bit so
i want to fix this so she's really old
she could be like
she could be here or she could be here
yeah ah
second try it makes sense okay grandma
uh wait was she don't know
oh god
who was the one who's not related with
anyone
there's a
jungling a young wing
one of the youngest ones
no
ah there it is easy
these how many are those one two
three four five five
four
oh maybe here
that's like four spots now
somewhere where there's four spots maybe
you know
just guessing now
that was louise which one
damn it maybe they're not that close to
each other maybe it doesn't matter
where do you go my master's friend oh
you're the father of that girl
oh
okay i have another oldie oh oh papaya
a baboo oh where you go
huh
[Music]
oopsie oops this one's also like kind of
old so somewhere in the bottom
ah there we go and you have a dead
husband right yeah yeah yeah this one
goes here you have a child
where's your child
but this one was the child of some dad
that we met where's the ah this one we
didn't place him yet
oh oh okay then i know where you go
you go either here or here or here okay
now
wherever these ones go oh nice
baritone
oh denise the age 50 really wow you
don't look that old at all
shouldn't pat get a special spot how oh
there finally we got pat's butt
and
how was he related
to him wasn't he just a friend
uh okay there we go nervous dairy
okay it looks already pretty full so it
seems like we haven't met like
about 50
of the npc's
pat is 24
apparently
he seems younger
thanks again dear come back anytime
not bad at all um
damn we met a lot of people all
right let's go to
hmm shall we go to the fan district
let's go to the fun district sounds like
fun doesn't oh we are in the front of
the street
oh i think we are in the front district
it was pretty fun
[Music]
puddle piece puzzle piece puzzle please
puzzle please puzzle please puzzle
puzzle puzzle oh i can talk to you
face constancy
ah did you say something
i see you over there writing my cards oh
wait oh you're the one and you're the
one
we were like low-key looking for her
yeah her neck is [\h__\h]
her back and her neck hmm
the last time i was giving cards away
was long before you were born and now
look at me i'm old
see what sharing gets you urging your
reparables
cat hair oopsie
i have about 50 cats at home you know it
happens one day your skin is sucked
close to your skeleton and then you turn
around and boom your jaws are hanging
down past your collar bones which are
now hollow inside
oh man
sounds tough
is that what you want hollow collar
bones with the nest of daddy long legs
inside ew
and stop staring at my guards with
[\h__\h] sake
[Laughter]
she scares me a little bit she
intimidates me
some some old people are really scary
um
that's only the business of me and the
nurse that puts the ointment on my back
piece three times a week
stop staring at me
okay okay chill not looking at your
cards where are you cards
why did pat tell you to go steal his
great aunt's cats
because if he did i ain't gonna give him
his christmas brand present this year
which is of course a bag of oranges and
a strange tin of popcorn from 1987.
oh wow that would make me so happy what
a wonderful christmas present
okay chill chill
oh my god someone help her calm down
i ain't telling a kid like nothing wow
okay your sister sister right
was better nicer
oh no you could blame me for the
information as long as you don't stand
back
what do you think you don't think you
can beat the old maid
all right we're gonna play oh alderman
again okay okay
she feels like a cheater
[Music]
okay
same game
yeah
tin popcorn i don't even know what that
is
oh she has fancy cards
before age my dear
okay
might go first
shut up
[Music]
first turn going well
how many pairs have you made alright one
which car will have me with i don't know
she was a good one
okay
compare of course it was a pair seems
logical doesn't it i'll take the middle
you'll get one back don't you worry
about it we've had this before
not close
close
[Music]
shut up
now it doesn't matter which one i take
okay now there's three cards please take
the middle one please take the middle
one gotta put on my poker face
shut the weight wait doesn't this end
lead to me winning anyway because i take
the last card it will be no no wait i'm
losing
ah cause i'm taking her last card no
my poker face didn't work
[Music]
she's cheating what's she cheating i
don't think so but we can we can claim
she was
that's right go home with your tail
between your legs bear you better you
maybe your mommy will wipe the tears off
you snoot
you know what maybe she deserved to win
maybe she needed a win i think it's good
that we gave her a win
[Laughter]
fine with me
uh
fancy influencer girl taking photos for
her instagram i assume
did you get the right angle on the right
filter
um hello
do you have been stepping approximately
three to seven steps to the right you're
blocking the sun and the luminous scales
highlighter i applied is not living up
towards customer review section go
[Music]
i've been out there all day with my new
phone trying to get the perfect shot but
i just can't seem to look effortless
enough
this one here i totally have an
expression which is super no no in
selfie town
i need to look just the right amount of
disaffected with just the right amount
of lip gloss this gloss won't pay for
itself after all you want you know cause
i pay for it
man yeah like i buy it not my mom okay
totally i'm using my own money
[Music]
i'm lizzie but i've been trying to get
everyone
start calling me elizabethary
sadly much like my attempts to be an
influencer it doesn't seem to be
happening you are
speaking off i'm promoting fizzy fruit
like croc this week on my social medias
would you like to try some so good like
oh my god this soda water that a fruit
farmer thought about in passing giving
just enough fruity essence to confuse
the plate
fizzy fruitless crock consideration of
strawberry hashtag amazing
pat you mean joanie's cousin pat you
know he's so lame
oh my god low-tech let me take it back
okay pat it's hilarious i was just
joking just kidding oh my god
couldn't you notice
last year when i spent the holidays of
joni's family
listen pat got so punked on eggnog
you thought the christmas tree was a
hired assassin and ran face first into a
santa themed nutcracker just playing to
escape it took us two hours to get all
the walnut shells out of his ears and to
get him to stop wearing the beard as a
disguise [\h__\h]
crack not case
he's kind of paranoid guy totally nice
though love the bandana
i would like to try that as like you
know maybe maybe uh could wear it as a
top i feel like i could totally rock
that it would like accentuate the rest
of my body perfectly
i don't know are you here spying for pat
he's not supposed to know anything about
this you feel me
i didn't even post about it on this
notebook or picture ground on my laptop
on my dead journal i didn't even write
it down in my bullet journaling journal
supposed to be extra save but did i save
on bullets
wait who the [\h__\h] so uses like journals
and pens and paper you win that [\h__\h] is
like so disgusting and it hurts the
trees and you know we need the trees
like oh my god they saved us like what
we do without them so please don't kill
the trees because yeah just stop using
paper why would you use paper and you
could just put anything on your
instagram story like yes
[Music]
so many more people will say it anyway
because i'm like fame yes
but maybe if you could help me out i
could give you just a little info though
uh you know a little uh you stand my
account and i stand in yours follow me
back you know follow for follow yes
see even though i'm totally a super tech
savvy super popular pictogram user with
over seven followers seven that aren't
blood related to me oh i still am having
some trouble with my new phone trying to
import my photos and they get all things
dunked dinked up i can't post things
photos what the [\h__\h] and what my
followers do if they are denied the
knowledge of their parasocial bff liz's
most recent vegan cafe exploits i need
to show them like right now i need to
share what they do all day every day
three times five times a day maybe even
ten times yeah i have big goals you know
i've been the biggest influencer ever
like i don't know kim kardashian yeah
right that's what hashtag give peace a
chance so will you help me fix my pinks
please i heard you're good with
photoshop
give me some more boobies please and i
want that like
one meter wide a hip please and the
waist shall be about as thin as my neck
yeah it's super realistic trust me oh no
one will notice how how deformed the
background is no one will notice that
the stairs are like totally different
size that the the railing in the
background that it's not straight but
shaped like [\h__\h] ocean waves now no
one will notice that they only look at
my body and my face it's like believe me
trust me like i don't know what you're
talking about don't look at the
background just blur that [\h__\h] out yes
put a sticker on it like a cute one
yeah this this one for example
that's the perfect one yes
yes i need the perfect hourglass shape
the photo is already divided into
sections click each section to stop it
in place a sample complete photo to win
the round one i don't understand man you
yes thank you we totally should get a
selfie to of this moment hold on let me
get my stick out of its swarovski
spelled holster oh selfie stick what
wait what
what oh oh oh my god wait that hurts my
eyes oh
oh [\h__\h] okay
okay i understand understand uh
uh-huh
hi
uh
okay oh no i didn't i clicked earlier
it's the [\h__\h] pain
um
okay food instagram here we go new goals
[\h__\h] oh oh my god wait i i absolutely
pressed it early but the pain helped me
this time it's going too fast stop no
[\h__\h] rigged game man
this is [\h__\h] rigged
and do it again this time for real
whatever it doesn't matter let's do this
one okay
after the food then okay there we go
click it a little bit early well yeah
after the salad
like right at the salad no what the [\h__\h]
it's like what
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god my eyes help me whoa what does
it say i want to read what it says like
i can totally read
okay
[Music]
uh
oh my god no [\h__\h] let me reduce
[Music]
save me
we're doing this one now
wait which one is that ah
i'll go yeah
oh
okay
it's your destiny
wait which one
ah
that one okay
i swear to god i swear to god
i swear it's gone
why is it so hot
why is it so hard
you can't see it it was so fast my eyes
are hurt
ah
what
okay now i can read it
it's so true
so [\h__\h] true
okay
eat it with little blue leaf and
at least she had a stance on alligator
healthcare reform and not just platform
of more sci-fi themed escape rooms
okay reset to your stats cause you suck
oh my god oh my god that
i can't see
okay oh my god
oh my god it does not hurt your eyes
guys if you're trying to look with
it uh if you're trying to follow the
pictures oh my god
is it just me
we try to focus on it like oh my god oh
oh okay okay oh my god oh my god i'm
sorry oh
and okay chill chill oh my god
oh
my god
legit my eyes hurt and my head hurts
oh my god i'm rocking it
k-pop band let's go
[Music]
are we doing a third one that's even
more
you're gonna kill me
i'm gonna kill me oh no
okay okay window okay window okay okay
okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay i can do this i can do
this
i figured out the ping now
okay i got the other ones immediately
though
the [\h__\h] i didn't even try
okay
hi
oh
which one
okay
[Music]
holy god jesus christ hallelujah
no that's not my room
i just climbed in the open window if you
don't want people taking pics of your
perfectly chic apartment for breaking
and entering don't live on the first
floor you dingus
uploading and posting
so many likes oh my god
keep those comments coming come on i
want to read your opinion only positive
ones i'll delete everything that's
negative so shut up be careful
only praise me keep the praise coming
[Music]
especially these cute candies of joanie
damn that was really intense for my eyes
my eyes are safe yeah but they hurt oh
my god i hit tweet oh jeans
sorry
guys i'm sorry
i'll come inside when i take cannons of
my significant gator they're like cute
and perfect but when joanie takes some
of me they're like damn
oh
yeah she's eating my chocolate chip
cookies hashtag relatable relationship
thank you alexander oh yeah about the
tween my line don't tell pax but i
totally did a playlist for it i think
he's going to be super surprised
about the tweet
a playlist for the party
well i'm not as surprised as the tammy
opened the closet and a coat fell on him
he screamed so hard that he projectile
vomited several liters of cranberry
sauce
content warnings bodily fluids
thanksgiving
thanks again we all you have stranger
make sure to like and subscribe how what
like
we're in the real world girl
imagine like saying goodbye to someone
and being so [\h__\h] immersed in the
internet world that instead of goodbye
you say like and subscribe bye bye
youtubers be like
like and subscribe mommy bye bye
see you tomorrow
i hope she'll not notice and what i just
said hit that notification bell
smash that like button daddy bye bye
[Laughter]
oh yeah
[Music]
i know we haven't figured out what the
family isn't telling the various secrets
yet i did
but maybe we were there together i'd
feel safer is that okay
what welcome to where
to the party
oh is it already time
this is already time
hello
well hello
and pleasant evening my good jump i
didn't mean to startle you
oh no
i didn't mean to start holier
not i
you see it is within my very nature to
skulk mysteriously around corners and to
like in-depth silence as my mother was a
mysterious slipper designer and my
father was mysteriously absent
he's buying milk
okay let's go
[Laughter]
welcome back it's team caster i'm afraid
our kitchen is closed early for a close
event in the hotel ballroom tonight oh i
wonder what that could be i provided mr
pat with some complimentary stale oyster
crackers and tap water if you follow me
i can show you his room
let's go
part of me will begin walking at your
leisure
okay
i know i know
maybe there's a i mean there's a puzzle
piece here that i didn't pick up
no
maybe not because like every time i
click something it moves all right all
right i'm here i'm here i'm here
are you dressed up bunny
i'm so glad you came back i've just been
guzzling tap one isn't stressing these
funny crackers the way they gave me even
though i'm not going to wear them i went
and got all my shoes out anyways i think
just from the company it's scary being
alone in here oh man he's such a freak
was so cute i love him so precious
and now the event is about to begin but
maybe since you're here nothing bad will
happen
no
this counts as something bad happening
don't worry i'll be fine
i'll save you
oh you have a flashlight i'm scared of
the dark and no flashlights but slightly
less
i don't know i don't think i oh i guess
i do
hey you found one do i look like that
one video by alex gator queen what
hopefully with this we can make it for
the corridors of the hotel to the
ballroom where the event is safely
so you want to go to the event
just walk really close with me okay we
have no way of telling who or what is
out in those twisty halls
a navigator
enough
[Music]
the power's out click and hold to guide
pat for the dark hotel all righty
we have to protect him our precious
little boy ah
okay
it's so cute i'm walking around behind
him
hey what
whoa oh which way to go straight or down
i'm going i'll go down
is it like a maze oh there's that's
something
that
i shouldn't be seeing
[Music]
[\h__\h]
yeah that is
terrifying
i i totally get you buddy on it there's
a wall oh wait i need to go for the door
hi
open it
what
or is it what oh it's stairs it looks
like a wall
but i can't oh oh okay okay
i guess it is stairs then we go down or
up
huh don't go there
am i going the right way
should we
what the [\h__\h] is happening oh they're
making out
is that someone we met the lady looks
like someone we met
should we say hello
oh
so a friend um i think we might have
gotten to something sensitive don't look
don't look don't look guys
yeah that's awkward
[Music]
i'll go up
wait where's my face what the [\h__\h]
did i just have no face
self-examination
he's so cute this is one of the cutest
games i've ever played
five
curious what's up there
oh there's so many
so many paths ah that's that one okay
okay that's connected
is this like a kitchen
oh wait that we came from there and now
i get it now i get it okay
okay
i think we need to go here then
is that the lobby no
i feel like we're really close there's a
picture oh my god a picture
oh that's really scary that's an actual
ghost
that was even an intense halloween
decoration to prove that life presents
beyond a smaller coil either way i'm not
really happy about it
doesn't
can't we can't go on there
did i miss something
ah it goes here okay it goes down here
ah left or right left is nothing oh no
there's something
um
oh god he's scary
will he kill us
it looks really
like he's about to attack me i don't
even want to really
encounter him
but so far everything that we
encountered didn't really hurt us can we
lose this minigame
he's about to jump at me yeah
i don't know man
i can't lose this game okay
[Music]
well he's actually scared i understand
that like some other things were not
scary like the clock was though but that
was that was also weird
and the ghost i get you
i can get you buddy what is that shadow
the floor's so cracking
that's really scary where am i going
where am i going
ballroom
what is this weird shadow
oh this is a huge maze
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] did they get here he's
following me
the deal was just as scary as this
obvious possession
i wonder if he can if he can get scared
twice no
he's so cute
i love him
he's my baby oh
[Music]
oh i can't go past here oh it seems like
a dead end
nothing spooky drawer mama mia please no
i beg of you please
have mercy on me
i'm so young 24 years old this path i
think
i'm still so much ahead of me so many
possibilities and so much potential
come on
please save me
some of these we have encountered before
so i guess this is for example someone
we have not encountered before but could
have there's just something unwholesome
about reading graphic novels in the
pitch dark sediment of a broken hotel
yeah i mean yeah that is pretty weird
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is that didn't we hear about
this dude
did you see it move i think i saw it
move
oh no
as good i would say on you well okay
that was a dead end let's go here did i
come from here
no is this it oh well this person looks
nice
[Music]
this one sound
that's it
oh that's what he's doing and when he's
attracted to spotlights
like a mop that smells like hair gel
i love this game i want to marry the
scam
where i have a wrap laughing
yeah that's the horror game for my for
my
batsu game for my punishment game right
i'm done now right
i'm sick
happy
birthday
happy birthday dear pack
happy birthday
birthday to you
happy birthday to your path happy
so everyone that we talked to is here
now
mercy it's been a dog's age since i've
been to swinging
you know
i'm just kidding what the hell is that
what she's saying
the
kids want
[Music]
we got we got a band singing for you
happy birthday to you you live in our
door
you smell like an alligator and that is
unsuspicious and correct
okay i didn't know that those lyrics i
guess i have been singing it incorrectly
all my life
[Music]
good evening
good morning
an auspicious sign that we have crossed
paths once more perhaps we have some
unknown star dying
connection what you really want to read
my scene about cool with that
check it out i have a whole chapter
dedicated to the
top because they're groovy
oh
man
how lovely
oh those two are hanging out
you guys just kept staying in your faces
when you came in it took like a thousand
pigs that looked like he thought he was
going to die or something long hold on
and tell me life vlogging this
[Music]
hey there i got word you guys wouldn't
make it on account of the blackout
backpack scared of the dark and hallways
and parties come to think of it this
usually doesn't end as well as this is
what i'm saying
[Music]
oh i'm so proud of my patchy it didn't
fight in the cold rock shadow of a
staple and jump out the window or dump
the punch bowl in in the toilet thinking
it was poison this is already going so
much better than his birthday last year
i already talked to him
[Music]
it's time for an old-fashioned shake
just ignore the snail trail i'm told
it's full of vitamins and helps it's
drying and that it comes out my limbs
and leaves crying oh hey where are you
going
[Music]
i'm gonna lose my ah irp
discounts being up this late they take a
hard look at your benefits if you do too
much staying up past eight or
rollerblading i'm not giving up my
tuesdays at roller world sounds like fun
man
i'm so happy oh there's pat i didn't
realize
you look different with the birthday hat
i wasn't getting rubbed out i was
getting perfect clouds
it's so nice to have my beloved family
with me we're going to take a big family
photo and everything wait so
wait judging by what the mom said
he gets a birthday party a surprise
birthday party every year no
but
uh
shouldn't he be anticipating it then
wait
he gets it every year but he's still
like so freaked out every time
he's so cute
wait if anyone ever asked me who's my
favorite game character
if anyone ever asks me that again
[\h__\h] all the characters see all the
tales of characters whatever
i'm gonna say patch from later alligator
it's my favorite game character
it's so cute
[Music]
he forgot
he's innocent he's paranoid relatable
relatable man
oh he's so cute
i love them so much
[Music]
ah that means you too that's okay
everything you did for me today and
really meant so much for me you're
really a special friend i can't thank
you enough oh come on everything is
ready for the photo except for you
follow me
i feel like i missed talking to someone
oh that's me we see my face now we
didn't until now that was that that's
why we didn't even see it on the on the
on the under in the mirror
ah
what kind of alligator am i
[Music]
oh they all look wonderful they all look
fabulous
oh i will be this one because it looks
like a candy corn
that's so cute
you get to be
now look at yourself
it's a difficult choice to make uncle
with this
oh
can i be a pink alligator no okay
i wanna be
this one
and
um
[Music]
i want that
oh
so many shapes of alligators
i can have a pink tie
the hair is important no how cute hair
oh so much choice don't you
that looks like my hair
can we have it orange no it has to kind
of be like oh i mean that's brown
i guess let's go with brown and it looks
kind of orange if you um
imagine
how long you know what's in the glasses
i want those fancy glasses i also like
these though
but i'll go with this i look like a
[\h__\h] weirdo
i look
weird i look like um
i feel like i feel like
let me look it up before i say something
completely wrong
[Music]
okay because i thought i look like elton
john right now
i don't know why i thought of that it
doesn't even look like elephant jumper
somehow i feel like i have a i have
elton john vibes like this
and you agree
oh my god i'm not the only one
[Laughter]
i've been elton john all along
oh wait take a picture
don't make it go away don't make it go
away don't make it go away
wait i'll make myself a
ah
oh well i'll be i'll be here
wait
i'll be here
and i'll take a picture from my side
snipping tool
[Music]
oh man oh wait i could do it late
uh maybe i could be late
come on come on you can do this you can
do this
let's see how it looks if i take it
like this
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] wait i'm taking it for obs it's
kind of difficult one second
[Music]
i'm not quite on it but that's okay
okay
let me try again let me try again
[Music]
a bit more
wait
[Music]
that was perfect no it's perfect cheese
oh perfect
i can't think
[Music]
oh you want to sing
i took the perfect picture
look
[Music]
maybe we should put another one in here
oh
it's beautiful
[Music]
happy
end the end
this is beautiful
oh i'll have to print that out i legit
want to print it out i have a printer a
working printer
i want to print that out
makes me happy
okay
[Music]
mandy right what's mandy
you're so this is so blessed it is so
blessed so wholesome the game is one the
stormy and sweet but though it seems
done has it's all been deceit
what's really going on does your tail
and right here the more family you come
upon the more truth will grow clear
there's a real truth
is the truth not that it's a birthday
party
oh that's so cute
[Music]
i don't know if i want to play more on
stream right now because i need to read
super chats and if i consider that it's
going to be late already
[Music]
the true ending is worth it
ah
i feel it that might take
a bunch more time
[Music]
maybe enjoy it for myself maybe that
gives you guys a reason to play it
yourself too
or the real ending comes after them and
then what after the credits what oh oh
okay
you unlocked path game scam more
mysteries await you and i'll go to new
york city what's pop game skip
it would take a lot more time i imagine
but you can continue
it's so lovely i love it so much please
do a second stream i don't know if
does anyone know like can anyone like
guess how much longer it would take to
do this part two
is it enough content
time-wise for part two
[Music]
i didn't expect until i thought this
would be a one-off
[Music]
anyone who played the game who can say
lots of content yes easily freehouse
[Music]
okay but not today because i i i want to
read super chats and then yeah you know
i've been trying to not uh stream past
midnight and now it's almost uh 9 p.m
and i gotta read super jets
it was so cute
[Music]
oh my god
i love it i'm so adorable
pat i love you
i love you pat
[Music]
okay
okay then let's move to my office and
i'll be reading super chat
yeah this game is also kind of taxing on
the voice
so i gotta consider that too also i have
tummy ink now
tommy hort
tommy hoyt
oh big big oh big tummy horn
[Music]
yeah
well we're gonna read super chats
i'm not gonna die
[Music]
ah maybe banana needs to come out just
kidding
no no
um let's go
office
[Music]
oh my god
oh the music is perfect i leave the
music
chat
i'll leave the music on if you guys
don't mind they're jazzy oh [\h__\h] you see
something
[Music]
the numbers what do the numbers mean
mason
what do the numbers mean i'm in my
uniform today by the way no particular
reason why i just felt like
yeah
i don't wear it that often
i don't wear that often so i feel like
you know sometimes why not
and birthday birthday for bails
not birthday
[Music]
wish
reading super chats supercars supercars
that's actually a term it wasn't it
wasn't that a term
okay
og is good yeah wearing it for the first
time in a while feels feels nice
still fits just like back in the days
yeah i didn't gain any weight
okay
where do i have to start reading super
chats
i'm not that far behind i think last
stream man being mario kart yeah i
didn't read the mario kart super chat so
mario kart and the ones from today i
think
[Music]
oh and overcat too oh right
oh i guess that's true
okay
no problem
oh and then
i said the members only once uh i read
those privately
so
[Music]
this one oh [\h__\h] i forgot i said oh damn
ah damn it i'll forget again can i do
something really quickly because
otherwise i'll forget again
i was supposed to send over cat the
names of of all the participants and
winners at like the one the
pre-selection
i forgot that
sorry
awful cool
[Music]
apple i've saved them all with names so
let me just do that really quickly okay
[Music]
i'm a cat there we go
okay
i'm in a category
and seven
colors symphony
already mccry
bryant brr ryan
got german oh wait i could just take a
screenshot
[Music]
i'll just take a screenshot that's
faster
[Music]
and the winner was
this one
[Music]
red circle in the winner
okay easy peasy technology
oh sure
and then
there we go
uh
that one was
grub numps but i forgot which outfit the
ah no this one this one the one that
kelly liked so much
[Music]
cowling category
thank you guys for watching by the way
thank you if you're leaving then thank
you thank you thank you for coming by
wasn't that an adorable game holy [\h__\h]
what a genius game
[Music]
i want to tell the person
the people who made the game
the developers i want to tell them how
much i loved it
[Music]
do they have a twitter i
wonder i need to tell them
it's like when i go to a restaurant and
the food was so amazingly good that i
tell the waiter
i need to tell them yeah the writing and
the art style the animations
oh wait i think i know what the truth
the trending is an animation right cause
like i um i read that there's like a
animation or animation or something at
the ending
[Music]
uh i guess you only get to see that if
you do all all all of the npcs
they retweeted the stream what
i wonder if they're watching
[Music]
they did
then i'll tell them i'll tweet them
[Music]
oh my god
because i love companies like that who
are so interactive they like notice when
people are streaming their game
they were told you loved the game what
by whom
home
[Music]
an adorable funny story yeah
man
alligators are now one of my favorite
animals
time to go to florida and and check him
out in reality
[Music]
now can't be dangerous can it
you saw one of the deaths in the chat
and being what
[Music]
did they have like the studio name in
their account
omg
okay i'll take a look after the stream
thank you for telling me i didn't
realize that
no don't do that hey i wanna meet ellen
but maybe i should go to new york city
to meet pat
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know when there was these ones
oops
[Music]
oh well
um
okay and keep one category
[Music]
oh they said this is amazing really at
what time at what point of the game
like midway through or or at the end or
in the beginning or when
tell me the exact timestamp i know you
can't
i guess that's difficult to say
[Music]
it was near the start oh
three hours ago
okay
[Music]
i have to i will have to write a
strongly worded letter about how much i
love the game
[Laughter]
i'm like i'm like i don't know i feel
weirdly really like in love about it
okay i'm done with my homework i'll read
super chats now of the omo cat
um stream
[Music]
it looked like the submissions were
closed shirts confused or chased you oh
my god no i still i'm also wearing i'm
also wearing uh
totally underneath this uniform i'm
wearing um my i have a second
uh
pixel t-shirt a kia t-shirt because i
actually i realized i was wearing m size
i ordered that one for my friend but now
i'm wearing s size that one is for me
yeah
nice fit
dark joseph thank you
oh no i have fallen into the fryer and
became a bucket
but a clumsy chimkey and turning your
membership is probably one of the best
decisions i've ever made
[Music]
thank you for an amazing year and i look
forward to having more fun in this
lovely family thank you you made me feel
so wholesome everything feels so
wholesome right now
i'm actually kind of scared to um
end the stream today something really
scary is waiting for me after the stream
i can't talk about it but i have a
really bad feeling
i kind of want to continue being in this
bubble for forever
[Music]
i'm scared
i'm scared i don't wanna i don't wanna
end the stream let's just read super
chats forever endless tangent thing
let's go
[Music]
good luck whatever it is thank you i
hope for the best
is everything okay we will see probably
not i'm not sure
i'm scared
you need to clean the dishes
no it's more serious than that the cat
is getting out of this
no
it's not no no it's like actually scary
but anyway
ah see us paulie thank you for the red
super chat attention i bought the ticket
of food fest from spawn i can't wait to
watch your first 3d concert oh my god
it's so soon it's great at home even
home idea first gen can attend hope i
can be there with you next year thank
you
it is indeed very very great it's so
nice that we're being included this year
and
first time for whole live english first
time for whole life indonesia
i i bet that they're like really really
over the moon about it too they've been
around longer than whole live english so
they really deserve it too
um
[Music]
but i think
um
i'm going to say this as part of her
life english i feel like we deserve it
with um
i think we brought a big big audience
two whole life as well
i mean they already built a huge
foundation but i think we did our part
as well and uh
i feel like being represented in such a
huge event is um
we deserve it so
i'll say that with all my confidence
thank you sis pauline
and skye
rainbow gazelle duncan oh what's this
really a teacher guy in the memory
stream yes i am an assistant english
teacher oh i'm legit wearing a jacket
and a badge to my lessons thank you oh
yeah i remember there was someone where
i was like is that person really a
teacher ah so you were not just posing
thank you russell oh dangos
[Music]
we don't deserve it right yeah you guys
are crazy
[Music]
what's the case being english teachers
yeah right
oh i i think i understand because i am
so bad at english english teachers are
being like
like um anger together
by my stream
uh
sucked
into my stream
maybe because english teachers have a
bigger
toleration level
a higher toleration level for people who
are stupid and can't speak english well
like me
so they they tolerate it more
and that's why they all come to me
maybe they're hoping for some kind of
to see some kind of evolution
no thank you snake logan
i was an english tutor for a bit no no
hold on
learn english cancer this will happen to
you i'm joking
[Music]
it's fine
speak better english than ninety percent
of americans oh come on
[\h__\h]
anthony
[Music]
call me sick because i'm positive i have
the omo cat variant
[Music]
i'm a bit confused i guess it's a joke
on the c thing
that omocat is
a virus
because she's so
i don't know
why is she a virus
she's so
um
[Music]
oh
oh because it sounds like oh
[Music]
it doesn't sound like that
oh but okay okay
contagious maybe she's contagious
[Music]
infectiously cute that's a good way to
describe it
drink from the nails eel
it's a bit of a stretch yeah i think so
too
thank you
[Music]
thanks for sharing my remix ah i feel
like your voice fits well in this genre
and hope to hope to hear more originals
in the style in the future also i'm
curious as to how to find how how to how
you found my song
i forgot i don't know how how did i find
it
[Music]
i think maybe i should saw it on twitter
because i posted it in the chat right at
the end of the stream right
[Music]
i feel like i might have just seen it on
twitter
or on youtube i don't know i'm not sure
anymore
i forgot i don't remember anything
but it was great i enjoyed it please
make more
channels
thank you so much for reviewing my photo
goofy as it was it was such a fun
project to work on by the way who took
the photo
so many fans came out to show their best
for you cali and um also had to rebrand
canes to chiara's as loyal kfp
[Music]
eve
canes oh is that the fast food uh
stuff that you used in the picture
that's what they've been saying it's a
fast food chain that i've never heard
about before even if it's kelly's
favorite chicken oh
is her favorite fast food uh
brand
restaurant is it her favorite did she
say that before
damn i have to check it out when i go to
america
[Music]
is it in what in texas only it's a texas
thing
you're saying i gotta go to texas to eat
cain's
i wasn't planning on going to taxes man
it is only in texas or is it just
popular in texas howdy
[Music]
it's in california too all right
all right i'll go there
they've expanded to california man they
must be doing well but not as well as
kfp we've expanded all over the world
even into the interwebs
minecraft has a kfp several ones
i see
i see ohio i mean i've heard of ohio but
i have no idea where to place it on the
map
it's all over south of midway i say
i say it interesting
i like your accent thank you does it
sound like i'm a texas man
yeah
thank you scissor
a fallout game stream oh i don't know
no no plans currently
casual gaming
thank you for the right super
[Music]
did you get some drip too
did you get some of the omo cat merch i
hope so
jim tracy dagger
stop
these ones are done mario kart is next
[Music]
no rage challenge which i totally
nails oh wait i was gonna put it here
i totally nailed that challenge didn't i
man i'm so amazing i nailed everything
[Laughter]
kakundan
[Music]
you're welcome
and you were the one in the bucket
yeah right oh you were where to buy the
skirt it's um brandon and the gift from
my mom pushing me to wear more grills oh
interesting well i feel like it really
looks good on you but you should wear
the kind of fashion that you like i
guess
but trust your mom
she has good taste wait what the [\h__\h]
your mom wanted you to wear that skirt
and gave it to you
[Music]
your mom i like your mom's fashion sense
jenkins monkeys
keep playing
languages
korean name
i want to do another korean duolingo
stream
but i still didn't get time to learn the
the the
writing
so i got i was i was thinking of doing
that first before doing another korean
duolingo stream
[Music]
i'll try to learn it asap
i feel like if i just schedule or do a
lingo stream
then i'll be forced
to learn it before that so that could be
uh helpful
hi
friends
i really like it i feel like we can
totally use that once um once we're on
vacation and need a thumbnail for one of
our streams because i'm planning to
stream if we if we were able to
[Music]
what is mama told his fashion style uh
i don't think she has a fashion style
it's just
normal
really normal
normal not girly um
yeah
oh i have fans
ah
[Music]
yeah this week it's kind of like a bunch
of short streams and so on relatively
short i hope that's okay for you guys i
kinda wanna
first of all i i i for the yesterday for
example
i had something to do
[Music]
you know sometimes you gotta live real
life too right
i do it very rarely
and on tuesday i had something to do and
um tomorrow i'm preparing for whole talk
one day i prepared for it oh my god yeah
yeah tuesday after homocat that was that
appointment and so on so yeah kind of
busy this week i think next week we'll
ah
[Music]
now my next week
next week there is gonna be two days off
as well i think
um but then after that we should go
relatively back to normal
[Music]
back to normal as in streaming
long time skin
but also um not not only me being busy i
also i'm trying to
um
how to stay preemptively
uh
protect my throat and my mental health
by giving myself a bit more time right
now because also i've noticed you know
the winter time
not not only my throat but also mentally
kind of like
um
[Music]
being kind of
difficult for me
but spring is coming
and uh
yeah just i just i just wanna yeah um be
careful so that i don't suddenly have to
say yo i'm out for one month see you
later alligator
[Music]
yeah winter depression
it's it's doing a thing
i took the vitamin i bought the vitamin
d i didn't take it yet oopsie
[Music]
gotta take care of myself so you guys
you guys do that too please take care of
yourselves okay
nice title trap
she said the thing
[Music]
that means allergy season i supposedly
have no allergens
but yeah i feel very sorry for all the
people who have like pollen allergies
for example
that's really tough man
did the tea actually work uh i mean i
don't know it feels pretty like pretty
much the same as normal tea
i don't know it just tastes
not less less good
but maybe it's a long-term effect or an
effect that i just don't notice that
well
[Music]
i feel like the t might have been a
little bit of a scam
or like a personal bias that the that
the doctor had but i don't know i'll try
it more often
but recently i haven't had so many long
streams anyway so it hasn't been that
much of a problem as long as i keep my
shorts
my shorts my stream's fairly short
uh i'm fine my voice is fine
[Music]
as long as i keep my shorts short as
well huh
online seems to align with it yeah i'm
sure it's a great tea
but yeah
[Music]
i usually take peppermint fruit tea yeah
i don't like peppermint very much
does it taste like peppermint
[Music]
streamed nine hours three days ago i'll
wear every once in a while you know
doc joseph thank you for the red super
chat look at that tasty thirty percent
youtube i love my attention please let
her start his stream
yeah youtube making that money cutting
cutting cutting
totally deserved
30 was it 30
yeah
honestly that's a little bit much in my
opinion but hi youtuber you do what you
gotta do youtube
[Music]
thank you doug joseph well youtube
thanks you too
oh beautiful beautiful love that emote
combination
i don't know what it is about it but i
just like it so much
alright so free thank you for the thank
you
hi daniel maybe it was stressful work
but recently i found myself looking for
asmr videos to help with sleep if one
day tends to get the chance to use an
asmr mic you would whisper this for me
you little [\h__\h] after the usual room you
go
i mean the microphone i have now is not
an asmr microphone but i can try it
[Music]
your little [\h__\h]
off to the usual room you go
over it
your little [\h__\h]
off to the usual room you go
how's that
maybe maybe someone who can work with
sound programs can kind of make it input
into asmr
i know you can kind of like make
something what is it called like a d
sound
something like that
[Music]
sorry i took away a bunch of them again
um
but but but but you know
i kind of suspected that it wouldn't be
possible because they were like
pretty much like
um
taken from the game
so we're gonna make like a an original
version with different poses and
different phrases
because i thought it was actually like
even if it's different phrases i feel
like you guys made such big
great use out of it
um
and it was so funny they look so cute
[Music]
so
we're going to make something similar
[Music]
that might actually be even better you
think so
all right
shouldn't take too long the artist is
very very fast
thank you
[Music]
account name thank you for the rest of
the chat
hi daniel it's been hard for me to
balance the sleeping schedule and your
streams oh i'm sorry but but
but wait you're in japanese uh
[Music]
wait so happy you scheduled a stream
from 10 15 that's gonna end before my
bedtime ten three
[Music]
okay so you are in japanese time zone
right now right okay okay okay
well yeah this week i feel like a lot of
my streams started early
especially the omo cat one so this week
should have been fine though or
something looking forward to the horror
game stream maybe owl only
oh
yeah i haven't really put much thought
into which game yet i could i guess
continue outlast or i could play like a
different one a shorter maybe like a
one-off
uh horror game i'm not sure
i still have a lot of time to think
about it so i'll take my sweet time
and thank you moto sam i'm sorry about
the shitty time zones really like i wish
i wish i could just
uh
have a good time for everyone obviously
but thank you for still trying to be
there it means a lot to me thank you
[Music]
baby little no dangerous and happy
birthday related but still happy
birthday
patrick and reggie
[Music]
it's a mixed english and and korean
super chat
[Music]
it's your birthday
today
oh you translated
[Music]
wait you literally translated everything
yourself anyway okay okay that's a
direct translation okay i get it
can you tell me the manager's shout of
rage as a gift after that a scream of
horror
oh didn't you get that during mario kart
you were asking for me to
rage as a birthday present well i did i
did rage at the end so i guess you wish
uh yeah i guess i just did that
for the sake of you for your birthday i
didn't rage because
because of of uh the raccoon no no no
i just wanted to make this person's
birthday wish come true
am i not super considerate i'm so nice
right
[Music]
thank you for your support also you also
always here even though
it's it must be like really really
really late over there thank you for
your effort and your determination to be
here
um as there is excel for thanks
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh vito you use that as an excuse cause
i
i used an excuse all right
oh happy birthday your birthday was on
march 1st oh
thank you
will also congratulate me and gift i
hope you play a horror game i can look
forward to it right what usual room
i think i'm
also i don't know i'm not sure like i
don't i don't want to play ring fit that
much because of you know why
just makes me feel uncomfortable because
other people make it into something it's
not um
and then horror games you know i hate
horror games so much
i just want to have fun when playing
games
this makes no sense to me why would you
play a horror game when you could play a
fun game like this one today
later alligator
but yeah
[Music]
we'll see rufus
and randall and duncan motor accounting
thank you
yamano
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
your red roses what do you mean you're
your shell
big swing thank you
g r g s punk thank you
very much
[Music]
trying to change your everyday speech
patterns is really tough yeah i think
this stream is shaving years of our
intentions in mortal life
it was very difficult to control myself
indeed
[Music]
that's a weird number you chose ah
of course it has a meaning between the
beginning of the second race and the
third strike where the rule set was
active 46 minutes and 29 seconds have
passed which is
2789 seconds it was a good try but i'll
keep watching you whether you swear or
not
thank you i'm happy to hear that
yeah i suppose everyone who is here now
doesn't mind obviously
yeah i am but i've read people say
before that they don't like my swearing
so
yeah
but i can't i can't completely like turn
it off completely so that's that i guess
you guys just watch someone else then
and we're happy in our little circle
thank you tiny delta
for accepting me the way i am
foreign
is cute
i don't know about it being cute but
thank you glad you think so
never turn it off okay
[Music]
i like to come up with uh things that
you can actually use so pantsu would be
that but i don't want to copy someone
else's merchandise
maybe a bra
maybe a broth or kfp
nah
but i i
already have at least one idea i'm still
like
thinking about what the other item for
my birthday should be
members will know what i'm talking about
like about one item but
so we need to make some other choices
anyway now we're reading the super chats
from this one later alligator the best
game ever created in this whole wide
world
better than eldon ring just kidding
i mean i mean it's a different category
you can't really compare but this one
made me happier than elven ring i'll
give you that
i need some new undergarments so that
would be lovely oh my god
well i'll find something interesting
useful
yeah thank you thank you dakuma for
drawing that art beforehand so i could
use it for thumbnail
um
so cute i didn't know before that that
was like pat but now i know it makes me
love it even more pets in our uniform oh
my god
oh my god oh my god
yeah we have a prayer and slippers
hmm
oh a tie could even work but not
everyone uses a tie against
well
don't worry about it
i i have a lot of ideas i did
brainstorming before i'm just not sure
what to go with
can i join gouda
she always streams at like 2 a.m for me
so
i highly doubt it
unless she starts early for me
[Music]
um
yeah
congratulations
[Music]
it sounds she's so angry what i talk
normally no [\h__\h] way now i sound
angry
you're not telling me that when i was
just speaking in german i sounded angry
to you that's [\h__\h] i'm angry now
i was saying wholesome things okay
in a wholesome calm voice
[Music]
how about line down javelin duncan
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
boss lady i would like to file a
complaint to the cr department what is
the sarah department you mean hr
one of the chickens slashed my tires as
a result i was unable to make my
deliveries can you please hold them
accountable
furthermore kfp employee not applicable
yes that is the actual username i know
has driven me into a river and stuck a
knife where the key goes can you please
reprimand them harshly can i watch
you guys
get a hotel room
i'm taking the resources
that makes so much sense i'll never use
hr ever again
anyway you guys get a hotel room
whoa seven two three targeting
and then have a death match there i
guess
[Laughter]
and the beginner's guide to ellen ring
oh
yeah i might check that out
petra 10 dash and pun pony clitty and
thank you for one two three four red
super chat the [\h__\h]
are you good
hey dancer today is my birthday oh once
i shared with my mother until her
passing last july oh no wait what you
had the same birthday
want to let you know how you have
influenced my life and how deeply i
appreciate it my mother was a teacher
whose work was complicated by the virus
despite 100 plus hours long work weeks
oh holy [\h__\h] she still made time to
watch each of you lord of the rings and
hobbit watch alongs with me all
and those were among the most relaxed
and happiest moments of 20 20 21. what
the [\h__\h] i can't help but be grateful
for those narrow replaceable memories oh
man
did you see it coming was she like sick
or so
were you able to prepare for it or did
it just suddenly happen
for me although you may not wish to know
exactly how you inspired my successfully
delivered master's faces wow
[Music]
why why do i not want to know how i want
to know how
and i and did you give me an answer
are you here right now
[Music]
complete accent what
what the [\h__\h] i'm so sorry
[Music]
you have also consistently been a source
of joy comfort and normalcy even though
i can't watch streams as often as i used
to or would like thank you so much
attention for all you do and please
never doubt the value of what you're
doing even even if it may not be obvious
[Music]
take care of yourself but know that so
long as this is where you choose to be i
will be cheering you on
i wanna give you a hug
i'm so sorry you lost her
it sounds like you had a great
relationship with her that i mean
watching streams together with her
that's
sounds like sounds like you were really
close
i'm sorry that that happened
both you and your mom don't deserve that
but
yeah
oh man please take time to heal
and oh my gosh you oh wait the [\h__\h]
you must be thinking over today if you
shared a birthday
hmm
maybe this one will be sad but i hope
that
the coming birthdays you will celebrate
not only your life but your mom's life
as well
as she can't anymore but you'll
celebrate it
for the both of you okay
every year
celebrated for the both of you
[Music]
okay
i don't know if i want to sing i'll be
birthday do you want me to sing happy
birthday for you
i'll sing happy birthday if that makes
you happy
[Music]
wanna tell me the name of your mom
i'll sing for her too
tell me the name of your mom
or nickname
no thank you really you don't want a
birthday song
all right now i feel like i'm making you
sad too i don't want to make you sad
[Music]
ah i'm sorry
i want to make you sad i should sing
[Music]
i'll think
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear pony clitty and i
probably pronounce it wrong
happy birthday to you
i wish you all the best and i hope that
you can enjoy many many many many more
moments together with me and my streams
[Music]
eat some
really yummy cake
and thank you thank you for being
part of kfp
hmm
thank you so much
thank you so much for your support
you amazing
we love you
thank you
[Music]
here
and i hope you'll feel hugged
by all of us big chicken hug
big chimken hug
[Music]
making your baking spirit girl nice it's
good to hear
spicy chocolate cookies
eh does it really need to be spicy the
[\h__\h]
yeah
uh so much love
so much love here
no
i forgot to put the ptm back on there
you go
i'm so hungry
and thank you thank you for the resume
thank you
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] i feel like i heard that
before somewhere sounds crazy alligators
despite being reptiles are actually more
closely related to birds and other
reptiles
that's so weird what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
tom tornadoes i can't give that to them
that's a weird request to make
how can i give it to them
i can't
[Music]
raka dear sanja thank you for the pinky
cannon let's say that bae appears in
your living room and flips some magical
cut it's it's one of those
what if super chats again
if the coin lands on tails you and fauna
will swap cats for the day if it's heads
bubba and mickey will live with you and
the cats for two days which would you
prefer oh my god um
i don't know what would happen if bubba
and mickey
would be with my cats i feel like i feel
like
[Music]
at least one of my cats chunkers would
be freaked out
no she's never been so close to the dock
before don't yo
so i prefer to swap swap cats or if
possible
uh not swap cats but swap apartments
like i live in florence place she lives
in line for a day
and then we can just take care of each
other's cats for a day babysit cat sit
that works that works
[Music]
that would work out i think
and i don't want to meet from those cats
[Music]
oh
i'm not sure if it was appropriate oh i
feel like he would have been
fascinated if he used service service
although i'm not sure if he
maybe i wonder if there's any germans
who would not know the meaning of
service
i thought generally they would know
what it means
so your professor should probably
understand it too
you can flex your
your dialect you should do it
flex your dialect yo
[Music]
jacob thank you soon
because they use it in bavaria too i
guess the game agreed thank you and
patrick
foreign
[Music]
it's banned in the uk considering birds
need a license to watch tv i don't know
we should take their opinions to use a
license
maybe it's just something similar that
we have here too um
we don't need a license but we have to
pay like if you there's like this this
like thing called gis
if you have a
even if you it's for tv and radio so if
you have a tv at home even if you don't
connect it to actual tv just because
it's possible to play tv
uh you kind of
need to pay yeah kind of like a tax
um
but the thing is like if they come to
your door
sometimes they come to your door and
they're like yo you haven't been paying
the gis yet
so pay up you could say like i don't
have a tv even if you have one have one
in your apartment and they um
they are then gonna
i've i've
i've i've had something similar like
this happened years ago um but you know
they're really intimidating especially
if you live alone as a little girl
somewhere
and they show up at your door like that
but um yeah then they're gonna be like
you
may i enter then to check and you gotta
say no because you have the right to say
no
they they don't have a right to enter
and but they'll be like okay i'll come
back
eventually
next time
and that that time um i'm gonna enter
apparently the next time they're gonna
have um permission that actually
happened to me um years ago and and they
never came back actually or i just
missed them whenever they did come back
thankfully but i was living in fear ever
since that day
if i actually have a tv or not i will
not state here um
i will say i definitely was not watching
tv
uh
so
yes
but now now i do pay it because um
i don't wanna i don't wanna
be bothered with
them annoying the heck out of me
it's so stupid like i don't like the
reasoning like you you have to pay it if
you even if you even
if you even if you only use your tv to
play with your switch
you still have to okay
i'm paying them don't worry about it
don't worry about it
[Music]
it's like for uh for the like a big tv
um station
in austria
no no i'm paying all my taxes shut up
[Music]
oh
oh senpai
i don't have to add senpai to her name
the [\h__\h]
oh she's telling me to you'll be still
oh not your mistake but i guess i can
say chan
[Music]
senpai
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
okay she's telling me to
this is really intimate like not adding
anything at the end is really intimate
so
you
[Laughter]
oh
she's asking me i don't think she knows
i'm streaming
she's asking me if elden ring was fun
um
[Music]
ring was painful but it's a beautiful
game so i want to try again
[Music]
we're planning a collab
tell her chad says hi
no no no no then she thinks that she um
disturbed me i don't want her to think
that i'm considerate
[Music]
i'm just chit-chatting now
no i don't think anyone in homeland
japan
ever told me to yobested
them
to not say to not give them a honorific
uh
ending thingy
with nagaji it's just like everyone
calls her an energy kind of so i
[Music]
got it
she says looking forward to a talk i'm
like what no [\h__\h] talk i'm gonna
watch it take it
nineteen is also not quite you'll be sad
it's more like saying nina jung but it's
just like a
cute nickname
um
but it just feels so natural
to say an energy
[Music]
is it kind of strange to sit through
your step but still [\h__\h] kegel i
guess so yeah but i i still i did it
purposefully
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
i told you now because it's dangerous
it's a dangerous game we're playing here
[Music]
yummy
maybe she should read my super chats
[Music]
she called me a vodka
she told me to reply to her afterwards
but how can i when i see a reply from
her i need to immediately answer her
[Music]
mata
foreign
[Music]
yo
but she said she said that she was
watching a little bit from the stream
actually actually so i told her if
there's a japanese version she should
play it
is there a japanese version
should play and it's so fun
okay
i'm gonna do my job now uh where was i
where is that i ayah looking for the top
dungeon the game would create darkest
and mao mao that isn't for the pinky
i don't think it's localized oh no
really is there only english
[Music]
can you see that on steam
i can't see it here
[Music]
maybe she's looking at the chat now
maybe
emmanuel schneider thank you for the
double red super chat
first paycheck came in oh
from a new job running bills are paid
and accounted for so here's to you for
getting me through my last year of
university ah
and a stressful job on wow you ended
university
and now you have job noise welcome to
the working world woohoo
you are absolutely amazing and deserve
the world thank you
thank you congratulations on i suppose
you you didn't cancel it but like
actually end it like successfully
congratulations
and uh
good luck in your new job
yay
first month done huh
i hope that it's a job where you feel
comfy
and happy
if it's your first first proper job then
yeah i think there's a lot of things to
get used to um
yeah jumping from university to
real job life might be a bit tough and
stressful but do your best fighter
fighter
but don't forget about kfp does this
mean that you're gonna be busy now
hopefully not too busy
[Music]
first month nine to five crazy difficult
yeah i think it really depends on the
job but yeah if it's a tough job then
i'm glad i don't have to work a normal
job anymore
thank you madame schneider i hope you
have nice colleagues too
that's really important yeah try to make
friends
i wish you the best donkey
like freaking talkation to go
astonishing for the pinky i would love
to see an mtg stream i have been playing
for years and it's a lot of fun also
depending on how old your cards are oh
this is the answer to my question they
could be worth a lot most expensive card
is black lotus can be worth over thirty
thousand dollars
i feel like my mom might have mentioned
before that she doesn't have
cards anymore
oh we should have kept them mama are you
watching
hastu
no magic content
manchester united feel engagement
i told her
[Music]
damn
thing is so valuable why they don't they
don't print them anymore
[Music]
that's weird though that then you're
still allowed to use it even though they
don't print it anymore
[Music]
i think i free one out 20 years ago oh
that must hurt so much now oh [\h__\h]
well back then you don't imagine that it
would be someday that expensive right
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
not old cuts they are no longer printed
alpha set black clothes only a specific
one uh-huh
you're not allowed to use
in standard ah okay
reserve list and band limited and so
forth oh okay
because it was so appealing ah well then
why would you want it if you can't use
it just to flex i guess
i guess
[Music]
ssr even when it was printed
only alpha which was the very first set
printed in 1993. oh
not a whole doll
thank you sticker wits for the answer
very interesting
thank you mental jetty donkey and
valkyrie
[Music]
oh
apparently
all the cards are with my brother
my my brother could use some money too i
think
is he not aware that they could be worth
some good money
[Music]
she won dragon
oh
that's a good price
apparently we have a bunch of shivan
dragons
which go for like
actually no there's some ah it depends i
guess there's some special ones
[Music]
ah
i only get a good price if if they're
unused also
[Music]
yeah apparently we might have some good
coins
[Music]
you probably have new copies oh i don't
know about that we played that years ago
centuries ago
yeah
it could be pretty old
it's funny how you guys even know what
i'm talking about there must be a lot of
x magic players in here noise
and jim tracy dankeshen alexander
kundan
brandon i am a team
tom tornado's duncan cruz duncan
damn
wait i refreshed oh crosstalk
they gave me free dungeon yet another
wonderful stream here it was a perfect
choice of game absolutely adorable thank
you yeah i should have played this
earlier man i kind of like kept it for
one day but yo
ah what a beautiful game i love it
if you had to pick between going to
pat's birthday party and going to on a
date with quesada from tales of our eyes
what would you pick
[Music]
[Applause]
i will act as if i have not read this
super chat yet
giant mod damaging for the pinky
dear denzel this game is cute but i
don't think i'd enjoy it as much as
watching you play you make it look so
much fun it is so much fun
it is believe me not just because of me
you're getting like confused here
it's not just the illusion of fun it's
real
[Music]
thank you
yes so cute silly fellow thank you
your sister
[Music]
[Laughter]
man your sister must thank you cringe
just kidding but like i feel like
between sister and brother
or sister and sister like siblings
that's the word
uh i feel like if you make your sibling
do something like that they probably
thank you cringe
[Music]
my brother probably thinks what i do is
cringe
i mean no no
he's actually really
sweet and supportive now maybe maybe in
the past maybe when we were both younger
he probably thought it was a little bit
cringe what i was doing back then my
sisters always think their brother's
cringe
and i think the other way around too
ewwah
[Music]
was definitely not me that sounds like a
lie but it could also be true i'm not
sure
until dawn
[Music]
uh-huh
interactive survival horror
horror games are boring
[Music]
my fortune donation for the pinky
sending this in advance since i probably
will miss elden ring on sunday saturday
oh my first missed kiana stream what
[Music]
what is so important that this will
break your streak holy [\h__\h]
i mean i totally understand but
if until now there was nothing that was
breaking your strength before
i really wonder
what's happening this sunday in your
life
[Laughter]
we're okay [\h__\h] work this is your job
yeah i'm surprised work didn't get into
the way of my streams until now
damn
what they're [\h__\h] breaking you
straight you should get like um
compensation money from them to you ow
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
like that streak man it could go into
the
guinness world records book
the [\h__\h] sue them yeah sue them
you know what will act as if it's not
you get one one joker
to keep your streak this will be this
will be it
i will still
act as if you never broke your streak
because that's [\h__\h] incredible
missing one stream is acceptable
i'll give you this one
and maybe maybe who knows maybe until
sunday magically
uh
magically
your workplace or the people there will
disappear and and you'll be able to
watch my stream
with no issues at all
[Music]
maybe
maybe wouldn't that be nice
[Laughter]
my first vlog
my first missed cat stream but will view
the vlog when i can hope you have fun
and hope the souls fans can control
themselves and not annoy you like they
do every streamer oh that reminds me of
something i wanted to ask the creator of
hyper chat um
creator of hyper chat are you in any way
able to do the following
get me a filter
that
only in the hyper chat window
not on stream because i mean here in obs
i use the url so it shouldn't change
there i suppose but on the hyperchat
window
without actually turning on members only
chat
maybe i could get a filter for members
only
and then hope that the members will not
be vaccinating i'm thinking like maybe
that could be a good filter
for um
all the
vaccineers
but but but don't put it so that they
see it
make them think that they are visible to
me
[Music]
make them think that they're visible
make them spam rolled stop rolling stop
rolling as much as they want
but
i on my chat
i mean i'm sorry for it for the
non-members but at least for eldering
for the non-members who have good
intentions i'm sorry
but yeah i need to i need a backseat
filter
i want backstage i believe you but i
don't know how else i guess i could um
i guess i guess i could also have an ng
word
yeah
uh maybe just for
maybe for elden ring i should just ban
the word um
rolling and roll i guess
[Laughter]
yeah i mean there's there's not members
with good intentions
especially the ones who are here right
now
nah
i don't want to hurt them
it's not fair
roll shut up
shut up
rolling rolling rolling around and
rolling rolling
[Music]
yeah that was the most annoying thing oh
i think i'll ban that
[Laughter]
okay don't worry about it hyper chat
karina you don't have to do that um
we'll find a different way we'll find
another way to
uh dodge the back seaters
[Music]
no no no no no
what about butter drills with a dash of
cinnamon
mama mia
did you try rolling for the backseat
comments you mean dodging them
you just need to dodge at the right time
man you idiotica
[Music]
yeah
the thing is like people say just don't
look at it but i'm a streamer i'm like
supposed to entertain an audience and i
i'm used to looking at the chat
very used to it and also like at the
same time i was looking for advice i
wanted like helpful advice
but yeah
like like
it's just not easy to
completely stop a habit you know yeah
so
all the other advice besides stop
rolling would be nice
[Music]
but i heard that good as chat was also
even worse
man that's tough
um
[Music]
do come up with kfb
i'm not sure if i'm allowed to do that
um like guideline wise i don't know
[Music]
oh no
but but maybe she's better at ignoring
it than i am
i'm so used to like back sitting i i
really normally i am
really welcome it with open arms
but the fact that for the first time
ever i got annoyed by it really means a
lot
[Music]
um
tom tonight is done soon and drowsy cat
comes and needs
soon
[Music]
oh she did get heated oh no
oh no
um
15 years wow decks worth thousands of
dollars
are you not going to sell it
[Music]
on
m
[Music]
um
m
sorry i want to talk a little bit about
um
mental health
uh for this specific person
um because i know that in japan it's uh
kind of
perceived differently and treated
differently
yeah
anyway
[Applause]
[Music]
um
yeah i said it's okay to
to first of all
accept that if you have depression that
you have depression
accept it don't don't don't act as if it
doesn't exist and or blame yourself or
anything like that anyway i don't wanna
i don't wanna talk too much about it
anymore i don't wanna make you feel
uncomfortable mistress thank you and
skydivers and eden excellent i am the
lord everybody no
but no is my name duncan
mr has been extended and game eight nine
one zero duncan i'm on the road really
oh oh wait you're making a joke haha
[Music]
harmony can i have a new unique phrase
what to say when i see off the kfb
chickens i can't say real safe anymore
now oh it was just before that one
stream i'll undo it
afterwards don't worry about it
[Music]
funny
i was thinking about you when i read
that
i know that hey again your friendly city
got here just wanted to say thank you
for this amazing stream you're the best
don't thank you for your guidance
all right we're done with the super
chats
i'm gonna um take care of myself food
wise now tomorrow is my day off because
it's friday right yeah it's gonna be
friday i'm gonna prepare hotel questions
and so on oh
wait i need to translate the name
[Music]
futile
and oh no it's the scary thing but
pray for me guys that's nothing too big
[Music]
for
okay
oh my god lord edward
oh i did write her she liked the idea
she liked the idea um she did she didn't
and james thanks for thank you for the
rest of my chat
love you guys too
thank you for coming by
the scary draw
something like that yeah i don't know
what's inside but i know it's scary
thank you
thank you lena roo
[Music]
okay okay that was a fun stream i love
the game i gotta tell the peeps that i
love it
thank you so much everybody for watching
that was a lovely game not many not much
time for me to talk about
um
you know things besides the game but i
was really i was really into it it was
so cute so
sometimes i think this is fine too not
that i really had much to talk about
anyway
okay and in germany we say i'll beat us
in and good good enough good enough good
enough
[Music]
everybody good night sleep well sweet
dreams
[Applause]
you guys need to watch the archive if
you came later on because that was
amazing that was amazing
i'm still on like cloud nine
what's up
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you