[Music]
DET
H
[Music]
DET
OG
[Music]
DET
OG
[Music]
Oh
Ok
oh oh, is everyone here? Let's get together.
Ah, gathering, yes, gathering, ah, gathering, gathering, collection, collection, collection, where, hahahaha,
Ah, Manekata, teacher, yes, teacher,
no, teacher, but not at all.
Sensei, please take attendance.Okay, I
'll go.Okay, I'll go first from the white team.  Ta-
san
wa
[Music]
Hamui-chan yes yes yes yes moomey Cha yes
yes yes nanai tome you Kaikai Miame Chanameame-chan
Yay, I'm going, okay, yeah, gogo,
gosh,
Eko's members are asleep on the phone, A  It's
people, yes, yes, B is heaven,
Choco-sensei,
oh,
yay.  I'll do my best
[Music]
Zuarigo Um, is it okay to go here too
? Should I go
? I think it's better to go. Ka-senpai is here. Yes, that day. It
's Raden-chan, but I'm a little behind.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.The
second one, my junior, Goza, is sorry.I
thought you were coming to apologize, so I did it the other
day.I was
nervous about doing something unusual.  Yes, that's true,
but we'd like to cover Raden-chan's writing as well,
so
please take care of it, but it seems like it's
gone. Well,
Raden-chan appears in Holomen Hunting,
but that's about it.  I'm
going to take your place as a hunter, and I'm not going to tell you
what will happen in the battle yet.I'm
looking forward to when you'll be wandering around alone,
or if someone will come.  I
don't know why, but I want to see you working hard by yourself. Maybe you're filming everyone by yourself. Do your best, hit me, hit me. There
's a spy here.
What's the truth here?
There's a matsuri senior who's acting like a spy.
There's a spy. He's leaving. He's
in the waiting room for the white team. It's a classroom.
Everyone is waiting here. Hey, hey, come on. I'm looking forward to the
competition, right?  I'm here. I'm
curious, but it doesn't seem like everyone is here.
It's good, it's good, it's good. It's good, everyone is here. Oh yeah, there's a
signboard somewhere. But I ca
n't seem to put it down.  It's like I
want to hang out when I open the door. Is
this what it's all about
? How do I use it? It's
like holding a two-handed signboard.
[Music]
That's
it. Poroporo came to scout out something. It looks like
everyone's here.  I wonder
how everyone is feeling right now, everyone is having
fun
right now. Yes, there are
a lot of them.  It
was Kirro, and it was all Mr. Rigro. Oh my god,
I couldn't get the signboard I was holding in my left hand, and I
couldn't get it off all day today. It might have been on the signboard, but I couldn't
get it off. I couldn't get it. There was a huge uproar and it really
disappeared.  Degozaru, I can't take it
after all.It's not just good, it's true, it's bad.But
what's wrong with this?Everyone is fixed on Ma.It's
too bad, but is it okay to hold it in a competition?No,
maybe there is a reset on the signboard.
I think that when Gozaru is infected,
maybe he'll be
okay because of the knowledge that he's using his left hand all the time.It looks like
one of the creators of Minecraft will be forced to debug it again.I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I
'll do my best this time as a debugger at the Minecraft Sports Day.  As expected of Tesato, he always
tells me everything,
so there's no way he's making it. It's true, it's true, it's
true, it's true. Is it
true that there's a new Minecraft game?
Wow, that's amazing. In the next video, I
hear something, but I
can
hear it. I don't know, it's dangerous. Here, we do
n't know where the camera is, but
hey, I can hear it. I can hear it, but I can't
hear it, but it's a misunderstanding. It
's a misunderstanding.
Internal broadcast: Okay, well then. I'm going to
call out to everyone.
Everyone, please. Aba is the first entry announcement. Oh,
everyone who came to the venue is not red, so we
're going to go, we're going, right? It's white. It's white
.  Merle Meruru is red Merle is good
Merle This is my friend Merle There it is there Merle
Merle Merle
Me this way
That group said you can go from here to there It was
down I'm
coming from here now
[Music]
Tosasa-san is here again this year.  You're a genius. They
're lined up beautifully.
Let's do our best. Let's line up here. Let's join
together. Let's stay here with mom. Let's
stay here.
What are we here together? 11  Can you please stay in one line?
Yes, so next I ask the white people to come in.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] It
's white, that's great. Lastly, I
'll call the yellow group's child.  Is it okay if I take it?
Mom, it's okay.You're hiding.You're hiding, too.I'm in
trouble.Wait, it's
me, I just realized that it's me.I'm sure
the camera was set up for this route, but I
'm hitting it without doing anything.  Yeah,
Shinden White
is
too serious.
[Laughs] Is that
what you mean
? There wasn't a white sign, so why not? Even hold the sign.  I would like to
ask you to give your greetings for the tournament.Hello
everyone!
Thank you so much for coming together.I'm sure you have all
helped your seniors and juniors during your busy schedules, and
have worked so hard to practice up until today.  Yes,
today is the real deal, so I hope everyone will give it
their all and come out victorious.
First of all, everyone should have
fun and aim to win.
Please enjoy yourself today. Thank you very much for your support today.
Please, thank you for your wishes.Yes, to continue.We
have received a message from Mr. Yago, the president of Cover Co., Ltd.Please
take a look at Enine.Yes, please take a look.Thank
you for your hard work, everyone who is watching.This is a
sports day for hippos.When it comes to sports days, it's all about the neck.  It's
not in the program. I hope you're watching carefully.
At today's sports day, let's cooperate with each other,
encourage each other, and fight bravely until the end.
And as
always, thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much for your hard work.  I hope you will pay attention to me and support me.
Please be careful of all the members.
With that, I will give my opening remarks. No
, I am injured.
[Music] I am going
to be a fist fight teacher.  Channel 1, please
, please
do your best, please do your best.
My
general outline is
definitely, please, please,
please
, please, please do it
, please do your best, thank you very much.
Something's wrong with my ears Goe Shiro-
gumi
[Music] It's
okay, it's okay
Big It's coming, it's coming It's dangerous, I can't hear what the teacher is saying It's dangerous
Sumo Hey, it's good I think I can do it Do
your best
Do your best Well then, let's ask the players to do it for us  Is
that okay? Yes,
please. We, the players,
as members of Hololive,
will have to practice good sportsmanship and fight.
November 4, 2023 What is the virtue of being the representative of the Red Team?
Yellow Representative Haspels
[Applause]
[Music]
Yes, it's okay to say it. Thank you
very much. I'm sorry for throwing bread at you.
Thank you very much. I was shining.
[Music]
Special
Motion? Motion?
Excuse
me,
but the
seven buff white team fugitives are the
contestants of each group. Please go to the white team's contestant channel. The
sound quality of the rear sports day is a
little bit realistic, so I'm
still not
home hunting.  I
guess it's only the people who are in the 1st game.That's right.I see.I'm
going to the white group contestant's channel.So, uh, Ame-chan, Kaela Nelisa.Yes,
yes.Go.Good luck, Team
Fight
Player Channel.  No,
[Music]
Good luck,
good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck.
[Laughs] I'm
confused about both Japanese and English,
so I'm the third person, right? Yes, that's right, Ka.
Yo, that's cool.
Yes, it's okay, we made it. Did all three of us make
it? Is it okay for us to be runaways, too? This is no good. But I
wonder how complete we are. The white team is the hunters. The white team saw the beginning.  It's
like a hunter, so it's like a grouper. I
'm going to cheer for you. I'm going to cheer you on. It's
okay for us to cheer you on. It's okay to be a runaway, not a runaway. What group is this from
? I wonder if there will be an announcement about how many groups we'll start from.  Is there an
announcement? Is there an announcement? Is there an announcement? Is there an announcement? Is there an announcement? Is there an announcement? Is there an announcement?
Or are you referring to the white group of hunters?
Which frame are you pointing at?It's not us
yet.Well, first I wrote red, and the rest of me is a red mark.So, I
guess I'm a runaway and only have one entry.Then I
can't go to the other side.
Hey, can I press this?
I'm a
hunter, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't enter, I'm trying to do it, so I'm not going to do
it.
It's better, I think it's probably already done on its own
. At first, I was able to do it with the power of God. You do
n't have to press it, it's okay, it's okay. Okay, I
'm sorry, I'll excuse Sado's announcement.
Itadakimasu Kairoha-san,
Roboko-san, Kiame-san, Anekata-san,
Nai-san, Yuchoko-san, Azuki-san,
please go to the contestant channel of the Eshirogumi.
Yes, it could be the
other way around,
or it could be the other way around. It's not because everyone is running away. The
broadcaster is moving. I think it's okay for the broadcaster to move to the contestant channel.
What number is it? It's the same place, the white contest
channel. That's what I mean.
Nasumi: Excuse me. I'm
staying here. I'm not happy, so Acha
and I are against it
. Today
[laughing] It's
really difficult. If I hear this, I can do it.
Okay, I see. It's perfect now.  Well, I understand. Well,
wait a minute.
What I mean is, at first, the red team is the hunter, and the white team
all runs away. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
but they're all contestants.
Right, so that's
what they're saying.  When the White Team hunts, the infected
will be separated from the hunters. I
guess that's right.  It's a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit like the
other team's fugitives is probably done automatically so that the fugitives from other teams don't get the word out
For
example, if a hunter is a member of the red group and the hunter is a
member of the white group, they will be targeted and run away.
Oh, oh, I feel like I'm clicking.
Even if I get caught with a rope, I
want to run away as fast as I can. Oh, I'm going to be
put in a cage, so I'm going to be thrown in. I'm
going to South Korea. I'm going to South Korea. I can't get
out.  There's no one, so the back of the cage is surprisingly the
hiding place for the cat. That's
right. I'm a little anti. No
one is there. On the other hand, the cat goes to the wide side opposite the cage, so there's no one behind the cage.  The
same goes for behind the pillars of the swings. There
's something I'm a little concerned about. I
wonder if that's what the staff are talking about right now. I'm
watching the text channel, and the
seven fugitives in the white group are contestants, so it seems like it's the case.  It's on the 2nd floor,
but I wonder if it's better to go over there, because Bai-chan
didn't call me that. It's a competition. That
's right, that's right. So
both the people from the first and second hunting competitions
went over there.  I
'm having a bit of a hard time thinking about whether it's
better to do that or not.That's better, but they called me that, but I guess they didn't get it across.It's
like that, huh?I see.  I
feel like it's a bit of a
nuisance, but I guess I'll just listen to it.
Please say yes to the person who announced it. Thank you very much. It seems like
Laren-chan
has something to do with it. I
heard that earlier.  I was called, but I guess it's still
happening. I wonder if things are still going so that Raden-chan will participate. Maybe that's how it feels. I see. I see. If that's the
case, then
only people who aren't really hunters can use this channel right now.  I don't know if I have to be
there,
but Amichi
has the power of God, the power of God, the power of God.  I don't know
if it's true, but I
didn't hear this kind of flow this time.Come to think of it, it seems like I'm
rehearsing the way things are done, but I
haven't done that whole flow.
I'm guessing that the materials I
'm reading right now say, "I'm sure I can
join
Degozachi.
" It says for anyone other than the contestants, so it says for anyone other than the contestants from other teams. So that's it. That's the confusion. I'm so excited. [Laughs]  Even
though I'm at Doki A, I keep hearing that the staff is inputting information, so I
guess it's tatakatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatachi type.I guess it's
a bit of a long day today, so it's
scheduled to be around 9 o'clock, but I
feel like I shouldn't press the button.  It
's a bit of an atmosphere, so everyone takes a break. Some of you are
hungry if you're saving up energy, so let's
eat some food and take it easy. That
's right, it's long, so
this is the best part of the sports day, isn't it?  That's
right, Daigomi is difficult garbage, is
n't it?
Thrill Real
Thrill An's Daigo To begin with, it's an
AB channel, so it's in its current form.  It's
okay to ignore the diagonal. It's okay, it's okay, it's not okay.
[Music] We
suddenly had 9 people.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your reply, thank you,
thank you, but in the first game, in the first game, if Red is the first, everyone will have to
run away, but I don't know.  It's just that we're
doing it together, so the voice
just
starts, suddenly, suddenly, suddenly, it's
coming.English
, run away,
run away, flicker around the English members, let's
protect them.Protect the
members,
protect the members.
[Music] I'm not
hiding and waiting, it's dangerous! No
way, my back is being watched. I'm
not an anti behind the prison. Let's protect Machi-senpai. It's
dangerous.
[Music]
Reru Na-chan, the title will change, the title will change, the title will change.
Now it's just a show of high school. I'm
squatting, and I'm 149cm tall.
Let me make a mistake. It
's 149 or below.
What do you think of the people who fail? The
perfect person is 149 or below.  I'm
149cm tall, so I'm small. I'm 149cm tall, which is amazing.
On the other hand,
small people don't run away anymore, they're confident. It's weird, it's
weird, it's
dangerous, what should I do?
The answer is the opposite.
I don't
want to be caught,
but I don't want to be caught. How can I catch
you? What do you mean? Who is it? But catch me, catch me, catch me, oh, catch me! Can I go? Someone can I go?
Who is it? I can go.  Chacha, I can go.
Can you catch me? I failed.
Well, no, it
was a dead giveaway, but I was like, ``Let's stay here,
senpai.'' It was like, ``I
wonder who it was, who caught me too?'' It's
over.  There's a bit of an awkward crackle that seems to be wrong with Anya.Here's the
book that says there are 6 people.Ayaya,
yes, I'm going.Oh, wait a minute, the
6 yen isn't here.Excuse me.Those eyes are
here, the white team's escape.  To all those who have just discussed this matter,
please move to the voice chat where White Group ABB was originally located.
Please excuse me. Thank you for your hard work. Bye-bye, bye
-bye.
Oh, I'm rooting for this.  Okay,
Kaela-san was there too, and I was like, oh,
yeah, I
got it, and I'm doing it without any omissions, so I guess that means I just have
to be in the audience,
so let's cheer on each other.  I
wonder if it's okay for those who have been caught to stay where they are. They've been caught and are still being caught. They can't come out yet. They can't come out. [Music] Let's do it. Yeah, we can't. Oh,
it's South Korea. It's South Korea.
Oh,
there's even an old man.
Come out until we start.  Maybe it's not there. Why
don't we take a picture?
It's Korea, it's a country. It
's Korea. Thank you for the
photo. The photo of Korea is being taken in Korea
. His face is chained to the grass. It's really
here.  Here, here, here, here, this,
this, this, this,
this, this, that's good
, that's good, let's go.  It's the
best shot, but even if you wait, you can
download it. I'm
entering the country. I'm
pretty big. I
think this was created by the infected person.
But in the end,
there are only 6 people.  I looked at it
and it looked
really good.If I
wanted to make a seat, it would be nice to
have a seat.I'm sure there would be a seat behind Korea.I thought it was
dangerous and went to the yellow team that I created.  I'm doing it,
Katsu. Are you okay? I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. There was an interview, so it seems like I went to the second game as well. I did an interview. [Laughs] I'm
just confused. It's okay. It's
okay.  Why are you losing? You're laughing out loud. It's
okay. It'll be fine somehow. It'll be okay. It'll be okay. It'll be
okay. It'll be fine somehow.
Yeah, I was worried, but from the way you were talking just now, you
sounded like you were talking, but that's
pretty good.  It was increasing, it was blurry, I
was blowing, I was blowing,
I was walking around, Mu-senpai, let's
do it, let's do it, let's go, let's
do it, let's do it, Shirotame, Chirotame
Shiro team Chishi Chimushiro team Shiro
Shiro ah, it's white team hunt, so we're here.
That means I'm not a runaway, right? Yes, I want to run away as much as possible. I want to run away,
right. I want to run away. It's okay, I can run away next time.
Yeah, that's right. Please wait a little while until the next escape. Yes, I want to run away
.  [Music] We're a
well-behaved,
well-behaved team, so that's right.
That's right. Everyone was so nice. The white
rice was lined up in the prettiest rows.  They're
lined up like colors,
right? Just like our white color,
clear, clear, white, clear, clear,
white, clear, white, clear,
white, clear, clear, clear.
Toy: There
's going to be a gathering, so it's going to be
dangerous,
so it's
going to be hard, so I guess it's the theme of doing your best.It's been
2021 to 22
years since their debut, and it's pretty recent, so this is just barely here.It's almost like it's going to
fit in.
2That's right.I wonder if it's up
to Holos.Rocks.  I see that the
3rd generation of Love English and the 3rd generation
of the ID of the 3rd generation of the ID
are 2 upoles. It's the summer of 2020. It's
so
long that it's hard to find.  No, I do
n't know the name, but even if I know it, it's still hard to find. Good
luck,
Mom.  I'm
glad that you can do it, right? It's
not that we haven't secured anything at all. There's
still a lot of people, so it's
okay. It's okay. Get everyone, regardless of
who you are. You can go. If you can, there's probably at least one Bob.
Short-
bucks are what you get for now.
There's another hair, touch, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Good Goro Kids,
no, no, I'm saying it was good,
but I'm sure I'm not a kid.  I'm
caught Oh, it's true
Anya It's a
scratch
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  You're not a kid, you're not a kid, you've got big boobs, you're
not in the frame of a woman's scars.I'm
going to get in, it's over, it
's over, it's over, it's
disgusting and I have no choice but to
run away.
Let's catch them, catch them, and catch them. Yeah, catch them all. If you can't
figure it out after putting everyone in, just
put them all in. Yeah, go ahead, it's fine. It
was quite difficult. It was difficult.  Hey, it's not consciousness. It's funny.
It seems like some people are thinking about it. It's
surprisingly true.
That's bad
luck.Now that I think about it, when it comes to kids, it's probably someone like ``
Mr.'' or ``Konoka-san.'' I
think they're definitely kids.They probably
look like ``me-chan.''They look like kids.Hi, I'm
sure.  I want to know the answer to the question.I want to know the answer to the senpai from just now.I want the
bar to be displayed at the end.I
want it to be displayed no matter who is the pair.You're the one who's in the match, you're
targeted.You're right, you're 6.That's
right.Nanan Karisa-chan.
But I'm feeling like that same guy,
because I couldn't get this or that, yeah, I was able to
secure it, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay.  It was more difficult because the
training table for all training sessions was too easy.
Yes, there are some things that can happen, but it's
okay. That leader and Chiara
will cover for you. It's okay. It's
okay. I'm looking forward to it.  It's going to hurt too. You're
good. Everyone. I'll put everyone in, so I'll
put everyone in from one side to the other. Anyone who finds it
will have to peel off their arms, right? Use your grip strength,
please. It's time to move. It's time to move.  Poino
[Music]
Everyone, please go to Mr. Uji's voice chat.
Wasirknow
about
ONE
So-so
[Music] It's
not bad
[Music]
What's this like in pro wrestling?  Where is it, where is it,
where is it? I can't find it. I
want to do this so badly.
If I open the door and close it right away, I'll
be in front of the closed door. If I do this, I'll be able to get in a lot.  That's
right.
[Laughs]
No, it smells like earth. It smells like earth. It's
kind of smelly.
What
do you say? It's
terrible. It's kind of heavy. Is it a
bit?
That's too close contact.  It
was really cute when it was turned into a la. Yes, it was cute. It
was upright, oh yeah, yeah, that's it. That's so
cute. It's
so cute. You
could sell it as a cushion or something like this. It's true that it's really
cute. It's the one on the head.  That's a really
cute head. The
soldering is over. Yellow
. Yellow. Yellow. It's
better to run. Run away. Let's run. It's time to run. I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'll run away. I'll run away.
Run, run, run.
Come to Korea.  But no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
only the runaways, only the runaways.Touch the
runners.Touch the fugitives.Maybe they're
too eager to enter.It seems like they've already entered.
[  [Music]
Da da da
[Music] Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da [music] da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da thing, so I'm trying to disturb Aoko and make a mess of it I'm Kanata Fresh I'm done I'm just gonna
go by Anya's body I'm
sure I'll appeal to her motivation  Give it to me, Nemore, I'm
new, I'm new, I'm new.
[Music]
Ruru, I
'm here, I'm here, too. It's 460, catch me.
There's no way I've been ignored at all. Wait a minute, Captain.
But birth 158, wow, I'm so
sorry.
Oh,
it's okay, it's okay, hide it, hide it. 165 That's right, hide it, hide it.  [
Music] I'm so
clean that no one wants to catch me,
but I'm sorry for the people who care
about me. I'm not clean. I'm clean enough to scream. I'm clean no matter what I do. I'm clean.
There are various complaints, and there are also complaints. Nice, nice, I didn't
catch him, I
didn't catch him.
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Yes, I'm definitely a member.  It's
cute when it's there.
What's going to happen to it? It's cute. It's
scary. It's so neat and clean. You'll never change. It's
definitely neat. That's great. Run away properly. You
're so cute. You have to
run away, too. You're neat and clean.  However, I
didn't think that I would be caught, but the
yellow was really strong. I
caught about yellow. It
was amazing. Well, I made a profit with this. It was
n't a group. I ran away one more time. One
more time. I was able to enter. We all did it at
once.  You
gave it to me, right, round, run away, run away, it's okay.When I was an older sister, I didn't care if I was the group leader, or if I was a sexy woman like a big sister, but I wanted to be chosen.Don't
say that.It's
true that I wasn't even chosen for my height.
Well, that's true, but the child who misunderstood me,
Kolka, misunderstood me, and
let me run a little too close.The cage
is too small.I really wanted to get out, but now I can
catch him.  If that's the case, you
won't be able to run away during the game, right? That
hunter has only a few days left until the next game starts,
so the remaining
juniors have to do their best. Next time, Mio-senpai, who's going to think that
?  There is a possibility that they will change it even if it is like that,
but there is a possibility that it will
change or it will be completely different.
If you do that, you'll want to be protected
.  It's
creepy trying to be like that,
but
no, no, no, everyone's buried. Everyone
's stuck in there. It's really a [ __ ]. It's so cute. It's so cute when they're standing next to each other. It's so cute. Someone please stand next to me too.
Reset
Reset will
probably start over again Oh
okay okay okay okay oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh that's a lie I worked so hard to make this book but it's
gone now I'm going to go out of my way to chat with you Subaru I'm
wondering how many nipples does senpai have?  I
heard that there are two, but of course there are more than two.
No, it's like birds don't exist because they're eggs, so it's
not a book, so I haven't gotten that kind of
thing. It's just that it's a specialty.
Even though it was supposed to be, I'm lonely. I'm sad. My debut was in 2019.
[Music] It
's not 2019.
It's 201.
Everyone
please run away. This is the year. It's a
shame.  It's such a shame, let's just say that in
2019, it's
been a long time since I've cut it. This work is bad. Run away, run away, run away, it was scary.
[Music] I had the impression that I was putting out a lot of stuff. [Music] I'm an
artist. I
was caught by someone who was acting like a total idiot, and I
was going to get caught by someone.
Look, I was arrested. It seems like I was arrested in a certain way. No, I have
n't been arrested. I haven't been arrested. I haven't
been arrested. It's
surprising that I haven't been arrested yet.
That's not the case.
[Music]
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
I answered all the questions, but I ran away. I wonder if it's an
easy move. Thank you for your hard work.
Only the three hunters remain here, and the rest.
People, please move. I
understand. I'll do my best. Bye-
bye. Do my best. Is this okay here? Maybe it
's here. Hey,
I've been arrested again. I've been arrested. I've been arrested again.  I
'll give you this too. What is Korean
? I don't know what you're looking at. I'm at a loss. I
'm at a loss. I
'm used to it. Let's put
this out.
Give this.
Teruko-sensei Gare
[Music]
Tayo's in Prison
I'm in trouble
[Music]
But it's a good place. Do
your best. Wait, I made a mistake. Wait a minute.
The mouse is
[Music]
Oh Tae, now pat it.  I was
stroking it, I was stroking it, and I was stroking it,
and it hit me
[laughs]
Hey,
it's cute.  Ah, it moved, it moved, it moved, it's
cute, it's cute, it's cute, it's cute, it's cute, it's cute, it's cool, it's cool, it's
cool.  It
was written in the stranger that I'm entering right now. I'm automatically taken away. I'm being
taken away by disappearing people and pins. Do your best,
do your best.
[Music] A
dangerous white brawl
has begun. It's so
cute, I didn't realize it's true.
That's right.  Has it been taken away? Was it YouTube-
like?
Naru just took it, but look at it.
This is where my father-senpai is hiding.Here, this senior
is hiding, but he's probably
hiding.He's hiding in a mess, thinking, ``I'm really close to entering.''U-
Senpai has made a big mistake.It seems
expensive.It's
true, but
ta.
Alright, alright, it's fast. Three people have already
been caught.
[Music]
Goza
[Applause]
I'm in the middle of nowhere. Do your
best. You're so nice. You're so nice.
That's the best record, the best record, the
best record. Maybe the best record is
messed up. It's
amazing. It's gonna be 2 if it's not the next one. It's
okay.  Oh, nice, oh, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice,
please
listen to me. Ah, ha, ha, ah, wow, that
guy from earlier, ah,
wait a second, what's going on here, Choco Sensei
's photo.  This is such a good photo, isn't it? It's amazing. It's
amazing. It's so nice. I took a picture just now. I'm going to send this to Subaru as a
friend. It's so good. This is so good.
Yeah, where's it? Oh, oh,
everyone. I'm going to take a lot of pictures on the way home. It's
amazing.  It was really good, but it was really hard. I was
really caught at the end.
Yeah, the last part was almost blurry.
The face I was looking at was really heavy. It's
surprisingly rare to have a dodge ear like this, though. It's
a little scary to hear that B-senpai has a kake-mimi.  I do
n't have an image of
this.I guess that's right.Everyone is so
stupid that it's not cheap to attack them.I wonder
if it's that stupid thing.But if I
judge by O-senpai, there are probably a lot of people who are quite stupid.I guess it's
not
cheap.  Mio-chan
Other than Kamio-chan
Or Miorando
Mirala It was a bonus stage in a sense,
but I'm sure I was able to do it. Ne will do it for me.
I'll run away. I'll run away. Let's do our best, let's do our best. Let's do our best. Let's go, let's
go. Nice. Nice kitty.
[Music]
After all, it was a little hard to catch them when they were all gathered in one place. It's
dangerous. Hide it. Hide it. Don't hide it. Hide it. Hide it, Chando-senpai. Hey,
someone got caught. They
got separated.
[Music]
Seniors like that are like 0 to 2 years old, that
's right, 4 years old too,
yoyaichi, that's what
Korea is saying, it's okay to stop.They
caught me and got caught.They looked like they were doing well.  It's
erotic, I
'll protect it,
Wow, it's true, it's blond, it's
blond, it's bad, it's bad, it
's the same, I'm sorry, it's the same, it's the same Damn, I
messed up but I'm
sorry I'm bored, I'm bored, I'm bored at this time
[Music]
Hey there, you can catch me for a little while
. I'm going to make a
break. I'm going to do it one-chan, one-chan. I'm sure you'll stay awake and ignore me. Why didn't you just ignore me? Famous
Matsuri Senpai  Matsuri Senpai Matsuri Senpai is here too Senpai
Sexy
[Music] I
'm here [
Music] Nainai Eko
How many people were here? 13
Nice, Nice,
Nana, Nice, it
was almost dangerous.
[Music] Nice, I'm
glad. I was
really a little surprised.  I wish I
could hide behind you.
[Laughs] We
're all here. We're
back, we're back. We're
moving on our own.
[Music] We're
falling. In the end, I wonder who's winning now. I
don't know. It's like progress.  I do
n't know, I wonder where the sexiness was
Wait, there's Kaela-san.
Oh, Kaela-san is sexy. Kaela-san is sexy.
Sexy, kaela, no, kaela-
san. Sexy is
[Music] It
's cool, isn't it? It's turning red, isn't it? It's not a comb, it's
not a comb. It's shiny.
Well, it's Butt Day.
Hey, it's Butt Day. I'm sure I saw your butt
earlier. But I was already in Korea, so I
couldn't get it. Is it sexy? Well,
no, don't make me look sexy.
Hey, that's already sexy.  It would have been better if it hadn't been. I wanted to be
sexy and
get caught, but I wanted to know a little more about it
. It's a shame. I can't tell
at first. It's true. I don't know what's going on, so congratulations
. I hope you all do your best, too, and the rest
of the team.  I want you to run all the way to the end.Yes, that's the
case.I'm
going to do white 20.I'm going to give you yellow 25, white 20, and red 15.  The
venue is a follow-up. Top Let's
go up side Afro up fall I
don't want to fall I don't want to fall
[Music]
No
Ah, that's too bad Kia senpai isn't here
English is
terrible
English English
Top second is here Let's go, senpai's dream Let's
go, senpai, let's go What's
going on with that person?  School School
School
's School School Upside School
High School
Crap Side Camo Stage 5 Follow
Up Stage Flow Up Stage Rooftop What do you
mean by love? High
Ground What is it on High Ground?
Ground
Up I
'm Roof Rooftop Rooftop Rooftop Rooftop
Gogoroof
Topgogoroof Topgogolftolft
Yeah, let's go, oh, I see, it's
almost like we're on the roof,
yeah, now.  It's all interview time for all the contestants.
I see. I see. Good
luck, Roboko Senpai character Senpai, really.
[Music]
Do your best, do your best, do your best, but that's it. I don't
think we can go together on the phone at all. Ah.  I
didn't feel like I was that serious about what I was looking at.In fact, I was really
grateful that Chiara's presence was so helpful.Thank you very much.I
looked up English today.  I'm
going to eat it here.
No, I haven't used it even once. I'm going to use it.
But, during the break, I was explaining to you. Oh my god, I
was listening to it. I was so
angry, I was listening to it.
What was that steak?  I
had a meeting with Mu-senpai about how to say pork in English. When I asked him to grill it, I
told him what to grill.
Good luck, Beef Fook, Chicken, Beef
Pork Chicken,
Chicken Pig.
Because I forget, so I have to shout this to him,
so it's beef, pork, chicken
, beef pork, chicken steak, steak, steak, steak, steak,
beef, beef, fire,
beef, fire, fire, steak,
spicy, go,
steak.  Eat, it's
spicy. I'm not
hungry. Someone said they were hungry. I'm hungry. I
'm hungry. It
's about 7:30. It's time for dinner.
That's why I'm hungry.  Yes, the overseas group is
right, so there's no difference, I
'm in the middle of the day, senpai, 33am, 3:30am, 3:30am, 3:30am.  It
's hard but
it's okay Good morning sleep It's so late at night
Thank you so much Thank you Senkyu It's
okay
Coffee length I drank coffee I drank coffee Corner
Nice Coffee Nice Coffee Nice Coffee Caffeine Minister
Caffeine Minister Caffeine Caffeine Caffeine Power Let's go Yay
Yelets
Goashi  A great person said that English doesn't matter.If you just say, ``Let's go,''
everything will
be fine.Indeed, if you
believe in that great person, everything will be fine.Sui-
chan was throwing a trident, but
Sui-chan was the only one with creative
authority.
Well, I heard that it can be used with that.It's throwing a trident.Oh, maybe that's
it, maybe it's the other
side of my house, or the home hunting I just did, I
was editing it in creative mode.  Yeah, yeah, that's right. I
still have some remnants of that, and I do things like
fly and throw javelin by myself.
For about three days now, I've
been holding a trident in my chin. It's a
sly trident. It's a trident.  Ah,
Mizuo-senpai, you can't
do this, huh? What are you doing? It's okay, it's okay. I'm creative, so I can't go up and do this. So, what are you doing?
Or are you annoyed that Mizuo-senpai has a leg? You can
go up and do this.  That's right,
that's true. That's
true. It's true. I can't pick this up. I
can't pick this up. It's the remains of Mr. Senpai, so I'll take a photo. The
stars are reading out. The
stars are reading out.
Teruhiha.  Chan's star reading is
showing up, you're such a troublesome person, it's too bad,
please don't say it to him.Are you sure you're going to say it?
Please stop it.Chan's face is clearly
showing.I put some dirt on my hands.I
put it in Gypro.I didn't write anything like that.  I was
checking the smell.
That's what I was saying. It's gone,
it's gone,
it's gone, it's gone, I'm in shock. Please
do it first. Oh,
what should I do? I don't know what to do. I'm going to
look at it later.
That's right. I
'm going to buy the rest of the papan fried papan. I'm
going to buy it, but I'm really going to lick my indoor shoes. I
wonder if you'll lick my indoor shoes. I'm not going to lick them. I'm not going to lick them.  I'm
not
going to give it to you. I'm glad you liked it. I'm
going to deliver the cookies. Look, I'm going to deliver the cookies. Look, the cookies are here. They're cookies. I want to deliver them to everyone. I'll
let everyone at the overseas stores eat them too.
Yes, that's true. I've
been telling the world a lot. I'm going to take a break from streaming
for about a month,
and
then I'm going to go out for some training.
Then I'll
give it to Karamui Ame-chan.
Cookie Presents Cookie Presentation Color
Cookie Cookie Color It's coming!
Star Star Oh, it's
coming, it's coming, let's go Roboco
Roboko-senpai, do your best, do your best, Roboko-san, do your best, do your best
! Good fight, oh so good! You were so good at it!
Practice
too!  It's not too early, Mr. Bi
is really good Why is Gozayo-chan so good? Mr. Biji, do
your best, Robo Koshin Noko is good,
good, good, good, good, good, now it's number 2. Yo,
nice, nice, yes, nice, nice. It's all right, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Dayu I've already fixed the startup, so what's going on now? It's
probably like touching a checkpoint, falling to death, and coming back. Yes, yes, yes.
Checkpoints are important. Paoi. It's
true that Sui-chan and I are really anxious. It's
true.  It's amazing, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, the
route is so solid, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good,
everyone,
oh, Mr. Business, Mr. Business, it's so good!
In the remaining time, I
'm coloring it, it's true, Sui-
chan, do your best, you're amazing, but you're in first place so fast.B
Too good to be true, Ao, checkpoint,
Nice-san, give me a break, Daddy, but I'm steadily
catching up.This is my point of view.  I can go all the way to the top. I'm
doing this. I can't go up to see this. I can't go to the top. I'm
looking at it from below. I'm just looking at it from below. I'm
looking at a sign that looks like it's around here.  They say that if you touch the infection sign, you
can go.Eh, this is the
first time I've heard of that.See, right click on the infected person, and it
says ``Enter''.Oh, it's going to
go up, it's going to go up, it's going to go up.It's true, it's amazing, it's
amazing, I'm going to chase it, I'm going to
chase it.  I didn't know it, I didn't know it, I didn't know it now,
and now it looks like it's in a close-up It's amazing, it's
true, everyone is
really floating, everyone knows it, I guess it's
just their heads floating, right?
Good luck.  I'm
going to do my best, I can't see the nice and nice spectator,
so it's okay. I'm really invisible. I'm
really in the goal.  Teru-
chan, do your
best, just a little bit more, that's awesome,
nice, nice, nice, that's awesome.  He's so
cute even though he's throwing such a great trident. I wonder if Tsui-chan's stars are coming out. I'll do my best to be a photographer with cute eyes.  It's
not up, it's up, it's not up, it's
not good, it's
good, do your best, do your best, oh, you're taking a shortcut, you
've been there quite
a bit now.
Good
Nice Nice Nice Like
EVERYONE Finishi Funinice
Nice GG GGROM is a jammed great game.  I'm
sure it's on, right? Are you
okay? Is there something on the screen?
Something strange has appeared on the screen. What is this? Is there a
controller for chat settings? I wonder if
there is a controller. I do
n't really understand.
Wait, wait, I can't get off this. It
's a shift. It's a shift. I can
get off with a shift. Is it okay to shift down? Yes, there's a
severed head flying around. It's a bit of a sticker. I'm
sure it's infected with this and that, so I'm going back.  Kaa, I
'm back, I'm back, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.  You ca
n't see our heads, right? It's true that when you looked at them from below, you
couldn't see them. You couldn't see them. You
didn't notice them. That's why you
thought they weren't there. I don't think they'll get in the way. I see.  I
'm back. I'm
forced to go back. I've been writing about this one after another. I wonder if it's
better to make them infected after the game starts. The entry is
like when you're looking at it from the sky after you die.  What do you mean by
separation? It's like an out-of-body experience.TanaeNextKiaraSenpai Yes, I'm rooting
for you, I'm rooting for you.Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight,
fight.  Hey, it feels good!
Hey, Chiara-senpai, it's amazing, it's extremely
fast. It's because you're so fast, it looks like it's the fastest. I've
been practicing really, so it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, it's
fast. If it's early, I'll do something until the last minute.  It's so good, it's so good, it's really good, it's really good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so
good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, Chiara-senpai, Kiara,
only one of us has already gone 70m, it's too early, it's too fast, it's sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooh  It's
too smooth. I can't
go there. It's too smooth. I'm
going to go there. I can
go there. I can go there. I'm going to go there.
Chiara-senpai Super Gia is
great. The bird is amazing. It's fast. Goha.
It's so fast, after all, I was really nervous during practice when I was flying in the air.I
said, ``What should I do?'' No matter what I did, I
didn't make any mistakes.
[Music]
I made a mistake.  No way,
no, I've come this far with a mistake. That's good. Which way are we going? That's it. I've
already decided on that. Even the speed is there. It's amazing. It's too
fast. It's too good to be true.
Nice. This is definitely one.  I was
going back to the bottom where it wasn't my turn.If I fell down here, the
checkpoint would be quite low.That
's why I'm an old
man.It's difficult.It's so big and so amazing.It's so
scary, Kia,
do your
best.It's so cool, it's so amazing
.  You
're a genius and nice, Kia
. You're a genius. No, you're so
nervous. You move like you're not nervous at all. You
just climbed up like a rock. You
didn't even stop. Nice, nice, nice,
nice. That's too good.  It was good,
but we haven't finished in 2nd or 3rd place yet.It's still only
half way.It's not even 150.So, we got
around 90 with the help of an old person.Looking at the bottom, it looks like we're going to finish it.It's so
fast,
hey.  Gini: Ah
, it's
true that you and Kuro-san are competing against each other. Ah, Kuro-
san,
Kuro-san is amazing. That's what I thought. It's really difficult to die,
right? The same goes for the sense of distance.
Kira was really practicing, so it's the
result of all of his hard work.  It looks like we practiced for a really long time yesterday. It's
amazing. I'm the only one, Wing Undokki, Aaayoi, Onopremushi, Japanese Amo, and finally, Wow, 2 yellows or 2 yellows. Wow, that's a shame.  There's only one step
left, no, there's only one step left. Oh, I'm
already flying. I'm flying. Da-
chan dropped it. I
saw
an amazing moment. It was cut off in an instant
. It was an amazing battle.
[Music] I'm
waiting, waiting, waiting.
Wait, it looks like the points from the second game will
be announced again, but since we
finished 12th, I think this
follow-up probably has the highest points.
Well, if this thing on the screen that is appearing on the other side of the stream right now is the
point of flow up, the
white team's points are now 20 and the number 1
point has come out now, so it's probably Ron number one
point.  I wonder
if I can catch up? It
was a nice fight. Hey, you
haven't come back yet. You have
n't come back yet. Are you still in the middle of an interview?
No, it's still like that. It's
just us, the white team.  Both of them are eavesdropping properly
. Go to Neane. I
wonder if I should stand in the mountain's Idaki and try to make it to the mountain's Idaki. I see, that's right. It
was a high-level match. No,
Nosu was amazing.
Tanane, you didn't make any mistakes, that's really nice.
Nice, the white group is currently in first place. Hey, the
time is close, but white is 40 yellow,
38 red is 37, wow.
Nice nice nice CM4
Points yellow 38 red
37 Let's go let's go.
Like Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice
Nice Nice Nice Nice This is a good idea to go to our princess escort, so it
seems that Rile seems to be reliable.  Yes, that
's right. There's still a lot going
on. It's true that I have to do my best. The pressure is slowly building up. I don't think I'm willing to do it, but I feel like I don't want to do it. The pressure is starting to build up. I can't help but struggle.
This time with Ramen-chan.
Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, I'm
watching you.
At 40, it was
probably 63 points,
White was 52 points,
or 3 points. We
moved to the venue for the next technique line in Lee Volume
[Music]
Masho Mase Jump from here
to that was announced.
What's the score? White got a
total of 2 Amadadone and 3. Yellow got
63. White got 6 and Kia-chan is nice. It's a
good game and it's a good game.  Good
game Good game Nafanafa 2 people
Wow 2 people
are amazing It was amazing I can't give up, it
's dangerous I can't do it It's terrible I'm
doing my best Chiara Let's
do my best I'll ride Let's ride I'll ride After that I'll
be first
Yo I'm the first one I don't want to do it  I don't want to do it.
Where's Miyo-chan? Amio-chan
is here. Enter on the right side of the entry. Where's this? That's cute. That's cute.
Here, this is it. You're
okay. That's nice. Nice, nice, cute. Nice, nice, cute.
If you're going to ride on top of the ship,
then you're going to be on top of it.The
person who's going to ride it is going to stand on top of you.Wait, the
general is on top.Maybe the
general is on top, so click.  I'm the
one who will be rejected. If you
don't enter, you can cancel.
[Laughs] In
the future, that
person from this pair will come. I
guess that person from my pair will come.  I wonder if
that person is there?
Will he come?If the
pair of the missing person continues like this, I
'll wander around everyone.
[Music] I'm
hungry and hungry, I want to do something. I'm
begging you to release the general. I'm
okay, so okay.
Here, everyone,
everyone is getting more and more amazing.
Where are they? I can't see where they are. Is it
okay to get off the target? Is it okay to get off the target? How do you
stop? That's the
same thing in the book.  Just press it once
Ah, nice, nice,
nice
[Music]
Hey,
wait a minute, did you go there in that outfit?
Yeah, he came in a suit, he looks strong. That's
amazing, he's dressed like a grassy suit.
Yeah, there's a guardian.  That thing looks too strong. It's
okay. I won't charge you a huge amount later. It might be
okay.
Thank you, Senpai, Thank you, Senpai. I was able to ride it
. I was able to ride it. It looked
like it was the strongest. I'm a pinch hitter.
Thank you
very much for helping me.Thank you very much for your help.Ao-senpai, please come.  I
'll leave it to you.
Thank you. I'm so happy. I can ride on your ears. It's
fluffy. It's stuck in my butt.
Yes, the corner of the chocolate wire is stuck in my butt.
Leader, this is the horn. The
corner hurts. Does it
hurt? I don't like it. No, I don't like it.  It's
better if the stings touch each other. Okay, I think it's quite irritating. That being said, it might be quite irritating to Mio-chan too. It's true that Senpai is also irritating her with the horns. It's a painful thing.
Hello,
Neko Maokayu-san today.  Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for letting me participate. I'm
most scared of Supi. He's become a suspicious person,
so I'm afraid he'll take me away. That doesn't
mean I'm going to say yes. How about you?
Are you enthusiastic?  Nanonemasaratto taught me how to do it, and
I want to lead it to victory. It's
so cool. It's fun. Please do your best. Let's do our best,
everyone in the white team.
We'll do it, we'll do it. We'll
do our best.
Yes, let's hear it at the end.  I want to do it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Costume Hey,
what's the strategy? Everyone in white is freaking out,
right?
After all, if you get the first kill, you
get 1 point added.  That's right, it
seems like the only thing you can do is to focus on the opponent you're going to attack while protecting Gozaru Nadada, and everyone should just wake up the one that approaches the general.If you're a
face-off
type, it's better to stay close.  I
don't think it's possible for someone to do something like that.I
want to beat up someone who is weak.I can see it, so
maybe that person wants to go crazy.At
first, stay close to the general and get 1 heart.  If you see it, you'll
attack. I'm
scared. Well, I
think this will probably be the pair's voice chat from now on, so I guess that's
right. There are so many voice
chats. Erm, at the
bottom.  I think there's probably a name for it,
so now that I think about it, there's a real Nakanata porridge.You
can't get it unless you work together, so you can't say you have to protect it that way.That's right, the
general, look at the landmark.  Let's do our best, let's do our best, we're
aiming for this,
yeah,
yeah, if we find it, then let's do it, then we'll probably have to move from here.
If you're going to win, it's probably
better for the person at the
bottom to
speak.
Music]
know
Allbasicallythrow
You
and
ATT
SHI
ickMaybeistherea
SHIELDyouhaveto
equiptheSHIELDIhave
anything
currentlyIthink
thereaSHIELDIthink
justabookandyouHit
Peoplewiththeoris
theresupposedtobeI
seeanybody
SHIELD
SHIJA
okayWhodowethinkthe
weakestlinkis
WhoisitTRUEthatifwe
gothatweGETMORE
POINTSInoIDEarePart
OfThe
Game
YELLhere
where where
meWhitekindharderto mongall
thewhiteshirts
hereapparentlyThey
havemoreHPTheyhave
moreHEARTSthanthe
othersIseewecould
alsoyouknowbully
Somebodyisthere
anybodyyouLonthink
gnagoleaders because
ofthemorePOINTSI
thinkifweMayHang
backandGetthepeople
inthebackofThe
crowdsWhotryingto
gettheleaderThey
mightnotnoticeusat
firstGivingUSthe
upperhandIknowmaybe
notgoodThisismy
first
timeokayIthinkagood
ideaWecangothe
unsuspectingOnes
ImeanthePRWecame
back
chance
care
me
Knottingthe
horsesosorryIthe
onlypersonever
watchedSpiritNoI
loveSpiritwhereget
allmyIdeasfromis
thatCrazyNoNonotat
allSowrongIjust
anywayI
horseiidhorseIam
ridingyouexactlyso
youaremoreofahorse
girlthanmerightnow
moreofaGirlhorseJA
SORIGHTIamaGirl
horseandyouarea
aGirlWhoisahorseand
Iamahorselovinggirl wholoves
younejnej
give
carotDoyoulike
carrotssugarcubesI
like
bothWhatdoyouprefer
IlikeIlikeboth
TogetherokayWho
faitemylittlepony
ponyRainbow
DASHOGOGOG ient
Whatokay
[Music]
unspecokayOhGOcome
youcarefulokayWeONE
Iokaynicenicenice
niceSorryOhshootthe
GotUsokayokayokay
Whodidthatwejust
talkingabouther
beforeIRGetIRGetIR
IRsomeyou
okayREVENGEyouwant
REVENGEyes
yesareyouREVENGE
WORKINGNo
oneonemoreOhSHShe
USOhmygoshILost
EverythingisLOWokay
yourheartNo NoIseeI
seegotohertoo
LLSorryno
okay
IknowgoingonRRunUS
WeforFokayifwecan
probablynotprobably
OFFNowAreyougetting
HerRokayscareHer makeHer shouldYou ShouldBeafraidvery very
afraidgood
all [laughs
]
sosorryIeventhinkI
waslikestaringatthe
screenIjustITellYou
Anythingthat
HappenedJustnowI
tellyouthat
happButwekilledlike
IthinkpeopleWealso
diedtcethatwasall
youthatwasAllYou
Killingandthatwas
all NoKSon
USpeoplesaying
TE
DownWhat
isgoingtoGivingthe
PEPRESSUREWhat
is
AC
FWhyIS
F
doitagainWe
individualsAgain
of
whatIdidokaymakeI
gettherightTHE
PERFECT
[laughter]
horck
okayIgot
it
[music]
NokaybrokenNowCrush
allmyhes
DreamsI
obedient
Whatjust
[music]
kidding
FfnysohappyWEED
Togetherme
toohappythatIcan
bewithSomeoneWho
seemstoalsobejusta
little
deliriousSuper
deliriousIhaveno
ideaWhereIamright
now
NoIstreameddoing
streamsfor
the daysI
knowICheckmyphone
likeIwonderlikeWhat
goingonlikelooks
likeNstreamingand
thenyouknowkindof
gettoitam
likeStillStillgreat
HaveAGlikeyou
knowfor
HOURIImadeAMaybeB
scheduleMOVEtoday
WhereIhadYouKnowMy
Oneofmylonger
streamshourseven
thenIEndat10andI
reallyfallASLEEP
earlylikeAgainstMy
WillIunderstandOh
YeahSoIkindofknew
thatlikeIwasgoingto
beabletosleepbutI
waslikegoingtotryI
needTry
TrymakesITWORK [Music]
LetdothisThingI
STREAMbutIHlikeGO
OUTIntoThe
World Ifeelabit
TiredI
understanddefeat
your enemieslookat
allGetniceokayokay
okayokayNEXT
iswhoever
okayokayJumpJump
JumpJumpJumpOhnice
[Music]
okayIknowSSS
Swing
okay
[Music]
neveryou
ALSorryIYto
[Laughs]
around
backforback
forokay
somedidit
DidIcanreadnamegoil
IThowkills
you
killyou
K
[Music]
kills
girlhorseeathorse
WORLDhorseeatgirl
eat
horseheTACusedhors
meatYesIdoRemember
ThatistruthTo
ThatI
know
okayTE
TEIloveWarRthemfor
melikeNoTheyvegan TheyfineIknow
thehethe
CREAMCRECREAME
CREAMpretendthatwe
OnTheRed
Team
AnotherItru doIcomplhestI
thoughtBeLikeAROUND
THELASTGAME IHowmany
roundsSsomeswichYou
tryingAgainyouwant
metryagainokay
okay ick
cck
okay
ick
horse
helpokayStandingthe
okayImakesurenoone
everstealsyouagain
thereyou
dockingokayokay
AgainIknownot
workingokayIdoIdo
itOhmynissIknownot
working
back
[music]
[laughing]
[clap]
[music]
know
[laughing] [
laughing]
[laughing]
[music]
OhGod
okay
[clap]
[laughing]
okayokay
[music]
[laughing]
okayrightccktil
SHIELD
okay
okaygirlThirstyHold
On
okayokay
okay
ONEWeTwookayokay
okayokay
wewegobackTurn
ReturnNousing
SHIELDIevenokayIcan
seeIcansee
okay
[Music]
okayHurtHurtUH okayHurtHurtUHnice okayokayhur
[Laughter] [
Music] [
Laughter]
kssokayoveryou
did
ohmy
godTeam
4okaywehavetobein
theLeadNowweGtobeWe
GotToBewinnersOhmy
GOnissaYouwereso
goodatdirectingUS
towards
peopleNolike
SeriouslyYEIfeel
likeyouwereIfeel
likeIkilledjust
peoplethatalready
hadLOWHEARTSor
something
IHnoideawhatIwas
doing towardsyoucouldsmell
OUTDeaththatwaswe
just
finalized
We
FPS
hours
[MUSIC]
May
WOWTeam
I
horseI
ACtohorseIcouldthe
horseMayMaybe
ITruthofLifeifyou
tellpeoplebugsyou
thensayitmorebutif
yourealizethat
nothingsandyou
just
youknowwhatiknew
thatMayDeepDownI
justItwasMy PlanIdidwanttobethe designatedHSEBrown IthewordforlikeD horsenotYouShould Knowhorsegirl horseIonly speak
HUMANisH
sand
S OH
rome
for
okaysupptogobackI
thinkIknowGdragUS
WeOUTIseeokaywehave
towait
forKOnlyKILeaveThe
Game
Oh
ohScared
CHANNEL
anyOh yeah it's important Nice Nice Strong
Very Strong  Degozaru Yes
Yes, Mr. Roboco-san pair was amazing too. That was nice. It was
super dead.
I got 3 kills. That's
amazing. Thank you for doing such a good job. That's
nice. So amazing. What do you think of this? It's pretty good, is
n't it?  I think I went quite far, but I still managed to make a
comeback.So,
I feel like I've made a comeback in the second game as well.I
think I was number 2, or something like that.I
got about 26 kills, so I've made quite a comeback, or something
like that.  Red was strong too, so it's
okay. Red was strong. Red was strong. It was amazing at first.
But I don't know what's going to happen. It's scary. I'm getting scared of Lire. Both the
princess and the princess are shaking. Today, the princess is shaking with her strings. She's
shaking. Now, Bume-chan, let's do our best. It's okay.  It's
okay, it's okay, we can win, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, we can win, we can win.During
practice, the yellow team avoided me for about a minute and a half,
but yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's right, even though they served me food, I
didn't like this at all.  It's a serious meta reading,
but since the update was released and the
content of Holomen Hunting has
changed considerably, it's possible that you're reading the mystery that the menu has also
changed completely.
Yeah, that's possible, that's totally possible
. I mean, I want to win. I really want to win. If I come this far, I'm
sure I've come, right? How far do I want to
go? Yes, I want to go, right?
At first, I felt a little greedy.  I
felt like I was starting to feel like I was
going to win, but I was
starting to feel
like I was going to win.I wrapped my arms around my sleeves.I didn't tear
them off just now.  You can't
tear it up, you can't tear it up. You've got
leftover skin,
but you can't have
too much skin. It's so wild that you can't
take care of it, it's muscular, it's
muscular after all. It's the
whiteness that's climbing, and it's the end.  Congratulations on your 41 kills. I
was blushing when Shimiko-senpai came home. It's too bad. How was the number of kills?
Who was the best person? Who got the most kills
? Kiara was amazing too. I'm sorry about the
rest,
but senpai.  I defeated 1 player in the 1st episode, and there were a
lot of people like that too.It
was amazing, amazing, yes.That's why the white team was amazing.In closing,
thank you very much Nekomata
Okayu.Please leave your thoughts.Yes,
thank you very much.  Thank you very much. I
was happy to play with you all. I will continue to support the white team.
Thank you.
Thank you. You disappeared in an instant.
Thank you, agent.
Me and my friends are also
scared of the numbers, so it
's completely different. I worked hard, I tried my best.
Thank you very much. It was really
fun to eat, it was fun, it was really fun, it
was fun.  It was fun and easy, but there's a lot of
pressure in the competition that follows.
Yes, the pressure is different. Let's hope it's
okay. It's okay. Everyone who can do it can do it. It's okay. But it's okay. It looks like it's okay. I
have to protect the princess.
Even if I have to protect the princess.  As a princess,
even if I make a slight mistake, I can catch up with the relay.
In this world where pressure is dangerous and dangerous, I
can do this. I'm going to practice that. I'm already
climbing the vines. Everyone's climbing the vines.
Even now, I'm in a hurry to climb the vines.  I guess I'm getting better at it. I can do it. Oh, it's
difficult, isn't it? It's difficult, isn't it? I
said, "When I asked you today, where did you do it? Did you say you were running?" So, let's tally up the scores.  It looks
like it's over, so I'd like to see it.
[Applause]
Look, the red team
scored 46 points, the white team scored 38 points, and the yellow team
scored 23 points.I do
n't know what's going on with this, but I wonder how the battle will
turn out.  So, okay, let's move on to the next one.Yes,
yes, let's
move on to the next competition, everyone.
[Applause] Let's go. Let's look forward to it. Good
luck
Princess Mikata. I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'll
do my best. I
wonder if everyone else can come.  Let's become a knight. I'll
do my best. I'll
do my best. Fat, I'll do my best. I
wasn't the VC of my team yet. I guess we're
all doing our best now. Pink, red, yellow, pink,
yellow. Red is fine, but you don't have to worry about it too much.
Iris.  Princess, oh princess, let's go, princess! There
's something about the status of this princess that she doesn't say herself. I don't know if she's super cute or a mystery.
Naked? Naked? Naked Princess! Naked Princess!
Naked Princess! Exposure! Yes! Entry for Kanata
Hime! Okay, it's the princess. I'll do my best.
All of these princesses look like they're powerful. We're all in a team now.
Why are we together?A
princess from a neighboring country has arrived.Let
's protect the neighboring
princess.Hello, princess.Hello, princess.Princesses, we
have to take a look at each other's faces.
Hmm, thank you very much.
The meeting between the stinky princesses has begun.
Who will write the book? Thank you, please,
please. It's the same,
after all. Yes, it's true. Let's
have that meaningful battle. We both
agree.  Let's go without doing anything. Don't
run slowly. That's
right. I could do my best, but I've never run in my
life. I guess I've
been living in a car all my life, but only once.  I've
never run before, so what kind of life is it like? Don't
run, it's seriously impossible. That's right, don't run, the princess is the strongest in our country. So
please, no, that's not the case.
Logically speaking, she's the strongest.She's so weak, yet
she's such a weak princess, but she's definitely the weakest.It's like she'll
crush me.Okay, first of all,
let's hear from the Red Team.The Red Team's Ehi is played by Tokoyami Toma, who plays the
cavalry role.  That's Shion-tan,
and it's dark blue, and it's fluffy, and
it's Moko-chan, so there are four of us here, and
Fuwamoko is one of those two, so
yes, yes, thank you very much,
please, thank you
very much.  So, what do you think? I
'm enthusiastic, I'll do my best, I'll
do my best, I'll practice till the end. That's right, I'll
do my best. I usually go to bed at 9 o'clock, but I practiced until 1 o'clock. No, it's
true. I actually
go to sleep at 9 o'clock or 10 o'clock on days when I don't have anything to do.  Eh, that's
great, so you got up really early. That's right. I'm sure you'll do your
best. No, no, let's do our best. It's okay. It's okay. We'll do our best. We'll
do our best. I'd like to go to the white team.
Yes, the white team can you hear me? I
can hear you.  So, I'd like to start by introducing the players. Ehiya ga Ame Kanata hai hai ahi It's Nei desu.
There's someone I don't know who Nedo is. It's Princess. I'm Hazu-chan, I'm Hazu-chan, I'm Kai-
ha-i-i-a
-hi, and I'm Nanamu.
Okay, so what do you think?
I don't have much enthusiasm, but those knights
will protect me, so I
think it's okay. I
'm a guardian princess, so I
want to protect three princesses this time.  Thank you very much,
Ehime.Hasui, so cute Azuki, and so
cute Mu-
senpai.Are you okay?I'm like Ao.No, I have a senior too.So,
please do your best in the zaru performance.Fuifui, that
's it.Finally, the wooden group.
I would like to go to the Kigumi, the Kigumi is Hini, the
Iris cavalry is the Summer Color Festival, and the knight
is Hajime Ririka, and the Hajime Ririka Festival.Okay,
so what do you think?Hatsuhime, how is it going today?
Ahime is established.  I'm going to show everyone how the princess plays with her
wonderful cooperation with the beneficial knights. She's
amazing. She's the fastest. She's already the fastest.
She won first
place. She won first place. She won first place.  I want it,
right Princess? Yes, I'm the true princess. Yes, I
have a fever. Please
do your best. Yes, thank you.
Please do your best. Please also enter. Yes,
yes, yes, then this is it. It will
start as soon as the entries are finished.
Let's go.  Let's go to the wall
Yes, yes, yes, it looks like it's okay, I'm full of motivation.
Subaru is also getting nervous.
In other words, I'm not a princess,
but I'm a princess. But
after all, everyone is working really hard.  I've
been practicing. This is
nice. I'm so
excited to see if I can make it. Wow, stubbornness is the
first step. Well then, next time,
uhm. Hey, I'll call out the name of the person on board.
Carrion
Carrion Kineo cake
Okay, I worked hard and was nervous It
was a ride Did you understand the ride?
Member name Seisen He is my senior, my senpai Oh Okay, my senpai,
Yuko English Sorry, I'm
also very reliable Good
time, move, move.  I'm going to stop when my name is called,
so if you say stop name,
say stop name, say it, stop name, say stop name.
Next, let's all climb up, now Mumui-chan,
Kazamakakore, Azusan, no, Mume-chan,
Kazamah, this is Achanzu-chan, no, Mui-chan,
okay, ooh, ona, nasuo, ok, ooh, ona, no, taku no taku,
ah,
oh.  Even if it's just for a moment, I wonder if I
should ask you to do this.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You might have
waited to see if
you could figure it out. Okay, now all you can hear is my voice. I
see. I've waited and figured it out. Sorry.
Sorry, sorry,
answer what I'm making. Wait,
open the book. Hey, it's Luna. Oh no, it
's a possibility. Luna, Cana, Luna's
bond. As expected, Karuna.
Meat, uh, uh, lamb meat. Lamb kud, too.
Tonmutton, the latter's characteristic hamburger is coming.
Please cut the characteristic hamburger, beef, potatoes, and carrots on a cutting board and grill them on the griddle.
But then, that's nice.
Meat not cut. Meat not cut.
I ate this, okay, okay,
so the next one is red, red, yellow, red, red, yellow from Hatena Left Up.
If I kill all three of them,
Nao,
Oooo
, let's go, ooooo, it's too funny.
Oo Fao, go
nice, quick, yes, yes,
yes, yes, let's
fight! Let's fight, fight, let's
go!  Kamawan
Chan I
want to run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, nice, nice, dangerous, dangerous, nice, nice, nice.
Kurusokomu Chanmu Chanmu No, I'm glad, it was fun, Senpai. You looked lonely. If you fail, the next problem will probably take a lot of time. Hey, you're 3 seconds behind the 3rd place you practiced. Missed the jump jump punch.
No, I'm back. I'm back. I'm
too nice. I'm with you all at the contestants. I found out that it's Princess Hatosama from
Iromono and
Unsa.
It's true. I think I'm about to go crazy. Stop.
I would like to interview the person who was TMT. Can you
all hear me? No, I can't hear you.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
By the way, knight Shion.  Tando:
Well, I tried it, and we really practiced and
practiced.The four of us got together.Yes,
and it turned out to be a result.I'm really
happy, no, I'm glad.1 And it was
really quick, really
fast.  Yes, it was
really
fast. That topic was Subaru after all
. Yes, yes, I was making something like that. That's why. I'm
curious what everyone was making. That's right. I'm
sure you'll want to check out the archive.  I
hope you can see it. So,
congratulations. Congratulations!
[Music] Let's do our best
in the last two. We'll do our
best and go to the white team.
Now, let's talk about the white team.  I'd like to ask you,
but yes, yes, yes, how was it? Well, I don't know how sloppy it was.
But at the end,
when I was about to defeat Anocha, I
got caught in a careless descent. It
seems like something between Wave and Wave is a parent-fold.  But actually, it looks like I got caught in it. I'll
leave it to you to do the pinching, so that's
why I'm here. Wow, I'm glad I came in 2nd place. Wow,
that's amazing. Well, I lost it. I did my best. There was an
accident, but I was still here.  I was
able to get in.
Who was the question? Who appeared? It
was Luna. Ah, Luna Luna, here too.
Kanaluna's bond was pinkish, so I
was wondering if it was Aku-tan,
but I already believe in Kanaluna's bond.
Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Next, I would like to talk to the Kigumi. How
was your experience?  Oh, I'm so frustrated
. I was trying so hard, but at the end I was
catching up. It was really amazing. I was
catching up. I was trying to guess my problem. I
made a lot of mistakes. I
just saw how hard Mom was trying.  Yes, we did our best until the very end of the sports day.There
is meaning in all of us putting in our best effort and doing our best.Of course, let's
all run until the very end, aiming even higher.Mom, you
are beautiful.Do your best,
Tsuyoshiao.  What was it? Lala and Ayappa.
It's Lapros. I showed it to you a few times. It was porridge at the end. It
was porridge-senpai. It was definitely difficult.
How did you make the
porridge? Mom, I'll check the archives later.
Good luck, good luck,
nice job.
Nice job. Well, let's interrupt for a moment. Yes, let's take a look at the scores for the Koshi race. I do
n't want to see it. I don't want to see it. I want to see it.
30 points for the white team.  20 points Yellow group
will get 10 points, Red group has
caught up a bit, but maybe the
Red group is coming, are they coming? I don't know yet.
Yes, it seems like it's still there. I still do
n't know. So let's move on to the next
competition winter race. It's
dangerous.  Hey, I understand, I
won't say that, but
hey, I'm
fine. It's a distant meaning, okay.
Yes, I'll move on. It's fine again. Uh,
where was
it? I was flying around on my own.
Ah, I'm going home on my own.  Niseira, welcome back,
everyone, I'm home. I'm home, and my
senior is doing some amazing cooking. It
was really quick. It was really quick. What was the book?
What did you make? It was lamb that made me understand.
Ram lamb lamb.
Ramji was Kataram. Sheep lamb.
Lamb grilled lamb.  I'm sorry for the inconvenience, but that's what you're
used to.Hamburger steak.I made
fun of it because it was so hot during practice.It's going to be tomorrow.
Before the announcement was made, the contestants were
surprised by the first technique that was so obvious that it was easy to understand.
That's
fine, right? I
entered the book and got a book, so I opened the book, chose whether I was the
overall winner or the number of white runners, and then I came, came,
came, came, came, came.
Hey, are you okay? Let's right-click.
Ah, in the entry list, it's number 8.
What layer is Ame-chan in when it says "I'm mine?" It seems
like it's somewhere in the middle. I
remember, it's where the leader is. Stop.  Chan 5th layer
Eye 5 No. 5 5th founder Hey, my chest is all over the place.
Chan is 33 Okay, I see. I
see. Are you able to enter with this? It's done, it's done, it's done. It's good to say,
oh,
oh.  Wow, today's character contact is shaky. What's
going on? It
's okay, I can do it. Don't be weak. I'll do my best.
Can I go? Ohanka, it's okay, it's okay. It's okay, it's okay. It's okay. It's
okay.
[Music]
have ah ah ah.  I've made an entry,
but it's 9, it's 9,
Nona, ah
,
ah, okay,
NNo
bebeJustJust
, oh, nice, nice, nice, oh,
nice, oh, good job, good job, nice, nice,
oh, yeah,
this big guy is going to dive into this water.
It's the order of the contestants.Yes, the first layer is the first layer.Yes,
Nerisa.The next is chocolate.Teacher, the
third layer is Mumeha.The fourth layer is Noel.The
leader is yes, and the fifth layer is Ameha.The
sixth layer is
Kaela.The seventh layer is.  Last but not least,
I feel like people who are familiar with Minecraft and are familiar with it are coming in. It's
true. I feel like I'm going to liven it up.
Yes, it looks like it's coming. I heard everyone from the white team. Yes, what do you think?
Then, who should I choose? Well, then, Iroha. When I
noticed that I was anchoring, I
became the anchor, but I'm sure the wind moves fast, so I'll manage.
Trust me.  I
want to do my best, no, it's great, I'll do my best.Then, the
white team, please try to take first place.I want you to do your best.Do your
best.I'll do my best.Thank you for your hard work.I'll do my
best.Okay,
then.Finally, group Yaberi-san.  I just
came back from picking flowers for a long time.Welcome home.You're coming
home.I was just about to go home.When Nerisa
-chan was looking confused, I heard her
say ``open book.''I did
n't get it.That's an
embarrassing response.''  That's right, let's do our best.
Wow, this is the luck of the water
. If you're at the bottom at first, you'll be able to go back.
That's right. Let's do our best, try our best. Let's try our best. Let's try our best. That's right.  Oh, I fell, I'm doing my best
here. The water is so bad, it's so
bad.
Wow, I'm so nervous. I've been practicing, so I'm not sure. It's
a little scary. I'm starting to get mentally ill. It's
okay, it's okay, Medi.
Do your best, Medi, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, even though you're in prison today, it's okay, I'll remember and do my
best, it's okay, I'm going to
try my best, I'm really trying my best, I'm
sure of it, it's the best, light last.  Nene, it
's the end with a smile, right? Now that this is over, let's
go eat some delicious meat. I was
talking to Choco, and I was talking to Azuki and Choco. Let's
do our best, meat, meat, shabu-shabu. Let's do our best, Go Go Go-san, do your best, do your best.  Do
your best, try your best, try your
best, let's calm down Come on, I'll be waiting for you Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, it's nice, nice, catch, nice catch, Nike nice, bread, nice, trap, oh wow, you're getting better.
It's okay, it's okay, it's a
fight against chocolate. Stay calm, you're good at it, you're the best. There are
times like that, there are times like
that, there are times like that, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay.  It's okay, it's okay, it's not at all, it's
okay, it's okay, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
wait here, help me. I don't know what to do anymore, ah, be stubborn.
Oh, wait, this bread, bread, right,
left, left. Good luck, stubborn, hey, I'm sorry.
Do your best,
do your best, do your best Yo-chan, do
your best, do your best [Music] It's okay, it's okay, do your best, it's okay.  Let's
run, but
it's a quick turnaround. It's fast, it's fast. It feels good. It feels good. It's a good shot. Let's do
our best. Give it up! It's bad. First of all, we can go, we can go, we can
go. We can do our best, Kara-chan.
[Applause]
Kaeru-san, we can do our best. It's a steady effort.  I'm
sorry, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to be
sucked in this kind of thing,
nice nice, good, do my best, do my best,
do my best, and I'm okay
with this feeling like you'll be beaten.  I'll
give you a good punch, it's okay, my husband.
Yes, try your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best. Hello, Iroha, good. It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
Yo, ok,
ok, oh, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.  Good
luck, do your best, it's
all over.
Nice, you're
strong. You're strong, you're strong.
Hey, I forgot to eat.
No problem, problem. It's
okay. I'm hungry. I'm hungry. Ah, I'm
hungry. When you're done.  Let's eat a lot, yeah, yeah, nice run, nice run, nice run.  I
want to eat, I'm
going to
eat it, let's all
eat together, let's all eat shabu-shabu, shabu-shabu, it's beautiful, it's cute, it's cute, it's soothing, it's cute, let's go, let's go shabu-shabu,
leave it to me.  Give it to me, let's
leave it all to the chocolate Choco-sensei chooses is berry Good,
super nice Yeah,
leave it to me, leave it to me
Ai, but I tried really hard, please, I did my best, I did my best, tao,
please, I'll interview you, Ao, white and white, you did your best, ne, you
did your best, it was
good, you did your best.
Okay, let's listen to Irohan, who will be the anchor, one more time. Yeah,
how was it? From the beginning to the end, it's
okay. Everything was okay. We worked as a team. We got along. It's
okay. It's okay. It's okay. The result.
There were times when I was passed and overtaken,
but I was able to finish in second place.It was a nice fight.Thank you for your hard
work.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your
hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Are you
making good use of it?You're making good use of it.Yoyoyo
Certification How long are you on vacation?No, this is good.Here
you go!Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.You did it.You did it!
It was
amazing, no, it was really good. It made
everyone cry
. Some of them were crying. They were so
sensitive. It was so good.
No, I'm in 2nd place. I'm in 2nd place. I
thought I could get it. I tried my best.  I
tried my best, I tried my best, and to be honest, at
first I was just having fun, and I was
just trying to do my best, but I didn't expect it to happen.I
didn't know until the end.That's why I'm going to perform this ceremony for
all of you.  Please gather in front of the school.The
first person to go
to the front
is the student.Okay, there
was a wall.I was surprised.I'm sorry.We were
sealed away.It
was a little closed in this school right now.  My throat is
rattling, yes, it's all white, it's
beautiful,
so
what are we practicing for?
It's a big lump of this big boy, after all, I feel like I ca
n't lose in a certain tonality.  So, the
colors are very different,
right?
Look at the volka, look at the volka, everyone is lined up
holding a lot of volka bread.
It's okay if I take it. I said
yes, and the
ceremony begins. How
was it, Moimi? I had no idea what was going to happen this year or anything like that.
But yeah, everyone was working together really well,
working hard, and it was a close battle every year.  Well, I
thought it was really worth watching and it was amazing. Well, yeah,
it's true. There was a drama in each of them,
or rather, there was a
drama. I think it was a drama, including the practice,
but I thought it was amazing.  I'm
not here, so Mio-chan just talked to me, so I'm
coming.
That's a good line up. After all, you're the one who said it. You're strong. Taka-chan's remodeled mother is amazing. It all calmed down all at once. I feel like I'm in trouble.  I
'm scared. It doesn't seem like it's okay. It's okay.
So, everyone, can you hear our voices? Can you hear us?
Yes, we can hear you.  There
were so many voice chat moves, but I would
like to say a few words to everyone who supported Nechan, A-chan, and Nodo-chan.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you, thank you, thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much for this year.
Your hard work and individuality are
overflowing, and it's the three organizers.
We all worked hard.  Thank you
very much for the
book. Thank you
very much for
your cooperation. Thank you very much for your cooperation. I hope it
was fun for all three of you to participate.
So please do your best until the end.Thank
you very much.Thank
you very much,
everyone.Then we will now begin the closing ceremony.First
of all, we will give a greeting from the club.We will have a
greeting from Ms. Samiko, the chairperson of the Sports Day Committee.
Please, yes, no, everyone at this sports day, was it fun?
It was fun, it was
fun, it was fun, it
was fun, it was really good, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for being so busy every year.  It's
Hololive,
but even so, I was so moved by how
everyone gathered together, everyone
taking the initiative to call out to each other and helping each other.
Thank you very much for your cooperation. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much for this. I would appreciate it if you could
take this opportunity to thank me
for the newcomers, the
members of En and Kari, etc.  I think it would be really great if we could have
more interactions with each other in the future and make the holo live even more exciting,
so I look
forward to your continued support.  Thank you very much for
participating, and you did a great job.
Yes, everyone is great, and we're
finishing this year as well. Thank you,
thank you
. Yes, next Subaru, and now Subaru. Hey, I'll
keep in touch with you. The
various teams.  I've seen all the different sides
of the team, and I think all the teams are working hard, and I
think we'll see some results this time, but
one big thing is that we all worked hard together like this.  I
think it will become a treasure, so I
hope you can make use of our bond in the future. It
was really fun to watch. Thank
you, thank you,
thank you.
Senkyu Senkyu Yes,
then finally I would like to announce the general benefits.The
announcement of the bonuses that I have received will be in the order of the number 1, then the
number 100, and finally the number 10.  I'd
like to come. Well
then, Mr. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day executive committee,
please announce the scores. Please. Yes, I'll
start by announcing number 1. Yes, then please
go ahead. I can see here. Red team is 8. White team
is.  8 Hey, I want to wait and see Yellow, but what the heck,
it's on stream right now, but there's still a long line of people, so let's
go ahead and get the 100.
Yes, here's the 100 box. That's right,
please. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, I do
n't know, it's all here, it
's all about 100, please, please, it's so bad
, no, I can't believe I'm going to go at the end, everyone, please, please, please, I
'll announce about 10 at the end.
8 White is
38 Yellow is 106 It was
a little more I
can't do it I'm
frustrated I know
but
raoraoraora oh friendly freeze freeze
Friendly and the 2nd place was 138 points
and the white group, but the 3rd place was the wood group with 106 points.
Well done, everyone, well done,
well done, well
done, well done, everyone, well done, well done. When will we
give out the awards? Yes, that's right, there will be an awards ceremony this time. Well done
everyone. I'll give the yellow group the
medals.  This is Geo.Okay, first of
all, let's talk about the representatives of the players and teachers from the yellow group.Hasbechanbe-
chan, please come to the front.Come to the
front.Come and
win.Has.Now then, where's the 3rd place medal?
How's the bread?
Congratulations on
that! It
's on everyone. It's on everyone. It's on everyone. It's on
everyone. It's on everyone's neck.
It's Jatamo-kun, and I'm Geo, who won a silver medal for the white team. Chan-
chan went there, so I'm looking
forward to it.
But I'm so excited, it's the Sua-chan medal. Congratulations
to the white team. I heard it's daring.
Congratulations on your medal.Congratulations on
your medal.Congratulations on your medal.Thank
you very much.Congratulations on the
gold medal for the red team.I
want to see a big medal.Thank you very much and congratulations on your medal.
[Applause]
Hey,
hey, this is the
king. This is the lie
. This is the lie. It
disappeared so quickly. Even
though there were so many diamonds, they became beautiful in an instant.
Well then, I would like to say
that I would
like to say that Hololive Sports Festival 2023 is a negative influence.Thank you
very much.  Let's
put it on that
table in the middle over there.Yes, please, yes, yes, yes, yes, it's okay, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, it's a
game where you can't go back.That's wrong.Let's
line up in the top right corner.Let's line up and line up.Are you going
this way?  I'm going in here too, yeah, I'm
going in here too, on
Hey, can you see me? Hey, I'm back! Hey,
where are you all? Ah, that's it, everyone! Hey, we're
still not in time. We
won, sorely, lily, I've been waiting for a
while.  Wait,
wait a minute, it stinks, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. It's okay
there. Yes, it hasn't arrived yet.
It's on us too. It's amazing, it's on us too. Oh, it's on us
too. I'm so happy. It's
gone once.  That's why I don't have a medal, but it's
true, I'm hiding
It's
true, it's not like that
[Music]
Emiko won't get mad if I do it, I don't have it anymore, it's
okay It's
definitely like that
Medal  I ca
n't say that, I can't give it to you. Wait a minute, Mio-
senpai. Mio-senpai will answer that for you. Thank you. I was
able to touch it. I'm glad I did it. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you
. Hey, everyone. Hey, everyone. That thing in front of me.  Wait
a minute, I don't know where to look at that
guy. Should I look at Koro-san?
Ro-san is flying like I'm looking at him. Ro-san is flying,
so I guess I should look at the camera. It's
really in front of me. It's the cameraman. The
cameraman is here, here, here, here.  Here, there,
here, there, there's that, there's that, there's that
cameraman.Okay,
everyone.Can you see it?I
'm taking a photo.The photo is taken very close to Mr. Merle and Towa.I'm
sure he's hugging me.Let
's go.Yes.
[Music]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, who threw it? Who
threw it just now? Who threw it this year? Just happened to throw it. I
took it. Everybody is
throwing something. They're throwing it again. Hey, hey,
don't throw away your trash. Take your trash home with you.
Look.
Thank you very much for coming to
see me. To all the listeners who watched the show,
and to all the management staff who helped out behind the scenes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank
you very much. That's it. Hololive
Grand Sports Day 2023 and above will be the end.
Yes, see you again, everyone. I
'm going to Deotsu Hololive. Yes, yes. Yes, I'm
going. Otsu Hololive. Oholive
[Music]
Live!
Bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye
[laughter]
[music]
oh
everytheSLE
[music]
[clap]
[laughing]
[music]
need
byby
[music]
by
[music]  ]
[Music]
[Music
] [Music]
[Music]
DET