[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
the song
it's
six a.m wake up we're going to the okay
good morning hello
there's cake balloons welcome we're
celebrating do you guys know what we're
celebrating
[Music]
three year anniversary everybody
yeah we sound like kids
we basically are three years old
that is the terrible twos
oh God
can we walk yet
um I think the girls can walk right
the most like chaotic destroy everything
age
probably times
and nasty yeah
nasty gotta have kleenex wet wipes on on
your person at uh 24 seconds
welcome everybody to what I like to call
um super
Polo Extravaganza whoa quiz money island
of magic and
Etc
I worked on a special
especially to be teleported to my
specialist
here we go teleporting
three
two I'm gonna snap my fingers and we'll
go one
welcome I am the extravagant billionaire
Maury Calliope who's no longer the The
Apprentice of the Grim Reaper but rather
a rich entrepreneur welcome to my
friends
don't worry about it it doesn't matter
can we do anything here can we bit a dig
like a giant hole I mean can we make a
sand castle all right hold your horses
for a minute there ladies let's let's
not get too drastic
[Music]
bikini
sponsored by Kaleo pimori it sure is
it's got all my money
the one and only the entrepreneur of all
time
so I am expecting a real life payout
next time I meet you IRL yeah I'm glad
that you mentioned that contestant
takanasi Kiara um I have some actual
prizes to award you depending upon how
much money you get at my Island are you
ready
I mean we'll we'll see how we feel at
the end but here are some of the
illustrious oh my God
it's okay you get used to it
some of the illustrious prizes that you
can win on Holo money Island
for zero dollars you can get a hug from
worry
a hundred dollars
I don't like natto can I get a different
one too bad that's the prize
I collect shirts of Polo members awesome
well hopefully you can get one it's not
just the shirt it's old shirts so she's
fine she's worn it even better I have a
really old shirt of Subaru that has been
washed a million times so you can barely
see what it was before I have a question
Miss Miss Callie's what's up uh if we
get more than the amount do we get all
the previous prizes do we have to get
the exact amount nah you gotta make a
purchase this is like a lot
[Music]
okay stop that you gotta buy from right
wait this is the Golden State the one
that we ate with the gold on top correct
does that mean if we get 365 one two
three four five six seven eight
365 million dollars we we get to have a
year of Yahoo
we're gonna have to play the quiz maybe
three million times but you know what
whatever works for you that's the prize
okay I'm ready I feel like Yago would
potentially spend a day with us if we
nicely asked and and like had a good
reason for it yeah
I feel like we have a chance too but
then like it never worked out
I have a handle over control I have I
have control over yoga right now
shut your mouth shut up
all right let's go get ready for holo
money Island now in order to get started
um we need to decide in order of who
goes first because obviously whoever
goes first has an advantage I'm thinking
of a number between one and ten
nine
sorry
girl what is it
not nine okay all right Kiara what is it
everybody has to guess what the number
is okay
you know
3.3333333 a whole number okay all right
the answer is
the answer was six
ow who was closest to six it was closest
[Music]
nine what's that seven
um no one everyone said three and four
and three point three and nine so three
four is as close as 10 right yeah I
guess four yeah four
I said four so Ahmed Kiara
[Music]
a category and uh an amount of money
uh collabs for let's go in the middle
300. all right collapse 300. oh my God
I'm the sound board person all right
the labs collabs 300.
all right what game did Bay and Iris
play together that began their unhappy
marriage okay okay so I get the answer
first yes eight seven six Minecraft all
right oh survey says she knows Minecraft
she's pretty good I don't know does that
mean I get to go again no no we just
collected money all righty okay back to
the boys
that question gone it's gone right I
have to block it out all right next up
okay Kiara
uh quotes
um
300 please quotes 300.
Bae said blank years old is ancient
Stars uh
[\h__\h] I don't know take a stab let's take
it educated yes 20 like from her POV
Maybe
not from my opinion but from her POV
maybe
20 to
get a sink like a baby
oh there was a timer there was a timer
29. the answer is 38.
oh wow
your old people out there I know it also
surprised me quite a bit what did they
do to her
I know it's strange the red squares
again I need to know the context
no money for me no money for Kiara this
time no that's okay it's okay I feel
like I will earn that much either
there's plenty of time to earn even more
money on Holo where'd you get this oh
these things anyway just don't worry
about it give you
uh all of the quiz questions are from
members
all right next up are they all about
bales
[Laughter]
I think I think a lot of deadbeats are
just also Bay fans but there are others
[Music]
[Laughter]
alrighty next up is Ina make your choice
yeah I'll go for
trivia 300. all right trivia 300.
everybody's going for that we're going
for the middle yeah
Ian member has a laptop named after a
bird
what a laptop
laptops
time's a ticket ah I'm gonna go with I'm
it no
no I hate that you chose this answer
this question because the answer the
answer is bae
there are other quests
it's not a coincidence if it happened
like how many times now three three
times believe me please in the future
when in doubt answer Bales okay I got it
I figured also that maybe the 300 ones
are all big well there's also that
possibility oh
double clicking Mouse girl it's your
turn wait what have you done what is the
just letters category what does that
mean it's a little weird it's hello
things that have to do with single
letters or double letters or triple
you'll understand if when if you and you
when you opened you see open uh okay
okay I'm gonna do trivia for 100. all
right trivia ones
slow it's steady alrighty 100.
what does the Second Law stand for oh
God
what do you mean the second law what
what
is
wonderful amazing humans wonderful
amazing humans is that your final answer
the good answer the answer is if it's y
I swear to God we are hype
hello
[Laughter]
yeah of course
sometimes you don't know I just I just
mistake which one is which wise which
but it's it's one of the original lies
okay
what what does the first one stand for
we're here ah we are here we are I know
we are hungry happy oh happy okay I
thought it was hungry because of cookies
I mean that is also one of one of the
laws I think there's a lot of them now
it keeps growing every single year and
there's like what like 11 12 now
but the way it's like uh phrased as like
the first and the second and so on makes
me think it's like you know the the
Testaments
the what
is
you're here
we're happy okay like okay I see yeah
[Music]
nice what is a valiant effort nice try
girl next up yeah yeah
next up I'ma give it another try
oh okay uh I'll take uh collabs for five
hundo whoa
there's just a lot of going for the big
ones a lot of things collabs for 500.
here we go now remember they get harder
the more expensive that they are so
let's go
she got this what was the name of the
ocean
I know this one yeah oh wow I didn't
even need to start the timer
it was the bitching kitchen
difficulty question when three of those
members are literally here that's not
true I could have gotten it right I
would have been like
the randomness of it all additionally
that was just one of the first collabs
of Halloween
memory it was a while ago yeah yeah yeah
would you say it was almost three years
ago
yeah
almost almost
just about now then I'm going to cover
that up collabs 500 next up is Kiara
okay I'm scared now so I'll go for out
of out of Interest out of curiosity I'll
go for just letters 100. all right
you're going for The Big Easy one here
we go just letters 100 some money out of
this yeah get a couple dollars
all right song collab with an animated
music video
aren't there plenty uh oh it's just
based on letters okay okay
[Music]
it always would be one letter yeah oh
then then one or two letters okay all
righty I'll give you that one I'll give
you that one the answer is indeed
category Works yes yes
a little confusing okay okay okay okay
okay I understand all righty 100 bucks
four
congrats on your 100 bucks
[Music]
buy so many cookies with that you can
buy more than one that's for sure
alrighty you can catch up with me no no
no don't look don't look at me don't
look don't look
[Music]
don't think about it bring the next one
bring the next one in what about this
let me reset the slideshow
we're fine
uh better kiss it better Mori kiss it
better all right now I just need to move
this red block over to here all right
next up we've got Hina
[Music]
okay
um
I'll do
just letters 200. no one wants to touch
total grass so far she's scared of me
there's too many episodes
sometimes
here we go
just letters 200. a perfect example of a
hit tweet
is that your final answer
yeah oh
I think
I think this is correct it might be the
right answer
after all
congrats on the 200 bucks
next up
[Music]
see how we've we're clearing the board
so far we're making good time I think
we're making good time I think so too I
think so too we're good in the time nice
alrighty so next up we've got era
give me uh can I get uh
for 100 please okay what what for a
hundred
co-lab for 100 please all right collabs
for 100. Here We Go
this Holo Series has had 34 guests thus
far oh my God
oh
what is the takanashi talk show that
I've just brain farted on
Hollow Taco
oh my God
talk show I mean she said it no she has
sustainable name
I
do know it I do know it
foreign
[Laughter]
it's all right you'll get them next time
no worries yeah I can get them next time
yeah yeah yeah I know you know it though
I know you I did know it look at the
next one everybody has weird brain
moments yeah
all right so true next next cue goes to
Amit
I'll do collabs for 400.
going for collabs
all righty here we go collapse 400 in
the myth Breakers ttrpg what was you'll
be all right's roommate's name oh geez
[Music]
here's the hint you will be all right
really hard
and I don't know this one I think
alrighty I'll just have to say you'll be
fine you'll be making yourself a hint
though by saying talk show that was
already the hint
s
but I was right though
with the hint yeah do I get a hint yes
the hint is that it's similar to you'll
be all right
yeah I don't know all right the answer
is
need a friend
okay we're up in the group party yeah
and it didn't yes it did and it showed
up again
that's why it's a high level question
400. show me it has the money yeah she's
got a crisp to Handy you know that's not
that's not chump change right
go ahead and collapse 400 cover up next
time let's go Kiowa
I'll go for quotes hundred quotes 100
I'm scared here we go
what did Maury say frequently in her
debut but stop shortly after
ah so easy
[Music]
final answer
[Laughter]
can we hear it again
I think I dropped a couple of keys yes
all right total of 200 bucks for
takanasi Kiara now
yeah big bucks this big boy books
already
hey
not doors
for 100 100 right no thanks wait usually
like in this type of game can't somebody
else guess the correct answer yeah no
but it you can buzz in you can buzz in
but we're not doing that this time
but maybe next time maybe next time we
will alrighty next uponnis
okay
um I'm just curious I'm gonna go for
holograph 200. all righty oh yeah I'm
curious what kind of questions maybe
you'll get lucky and get your own who
could say
in Ina's episode hold on a second Ina's
episode
she uses two moves to fight back what
are they oh no wonderful Taco kick and
then ah
okay
Pentacles
[Music]
too powerful
all right the answer is this is a gift
question to you raging Taco punch and
sorrowful time
there's no half rule sadly
yeah
it was for you but it's just that like
silver Taco King is so memorable you
know when you have like super ultra move
and then you have like a normal move you
know you just don't remember
[Music]
um you should remember your own moves
they also made me say Soulful Taco cake
so many times
lots of retakes huh wait something
little graph questions are all like
concerning one of us maybe maybe
true it just might be
all right so I can at least get one cent
I feel really bad for you you know so
you know what let me open up my
billionaire pocket and give you a sense
there you go
do you want a scent as well
uh no okay yeah that's what I thought
all right okay now it's actually
centered beautiful can you smell weird
yeah all right
sorry what was that
you're saying something about the way
I'm centering my board
wait 100 was that 200 yep the 100 ones
alrighty that's all next up gura
time to get some money Let's do let's do
a trivia for 400. all right
400. let's go and say a prayer for my
brain all right who in myth has the most
outfits 3D Maury
hold on hold on look at the question
3D and infinity
[Applause]
yeah and one piece
[Music]
outfits too yes
[Applause]
all of them over and over again
oh those are unofficials
well I thought I thought the only
official ones are like company made and
the other ones are unofficial I mean I
meant like like they had reveals and
stuff yeah no which is which is like
objection all of them I'm trying to
fight you fight you did I turn objection
I tried to find you already
know something Sans
but you know that then you were trying
to hint uh give her a hint Cali and this
question should be answerable without a
hint but so therefore in order to be
able to do that the questions phrasing
in the first place should be more
obvious as to what it's trying to you're
not making a difference
you're not making sense
[Music]
so I think it's the best outcome
comedically
[Laughter]
well it was a valiant attempt and again
that was a short question
[Music]
such an easy question
further down oh next is me
um
I'll be back next okay
um I'll take quotes for 400. all righty
Kiara said that she eats 53 of these a
day during myth's first collab
three I remember this I remember this
uh um chicken nuggets
the answer is chicken nuggets
chicken nuggets one step closer to
yako's Freedom
what oh no I mean he's fine don't worry
about it
don't worry about it looking real Rich
over here on me
[Music]
congratulations stuff thank you thank
you wow I'll buy this island
to make her lose money
she's not a pinata
I'm sure she would love to be one
that would be cool actually let me try
I mean it wasn't that one of the one of
the goals of um
back off
because I have nothing to do with this
violence
it was worth an attempt
you ladies behave yourselves on my
Island I didn't do anything all right
all right I didn't do anything either it
was my hands not me
um your next Kiara choose a question
um you said hologram 100 diseases
all right hologram 100 here we go
the question is
in Cali's episode who does she own
summon as a distraction
oh I watched the episode
but I don't think I remember
how was everyone's memory so bad
it's literally so obvious she's in it
from most of the episode
yes the answer is
yeah
they get harder from here
it was not bait shut up Chet shut your
mouth I don't know what you're talking
about
no you haven't stop trying to play on
their sympathies
[Laughter]
I I see I see your true colors kiwawa I
see them
all right all 100 questions are gone
next I wonder you know let's go
um
I'll go for just letters
500. all right just letters 500 here we
go
just letters 500 put together a bunch of
singing holos to form a unit this is
their abbreviation
oh
well I wonder if I ever would say oh put
together okay a bunch of singing holos
to form a unit
what is their abbreviation I'm just
thinking
lunch a bunch of a whole lot of them
a punch
is it a specific one or just it's a
specific one
but it's a whole lot of them it's a lot
let me see
is this I feel like she should get this
right
what's your answer
let me see
the answer is BJ
[Music]
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
everyone says blue Journey look at every
JP member's [\h__\h] Twitter right now it
says AJ
go back to the question please
a question
what
shouldn't it be phrased put a bunch of
whole singing members blah blah together
to form a concert not a unit they are
unique baby but no there's like units
within the blue Journey concerts but
they are a unitard it is the unit it is
blue Journey a con a concert name or
they're doing more than just that they
aren't it's not just a one-off thing
they are a group
why BJ I don't get it that's what I said
which is because yeah like one or two
letters so it's gotta be something short
all of you saying really get mad at the
deadbeats because they're the ones that
came up with these [\h__\h] questions
[Music]
what is the definition of a unit they
are doing activities together as a group
has a group
too many possibles yeah the phrases yeah
I mean it's like okay fans Etc
yeah get ready for the next stream
oh boy
[Music]
very scared
I hope you prepared that game show real
good
I'm getting like I'm getting like
flashbacks to our 3D showcases where
Cali was you know asking people to do
the worms yeah and you know I was like
and someone else was like oh get you
back for that just like that
same thing
what I'm gonna get a billionaire doesn't
seed
next up I was talking about this yeah
and never mind okay next yeah go next go
next I'll do trivia 200 wait it's not my
turn
hold your horses
I thought it was me
wait was it no it wasn't it no it's it's
no it's my turn
I don't know what's going on yeah
I'm gonna do billionaires game
oh let's do
a big one you can just say yeah right
it's good go big or go home oh 500.
for which one which one
which one 500 for trivia all right
trivia
here we go come on bring you can't do it
trivia 500. how many Holo en members
have just one stalking in their default
outfit and I mean one oh not a pair
is that a sock yeah sock I think I know
he answered is it like just one of one
color it has to be one only only one
okay like the person is just as if they
don't have another they don't have
anything else on the other leg it's just
on one leg oh okay one stopping
oh my God
[Laughter]
all right I just started this armor the
timer yeah who went who in there right
mine would only wear one stocking or one
sock anime girls
who would do that somebody with all the
time or very busy yeah I mean I mean
pretty pretty pretty cute
all right fine I think there's anybody
in maybe one in this right you know this
one
because you have a stocking and then
something else
oh
what's the final answer
visualize it
aha trying
I have no idea just throw out a number
what's a lucky number for today three
three is today oh the dancers three
that's a good one the answer is I would
say that's wrong it's four okay
[Applause]
oh
yep oh yeah four members today you got
close though
[Music]
pretty close
that's that's a what do you mean a half
member you get out of here
get your mouth Iris has two stockings
[Music]
alrighty yeah
there we go
so that was the Valiant attempt
that was a valiant attempt but not the
other Red Square copy paste
[\h__\h] all right uh next up all right oh
nice
next up
is oh
Amish
I'm losing it uh I'll take
um collabs for 200.
on my shoulder wait wait let me just
blow my nose
all right collapse uh 200. here we go
yeah
who holds
the record
for a long distance
[Music]
that recently changed very recently that
changed as far as I know only in Ian no
other members outside of the end only
Holo en
I would say probably Cali because you
have a lot of uh jump jump King long
voice chat sessions this one is a collab
I think we're counting like oh I have to
say who yes
uh who was the collab between maybe
Italian Bay
maybe but if it's new if it's recent
then
but but it is
the answer is I didn't even start the
tar the timer it doesn't even matter at
this point [\h__\h] the timer forget it Mori
and Sana Pokemon Diamond
because it was the shiny hunt that's
right Bijou and Kaila that's ID included
[Music]
yeah it was about 11 hours or so oh holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yep whoa it's not all Cali related shut
up they're non-cali questions there also
by the way keep this in mind
if they're all related to everybody else
too much then maybe it gives people an
unfair advantage
why wouldn't it be related to the
billionaire that owns this island
it's all about Kelly just Kelly that's
right just Mori for once I accept your
philosophy
yeah I mean this is the collab that's on
Kelly's Channel okay today yeah it makes
a little sense just a little bit yeah it
makes sense it can make sense it was a
nice try though nice try it Ahmed let me
go ahead and block off the question
collabs are gone no more collabs
no
[Laughter]
[Music]
next up single streams forever ah
um let me go for I'll fail this but I'll
go for it I'll go for quotes 500.
believe in yourself
hi
Brainiac please
oh this member once said I'm going to
pound you like my dad Browns me
what what
what is this person okay they should be
questions
imagine a GP member saying this
yeah
okay okay good luck
I mean Emma mention it's a lot of ground
pounding but I don't think she ever said
something like this
uh
uh can I get a hint if it's like someone
a mortgage
someone who's dying from laughing
off you're cutting off it's someone I
can't believe I can't remember
what the heck okay if it's someone here
it's not me I would remember that I'm a
that wouldn't say this Ina wouldn't say
this if it's between Kelly and Guru
is it the person that's literally
freaking out
hey
I think
wait but why would she say the person
doesn't remember it when then like yeah
logical conclusion is good up
true yeah look at that face look at that
face
okay
[Music]
it does sound something like something
that would fit in there
oh
no except that it's good for you
it might be good for me but might not be
good for my nose and my tummy not good
for the soul
not so good
it's yum it tastes like fancy cheese
auntie okay
but I imagine based on the smell of feet
that they might taste like
imagine the smell nothing sometimes
all right Inna your turn pick one yeah
[Music]
um I'll go for trivia 200. all right
trivia 200 here we go what could it be
but I don't remember
who started the trend of having a go
model their merch oh that's a good
question
I think I know this
that's interesting I want to know this I
know it's one of two oh
oh I know I know okay
senpai
[Music]
is there a giant plushie I remember the
answer
wait huh was it matzo
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no
it was not the first I was not the first
okay yeah
I mean give you the points if it really
is Matsuri Senpai but what the [\h__\h] yeah
it was like giant plushie and then it
was Coco senpai's tail
and then it was me
yeah I had no clue I mean I didn't know
the answer I just said well I'll give it
to you I'll give it to you because that
is the correct answer I'm supposing
everybody's saying it is correct yeah
401 Cent yeah wow interesting I had no
idea I'm gonna guess it figures it
wasn't like an En started thing but
um
has got to warm up on on your trivia
wow almost scammed a player there for
200. that's so good that's no good I
can't I can't be scamming my my
contestants
no I I will stand firm on some of the
decisions I've made on this show that
one that one I understand alrighty next
up we've got girl
yes letters for 400.
just letters for 400 Here We Go Go Get
It Go Get It When you struggle to answer
in jackbox what can save you
said this
the one
box when you struggle when you're
struggling to answer and check oh my God
it Jack box
ah what can save you I don't know Lori
said this
it's based on a letter it's based on a
couple letters
a couple letter yeah
[Music]
like how many letters it is like in
brown that's a good idea three letters
yeah for next time for next time when do
we come back to this magical Island
zero idea I have no idea alrighty you
will remember it the answer is
[Music]
I would not have remembered that I have
no idea it's been too long when was when
was that stream
when was it like two years ago
yeah I don't even know what I eat
breakfast
someone should do somebody should do
like a Holo trivia actual game show I
want to see that because we got some of
the fans here that are like oh remember
girl they're playing the the what was
the gamer playing in the break room
where we're guessing the letters and
stuff
[Music]
Wheel of Fortune yeah girls we got a uh
it's nine minutes left oh okay okay okay
speed progress
um
just letters 300. wait after girl is
oh wait it was gouda yeah
[Music]
let's go
who coined the term Ian's law
we did
yeah
it was in the curse I
oh wasn't it fauna or Bae I'll go with
uh fauna no no Bae I would say Bae I'll
say bae
for Ian's law not Ian's curse we're
clear on that right before yeah all
right because the answer is Mori
because we said curse okay Ian's law is
based on the principle that the more
people enter a collaboration the more
likely there is to be scuff is perfect
let's go right now I know right
it's pretty crazy well there was a
little okay
next up next the just letters 300.
and just letters three
pounds here we go just letters 300.
an abbreviation for an angel
[Music]
it could have been both but oh my God
that's all right let's go I was thinking
honestly the first thing I thought was
TNT
close close okay that would have been a
nice trick question but I'm not that
evil all right let's return okay
hold on I have to copy paste you guys
are too quick for my red squares all
right let's choose
um
okay holograph 500. okay
500. what is the Phoenix Burger order
read out loud in Kiara's episode
I couldn't I couldn't even do that yes
you could you said
um can I get number nine
weren't you just dissing enough for not
remembering the names of her attacks
yeah but that's really really really
long it wasn't that long
thank God I didn't get it yeah that was
my answer would have been embarrassed
can I get a number nine the answer is do
double cheese Phoenix burgers with extra
virgin oil and no whipped cream
[Laughter]
500 answer
no Mark the money worth the money
money uh holographer which one is mine
Cali
[Applause]
uh we're 400 please here we go isn't
there gonna be one left over there is a
final Hollow money at the end but for
now all right here we go or any of you
can buzz in to answer it all right okay
here we go 400 pellegra
in ama's episode oh sorry Flair requests
a certain item
[Music]
magnifying glass okay yeah that's a good
guess all right
all righty the answer is what is a
magnifying sauce
[Laughter]
about other people but these are even
our own and nobody remembers I
remembered most of mine I only know mine
because I all right gonna give me the
next answer then okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay only if you split your winnings
with me
all right I'll buy you something you're
ready well it looks like uh last
question goes to AME 300.
endurance episode the members created a
Holo centipede who was in it you don't
need to know the order oh
um oh oh dear I thought you're gonna
help me out here
um okay tell me if I'm wrong Marine
what is that what is that
what is that to counter
uh
hahaha
oh oh
okay quacking randomly okay I can't
guarantee that somebody was in there
I sent some files another bird another
bird okay um I honestly don't know I
just thought this was funny
[Music]
did she have
okay I'm gonna have to what
um
part of her own centipede
correct I recommend I I asked for it
oh you're the one of course of course it
wasn't originally
all right well I'll guess one now I know
Subaru I'll just say Subaru marine
and uh yes
[Music]
all right all right well it was it was a
valiant attempt all of the whole board
is cleared out now except for final Holo
money oh okay if you know the answer say
your name okay to buzz in okay fast all
right okay here we go final Hollow money
and this one is worth this one is worth
a million bucks
whoa boy it's worth a lot of money here
we go final hole of money okay
here we go topic Council risks okay
how many times did hope descend in her
debut stream not including the MV
Wawa chiarius just because I don't know
so I'll just attempt how about
six times
[Music]
you know what's your answer three
okay any other answers
uh two okay good uh yeah
three I can't do this one pick the same
one
the answer is three times
[Music]
I'm not letting him go
I'm not letting you okay
as a very last bonus question how about
I throw a random
trivia to everyone okay and she's gonna
give us money but gotta be quick because
we have one okay who first coined the
term miago
I know it's about it
I need to say how much but okay
[Music]
congrats guys this is not the end we are
still doing four more collabs Ryan wow
four more yeah
will there be a delay
Oh by Maury merchandise
yeah
by the more emerge oh it's cool there's
a rocker
is what they decided to name it so I
guess if you're not a rapper I can't buy
it
I guess I can't buy it oh you can be a
rapper but you guys can follow your
dreams yeah oh oh why do you guys get
your tongue
in a way yeah get them
we'll see bye