[Music]
for Life English worldwide opinion poll
part two yeah
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
first three let's have you guys
introduce yourselves so firstly
I'll start yeah oh my God this video is
so good
[Music]
yeah I will get all the answers and all
the questions right because I I also got
them right last time when I was watching
me and now leave it to fauna oh
my whole life English Council we're on a
team right it's a team so as long as you
have Kiara we'll win
we have to decide together yeah
and I Believe in Us okay
you're next
[Music]
this is Oro crony from Hollow live
English Council and I have high
confidence that you will win because we
know us better than anyone else
in in Hall of life right yeah
thank you so much
yeah yeah and
it's me hello I'm nanashi
I also have confidence we will win
because if we get stuff wrong it's not
really wrong
we know ourselves the most true exactly
um
hi today we'll be looking at the answers
from part two of the whole live English
word opinion poll we also be re-wazing
more new information about whole life
English first concert connect the word
near the end of this blog
[Laughter]
this program we look forward to it
[Music]
and we are gonna to take a look at the
results I'd like to ask you all what
kind of implications do you think your
fans have about you
[Music]
[Applause]
you Mommy
oh yeah
yeah the others I don't remember anymore
but I think I think I think people see
me as a boss boss or or Communicator
yeah that's right that's right like a
leader yeah
I have kfp and also I like
collaborations often yeah
what about you girls what's the image of
you girls what do you think I think
everyone thinks I'm super smart oh
[Music]
thanks guys for helping me chicken yeah
yeah you're cute but sometimes your art
Thug I find I find sometimes um a little
bit terrifying
you should see them as friends your
friends okay okay
[Music]
they can be your friends too oh okay I
will try
perfect I think yeah you know there's a
whole stick about being perfect because
it's a stick not real I mean it's a
stick because it's so real you know okay
it's so real that it's not even funny
um I guess there's
some people think that I'm clumsy which
is not true I never make mistakes
I I remember you're being clumsy but are
you are you actually clumsy yeah I don't
think so but
people seem to have weird Impressions
[Music]
they're weird they're always weird
okay
mommy yeah
extremely
popular mom she's so cute too
she's so sweet
her voice would put you to sleep yeah
that's why people vote for Mommy
[Music]
whole life English word of opinion
pulper too it's okay are you ready for
it yes
yes Starts Now
[Music]
we're singing We had a whole live
English fans failed in the survey about
their inflations of whole life English I
don't ask you four to guess the answers
of the survey Wizards it's your fans
opinion so you girls should know right
[Music]
but I actually also voted did you girls
vote
no yeah at the point of this recording
but um
I partially remember when I voted for
last time
um you had to get five out of the 10
questions collectively as a challenge
last time
this time you need to get
seven out of the king Christians College
to pass
seven yeah let's find out if you truly
understand the fans seven yeah that's a
lot what if we ain't done what if we
can't do it yeah I believe you can do it
yeah your profit cards right perfect
Idol scores right I'm perfect but I
don't know about the others yeah you
betray the others
if we put our heads together maybe some
of your Perfection will rub off on the
neck on all of us this is true this is
true we have we Pat your head
it'll hurt
okay okay so that's a problem for you oh
I would check you are a perfect girl so
let's look at the first solving question
oh
um
[Music]
picked up most likely to get lost in the
mall
now it's thinking time
[Music]
's perspective
that's whole stories on my streams about
Amma getting lost a lot
but it wasn't in a mall but I did end up
voting for Ahmed because she and she's
the only one
getting lost do you in Council Iris do
you have anyone who gets lost a lot
do not feel like a lot of us could get
lost in a mall yeah
I think it's difficult to get lost in a
mall though unless it's like a crazy
huge one or unless you're in a foreign
country where you don't speak the
language no but that wasn't specified
but we can assume I thought that is the
same situation separating from your
friends in the mall
to get distracted and go off somewhere
yeah I think that would be on it
in Japan and and uh you know we were
going to the dance studio and then she's
like oh actually you guys go ahead I'm
gonna check out the bread store and then
we waited for her outside the bread
store but turns out she never went into
the bread store after like half an hour
I was waiting we looked inside the bread
store and she wasn't inside and later on
she told us when we found her again and
she just went elsewhere actually
and she was waiting for us maybe we got
lost actually
um thinking about speaking with this
wizard I didn't have image oh for the
number one last number one girl I didn't
have
um image to easily get lost yeah so it's
a little bit surprising for me
and so
um yeah it's a little bit difficult to
guess
you know another thing I'm thinking I
can't see a girl getting lost like in a
grocery store and having to you know go
on the intercom someone say come get
your lost girl
who's just lost it I can at least see
that the fans would think Coulda could
get lost
about experiences
lost in an airport maybe
where people thought she was a lost
wandering child
but she wasn't lost at that time either
but yeah I can see how they would vote
for good at first and I'm a second baby
yeah it is
we have to choose one person yeah yeah
one person
unfortunately one person yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
lock in please okay okay final answer
okay final answer your final answer is
the point if if second is Ahmed please
extra points
Mercy please
okay so now let's look at the results
here are the results of this survey yeah
[Music]
I'm not entirely happy with this like
with this results here what makes them
think that you got lost are there like
Clips or anything that maybe I get lost
in Minecraft
[Music]
yeah we can't see a glass so okay here's
a glasses
[Laughter]
you got it right congratulations
questions
[Music]
come on here it is the one food has the
best table manners
ah I was so unsure about this okay I
want to hear from Council dinners and
lunches I see who who is the best cable
manner person
people have good manners yeah yeah yeah
I think fans out yeah
like in Oregon way yeah yeah it's a
pound's perspective yeah I think
I feel like Cali has really good table
manners but I don't know if people would
expect it yeah true I I can't really
also remember any episodes that would
give something away to the viewers like
that so they might be going with their
guts you know what I think of from a
Fan's perspective is fauna's teacup that
she had for March and I imagine holding
the teacup with her little pinky yeah
not only that but she also seems like
kind of sophisticated and sophisticated
people have good table manners you know
I do think I could possibly have tricked
people into thinking that I have a good
table manners when they're really just
average yeah and you look like the type
of person to hold tea parties
your fingers you know to wash them and
that thing like do you know what I'm
talking about a dishwasher
are you doing that I can't see anybody
else doing that
um
but do they see that
[Music]
I have I have one more like idea but I
I'll
um I feel like it could possibly be Iris
I never ate food with her but I feel
like you know she kind of is used to
Japanese culture and they have even
better table manners than overseas
and she probably can be good in a you
know Japanese setting where some foreign
members maybe don't know how to do
Japanese table manners but she can also
do it well in a western setting right
let's just you know
reasonable idea but in the end what do
the fans think I don't know the fans
thought so much about it now
what do we want to go with what's your
guts feeling girls
I think it's fauna
I'm fine with that but wait inside me
don't don't let it fall on
my idea
um what do you think chroni
oh oh now the responsibilities on me
um
yes going by you know merch
like on this teacup and even in her own
you know own map she has little teacup
set so I guess I could and I threw them
on the ground
yeah
that wasn't the best table banners
that's true but
I still have him
that's true okay I know what you're
saying that the fans would go with that
I think we might have this image I don't
think it's correct but I think they
could have the image okay okay I think
we're locking in with fauna okay right
if it's Iris I will I will slam my table
on my keyboard
yeah whether it's throughs or not true
so it's a fun email so let's look at the
wizard it's okay yeah okay foreign
[Music]
I am the best for PR
right
and I think the fans with a green with
it yeah
we can lock it already
oh my God
it's not true oh God I should implore
you as a salesperson
okay so did you yes did you decide yeah
okay yes yes okay now let's look at the
results here are the results of this
survey
[Music]
very fast
what does I'm selling what is crazy
selling yeah
it's your commercial voice yeah
[Applause]
let's do it with the script but without
it I can't I can't do it that's why
you're number two yeah exactly
well good with just you know
[Music]
somebody
oh
yeah I'm down there
are you guys like struggling in
sponsorship streams or what's going on I
don't think so
I think you guys do great I think I do a
good job I have a certain style where
maybe on first impression it looks like
I'm bad but really
I know what I'm doing yeah you're
thinking five steps ahead that's what
you're doing exactly maybe you're trying
to make people want to buy a product by
by making it look you know not so
desirable it's so hard
[Music]
oh my God I gotta try it yeah yeah
ever I I think you you guys uh uh oh
super sales women I think but
I believe that's a different perspective
if anyone wants to take a sales PR class
I will be your teacher don't worry I'll
help you out
you were appealing yourself Kiana
what are we paying how much do we have
to pay of course
[Applause]
okay and you got it right so you got
three points wow
question
[Music]
next every question is here
the one for you would want to be your
younger sister
[Music]
actually do you want to sleep under the
same roof as me no yes I I wouldn't want
mermaid to be my younger sister
I I would like to be her friend instead
you know then let's ask the question
differently crony who would you like to
be your younger sister in Ian
hmm
I guess
from a band's perspective I can see mume
being the younger sister yeah
I feel like it's either gouda or Mama
yeah because you know she just is small
so short yeah yeah
I mean they give up younger sister vibes
[Music]
I think that more people would say girl
though yeah I think so too yeah
[Music]
I think so too I think even though even
though I voted for mermaid too
my bird sister oh I see yeah
to be my
yeah
[Music]
are you about to confess my my good
friend
a very good friend
what about a great friend a great friend
a great great friend
with your little sister I mean that it
should be ideal it's just
you wouldn't understand
inner conflicts right now or what's
going on don't worry about it okay
you're complicated for this stream
it's interesting
they're coming out
what do you think though I don't know I
don't know
[Music]
correct answer is movement but I don't
know if the fans answered correctly they
might answer
I think more people said girls I'm going
to go girl yeah
[Music]
Google
do it just do it okay
your final answer is no there
Gula okay
okay now let's look at the results here
are the results
spells
you should
know
yeah
think of that
it was me yeah baby it's because phase
12. she's 12. yeah she's 12. okay when
we were in Japan with her she was
cooking breakfast for us
we didn't really seem like a little
sister ignore those kind of stories when
it comes to the polls but she is kind of
the smallest in Council right I guess
she gives off this like little sister
and a gym
one out of three questions that we can
have wrong already wrong
[Music]
right
wrong right
okay okay okay and we have to get four
more four more right yeah okay okay okay
it's a little bit long yeah a long bed
so you can do it I think
okay let's look at that next survey
question
dada
[Music]
I wasn't sure I'm sure I'm not sure
it was Sunday yeah
my mind goes to girl because she reads
the tsundere copy pasta
[Music]
interesting
thing
for Cali I think it has also a lot to do
with her relationship with me you know
relationship
just to be there with soon and now she's
mostly dead towards me
[Applause]
I see I see yeah I understand
but does does crony have some native
Vibes to you girl yeah do you do you
feel more Gap yeah
[Music]
kick okay so good answer
I like that answer
she's happy with it
[Music]
are we not forgetting anyone do that
just let's just make sure everybody can
be soon day towards each other as well
that's a Paris yeah
is that Iris or obey on her own kind of
ah I don't think so
okay
yeah yeah I think Cali would make sense
because she found it on stream and not
not a wink blink blink blink one blink
once if we should go for calling you
or something yeah there's possible
blink blink when yeah and we should go
for Cali
[Music]
um
she doesn't seem like a very corrupt
person so I feel like you can do it on
our own yeah okay we don't have to
resort to tricks I Believe in Us how
about uh we count down to zero and on
zero everybody says what they think it
is
prick no one Cali Cali okay Kelly Kelly
this
oh don't you believe me don't you
believe me
okay
[Music]
it's okay you're yeah your choice your
choice yeah oh that doesn't care
okay here's the Wizards of this survey
[Music]
is it number one
is there a reaction though
no yeah oh oh no now it's a soothing
reaction
[Laughter]
one of them this is me too I voted for
chronium I think oh God 11
[Music]
what is wrong with you guys
get your ears and eyes checked what is
wrong why
maybe you should do this stream where
you explain all the different something
something dead ends to people
right maybe I shouldn't ice cream I
thought they were joking
yeah so unfortunately you go it go it
wrong
we're getting into dangerous territory
okay next survey question
here's a question
you would want to be
oh man oh man I think they would vote
for fauna
[Music]
yeah I think crony could be up there
really
yeah it didn't specify what it meant
I hate that I can't deny it
yeah I feel like this one could be close
yeah
well
I I know like you know people
um a lot of us have pets but a couple of
us have like very close connections that
make it very open and obvious in our
streams as well that we have a close
connection with pets and those I say are
uh specifically fauna and me but also I
think the teammates would go very crazy
about this and vote for Ahmed because
position
sorry Baba's position
um I don't think it's me but I do give
my animal belly rubs while streaming
because
room just now so okay
I have to what's the question
yeah
what do you want what should we do
should I eat it should I be petting her
during this yeah
oh get her to chill out when she's in
the room he or she I don't know
and the animal
[Music]
s
that is so easy what should we do I
think well here's the other thing I
think people could
[Music]
they could be pet as being the closest
thing to
um child
yeah I was thinking that too it might be
similar to to Mommy yeah yeah and again
people want fauna to take care of them
so it all circles back to fauna oh
so your answer is yeah
okay so now let's look at the results
[Music]
[Applause]
everyone wants to be snail I don't blame
them sometimes I want to be snails too
yeah he has a pretty good life
yeah I saw snails snail has a really
good life
I envy snail
okay
my cats are very happy
I think so so let's cut the glove
[Music]
look at the glove
fourth
[Music]
one two three four five
six six
yeah yeah yeah
it's going to be a cat or a chicken
wow oh
does the the lowest one yeah yeah she is
really tiny so
she's
can't take you
she should be
I think bye
she's a little sister
[Music]
[Laughter]
how many how many answers how many a
more
I can't remember if we got correct yeah
yeah cool like maybe maybe four more
questions free we have to get correct
one we can get wrong
that's it
three out of four you you you should get
it by slay more
a little bit hard there's one upcoming
that I I have confidence in okay oh okay
okay
yes okay well come on the next survey
question
here's a question
the worst driver huh worst driver
it should be someone who doesn't know
how to drive who doesn't know how to
drive me I don't know how to drive yeah
I better knowing that you guys don't
drive too oh man I was scared I think a
lot of us don't have a lines
okay
maybe we should think about streams you
know like uh Euro buzz what simulator
stuff like that whatever people did
where girls did really badly
do you think that would influence the
results of the questions
but what is that moment was actually a
skill like how did you get to that point
that is a pretty cool move there
um
hmm
[Music]
possibly it could also be gouda again
because I don't know because it likes
like short clumsy yeah she can't even
see it over the wheel yeah yeah she
can't even reach the pedals
maybe some people just like to open up
yeah yeah when in doubt it's good
we thought this it was nice yeah okay so
let's give them a bit more credits
and anybody ever told like driving
stories I know it cannot be Cali because
we at least know stories about Cali
driving I had like an entire Ranch dream
about driving
a dream no stream a stream
but people could have taken that since I
was so angry I was actually the problem
but I don't think enough people could
have voted for that yeah like a Karen
driver
um
difficult yeah difficult
it's just the first perspective I think
it's not really to some live streams or
yeah some skills or
just from the look of us
I would go for uh if we're going off of
how we've oh yeah yeah
I think yeah yeah I think it's really
hard to choose one person but so your
answer is good okay
okay okay so let's look at the results
here are the results of this surveys
good luck
yes
and fails
this is pretty clumsy Ryan all right I
have Iris in my head too
um
on wrists always yeah always right yeah
I don't want to ride with her
I can't will not get into the car with
Iris okay yeah
it's okay
people she's chaos right so she must be
a chaotic yeah
[Music]
okay
okay let's look at the next survey
question here's the survey
the one with the most infectious
laughter
[Music]
too because Kiara is a pretty iconic uh
laughter yeah yeah really I thought yo
it was more iconic really I thought
yours was pretty iconic
thank you
halfway
[Laughter]
cronies is more like infectious though
yeah I think so like that
yeah yeah
are we forgetting anyone
yeah
okay
that's true okay okay I don't know what
to say about this one
okay
let's look at the results here are the
reasons
[Music]
ah
this is
[Laughter]
please please
it's too close
if it's still open it could be even
different now yeah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
you want to hear a point
no
this will be our downfall
I'm so it's not allowed to give you a
point
well then don't play don't play when we
cannot announce our announcements at the
end
wow there's no info there's no need for
this video yes
[Music]
ah
you can answer two questions you can
be a winner
okay okay
so generous
this is just how this is literally the
last two questions we have to get them
we have to get them okay two more two
more yeah easy easy I think let's look
up the next survey question
don't touch it up
that won't fool the most likely win in
the fight
ah ah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
this is yeah
see there is this whole lore problem
that we have
but I think let's think about girls who
we are aware of the the them working out
which I think is
chronically that's the iPod I think
crony could win in a fight but probably
Cali could too yeah well if we if we set
up crony versus Cali
I guess we should try it out next time
wait
[Music]
versus Kelly
I definitely lost and Ina was week two
good I was pretty weak too I
got I have just watched all the fan
animations of Ina killing everyone yeah
I want to defeat her um yeah the myth
floor animations The Unofficial ones
yeah yeah
I think it should be simply yeah
[Music]
and even if we look at our powers then
still Cali is you know able to rule
everybody so
that's pretty safe bet I would say
[Music]
crony would fight anyone
okay in real life
I mean
I had with you I think you talked about
like wanting to beat someone up
[Music]
[Laughter]
I will never make crony angry again
it's a secret it's a secret oh okay
[Laughter]
do you think it's crony as well
no idea it's between I think it's
between Cali and crony but I feel like
almond could also be a possibilities
wait wait
um there was this uh I think some fans
know about this episode that like when
myth stayed together in America I told
the story that Ahmed was like sleeping
next to like a metal object to protect
yourself in case someone breaks in and
she then later I guess kind of told that
you know she she always has something to
protect herself with to beat someone up
if it's necessary and I don't think she
has the confidence the guts to do it
when it's necessary
so I cut their hair not being first but
maybe being second or third would
everyone know that would would overseas
fans know that or overseas I guess
also because she has uh gun skills that
she showcased in her stream shooting at
things
in real life you know not only games
so she showcased her her self-protection
skills a lot this is difficult
I'm not saying she should be first I'm
not saying that yeah yeah yeah I could
get could be Crowley because you know
Laura why she's dead but also she does
work out but I guess it could also be
Mia because
[Music]
um I think
when I first debuted I was talking about
how I punched the floor oh like I was
sleeping on the floor and then I had a
dream where I was fighting someone so I
punched the floor as hard as I can and
my skin got ripped
does that mean you lost against the
floor I mean this is the thing that I
won in the dream but maybe against the
floor it was a time
it sounds
[Music]
[Laughter]
with the spider bottle right so
you you won't or you lose you you lose
right
I did win I won every every piece
actually and I was left traumatized
okay is trying to lead us away from
crony maybe with that fun maybe Cali
then oh maybe it's Cali
it's my my kindness yeah
[Music]
and she is only human during Ian talents
right
[Music]
because she you know has history in
teaching
yeah but Kiara also has teaching lessons
yeah
uh the same yeah because I I taught uh I
taught the English to Japanese members I
think before and German and Japanese to
Buddha and so on but you crony you
taught me uh Koreans but he only did it
once I think I feel I feel
um she is she don't call to her students
I think so
don't be mad or I think she is not mad
at something or you mean you mean the
person that is the answer is someone who
would not scold yeah I think so I think
so yeah I think so yeah but I think Cali
wouldn't scold anyone
very kind she may be between us
[Music]
yeah she could be I think it could be
another mommy question in disguise
actually now that I think of it I think
I also voted for fauna even though I
think it it Cali is you know she has the
experience
you know we'd learn we could go to the
next grade but she made it she would
make it fun yeah yeah she would be sweet
and you would feel safe with her you
know there's always like some teachers
that are very strict and you feel scared
of going to their their lesson but then
there is fauna the teacher that you
always feel safe and comfortable with
[Laughter]
you better be right
okay is that it is your final decision
right I don't know
okay okay
[Music]
the other guard is okay the other guards
you're checking if we're okay with it
quite a bit
[Music]
um
is it
yeah what do you think what do you think
about our answer or I guess yeah
oh you or killer I'm Gonna Be My Teacher
yeah Bulls I'm glad Paul's yeah
I think the fans would like um but I
think you can believe yourselves
[Music]
kind okay
now let's look at the Wizards here are
the results of this survey final survey
[Music]
yeah
we can reveal new info I feel believed
now that we're going to understand our
fans a bit better let's announce the new
information about whole life English
first
Ulster concert whole life English first
person start going to work
all right first let's check out the key
Visual and the main concert in full
again
[Music]
connect the world will be held at the
YouTube theater in Los Angeles
thank you thank you the date of the
concert is on the 2nd of July the doors
will open at 6 p.m so be there on time
and the concert will start at 7 pm don't
be late and JFC that will be on the 3rd
of July opening at 10 A.M and starting
at 11AM in case you are streaming from
the Glorious
hi
all right
[Music]
well then your tickets are no longer
available you can still get streaming
tickets on sale for the concert if you
want to watch from the comfort of your
own home
what a deal
what a deal and we will be having guests
from Hall Library JP tokino sodas and
five
[Music]
amazing we'll be having guests from a
whole life ID as well
also be making guest appearances
[Music]
[Applause]
we're looking forward to seeing all
torrents and old guests yeah
finally what new information do we have
um
one two
one
[Music]
[Applause]
finally yay finally we have our own
original song it's the first one
featuring all of the whole life English
talents are you guys excited yeah
yeah
and what's more the song will be
released the Pacific special free of the
music videos
to show it off to you guys please wait a
little bit longer and it will be there
and next with the concert coming up soon
we've made a list of things we hope
everyone will be aware of when coming to
the concert you know it's available
under the information menu on the
website so please check it out
[Music]
this concert was made possible by all of
us talents and fans alike so let's make
it an enjoyable experience for everyone
yeah thank you guys
[Music]
and last we are happy to announce that
Boosie Road will be our official premium
an official premium sponsor now that is
amazing what does that mean though
super special
thank you for always supporting us and
the official title of the concert will
also now be hello live English first
concert connect the world supported by
bushy Road
it's even longer now wow
thank you for supporting always ah thank
you so much yeah really happy
information
now that we know this new info I'm
really excited for live English first
concert connect the word since we are
here right before let's hear how hyped
you were for the concert yeah it's soon
yeah
[Music]
um well I I I'm so proud that you know
we finally get to have our own concert
we're still sharing it with senpies and
you know ID as well but uh you know I
still have a concert and we'll make it
our own and I hope the fans will have a
great time with great memories it will
be something that we give back to you
guys
yeah I'm just I'm feeling super proud of
how Ian and super lucky to be able to
perform with the girls that I love so
much on stage and in front of all of you
guys I'm very excited so thank you for
letting this happen it couldn't have
happened without you guys thank you
thank you so much
I'm just really glad for this
opportunity to be able to share this
experience with all the girls and to
everyone that'll be watching the concert
so again thank you thank you thank you
so much
[Music]
oh I'm really happy that we're finally
able to have a concert for hollow
English not just that we can have it but
that it can be in the States because not
very many people have the time and money
to go overseas for concerts yeah so I'm
glad we were able to have this closer to
a lot of our en fans so I'm super
excited very excited very excited yeah
thank you so much I can't wait for the
concert yeah I'm looking forward to
seeing you were shining idle on the
stage yeah
well that's all we have for these shows
so goodbye everyone goodbye
[Music]