[Music]
up
you
[Music]
me
um
[Music]
oh
me
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
me
it
[Music]
foreign
ah
okay
i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i'm gonna cry
[Music]
i'm sorry
sorry that stressed me out so much
i was running to buy a
stupid [\h__\h] cable
ah
it was so hot i was so stupid i put on a
big [\h__\h]
hoodie
and long pants what was i thinking i was
like getting a heat stroke
[Music]
and then it took me a while to find the
cable first i
uh i couldn't even find a an employee
and then and then i found one but he was
an idiot
because like i'm like asking him i'm
standing in front of you know those
cables
i'm asking him
uh do you have a usb
usbc
to
usb
3.0 cable and he points to the usbc 2.0
ones and i'm like are you sure that's
3.0 and he's like this this is usbc to
usb and i'm like yeah but there's like
2.0 and three points there and he didn't
know that he's like no this is dead
they're the same and i'm like no the 3.0
are blue inside
they're different so i'm like can you
like open it up to check so he opens it
up and i'm like okay that's not it
and then yeah he still pro he probably
he still doesn't understand that there's
a difference
and then i i tried to find a different
employee and then we found
we found the right one
the right cable actually
uh oh man
uh
who doesn't know that by now like if you
work in the shop like that shouldn't you
know that there's a difference between
2.0 and 3.0 like that's not like like
big brain knowledge to have
that's relatively minimal knowledge for
working in like a tech shop what the
[\h__\h]
what the hell man
it's maybe it was his first day
maybe not his first day but one of his
first first days one of his first days
maybe
um oopsie i'm bigger
i'm so sorry the first first time you
know actually i you know when i took a
nap i set my my
my alarm to half an hour before the
stream so that i could prepare
um
but even even if i would have woken up
on time i guess i
um
i would have still needed the cable
i'm so sorry i'm so stupid
i'm gonna cry
[Music]
okay
i just want to play wind waker [\h__\h]
wind like a weekend that's [\h__\h]
cursed
i just want to play window anchor
i just want to play windowing
[Music]
i just want to play with
what were we doing
um
foreign
oh i don't know how to be kiwawa anymore
how can i be kiwawa existential crisis
let's go
[Music]
let's let's go to the motives where the
fish where the moldives
where which direction is the mall leaves
why do i have to go anyway
oh is there like a
where is where's like my goal like
what's my goal
do i see on the map what my goal is
what do i need to do
i wasn't that going like this way wasn't
it going here again
i'm lost i'm lost at sea it's been too
long
let's talk to the yeah i think you know
because we're almost at the
top left of the boat
hello why do you delay we must head for
the forsaken fortress okay
let's head oh yeah the weather is
getting [\h__\h] i'm scared or like the ah
ah
okay let's go to the forsaken fortress
let's go
thank you for waiting
uh i wanted to do you know i know i
could have just played something else
but the thing is i wanted to have a long
stream
uh whatever
i wanted to have a long stream so we can
talk and all that
and i don't know we could have done
minecraft but i
i don't know i wasn't in the mood for
minecraft
you will probably you guys are in the
mood for minecraft either are you
i fish i talked to you before no
ah
cause i think i have oh god oh god i
think i have the map already holy [\h__\h]
what where where where from where should
we enter
what is that is that a sword
what is that
that's a dude
what is he doing there
is it too dangerous to uh wait
god that's really dangerous
what's that doing there i want to talk
to him
um
oh why is she sad because i [\h__\h] up
maybe we need to enter from is there a
side where they don't shoot at us
are we here to rescue my sister yes yes
yes yes we're here to rescue my sister
uh
i don't remember this part at all
where can i enter
it was a gate i passed blow it up oh
okay
okay ah this one
how to use the bombs i don't remember
how to use the bombs
are they going to shoot at me how do i
use the bombs again here we are
okay okay
hi yeah
infiltrating
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] you don't see this
oh
why why is it there here how oh whoa
uh
was just no it wasn't like this was it
like oh was it like this
was it like was it like this
ganon has likely been made aware of our
little incursion already
that that's what i did i think i think
that's about right
but you have the master yes i do
wait
i have the master suite let me put bring
out the
muscles
[Music]
this is the master sword yeah small it's
all about strong you guys also always
make fun of my sword but this one is
also small and no one makes fun of it do
they
there we go
this is about as small as my old sword
everybody makes fun of my sword but make
fun of this sword
but it takes up so much space so we
should um
nice one thank you
[Music]
okay is this okay
okay huh
this is full bladed but your sword's
length is mostly not the blade
what
what does that even mean
shut
uh up
you don't need to see how much money i
have that's too private anyway
uh but you have to message
that sword shall shine in the darkness
casting back evil
with it in your hands no one can keep
you from rescuing your sister
do not be afraid
i am afraid
you say it so simply don't be afraid
you're for real bro i am very afraid do
i have everything i need because by the
way um i
i only have
uh one one of those
snake snacks
um i hope we don't need them but i do
have the soup and i have a fairy and i
have 23 bombs and i guess i have 30
arrows
i don't know what we'll need but oh god
it's been so long how do i fight
okay
sashi
oh it's so quiet now
where do i go
don't
do i need to do the box thing again
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
i don't know how to play this game
anymore no
i need to use my shield how to use my
shield how do i use my shield
i should
take this ghost gun
here's my shield i can just hit them
okay oh yeah this is how you fight with
god
yeah you do it again and again but like
uh how did i focus on them
i should have fought like one at least
one like normal enemy holy [\h__\h] ah there
you go
oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
that's probably just three times oh god
what is he doing
about it
it's so typical this is so [\h__\h]
difficult
can you not get so close to me please
oh
whoa
oh sh quick
and you're a ghost why does my sword
even go through you
logic game logic
[Music]
and monkey
wow
he didn't expect that
oh my god okay
so nice that he greets me like right in
the beginning so i don't have to go
looking for him
i [\h__\h]
come at me bro hey
hey
yeah
slice them up
let's go
wow
okay so
that was i guess just like phase one
oh thank you for opening the door
so sweet he's like nuts to round number
two you girl
you're entertaining me
oh nice what is this
do the lights not bother me now oh [\h__\h]
do i not care about what is the sound
what the [\h__\h]
what just happened i just tried to open
the [\h__\h]
treasure chest
hello
[Music]
ah the hammer
ah
yeah those stupid demons i was confused
now
uh so wait the the lights don't
matter anymore because i think i've been
in the light and nothing happened
hammer time it's every
is that the same song
it's so nice that he gives me this he
wants to be bunked like a like a bad bad
bad boy he's been a bad bad bad boy he
wants to be bunked on his butt
butt hooks
i don't have to sneak around
since i got my weapon
okay
i don't have to sneak around
anymore also not in front of the enemies
no
no sneaking really
some enemies even get stunned by the
shock waves it causes when you pound to
the ground
where the [\h__\h] did you come from
what did you drop ah
and they make funny sounds i like it oh
okay so we pound the ground here
oh there's more coming oh wait shut up
shut up go away
hi
wow oh okay now that just uh
automatically used the
that okay how do i
do i not be to be do i not need to be on
top can i
nice no no
new weapon let's go
there's more of them there's more
stop stop stop stop everyone stop
following me
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
once
i
saw one of those um
yeah big
bots in the chat but i don't have the
pictures in my
in my chat so i guess
and it got bonked immediately i don't
even even if it even showed up on the
on the screen
um
this is fine
oh
i'm gonna hide the chat for a while
um
yeah
i
uh better better be safe
uh
yeah
yeah as long as it's not on the screen
it's fine right i didn't have this until
now didn't have this problem until now
but i think as long as it's not on the
screen it should be fine
okay
uh where was i a
resume
okay okay um that is not a good place to
be uh
which way
maybe this way
um they don't stop coming and they don't
stop oh hello hello hello nice to meet
you sir
this time i'm not hiding from you
yeah yeah
no need to hide anymore
i'm gonna let it all out
oh okay yeah i need to go here
apparently but
there's nothing to hang on to i don't
think i can do this jump but i can maybe
go
there ah but i can float do you think
that will
do the trick
but it's not the same height
i don't think i can float over there
eh
what do you think i don't even remember
how to float
[Laughter]
it worked
hey
[Music]
okay am i going the right direction i
wonder
yo
i know that chat is not in the stream
anymore have you been listening why i
did that
some people just don't pay attention man
is this
that is is that really really
i need to go down in this case no
eh
because now the things are down there
i feel like i need to go down
um
i can arrange are you sure
i'm scared
yeah oh it's okay
i feel like i'm gonna
you know lose altitude really quickly
i guess not
second place place second floor is the
place to be okay
that looks fun you never noticed that
statue before
it's not suddenly gonna
come to life right
hello
it was just so
obviously placed man
no i didn't know but you know that is
just like placed in the way that makes
you think and it's gonna come to life
yeah that's so scary but it didn't come
out of the wall
i was like am i seeing things
wait what is it what is this gonna do
like you can just run past it
okay can we we can run past these people
too i guess but i'm gonna try to fight
them
yeah
oh so easy
oh my god let's kill him too
let's try this you set me on fire and
this doesn't even work what about the
shockwave i was promised a ground pound
shockwave huh
where's the shock
with doesn't work for this enemy i guess
man
all right
we're just going to the top again
this is the top
started fire today
have you guys
have you guys seen the the teaser i
think the teaser i know it's very short
but don't complain because it gives at
least it gives you
a very obvious
hint of what the
what the genre is
about you [\h__\h]
so
i saw like a few tweets tweeting at me
city pop it's not city pop
it's synthwave but it's uh specifically
we aim for
80's
80 cent wave
[Music]
oh my god they don't stop coming and
they don't [\h__\h] stop coming and they
don't i'm just gonna i should just
ignore them right
it is cool yay
i know i know it's so that's why i was
like you know
it's very different from before
are you guys gonna like it
i don't know
how
i was worried about that you know don't
fall down
um
no no don't don't you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] this is literally the
personification of a little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
yep
oh they stopped they finally [\h__\h]
stopped
it was about time
okay
so uh yeah i was worried about
are oh do they come every time i'm in
the light
i was worried about if you guys are
gonna like it and been working on it for
a long time
i i feel like you know when i was
thinking about making a new song i think
it must have been around the same time
as when the hinotori
[Applause]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
oh my god
do i need to take out the lights because
they shoot bombs at me
ah matty i thought you guys said don't
need to hide anymore
no need to take down the lights
oh man
this one
or a different one don't need to take
all of them
i could have used the leaf ah
amen looks sad that's so annoying
[Music]
okay
whatever
um so yeah i think it was probably
around the time
when
i released the hinotori remix says
i guess because i don't i don't really
remember man but that must have been
where i got the the inspiration and the
the wish
the wish to
you know
make something in that genre
[Music]
um so i'm not not suddenly gonna you
know
be a
sinful artist
but i thought it would be a nice change
um
i wonder who you hired but a lot of
people already guessed
um it is astrophysics
i didn't put any credits yet into the
teaser but all the credits will be there
for the actual uh music video it is yes
the one and only
who else would i ask for that huh
yeah because i
first originally you know i i asked him
to
make a hinoji remix for the one year
anniversary
and then
i asked him if he like if if he thinks
that that he can also make like songs
from from scratch original songs
and he said yeah he would like to do it
so then we started working um
on a song i sent him some inspirations
of what exactly i want to do because
like even
i i've learned this now even within the
synthwave uh
there's like several
like
how to say
not genres but
there's like
several like different types i guess
sub genres
yeah um i want to get killed again
did i take down the correct light
probably not
it's gonna bite me in the ears
[Music]
go home
what if i go in here can i no
stop following me
oh
um
so i forgot what what eventually like
he said he he told me
what kind of like
subgenre it is but i don't remember
for me in my head it's synth 80's retro
synth wave
yes
with a maybe a small
inspiration from k-pop as well
synthetic
ah that's the light ah
could i in fury go down there do i have
that shortcut i guess i do
let's try to go
like this oh god where to uh
uh
no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
i can still get back up here right
i think
just change winter action ah ah whatever
watch out
okay and yeah the the whole music video
uh is gonna be in that style too
in the teaser you already saw like a
little bit of it you know like
like the
the
tapes and
yeah
the synthwave helmets and
um
what if i go over there
it's that ladder because i don't think i
can leave leave glide there because it
doesn't hold on till it does he
[Music]
ah the [\h__\h] wind
what direction do i need to picture
stupid wind
yeah the box i thought the box was still
there from last time
they reset the dungeon
what go
how do i make music again
what ah
i was the right joystick
happy birthday jackson
thanks for the membership welcome movie
uh
this one
no
yeah
this way
[Music]
yeah no no yeah let's see we'll see
please please
i mean we're lower so i don't know if
link holds on to the ladder but
no he doesn't
dump it
[Music]
i got a new song coming out tomorrow yes
what did i ask
well let's go here instead
hey buddy
[Music]
okay
sorry one more time
i'm gonna celebrate oh yeah oh yeah all
right one more time
dancing
like the legend of the phoenix
and ends up beginning
it keeps the planet
[Music]
last spinning
i had this dream about you
in the stream i'm dancing right beside
you there's nothing wrong with just a
little bit of fun
we were dancing all night long
[Music]
i hope this dream comes true
one more time
i'm gonna celebrate oh yeah oh yeah all
right one more time
work it harder make it better do it
faster it makes you stronger
[Laughter]
one more time you just got me feeling so
free we're gonna
i love that one so much i love that
pentatonix
mash up compilation thingy so [\h__\h]
much
it's so good
yo i want to listen to it right now it's
the best thing ever
right
agree agree
agreed
was so good
chick punk
go go link you idiot
pentatonix is so good everything they
touch i love their perfume
mashup
they sang japanese for that one which
they really
did a good job at
i'm not gonna fall down again i'm not
i'm not gonna this reminds me of the
time where we in that when we were in
that bird um dungeon and outside i kept
on falling down
don't hit me don't hit me don't hit me
now
[Music]
you
why aren't i [\h__\h] everywhere it's
like they're goky buddy cockroaches why
is he on the wall
cool red dude what the [\h__\h] thank you
no message why since [\h__\h] double red
super jet and doesn't tell me why he
loves me so much
oh hello sumimasen
hello
oh
oh wow
wow
oh my god i'm also freaking out don't
don't freak out link you're not supposed
to freak freak out
[Music]
yes i want all the other [\h__\h]
i just want to listen to the soundtrack
[Music]
you guys hear this
link what's
link are you good
just look at your sister why are you
looking around so much he's like i'm
gonna look everywhere except into your
eyes
but the bird the bird to be watching
though
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
dizzy
you're okay
i was worried we were worried about you
[Music]
it's not going to be that easy is it
[\h__\h] scared me
the cell won't open that easily
there you go acting before you think as
usual
don't scare me
[Laughter]
i swear do you even realize that we had
to draw that monster bird off for you
um well i i fought ganon
this ghost version so excuse me
it was about to come flying in here
after you again
[Music]
eh
what was
why
oh
she's shook about my master sign
because she realizes
i'm the hero
i guess
that sword
where did you get that
are you
is it even possible yes i'm just that
cool yeah yeah
[\h__\h] respect me now girl
how could it be
[Music]
well never mind about that for now we'll
just take these girls
i'm sure their father back in town will
pay a handsome reward for their return
yeah for the rich girl yeah
ah you don't have to carry them like
that
[Music]
oh
cute look at their dead eyes
i'm so sorry to interrupt such a
heartwarming reunion
but
[Music]
but isn't there still something that you
need to take care of
huh i thought you took care of the bird
oh you mean i should take care of ghana
[Music]
there's no way that we're taking care of
ghana now this is still not the end of
the game
if you're worried about your sister
don't be i promise i'll deliver her
safely back to your little island really
at this point like wouldn't link not
want to let her go alone anymore
no matter what
don't leave her with anyone else
[Music]
normally i'd expect a huge reward for
something like this but this time it's
my treat
listen ariel your brother still has some
things to take care of big important
grown-up things
he'll be back soon so you just wait nice
and quiet until he returns okay
[Music]
miss gets well we have to hurry the bird
will be here any second
[Music]
gonzo excellent you're just in time take
this one for me
[Music]
but she's
one
she's fine just do as you're told
what is she
you mean what she's
[Music]
okay what's [\h__\h] scary what are you
trying to say
wow he's got some cool feathers on his
back though i gotta give him that
like almost like phoenix feathers
oh god is this a panic moment why are we
in water oh god
eh
what huh
uh okay
uh what do i have to fight him while i'm
running
uh with what
[Music]
i can't i can't focus on it do i just
run just run oh okay
[Music]
fight it
run run run run run run run run
almost there i think
not for the store right yeah
not for the door
can't open it
is it always timed when it does that
so kitty kitty
okay okay i think it's time
mommy
[Music]
help me
i'm almost there i don't need your help
eh noni ah maybe this on your beak yeah
yeah okay okay
cause that's the new item that we got
it one hit really
eh
is it gonna rise again from the water
yeah
okay and then it closes and then we
fight up at the top
ah where are so many feathers man you're
losing a lot of hair are you that old
i could tell you
you're going to get bold verb both good
is that what you want to be
how do we fight you huh
can i focus on you now
there's stones lying around here why
why
so i can get hearts for example probably
yeah
he's so cute
his toes his feet
ah the way he
walks landing time
it's move
[Music]
smooth as [\h__\h] bird oh no no
not you literally cannot get me off of
here because there's
uh walls everywhere
that move is useless
hello come here
just stand still maybe wait for him to
do it
okay
hey
i know i see the spike ah i guess
there's some sideways spikes okay oh
dear
then let's uh stay here
oh where you going bro
[Music]
do it do it do it do it yes
yeah
one more time more
yeah it's three times not the charm
i bought three times what is the charm
i'm just gonna wait here
loud here
landing zone is right here
yeah
do it do it do it
it's too yep oh my god okay face two
hey hey it's like a chicken thingy
i'm so sorry i must hurt tom so sorry
i feel like the bird is he's a good bird
at heart you know
he just tries to protect his owner and
his home
he's a he's a good bird
i still gonna do the same thing
so stupid
[Applause]
[Music]
i have a banana by the way half a banana
i was too stressed out to eat the whole
thing now i'm going to eat it
[Music]
hurt container
oh my god
our stream hard banana
just two bites i have two more bites for
later um
shall we go to the top
i guess
why we killed the birds what's there
left to do
are we gonna say hi to ghana and he's
gonna kick us off and then we're gonna
be picked up by our boat
is that it
cool entrance here
look
so very threatening i like the
decorations
are we sure i want to go in here i'm
scared
i'm gonna save
inspired oh
oopsie wait did i save
you never know oh it's safe twice
ah yeah okay
continue okay
open up kfb
hello
oh god
come on let's go
oh
you have done well to sneak into my
[Music]
i suppose the least i can do is command
you for your reckless courage
[Music]
and i
am the master of the forsaken fortress
[Music]
out of its western place
if you by chance notice how all of the
monsters frozen in time down there
suddenly began stirring again
[Music]
do you understand precisely what that
means
i highly doubt you do
bullish child
while that sword is indeed the blade of
evil spain
at the same
time has long played another phone
[Music]
you see
it is also a sort of key
the most wretched little kid has kept
the seal on me and my magic intact
[Music]
by withdrawing the blade you have broken
that seal
thank you
not so fast little boy
oh [\h__\h]
you cannot defeat me with a blade that
does not sparkle with the power to repel
evil but your home is useless
[Music]
its power is gone and its edges are good
get up
[Music]
is
what are you talking about i don't know
any zelda
[Music]
fading ignorance will gain you nothing
tell me if you are not zelda then why do
you have this fragment of the slag force
it's like it's like it's like
[Music]
oh
yeah let's go
[Music]
wow start a fire today don't stop do
stuff just go your own way
[Music]
[Applause]
and that is a good part of the game
wow
cool cool cool
[Music]
we found out something very important
that we already knew
it's all right kiwawa she has merely
lost consciousness
your sister has escaped the forsaken
fortress of the pirates you can relax
she's safe now
oh
no why is it only 100
okay
lord lord lord lord lord lord value
your arrived not a moment too soon we're
deeply grateful
[Music]
i am aware of this
yet i thought our first priority should
be to separate these two from garden's
grass
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
we're back in this
world
uh oh
kiwawa
you are right
what is this place
hey encounter what happened to him
[Laughter]
[Music]
what are you doing
you must come now to the room where you
got the master sword
who is who's using the stone oh yeah
good question who's using this john
this is not the ship yeah but the ship
is right there so why would you talk to
us for the stone
kiwa and i are the only ones who can
speak for the stone
how dare you use what's not yours
oh
your name is tetra correct
you must want you must come with your
hour to see me at once i sent her
i have an idea was it her
something with f
[Music]
huh um don't you sound important fine
we're on our way just hold your horses
whoever you are
come on what are you waiting for what
you waiting what you waiting what you
waiting what you waiting for
you heard the stone you're supposed to
show me how to get to where that voice
is
okay follow me
but look
first look
look at this
it's amazing right
wow beautiful
i mean
it looks okay well that spot over there
looks like from
the pokemon
game
the pokemon breath of the wild i don't
know
no don't mean the i don't mean the wall
guys
why is there a hole right there
oh it's not a real hole
okay let's go inside i guess
yeah
are they alive again
i guess they are
i already killed everyone though oh no
they're gone
look tetra that's me that boy that's me
you do you feel like you know it looks
similar from the back side
realize it i'm like a [\h__\h] legend
here
ah
uh is it downstairs
oh my god so kakoy
so kakoy oh my are you good she's
stuck can you get out of this yourself
or do i have to help you
yeah she's too stupid for it
come here
look this is like uh
this is called the triforce
in case you really don't know partially
i feel like you're just acting stupid
but
just in case you don't know actually i
want some i want some flying magic
thingy this is maybe in here
and this is not so bad at least she
walks fast yo escort missions are
usually [\h__\h] because they walk like
[\h__\h] snails
no
no no
magical
energy here yeah
it's never the thing that you need
[Music]
and smash the pot on her head
i'm sure she doesn't mind
[Music]
okay
uh whatever i guess
it's called flirting no that's not cold
for nothing no one no one believed that
guy
ah was not
here where is it here we don't have to
no we don't have to go here we have to
go where i pulled the sword
ah wait wasn't it through that i uh
around that
around the statue
[Music]
here it is girl can you follow
[Laughter]
she's so stubborn she just wants to walk
straight through the wall
oh my god some people are like that
hello
yes okay
yes it's the f
i thought so
are you him are you the one who was
speaking for my stone without my
permission answer me
um
[Music]
okay
that's man why does it look why does it
sound so feminine i have like the uh
gender the other way around what the
hell
ah
uh that stone that stone is an enhanced
version it doesn't sound good that stone
is an enhanced version of the gossip
stones long spoken off in the legends of
the hyrulean royal family i am the one
who made it
you made it the royal family's gossip
stone
i'm sorry but i have no idea what you're
talking about
have neither of you heard of the tales
tales of iraq
the kingdom spoken of in the legend of
the great hero
the place where the power of the gods
lies hidden
this place where the two of you now
stand is that kingdom
this is hyper
[Music]
[Laughter]
and i am it's king
darkness no hansen hyrule
[Music]
see this is when i completely forgot he
was the voice of the boat
do you not recognize my voice
indeed i'm the one who guided you here
i'm the king of the red lions
how did i forget that detail
there was no need for me to reveal my
true identity to you so long as that
blade the master sword could defeat
ghana
but now both of you must listen to me
once long ago this land of hyrule was
turned into a world of shadows by ganon
who sought to obtain the power of the
gods for his own evil ends
my power alone could not stop fiend finn
finn fine
and our only choice was to leave the
fate of the kingdom in the hands of the
gods
when the gods heard our pleas they chose
to seal away not only ghanan but hyrule
itself and so with a torrential downpour
of reigns from the heavens our fair
kingdom was soon buried beneath the
waves forgotten at the bottom of the
ocean
[Music]
yet all was not lost
for the gods knew that to seal the power
away with the kingdom would be to grant
cannon's wish for the destruction of the
land
so before the sealing of the kingdom
the gods chose those who would build a
new country and commanded them to take
refuge on the mountaintops
those people were your ancestors
hundreds of years have passed since then
so long as ganondorf was not revived
hyrule would remain below never waking
from its slumber but i i woke them is
that a good or a bad thing
when doing that voice hurts me
tetra come to me come to daddy
you disgusting
no
tell her already
[Music]
this necklace who wears part of a sacred
treasure called the triforce of wisdom
which has been passed down for many ages
within the royal family of hyrule
[Music]
your mother passed this down to you and
instructed you to treasure it and to
guard it with your life
am i not correct
the triforce of wisdom is none other
than the sacred power of the gods that
we have kept from ghana's clutches for
so many long years
the gods placed upon your ancestors the
task of protecting it from an evil's
grasp
you too must abide by the laws of the
past and so the time has come for me to
teach you the fate into which you were
born the very reason that you live
wow
oh
[Music]
don't look like ted freaking me out
wow one triforce
whoa
[Music]
and princess
oh my god
the makeup
[Music]
her voice is higher now too
my
fate
you are the true heir of the royal
family of hyrule the last link in the
bloodline
you are princess zelda
wow
oh my god
[Music]
can i bring back the chat by the way
oh
[Music]
that is a sweet
zelda
i'm
a princess
well i always wanted to be a princess i
always was hiding it under tough skin
saying i wouldn't be a pirate but in
reality i wanted to be a princess like
every other girl like when i was playing
with barbies i always had to do it in my
room and close the door so that the
other pirates wouldn't sing they
wouldn't make fun of me but in reality
you know i like those princess barbies
you know
you are confused aren't you
i suppose such is to be expected
yeah
kiwawa
i'm terribly sorry that you have been
caught up in these events
[Music]
but now that is known that tetra is
indeed princess zelda
wait is she talking oh no he's is is the
dad talking
yeah that's sorry ganon will be
searching frantically for this child in
an attempt to get the power of the gods
that she possesses he will not rest
until he has found her
if he succeeds my ancient kingdom under
the sea will be turned into a land of
shadow and despair and so will the world
you know above the waves
a little by making me sleepy
i need you to lend me your strength into
star power
i have a suspicion about what caused the
master sword to lose its power
i need for you to come with me back to
the lands above the water and return to
the power to repel evil to the master
sword
hi
zelda
it is far too dangerous for you to join
us in this task
fortunately the sacred chamber is not
yet known to gannon
it's my wish that you wait here in
hiding until we return
all right
well we must go
oh
what we can teleport nice
wow
damn
quinoa
i don't know how to say this
everything that's happened to you and
your boy sister
it's all been my fault
[Music]
i'm so sorry
no problem
bye bye group
you should have kissed her goodbye
chihuahua
i love you
be careful
[Music]
lol and me
later
it was a scary boy he said to me a
little boy he wasn't good enough for her
[Music]
okay zelda you stay down there okay
you wouldn't know with your shitty ai
how to get out of there anyway upstairs
[Music]
yeah
all right hey boat what's up
oh okay
chihuahua listen well
the fact that the master sword lost the
power to rebel evil suggests to me that
something has happened to the sages who
infused the blade with the god's power
the sages should be here in hyrule in
the wind temple to the north and the
earth temple to the south praying to the
gods
you must head for these two temples to
see what has happened to the sages in
attempt to find a way to recover the
power to repel evil
unfortunately ghana seems to have
erected some sort of magical barrier
down here in highway blocking our path
to the temples
but each temple should have another
entrance high upon high rose
mountaintops which are now islands above
the sea
as always i shall mark these places on
your sea chart
now then if we stay here my song
okay
is there already a market no i don't i
don't have an area map yet
okay
leaving this beautiful place
two temples
huh did i see them before
you know the legend of the hero time
once long ago he defeated gallon and
brought peace to the kingdom of hyrum
which was uh yes uh ocarina of time
piece of the triforce was given to the
hearing of time and he kept it safe mrs
stella kept hers did she know did she
that sacred piece is known as the turf
of courage
when the hero of time was called to
embark on another journey and left the
line of hyrule he was separated from the
elements that made him a hero
they said that at the time the trappers
of courage were split into eight charts
and hidden throughout the land
eight
eight [\h__\h] shards
you need me to pick up eight [\h__\h]
shards
eight
eight shards
wait with my with my fishing device or
even i do not know when i rest well
great but this much i do now they like
hidden somewhere in this great sea okay
okay
oh no
how do i know they're different from the
other treasures in the water though
someone who knows much about things that
lie hidden in the depths
who could it be
fred not if you can think of no one
though maybe you would come upon the
knowledge by asking around in a place
where many people gather
oh uh-huh
open world unlocked wait how was it not
open world until now
[Music]
wait what do you want me to do go to the
shards go to the temple
dude
how do i
do this thing
where where was it i was just looking
away
looking away
i'm so good at this i still got it
[Music]
is this a
shard
ah
oh
really
okay you know what i'm so sorry to the
um if there's any
people who are not subscribed i'm sorry
but i'm gonna turn on the subscription
thingy
although i feel like
anyone who watches this stream
is normally a subscriber
[Music]
this kind of stream yeah
nice show
subscriber mode uh 20 uh two weeks
okay now it should be fine right because
like should be fine right
yeah get them out of here
wait but let me see
uh if
are they timed out or banned
okay should be banned i guess
a purple ruby
that's not a shard
okay where are we going where are we
going where are we going let's go down
over here
[Music]
yes you all should be subscribed now
it's time if you're not subscribed yet
why the hell not huh
why why are you not
i forgot to subscribe up to so many
moves
yeah right
oh this wait what do the verbs mean what
do the verbs mean there's so many verbs
here
what they mean what do they mean mason
what do the birds
oh what mean they mean again
[Music]
treasure
cycle
i squint
oh well oh wow
[Music]
oh wait no not that are they following
me
what do i do with you
guys i know what you want from me
but look there's a fish
stop stop
let's feed him because we don't have to
map from here yet
hi
my last
snack for you
yeah i like the way the ocean looks in
the game too i know it's like cell
shaded and really like simplistic but i
do like it a lot um
small fry yeah yeah i've heard i take it
you want the chart and information about
this island yeah yeah
and rats right in there in there yeah
yeah
be careful don't
don't mess it up
wow amazing what is this place
did you like um
my my breakfast
have you heard of the golden set of
triumph forks it's right there i tell
you the article genuine in that house
if you wanted you'd better go in there
and score the place from floor to
ceiling
uh-huh okay let's go in i don't know
what that means
let's check it out
i don't think we entered this place
before
get off the boat
oh and it seems like i have uh i got
mail
now this doesn't look like the maldives
but
still reminds me of it
oh
purple bulb
and waffles in the water they look like
waffles
wait this place is nice nice island oh
there's a cool docker
ah what was this again you wanted to
plant trees what do you need again
huh
[Music]
is this a side quest
i don't need
i need to do this right what what do i
get if i do it a heart piece maybe a
heart container
side quest okay we're not doing that one
because i gotta like all the time fill
up my bottle with forest water then come
to these guys and then go back again
fill it up
a again
what just a rupee no way
one ladder
yay
eh
cash on delivery
i have to pay
what
why i don't even know what it is
it's 201
it's a hard piece no way
wait heartbeats you mean from the
sidequest not from this right
am i being scammed
i guess yeah
[Music]
esteemedness the fairy person thank you
very much for your purchase and close
purchase
and pers
wait is this how you make people buy
something you just send it to them on
without them ordering it in the first
place so did i order it this child will
show you where you can find ah okay okay
wait
wait is that a
just a side quest too
the triforce shot
if it's not a side quest then why do
they make you pay for it
it is required
oh okay but then i'm surprised they make
you pay for it like this
also sir have you been checking your
tingle chart have you seen those giant
fairy marks follow the chart to them and
your fortune will increase greatly nah
tingle
[Music]
incredible chart now you know where all
the triforce charts and triforce charts
are hidden
wait i know what the shards are but what
are the charts
that's positively incredible open a
chart on the map screen to view it
what are it drive dude do the triforce
charts show me where the triforce shards
are and not the map that he just gave me
do i need to
what if where is the opening
what
i hear
yeah whatever
victory spoons
oh
you said a joke
are you joking
some of them are there right some of
them need a chart uh-huh finally some
magic
[Music]
you want me to get water
eh
i thought that was smart of me to pour
water in it from
the
thingy
it's not for dad
oh uh crawling how do
i crawl again
without the weapon probably oh the one
that's so [\h__\h]
what
pulled away
yes okay finally
i'm hiding
what are those sounds
do i get something if i collect every
coin because i already missed one
why is it so wonky oh
huh no why is it so monkey
coin
okay sorry it's a rupee
i'm
sorry wait i still have mail
i thought i only had one letter
got everything
you said i only had one letter before i
already took it
cover your mouth before you sneeze on me
oh my sister how have you been
i'm hearing the pirate dip riding here
this letter is nothing and first i was
really scared but they're actually nice
for pirates i mean mr clunch there's a
really big guy but ever since miss
touchdown left he's been crying like
completely kind of funny
not just a little strange but nice too
and as for santa his beard makes him
look pretty mean but he tells really
cool stories when he gets in the red
moon
zuko's kind of weird and michael is
pretty quiet malcolm only gets mad
whenever i try to take his glasses short
do that a lot he essentially is always
fooling around he won't take anything
serious actually he seems sad not to
have you around anymore but you guys
good friends i have them all out with
the tours and they actually paid me a
little forward so i'm oh
just sending me the money i'll loan you
my telescope for a little longer but you
have to return it to me eventually okay
i'm doing fine so you don't worry i'll
take care of myself and you'll be sure
to take care of you
oh you're ready for me oh so swing
aw girl
don't touch me with those fluffy hats
you mischievous little scoop
this cabana belongs to mustard the most
alone
you grimey trespassing little scandal
away with you wait a second how do i
enter
well this is us
license object
no [\h__\h]
but the buckets
did i not have to fill the bucket how do
i just place it uh
it looks like it would fit perfectly but
it doesn't
i can buy this island what
i would buy it in reality
yes
i already talked to this fish right i
don't even have food anyway now okay
let's just go straight to
ready to go
[Applause]
i think you have over one of my cables
ah i just noticed right before the
stream i'm missing 1k before my switch
oh man
now you fall down i went to buy a new
one
oh man
one usbc to
usb usb 3.0 game bomb for the elgato
i feel like we mixed it up when we were
like separating the cables
ah
it to be like that it happens 50 rupees
not bad she said she doesn't have it
really but i looked for my whole
suitcase as well
what the [\h__\h] is that
whoa scary
way so
it's so snowy here
ah now you get what i mean no problem no
problem
it's okay
maybe i also have something from you
and
can i enter this place
please hello
[Music]
okay i thought so
i i died
you died
there should be like a warning sign or
something
man
elena you're missing something
i think the cable is the only thing i'm
missing
but i didn't properly unpack it i just
threw everything out of the suitcase on
the ground to look for the cable
i need to unpack properly man it's
already friday
it's friday friday
getting down
friday
almost there
i don't know if i didn't know well i
didn't unpack properly
[Music]
why are we so
so bad at this man
it's been it's been
uh five days or so
we need to unpack
i'll do it after the stream
i'll do it after the stream birds have a
feather flock together we do we do but
you guys don't you also take a long time
to unpack your stuff
come on
come on it can't just be us
where's the tower is this tower
is that what i'm looking for
oh i guess so there's like a head there
but can i even do something with that
yet before finding the
the
the shards crabs
look rain the crabs
are they so cute ah no they disappear
you're so cute though i do that thank
you for being honest
cute
oh cute
they're cute these are even cuter cause
they're like bigger and they go sideways
there's a
cuter i still got boxes from two months
ago oh yeah with moving it's also like
that last time i moved i have like
i had some boxes
um just standing around
for ages because i didn't know where to
like
put what was inside so i just had them
standing around open
for
at least
nine months
[Laughter]
so what is this
huh
yo dude with the power you have now you
can never lift it
somewhere in the sea the power to do so
lies waiting for one to find it
you mean the shards
okay so you should tell me to go for the
shots first
okay
[Music]
we need to
need to get the shards that's okay so
something on my map
someone's shooting me
i'm not even visible to anyone oh
wow
they see my boat
you sent for this freaking game yes i
love it so much
i'm glad you guys are enjoying it and
and share my love for wind waker
it's just
very nostalgic to me okay so
treasure chest do you need to look for
these treasure charts is there gonna be
like aya incredible
chart this map isn't open without how do
i open it
there you go aha oh there's one very
close by
uh on the
uh
square right next to the one i'm in
right now
but then my question still stands is it
i need to fight oh
okay
my question still stands does it look
the same as the other
treasures
we're just gonna start by getting these
thingies now
and then later
we'll fight the cyclone
i guess
is that a good order
of doing things
and here
oh i need to buy some food
from the shop
i bring a huge pimp all right okay okay
so this is not it
[Music]
i'll take the money because i need to
buy some stuff anyway
but there should be one on this
square
and hello home
hello
[Music]
pop
da
oh yes i've seen all the new designs
yeah actually me and elena looked at
them a little bit um
on vacation
because i i had it like
pop up somewhere on my social media when
we were looking at my phone together
yeah
so we looked at the new designs
they didn't look so closely though but
they look good
[Music]
a bashful look on my face
yeah shut
[Music]
this music is so chill
do you know my favorite babies also
playing my favorite zelda yo i've been
doing uh actually i'm already pretty far
yo
wind waker weekends have been
interrupted many times but
here we are
kind of midway through the game
shall i have a cat hair in my mouth
uh should we buy one more
one more please
[Music]
i would check how many map squares there
are left to find and buy that many fish
paints oh
oh that's smart
i have a lot a lot left
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen
fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen
eighteen nineteen 20 21
22 23
24 25 26 27
27 it should be
and now i have
way less uh three three six nine twelve
twelve baits and i need twenty seven oh
okay i don't think i even can get 27
baits in my bag so let's just buy
a couple more
i guess
[Music]
what do you mean 49 in total no no no
thank you
plus stanley casey i wanted to say that
yes
you know me too well in case i
accidentally button match
and throw the
throw it out in moments where i don't
want to throw it out that's exactly what
i would do you know me too well
i was thinking the same thing 49 map
squares in total but you've already
uncovered some oh
okay yeah i'm missing 27 out of 49.
it's not
where's it going to it's not filling up
where
bye
it's not and now it filled up okay
wait how
how much space is in this back if if i
buy one more can i even buy one mine
thank you
so i already i still have the grandma
soup so i don't need to say hello to
grandma but we're gonna look for
i'm gonna look for the
light and that's not it
[Music]
i'm gonna get it anyway
yo all these first tries let's go
[Music]
would she react if i tell her
cause my sister's not here yet she's
still on the boat right
but if i tell her that i
got my sister is she gonna react to that
[Music]
it's a beneath a giant headstone here oh
okay
but on the water right
[Music]
ah
i can just speak to grandma hearing that
link's bird was in the area and getting
so excited to see him but he never shows
up
no no i'm here here i'm here
whenever you have an empty bottle see
she doesn't even change what she's
saying oh man okay
maybe i should drink it
and get another one
i've never drank it before
it's time limited or is it is it um
like drink it once and then
let's drink it at it
don't drink it
[\h__\h] oh wrong one
oh
ah it's not
it's not a time limited thing wait now i
can shoot lasers right because i'm like
full everything
wow
or is that not in this game because my
my sword is um
my sword is
sparkling
i thought it doesn't sparkle until i
have all the shines
no lasers
oh is that just the effect that i have
on my sword um from the soup
oh wait there's two fillings
ugh
all right i guess i'll have the second
filling
thank you 13 moms let's go
double damage yo okay
well then let's get the soup
[Music]
yum yum yum and i wouldn't mind some
nice
pumpkin or tomatoes soup or something
right now
um
[Music]
i understand
you need two bosses and eight rifle just
before you can challenge
yeah yeah that's what we're gonna go
find now
thank you ghost your key
okay so a giant headstone what
is it right at the island
[Music]
is it on the island but they said it's
on the water
[Music]
only three triple shots you fish up the
[\h__\h] i thought they were on the wire
how misleading
i yawned a lot yeah i'm sorry
i think i i'm lacking um
i'm lacking oxygen how do i get over
there
[Music]
how did you get so fat
i didn't feed you
was it so fat
oh look you won't want your mixed [\h__\h]
come on you remember the day you first
caught this oinker and brought him over
here just look like our friend i said he
a lot bigger now than the last time you
saw him and also a speaker he's a little
heavier too come on is there any way you
could pick him up but jacob will walk
really appreciate it my back is just
killing me take it for a walk look at
that aggressive jonker
i'm scared it's gonna eat me
[Music]
oh i don't have the strength to pick
this one up either
for real
do i need to kill the cyclone for that
damn wait what's in this house
never been inside i think
thanks back
ah
cute house oh my god that's a lot of
huge books they're bigger than my face
[Music]
yeah
i've been really like i don't know i
wake up so early
ever since the first day of the maldives
i didn't even need to adjust at all
um
but i feel like when i'm on vacation
with someone
or traveling with someone
i don't know i generally
i'm able to
like sleep earlier because
my mind is like
[Music]
but first of all
you know wake up early for breakfast but
not only that it's also just like
i need to
[Music]
fall asleep because you know there's
someone else there and like
there's
i don't know how to explain this
to explain this but my my brain is just
like okay you're not alone
so we're watching netflix and stay a
little awake for five hours
it's pretty meaningless
[Music]
so
yeah i don't know
and especially when they're already
sleeping or trying to sleep
then i'm like
okay i guess like
if they
yeah yeah another thing i always
consider is like if they sleep before me
then i feel like you know
they're gonna wake up before me probably
they're gonna get more sleep than me
and then i'll be super sleepy because i
have to kind of usually get up together
with whoever i'm staying with right
so then i'll be lacking sleep if i stay
up too long
just because i have to get up at the
same time
i'll just do it again
well they can fly to the top of ah oh
can i fly from here
i see the guy who gives hints about the
thingies
okay i'm glad i can fly from here
let's go
oh [\h__\h] the wind ah
uh
we might still be able to make it though
no no we're already lower ah hold on
[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
i need to lift it
for [\h__\h] sake
i do need to cyclone first
didn't they ask each other that's good
[Music]
oh man okay well at least we know
what why would i because i thought that
we have to
get it from the ocean so i didn't think
we have to lift something and also i am
paying attention to chat there's just a
lot of comments all the time you know
giving different kind of
comments
so
excuse me for not picking up every
single comment in the chat
i'm still one of those streamers in our
whole life who pick up the chat more
than others
excuse me
where's the stupid cyclone
where the birds wear right
is it is it where the birds are
is he randomly placed
very true
uh-huh uh-huh
[Music]
are the birds are where the octopus are
where is the cyclone
[Music]
so now i'm looking at the chat you can
tell me now
you can tell me now
oh left to right second column second
square
so
second column second square
left to right
second column
okay so at the top left almost
[Music]
cyclone is not going to get the item you
need to lift this what
[Music]
second column second row
it'll give you a good ability
[Music]
but
what about the item that i apparently
need cyclone gives me fast travel
okay
okay can i choose the square then that's
cool
[Music]
oh
by the way my sunburn
since like um already like three days
ago or so
it's been kind of like low-key itchy
[Music]
but i think that's
i mean
i've never had it before but it's also a
normal thing apparently
oh
okay more to the right you say
yeah it's been weirdly itchy and
don't go too much to the left side
and yeah it's just it just started to
peel but
oh shut up
it looks very very
very spotty
like my arms and my legs
they're not red anymore
they're like
kind of tan but like really really
spotty it looks so stupid
[Music]
yeah my mom also said you should use a
peeling
okay i wonder if i have a peeling
at home
i guess i could do like a homemade
peeling maybe
i have like coconut or oil people like
to do homemade stuff with coconut oil
and then i don't know sugar
sugar and coconut oil i can imagine that
being a homemade peeling
but i'll just wait i mean i don't really
care long you know
i'll just wait so it should be over
there
[Music]
i think
if i got you right
second row second
um
column
[Music]
should it should be here
should be easy to spot ah yes is that it
do i go inside or do i just shoot into
the winch
do i just
is it coming at me no
[Music]
all right
let me just shoot inside or at you
wait what
oh [\h__\h] now
huh
so what the [\h__\h] is that
look
what
what is that
my skin is so weird now after this
summer
[Music]
and
there's like bubbles
yeah honestly though like the sun bin
was really bad in some spots i feel like
i have like a some certain degree of
like um like a real burn
bubbles
you you you you you you
oh wait i can open it i think should i
eh
looks like blisters what the [\h__\h] what
what
my skin
what's happening it's weird
i feel like there was like some some
you
don't
i don't know they're like small don't
pop them what why are they in places now
my skin keeps on transforming
is this your first no it's not my first
sunburn but i never had like such bad
like
effects from it
why do they come now don't don't don't
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys would be a stupid meme i'm
gonna give you that in this case i guess
i can say i'm morbing i don't even
understand is it like a matrix movie or
what was that
oh [\h__\h] thing okay i'm not gonna touch
it i'm gonna leave it even though it
bothers me
do you have bubbles anywhere else yes
wait oh my god this is also bob
and they're everywhere
but these are they're like really small
i don't know
they're all over my arm
[Music]
and on my leg
but on my leg they're like a little bit
bigger bubble
and don't touch
why don't why why did they show up now
they're really tiny though
yeah it was a really bad burn
i don't think i should do a peeling now
when i have these bubbles
why are you just noticing it that they
were not there before
where the [\h__\h] are we no we're at the
very bottom of the map oh my god i'm so
mad
okay okay okay let's
let's not be angry
let's
let's be happy
hello i've been uh putting a lure on my
skin several times per day yo
ape does
am i turning into a monkey
i don't know what this is
eh
it had a great fairy oh should i go
there
oh [\h__\h] it man
i don't know where i came to anyway
hello you biome
math is my bubbly personality shut up
ah okay
and where's that fairy
ah that one that thing i saw
okay go go
uh give me the [\h__\h] fast travel
i'm going to
i'm confused i thought you know
the recently there's been two new words
showing up on the internet
first wasn't it molding
molding and now now there's more being
they're like practically the same word
to me
but molding is being angry right and
morbing is like turning into something i
guess if i understand this new
vocabulary correctly
oh my god i threw it on the other side
yeah
okay
morbing is a joke about a new movie
which isn't in the film uh-huh yeah yeah
i know it's a movie joke
wow
oh fairy
oh
where's the great fairy
[Music]
huh was i not already here and then
that's just a small fairy doesn't that
mean i've already been here
you gotta talk
look closer oh mama
oh
there she goes
[Music]
young waker of the winds
allow me to aid you in your quest
what you're gonna do screwdriver girl
[Music]
more bombs let's go sexy bombs okay
the fairies in this fountain shall ease
your weariness when you grow fatigued
from your battles come here to be
refreshed
oh okay well i don't need any fairies i
still have uh
one with me
thanks for telling me though
thanks for telling me about the ferry
[Music]
do i have the map from here
i think i don't
oh i don't know when whenever i'm on the
square i it's really hard to tell for me
if i already have it because it turns
red
or like orange
yeah don't think we have the map from
here where's the fish ah it's already
we're ready to fire i see the fish
ah let me come and get you
[Music]
where is it
okay
i feel like the exciting part
of today let's play through it's already
over
because now we're just gonna look for
the stupid shirts
it's gonna be a pain in the ass
apparently i did have the map already
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
no
sorry i'm stupid i'm stupid i'm stupid
[Music]
it's raining man hallelujah
going back to the cycle now
i am going back to the cyclone
[Music]
if you have the island already by seeing
if the fish advisor con is available for
said island oh
aha okay
m and
boat and sheep
oh
hello hello hello
come here
faster faster faster it's gonna go away
wasting my food
i have this one
see i don't have this one
i don't have this one
oh no it looks on my map this time
[Music]
try on fox oh yeah oh trump
yeah i wanted to i guess buy them but i
don't know
or you could even batch the thing though
yeah i need power
i need the power
tell me how to get the power but i guess
first we're getting the cyclone
and then chat will tell me
where to get the power
[Music]
waves are so big
big ocean waves
okay
let me think oh yeah so sunburn uh itchy
and bubbles
but no more red
that is the current state of cuba
and also very spotty
um
thankfully my face is okay
but yeah i feel like i look very stupid
um
[Music]
i'm gonna try to stay out of the sun but
let's be honest i don't even have to try
because that's just my normal
way of living
yeah morning he was at 11. and then
oh yeah i wanted to update you guys so
tomorrow
uh because i switched things around a
little bit how we're gonna do it is
um the music release
on
music services thingies
are usually they have to be
at midnight of every country apparently
so it starts with midnight jst
and because of that i thought okay
let's try to have the music video
release
somewhat close to that
and not like at the time i originally
intended it to be
uh can i go on this
fairy island there's fire
i think i can because now i have to have
her
that's right
yeah uh to to my
[Laughter]
okay
i can't this hurts me
i can't do a voice crack
come on but my tummy hurts
[Laughter]
that one was close maybe
hello young waker of the winds
i can't
oh my god
[Music]
wow
what is this oh more arrows okay
here i go i'm just getting stronger and
stronger and stronger
so what i wanted to say
what i want to say is um what did i want
to say
what
every german speaking person should know
about them well i know about them
i know about their existences
so so what
what was i saying what was i saying
focus
oh yeah okay so um my plan is kiwawa
standard time gmt plus one
or two
wait do i have to fish here
yes i have it
oh no we're wrong don't he's gonna be
mad again he's gonna be mad
yes
um
oh stars
verbs be like those thoughts um um i was
saying okay so q standard time gmt plus
two uh
4pm
is gonna be the music video release
and then
uh i think i planned
9 or 10 p.m so a couple hours later like
five or six hours later we're gonna have
the aftertalk
yeah
so there will be some time in between
as
black friction for example requested
calling you out here um but just because
uh yeah i guess i'll give you some more
time and then um
[Music]
yeah
yes
yo black friday where's your membership
yo
[Laughter]
where did your membership go okay i'm so
scared don't [\h__\h] it up again
i have to move in first but it happened
so fast
oh dear oh dear
uh dude don't don't don't i'm gonna
[\h__\h] rage quit
how do i how do i i can't i can't shut
up
[Music]
i'm so mad wait what where am i
oh i need to save my voice but i'm so
mad
i need to save my voice i need to save
my voice i need to save my voice i need
to save my voice
i'm so mad i might cry because i can't
scream
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't be mad don't be mad don't be mad
don't be mad
is there a cyclone here there's a
different one can i take this one
huh
[Laughter]
[Music]
so mad i'm so bad words can't even
describe how mad i am
okay okay okay i'm not even gonna read
your dialogue because you don't deserve
me reading your dialogue out loud you
guys are welcome to read it yourself
but i'm not going to do it
no
[\h__\h] you
uh-huh
down
down right left up
right nope
down wrap
down
right left up
[Music]
i hate those
i hate them so much
wahoo
in the hands of a windward girl like you
my adorable little cyclones will be as
happy as can be
if you need to move like the wind over
the ocean deep just calling my cyclones
[\h__\h] you
i'm so mad
i'm okay i'm okay i'm okay
so what now
where is the power chat
where is the power
please tell me please
please tell me i'll finish my banana
hmm
teleport to where
click travel top left
write a song here's the song
top left okay so many people say play
the song but you don't tell me where
it's golden
i'm so mad
[Laughter]
just playing with me
hmm
no
[Music]
yeah
wow so fancy
top left you guys say
i can't
i can all only go to certain
destinations
okay me too i'm here
you better give me the power
oh
i'm not landing outside
i'm landing here
in the in the fairy fountain directly
can you only enter this one like this
wow wow wow
secret
it's the only way to get there oh oh
she's pretty oh she's cute
no wait she's creepy
wait [\h__\h] she's creepy
tell me little boy can you answer me
can you control the wind
so young to have such power
how did you know to find me here
i am the queen of the very world what is
the matter my child
does that not surprise you
young one
i like you
you
and so i shall give you new power to the
boat that you wield
[Music]
oh
crepe
no fairies
whoa
oh fire into ice
heroes
let's go
but that's not the power i was looking
for
eh
ew
[Music]
now i can end the fire mountain and i
suppose also that i ice island place
the power fire and ice have been added
to your everest when you take out your
bow use that art to change our heads and
then fire away
yo
there is no limitation
eye sirens can freeze the hottest flames
and fire hours can melt the coldest ice
the ferris and this fountain will ease
your weariness here's a mess you need to
[Music]
child
i must tell you you are just my type
[Music]
well she seems she seems around his age
at least
that was uh weird
um
how does one
leave this place and why did i not get
the power of lifting things
do i need to get them from the fire into
ice mountain
masaka no masaka everything is connected
everything is connected
teleport out play the song again ah ah
okay
let's do that
[Music]
where do we want to go
does it matter
oh
should we go somewhere you get the
lifting riser from five mountain f3
first to top second to right
uh somewhere close to here
i suppose fruit to top third from the
top
right on roof island
and one sap okay
we're all in this together
thanks for the membership welcome
welcome
welcome welcome i'm gonna do a
membership stream next week but also
next week i'm not gonna be
streaming that much either because
obviously i'm going to doco me
don't call me
um
but there will be a collab of iowa's
at least
uh one one south
and
um
you know because dokomi's happening on
the weekend we can't do wind wake a
weekend again but maybe i'll do wind
like a wednesday i don't know
i don't know man
really going in for him
where is the fire
oh
is that it that's it
that must be it
is this like a whole ass dungeon
what was that was that a fish
did i see a fish
no
i guess not
oh
there it is
[Music]
limited time short dungeon mini dungeon
okay
where's the limited time
uh
hello yeah map please thank you
um
so i i will take monday off because by
the way my
my mom's gonna be coming over and um you
know
i like to take mondays off when i did
streams on the weekend in a row so many
mm-hmm
yeah you sell the treasure okay treasure
yes okay
great balls of fire you wanna you ought
to go find the island that's one square
north and four squares west of here
that's where the power to freeze
anything is hidden yep i already have
that thank you
yeah
um
and um
what was i saying holy [\h__\h] the weather
uh
i shall
how do i switch
see
again don't even talk to me
hey what the actual [\h__\h]
sure
why is it so slowly shooting
why does it not shoot faster
oh
okay
huh
oh this is a magic
yeah i thought so it has to use up
something
hey it's really five minutes it's really
time limit are you kidding me
five minutes
i already have problems here getting
inside oh it's five minutes because the
lava is gonna come out again huh oh god
oh god i don't work under pressure like
this
okay here's the entrance perhaps no
maybe not that's not the entrance how do
i get inside eh yeah here here
[Music]
one hit
i'm so strong
i guess because i have full hearts
[Music]
i hope that wasn't a mistake going to
pick up the feather but we have four
minutes
yeah the soup off
as long as i have full hearts near
yeah yeah so um
yeah next week's schedule um i wanted to
do you know the thing with the vr but i
might just like record it and then
upload it as a video okay i guess that
was a wrong one is that like a maze
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
ah
i'm molding i am holding
um
uploaded as a video
on like i don't know friday or something
where the [\h__\h] is it
um because i wanted to do you know like
a chanting guide kind of thing
uh i need to like find a way to
um do that maybe i'll ask amma for help
i just need to record it on some green
screen i guess and then i want to play
it on the the screen when i'm performing
as well
three minutes three minutes
i hope there's nothing else to do
besides getting up here
i could fly but [\h__\h] the wind
um
yeah and um
uh
oh yeah there's maybe something else
next week something
big but i don't know if it's next week
or the week after dokomi
at this point you will see
oh sh are you [\h__\h] kidding me are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
where are we going i can't do this at
two and a half minutes
i mean wait a minute
two minutes
you kill me
you're kidding me
[Music]
what is this what is this who's this i'm
here i'm here go go
huh
okay oh i just have to kill him okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
did i do it did i do it there that did i
do it did i oh do i get the thing to
lift it now
[Music]
what if i would have gone to the ice
ice dungeon
what do i get in the ice dungeon
yeah
can i lift it
[Music]
indeed
uh
teleport me up scotty
i'm so strong
even though i was wasting so much time
it really sounds like a baby crying
[Music]
a nice shot what the [\h__\h]
out
what what's happening
i broke
and what now
is it still live
wow that was a nice shot i was moving so
much
i didn't think that would work
okay we have the power now
can we like
collect the [\h__\h] shards now
[Music]
kenny hi takada
there's one at the top right
apparently
yeah nice so
okay
let's do this
guys let's do this go you can do the ice
one where was the honest one i don't
remember now um
ice island
somewhere at the bottom right but i'm so
close to the top right right so let me
do that first
i'm so close
let me do that one first
i just want a bit trickier really
hmm
anyway
uh
you guys have
you guys have questions
about this song or i don't know i mean i
can't i don't really want to answer too
much about it until it's released
but what is this
there's so many birds here
can i fight uh octopus
how
is it good
yes i think so
what's the song about it's about you
you
that was the recording oh i just
recorded it at home
i recorded everything at home like ever
since i left
japan yes of course english of course
english
it's gonna be an english song i think i
told you this before though
um i asked the
specific person
not cali
for english lyrics
yes
how 80s is it
what do you mean how 80s
i don't know it's like it's just
inspired you know
um the music video is very 80s though
more even than the song i think
is it here is it on that weird island
let's get fish first
take this
who would sing it imagine i'll kill you
none of them
the girl
no it was not inspired by yakuza no no
no no
not at all
but i know you guys have been talking
about it being friday night just because
the
initials were fn it was supposed to be
released on uh on a friday but now it
moved to saturday and now you know it's
called fever night
not friday night
i was like thinking about a song title
and this was for the longest time it was
just supposed to be like a
contemporary working title but then i
never was able to think about like a
better title so
i just went with it
saturday night fever no no no no no it's
favorite night not night fever
i looked up there's like a lot of songs
that are called night fever but i didn't
find any songs that are called favorite
night okay and it's some it's on purpose
okay because it's not supposed to be
night fever it's supposed to be like a
feverish night
i think yeah
yeah a night that feels like a fever
it's different
he's telling me again about the forks
again
you gave me the map though didn't you
okay so can i go in here and what is
this where it is
what
is that sus
uh
should i kill them
how do i get up there
can't go there yet
god damn it everywhere [\h__\h] go a kid
go
sorry dad
future
uh in in law dad what what was it
dad father-in-law
um okay then let's go to whatever
a b c d e f
somewhere at the bottom right i s i see
i see place
he took that bomb like a champ he did
father-in-law
all right moving on
he's not i guess so huh maybe he's not
but he's at least her ancestor
and like her only relative alive
probably anyway so we might as well call
him dad
[Music]
i forgot i can warp
i forgot about that all right
[Music]
this one maybe
fairy island
which one is this it doesn't have a name
yet
you guys
will be stupid memes
no
no morbing
no mormons no no no no
uh
hi fish which way was the ice island was
it one of those two
[Music]
this one maybe that one with the dragon
head
it looks like a dragon head from afar
an open dragon head
now
[Music]
that's the one nice
i'm too fast
how about now
uh
is this good no
so far
[Music]
yeah
oh
one error was enough
damn
and you guys said this one is trickier
oh dear
have a bad feeling
i have a bad feeling about this go go go
oh it's slippery
ah
a chest
uh it's probably just uh i'm not worth
it
over here maybe
[Applause]
i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna make it
ah
we should have started from here
oh man
is it trickier just because it's
slippery
i hope that's it
i hope that's all there is to it ah
let's go super mario 64.
okay i see why it's tricky
there we go middle
or over there
down down
down
okay so pretty good so far no fails yet
whoa
wait wait wait wait
come on
oh
yeah let's [\h__\h] go
this is it is this it
was that the whole challenge no probably
not
that's just uh going inside but i've
already done a better job than at the
fire dungeon
i would say
two two minutes and 50 seconds left
it's kind of hard to see
i guess this
[Music]
way okay yeah go away
go away
don't you dare touch me
maybe i should kill them first before
they throw me off here oh
[\h__\h]
i don't know where i'm shooting i just
come here [\h__\h] you whatever
that's it that's it did i do it yeah
boomerang would be easier oh my god i
did it
let's go
oh iron boots
i iron
these boots are so heavy you can hardly
walk but the wind can't blow you around
when you wear them oh
sans useful in the future
what about ice if i wear them on ice
am i like automatically wearing them now
what what do i have to put them on ah i
think i have to put them on
cute
dunk dunk reina walking around doing the
stream don't dunk in the room which i'm
sorry just kidding
eh you wanna jump through this
i'm hole saying because remember she was
she was uh stomping you couldn't even
hear it my microphone picked it up oh
[\h__\h]
it's like free challenges or what
okay let's start with this one
come at me bro
[Music]
uh-huh
okay
exciting
[Music]
and many many many rewards thank you of
good de guzmas
let's do
this one
yeah
ice baby
wow merry christmas oh speaking of merry
christmas did you see like apparently um
valkyrie connect is now gonna give us
even more presents
thanks to you guys doing an incredible
job already in the first round
and i suppose there's gonna be more
gifts from the viewers oh oh yeah i
think someone on twitter asked me to
mention
gifts that i would be happy about that
you guys should suggest and i guess that
makes sense
yeah i don't know what your budget is
for the viewer gifts though
i know what what's realistic hmm
[Music]
they will do
it they said that really
why do i not know anything i probably
don't know anything about it because
maybe they're gonna choose other girls i
don't know
i don't know probably what makes sense
right
that would make sense how do i fight
this guy again i need to get rid of his
armor but how do i get behind him
[Music]
okay easy
easy
peasy lemon squeezy
let's go
ahead presents presents from the company
that they can send to me um
okay
uh oh bicycle i could use a bicycle um
bicycle
um
and
a running machine
an xbox the new one because i don't have
an xbox
[Music]
mo capsule no i'm getting a mo cup suit
yeah like a treadmill yeah
um
let me think let me think let me think
uh
snorkeling
equipment
that one's cheap
um probably
[Music]
cute dresses from a brand of my choice
[Laughter]
no not gucci
should i ask for a new graphics card
it's too expensive how do you even get
your hands on a graphics card
and what do i need what do i need um oh
another i never um another cat tree like
uh there was like a fancy cat tree that
i wanted to buy but it's too expensive
man
um
like a handmade cat dream but i guess i
didn't you would guys you would have to
know which one huh just just uh right
fancy cat tree
[Music]
it's not cheating you guys just uh
know my preference then
stop cheating the other girls can say it
too that we would be smart
especially inna should say what she
wants because like
she's still getting the
the present that's
uh
that she thought would be like digital
present but yeah shouldn't make use of
the
what it really could be what it could
have been
i don't know
[Music]
um
pretty
jewelry from
nano swarovski because from my country
[Music]
oh a trip on a air balloon
um i don't know why
food items yeah because they could
actually give me food items huh
um
what would i ask for in food items like
[Music]
oh
lots of
lots of milka and rita sport chocolate
[Laughter]
oh a trip to a spa
a trip
one night in a spa
mm-hmm
of my choice in my country
uh
i love kinder country too
um
yeah the valkyrie connect advert as a
live 2d model outfit yes that would be
nice too
another cat no i'm not ready for that
i'm not ready for dance
what else what else
there's some didn't they say 30 gifts
from the viewers 30 yo 30.
what do i need [\h__\h]
ice cold ice cold ice cold
purple ruby
[Music]
i already have an air fryer
uh
hello fresh subscription because it's
kind of expensive you know
i'm paying for it but it's kind of
expensive
[Music]
another
a second tv screen because i only have
one for my bedroom i need one for my
living room
tv screen
[Music]
oh wait which one do i have now vive or
valve
which one do i have guys i have the one
that's not so good
because i want the one that the others
have
i guess
i mean the one i have now is good too
good enough
i have an htc okay i want the other
thing
[Laughter]
i want the valve index so that's what i
want
they have a cap of 50
per gift i didn't know there was a cap
oh did they say that oh [\h__\h] then all of
these gifts so far are empty
no the hell free subscription could work
because um i no wait maybe not
uh maybe not
also i don't know [\h__\h] that chest
there's probably nothing good in there
yeah
it's 50-50 per
gift
can we not combine some of them
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ah you can erase everything i just said
where are we going now
ah we can collect the things now
okay
um
fifty dollars
what can you buy i mean for fifty
dollars i feel like
no wait what was it
no for fifty dollars i think a massage
is gonna get
uh
something you can purchase
[Music]
oh wait it's written here
no
no [\h__\h]
there you go wasn't that hard
fifty dollars in cat food okay yeah
let's save some money on cat food that's
a good idea because that's something i
always have to buy
uh no not here
um
a fruit basket
can i get a fruit basket
uh
um
[Music]
not there i don't know i don't know
where i'm going i thought i wanted to go
to my home island
oh [\h__\h]
can i not go outside this
[\h__\h]
well that's cool again that's good good
question man
fifty dollars in cooking oil
stock up on things you actually need
who said toilet paper
i don't use something like that
but
you know even though i don't use
something like that no one one thing
that surprised me in the maldives
uh was
but i recognized it pretty fast because
i've been in brazil before and made the
same experience
um
where do i go where's home what's what's
home called again
windfall no isn't that the top left
island
uh is that they they don't
um you don't put the toilet paper you
don't flush it
um
but i'm left outside okay
uh you don't flush it but like
uh
like there was a there was a big day
right next to the toilet so
and and uh
um
a trash can
so i was like
i pretty quickly realized what's going
on here also there was a hose
right next to the toilet
so i was like okay i understand i
understand what's going on here but it's
like
so i'm so unused to it i mean like in
some countries it's probably so normal
so you're like
what's her problem
well i don't know
obviously i don't go to the toilet ever
at all so i'm just not used to it you
know
and then sometimes out of reflex
i would flush it anyway
and then i would be like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
it all happened too fast
yeah
um
so that's that's a thing in the maldives
but it makes a lot of sense
actually uh dana didn't realize it until
i told her
it was like i know
yeah
no flashy
no no you can flash but like don't flash
the toilet paper because think about it
it's an
island they're pipes like i mean they
have i guess pipes for water
for like flushing
but you shouldn't flush the toilet paper
or anything else because
it messes up i don't know their their
system
so in this case you should be part of
the system
[Music]
because you know it's an island we don't
want to pollute the island
don't want to pollute it
yeah
uh let's go
ah [\h__\h] the wind
i did it again but it's fine we can make
it we did it last time we're gonna do it
again
oh [\h__\h] i don't have
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] okay
never mind then um i need some energy
maybe next time i remember to change the
wind direction
for the toilet paper on the ground no
throw it in the trash can
[Music]
it's just like
really really really unused to something
like that it's like a different world
like a different world but it makes
sense it's an island so
uh why are there no
hello i need some wind energy for [\h__\h]
sake
it's pretty normal
oh not here
not in
austria not in germany i think a lot of
people who don't travel they wouldn't
even know that that's a thing
anywhere and i feel like because there's
like no no notes or anything like the
staff also don't tell you so i have a
feeling that like tourists never
have been to a place like that
wouldn't know and would just flush it
without knowing
so
one advice i have for these places
because in brazil in the hotel as well
did i say that i don't think there was
like any note that tells you about it
uh my hint is to maybe put up a note
because not there's a lot of tourists
who come from countries
that don't realize
what they're supposed to do
you know
i can move the pick now oh
now let me do this other thing first
i still have enough energy
there are some notes like that in my
country really i've never seen something
like that before though in the maldives
so
yeah
yeah if they don't want to mess up their
island they should put some notes here
and there
yeah yeah
just my two cents huh i know the soup's
magic i guess because i'm here i could
drink it huh
but now now i'm getting
now i'm getting it filled up
give me the magic
i mean i guess that's enough
that's probably enough
ah
that should be enough
especially if we change the wind
direction
oh
there's more
it doesn't drop anything
it gets drained quickly no
it no that is not true just because
there's a trash can doesn't always mean
that you're uh
that's supposed to
flush the toilet paper maybe it's only
in female toilets but often there's a
trash can
for
you know um girls items
if you know what i mean
oh sure maybe that's only in female
toilets no
for sure
[Music]
oh i'm so slow what the [\h__\h] why am i so
slow
hello
that's so close
[Music]
okay
oh thank you
finally this should be our first shard
[Music]
maybe
i'm drinking um
i'm drinking fit chill water you know
the gatorade but not gatorade in a
different brand
a bubbling foot spa
oh
i don't know like
foot spot has anyone tried that is that
really that nice
i can't imagine it being that
amazing i probably wouldn't use it
much
[Music]
isn't she doing this way too early no
i'm just doing what the game is telling
me to do what is this
stone
the savage labyrinth huh
deep in the never-ending darkness the
golden shard you seek awaits okay
very early what else would i be doing
[Music]
why is it hard oh i gotta keep on
fighting
oh [\h__\h] oh
is it something like that do you think i
can do it we're already in so
don't have much choice
actually boomerang
i can do it
[Music]
is there no accident right there's only
going forward no going back unless i die
i guess
and if i die or die
it just is what it is
also i have the soup i have a soup and i
have a fairy so
i'm gonna be fine
[Music]
and we want some excitement in this
episode after all right
other checkpoint leave early rooms
uh-huh okay
wait do all of the shards have like
challenges like these
oh
the electric ones those are gonna be the
biggest enemy for me
for electric tutus
everything else no problem
just the electric ones are my biggest
enemy
not all of them okay
not on now so accidentally my first one
is one with a big challenge
that's all right bring it on oh i hate
these guys too
[Music]
okay
okay okay so far so good
i only took like one hits until now and
it didn't do much damage
[Music]
what were we talking about ah the gift
so yeah yeah i mean a football honestly
i mean why not what else should we get
what else what else i mean maybe they're
not so strict about it maybe if a lot of
people ask for the same thing maybe they
will just combine two gifts or something
oh a perfume i don't really use perfume
that
much to be honest
[Music]
i'm more of a
natural type
and when i use perfume it's a really
like sweet type you know
perfumes
i like
i don't know they're often they they
smell so adult you know what i mean
i don't like that adult smell
no not stencha
what i used to
um use a lot instead is like there's
like really fruity nice sweet
um spray deodorants that you can also
use on your clothes
i used to use those a lot
it had a really really sweet scent to it
but perfumes i know
[Music]
but i guess if i would have one i would
try to i mean i have to
i would try to use it a little bit
more
a bath bomb flash bath bombs
yo i'm always up for lunch bath bombs
and oh like a lush gift card
large gift card very good very easy to
give to someone
because i think you can use it um all
over the world in any country
yeah slash gift card
or um not only lush what's the other one
i like the other ones too
any any kind of
company like that to be honest oh here's
a saving point
oh with some refreshments nice
[Music]
arrows haven't used them but okay
bath and body works oh wait i don't know
bath body works i don't know that
donkey cat oh yes yankee candle please
yes
i take yankee candle
i'll take it
uh wait which is the way
the hole
shouldn't you be doing the dungeons for
the sages to power up your sword um
i don't know i fought the shards at
first
whatever
i'm just that strong okay i'm
speedrunning
i'm just that good at this game how do i
fight
it
[Music]
okay
okay get some distance
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay
okay that's better
that's way better
is back under control
[Music]
okay
aroma diffuser
actually yeah i think i currently don't
have one i think once
my my
my air thingies i think they can be used
and then they're wearing my diffuser so
how about the oils i guess
maybe
[Music]
are they serious these are not
enemies that are stronger than the other
ones you
[Music]
um
those aren't good ah yeah that's true
okay that's that idea
um
a plant a nice plant
please i don't know how they would send
that to me but i want plants i want more
plants
i want more plants
more plants
oh and i don't know can you buy it for
50 like a hand um
vacuum cleaner we're just making a list
for christmas at this point
a hand vacuum cleaner
like a small one
the ones that you can pick up with your
hand
[Music]
a room but no no i already have one
no don't call me meet and greet no no no
no no
and if you want to give me something for
document you can take inspiration i
guess but like how the [\h__\h] are you
gonna give me a bicycle right so maybe
choose like one of the smaller ideas
although
what the [\h__\h] here connect ends up
giving me something that you got from
this list as well and then i have a
double but last last gift cards
i can have a million of them and
still make use of it so that's okay
um
they look so scary but they're not a big
deal
my dokomi gift is almost there oh you
ordered something
yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
can they grow back there
uh flying
helicopter thing is i hope not
um
okay oh how about um
uh expensive makeup
like a chanel foundation people always
girls women always swear on the chanel
foundations but i've never tried the
chanel foundation before but apparently
it's like one of the most amazing
foundations ever
and that's something that works for
fifty dollars i would say
i don't know how much this chanel
foundation costs
i think it's probably it
should be fine
stupid [\h__\h]
wasting more time
[Music]
oh heart to match skin tone oh um the
lightest one
after after i'm not pencil anymore tan
choke
then
i'll be back to the lightest white skin
tone
now generally look at my anime skin
doesn't it look like the lightest skin
tone i think so
yeah usually i always go for the
lightest ones but the problem is like
when i buy makeup in austria
usually
for many or most brands they um
they don't go as light as i need them
but then what i would do is whenever i
go went to japan i would like stock up
on foundation in japan because they have
lighter foundations over there in korea
too
so that's magi toscato
in case you haven't noticed i'm playing
a run of wind waker where i'm not
allowed to use my shield ever
because i'm just that skilled
this is why girls thought collab should
happen
i say i say it
you guys really want that the girls
girls talk cool out huh
get these off of me
[Music]
disgusting
[Laughter]
speaking of collabs
i am i'm actually
um
yeah i must really have a talent for
seeing things in a positive light
because remember last time
when i told you that it's looking really
bad with the studios
now i was a little bit disappointed with
that at first but i found a way to look
at it positively
now i'm not gonna spoil why but
i've realized that
if i record it at ama's place
there's one thing that um
[Music]
is
in easier reach
an easier possibility
if i do it that way just i need to drink
something
yeah
so looking at it positively
i i'm not only not only like off collabs
but to be honest when i when i'm going
to
if if i go to
the western lands westeros
then
um
i'm not gonna
stay there like forever oh last bus
or mid bus
oh hello
uh i
i can't stay there for too long
how do you fight things again
just like that okay
ow
[Music]
it would be good to know how the shield
works again
no no however hey i reject that
[Music]
[\h__\h]
bastard
okay
is that iron yeah whatever
hurt cats
i heard cats uh okay bombs
oh how
are they need to eat it wait i know wait
do i just have to hit them was it not
the bums
um
come here
[\h__\h]
arrows oh
you need to shoot them in the middle
um
[\h__\h]
[Music]
all of them
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay
okay okay
what are we talking about liam oh um
why not if i if it's not 100 decided yet
but if i really uh
should
go to
westeros
i'm planning on meeting like maybe also
some none
whole life old friends
[Music]
i don't really know
that like i mean i guess i know a lot of
people but i don't know many that
closely like i not i don't have many
people that i would call friends that i
would
like go visit i suppose
um
but i can think of at least one person
okay time to drink the soup
meet up with arya yeah meet up with
aliya stark
no but that i thought yeah it would be a
nice opportunity
[\h__\h]
make use of it while i'm there i guess
if i'm there
if i go let's i'm just gonna repeat it
and i don't know for sure i am but
yeah
and i need to warn you guys in
june
you know dokomi is happening and then
maybe maybe i might need to go to
the westeros right so
i also need to learn a lot of
choreography still
so in june in preparation for many many
great things
that was not it
there are not
oh going to be as many streams
i kind of want to
force me force myself
to stream less because i know i will
otherwise
um stream too much and then
end up like stressing out
close to the recording date and be like
[\h__\h]
attempt
i'll be like sin i should have uh taken
more days off to practice
so i don't know i'll still do minimum
three
days a week and probably
even more than that maybe four days a
week i have to i have to really try to
limit myself
[Music]
yeah
once i have some choreographies down and
i can safely say that i'm good
then i might go back to normal a bit
more but maybe the first
after document
the first
two weeks
i'll be
[Music]
probably
taking more days off than usual
yes
this is not how you fight them
i guess it was ariel huh
or was it also possible with the what
the
uh what's it called
tickle leaf you can blow them oh
okay
okay okay
i think i never really fought many of
these
just gonna try to stay out of the way
it could take two weeks entirely up no
no no no no no we're not doing that
no no no i don't have like even i feel
like
even if i do that i don't wanna like
practice dances every day that's gonna
make me go crazy
i just need like a few hours per day in
theory
um
but i don't see myself
really like
really sickly speaking i don't see
myself practicing every single day so
there can be some streaming days and
then there can be some
complete practicing days i think i think
um that would work well
yeah but i need to focus on that for
in order to make the
my birthday a success yes
i have
way more than one song planned so
um
[Music]
let's go
yeah
i'm getting
like really worried about a lot of
things
um
actually now maybe now i can say it
because now
no
no it's okay um
you know preparation time for birthday
merchandise is usually like i don't know
six months or so
um
so usually last year as well
we would decide on the artists like
six months ahead of time and then they
would have like six months to draw
whatever they're gonna draw
but i had a lot of issues
this time
and um
artist for one part of my birthday
marriage was decided like
um a couple days ago
so that was also something i was really
really stressed out about because
we only have like about a little bit
more than one month left i'm like holy
[\h__\h]
yeah
oh hello
yeah um
but now it's now it's good
now it's good
we have someone
can i shoot this guy too
yes okay oh that's way easier what the
[\h__\h]
look at them
okay
yes
[Music]
how the hell did that happen um
scheduling problems with like literally
every artist
we would ask and then you know the more
time passes because we always gotta wait
for the reply and then a lot of time
passes and then ask the next one wait
for reply scheduling and then more time
passes so of course even more artists
are gonna be like no we don't have time
so
i was really panicking um what is going
on here
what is going on here
yummy
ah
okay okay
[\h__\h] let's try to get those these skulls
first maybe
okay okay okay okay now i can focus on
the other ones
whoop
pick it up
okay
yeah it's getting chaotic it's getting
chaotic
oh
at least you know what one good thing
actually i mean there's a few good
things but i'm gonna meet genma
[Music]
has again extremely busy
emma has been absolutely busy so i've
been trying to also you know do a lot of
things on my own because i didn't want
to
load on too much on on genma i was
trying to
keep at least a little bit of the
workload away from her
and uh
did some more of the communication with
the people i've been working with on my
own
um
so yeah i wanted to help out a little
bit because i know i know
genma had and still has a lot
to handle right now
oh my
god why is that two
[Music]
where's the eight where's the a what the
actual [\h__\h]
my d
[Music]
maybe i don't know
does this help
no okay cool
take your sword out
i didn't draw my sword oh
uh huh that explains a lot
[Music]
was locking on
yeah i was
did it
realize that
i swear i was pushing lock on
um
how much longer is this
i'm done with
[Music]
um
how about how about we try
taking him but he's so fast
[Music]
what smash
[\h__\h] button smashed yo what's up
what's going on what's going on what's
going on
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
this works against them right no
okay [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
what throwing it works
all right um okay
holy macaroni man
oh it's recovery time i just recovered
with my soap i should have hold on a
little bit longer
hey are we done
this looks like we're done
20 more no [\h__\h] way
hey what if i oh we have a thousand what
if i leave now can i
come back here or do i have to start
from the beginning
two more flowers for useless item oh can
i get the shard at least
now
oh so much money
plate song oh
here
check check
check
designs that reflect the wind are drawn
here
and here
i mean i know what it is but okay
which one are we drawing the wins
requiem
[Music]
is that from the beginning
that's a useless item
like what like money
[Music]
i don't care i guess
mirror shield ah
that like um
boing flips everything
right boing flip is just i remember that
perfectly because i was just watching
that scrubs episode where um the guy
went dead he goes like bow and flip when
people are mean to him
blame flip shield
wait there's no mirror shield oh in this
game
oh it's an extension oh
so it's not the useless item
yay my first tripod start
yo finally
i didn't want to
i guess we're leaving i guess we're
leaving
are we leaving
oh we could continue here
ah
no
i feel like if there's 20 more levels we
might actually
fail
oh hello oh since i don't have soup left
i bet there's a soup places right here
we're like right there so let's get the
soup
it's not worth it okay
[Music]
if you guys say that
then let's not do it but
uh let's
change to daytime
um
[Music]
there we go
because i want to say hi to grandma
again this time i actually needed the
soup
so that's cool uh
[\h__\h]
i thought that was where i had the leaf
sorry for blowing
up your backyard i'm so sorry i'm so
sorry
optional challenge dungeons
returned welcome back
[Music]
okay so now um
people said i shouldn't be looking for
shards i should be going to the tower
i guess so
i tried going originally but then i
couldn't go right
i guess i can go now
yeah the temples
okay
i will be part of your system now
i like how we docked at an actual dock
for once how did we do that
was that really me
doesn't seem like me
nice
so one is right next door basically
over there
was it was that me gameplay oh
see that makes a lot more sense
you know yesterday when i cooked my
hello fresh thingy
i don't know if it's only me but i seem
to have a little bit of
uh
not so much luck with like
getting uh ingredients
that are sometimes
uh
oh
um
already molding so the broccoli that i
was supposed to use yesterday it was
starting to mold a little bit
but i was lucky i had um
frozen broccoli
actually in the freezer so i used that
but does it only happen to me
because okay this time i had just by
coincidence i had the thing i needed
in the freezer
that was necessary from the recipe but
what do i do if i don't have it
last time as well when it happened there
was a bell pepper that was completely
molding inside
and i'm not bad because you didn't
really see it from the outside but
yeah i had to use a bell pepper from a
different recipe that was i was supposed
to cook
it's a known problem
yeah i mean the one on the broccoli also
honestly i don't even know if
because i i i
you know how they put like the things
that you're supposed to put into the
freezer they're in
a bag
with like ice
and the broccoli was not in there so i
just kept it outside for one night so
maybe it was that one night that let it
mold i honestly don't think so but
but um
[Music]
it was just a tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
spot
so sorry um maybe like i'm not mad at
them like you it's hard to see
you have to look like really really
really closely to see that but i don't
know if it was even molding already
before they sent it to me
um
what the the
bell pepper dough hmm
oh well but uh besides that i've been
really happy with it i want to
try cooking something for my mom
and also
um if if
someone comes over from the whole life
girls
i want to cook something for them too
[Music]
heavy stone
i already have that thank you
yeah mommy comes over on monday so i
told her i'll be cooking for her
yeah
oh but you know what happened again now
this really pisses me off they sent me
the ingredients on tuesdays
but you have to choose the recipes until
thursday midnight and yesterday
i just completely missed the timing
so once again you know i'm really picky
like i don't like spicy food
i don't like spinach and then they put
spinach quite in a lot of things and
yeah they now they're two two i think
two out of the dishes that they
now okay wait this time i think it might
have just been one
one of the three dishes that i
that were picked automatically for me
it's something i don't i don't wanna eat
or make and you can't change it anymore
after that
so that kind of sucks oh yeah seafood as
well like when they give me like a
shrimp
meal or something
that's also very very danden
very mutainai
wow it's hard it's really hard but at
least this time
because i noticed i missed the timing
for the next week i already chose the
recipes for the following week after
that
yeah
i always gotta think ahead you know
surprised you have to like choose so
early though
wait i kinda what is this what's gonna
happen am i going in a dungeon because i
wanna spend my money first before i go
in a dungeon is this gonna lead me to a
dungeon
five million of sriracha
that might partially be true
uh not yet okay
just a cutscene first okay
uh but wait that's way too long
[Music]
i'm feeling sick i need food
down up
down down middle right left middle [\h__\h]
down down middle right left middle
i sleep early i wake up early and then i
even take a nap
i'm always so tired
especially after the mall leaves though
but i don't think i'm jet lagged first
of all oh hello
does she have bread on her head
oh i thought it was bread a toast
i wanted to say
i don't think i'm jet-lagged because i
think the time difference was only like
three hours
and i adjusted just fine i think
[Music]
i guess i should take vitamins oh no
i have no energy
i'm dead inside and outside
just dead
there's a zombie
am only
now it's too early it's only been like
three and a half hours i don't know
maybe i'm getting old maybe
maybe kiwamo the endurance streamer is
no more maybe kiwamo from now on every
day maximum three hours
so sad what happened
what happened to me
keep up
oh i think but i think it's like you
know after doing this job for over one
year i just
uh i don't know how the japanese girls
do it they have like endless energy
to keep on going but i can't stream that
long anymore
but i don't want to lose my
my title you know
of endurance streamer of ian or like
long long stream
i don't want to lose that
oh but like
so dead inside and outside my face is so
tired my voice is tired
speaking of that let's take a fruit
candy before i die completely
[Music]
maybe we need to do
ptm fitting maybe we need to do shortest
dreams for a while i don't know
um
uh sure it's chat like i don't think so
i don't know but but one thing that the
jet lag did is that i like wake up
earlier
but i still need my naps but i think
that's okay
i was talking with my mom today and she
was making fun of me that maybe you know
maybe i'm like a grandma now who needs
their naps and i said no it's the other
way around don't you remember how like
when you were a child you also need to
take a nap like even even the school
makes you take a nap like when you're
really really small
mm-hmm
yeah it's like that i'm going that way
not not to grant my way no no i'm going
the other way
see your style
yes
vitamin mineral deficiency maybe yeah
maybe i've been feeling like that for a
while to be honest
i've been just trying to keep on going
because that's just like
i don't know the pressure of
having to keep on putting out content
and
wanting to make the most out of it and
wanting to
work hard and until
a certain point of time like for example
like my birthday and then i'm like after
my birthday i can chill a little bit
but then i don't know
uh it just keeps on continuing
[Music]
i know i'm always the one who says take
a take a break but this is also a thing
like i i just took a break
i can't like say
i'm exhausted now i literally just came
back from the maldives you know what i
mean
that's why i didn't want to say anything
and that's why i also don't want to
stream less in june because i just came
back from a vacation but i have to
stream less in june because i need to
focus on learning choreographies um
i did work in the maldives i know
[Music]
i'm not kaicho i'm tensha
sometimes people get that wrong
[Music]
it's okay i'm not mad
um
i also need to
practice one or two songs for dokomi um
that's okay dokomi is gonna be fine
i think
[Music]
i did see by the way
um the
winners for the meet and greet
so you guys should be notified soon i
think
and holy [\h__\h] i am
shocked
guys
i am
shocked
uh at the sheer amount of
people coming from outside of
germany i mean i also obviously i
appreciate everyone coming from germany
too
but
you guys are crazy
you guys are insane
shukev i am
shooketh
for like i i feel bad about it because
it's like just one day
you guys come from so far for
one freaking day
i feel like and i i don't know how to
give back enough
to make it worthwhile for you guys for
one day
[Music]
i'll only be there for one day
you guys are crazy i hope you'll enjoy
it i really hope so
[Music]
my name is
for an age i offered my prayers here in
the earth temple
praying that the power to repel evil
would ever remain within the master
sword
[Music]
and yet
unfortunately due to ganondorf's evil
designs the mass desert you hold has
lost its power
after his defeat at the hands of the
hero of time ganondorf was sealed away
but not for all time he was revived and
he returned to hyrule in a red
he attacked his temple and stole my soul
knowing that he had to remove the power
contained in that enchanted glaive
in order to return the power to repel
evil to your sword you must find another
to take my stead in this temple and ask
the gods for their assistance
you must find the one who carries on the
bloodline
the one who holds the sacred instrument
well i know
a bird but i thought i need to find a
dora
is it okay if it's a bird
[Music]
nothing can stop the flow of time or the
passing of generations but the faith
carried within my bloodline endures the
ravages of all the years
it survives
the song you just conducted is one that
will open the eyes of the new sage and
awaken within that sage the melody that
will carry our prayers to the cons
the door that blocks your way will only
open when the sage plays that song
may the winds of fortune glow with you
yeah
you know i was gonna say it where the
[\h__\h] do i find the zora but then she
they hinted at the the instrument and i
guess okay
i guess they just want
the burp girl from the very beginning
there has evolved to read us
that is interesting lore
no more yeah
you're right we haven't met the single
dora
okay wait took them out there where is
uh that island again
what's it called again
uh
huh
dragon roost
uh
here let's go there
i hope it's not too difficult to get a
hold of her
[Music]
name
let's also go shopping i
i need to guess
my money somehow
but what is there to buy besides bombs
and all that [\h__\h]
why doesn't he not have something more
interesting huh
how else do i spend my money guys
in the game
save it you're gonna need it how do i
save it where do i put it
can i save it somewhere
was there a way to put money away
auction
what's there for me to win in the
auction still
golden beers trump local
appears i will need them pears
[Music]
[Applause]
stop
stop it
thank you
a bigger money bag yeah that would be
nice
i don't know where that another fairy
island is currently
we should find that
hye pear
can i please buy more than one at once
oh my god
[Music]
buy seagulls berries yeah guys for now
thank you
ah at least he always says thank you you
know very important
gratitude
huh what
are you telling me i have enough of this
that's the maximum
[Music]
i need to use my money
we have to
use it somehow
they share a bag oh come on
it does look familiar to me um but i
need to do something
[Music]
so we either go to the ferry
if you guys know where it is or we go to
the auction
what do you think
[Music]
no
no black fortune no
no i want to mix
and like when i'm like okay if i just
finished like a long
playthrough then i don't mind doing like
shorter ones for like two weeks or so
but one as long as i'm doing a play
through i'm not gonna have like you know
one week
wind wake awaken and one week no i mean
that right now that's unfortunately how
it's been happening but that's not
supposed to how it's supposed to be
happening
anyway
what
no as long as we're playing
a longer one but you know after wind
waker
for june we're not gonna start anything
new
uh that quickly
we probably need
i don't know how many more streams if we
play it on sunday again and then maybe
on when on wednesday
maybe we can finish it
and then for the rest of june we don't
we're not going to pick up any
new big game
so
um
because i don't have time for it anyway
um guys where do we go
um do you guys know uh the island the
fairy island that's close by
uh that's um it has the
the
money bag
warped to windfall
windfall
[Music]
ah the tingle map shows and oh i forgot
about that
oh wait that's also close so here uh-huh
we could also go to the auction but oh
well um
no foreign
i didn't hear that
you did not hear that
i see it
[Music]
yesterday when i cooked yesterday
the chicken by the way was really
good it was chicken breast so maybe
that's why this time i had an easier
time
baking it
i'm gonna eat that again today because i
have two more pieces of the chicken
breast
already
you know um
breaded and fried
in the oven
but i think this time i'm gonna
combine it with something else not with
what you saw yesterday
cause someone on twitter told me i
should you know eat it with
um
bolognese and spaghetti and i'm like yo
yo yo yo yo that sounds really good so
i'm gonna do that
i still have bolognese sauce in my
freezer from like long ago
yeah
billy deserved it
it was a volunteer
what's that
yeah chicken parmesan i know i know
which is perfect because like the
breading of the
chicken breast
um is with parmesan already
that's the bubbles that you can see on
the picture
the bubbles those are not bubbles those
are just uh
the parmesan that i put in mixed into
the breading the panko breading
yeah rachel
why is that dude here
what is he telling me about a piece here
i'll talk to you in a moment
[Music]
why the chunks so big
i don't know they uh
like sometimes
recipes are a bit weird sometimes they
don't
say
they don't write things accurately but
they wanted they said they said
shaved parmesan
but what they gave me was
um chunky parmesan but maybe it belonged
to a different recipe i'm not sure
but i couldn't find any other parmesan
so i just put the chunky parmesan into
the breading and i'm like yo this is
kind of difficult
um
shredded yeah but it was chunky chunky
pieces of parmesan
money back
become big
it was good though the chimpkin was
really good
5000 all right
that's much better
that is much better oh
we have the soup we have a fairy all
right let's go
maybe so you can chop it up no that's
weird
and they should have just given me a
proper piece of parmesan and then make
me
make me shredded
hello
oh-ho-ho so that is how that works it
oh he's looking at something over there
should i look at it too but this dude
um
let's look at it from here
i can't see
can't see [\h__\h]
is he looking at that
i don't know what he's looking at
yummy
okay
i don't care
yeah like little blocks
okay
tsugiwa let's go to where
uh where are the other temple which is
right all next
to this
one
the top one we didn't go to yet i think
really gonna go there now i'm hungry
though
dragon worst oh
should i not go to this island yet okay
dragon balls where was dragon roose down
down here
okay
hey guys how can i go to idol meeting
and
hungry but
i'm hungry but wants big food not small
food
[Music]
let's see how i feel after idle meeting
maybe i'll feel more refreshed
i'll bear a beat one second
yeah i have chunky monkey
i'm gonna eat chunky monkey
hello
um yeah
no
just kidding
i'm just gonna give her kisses
oh
but
um
[Music]
yeah wait it's already oh [\h__\h] it's
already here
i first have first nine
[Music]
i was gonna
make a make a baguette
put a baguette in the oven
and then
play
um like a couple hours longer but if we
end up like playing so long as midnight
then i should just
not eat the bucket no
because oh no maybe i'm fine you know
what the paquet is on
baguette now
and then
in
it will be done in what 20 minutes
and then in three hours when i'm gonna
end the stream
now i'm gonna make my proper food
yeah i'm heating the oven now
i have like uh
unfortunately not a garlic baguette but
it's an interesting baguette
because it's a logan
bucket with
herbs
logan bucket
what's logan
[Music]
in english
chunky wonky is getting impatient too
i'll see people are coming back that's
interesting
welcome back guys did you like uh
did you change the window and that's why
it went down by like 300 is that what
happened
does it like not count you once you
switch to a different window
chunky requires the bread she does not
get the bread
yeah laughing bucket with koita
thinks
it doesn't count tapped out yeah
not
but i don't know if you guys have the
answer to that let's say you have for
example free screens
um like me and you have a screen
on one one screen you have
in a window you have a like a stream
open
and on a different window you have like
i don't know for the shop or whatever
open and you're working on photoshop
does youtube recognize that your mouse
is currently active somewhere else on a
different screen since you clicked on it
and does it have to be like the active
window so would that also not count
it won't
we don't know
active one really oh my god
even though like i have it open in full
screen on one screen
that would be really [\h__\h] because like
let me watch something on the side hello
yeah
i was wondering about that also when
like you know
um
streaming music on youtube
like music videos
like i was wondering if it's okay to
just have it like open on one screen
does it
is this counting method only for streams
or also for videos if i have it on one
screen and i i do photoshop on the other
screen
and i have the music video running works
the same for real
wow
the more you know
eh
everybody who's watching right now and
not tabbed in tabin right now let's do
an experiment or everybody tap out for a
moment
everybody tap out who is not on the
phone
who's on a pc i guess everybody tap out
and then come back in like 10 seconds
i want to see this
let's see if people follow my request
experimenting
can't phone that's okay it's okay you
can't tap out on tv oh you're watching
on tv not a hotel
return from that's too fast i don't see
a change in my
you guys are too fast impatient didn't
see a single change in my
viewership here on my
on my stats
okay okay how about how about uh 45
seconds i'll miss you though okay let's
start three two one go
45 seconds one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
18. i see you guys still in the chat yo
22 23
20 are you guys really gone 26
27 it's not going down
it's not really i mean a little bit you
guys are not following my order i told
you guys to leave and you're here
30 41
35 no 44 what's pretty free
but i don't wanna
be lazy
lazy little [\h__\h]
whatever
46 37 48 49
40.
nothing's changing
i don't know about you guys because you
look at it from
a different window i look at it from
youtube studio honestly it just changed
by maybe
um
viewers maybe and that's just like a
normal
fl flexion
what do you call it
i don't know did you guys really leave
maybe you didn't leave for long enough
or
maybe you being in the chat fluctuation
thank you
oh [\h__\h]
i need to quickly send a dm
and toto
important it's about my song
it
okay
i have so many dms
[Laughter]
something about the
thing that i told you guys about that i
can't tell you about
oh i want to look
[Music]
top secret
forgot to come back after 45 welcome
welcome back we kind of gave up on the
experiment
uh-huh
oh
did you guys know um
oh baby my my oven is heated
you guys know there might be
we might we might play um
catherine or
or
one of the persona games in the future
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't know much about persona i just i
like the visuals i never played one
before but it seems like
we
we can play it
soon and maybe after maybe after
wind waker you know after june
after my birthday i i do like catherine
dell like i i know it's a
a funny game
um i did see a playthrough for catherine
like a long long long long long time ago
very funny game
yeah i know kelly's screaming i still
hear her she's been screaming for a
while
[Laughter]
i i really don't know like which persona
game is like good and
which which is the popular one
well but i want to try it out because
like the the aesthetics are the visuals
are definitely
my kind of stuff right you guys you guys
know i'm a sucker for those anime
graphics visuals
five royal three and four
aha is it but is it chronological do you
have to play them chronologically
they're long that's okay we always play
long games
no okay
wow take a look at it
and see
uh which one i want to play
i suppose we should also just not play
the one that kelly's gonna play because
i i assume that she's gonna
probably make use of it very soon
ah wait i need to put the baguettes in
the oven
let me put the baguettes in the oven
are people tabbing out again
nope i'm back
uh reminds me in
nine minutes
maybe
all the time yeah the time is very wrong
ignore the time
because it's the second hand when i i
didn't change the time i think
nine minutes for the baguette where are
we going uh dragon wrist island
let's go
i have energy where does the energy come
from
it's me looking forward to the buckets
[Music]
oh foreign
look at that
would you look at that oh by the way
since i look at this bad weather and i i
think of the monsoon weather of the
maldives
i'm
in hindsight
you know during the first couple days
where it was so [\h__\h]
uh
we say it like that but honestly i mean
[Music]
it was okay
like i think if i were to go against the
maldives i wouldn't exactly mind
going to the maldives in monsoon season
again
because
if it's already this hot
during non-monsoon season
during monsoon season
oh
look at that then i think
i'm gonna have a problem
uh
i should wait i don't have it
i'm gonna have a problem when uh it's uh
like
the best season you know um
the full heat was yeah without the
clouds and all that
it was pretty tough to handle
and if i if i think about like being a
full week
in that heat
i might die
uh
[Music]
yeah and and and i i don't know how true
this is but the staff from the island
told us that even in monsoon season it
is very rare oh
i thought i would get a
i thought the tall um
beams of lights are
the shards oh well
um
what was i saying oh yeah the staff told
us that it's not that normal
that
even in monsoon season it's not normal
to
you know
have it like storming and raining for
three days straight
that's
apparently not normal oh it means i have
a c chart okay okay
so
that's good to know
that means that normally maybe there's
just one day of storming and then two
days of sun and one day of storming and
two days of sun but like three days in a
row it's apparently not so normal
so
yeah they said they were surprised too
about the shitty weather
maybe we were just pretty unlucky and
normally it's not that bad
but even with
even with what it was i think
it was manageable and um
i don't know i would go again
it's unpredictable yeah very
unpredictable like i would i would look
at the weather report in the morning
and even for the weather on the very
same day
it would be inaccurate
so when we checked the renova port like
one week ahead of time or so
you know it was absolute [\h__\h] we
were not only me you guys you chat you
were so worried like oh my god she's
going to the maldives but look at the
weather oh it's going to be ruined
but honestly it was all [\h__\h] like no
worries what is that up there
no
[Music]
where is the girl
i was panicking young i was worried i
didn't know what to expect
up okay
where's the girl
where is the girl in here
oh
hello
hope you oh i hoped i would get the
chance to thank you in person
are you gonna give me something
[Music]
no
you're not giving me anything
you're thanking me for like helping your
both of your children
oh no one of your child and one of you
or i don't know
are you not gonna give me anything
wow
[Music]
where is she
here
[Music]
she's outside
oh that freaking mini game i'm not gonna
try this one again
oh i hear the music she's there
i'm on my way
[Music]
oh she's not really good at it though
she's just playing the same root uh note
over and over again
ah she changed one
she's not that good though are we sure
we should leave it to her
are we sure we can leave that job of the
gods to her
she sucks at playing that harp
[Music]
are you hearing this
are you listening to this campaign
ah okay if she's tuning it yes okay
maybe she's tuned it doesn't look like
she's tuning it though
she's she looks like she's seriously
trying to play it
can you say when it will be released uh
well yeah it should be
between saturday and sunday it's kind of
like difficult to say because like it
will be different depending on your time
zone but if you're on the sea time zone
then it should be like
on
like
midnight from saturday to sunday
but
uh
if you're
not sca then it might just be saturday
um
but yeah the music uh service release
like spotify and so on will be
midnight of your country and then the
music video itself will be kiwa standard
time gmt plus two uh at four pm
i think
four pm
you okay
should i hold my nose when i do her
voice maybe it will sound more
like a bird
no
principal molly's been asking me all
about your treacherous chihuahua
well that hurts
i can arrest easy now that i'm sick or
safe and sock with my own eyes
but come on you turn into a young adult
hesitate
recently he would begun doing links on
his own without my guidance
every conversation still ends up
centered on youtube i can speak
perfectly normal
what what what's
watching
grow up fills me with pride but it makes
me a little sad as well i wonder if this
is how a button feels
listen to me go on how long am i
well i'd better continue practicing so
that i could be useful around here too
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'll conduct you
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
my nose
why did i do that
let's watch this scene
with a mysterious song it sounds
familiar
it's almost as if something i've
forgotten is trying to be remembered
oh
oh i feel
oh [\h__\h] she's dead
i killed her with my music
oh
no
no bucket is fine it's going to be fine
oh
huh
[Music]
oh
that sounds familiar
[Music]
that sounds very familiar what is that
again
which soundtrack was there
[Music]
she can do it she can do it after all
okay we can leave it to her
[Music]
don't even get me started
oh
hot
oh is she back but she's still dead
just now i still spoke to me she spoke
so gently i don't hear her speaking okay
there's something something that i must
do
kiwawa thanks to you i've been awakened
to the knowledge that i'm a sage of the
earth temple holy [\h__\h] was she always
destined to do this i wonder
man
she's so young and now she has to leave
her home
and we'll go to a temple when basically
no one will visit her for another 100
[\h__\h] years so sad
the baguette i know
there's actually something that i can do
to help this word world it's incredible
i bet my teacher knew all about this oh
he cried
come on please you must take me to the
earth temple
you must hurry and make the power to
repel the evil that sleeps within the
monster sword
okay
hmm can the bird take us
uh
i can't go now to the baguette this is
really emotional
let's go now quickly and quietly
wow the music
oh kumali i just want him to remember me
as a simple attendant is are you in love
thought she was in love with me
why are you eh say goodbye come on
you could have said goodbye
she's even just sitting there in my boat
unbelievable bucket
it's so hot
ah
are you so hot
hello
hello hello
where did i put my glass
where's my glass
i don't have a glass
where's my class
what
okay okay okay i have the glass now
we're sure
we're sure there was no fire
it was all right the baguette is fine
it's looking delicious but i have to
wait because i'm nekojita
i am
[Music]
yeah it will be very crunchy though
oh
it looks amazing don't forget if only it
was garlic man garlic would make it even
better
but it's okay
we'll make the most out of it
we are gonna go while waiting for the
baguettes to cool down a little bit
we're gonna go to
uh
the temple at the bottom right so
we have to play some music again
um
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h]
wind waker be like
this one
it here
[Music]
not going to impress the girl like dad
huh not trying to impress her anyways
i like tetra aka zelda more
over here
[Music]
power of spin by the power of spin
i teleport die
to
the place you
so desire
[Music]
let's go
ah one more thing yeah
remember how i i wonder if i told you
this
remember how i requested um that game
for members only
oh
uh the one the townscaper game
and after a while finally we got
permission so other people started
playing it too for members only did i
tell you that i got another one
approved
did i maybe i did maybe i did
did
i not
see cities skylines
which i feel like ahmed will enjoy
playing in members only as well
yeah yeah yeah that's it is a good game
i've seen uh someone play it before not
a not a youtuber but yeah
yeah so uh thanks thanks to me once
again we can play another members only
game let me know if someone else plays
it
[Laughter]
let me know
huh a dlc is available at humble bundle
for
an 20. you like
i don't i look you like like part of
their
promotional team or something
advertisement team
uh
no of course uh for non-membership too
but you know i was just looking for
games more games to play on membership
so i will play it on membership mm-hmm
simcity is okay for no membership
streams but the
city skylines i got specifically for
members
there's a europe dlc
wait i want that i do want that
okay so
i want i want to bite into my bucket
oh yeah
good stuff
um
my tummy is so happy now
no
floor is not messy i have a plate hmm
[Music]
mm-hmm
okay
so i can make her shut up and follow me
okay it's that r
um
[Music]
no wait which song
no teleportation song or what
okay
um
and the stone statue one okay
ah
um
[Music]
even with one hand
ah
wow
oh the baguette is so good
um
come on
uh-huh
with that eye she follows me if i do it
again does she stay
eh
i can't do it again but if i do um a
i can pick her up and we can fly yeah
let's go
hold on no problem
okay do you follow me now girl
oh
open up where is she
ah she's in the beginning follow me
i said art doesn't work
i should carry her through the doors
oh okay
she won't walk for doors with you you
have to carry her
oh escort mission let's go
thank you lenska thank you
i'm sure it will be a banger yeah i was
really really really happy to see that
so many people
were excited about the genre already
i'm actually
oh
they're looking for me i'm actually
surprised though that
really not many people guessed
synthwaved up
because i kept on asking you guys what
do you think
what do you think it's going to be
and yet
yeah most of you didn't guess it most of
the time should we kill this guy
i'm gonna fly over
at the buttons
okay
i suppose we can
um
both be on one button at the same time
[Music]
steal his stuff i don't need this stuff
my stuff is better
[Applause]
um good job how do we land oh thank you
and now
uh i guess i could fly over there with a
leaf
because
i'll just uh how do i
place her normally like this
uh
oh wait can i control her as well
with the yeah
i have to control her
of the with the command
[Music]
then i'll stay here
um command melody
and i fly with her
while controlling her over to the other
side and stand on the button
i guess was it also an option to
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i thought she would fly it like kind of
like automatically okay um
was it also an option to oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
to fly with the leaf i wonder
ah
okay this is how you fly
learning by doing does it load up back
ah again i wonder
go ah [\h__\h] again
oh no you didn't well now they lost
track of me so uh very nice
okay start flying before jumping how
about that
okay
uh let me take a bite
hey why's she walking oh my god the
drifting holy [\h__\h]
yummy
um
and go back
we go back
we pick her up
see because like if you do it like this
she flies automatically you know what
that means
you come down here
what was it about you know having her
follow me silently
why does that not work my father was
that r
it was not this one
um
said i went close ow
i'm close am i not close
she's stuck oh god damn it
it's already a wonderful start
[Music]
stupid girl
um
[Music]
wait for the next one uh-huh
yeah i know that was only just the
beginning
um there's just a lot of them
you just wait here i'll take care of
them
show him those moves
all those are really strong
and
how do you kill them
i never had those black ones before
ah because like they disappear once i
hit them
sunlight
sunlight i don't have the mirror shield
though is that okay
oh i just have to leave them here
no
i've picked them up and throw them
[Music]
aha
that's what that light is for
now you took the whole dough
works before they
ah just when they are stones right okay
i remember
oh
her heart is a mirror
i think i remember that
uh-huh
um
wait
do i have to do that well
no i'll just put her
with her back
to the chest
i'll just put uh right here
oh no she looks at me okay okay
eh
i think she has to be higher
um
i guess i'll control her then
[Music]
seems like we have to do this a lot of
times
[Music]
nice
it's probably just a rupee
[Music]
i've been eating a baguette but i
haven't been uh
haven't been chewing it so well i keep
on getting like some big uh spiky pieces
in my throat that's not so good
uh i should put a bump on this one right
uh
oh that works if it's just been
the sides on the side okay okay
okay girl let's go
oh you're so sparkly
what about these boys though they look
so sus is there nothing with them right
now
all right next next one
can i use my shield too
as a reflection even though i don't have
the mirror shield
so you stay here
and i guess i'll go here
and then
i
it's not that easy isn't
it
as if as if it was that easy okay
okay do i maybe i don't have to do them
both at the same time
ah
ah come on
[Music]
it has to be at the same time
so what does she stay like this
different
ah
did she stay like that
she doesn't stay like that perfect okay
but then what about me
um
i don't reflect the lights though
you can clear the fog
oh okay
i don't have the mirror shield then
we're gonna be missing out on something
ah there's a hammer thingy
yeah i'm getting sick of it
i can't use my weapons when i
i'm sick okay
uh
how much time until the fall goes back
let's just make it a bit more
clear
yeah
and back
oh that opens the door
is that just a
a different solution
if you have the mirror shield it's like
kind of easier maybe
oh no
no i get the mirror shield later and if
i do that then i can open that door
maybe i don't know whatever
we'll see
we'll see we'll see
we'll see how it goes for now we have a
new open door
and more bucket ah
on
[Music]
okay
you're safe girl i'm surprised she
didn't burn because of that
[Music]
yeah yeah that was killed
i was killed she was like yo i can't get
up there
it's okay i'll protect you what do we do
about this one we need some light here
oh a button
18th birthday but i've only just gotten
the money to give you my super first
superstar thank you
happy belated birthday
[Music]
she has plot armor
oh
so this uh of course
uh goes back to its original state maybe
we move this down
can we
oh
i didn't expect that okay
but it was necessary
come here
sorry come here come here
and now
you do the thing
right
i know we already used it
we're already used to before it is not
my first time
i'm surprised she tells me now
[Music]
you
link feel the lights feel the power
can i not turn around like oh wait
okay
wow
[Music]
yeah blind him forever
that that will be her way of being
forever with link because if she's if
she is at fault for blinding him for the
rest of his life
then it wouldn't wouldn't it make sense
you know to have her
be his
guide for the rest of his life and then
then they get me forever together
exactly what she wanted
[Music]
kind of yandere but
you have to do
certain things sometimes you know
uh
i have a key
should i go for the other door with the
key first
why that's so scary no go away
i don't like this enemy
and there's two
why no i don't like it
no i don't like it and don't show should
i go back or should i go
i go away
[Music]
how did i kill them
i don't like them do i throw like a bomb
into them can i do that
i don't like them
i don't like them at all
um
yeah
pro girl now
[Music]
that's kind of difficult
i'm not gonna throw her in there no um
i don't know should we go wait let me
look at the map
ah there's just one more extra room
there that probably has a key too
[Music]
okay can i like go through without her
she just stays here
how about that
can i do that is she gonna be safe
without me
she'll be at the beginning of the room
probably if i go back
will you stay here
i go through without you can you stay
there ah
[\h__\h] i got a minute yes stay there
wait you went there on your own can i
make you stay how do you make your stay
again um
um
stay
i just oh
uh does she stand like this okay
okay okay okay
okay put this up
you can just bring her back here
[Music]
no i can't
i wouldn't be able to do that
i think
[Music]
i need her in here
i need to shell shield either i need to
shield or i need
her with me
but okay
oh [\h__\h] our eyes are scary
quick let's go
let's go
fast
pretty the other door first
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
wow
yum
[Music]
even though it's not garlic bread it
definitely has garlic in it i love it
garlic bread the love of my life
yeah
the garlic bread facebook group is the
only reason for me to still open up
facebook
besides that
there's no more reason to
use facebook ever again
i need light
can i
didn't i have a
like a vacuum machine or was it a
different dollar game
maybe maybe maybe it just works anyway
or i can boomerang it or when i need to
get high fire
oh i forgot about the errors
um they can't go up right okay
or can they
i shall
switch arrow
uh
[\h__\h]
uh one more
oh one of them was a ray of lights just
go who would have expected that
[Music]
i think
i can use them
to put them on the on the switches now
[Music]
appleton
hmm [\h__\h] yeah okay they give you more
because this happens
if you're a sassy buckler like me and
this happens
[Music]
okay
let's see how it is i see how it is oh
[\h__\h] no no for god's sake
[Music]
okay okay okay okay go go go go go go
come with me
come on faster
i was gonna
mold at you
he's gonna yell at you girl you saved
yourself
oh she could have fly a flu flow flew
nap yeah i guess so
i
tend to forget that
she's pretty useful
oh she even walked through without me
carrying her
yeah
oh no there's the hand again what how
did i kill it is there no way to kill
is there it way to get rid of it
can i just attack it when the hand is
like out sorted really okay i'm scared
arrows are safest okay
[Music]
oh my god
that's terrifying
that is terrifying
i'm so scared
huh
[Music]
hmm
well think about that one in a second
first we bring you over there
that wasn't necessary but okay so
control you once again i wish there was
like a shortcut man
[\h__\h]
no
no no
[Music]
um what's your name again medley
medley and medley do i have to
uh
light it at this thing there it seems so
wow
mainly like a song medley
wow so smart is that a shortcut to the
first room
no
no uh not this but uh the the pot itself
is a shortcut i suppose
okay
don't really need that but uh
that works
i was
i was just testing things out but yeah
that's how you play games you test
things out you know
i didn't really expect that to work
there we go
[Music]
that does not look important enough to
be the mirror shield but maybe
[Music]
maybe it could be uh the compass thingy
oh yeah i need another ah wait there's
one more
down down
results into nothing upon being hit with
light yeah
logic but okay that's okay we will
accept it and be thankful and grateful
for it
i don't even need to hire one toy
just for completion's sake
okay
[Music]
uh-huh
um
i'm almost done eating it though
[Music]
girl
come with me
can you get up here probably not
um
[Music]
sorry guys i'm not talking much because
of the bucket hmm
[Music]
yeah but thanks to the baguettes i can
at least keep going a little bit longer
but i should start reading super chat
soon
i wonder how much longer this dungeon is
we will definitely stop
uh at the end of it
i don't know how many super chats i have
to read um
[Music]
fairies
i didn't really need them but okay
it took you two hours yeah
so so long oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] he saw me
oh he lost track of me okay i'm going
again
[Music]
um
first take care of them and then take
care of the ghosts
how do i take care of them i don't know
wait no i want that
okay i think oh i think i have an idea i
think maybe let's try grabbing
uh uh
okay
yeah can i i think my idea was nice but
oh it does work so what happens after
nothing really
it's controlling me
as long as it doesn't attack medley all
is good
can you please get out of my body excuse
me
um
wait ready to go
[Music]
is that how you kill them you let them
um control you once
there must be a better way to fight them
[Music]
come on come on
it can't be that [\h__\h] difficult to
get the thing why did it work the first
time it doesn't work the second time
oh [\h__\h] you bastard
[Music]
that makes no sense
oh
ah
[Music]
i thought link could take care of it but
i guess i need the girl
uh
[Music]
okay
what
hey you don't like that do you but the
other one really disappeared after
taking control of me
quick quick quick quick
[Music]
okay
well that's that
nice so that door opened but we i guess
we can get rid of these ones as well
[Music]
you need to put the ferris inside the
bottle yeah see the thing is you don't
see my inventory but i already have two
full bottles so
i know how to deal with fairies but i'm
just that much of a pro gamer that i
never have an empty bottle you know
but thank you for
worrying about
me picking up the fairies
i have one with a soup and one with a
fairy i think i'm perfectly covered
man too good to get hit
but okay i i don't want to
be that cocky because
the game is relatively easy
oh is that that remember
no no i guess not i got too excited
oh
you're kidding
uh
that sucks
come on
what about that light though
maybe for later when i have a shield
mm-hmm
i've never seen someone climb stairs
like that before
ever
oh [\h__\h] up nice
it's scary
i'm gonna open up once i get closer to
my supplies
so you should stay
for now
oh [\h__\h] these ones i
scream at you
how do you
after
you're done being shooketh it's fine but
how do you
like
not to get screamed at
um
[Music]
hey it's not even one of the monsters
i thought they weren't all of them
yeah
okay that should work that's close
enough
nada
[Music]
i always tank the scream yeah it seems
fine they're so slow but like there must
be a better way to do it
ah maybe wait why can't i not just shoot
it down with an arrow
hey they don't they don't care they just
look at me
maybe fire
wait turn around
[Music]
then i don't know maybe the hammer
there must be a better way
[Music]
let me test it out though okay that's
not what i wanted to test
[Music]
out again
i like hugs but that kind of hug is not
really
not really what i
expected
this is like when you meet your
grandparents for the first time in
one year because you never go visit them
and they're like oh my baby finally you
come visit me
a little [\h__\h]
which i don't experience anymore because
no grandparents sad
i want me a grandma who gives me
soup man
that's okay i'm okay
you guys just be my grandparents instead
okay
girl i need you
can can you guys be my grandparents
can you guys give me soup i want that
soup
cheek finches
well all right i guess
i guess you can cheek my peach what what
girl girl follow me
looks like a dangerous room
[Laughter]
wait wait wait wait
wait am i supposed to go in here without
you
[Laughter]
is she not i don't need her okay
yeah um wait no no let's forget what i
just said that was a mistake
hello
um how do i
fight you friend
[Music]
i don't know
so much for the shockwave doing
something for me
oh ow hey
really
whatever i'll need anything
ah
[Music]
so easy another one
okay okay okay i don't mind fighting
more than one
yeah this soundtrack is nice can i
please um get my items though thank you
for the cutscene
but
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
okay i picked them all up should i use
this can i use this
oh so good
[Music]
[\h__\h]
stay still
it's a little bit loud though the
soundtrack
[Music]
all right come at me bro
here he comes and he's dizzy
[Music]
oh well brute force it is
come here
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] i didn't even need to use the
hammer did i
[Music]
don't make it so difficult for me
here we go
bumps i didn't need the bombs
[Music]
for once i wanted to use the hammer
yeah we don't get to use it that often
so
it's the mirror shield it's the mirror
let's go
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah
[Music]
hmm
nice one
oh
what
look at that drift
hmm
yes
i need some time
i'm eating but i have one last piece of
my bucket left one last piece
look at that sun it looks a little bit
drunk
also it's part of like the yin and yang
balance
as all things should be
future is so bright you need a pair of
shades
which uh yes uh
i'll be getting from ina
in the valkyrie connect collab
right
what was this door in order
i had that room
yeah you know you know it's getting me
those shades
uh
oh hello you again wonderful
i need to go
uh to that room
oh gosh it's pretty far can we like um
speed through here
i guess so
do i really have to walk back
oh no
oh oh ah you can't get me
what if i take the pot hello
we're going this way
this feels wrong like normally you don't
have to like walk all the way back
just feels uh like something is wrong
[Music]
here this is where i wanted to go but i
feel like maybe i wasn't supposed to go
like this
all right anyway
[Music]
and leave it right option
leave it right
[Music]
here
and i try to do it just like you
hey wait doesn't that kind of look like
the
screaming monsters that were coming out
of the
that were coming out of the out of the
scary
[Music]
oh
okay
i'll read that statue
um
this is the last boss something like a
re-dead i hope not
all that screaming man
oh but that's so fitting because ollie
also screams a lot
maybe that's just a thing that zombies
do like they're like i don't know
they're so
um
lacking of life
that it makes them scream i don't know
what is the reasoning i wonder
um can we not fly
all the time
oh yeah only hugs i i think so
i think dana told me a little bit about
like other whole live indonesia members
we talked a little bit about kobo
and muna
and dolly
i think i think she told me that ollie
is kind of
touchy
[Music]
reina told me that the people like i i
told reyna that my
like expection of her expression
expectation of her was that she's gonna
be really touchy because people were
saying that she's really touchy
and then she was like no that's not true
that's just no not at all why do you why
why do people say that like she
yeah i was surprised that you guys you
guys were like the whole life indonesia
fans say that about her
she doesn't see herself like that
i think she said that it's more like the
other members are touchy
and then and then it seems like she's
the touchy one but that's not true
oh yeah
wait
i angered it
[\h__\h]
[Music]
wind uh when they're coming at me but
maybe cause like from here i can't reach
because they're up so high
so i'll have them
[Music]
come at me oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh
oh okay i think that one is done for
hello
can you see me
yes
[Music]
oh i needed to land here so i can kill
it properly that wasn't good enough huh
hello
wait that door
it's like we're already at the end
how did that take someone the two hours
[\h__\h] you come here come here
no
yeah
and fell down
it's coming back
[\h__\h]
wow
um hello
notice me senpai
i don't need to kill them
i can stun them i want to kill them
because they're annoying
they always you know when you want them
to notice you they don't notice you but
when you don't want them to notice you
then they notice you
see i'll show you now see how it didn't
notice me when i wanted it to notice me
now we're gonna run for hoping it won't
notice me
it's going to notice me yeah see i told
you
i told you
now she gets hurt oh my god
i can't use it
[Music]
hi i'm here
hi
okay you know what
um
is that the same again
it is
[Music]
i'm just gonna play my music now
[Applause]
[Music]
sounds so holy
huh
okay
oh no
huh
[Music]
okay that dude he really pisses me off
also i forgot her
as holly as kiwami's upcoming song check
it out
thank you
for the advertisement
i mean i don't know if i would call the
song holy although it is pretty say so
i would say it it promotes a straight
edge lifestyle
the lyrics
[Music]
um
okay let's just take it
unless they're too slow to get up and i
kill them before they get up
[Music]
natural
okay we have two mirrors
i think
uh we can also get rid of the
uh
flags first
i don't know what that gives us but
maybe some lights
oh
no
uh-huh
okay
um
okay not very 80s of course
um but you know it was supposed to
reflect me you know and i'm straight
edge so
it has to
has to be like that
well yeah now that you say it it does
feel
kind of unfitting doesn't it
i'm so online yes i'm still going strong
can i go
do this one too
really that big one with one mirror
strong
what happens if i mirror it to the
mirror
oh oh
oh
this is so hard because like with medley
at least you can like tap out and then
she will stay in that exact position
ah but for link
it just doesn't stand still
[\h__\h] him
i don't even i just wanted to see like
you know where it goes but ah
this one this one i need
patience is a virtue
yes
you have to let it drift down
and then eventually you'll get it right
okay where do we go
first um
yeah
yeah that joystick i don't know if it's
just mine
michael
come with me
let's go this sign
i can move the mirror oh
anyway we're going here i guess
[Music]
uh-huh at the end of this room there's
um
there's a
chest
[Music]
there's a hand
what am i supposed to do
maybe go this way instead
maybe this way is safer
oh [\h__\h] i'm already
ah but it's just reversed i was fine
right it's just reversed right
okay
i smoked
[Music]
oh oh now the fog is gone
brute force is this is this what you
were supposed to do just run past that
wasn't even really a challenge
i thought it was reverse but i just went
forward and that was it
okay
now we have more of that
you throwing [\h__\h] at me riley how dare
you
try it again try me
there's another mirror over there
does that lead to a room huh no no i was
not in there before i have maybe i
should go to
a little [\h__\h]
okay i shouldn't try fighting you
foreign
you know what i saw today on twitter
that um
four whole af japan members
uh had some kind of like
sponsorship collabing me with a real
live
idol
maybe you guys saw it on twitter
and it's
it's
goto maki
who is like a really really really
really famous x idol from whole life
she used to be
super super super super
popular in morning listener and when i
saw that oh
farmer when i was like
why
did they not ask the huddle
hello project otaku number one
takanasi kiwawa
to join this collaboration huh
yeah loki disappointed
well okay
um but cool to see i i didn't even know
like what that
uh person was doing now apparently now
she's doing gaming streams
or gaming videos what does that even
lead to
that is not the first idol x idol that i
see that does
uh
that does um
gaming stuff now
very interesting
they become
gamers first idol now gamer wait now do
i have to move this
ah
just move the whole thing
no
then it goes through there and then once
i'm on the other side i
i redirect it from there
can i do it from here
no whatever i guess i'll just gotta i'll
just have to go to the other room i
think
gamer the game streamer idle pipeline
goes both ways
yeah but it's so cool to see it
exhale alive
hello project it's very similar hello
project um idols
working
with
whole life because that gives me hope
that maybe maybe maybe maybe somehow we
can make a connection
but i wonder how that even like happened
in the first place how they got that
like
to like how they
organized them like who asked who
why
what why
um
can we move them
no these ones we cannot move
okay
and then we'll get that cannabis but i
don't think so because veggies cobalt
doesn't exist anymore not really
um
damn it
but i mean there are still some members
ah [\h__\h]
who are somehow like ah
active
separately not as a group anymore
hello life
you know how hololive sometimes uh
calls itself whole life
project or whole live idol project
that always makes me think of hello
project
yeah very confusing for me
uh not you again
ah you too
uh oh god okay i'm confused i'm confused
i'm confused i'm confused
oh yeah baby
oh there's so much going on there's so
much going on
they're all panicking just like me
oh [\h__\h] here we grab it
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] that's bad oh [\h__\h]
that's bad oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] ah this is
reverse controls
this was it
okay i'm free i'm free
[Applause]
sending those two enemies against me
at the same time
that is quite the challenge
okay so now we burn some more statues
oh [\h__\h]
okay we can do
we're gonna do this one
hi attention good morning good morning
did you just wake up sleepyheads
turkanasi kiwawa recently has been
waking up at seven and eight a.m and all
those
weird human times
i feel like a different person yo
and i'm i'm even trying to get up later
but i can't
i wanted to wake up today at like 9 30
but i had so i had my
had my alarm for 9 30
but i woke up already at 7 00 am
partially because i needed to go to an
idle meeting and that always wakes me up
in the middle of the night i don't want
to go cause i know that once i get up
i'll be like
too
too awake
do i have to reflect and then reflect
again
i saw wenger on idle meeting and then i
couldn't sleep anymore
why i need a bigger idol meeting
toleration
[Music]
[\h__\h] ah
oh maybe i can make her look at me
[Music]
i know
thank you
uh
it looks like go over here to me here
come on
[\h__\h]
i'll just i just place you
um
place you here
ah
come on
i'm getting tired man
i'm so tired how much longer for this
one it's 11 p.m and sleepy time for
smoky while up sleepy time
i don't know i can't think anymore
it's sleepy time
[\h__\h]
halfway i think we'll end it
i think we have to end it i'm so tired
man i fall asleep man
[Music]
uh
i can't do this anymore i can't do this
anymore
sam
rescue me
save me
and when i'm going go into i still have
to cook for [\h__\h] like no
okay maybe the baguette was my dinner
oh
maybe i was just going to sleep
like that
[\h__\h] no i have to now after my stream
i'll try to
i'll try him
no i shouldn't have eaten the baguette
because now i'm like chew to hamper like
like half assed hungry
i'm like kind of hungry but not really
awesome tired too tired too
yeah
[\h__\h]
damn it
don't wanna no
anyway did i save
i'm tired under um i'm tired i'm tired
why am i so tired i need to uh
i need to take
vitamin d like every day
i tried taking it but then i kind of
stopped
i need to take it every day because i
think like i i cannot function
anymore
like a normal
human being
i can't
which is makes sense because i'm not a
normal human being i'm a phoenix
but i just i just can't
i can't get out of bed and i keep on
sleeping and sleeping i'm just so tired
all the time no matter what i do i'm so
tired
i did have an appointment today by the
way
so i did do something before the stream
and the appointment actually was a good
one
successful one
uh with a nice outcome i think um so
that's that's something good i can't
tell you what it was though
oh but only something could happen
or like relatively good
um
considering the circumstances
ah
okay
um so i did say i won't read the
maldives super chats that say that
before
um
i don't know how far behind i am does
any
uh kfp member know
because tomorrow i think we'll have a
lot of time because we honestly it's
just like a little bit of a celebration
and then we have a lot of time to read
end of welcome back yeah i know there
might have been like
something from a certain vr
chat
but that one i didn't i say
i won't read those out loud i don't know
or was that just about the maldives i
don't remember anymore the vr one was
too long ago
if it's just the ones from this week
then
it's only the recap and today
the collab recap right because the solo
recap solar recap yeah the one from
monday i already read i think
we could count them as vacations yeah
yeah yeah yes
uh
but i'm not that far behind am i at all
oh
[\h__\h]
okay let me put the wheel away
uh
still a bit from solar recap uh
oh okay
read them tomorrow after the premiere
yeah
i guess so
um
[Music]
well but i i do hope even
though i was so late i'm sorry about
that i do hope you guys still enjoyed
the stream today
um some gaming five hours 40 minutes
after all oh hey we did we didn't end up
playing pretty long i guess relatively
long if you consider in the flight that
i didn't raise of a chats then and this
is just gaming
then it's pretty fun
[Music]
hour delay
i'm sorry oh yeah
no i'm sorry
[Music]
early it's not ending early it's already
11 pm
ah
[Music]
i just realized i can't i can't upload
the music video before going to sleep
because it's not done yet
i'll ask
maybe
maybe i can ask
genma to upload it while i'm sleeping if
it gets done before i'm sleeping
yes it's not finished it's very close to
being finished
oh
everything's so kitty kitty man
everything's
always okay to get in now
my birthday merch my birthday concert
recording
everything getting in
i hate it
uh
do i know
oh wait no actually it's
oh it's being
rendered
i think
um
i see my mv maker typing right now at
this very moment
maybe it's done
there's still some parts that i
didn't see yet because they were not
finished but what but the one the
version that i've seen was like
maybe um 85 to 90 percent finished
so
yep pretty far pretty far don't worry
guys
[Music]
oh i think it might be it might be done
maybe maybe maybe it's done i'm not sure
they stopped tapping
but it's gonna be a great music video i
want you guys to see it there's uh
some great art for it and uh the envy
maker is someone i haven't been
i haven't worked with before
um but they did a really really good job
capturing the whole vibe that i wanted
so
i'm looking forward to you guys his uh
opinion and reaction to it it's pretty
pretty hype it's very uh how to say
atmospheric is that a word
it should be a word
push the bubbles on my body
but those i don't know if it's bubbles
it's just skin that wants to be peeled
off
so weird
so weird i've never had a
weird-ass sunburn like this
and my mom also scrolled at me she was
like yo even even when there's um
oh
oh okay even when there's like
cloudy cloudy
skies and you know the maldives are
close to the
what's it called
a quattro
the middle
of somewhere
are you sure i shouldn't pop them i sure
like it i'm not sure if it's like even
something you can pop
i'm not sure if there's something in
there maybe there's
how do you say it in english how do you
pronounce it equator equator
yes so when you're close to the equator
then the sun is really really really
really really dangerous
don't don't
okay back stealing my skin
they're vaccinating my skin okay
okay okay
mother
um
[Music]
don't want to get infected no no no
not a hotel
um um you know what i don't know i don't
know i don't know i don't know i wanna
i feel bad for not reading superchatters
i want to read them in the stream
but it's already past 11 pm
but tomorrow i need i don't need to get
up early do i let me look at my schedule
oh come on let me look at my schedule
yes all good
oh i did oh
because i guess this is okay
i guess this is okay
okay
um okay what should i go
[Laughter]
can i take you guys with me
would you come with me
cuddle with kitokatos
okay
wow
follow me uh you guys are so sweet you
guys are so cute did you guys know you
guys are cute because you're so sweet
and cute
you guys are so cute
what would i do without you so cute
i know that there's like
it's so crazy i heard that there's like
being uh like
a fan booth organized and doklami i'm
like what the [\h__\h] the first time i
heard about it i'm like am i supposed to
know this is this supposed to be a
secret a surprise
what's wrong with you guys
you're crazy
who who
why what
freaking fan move and apparently there's
been a lot of work being put into it
a lot of love so if you guys go to
dokomi
you don't only check out kiwawa concert
and all that look for the fan booth hmm
kfb so
so active proactive
so sweet
hey i want to check in
i'm really curious
yo
yeah
how do you know
eh
i've i've been asked something about it
um
if i if i give my permission for
something but
i i also thought like am i supposed to
know this like it shouldn't this be like
a surprise or something
but also like on twitter as well i think
i saw like some
illustration ah this was made for the
kfp fan booth or something like that
if it's supposed to be secret then you
guys are not good at keeping it a secret
especially if the organizer tries to get
permission from me first from something
then at that point it's not a secret
anymore
on the public document thingy well yeah
yeah i think i started at several places
at this point
not a secret would have been an insane
surprise though but
um
color me surprised i was surprised when
i first heard it
i was very very surprised
it's on the document twitter and there
you go that's probably also where i saw
it
yeah
oh
my skin is peeling let's go
yay okay this is actually peelable skin
let's go that's fun this is where the
fun starts
yay
skin who wants my skin idle skin
phoenix skin who wants it
no more gamer bathwater how about gamer
girl
skin
old skin and snake
oh nice this is so funny it's been a
while since i've skinned
ew
i'm a snake
how about
my skin
yeah that's gross excuse me what's gross
about that have you never had a sunburn
before
that's a pretty normal thing i don't
know what's gross about good
wow it peels off so nicely
[Music]
oh my god
my on my upper arm
it feels kind of moist though
maybe it's all the the the ten layers of
aloe vera that i've
put on it
give us more details i don't know it's
very very um
i don't really see much difference from
before and after
like it's not like the
not like underneath it's much brighter
it looks pretty much the same
so i think i'm gonna have really spotty
skin for a while that's funny
am i ever gonna learn from many mistakes
can we fry it
i like how chicken skin
is like really really really really
crispy after putting it in the oven
that's really nice yeah no this is not
like that it's too thin
my skin
is more um what's the word
what's the word that i'm thinking of
pe petite no
delicate delicate my skin is more
delicate yes
more delicate than your chicken skin
why is it moist though that actually
freaks me out
a bit
okay i should go but i'm like peeling my
skin right now it's fun
delicacy no no no no no not like that
when they say it's delicate i don't mean
it's a delicacy that's two different
things why are these words the same then
then
damn i put myself in a difficult
position
skin feeling stream let's go
how far can i get
[Music]
this is fun
okay i think i reached
oh you guys you know what i had a dream
like yesterday during oh pro i think i
had a nap yesterday
during my nap yesterday i had a dream
where
um
[Music]
i was
playing a game
on my phone
that was a mix of apex and world of
warcraft
it was actually cool and it wasn't it
was also yeah an online
game
kind of like the whole world setting was
world of warcraft but it was a shooter
like apex
yeah
and you would aim by moving your phone
and i had like god aim my aim was insane
sounds like a cool concept
i mean in theory that probably already
exists like a shooter in that kind of
world setting but it's also like with
like it had the whole world of warcraft
equipment interface
and all that
yeah
and the levels like the whole like
mmorpg aspect to it as well
and there's no like getting in lobbies
or something there's just this world you
know that you're in constantly you know
what i mean
i wonder i wonder if there's like really
something very comparable
because no paladins is not
what i mean you know
because when paladins also you like load
a game and then you're in and then
you're out again
but it was weird because i was pretty
good at it
and you know i'm not good at shooting
games
that that's what means that it's a dream
because i was good at it
did you write the dream down well yeah
but only the parts that i told you now i
wrote that down
write that down write that down
destiny
sounds like destiny 2 even though it
probably isn't
oh
destiny 2.
i'm describing destiny too that's me too
what
does that mean
too
oh
[Music]
no but that that looks too futuristic
in my dream it was not futuristic it was
like world of warcraft
um but maybe the whole system is similar
but in the end it was a dream so
um
destiny too
yeah like fantasy fantasy style
i don't know this game
i don't know
oh anyway i'm procrastinating i'm
stalling
i should go
i guess
uh
there might be
yeah i probably will upload the mv but i
probably will keep it on private for a
little while so that genma can check it
and if she deems it appropriate she
might
unprivate it while i'm sleeping
okay
so keep an eye open but i mean it will
still like it will be unprivate but then
made into a premiere
coming soon
yes
okay
oh gosh my skin freaks me out
okay then in german and german we say
you should auf wiedersehen and see you
tomorrow good night thank you for your
support and the sweet super chats i will
be reading them tomorrow i promise i
promise
yeah
and as i said there will be
um premiere a couple hours before the
celebration stream so
yeah i'll see you
tomorrow
and my new song that we've waited so
long for will finally be out so i'm
hoping for your support on that it's the
first one in
a long time almost a year
so
yeah i i hope you guys are gonna like it
and hope you guys are gonna stream it
and watch it as much as you can listen
to it but i also just want you to enjoy
it so yeah
uh
[Music]
yeah
favorite night
coming
to you
very soon
hopefully
if all goes well
i'm a little bit worried if everything
goes free properly
um
if everything goes for a legal check
well
but
but it will be daijoubu right i
i believe i believe
[Music]
[Laughter]
how do you crack your voice
intentionally
[Laughter]
that that sounded
something like that
okay okay okay okay i'm leaving
[Music]
do
you