[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
okay
are you ready
sorry i got some water and some
snackles
sure
are you ready
zoom
um
[Music]
look
i made this myself i made myself a scarf
and the hair that
the little fox has
yeah
[Music]
the hair sticks pretty well the scarf
could be better but oh well
i'm using my sword yeah because i guess
my sword and my shield look i guess at
least like at least i have a sword and a
shield
a [\h__\h]
oh my god there's a potato chip that's
like folded in a funny way i love it um
may work better with my other hairs
[Music]
but this one
this is my only outfit that has the cat
ears you know so i look like a fox i
think this is the perfect way to combine
it
[Applause]
i made it before the stream yeah i was
motivated
[Music]
i wanted to become the protagonist
kitty
thank you
it's cute right
like whenever but never like a
like a game protagonist or so
has something
that i could recreate and put on my
outfit then i want to do it but you guys
can also do it like if you see me
starting a new game or
or continuing an ongoing game
and you wanna make something for me to
stick on my body
i think i have um a hashtag for that kf
kfp and g's was it carefully ping jesus
what was it i haven't checked it in a
while i feel like you know we should
just go with key arsenal because at
least that one i remember and it's
basically the same thing
okay of props oh
is there something new there i haven't
checked in a while
on the flaps
see i want to use the flaps but today i
have to use my cat ears
so
yeah okay snooki arson no
there's an apron cute
some newfound confidence in the kitchen
oh the animaplus cafe drink
i'm going for the
what the [\h__\h] is that hat
i'm going for the tag right now
oh i can put a cobalt doll on my
shoulder
[Music]
oh yeah i saw the
the louie
hair before
i'm gonna use that too
[Music]
okay so by the way guys i was asking
last night in pre-chat
um
if i should like wear with what i should
play and then if i should just play ps5
and i was gonna play ps5 but then i
opened the shop today and i realized
it's not on sale yet
[Laughter]
um by the way if we're gonna take a
picture take a picture of me right
[Music]
yes i'm playing on on steam
but with controller cheese
i will take those bastards down
yeah
alden ring style
bloodborne style
eh you want to fight eh eh
well fightmate fight me
i'm gonna munch on you like on those
potato chips
i'm a hero
once again i'm a part-time hero warrior
hmm
you like my hair
[Laughter]
i look edgy with that tuft of there it's
cute
it's my my bed hair my morning hair
just woke up
um
and my protagonist
thank you so i think i'm ready for tunic
today i'm ready for an adventure
[Music]
oh my god sorry um these are yummy i
really needed something salty because i
had like a sweet breakfast but now i
want something salty
good luck out there yeah so the thing is
[Music]
apparently the game is pretty difficult
i watched a little bit um of gameplay
and yeah i mean
it's like
you know you get a lot of damage you
can't take a lot of damage and
then there's these like safe points that
respawn the enemies that's kind of like
elven ring
and you can um heal yourself on those
safe points it's like it's like those
fire places like an ellen ring
and you get a certain amount of flasks
you can make the flasks stronger too
and all that so there's like it's it's
mixing elements from uh link i would say
personally because that's what i played
link's awakening
and
uh eldon ring or like you know those
kind of games there are souls shows
games souls games x zelda games
but like not blatant copy
i think it's a it's a like a good it's a
good mix it's a fitting mix
so
we might struggle a bit but i think
we're gonna do fine
[Music]
area
all right
i have the game open uh okay what's the
capturing window
oh oh why is it called secret legend
when you
you know how
in obs you know you choose what window
you want to capture and there's like you
know they all have normal names like the
sims 4 and northvpn and so on but tunic
xe is called secret legend it's not
called tunic is that a hint is that a
hint
is
i was like i don't see it on here but no
it's secret legend
sponsored
[\h__\h] lord vpn man didn't do [\h__\h] for
me
close that app don't want to see it get
out of my face
okay when is it gonna is it ever gonna
i selected it come on show up
ah
the soundtrack is really good there we
go from this game and um
i love the art style
i think we're gonna enjoy this we might
struggle but it's supposed to be like um
where's my mouse
supposed to be like
12 to 20 hours depending on how good you
are and uh how much
you want to complete
and uh my game of the year oh
um okay wow
and what did i hear that this game is
made by pretty much one person
did you really make everything
like the music too
that's just what i heard
it's an it's an indie game yeah but for
an indie game it's amazing
okay
one one canadian death oh
wow
it's originally named secret legend oh
they kept the name in the
in the code or whatever the window is
called secret legend okay one more
potato chip only one more
that still comes as one
[Music]
oh sunrise
i'm gonna do in the box
cute
is um
volume okay
um
yeah once again we have a protagonist
and doesn't talk
okay so i can
do a roll but we have stamina god damn
him
oh oh we can go into the water but how
far uh not really far okay
what would the fox say
so this is me obviously i mean we look
perfectly alike so
there is no doubt about that
what else can i do so far what is that
is that like a focus button
what is this
golden platform
golden platform can i do something here
oh menu lb is menu
so i know that like in this game there's
like these
there's this there's this box that you
can't read
i don't know if you will discover later
on what it means or if just it's just
gonna stay like that to like stay
seem mysterious
but yeah
bjm a little loud okay uh
there we go
maybe 70
i got sound
oh was that too much
chat on screen oh oopsie oops
thank you
yeah i should cut it
cut it there we go
no bit more
now it's too low was it too low when i
tap out it's muted
where's my mouse
where did my mouse go hello hello
what the [\h__\h]
oh oh there it is
it's so weird because when i go with the
mouse over the window my mouse
disappears so i can't see it oh by the
way thank you uh kick for the red super
chat i haven't seen you in a while i'm
taxi thank you too
[Music]
if it was a little bit
too quiet now then i'll make it 80.
and return
return to game okay
[Music]
so the angle
is like lynx awakening and i feel like
you know
i saw a little bit of the world design
that also reminds me of link's awakening
but it seems to be on purpose from what
i've heard like the
the developer admits it so it's not a
secret should we go in here it looks
dangerous
oh
a chest
[Music]
a stick wow
amazing what can i
uh-huh lb
can i equip that what's the red button
ah
ah okay
well can i equip it here
what is that
okay but for now uh these buttons are by
the way not accurate i i'm using a
playstation controller but it shows me a
xbox controller
but for now let's do that
[Music]
the money in the game is these cheese
balls
these cubes of cheese
oh you see
now
what is what are these
effects
when my screen is
doing weird things
can i go for that grass
oh yeah i can
oh i can't but i think the game wants me
to go straight up now
the early fox gets to chase
yeah i'm excited to play this game
because i've had an eye on it for a
while
i think maybe even before release
uh but i didn't get to play them until
now like for a while it went under my
radar and uh
yeah recently i was thinking oh what
should i play what should i play
a
a is i guess x okay but i don't have a
key
and now i needed something so i was like
oh it's perfect what does this say by
the way
hero's grave
with a sword sign is that where my sword
is going to be
hit
it was after the xbox presentation what
that i said i had
eh what did i wanted to
what
did i found it
really did i talk about it i i
definitely talked about the game
ah which way do i call
you guys probably have to help me a lot
oh i said oh i oh yeah i tweeted about
it
um
maybe i was even the one who requested
permissions what did you guys see that
glitching what could that be
maybe i shouldn't get in the middle
you guys see the
screen please like flashing like that
how do i what what could that be
i mean it's not too disturbing the town
what town left
okay
flickers
yeah rolling mechanic i wonder if it
matters like you know like an elven ring
when you roll at the right time you can
you know
dodge
anyway
basically
maybe that helps
let's see if it's not happening anymore
for the next 10 minutes then i think
that did the trick
oh oh oh
here we have one of those shrines
where you can heal yourself
and it refreshes the enemies spawn
there they are again
i'm guessing just like an elden ring it
only refreshes the small maps but not
the big mobs
oh
okay
whatever that means i guess it means do
we want to pick this up yes i'm picking
it up and i'm gonna use it on the door
that we just saw before somewhere
[\h__\h] stills
fox shows yeah i think it was
down there
was it oh yeah it's over there
wait wasn't that where my sword is
it said that's that's where my sword is
right oh [\h__\h] oh yeah
i wait wrong button
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i put the
the attack button on the circle remember
remember
yes open door
i have to be careful in this game
yeah
because
it's tough
is there any way that you can like turn
it too easy or so
or is there no no game modes like that
no
[Music]
no baby mode oh my god
um that's okay
[Music]
there is unlimited stamina that said
stamina sentence oh my god i heard
something about that
um
what would that be
accessibility
no fail mode
no stamina oh so there's no dying and no
wait
[Laughter]
let's see how we do first
and if we have some problems we might
you know give ourselves a little bit of
a handicap because
this game is tough okay
i already know
whoever said nope lies to me
why are you hiding this from me hmm
what is this
beginning your adventure blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah
ringing the east bell
east forest heroes grave guardian
captain oh is that like three bells that
i have to ring and oh one two three four
five bells that i have to ring in the
west
was that what was going on
in the far of land a great treasure was
sealed away forever some say it is the
power to defy death
oh what like immortality
i'm what i'm muted i'm not muted what
are you talking about
it's the path of how you get to the two
bells
ah ah it's two bells okay
but why is it like a checklist then
i have to go to the east forest first
and then i don't get to the hero's grave
unless i went for the east forest maybe
okay
interesting note
[Music]
i can turn the page oh wait what
i'm gonna look ah um
the game screen ah
well thank you for that explanation
that tells me partially nothing okay but
at least some yeah okay
some things are in our language some
things are not
[Laughter]
you
know
everything hurts way more when i'm tired
stamina points important uh when you go
to zero sp you die is no you can't
no what is what does that you don't die
if you run out of stamina plans right
what is that red thing
probably
you faint i don't know
you you can't move you can't run
something like that
ready equipment magic potion
focus preview
health point stamina points magic points
we're gonna get magic points eventually
i take more damage
thanks game for telling me
[Laughter]
for telling me that so clearly
price and treasure yeah okay okay
uh lt
wait why is that chest open
did i open that chest was that where my
stick was
[Music]
i didn't come here before
why is it all for now that i didn't know
[Music]
it was already open right
i wonder who else is here besides me
oh who's that
magical thing is there a map that i can
look at
i'm guessing not
right now
okay uh uh we can go up here
this game is very cryptic yeah i don't
think that's cool it's mysterious
let me go into the ladder
onto trees oh i can go for the trees oh
chest
what what's that
it's like a
plushie of myself
[Music]
like a meat bun that you can get in
convenience store
i love those pizzas
so many yummy
so far i'm handling them well i think
relatively
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
you picked them up i guess not only bunk
them
what is this
that outfit you have one is the cutest
thing ever
thank you i dressed up for it today
i made some some nice accessories
i love this orange pizza but yeah
i love those i ate those so often the
pizza buns
[Music]
ah separated no pizza mom
aha
[Music]
wait a second
it looks like
crc rcr
cm
it kind of looks like you know from the
top from the left i would say
s-m-s-m-s-m-c-r
something something
i wonder if there's one of those letters
for each letter of the alphabet
or if there's more if it actually is
like a properly made up language or if
stream sparks oh wait we were here or if
it's just a mess that
you could not make an actual language
out of
i would hope that there is that it makes
sense what is this east forest oh we
need to go there are we ready for that
i can't go there because of the bushes
so we have to go here
all right first dungeon
hmm
east belton uh-huh
okay the first dungeon must be nice to
me right it won't it won't like be too
too mean right
i'm always already halfway from my hp
crawler
yeah so far i love the graphics
i love the
the light effects um
the vibes the atmosphere
okay we'll just do oh more introduction
stuff wait what
here
aha controls yeah focus
it's like it's trolling me
it's like
i could tell you what all this means but
no [\h__\h] you i'm not gonna tell you
okay um
archie is blocking
our
beam is a potion later i guess
[Music]
wait was there more
wait if i hold it it does something else
a and hold
um
okay
as opposed to ah if i just hold it he
continues running oh
oh i can run but only if i roll first
i'm not a
hodor okay
oh
i find a secret no
oh no i did
but if you hold a the whole time it
doesn't show you what like that you can
push something okay so i guess i'm gonna
be you know
careful i'll have my eyes open for some
secrets too
oh oh
what's that big fork
it's quiet right now there's no btm here
it's so quiet and serene i can't reach
that place
winnie can it
what about this side
well why was it rumbling ah oh [\h__\h]
i mistook the
wrong button for the attack button again
mata magikari
and eerie quiet yeah ouch what the [\h__\h]
who took away that ladder
put it back up man
was it you big fox lady
was you
oh they healed me hallelujah wait was i
here before
[Music]
oh the green is so nice
they have a laser
i want a laser too it's not
fair and they're so spiky
okay those are a little bit more tough
than the ones we met so far
was this
i wonder what that means
[Music]
exactly i agree i agree but i also don't
understand
[Laughter]
i haven't heard that in a long time oh
can i get up there
oh it's so pretty
on that
oh my cheese balls cheese cubes
oh
oh okay i can go to the right get up get
it up go to the left but the door is
closed there
now i can go into the to the very bottom
right to
into like some
cave for sure
where should i go we can also go like
to the nearest one in the middle
you love my scrappy looking hair thank
you
it's my bed hair
choices
first the east is on the very right
um thank you noob
[Music]
can't go for brushes oh yeah right
true
okay sorry i'm so into these chips right
now
oh
can i find the secret
no
nothing in particular
[Music]
okay
do you guys hear the music
properly
maybe there's something here
that was an optical illusion i thought
it was on the upper level like where the
the the
the looking hole thingy was i got a
fruit
another one of those notes
show me show me what's up
lt for target lock yeah plus a is focus
and evade aha i can't evade and focus
and block
face your adversaries
moment of safety
there it is okay okay okay
check for this ah as long as there's
dust that's when i'm safe
stability flinch knocked over
wet
you can always attack even without
stamina
okay
so what's
i just can't run then and i just can't
roll anymore okay
[Music]
okay
useful good to know
good to know okay
let me go
wait and let's just check this one heal
ourselves
if you turn steams if you turn off
steams control the support for ds4 the
game should detect you are using a ds4
and show ps4 button print yes i mean ps5
maybe
these ps4 it did i checked and steamed
let's check the settings and it did say
it um it recognized that i'm using a ps5
controller
so in theory
i think is it our
[\h__\h]
i think it did recognize it but i always
have this problem like it never properly
does it he was grave oh we need to go
there but what's left
what's here
curiosity kills the fox
baby
aim his poise
wait what was the poise again i forgot
like not being broken not having your
shield your guard broken
oh it's nice that you can you know
endlessly attack i think in an album
ring you couldn't do that in seoul's
game oh i see you're watching me can you
shoot from there
no
[Music]
okay
let's go up
press lb
so you can level up
[Music]
[Laughter]
i got the upper hand let's go i'm taking
all your cheese balls cheese cubes
why are you coming to korea soon
oh [\h__\h]
i am
soon very soon
very soon um that's also why next week
there will not today's sunday right
there will not be a schedule for next
week because i don't want you guys to
know on which day i'm going but yeah
going next week
a person it's good that
[Music]
should i go here can i go here oh it
looks like you know some stairs but i
guess not okay
i have
um
a potion now that i can use with
rb okay good to know
i wish i could shoot him
okay
[Music]
there's no ps
times ms exclusive so there's no ps
button assets yet
oh is that really
oh
oh oh oh yeah maybe maybe they won't
have it until it's actually released on
ps5
race season starts next week oh that's
good
because that means it won't be so hot
right i'm happy with that
although the timing once again just like
with my trip to the maldives
are you for real why am i always hitting
rainy seasons
well how rainy is it gonna be
[Music]
i did check though
like two days ago how the weather is
in korea compared to
austria
and it was generally much chiller so i'm
actually surprised and i'm really glad
but the heat wave here in austria
um yesterday it was chill so the heat
wave moved on today is also pretty chill
it's getting better i think the heat
wave might be gone
[Music]
can't be that bad right no i hope so
yeah rain is okay if i'm like not it's
not like i want to go to the beach
so that's okay this is it's a city trip
so
um
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] no it's not what i wanted to do
i think
um
is this where i level up but i don't
think i can do anything
yet
today i learned korea has beaches
i i know there's like one really really
really popular
um vacation place in korea
um
i don't think i can wear this
oh wait what
how did what
what what does it do
[Music]
oh i'm supposed to break these and what
does a very do i want to know before i
do it does it heal me
i was very violent
i thought it was a plushie it's a fox
money bank
you know the berry probably does some
healing
maybe
don't use the fruit okay
here was grape right side what about
going to the middle
oh no
cheese balls cheese cubes
thank you i'm gonna make a cheese from
you
and the fur wait on the ground pepper
hairstyle okay wait i don't know i have
to check out the
this place first
can i go in here
this place looks important okay why is
it rumbling
oh
i can't reach
i don't think i can reach
okay
that's for later
ima can i
okay we'll go this way after all
we have to check out everything we have
to say you know
that we are not missing out on
everything anything
or you beep what
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] okay
um
i cannot
be too cocky i need to take my time
and uh dodge oh god oh god oh god
come here i can't find you there
[Music]
and i practically did oh i have a
healing
thingy
okay
that's something i'm guessing it fills
up again when i'm in one of those save
points
well
i take more damage when i'm tired okay i
forgot about that mhm
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay so they can do the laser but they
can also do close heads okay be careful
be careful i'm almost dead again and
there's like a big bob mop over there
big buff
oh
[Music]
i came in mentally prepared baby it's
getting hot though i'm going to turn on
my
it's like i feel like my my apartment
heats up faster
um
like it's it's getting hotter in here
even when i already like when i chill
down my apartment overnight
by having the window open
then it gets chill and then i close it
and it immediately heats up even though
it's not even hot outside
what the actual [\h__\h]
alvin rain trained you well
and hopefully hopefully we'll
we'll get the hang of it and this was
not just a lucky strike
my lucky strike
[Music]
on in a million my lucky strike oh what
is this
what is this
maybe we'll get there later and can i
open this up
no okay going up
mm-hmm
you need the enemy to cut the bushes no
i don't think that's what it is
but here yeah i can't go here we'll get
a proper sword and then we can probably
cut through it oh oh here we go down
i tried pineapple pizza it was okay
the next started pizza and corn how
about you go a step further you just do
pineapple and corn it's amazing
yeah when did fuki have a cute orange
little sister
she always had her
[Music]
that opens the gate right yeah
hold on
give me my sword i want my sword
[Music]
oh there it is
am i just a ghost or like
or or is that like a
um
a relative an old old relative of mine
who died and left their sword here
and now i have to
use it okay
go go away
stick we don't need you anymore
yeah
okay
we have
[Music]
the
sword
look at that
oh
now all the green broccoli is no match
for me no more and we can open this
chest
oh
cubes cheese cubes
let's go was there something here i
wanted to check out
no
okay
[Music]
broccoli
i'm gonna make you
into a smoothie
it seems like they don't
produce or drop any sort of
secret
any sort of money was what i was gonna
say there we go
found the secret
not much of a secret though if i was
able to find it
whoa whoa whoa okay let's break it give
me the money uh
we can i guess do this and then do this
break it
get those cubes
yummy
cheese is good for your body
[Music]
okay yeah let's talk a little bit about
crunchyroll expo cause for me it's over
but today it's still going on right
today is the last day
crunchyroll expo in do you pronounce it
san jose
jose josie
[Music]
yeah i think ina has her meet and greets
today but no more panels i think the
panels are over
but there's still some meet and greets
jose who say every single the thing is
like
while while me and ina were waiting for
a panel to start um we were already able
to look uh at like two camera angles
that were pretty high quality actually
um we were watching it for zoom
and then
um
we were like commenting on the people
who were walking in and before that even
i noticed that there were a lot of seats
reserved and blocked and i was like
what's up with all those blocked seats
man
and then
later i noticed oh yeah oh yeah
oh wait now we can go here later i
notice before the panel starts still
yeah go and some staff that i uh that i
know are walking in
and i'm like [\h__\h] the audience can hear
me right now i shouldn't say anything
out loud but i wanted ina
to see it i wanted to point it out to
her but she didn't see it
but i noticed him already bombed
when uh when he was walking in i was
like yeah
is the audience going crazy when they
notice him but i guess nobody really
noticed him when he was walking in most
people seem to have only really noticed
after the panel was done and he turned
around because well i guess he was
mostly facing his back to the people
but yeah sometimes during the panel
also when i was talking about
the when when i was pitching
the
uh no when inna was pitching the item
that i chose
a bubble bubble pacifier
the whole time what i was saying was um
the camera angle where jago was sitting
i was like i wonder if he understands it
but
from from when i have like the
conversations i had with jago so far
he is surprisingly good at english
actually so
you might have been understanding but i
mean come on
i don't think
i don't think he
really
was like thinking anything besides haha
funny
or like that's my girls
oh my god
oh [\h__\h] what [\h__\h]
can they climb up ladders
no okay good
uh can you guys chill go somewhere else
i want to go redo this okay
because i
i didn't want to alarm you all at once
quiet
hey
i love them again so fast eh
so many ah wait they want me to use the
bomb
wait a second uh
okay so we can like put it
on here and then we we alarm them and
then we throw this down and then come on
[Music]
did that just
glitch for you and went to the very
bottom
[Music]
and now i'm a little bit mad
now i am a little bit back
there
okay well then
maybe they want me to drop it off
ah
[Music]
not the most
effective okay
okay we're fine we're fine
[Music]
it's okay we're good
why am i so
little
i didn't just take damage did i
i think i didn't take any damage but i'm
good i'm good we just wasted my bombs
because
it glitched through the wall but okay
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] is there like a safe point
somewhere close by
[Music]
um i don't want to die
just
[Music]
oh my god
that's disgusting
help me
i need the same point
what happens if i die now
is that a safe point here
east forest
what there's like
what oh did i go in a circle
oh i went in a circle what
oh no
um
yummy
oh my god
no tip left behind yeah
i'm the captain
of this bag of chips and i'm not leaving
anyone behind
of course i picked it up and ate it it
was clean
of course i did
[Music]
there were no cut hairs on it i checked
i
did
yeah
i checked
i always check
cause i don't wanna i don't wanna eat
cat hair
now
um
this
got me kind of curious should i go back
this way
cause now i walked in a circle but i
feel like i ran by some things
are the spiders dangerous i wonder
what is this
[Music]
myself and then redoing this [\h__\h]
it's not there i was focused on the
enemy a level above me why did it not
just focus on the spider huh
now we're fighting those oh yeah i mean
i guess it was strong pretty strong
i think it's not work
where do i go then
oh was there something here that i
couldn't go to before
i think there was something
oh wait to the mata like this for
example
some secret
oh no oh my god no
that i don't like
that i don't like at all
i don't know if i'm ready for that but i
mean there is a safe point right there
[Music]
okay
i'm scared maybe i can get one of them
down
to like walk down with me
okay come here yeah
oh
foolish foolish foolish of me how
foolish of me to not um
dodge earlier but okay we took those two
down um what do you want
now let's take
the big boy down i'm a little bit sweaty
my hands are a little bit sweaty
no
scary um i don't know how he's gonna
attack me
dorcio
can i survive this
he has a shield though
let's get him to attack
no way
[Music]
not doing that
oh my god sweaty hands sweaty spaghetti
maybe i should be wearing gloves
skeletons
[Music]
holy cheese balls of mother of cheeses
speaking of cheeses you know what i'm
kind of into recently with what pizza
means recently
burrata
pizza
something
i've ate for the i've eaten for the
first time when i was in italy recently
and now i kind of
it's like
it has become one of my go-to pizzas
but what kind of cheese is burgata it's
like mozzarella but not really
how do you what is that can someone
explain burrata cheese to me never heard
of it it's like some kind of mozzarella
cheese and then the rest of the pizza is
like normal and has some prosciutto
[Music]
sometimes cherry tomatoes i guess should
have cherry tomatoes
it's mozzarella that has been tweaked
brought as an italian cow milk treatment
oh my god the outer casing is solid
cheese while the inside contains stretch
nutella and cream
no my burrata did not have stretch
nutella but yeah the inside is a bit
creamy
a buffalo
yeah but it's like more creamy
inside definitely
okay
oh you want to help your friend it's too
late i already killed him
you're always too late
you gotta be fast i gotta be ready for
everything for everything
always be on alerts man
you don't know how to be a hero
and you will never learn
[Music]
so yeah i ate that pizza like two days
ago too well i guess no two days ago
yeah yesterday guys was the first time
i turned on my stove again since the
incident
i didn't really cook anything per se i
just um
heated up something frozen and in the
frying pan but i was so scared
to do that even that but it went well
it's okay it's all good maybe my
trauma is
healed for now
i know
how to make the
i'm still scared i'm still scared
i'm so scared yeah i didn't talk about
this at all um besides in a member
stream
maybe i should uh explain a little bit
uh for the non-members
oh hello oh you look strong too and i
don't even have full hp
hm
let's see oh my god
[Music]
i'm in
what
i can run past this what
hello
mommy sorry mommy mommy
sorry sorry i died
oh yeah i love that i'm not stopping i'm
more damaged
[Music]
that was pure panic
hmm
was that something
i'm not ah [\h__\h] was that something i'm
not [\h__\h] what am i doing sorry sorry
sorry mommy ah sorry mommy
sorry mommy i was confused
let me go
back what's the dungeon that i just went
into or the boss fight something i'm not
ready for
wait i lost my money
huh
i have money i don't know how much i had
before
uh
[\h__\h]
oh my sword
what the [\h__\h]
i did oh
by accident
it took so much
what am i doing
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] i accidentally go to the
menu and then change my controls like
that okay
holy [\h__\h]
don't do that
i know why i'm doing it because
i'm stupid
now i kind of want to hear myself again
yeah
i pushed the the button above then i
wanted to focus though okay i know i
have to kill him again but i just want
to get out of this with no damage
did i like stun him
it's not crazy it's sweat like i'm legit
sweating i'm telling you i know the
difference
um
yeah practice makes perfect
why do you two minds a thing just show
your dead face and play the game what do
you mean this is my [\h__\h] face get out
of here if you have a problem with it
you're in the wrong
place buddy
if you have a problem with this you're
in the wrong place
[Music]
wait did we ah that's where we went in
is that where the boss was right there
oh
[\h__\h] no not quite not quite
[Music]
yet don't worry about it it has just not
been enlightened yet
oh wait what
i didn't see that the first time
okay so um
i don't think i can
i don't think i can beat this dude but i
would like to have my body back
is even that considered a secret it was
hard to say so it must have been on
purpose
what if i just
run past him and activate that thing
he's
beatable
how do i get my body first though this
is like an elden ring
style
cool
maybe grab body first and then run out
and then go back in
maybe
oh god
oh god oh god excuse me this gives me a
trauma
elementary animal version
don't spam attacks one at a time so this
name
that's by the way
at some point in the panel i said so
destiny because i was like looking at
jago in the camera point of view and i
wanted to see if he reacts if i say it
in the middle of my english talking
but his face didn't do any particular
reaction
[Laughter]
now that makes sense
i mean i do sometimes say it even when
yago is not watching me
[Music]
did you see how many [\h__\h] photos he
took with the audience
afterwards he must have been bombarded
with requests for photos
oh my god he did so many poses so many
selfies and photos then he was
apparently in that fear to her with with
small ammo
what was going on
did he want you know his
like he wanted to to feel
the fame for once i wonder how that felt
because like i don't think he
he
did he do that before in japan like that
taking photos with the fans i don't
think so i haven't seen it
it kind of must have been the first time
that he really
did something like that so openly
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
i'm just gonna i don't know how much i
lost but whatever
i don't need it
ah
i know i can heal but i only have one of
those and it only heals half of my
health while that dude
uh does half damage
half of my health's damage
[\h__\h] again i did it again i did it again
it's becoming a habit that's not good it
can't become a habit
i'm gonna it's okay i'm gonna go down
anyway
remap the menu button oh
yeah i want to do that
uh
but there's only keyboard controls
wait what there's only keyboard controls
that i can change
uh
cool
can i not change controls
[Music]
the game knows i'm using a controller
but
it even shows me that i'm using a
controller in the the menu things that
it's giving me right
[Music]
let's drive
um wait where was it
something with menu open
[Music]
um
open inventory
let's do
no i can't do anything oh wait
no
i can
i can only do it on the keyboard
[Music]
okay
i guess i'll have to get used to it
[Music]
i might have to do it for steam settings
no it's okay
i'll get used to it
do i still go the same way because like
i
i don't know if i'm really
supposed to be killing that boss yet
[Music]
oh that was close
okay
no damage ron let's go
yeah
that's what i'm talking about
so i tried one more time i opened the
shortcut
to this place
huh
you want me to open the shortcut i
haven't explored the spider go explore
the bottom area
okay
should i
mean where the spiders are
it would be nice to you know get some
upgrades
but i don't know where
how when is that a thing that i'm
supposed to do
already
let's try to kill those spiders let's
see if i'm a match for the spiders
lower forest
okay okay that's stupid spider
i mean i go to the other spot at first
oh yeah ah [\h__\h] oh yeah oh [\h__\h] there's
so many there's so many i forgot i
forgot there were so many
they're all hidden in the in the bushes
[Music]
oh my god
am i still there
oh my god i wish i still had a bomb
[Music]
i can find the shield oh really is it
there
really
it's an ambush yeah what the hell
okay okay i'll try i'll try now that i
remembered where they are i will
give it a try again
anyway
holy [\h__\h] once they don't go away
can i in the skittle
the other ones went away pretty quickly
when i did something like this before
maybe there's something else i can do
[Music]
like what about here did i
enter this place before i think i did
yeah what was what was in here again
sorry i need to check i forgot oh guard
house
was i here before
isn't this below
where the boss is
[Music]
it is
ah let's explore this okay okay okay
[Music]
oh yeah i went up here though i went
here
and then what happened
what happened
[Music]
uh-huh
oh didn't i just go
back then in a circle um no i got
something here and then i was stuck okay
sorry
sorry i was stuck here
i couldn't
continue
this now
[Music]
okay
okay well i have full health
i have full health so
up to me to call
my body still there
so if i die again the first body will
disappear i assume
so the snare
if only there was at least only one
enemy that i have to take care of
maybe he has like really strong attack
but also low health
and low defense
[Music]
holy
oh my god no i can't oh but wait i
already did some damage there there was
some explosion but no i can't oh i can't
oh now he's back to fall
his stamina was red
ah
[\h__\h]
i can do it no i can't uh
okay i need to heal already
i can't i thought she looked it
i'm so sweaty too
[Music]
okay
what
so that was a shortcut right but no you
have to kill so many enemies there too
okay anyway um
oh nice
okay i i
think
i can manage
i can do this
somehow i won't know what the reward is
kill a small one i don't really have the
you know i i ca i can't there's too much
going on like his hits are too too vague
the only thing i can focus on or need to
focus on is dodge
everything
yeah i don't really i don't i can't
focus on that small enemy i just need to
survive that's that's the only thing i
can focus on
okay so if i run into my body apparently
there's an explosion
cause that's the only way i can explain
that to myself
okay
so that actually did damage to the dude
though did it do damage to me
okay
he seems to also have two different
kinds of attacks the thrusts are
straight and then there was a kind of
different attack but even though the
frosts are big they're straight so if
i'm like just a little bit to the side i
survived
oh
i'm kind of stuck
[Music]
sorry sorry mommy
can i do it again
it'll take a few tries this is like an
elven ring you know it's almost to take
a few little tries
oh god the controller doll the doki doki
freaks me out i'm gonna turn it off
there's like uh
where would i change that graphics no
excessive oops
no oh accessibility
there's oh god i can't i can't handle
the
vibration
turn that [\h__\h] off yummy
it's freaking me out it's making me even
more nervous
oh man i already have a handicap
already handicapped guys
okay
i i thought wait it does not activate
automatically wait let's kill me just
kill me
[Music]
what
i was just gonna give up you know i
actually just attacked so reckless
recklessly because i thought i was gonna
die anyway
[Music]
oh my god you know sometimes you have to
just brute force it yeah yes you just
you just go you just go
just
accept that you're dying anyway and then
you'll be less worried about things
i can use two now
oh
no secret
maybe here there's a secret here no
oh no that is the secret there is no
secret
yeah
[Music]
good stuff though
i am surprised that i managed to do that
i thought it would take us a couple more
tries
[Music]
so proud panic best strategy
i think now i can go back to alden ring
huh
oh what are those tiles i like them
what no money out of those [\h__\h]
ah it's a drink
channeled the spirits of unga and bunga
now it would be easy an easy ring
what is this
oh
i was looking up to that when i was down
there now i can reach it
east belton strike strike it okay wait a
second
shortcut
yeah
[Music]
isn't that like uh don't you call these
things like um
something like
clang
gobble something like that
i feel like there's a tuning fork yeah
yes yes yes yes that's what that is
oh oh
money
wait what does that do i activated it
and it looks really [\h__\h] bright now
but what does it do
what did i do
oh my god
yeah so maybe no i mean i think they're
doing like some wordplays here you know
obviously he's wearing a tunic but it's
also about tuning
huh
what do we got
uh-huh
some
something
that i don't know what it is okay cool
oh what is it did i look at that too
yeah i looked at that too wait how do i
reach it
i don't think i can reach it from here
unless i can swim no
yeah
no
maybe this is just a preview maybe this
is just for me to get that item
now
okay crystallized copium
how would you know
did it help you cope with something
foxy and learn to swim we'll teach will
teach him eventually
man my sword is so strong though
i went here before right i opened the
chest yeah
sure
okay then i guess we did uh one of the
things we
ran one of the vowels wait where was
that um
there it is
we did
do i get a check now
wait what is that not considered the
bell
i does not give me a check mark because
i think i did it
i rang one of them
didn't i
does it not just not check it off but i
did it right i rang the east bell
[Music]
so we can say goodbye to the east and
now wait we want to go
how do i get to
what which part of this controller is
that now we go to the west okay
so we can leave that area now ah and now
we can go over here because we have the
sword
so
[Music]
it's not like i really had much choice
besides defeating that enemy after all
almost you i
interesting this man
oh it's on a map oh my god it looks like
link's awakening
[Music]
okay where are we
see myself
around the right side in the middle
kind of hard to see
um
do we see the
the ringy thingy
is it the thing at the top left no
i know i see it at the um
left middle top somewhere i see it
bell tower ringing a west bell
west garden dark tomb is that where
where we have to go through
oh it's gonna be a long way this place
is big the east was relatively small i
guess compared to that
where are we supposed to get a map from
the east
i don't think we did
maybe i missed it
ah
the storm wants to be close to me
starting by blocking auto bolt it wants
to protect something but what circle
around and use the shield
i don't have a shield yet
we need to get the shield and yeah the
poor swarm it has a pn phase pn
[Music]
time to find the shield yeah
hmm
there's some kind of like mark that
looks like self made
at the old house in the very middle
what what is there
it's interesting
i
i i hurt
[Music]
oh i want to go to the chest can i go
no
can he even like jump over anything at
all oh wait maybe secret
[Music]
oh
there's so many secrets in this game
oh where am i going
oh
oh my god
one of those big boys wait we saw them
before
i think we saw them before
let's just say
forest fortress
[Music]
fortress that sounds a little bit oopsy
dangerous [\h__\h] i'm dying
drinking
a safe point would be nice also we have
a
shortcut maybe for later
nicer
again
i love secrets but this game is very bad
at keeping them also why did my
controller just vibrate i thought i
turned it off
it's a different kind of a vibration
i have 600 of the currency
can i like save them somewhere
andrew's good at finding them
you can't hide your secrets from me
okay
you know one thing let's talk about
crunchyroll a bit more the expo one
thing i
noticed about the meet and greets
were i think it was like
i think we accepted like 20 people or so
and uh
what cute
does this one have money too
should i use it
[Music]
tell me first
before i use it
kayloon this is cute it looks like you
don't use it okay oh my god
i wish the game would tell me to not use
it uh can i take it off of my
or maybe if i do this and then this okay
yeah i was gonna say um
it was about 20 people and like uh three
minutes each approximately
um
it took me like an hour or so i think
and um
first of all it was a lot of fun doing
that again
but i've noticed a difference in the
dokomi meet and greets because like for
dokomi i know that
like
um
the people who signed up for it the
people who went to dokomi
who signed up for the meet and greet
where
90 percent
also like big fans of me
and maybe maybe a few ones were just
like
maybe low-key fans but
most of them were big fans of me they
went to dokomi with a goal you know
oh
dead
what
it doesn't work
[Music]
and uh
yeah yeah yeah and then for crunchyroll
expo
i noticed that the people who
successfully made it into the meet and
greets who got chosen by the raffle or
lottery or whatever it was
um
where like a lot of them didn't even
have me as their oshi
which is totally fine but there was
definitely like a difference in what
kind of people came to the meet and
greet
i think a lot of people who signed up
for the crunchyroll
meet and greets were like they signed up
for every
meet and greet and just hoped ooh
to get into one of them
um
the person you guys random
wait do you sign up for the meet and
greet but you don't know who you're
signing up for
was that the system
you had to pick three people ah
or four
three four four people that you wanted
to meet uh-huh oh
and then you uh randomly get one and
then it's not necessarily your oshie
because you know i didn't know that and
i thought oh these people are gonna have
me as your oshie right so i asked them
and like a lot of them were like oh
no no sorry i like you second most or so
and i'm like oh oh oh okay so sorry i
guess
it was a bit awkward
but don't worry i i don't make these
situations awkward i was laughing about
it
and then one person actually had ame
as their oshi and i was like oh my god
me too
who is the bigger ghostling and then we
talked a little bit about ame and
our conclusion was that i'm the bigger
fan of amen
he admitted to it so it's just fair
fair and square oh
what am i finding again
huh
where is the chest where's the treasure
chest
[Music]
there's no competition
yeah so some interesting um
uh interactions were held
and yeah um
not so many hardcore fans you know
but maybe the meet and greet
is like you know making them into a
hardcore fan
who knows
okay do i need to
check out the the weird thing over there
[Music]
does that can i do something wait i
think i can't do [\h__\h] here in this area
i'm not ready for this
[Music]
so
i think i'm too
early for this yeah okay
yeah i i
honestly you know i i wish a few more
like
hardcore cafe
would have made it because
you know
i wanna i wanna talk to them
i don't know it feels a little bit
hmm
lonely
but
it was still nice talking to people that
i i don't know i didn't know them like
none of them i asked all of them about
like their nickname the nickname that
they go by on twitter and so on most of
them said they don't use twitter and
they said they lurk in chat and all that
uh that they're not really active and
all that but they do watch
so yeah it was mostly lurkers
so it's nice to talk to them too for
once i told them to uh chat more
told him to use the chatbot
[Music]
found something
you have to really run
like behind every wall here to make sure
that's not nothing hidden
stop lurking okay i will there you go
perfect
just join is this better or worse and
links awakening
i wouldn't say it's never better no
worse
it's different but it has uh like
some charms of lynx awakening
for sure was i here before
yeah i made a shortcut
i was here before
heal me [\h__\h]
what do you say hello guys can't make me
start chatting just like i can make you
suck
but here you are chatting and here i am
using light mode
who won i think i did
i think i did
where should we go
oh let's look at this place
[Music]
battle of wills
you played yourself
yeah i got you
i'm a little bit more louder in chat
nowadays that's good
yeah thank you
trevor t i think by the way i think i
saw i'm pretty sure i saw you in the
audience i noticed you i remember that
face
or that
bad body
i didn't see your face clearly but i
think i saw you sitting there you went
there right yeah yeah okay i'm not like
imagining things
[Music]
i just remember some of you guys from
dokomi
and now i remember
i burnt your faces into my memory
it was nice
it was nice to see you guys
again
also um
yeah oh my god there's so much to talk
about
like uh
i am gonna be honest
i did not expect
too much
from the concession stand because i was
also told not to expect too much
because it's it's
just like a low-key light version of a
collaboration and takeover
um
i was told okay wow please don't get
your hopes up too much you know
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
yeah so what i basically did is like oh
i recorded um like a video for it
that i wonder if you guys ever saw i
actually
by by today
um the playlist that plays
um at the concession stand
has been shortened there's less videos
playing there now because i wanted to
make the possibilities of you guys
seeing the actual video that i recorded
for it
higher because it was rotating and i
don't saw i didn't see any reports of
anybody having seen it
what the [\h__\h] is this
so now the chances should be higher that
you can see it
um if anyone's still there
uh
check it out there should be
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
can i take
oh it's a shop
[Music]
all right dynamite that's not the bomb
right
and uh
i have a lot of money right now but i
don't know if it's worth using it on
this now
[Music]
shouldn't i be like
also able to upgrade like my
wait we'll think about this later
get the potion really
shouldn't i be able to upgrade my hp and
[\h__\h] tudor with money like i don't know
if i want to use my money on on this
right now when i have yet to
get the potion okay
okay
oh he's kind of sad when i leave
[Music]
upgrades need special items not money
wait can i not upgrade anything yet
let me see
huh
oh wait
when i'm there i have to open this
it or can i do it anywhere
what does that do
question my question mark one goes to
question about question mark two
what am i upgrading
with this
see it does need money but also an item
[Music]
i would love to do meet and greet but i
would be finding out so much that i
don't know what i would say i would just
be pressing the whole time
that's that's good that's what i like to
hear
but yeah um a lot of the meet and greet
people were like pretty
unprepared didn't know what to say and i
was like didn't i tell you guys to
prepare what to say and they're like
yeah i'm sorry
okay let's do it what is this
so then i asked questions of course i
had questions prepared you just accepted
i asked them how long they were watching
they were actually like a lot of
um
lurkers who were watching
since the beginning but we're still
lurkers and then there were a couple who
were more new like three months ago or
six months ago
yeah wait what did i just upgrade sorry
potion upgrade oh
they heal more now nice okay
okay should we go this way
oh my god
[Music]
what
why am i dead
am i dead
[Music]
what
am i in there
after life
oh the fps you good game oh it's only on
my side not on obvious kusa
no it's partially
oh it's back to normal
oh
what
[Music]
this is because i already rang one belt
so i can go for the first door i guess
what
[Music]
what is going on
oh but here the cap ends but i can still
walk that way
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that a sword no
huh
what is that
some intestines
no wait it's
knocked over figure of a
fox
i was seeing some other [\h__\h] there
[Music]
okay
talk to me
wake up mommy
mommy
it looks like a chess piece in that
woman yeah
and the insides of your body
what you're stuck
oh
what
dramatic oh no
um
why are you stuck there
it's vibrating the sound you know the
from the
[Music]
it's the vibration from
that oh
oh good morning sunshine oh wait the
eyes are glowing now it wasn't glowing
before but only one
maybe if i ring the second thing then
these eyes will glow too
yeah i can go inside again will i just
see the same thing
seal forever
pretty sure about that i feel like it
will unseal itself again if i ring the
second bell
i don't think that's surreal forever
[Music]
i'll be back
hey lady
so
just gonna go here just in case but i
can't upgrade anything else right yeah
okay
okay but we finally got one upgrade nice
i need more of those items
okay
so far i really like this game
[Music]
i
i don't know why not more people are
playing it in the whole life what the
[\h__\h]
it's great it's amazing and it's not too
long like it's not even that much of
[\h__\h] i should have read that
it's not too much of a commitment you
know like other like adventure and rpg
games
i understand them not playing those
but this is relatively short you can do
it in three parts
two parts even if one if you're pro
i know yeah i know football keep playing
it i know
but besides that you know i want some en
members to play this [\h__\h]
i should play it
and i'm not just saying that because i
like got me i feel like ame would like
the game you know
and maybe fauna
[Music]
who else should play it
oh yeah i could see you not playing this
too
like it's not too much of a commitment
so that's good
and you know inna has those elden ring
skills
is this
can't go down
why
not
piece of cake for inna right what's this
again the second one we get
oh oh
didn't see you there buddy
holy [\h__\h] i think i'm not too bad at
this game so far
there was a little moment where i kept
on
[\h__\h] messing around with the menu but
besides that
i think i'm doing okay so far
there should be a mechanism to open that
somewhere
[Music]
and i keep on finding the secrets too so
you know
i think i'm doing fine
there's a ring lingering
oh it's
here can i is that honest no
okay i thought that was optical
illusion
oh what the [\h__\h]
ran right into that
i won
wait what
oh because i got an achievement just at
that moment when i rang the bell but
that was about the grass but when i ring
these the small ones
does that not do anything at the moment
huh maybe they need to be gold
oh what
too many enemies
way too many enemies
i can handle it
enemy rush
he just killed his friends you made it
easier for me thank you thanks dude i
did it
success i didn't panic i didn't panic at
all oh my god what the [\h__\h] is your
problem
man that's a stronger one than before
and we have one of these menus again
ah uh-huh no stability
uh low stability no safety heard more i
learned that kind of already vulnerable
damage taken 150
uh-huh stability low oh they mean poised
with that
do they mean toys
[Music]
those numbers are like they look so
realistic someone used a freaking
ballpoint pen
to write something on there it's like a
like literally
like some realistic notes
they say that if you throw enough bombs
you'll get a prize so don't be afraid to
use them
a prize
really
what's the point yeah i didn't take
those notes who did that oh
my mommy maybe my mommy
mommy you
could have maybe left me some notes that
i can actually read how about that
wait a second what are
oh
you see on the left side
next to the bombs
there's three different squares
with small dots and big dots
that looks like a pattern
that looks like a pattern to me of maybe
where i can get those bombs
maybe
because it looks like like a map almost
zoom in button
[Music]
ah there you go
yeah i mean that's what i saw
[Music]
hot pepper ivy
effigy that's the money bank
and the lure and the golden coin okay
some of these items we haven't found yet
and there's then there's magic items
[Music]
notes holy cross something something i
need magic points for those
magic potion checkpoint probably is
where you load it up
oh wait those things that i've been
collecting if you have enough of them i
guess because they have the same color
they make one more magic potion ah
it's like a heart piece but it's for a
magic potion
uh-huh
and some kind of weird cards at the
bottom
okay
interesting
[Music]
okay
what about these uh platforms though
i've heard
wow
[Music]
that's what accent i was testing out
buttons because i've heard that you have
to like
pray
[Music]
i don't know what the button is
i pressed every button by now i think
the waves are so wasted
[Music]
you've got no toys bunny weak
you can do it now check the manual i
don't think instead of anything later
ah okay i'll find it in the menu okay
okay okay
[Music]
sometimes you can fall off of these
things
she had a shield even
i don't even have a shield it's not fair
honey
where are you going to answer are you
going to give her to her uh she didn't
ask me i guess she's planning to go
alone i would give her a tour
when is she going
let me check here
[Music]
oh this music is nice
oh
other traps here too
[Music]
wow this is like a treasure girl
can i don't
make these things fall down no okay
wow that's not bad
that's not bad can i use one of these
for an upgrade
shall we go back and check
but then the enemies are gonna come back
here all those
[\h__\h]
are worth it probably
and i get my flasks back too
[Music]
wasn't it here
am i remembering wrong [\h__\h]
did i go the wrong way
oh
no that was the right way oh [\h__\h]
okay
we have
something for 200 we don't know what it
will do but we'll test it out
a girl
tomorrow's my birthday ah jimmy fred
penguin
oh no
oh it's not about youtuber there's more
to me don't worry don't worry it's a
different jimmy that i'm selling at
crunchyroll expo
oh yeah i need to continue talking about
that
wait that was hp nice
oh i need more of those flowers
okay
it's bigger fuel
happy birthday to me
happy birthday
happy penguin day
congratulations
okay so the the the
sword damage can go attack the other
enemies but the lasers of these and
those white ones
doesn't go through
the other enemies if you know what i'm
saying
interesting
observation
yeah so
jimmy's legs the the thing is um i was
asked besides you know making that video
something else i did was naming uh the
menu items
and
yay have you noticed everything was
chicken themed everything was chicken
jimmy's legs everything had chicken the
sliders the phoenix liners i'm so sad i
can't test them out myself
wow but i've been told that they were
delicious generally the food looked
really good
like
genuinely good
so i'm really happy about that because i
was worried you know convention food
maybe not so good
putting kfp
on top of that i wonder if it's gonna
hurt my reputation huh
no but the food was great
food was great
i could not come up with you know
completely like my own menus
um but that's okay like you know they
had certain things that
um
they could do that i guess they normally
do at conventions
but we were able to go with
chicken themed things so that's great
literally all the food was chicken for
everybody who doesn't like chicken i'm
sorry
[Music]
oh my god
even the fries had chicken yeah i think
so wasn't there some
chicken in the fries too
i think
thanks
yeah so i'm like super happy about this
that we were able to do that
can't open that okay uh cause i wanted
to do this for a long time
not even at holy fest
they could do it oh
i just went down
oh
you see at hall of fast i thought you
know we should get some kfp food a coin
oh we didn't get anything like that
there
so
wait why am i
why am i white
[Music]
i changed colors
the moment i entered
do i need to ring them in a certain
order
[Music]
changing
why am i orange again
[Music]
oh wait i go behind maybe and then i
change oh
wait no i'm just
did i change
am i am i white now what
[Music]
what
they changed certain things wait wait
what did that just change
i didn't change the scarf because now
it's purple
and now it's black
[Music]
okay that changes
the tunica itself the top
okay we have black and green
oh only those two
okay what about
i don't want to be it no you know eh i
want to be orange because i'm going to
do it but the white color was special so
let's go with white for a while can i be
white again
no i'm kind of yellow
[Music]
mom dark blue
oh the other direction oh
now i'm like
red so many colors
no i'm purple
oh now i'm blue pink blue pink
fun
now wait is it wait has it only changed
um one color does this change the other
color
wait what just
what did that change
[Music]
pink and blue
i'm still pink and blue
is it changing
something is it my nose
or the shoes
oh it's the nose and the shoes
[Music]
yeah the nose change ah it's the tips of
my hands and and feet and my nose tip ah
cute what there's so many
options
okay oh my god come on
yellow
[Music]
green
blue
a nice light kind of blue
sky blue customizing folks where was the
white
i can't do it anymore
this is kind of a darker orange almost
red
maybe i should take that i don't know
dark evil okay you know what for a while
i want to be in this
just because it looks cool and give me
some cute tips
i could be rudolph the red nosed
reindeer wait
give me some red nose
[Music]
or i don't know oh
out a lot oh
cute
[Music]
is there are there any
black
[Music]
undercover
sneaky fox i like it i can go completely
black
they won't see me
[Music]
they won't see me but the bounce always
stays white
yeah the belt always says white
unless you
[Music]
okay i think this fits well
what is the belt
[Music]
wait huh
wasn't it just a different color is that
like a slight adjustment
i don't know what's happening
the batteries ah the bell resets it ah
okay i like this look at me look at my
fox
wow
about the chrome fox
bono kono focuser
oh
this is so cool that i found this oh
top secret
okay
i'm done
i look stylish
out ready to go where am i
oh here
oh
[Music]
oh how do you like a new look
i mean honestly the previous color stood
out more
he keeps on looking at himself did he
always do that
but we're gonna go with this because
it's cool
the room is really hard to find yeah
what the hell
[Music]
i'm proud of myself for finding that
so proud
that's a lot of enemies oh but he has a
key
he
am i stronger now that i'm this color no
probably not
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
you're little [\h__\h]
mommy
why is it vibrating again
okay now that was just
nothing
oh was i here before
did i find this before no
need to go and get my body though
what's this
i don't think i can go for the door
i think i've noticed the pattern only if
the door is golden then i can go for it
only if the
and the door is only golden when i rang
certain
of those silver things and made them
golden
yeah big brain kewala i figured it all
out i got you all figured
that's my shield
i'm on the other side
hello from the other side
[Music]
i need my [\h__\h] shield back
without you i take
too much damage so please come back to
me
and protect my flesh
hello from the
should i go back
i'm going a completely different way
right now anyway this is not good i need
to go get my
[Music]
okay i'm gonna
i'm going back for the upgrade and holy
[\h__\h] they follow me so far
what
[Music]
okay can i please
oh
so we upgraded my potions and my health
before what does this do attack maybe
yeah okay what did that do nothing that
i can see so maybe it's damaged
oh weren't those two hits before
i think those were two hit enemies
before
okay
nice
just in time to go back there and uh
kill those who have wronged me
okay
more of you guys i'll take you all come
here
and you'll get a kill and you'll get a
kill
you're not very smart guys because you
try to shoot through those walls
you think you see me ah [\h__\h] this dude
gets me every time
okay
let's talk a bit more about the
concession stand i actually for the
longest time i didn't know what that
meant
i felt like concession
sounds like um
what's the words for
i don't know for for like giving up
something conceding
no
i felt like i was giving up something
but yeah apparently it's like a takeover
that makes a lot of sense
that's it
thanks a lot surrendering yeah i thought
it was like surrendering wait is this
correct it doesn't mean oh i guess
they're they're they're they are
surrendering to me
maybe which one ah there that's my body
give me my body
[Music]
we don't want to activate that thing too
early and i don't think i can find it so
okay i'm safe okay okay you can go back
now don't stop shooting me stop
stop shooting me
you don't need to shoot me
good good good good anymore good
[Music]
so
what else uh so i recorded the video and
i made um
um
uh the the naming decisions
and uh then they also had those those
big screens with the menus they
implemented the kfb logo and the tacoma
chicken
so that was really cool like the cafe
was like so apparent
and so out there
i thought it was really awesome actually
like it kind of was a big advertisement
too and then the staff showed me
a comparison
of around the same time
uh the concession stand of kfp
versus the different the normal one
somewhere else i don't know where that
was but somewhere else in the
oh
money and the cafe concession stand had
a huge line
while the other one
didn't
i don't know if it i don't necessarily
think that it's because every all the
campaign people all the whole life fans
went there but just
maybe it looked more delicious but maybe
it was a mix you know
of of
uh okay of people and good looking food
hell yeah so i think it was a huge
success
[Music]
the only thing that was missing but
that's totally okay because like this is
just a small takeover
it was um like you know having the
packaging
having the packaging have my logo on it
too oh what the [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
what am i doing what am i doing sorry
okay
that's that's for another time this was
just you know
kind of a testing
testing phase
he's shaking he's trembling in fear
um was i able to kill this one last time
i don't think i was
okay
oh
[\h__\h]
that one's tough
[Music]
oh
no i'm scared well let's just throw one
more uh
[Music]
okay
no i could have you know i probably
could have if i knew
how it would go i could have ran and
attacked him at the same time but it's
okay we have a key
not sure for what door uh old house
thank you
old house have i been there before no i
[Music]
everybody for uploading pictures of the
food it felt like
i was part of it a little bit thank you
soon for using a hashtag
i'm so happy because like we got to
spread the the whole theme the name of
kfb all over the convention you know
and i i feel like a lot of people who
are also not
um number one piano fans they also ate
the food and they were like hey i can't
be naughty
they make they make fast with nice now
they heard of it and my videos were
playing there it was it was kibaba all
over that food stamp
yeah my videos were playing there
constantly
my my menus were
there phoenix sliders yeah yeah i'm so
happy it was really cool it was more
than i expected to be honest because i
guess they lowered my hopes and
expectations but
i got i got more out of it than i
thought i would
i'm so happy that they were open to
doing that
and now i hope that we can repeat these
kind of things but it's honestly
it's not always possible i i don't do
all the behind the scenes things that
management does
um
but what i know is that you know the
convention needs to be
needs to have a vendor that's open to
that sort of cooperation and there needs
to be budget and all that
um that's why it didn't quite work out
for dokomi even though
i was told that it was going to happen
so then i was really sad because i also
kind of hinted at you guys and dokumi
themselves hinted at it uh
you know a while before the convention
and then it was like sorry not happening
um so
i was kind of sad about it but this time
we finally actually got something like
that to work and then that was really
cool
what do you mean you almost unsubscribed
what's your problem so it's my fault
it's not my fault you're just joking
right
yeah
render stuff complicated yeah i um
especially if the vendor themselves if
they don't quite understand like what
they're dealing with like what the what
youtubers are and all that then they
might not be quite open to doing it you
know
um
so
everything worked out well this time
even though it was also i'm gonna tell
you was actually pretty last minute
it was kind of
uh
i didn't know that this was happening
until like
pretty recently
[Laughter]
that's um yeah just kind of a recent uh
thing i don't know if they were planning
it earlier and just
told me so late about it but
i didn't know for most of the time um
they wanted to surprise me i'm not sure
they were probably just you know ironing
out details until
it's really short so that they wouldn't
get my hopes up you know like with
dokomi
where i thought it was happening and
then it didn't happen so maybe they were
just waiting until it was 100 certain
that we can do it
um
which i guess makes sense is i don't
want to be disappointed again like that
yeah
yeah okay so what do we have here we
have another map of some sort
uh
huh
am i on this map right now
because what i find interesting is that
at the top like in the middle
to the right the icon has an x on it to
the left the icon has no x on it doesn't
mean like i would what does that mean
and we have different new enemies ah we
have the the spider is it the same
spiders that i ran away from before
what is this place anyway
is that the spider place no ah it's the
place that i couldn't go any further
before oh yeah maybe
oh yeah maybe
the ruined at all
not
i can't read this [\h__\h]
huh
that didn't help me much
oh chest
right other side
another coin what do i do with those
so i know it does
find out maybe oh wait
golden piece of like something it's gold
golden and that makes it
makes it sense for me oh you're right i
have like no hp oh [\h__\h]
time to go back to a hill
yeah very nice peaceful
of course it fits into my pocket
now let's go to the house again i guess
but what is this
chest hey chest
chest off
what is inside more money okay cool
and money important how much do i have
right now 360 okay
that is fine that's pretty good
because i already you know did some
upgrades just before
what okay i'm going back i'm going back
and we're back retreat tactical retreat
we got the key we don't really have to
go here right now we got the king now
[Music]
yeah i sang sparks
i sang sparks at the
at the panel inna seng violet
oh oh the shortcut hope you liked
the singing and the idea the idea for
the for the you know the game itself
don't die now
[Music]
came from inya
but she saw it like on youtube i think
from the ellen show
[Music]
and uh yeah
i think it was a cute idea but you know
i was i was saying i was talking to you
know like uh how many should we prepare
like maybe
two each or three each you know have
like four pitches or six pitches and she
was like oh i think we
already take up too much time with just
two
and i'm like okay i guess but then
we only prepared two
and then we did have so much left over
time
and we were stalling so much because
like i was looking at the discord chat
from our management while we were like
at the moment when we were done with the
two pitches
and uh
they wrote to us guys you have still so
much more time please stall
and i'm like ah [\h__\h] i knew what we
should have we should have had more
items
i tried my best with the wave and chit
chat
to stall as much as possible
until we had the songs um the
performance for the songs and then but
even then we were too early so
so
um
yeah kind of like
behind the scenes
we're trying to
um
you know i was i was trying to tell inna
without telling her like
too obviously because i didn't want it
to be too obvious that we [\h__\h] up
like hey one of us should like prepare
another image but you're you're you're
controlling the screen so
uh
i think we have to do it so that that i
pitch it and you choose the image so
um yeah
we are kind of worked out in the end
yeah
but even with that one one more item we
were still stalling as much as possible
and holy [\h__\h] i just
i was actually i was i was so nervous i
was so
god
i was like sad i can't stall anymore
and this game is fun but like it's kind
of
always the same arguments like oh why do
you
why do you have to have this in your
life and it's like oh because it changes
your life oh it's amazing
yeah there's not
if you watch the ellen show
it's like not that much
different kind of arguments
um it's all they always
they always use the same organs what the
[\h__\h]
well i didn't even go inside the
windmill yet didn't i
i have the keynote for that one door
that's the door that's that's the door
wait wait let me go there
you played it off well really
i'm so happy about the positive feedback
because i thought the stalling was so
obvious that i would get a lot of um a
lot of [\h__\h] for it
oh but thankfully you guys were so
positive about it oh
[Music]
huh one cheese cube for real mate
one cheese cube
[Music]
there's a
can i go for here yeah
light rider left
left a ride
right
oh there's my shield
so that was just a decoy the one cheese
cube was a decoy
it was obvious but you guys played as
well really thank you
i knew we should have prepared more i
knew two was not gonna be enough man
uh
actually i already when i was looking
for the items beforehand i already had
some ideas for other items
i should have
should have thrown them in there anyway
okay now we're here but like we've been
there before like kind of
you know it's always says
when the side is kind of blurry you know
here when there is not a clear edge
what the [\h__\h] is this
nanny
ah
what is this
can i see myself on the map
where am i
i'm like uh
i guess because i'm underground i can't
see myself but i think i'm like around
the well in the middle top
like here much later
yeah it looks like something for much
later
[Music]
well at least we know where it is
and i'm finding them all all the secrets
[Music]
you know at like the at super mario i'm
really bad at finding secrets
right
i'm i'm actually really surprised
[Music]
that i'm i can find all these secrets
eye
i don't know how how good is my progress
though i wonder
i'm not sure if i made more progress now
i have an idea
[\h__\h] my react is silly
uh
here oh
well what the [\h__\h] did i do though
my achievement says nothing happened
should i have so far in the the second
one
keep going
[Music]
does that count for all wells because um
there were more than one i think
are they connected
i want more
one more i can make a wish okay
cool okay let's try to find one more but
they were kind of um rare
where do i go next
[Music]
little [\h__\h]
not you guys again
no wait i wanna
wanna go here
i think is that where i wanted to go
yeah yeah yeah i wanted to go here
and then go this way because i haven't
been here before
oh yeah wait i got my shield
how do i use it oh wait wasn't it like
our
i just want this button
well what is this
spacey freaky
hmm
[Music]
i can't do anything here i think
i entered from
the wrong way but i can leave here where
does that where does that go
[Music]
see it's never one of those pieces or is
that the same no it's another one
another one
something fell apart now i need to
reconnect it maybe
remember [\h__\h] oh yeah right but
oh yeah there's a chest okay let's try
to get past it and open the chest
wait
[Applause]
okay i got it but at what cost
at what cost
maybe i cannot reflect shield at some
point but holy [\h__\h] i'm gonna die
[Music]
how do you deal with that [\h__\h]
yeah i can block them i was blocking
them but then at some point it runs out
it keeps on like pushing me back
no
upgrade no okay
i can attack them really
oh
maybe we should have tried that
okay
by the way what was this again oh yeah
the shop
and that was a show
okay okay
very interesting game
very interesting game i have to say
it's fun
it's
we go fun way
i look like an evil fox i look like dark
link it's dark dark tunic fox
okay
and here we gain uh when you regain a
stamina faster if you stop blocking when
it doesn't shoot ah
okay
okay but now i just think oh i'm scared
are you done
[Music]
nice we killed it oh there's another one
coming here
[Music]
okay foolish foolish
okay
stupid little [\h__\h]
i need to get used to those
monsters
do i not have any other shortcuts to get
to that place
man
oh no stamina oh
why did i not just kill i don't know
because i was also
at risk
uh-huh
[Music]
like a boss monster
stop rolling don't you dare say that to
me
don't you dare
my tooth kind of stings
[Music]
no please don't hurt me
at least i died
so far away hallelujah
yeah ptsd
man don't remind me about the ring
where's this place wait haven't i been
here before
oh dear
yeah yeah and i didn't go past here
because of that thing freaking me out
but wait there's this chest
ah
it's in the shadow so you can barely see
it
young
[Music]
upgrade
killed it
oh [\h__\h] i forgot about it again
sorry i'm not gonna have to stereotype
you
no for god
i forgot
it's just the second time i killed it so
what are those twitter birds ruined
that's all i needed did i uh wait i
don't know do i need to go one of these
birds
it's running away from me
twitter doesn't like confrontation
but it showed me this pump thank you
should i kill it
die twitter
wait okay it's scared it doesn't attack
me i guess let's leave it alone i guess
well maybe not
sorry um
what's this
we saw those in the menu but i don't
know what it is
i can't equip it
but it looked like um like an
arm coupling out of leather on one side
you know the art on it looks like it
[Music]
what was that
is that all i can do can i not get like
higher oh
no
what are
r1
r
the [\h__\h] is r1 this [\h__\h]
how's it r1
[Music]
ah
mamma
[Music]
i can equip it what what what
you mean that's a that's l one
you owe me a potion
uh here ah
so maybe that is some kind of armor like
i have more defense of that can i like
see that happening anywhere
i don't see anything changing but
[Music]
maybe i i am stronger maybe i have more
defense than that now
look at so
so i think really i can't
do anything else here
eat your disney
bird's point of view is freaking me out
right now
okay okay
going back
oh no no no no no
library annex interesting though
okay where do we go next go next but
where
do cool
oh that thing is so broke red when it
breaks
there's one of those
the forks
the tuning fork comes out of it
huh
[Music]
yeah those at least stay broken but
not when i
not when i revive ryan or do they those
actually stay broke no they don't
because i killed
that one up there once didn't i
i'm confused
i need to get past that thing i think
[Music]
i need
explosion was coming but i had no space
to escape
another one right over there
okay now i can open the chest and pistol
oh
it's me
okay how do i reach that one i can't i
can
[Music]
sorry okay i need to learn how to jump
or something
[Music]
what about here
let me jump i want to learn how to jump
where am i
need to go to the dark tomb
i need to go there
do i see myself
yeah okay i'm at the very bottom oh
there's nothing there okay
okay
let's go
i don't know
where do we need to ah top let's go to
the let's try to go to the top where the
dark tomb is
we need the meal
from where
where should i go
what else did we talk about
i think we're kind of done with
crunchyroll um the panel went well but i
was nervous
and i was stalling but it was fun it was
nice to see so many people there
nice to see people in the merch
very cool
what else
yoga was there
attention
yeah lots of quiver cosplayers i didn't
say it on twitter but i was very happy
to see that especially because
last year at all of the na conventions
if we remember
um
there were like no kiwas right and then
this year i saw
so many
yeah
i saw so many i saw like at least like
two casual ones and two default ones
i was so happy to see that
yeah thank you to the cosplayers
more representation of kiwawa
how do i get ah maybe behind the
waterfall
[Music]
oh yeah and the sparks
two d phones two casual
one sparks quiver and who knows what
else we missed out on
america
karaoke
saw a few of them as well so glad to see
people cosplaying
more yes more yeah sparx so sparks
cosplay very
nice because it's not really you know
it's not a live tv outfit what the [\h__\h]
oh yeah right oh i forgot about you guys
oh nice kill
no damage kill
[Music]
secrets
no secret
really
[Music]
no okay i was thinking
um
yeah
yeah i'm so glad that um i chose
a casual outfit that's so
easy to cosplay
i don't think
i don't think i made it with that in
mind not necessarily no not really i
didn't
um
but in hindsight i feel like it was a
very smart decision
oh [\h__\h] oopsie what
it's dark
um
no i think
i will be getting a lamp so i'm not
oh
i'm not doing this now what what
the secret finder in the dark
nani
oh dark tone
but
under the well and beneath the earth
lantern is it telling me i need a
lantern for this cause i don't have it
yet
oopsie
where am i
well we can safe at least
there's a land planted here or do i get
it somewhere else
i don't see [\h__\h]
maybe there
[Music]
did you go visit you no um he only went
to the meet and greets that happened uh
yesterday and my meet and greet was the
day before yesterday
i have no dynamite or so oh wow hmm
wait the door is closed i thought i
could go through but no i can't
i have to go from the other side
but i didn't know that jaguar was around
i was aware of it because i was told
but he didn't come to the meet and greet
on that day i guess he was busy
yeah but i mean i talked to him before
so i'm good i'm good
i don't need yoga to talk to me
okay so i feel smart for finding this
but it seems like i should have found it
the other way around
maybe i entered from the wrong side
like
[Music]
what does it say
danger
[Music]
you can't write danger without anger did
you know
[\h__\h]
press the wrong button
okay i have to wait for that
[Music]
time
oh [\h__\h]
it's dude
stop man
there it is i want the ring in
yeah i'm right can't spell
with lava
can't smell cute
without a
so what
i guess you're trying to mix it no my my
word actually had a meeting though
give me that when will i get like a
thing to grab things
oh what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
not worth getting the chest right now
i'll get there eventually
but
so
how do i oh wait just go up here
[Music]
can't spell takanashi without cash
or or
i don't know
nothing
[Music]
how where do i have to go to enter that
i guess i maybe for that gate but then
first i have to open it up from some
other side too
where am i where am i
[Music]
here okay
what is the right way to enter that
place that we just came out of
[Music]
i'm not sure i'm just going to continue
riding around like a crazy person
[Music]
i guess i'll go here afterwards after
don't all me i just want to open it
don't kill me
cool not so bad
i'm gonna die
i almost got to the shortcut there's a
shortcut there oh he died too
from the impact of my body
i am fine with this
i think we're doing fine
yeah the shortcut opening
i mean even that doesn't really help me
much though but um
i also want that piece of paper oh wow
okay
move your body
[Music]
yo
i'm so good yo i'm actually good at this
game
i think i've got a bad one yeah you're
translating something i tried that
argument too but no it only works in
japanese
oh yeah
did you see him um speaking of figure
did you see it because i saw it in the
comments did you see um
uh that i uh
open fast open oh [\h__\h] open
okay [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
the fact that they can attack you while
you're doing
these animations is kind of rough
horse hoof yeah now it's open
but wait where is my body now on that
side right so i need to go for that side
again to pick it oh i go for the other
side
and then um
let's see
all right never mind okay
ow
well when they're flying it's kind of
hard to find those
okay
how did i not run from here before
[Music]
okay
cool cool sorry bro
thanks helps me a lot
[Music]
this place guys
i didn't go in
secret behind the waterfall next to that
dark place okay
remember
killing you again
how many times do you want to be killed
we're talking about it
died
[Music]
getting mad here getting pretty mad
uh what you call that place so we can
remind you
um
waterfall
dark wonderful secret
i guess i don't know
so yeah uh
this this figurine is coming out then
they showed it off so the gray version
great ada
was shown off
yeah
[Music]
yeah finally and if you saw you may have
noticed
that they're
[Music]
like art inna's first art of us that's
what i wanted to say
[Music]
no
all right
a nice touchdown
all of our poses are like modeled after
the first piece of art that ena did back
then you know
really cool
[Music]
yeah i hope i don't stay gray
forever nani if you seek to increase
your power ah attack death hp potion and
the other ones i don't know yet
ooh
[Music]
okay you already did some of these
upgrades
[Music]
nothing
new here
what this oh no half points
i die thank you forever
echo of self what does that mean
white [\h__\h] oh my god
what what does that mean
ah my body that i can pick up and then
oh it tells me it makes an explosion
kaboom
oh oh and then it shows me these cards
again maybe it tells me oh you can get
stronger with this i don't know
you can do it garden night
try to be this strong
okay three is the maximum then it wants
me to go to the maximum okay i think i'm
about to die though um
okay i did not die that is incredible
how did i manage to survive well
stay alive
oh maybe that's the entrance that i was
looking for but wait let me um are we
close to like a checkpoint where i can
heal myself
that would be nice
yeah okay it's very close
thank you and maybe level up
oh
i can
do both let's see
hp to free
already maximum oh
hello
nice
damn i like that that's so
satisfying look it's so much bigger now
oh [\h__\h] no wait that's not what i wanted
i just wanted to upgrade some more
oh we can't do it we're so close and
then we can get the potion upgrade to
maximum
just a bit more money necessary
okay
okay so far i'm really doing well i
think
i didn't need to turn on baby mode i
didn't turn off stamina or health but
i'm i'm
you know surprised that that exists i
guess there's always we need to go
because there's always a
uh game recorder mode
but that's not the way what was the game
journalist journalist mode oh are you
[\h__\h]
i've heard about you
yeah oh wait go away
i knew that because i saw that
i saw that in a clip of the game
and yet i was too late
but this time i made it okay
what is this
spooky
disgusting water but i can walk in it
okay
easy
holy [\h__\h] i blocked it
we can get another upgrade wait
so i have enough money for the potion
upgrade and then i already uh
wait why is 300 in red as if i don't
have that i have 310
should i go back nah we don't need it
that badly
i knew that i knew behind that waterfall
that would be something more fruit
oh i can't roll in the water
it's kind of sauce was there no secret
up there
oh no really really
you want me to believe that
all right
okay
all in all
to end the crunchyroll talk i think it
was great you know there were so many
members invited and involved in
creating content for it like me kelly
and i'm recording something behind the
scenes and i recorded some other things
like the the full-size videos and the
the
wide screen video the greetings and all
that
so they asked us to record a lot of
things like the food style thing it as
well
but i think we got some
yeah a really cool result out of it a
really cool experience zone that was you
know we never had something so big
before i think an a convention
i think it turned out great i'm i'm
really happy with the results
the whole meat experience yeah
one more upgrade
yeah all the pictures that people were
taking were really cool really sweet and
cute
and it was just like
full with so much whole life stuff and
so many whole life fans
it's like an invasion
let's show the video later um i don't i
mean we recorded it specifically for
that so i don't think that um we're
allowed to like show it or upload it
but i think there's
um
nah i don't think we can do that no
oh look at this
pasta a friendly bird that loves to eat
slimes oh crap oh crabbit grandpa has a
hard shell but krabit has pals
envoy more questions and answers wow
that's the whole game
this gives me more
more questions than answers that's
literally the game envoy
and then there's a weird bird one of
those birds that i killed at the very
bottom the square world oh
and then there's some music notes
scribbled and i wonder if that has any
meaning then probably not
yeah it would devalue the crx experience
exactly so we can't upload it but i
think
i think i was on fire during that
recording for
that
[Music]
like we didn't
like we just roughly had an idea of of
what we were gonna do but
i improvised so much and i feel like i
was on a roll with my jokes
i i i was on a roll i was that's
actually why i feel like it's a bit of a
waste that is not public because
i was on the [\h__\h] role i think i was
really funny i was quite the comedian
on that day
i was so satisfied with myself
yeah
it was fun
so it turned out pretty well i was
surprised
[Music]
at one point callie was like
um
blaming me or like complaining to me
that i was
destroying her business because i was i
was saying like hey i'm gonna give you a
really bad yelp review and then she was
like oh you're you're hurting small
businesses and then i was like
i don't think you can call a 2 million
subscriber business with some with
topping the charts the music charts
small pieces
and then she was like oh yeah okay
i want the fight i want the argument
[Laughter]
hmm
roasted but like in a good way
you're not small anymore callie
you have to
you have to realize you're not a small
small rapper you're a big raptor you're
big rapper now yo
you have so many fans everywhere you're
you're getting number one in the charts
it
there's no way of hiding it yeah
destroying cali with her own success it
was basically a compliment
my brain was on fire on that day
just like my frying pan
[Music]
yeah i mean she's even signed on the
universal so there's like no
i mean the whole thing was you know
just a joke acting anyway a skit but
there's no way of like denying that
she's successful so
you can't hide it you're not a small
business cali
say it admit it
admitting is the first step
be proud
no
damn i love potato chips
i feel like i've eaten so many
that my tongue is burning from it
[Music]
this bag never ends
no i said i love potato chips not olive
mmm
wow
yeah humble break yeah it's
fine i mean it's like those those girls
that say
i'm not pretty even though they are
pretty
[Laughter]
i mean i mean i get that myself
too because like you know i don't think
i'm pretty but then people
say the same thing to me i guess like a
lot of the pretty girls who say it
really don't think they're pretty
they're not always fishing for
compliments some really think they're
not pretty even though they're pretty
it really do be like that
no it's not always fishing for
compliments
you just see yourself way differently
you you perceive yourself differently
than others dude
and
and you see yourself without makeup too
you know like like often often what you
see is only the the face with makeup and
it does a lot it changes a lot
so that girl who's saying i'm not funny
may
mean that i'm not pretty without makeup
with makeup i'm okay
[Music]
shut up
i don't need to be praised of course i'm
pretty look at me
i'm perfect
i yesterday to like uh the day before
yesterday when i was setting up for the
meet and greet
you know there were like staff members
you know
you know we were trying to figure out
like the internet connection and stuff
and then
you know i turn on you know this camera
and they're like ah you look pretty
today and i'm just like questioning my
question my question
whenever you say that to a victor it
makes no sense
i look the same every day
it's not a compliment
it makes no sense
how can i not look pretty
i'm always perfect
[Music]
i i don't i don't
i don't have an option
my face is always the same
[Laughter]
my hair can change but my face is always
the same
it's not like i can suddenly have a
pimple or something
my [\h__\h] rate
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah i can put pimples on my face i guess
yeah
pinky pimples
[Laughter]
oh i can put png um freckles on my face
maybe
hmm
and lipstick oh and mascara
oh my god let's do a makeup i thought oh
my god
you know i was thinking like i wish i
could do you know all the things that
normal youtubers do like i do your
makeup haha
um and i was like too bad we can't do
that but we can kind of do it
low-key
only low-key
yes
freckles activate my nerves
i like freckles too i did ask um for
them for uh the the dimble outfit but i
didn't get them
i was told
um
it's it would change
[Music]
my image too much
even though you know
girls put on freckles as makeup and
stuff
um a lot of girls do that
it's like a
trend
yeah but i wasn't allowed to get
freckles i'm sorry guys i tried i tried
but i think if i do it as a png i can
get through with it
[Music]
it would look cute i think so too
also with these with these braids it
would look so cute and freckles makes
sense because i'm a i'm a red orange
head so
stop and i was saying like what about
you know summer freckles
some people get freckles
momentarily temporarily in the summer
yeah but oh well
oh i already did png freckles what
when when when i didn't see oh my god
i can have a pacifier with every outfit
i'll even use it in this one
a while ago
oh oh my god
i need to see that
sorry i'm just snacking on
chips having a little break i think it's
good to have a little break tucked on
the cue case there or not
qk2
um
by the way guys
i can give you two choices
um
either we only play but we play for a
long time today or we end the gaming
part early and then the super chat
rating
i don't want to go too late because i
want to either order food early enough
or i want to go uh out to get food early
enough
you want the super generating i also
want to play though
hmm
okay but we'll play maybe for one more
hour
i also have to go to an idol meeting now
you need to catch up
i don't think there is so much to catch
up don't think there was that much
okay
i'll go to an island meeting now
and then we'll continue
um
[Music]
need to hydrate because i ate so many
potato chips
[Music]
thank you
away with the bag no need for you okay
yeah i got enough water
no more cherry juice i was drinking
cherry juice did i tell you
sour cherry but now it's just water
there's a frog's domain
domain a frank's domain at the top right
i'm very curious about that but i don't
think we'll get there anymore today
we'll see we'll see
we currently
are in some a dark place but that's not
this place right
why is the map that we got
here like
something completely different
and also this was that was i able to
upgrade anything else
oh [\h__\h] oopsie
frog dungeon
a thousand i thought three was maximum
but you can go even higher
oh
what
not a little okay
so where do we go
oh i can jump down here sometimes i can
jump down and sometimes not
interesting
also guys was there uh what else should
we talk about we talked about
crunchyroll expo
what's next
ah [\h__\h] i forgot about the explosion
but if one hit killed that mob nice
but i keep on forgetting about the
explosion
understandable right
hello summer well i can't say anything
about that we're not included
uh korea
not sure what to say about that either
[Music]
did you know what happened with vesper
no
what happened
did you get in this keyword i did but
the thing is like i didn't unpack it yet
because i was i'm still wondering should
i unpack it on stream
also there's snacks like i wonder if the
snacks are enough snacks to make a full
snack box review out of it or if i
should just like you know
do it maybe i should just do it all
behind the scenes and then post pictures
and if it's enough snacks for a stream
then i'll make a stream out of it but
um
why did i do that
i can't even roll away you know i
just need to block it i i can't roll in
this water so i just need to block the
explosion i should try because i can't
get far away
uh quick enough
anyway
[Music]
i don't i'm getting better you know i'm
not scared anymore of those things i
i confront them now
what
super spicy hot sauce nearly died on
stream
dinner
uh what's hachima who also did something
like that ages ago
i wonder how the original song envy is
going
um
well you know you guys know i'm i'm
having uh canado work on it so you know
he's been very busy
but
now
it should be
uh
in the beginning
phase it you know originally
i would have wanted it already in end of
july but you know this is how things go
sometime it's fine
i can wait i can wait it's probably
better this way because then the hype
is like more spread out you know the
because we had the 3d birthday if right
after the 3d birthday concert the song
comes out then the hype is too bundled
up you know so this way we can have
something nice a bit more spread out
what the [\h__\h] is this
so mysterious
fight me
ow i'll okay
thank god i drank that
thank god i drank it right before he
exploded
oh my god
free at once is khanna
tough
i'd think that striking while the iron
is fun is the correct way
i mean that wasn't possible this time so
whatever
we deal with what we got
wanna fight
fine with me
what are those cubes there
i only get those from
the exploding enemies i think
if i observe correctly
[Music]
because i think i got him from these two
i thought i had my shield out
did it break through or did i can you
not uh
open the shield once it penetrated you
once
[Laughter]
there
is
oh
all good
oh good
maybe you're staggering i'm not sure but
oh well so is this thing back now i
think it's back
yeah okay
oh [\h__\h]
oh wow
[Music]
that was still fine
that was okay
[Music]
that was not good how was that one of my
best fights but that's okay
a lot of damage yeah
okay when when when wh
where where we what were we talking
about uh
yeah music video but besides that what
else was i talking about
ah not only
oh like a swirling attack would be
i was just asking us for a funeral
yeah
mario oh yeah that's something i totally
forgot and i wanted to talk about
[Music]
okay too reckless too reckless
i wanted to tell the non-members the
story uh like a little bit of an
explanation of what happened the other
day
[Music]
so
at least a few days have passed so i
don't feel so embarrassed about it
anymore i guess but
um
i tried out a new frying pan because my
other one was broken and it didn't come
with the lid
that's important for later
and
um
yeah i made the mistake of leaving it
alone
for too long when there was only oil
in the pan
i saw it coming
[Laughter]
and
yeah when i came back to it it was like
it was smoking but it wasn't on fire yet
and then i picked it up i was already i
already noticed oh [\h__\h] this is my bag
there's something
ha [\h__\h] you man
there's something wrong here this is not
normal
good smoke
this is young my smoke then i picked the
frying pan up and
it
catches fire
and i scream and i panic
because
i didn't like i was like who i was
trying to
in a short amount of time figure out
what to do
what why again
no wait did i lose that one body now
oh
no
oh whatever that's okay
those [\h__\h]
yeah and then you know my first
thought was like i probably
should not
pour
water on this [\h__\h] palette
interesting
interesting how that one went
so thankfully i didn't pour any water on
it
but then i just couldn't think like what
to do because i wanted to smother it
smother i want it
um
[Music]
the
[\h__\h] but i didn't have a lid and i
wasn't sure like oh if i put some fabric
on it wouldn't that like
catch on fire too and it was a whole
panic situation so i wasn't um
i was scared because that never happened
to me before that never happened to me
before like i've i've
i've learned
like
seven eight nine years ago in school
in hotel
kitchen training
how to deal with that but
you know when it's the first time that
you actually confronted or something
like that then you panic and and i live
alone so i
i don't know if i didn't live alone
maybe i would have had an easier time
figuring out what to do
well in that moment i was actually
scared i was scared i was going to burn
my whole kitchen down and then the the
pretty soon
before it even caught fire
um there was um
even before even before
it caught fire the the smoke alarm the
fire alarm smoke alarm already turned
itself on it was so loud it was
it was piercing my ears and my brain
because it was like
making me even more nervous and even
more panicky it was really [\h__\h] loud
i think you heard it in the whole
building
it was everywhere the elevator shut down
and yeah it was [\h__\h] good
terrible
and so i couldn't think too clear but at
least i didn't pour any water on it huh
and um
yeah the alarm
the alarm did um
[Music]
something like a fire department
so i was really worried about that too
like holy [\h__\h] and then all of that
happened right before the stream that we
were gonna do mario kart
um
so i was kind of busy i couldn't i had
my hands full man i couldn't notify your
girls
you girls you girls the girls and you
guys um yeah and then while i was
waiting
i actually got the fire out by
cr
crazily blowing at it like a maniac and
i know you might think how is that
possible
cause i didn't i wasn't sure how it was
possible either
you think maybe the so the reason is
that i blew it so long that uh it just
like um deleted itself
by getting rid of all the oil but there
was still oil
i saw there was still oil in the frying
pan
after the fire was out
so it did not deplete all of the oil
[Laughter]
that not all of the fuel was gone and i
it really felt like i blew it all out i
was just blowing at it like a crazy
person
beautiful translation
so anyway whether or not that was really
me let's put that aside but that was
basically how i got rid of the fire okay
and then uh i was like crying and
ashamed and panicking and i looked
outside the
the
my apartment
to check if the neighbors are like
outside or so like in the hallway
and then like one one neighbor came out
and she was like like calming me down
soothing me kind of
and i'm really happy and thankful for
that because
i was freaking out man
oh
okay there we go sorry
i was freaking out and i was
scared if i you know if the fire
department comes so i have to pay a [\h__\h]
ton of money and all that i was really
worried about all kinds of things and i
was i was embarrassed and i didn't want
to put too much
trouble i didn't want to bother the
neighbors too much but it was [\h__\h]
loud for like
20 30 minutes or so
it was insane
and every now and then some neighbors
would come out and they were like uh
what's going on
excuse me
and i'm like sorry this is my first time
i'm so sorry i didn't want it to happen
it was an accident but no actual fire
it's okay
and uh yeah
finally
um
oh [\h__\h] what am i doing
finally
it was all cleared up and they turned
the alarm off and everything was cool
um except me i still was mentally
damaged and scared and
embarrassed ashamed
and yeah
i needed to calm down so i cancelled my
part of the stream
and the other girls yeah they also
rescheduled we might do it next week
[Music]
what
how do i was i doing any damage
i wasn't sure if it was doing damage
but i don't want to die here again so
i'm just going to move on first
let's just run oh yeah
i thought that was a path what about
here no
no
ah here
okay
oh we're on that side now so we can make
that shortcut
[Music]
use a damp towel yeah i didn't think of
that in a moment i was just panicking
you know
but next time
i want to be prepared and have like a
a fire what do you call it
fire extinguishing
thingy fabric uh
i don't know what you call it what is it
fire blanket or it's just called fire
blanket okay
isn't that literally my birthday
merchandise
well well that's what this is
but yeah
all in all
uh i'm okay nothing was damaged in
theory
oh what that's new
nothing was damaged and i was just
hecking scared to ever cook again
oh my god i'm gonna die
i need healing
one more chest
don't you dare kill me don't sit there
yes
one more hit and i could have died
oh magic potion that i still can't use
let's go
i'll have them all ready whenever i can
use magic i'll already have free potions
of that
isn't that nice
secrets
what is that
where did i go
what
it's that place
that we stop from the other side but i'm
not ready to fight this right now i have
no health
i can't do this right now
why am i
i don't see myself
oh i'm under the bridge
here we cook starts an oil fire until
yeah i was watching all kinds of
gordon ramsay gordon ramsay that's his
name brian
why does that remind me of game of
thrones as if it's a game of thrones
character because of the ramsey wasn't
there a ramsey
oh my god
that's messing up my brain right now
cause ramsay was such a piece of [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh my god that's terrible that's
terrible
gordon should sue game of thrones for
that because they ruined his name
oh my god
oh the other side lamp
was it always there i didn't see it from
the other side i never noticed it
[\h__\h] finally
grab a lamb
nice find your tall i needed that ah
i can see now in the dark
uh
can i get my hp recharged too
ah look at that that's where i was
running towards
when i can give it a try the worst thing
that can happen is that we die and then
we come back here and uh eliminate them
properly
do we have a bomb or so of course not
[Laughter]
let's uh let's go let's do this
[Music]
[Laughter]
one hp and a dream
oh
wait can i go there from here
is there is there some kind of shortcut
oh
yeah wait i mean there's a shortcut we
can go
up and then left i guess
can we afford any upgrades right now
we can
wait that's a new thing here what is
that what is that
huh
does that give me another life or
something
oh no no no how do you make it
excellent right thank you
defense oh
okay cool thanks
thanksies
here and then down
no
okay i don't have to fight you guys i
guess but whatever
what was that what was that
what
was that was that just and
pose how did i do that
shield attack how how how
how did i do it
explosion
[Music]
okay
easy clap
blowing on a grease fire extinguishes
fires or it could cause another grease
fire or cause the fire to fly in your
face next time you use salt
i didn't know about the songs
but okay see it apparently it is really
possible so i really think it was me
honestly i really think it was me
i saw it in front of my eyes working
but i was also like hyperventilating
i was like
like crazily
i was i was basically blowing for my
life
okay here we are again so this is the
correct order of doing things
now
yeah
i was so scared man i thought that my
kitchen is gonna
be on fire
i'm so glad it's over but i'm really sad
it happened in the first place but yeah
we're gonna play mario kart maybe in
this
uh coming monday or tuesday maybe even i
hope so
um
yeah i need to because the dlc came out
i want to test it i want to check out
the dlc
did you guys check out the new roads
already
also where should i wait no i can go
that way right i didn't go before i
couldn't see
your courses are good
not yet not yet
not yet one oh yeah monday is tomorrow
[\h__\h] hey why is my light not working
is it on purpose am i not supposed to
see anything
i saw he wanted to attack but he has no
poise [\h__\h]
[Music]
you got nothing what
on me holy [\h__\h] what okay we have to be
careful here
can you go in the sign
oh my god that's so scary
these ones don't even activate why
[Music]
slowly
what's this oh it's a grave
yeah it was called tombs wasn't it
i feel like i'm in diablo now
what if there's like some mechanism
where you can turn on the light and then
suddenly you see that this whole thing
is like a huge huge skeleton that i'm
walking on or something like that
[Music]
please feel free to come over here
oh wow that kind of hurts a little bit
that would be crazy you know i can kind
of
see it oh
we turned
him on
but like
what does that do those monsters we had
the floor okay
chill
the music has an interesting beat
[Music]
so cowardly of you
to fly around at the top when i can't
fly though i still don't even have that
that grabby weapon
grappling hook
i don't like this place it's cool but
it's i don't like it when i can't see
[\h__\h] i like my games to be bright
and clear
let's see what i'm doing but okay we
just did something oh
can we move it
oh it's opening but
can i
walk up somewhere but okay now we have
to go down
oh we're going deeper we're going deeper
okay
like my light mode yeah i don't accept
any hate for me using light mode okay
are there monsters in some of these
i heard it wrong i felt the rumbling
there's some enemy there
but also fox statues oh and statues of
the lasers
the enemy statues
and they're but they're statues but they
shoot lasers
that dude is this like a mission
impossible kind of thing
impossible call me beat me
[Music]
finally a new bomb
about [\h__\h] time
i'll put it here hopefully i don't push
it by accident
[Music]
um i hope i don't get pushed into
but i can push the enemies into it too i
think
which is fun
wait that's for um mp potion right a
piece
of potion
wait no it's not just because of the
light okay we did get a new hp potion
not in pink
it just looks different down here
oh
a fourth one
the last piece
of flask
wonderful all according to cake
well let's drink one of those charlie
hi come at me why is he not
i can't even focus on him is he in
chains or something ah there we go you
didn't react to me
come try me i'm not gonna run after you
give me my cheese cubes
all right then
they're going fast
sheesh where am i going anyway
[Music]
i wonder if the slicey thingies are one
hit kill
i thought
it's hard to look for secrets here
because it is
dark in general
but i hope i didn't miss out on anything
we need to go this way
nice
made it my way through here pretty
smoothly
yeah
uh and now we have these things here hmm
can we kill them
or can we move them
oh okay we can easy
wow
okay now we see what happens if we were
to walk into one of those which we don't
want to do right
so very carefully
ah we could just throw a bomb in there
probably
to make it really easy but is that
necessary it shouldn't be necessary what
if you don't have any bumps
oh yeah we can do that
but they roll pretty far it's hard to
test it but
oh yeah okay
they're gone
now we have a free field to find this
thing oh he's pretty strong
okay oh no come on
it died right after
[Applause]
i was just realizing that that's not one
of the normal skeletons it's stronger
but it was kind of too late where the
[\h__\h] did i go to reach that place
uh
look was it that way really
it's open now but no we have to go up
i guess
ah
could i have used maybe and maybe the
maybe the turrets would have killed him
if i but you have to get really close to
them to make them walk towards you
so i'm not too sure about that but now
we have to do the whole dungeon again
for real
that's actually mean
but now we have four full flasks i
that's guess really [\h__\h] mean
why was there no checkpoint in there
er
okay i'll try to
get through it as fast as possible oh no
wait this place is already open i am
leaving see ya
okay that's good
that is
and then we go that one no we don't go
that way we already want is there a
shortcut here though i don't think there
was a shortcut here
but i don't have to go for the chest so
high
uh why do i keep on letting these things
hit me
now and that's really not good because
when i even when i block them they push
me into
the spikes
that's not good
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah yeah sure thank you for
doing that for me
very helpful
okay okay okay how much damage did that
uh dude do to me
did someone see how much damage i had
when he killed how much health i had
when he killed me
a lot okay so you want me to do full
heal okay i mean i can do this
um
now should we do the bomb again
the good thing is i also have a bomb aka
my body because my body's a bump
can i roll for the lasers see i don't
want to test that out because we haven't
had the opportunity and i don't want to
risk anything
yeah no he faces the other way so he's
not gonna notice me
he's not gonna notice me no matter how
close i get i have to do the bump i will
do the bump
and then i'll get my body
as another bomb
i'll be careful
yes
yeah okay that's okay i'll drink another
one just for safety
yes
i killed him
he's there the second time
skeleton is dead
skeleton is in shambles
oh there is one of those
oh it turned off its laser once he was
dead
did i kill their leader
and i can't
oh no i guess it was exploded by my bump
my body bump okay
[Music]
nice thank you
i'm doing way better at this than an
album ring do i go here first is that a
secret
[Music]
okay it's a chest
oh it's a coin the last coin that i
needed for wish but it's hard to see
what the [\h__\h]
i'm just gonna go back i'm just gonna
assume it was a straight path
where my lab for some reason didn't work
explain that to me
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
no problem there's no no problem no
issue
oh
oh mama mia
that blocked another laser once i got
rid of it the laser appeared i can be
lucky that it didn't kill me what the
[\h__\h]
should i just throw a bump in there
because like what the [\h__\h] i'm kind of
stuck
[Music]
don't you
can i
should i roll does that actually work
okay i can try
[Music]
that's so scary
why did it rumble why did my controller
rumble
oh i see
let's see first through this one
and then do this one
okay
i only have one left
okay i don't know how to adopt the first
one that's a miracle honestly
something special
oh it's just money hmm
okay
i'll take it
64. oh you were close to greatness
assassin job
yeah
isn't this like um
what's uh what is the
what where where who does those parties
where you break all kinds of things
some
religional culture where you break
everything for like celebration purpose
no not a pinata i mean like actual like
things that break like like this stuff
not a pinata
it's uh was it a greek thing
oh
[Music]
yes yes yes i think so i think i saw
that before in like movies or so
we're at weddings actually at weddings i
think
i think they made me just break dishes
though
i'm not
oh sure light
oh it's the accent
oh
okay i'm out of here did i clear it
i didn't get anything like big out of it
i feel like
like a like a nice item like the
grappling hook
could have been in order
[Music]
maybe maybe now we get it outside maybe
oh
[Music]
we're at the bottom of this big glowy
thing
[Music]
nice nice nice nice nice
grappling hook
no
it's one of those upgrade things okay
[Music]
but we cleared that thing didn't we
and we and we would leave here
first things first chest
i need to collect my cheese
and take a look oh
i feel like we're so close to activating
the second
pink thing
a second fork
yeah
oh wait i guess it's a german thing too
no [\h__\h] i wanted to read it no wait let
me go back
you can't help but be really aggressive
man
let me read
west garden
uh let me see
like where are we
ah at the very edge of the map
okay
oh
oh is this
is this
[Music]
is this this
nah
that says the ruin no that's something
else again right
oh
[Music]
this is not this
it's so pretty are there no enemies here
maybe maybe it's just peaceful
cherry blossom
[Music]
mmm
oh it's so pretty
okay
wait let me look again
which way do i go
[Music]
but we are at the one hour mark that i
said uh
let me just check out this place and
then we'll end it look at that
work in the figure of a fox
oh oh oh where does this lead
can't open
can't go there okay maybe i should have
gone up the stairs but look at this we
can activate
oh and there's a well now i will find
out the answer if it's connected with
the other wells
it is
we can throw in the third one
[Music]
what kind of wish can i make oh maybe
for hp and like defense or so
or not
i gave me a second slot for armor
oh you mean i could make a wish
so nice oh secret
[Music]
i just have a shop maybe it's another
shop probably
yeah what's up
what do you got oh so much stuff huh
i have 476.
i have a coin this thing that i don't
know what it is or bombs
we already have four hp
flasks but
how much
[Music]
i can't even afford it
i don't know about the other stuff
these are so momentarily you know the
flasks are forever
the coin kind of too i guess how much
999.
[Music]
90. this one's cheap but i don't even
know what it does
shopkeeper looks a bit haunted
only a bit
on
[Music]
i've yet to use the dynamite i'm not
sure where the difference is can you
like activate it
like whenever you want
you like you throw you
maybe you put it somewhere and then you
activate it instead of the bombs which
kind of go off immediately
then i'm like very helpful a hundred
okay
i did use it i guess so
oh my god thank you wait your name
your name looks like the the signs in
this game
how do i read that
[Music]
peace
hey
something like that
those are runes yeah is it what same
oh no is it
[Music]
okay anyway we bought the
dynamite i'm not gonna put it on my slot
because i'm too scared to use it
accidentally
i'm not gonna buy anything else now
i'm fine
thanks dude
okay
remember this place there's a shop here
that apparently sells other stuff than
the other shop
[Music]
there's a monster here what the [\h__\h] is
this
do i fight you
oh i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry was that i feel like i kind
of disturbed nature right now
because this feels like such a peaceful
place maybe i shouldn't have killed it
i'm sorry
i wonder if it would have attacked me if
it saw me first
i think that was evil oh oh i can walk
here
get to the chest
oh yeah baby oh yeah
that's what i'm talking about a golden
chest
money
there's a lot to explore here too huh
what is this those are the free signs
that we saw
dark fox
is on an adventure
it's so cute
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] i thought
there were no enemies here come here
come on kill me
okay don't be scared don't be scared
don't be scared
can i reach it
i can't okay i'm gonna run
i did that thing again i'm not still not
sure how i do it
um i'm gonna run this way
[Music]
i think i need like the grappling hook
or so oh i can't run here
i think i need the grappling hook or
something like that here
[Music]
how long are you gonna follow me
until maybe i enter a room or something
he's still following me
oh my god
i'm out of here [\h__\h] you
hallelujah
they follow you forever
what's going on
hit adam away man
[Music]
okay now we actually go up the stairs
i
went
a different path
hello what is it oh
it's not one of me
like previously we got the sword in
front of one of those maybe now we got
magic
here lies the hero oh no it's a grave oh
we don't get anything
another hero
how many heroes died here oh no is this
like
am i gonna die here too
[Music]
this is my destiny as a fox dying
so the mommy is like looking right at
him with open arms like welcoming him to
afterlife kind of oh man
that's so dark
and so bright at the same time
yep so what am i supposed to do here
maybe nothing right now
imam
did i go here before
nope
nope i didn't
you already died many times yeah
oh a chest
it's the other part of the armor it's a
is that a magic ring no that's just a
ring in general what did it do
what does it do
[Music]
i know
it looks like something there's a shield
and then ah like a ring a shield in the
ring
i guess it's just another kind of
defense
reese's defense when your health is low
it fills the slots
[Music]
in any case it surely helps so let's put
it on
and i think because i'm kind of lost
right now anyway
i guess so
ended here for today this was for four
very productive hours in this game
[Music]
let's do this too
we'll end it here do i have to save in
this game
or is there all the figures
and then we'll read some super chat
you've convinced me to get this game yes
hello good maybe you can get it now and
then try to finish it before my next
stream
i don't think the problem is i don't
think i can play it uh anytime next week
because
like i'll be going to korea and um
i mean i could play like tomorrow maybe
but
i don't know i wanna do some short
stream tomorrow i think relatively short
i don't know i'll think about it i'm not
sure
are you safe i guess there is no saving
[Music]
i did however in order to be able to
stream better while i'm in korea um
i mean like for example the offcorable
that i'll be doing with nabi will
probably be doing at nabi's place but
um i did however so that i can stream
better in my hotel room
by
a second
uh not second but the first i guess um
mobile um mobile monitor i don't know
what's the right way to say it like a
like a like um a monitor to add to my
travel lineup
a portable yeah portable monitor
yeah
that will be
very helpful because streaming with one
monitor when you have so much [\h__\h] going
on on your computer
is tough and this way we could even play
like a little game like sliver or
something way easier
i haven't tested it out yet but i think
it will be fairly easy i should probably
test it out before i go though
yeah
a little monitor that i can connect to
my laptop
[Music]
yeah they use hdmi i don't i didn't read
was mine like something you have to
charge i think you just connected to the
power source but
yeah
yeah i hope that will help with the
setup
is it safe to go to quite the title
screen i hope so
huh
aren't making a little calculator what
do you mean
yeah i would test it beforehand um
okay quit
the all-time safe ones okay
wow that was so much fun i love the game
i was kind of to be honest worried
by
how
much i was warned about how difficult it
is
but i
did not struggle any more with this than
i did with link's awakening maybe i even
struggled more in ling's awakening
like uh combat wise
maybe i was more reckless in link's
awakening
but
i feel like i i feel like i adapted well
and
it was fun
and i found so many secrets so we were
able to upgrade quite a lot too
yeah i'm a good secret finder in this
game apparently
and yeah i love it i love it
i'm excited to play more and i'm glad
that i chose to play it in the first
place
definitely a big recommendation
there's not
too much like
actual story that you can read or that
is being told to you directly
i don't know if that will be changing
later on um
but i don't know this way it's pretty
mysterious
yeah maybe we'll learn later what's
going on though
who knows or it just wants to be this
little mysterious game with a cute fox
that's going on an adventure
do we learn to read later that's a good
question yeah
[Music]
um
yeah
i've i've really enjoyed it i had a
great time playing it it was chill too
and i was able to chit chat with you
guys too so
10 out of 10 so far
graphically
um
[Music]
but maybe i'll put away my weapons
yeah that's for super chat reading i
guess i don't need them
out there i will
i will
oh tank off
wait i think i can do it can i do it
here
did you enjoy it you guys should play it
too
maybe alongside or
after my stream you should play it it's
really good
you don't have to think too much about
it oh
hey it's kind of something i look like
ash
i feel like i look like ash
pokemon trainer
[Laughter]
what's up with my hands man
take down your hands
i look funny
almost annoying
i like this piece of hair
i should give myself some hairstyles
that should give us an option to have a
bald head because i'm pretty sure that
that's possible and then we can put all
kinds of weeks on
i look like a torchic
i'm a pokemon
oh yeah eofy's dreams would come true
that for like with all the hairstyles
that she's done for like whole life
members so far
i feel like she would make
um the most out of it
uh i guess i could keep the head here
the hat it actually works
i like it but maybe i'll take off the
this thing
uh
just go somewhere else
go somewhere else
oh no i'll keep it
okay but whatever
too much effort
okay
everybody
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's so stupid and cute
[Music]
all right all right all right all right
i look funny
to my dad
um
since i just checked out
the png's before
i just went on twitter and document
posted a
fat out of me looking like this
let me check kfp props again oh yeah
because we have this
drink
have you guys seen the curry
the fried chicken curry that they're
selling in the ani plus
shop in korea right now
have you seen
looks yummy
yum
people are standing in line for my curry
right now as we speak
it's already the third or fourth day or
so though
hmm
it's like
curry doesn't the breading get soggy no
not really it's um it's not like the
typical uh like american style
um kind of fried chicken i think that's
uh you know kara again type of chicken
uh i'm looking for
[Music]
the mug
where's the monk there
ah that's the wrong mug
where is the under mug
only saw pictures wish i could see the
real thing
[Music]
i can't find it i want to replace the
the kotori mug
ah it's this one
just for now
yeah
i also really want to eat the limited
edition ame food i'm not going to say
what it is yet i guess she already said
it
the pancakes
i guess i will say it because she
already said it
because i've seen a picture of what it's
supposed to look like too it looks so
yummy the aesthetics are so pleasing
it's like if i were at some restaurant i
would even if it was not ammo related i
would 100 order that
definitely
oh
okay i have my drink out
ready to go
but we need some music
[Music]
i'm gonna bring your own nutella no
no
yeah i think like japan and korea
they're like really good at making food
look really astoundingly pleasing
like really good what are all these
tracks i didn't name
[Music]
okay it's a [\h__\h]
pixel tracks
eight bit tracks
[Music]
well
now that one makes me crazy after a
while
[Music]
remember this i played this once before
i think
[Music]
yeah
[\h__\h] swing
oh [\h__\h] out controller i dropped it
almost
[Music]
okay where do i have to start reading i
wonder
[Music]
another rabbit hole the tunic rabbit
hole i think i'll be having fun with
this game
i'll read that later uh
let me see
did you sing
when i was preparing for this straight
live song i thought i was doing duolingo
german
[Music]
oh
she wants to learn german i don't know
i didn't know she was interested in
german
[Music]
i hope the book did a good job i just
watched a little bit i hope it didn't
teach her any weird things
no bird is not back from vacation which
is why i was also wondering maybe she
asked like ages ago about it about doing
it or maybe she didn't but i don't know
you can see emma in german
i think she's not that far yet
okay i'm going to read the super chats
from the snack box stream i guess
[Music]
no i did
because i read that really
exaggerated fro fro
uh
super chat i remember that
i guess from that spontaneous stream
i guess okay
okay
[Music]
it will probably just be a lot of super
chat saying it's okay chihuahua
[Music]
okay here we are
we move it over here and move this over
here
[Music]
no
now
you have the thumbnail somewhere here
[Music]
ah yeah
so you know what guys like recently um
i've heard from like acquaintances and
friends
uh that a lot of them are getting
into japan
on like short term uh visas for
number one
the world cosplay summit and number two
tokyo game show
and i was like um i actually asked uh
a friend
who
just got her short term visa for tokyo
game show how she did it and all that
and
apparently even i could have gotten one
really easily apparently
but you know i didn't really want to
like risk anything and i only had like
24 hours at that point because there was
a deadline and all that but
apparently it is possible
yeah i know like i see it here and there
i see more and more people going in so i
i did write
that i did relate that to my manager but
um
yeah i just thought it was
bad
i felt a little bit
jealous obviously because we've been
waiting for so [\h__\h] long
and i mean we're always ready
i can i can go anytime and
we've always like you know
working on it
no
trying to get
in
um
[Music]
but it's a process and i don't know why
it's so hard for us but
we want to do it properly i guess
but it gave me also a little bit of hope
seeing how
um a lot of foreigners got into japan
for world cosplay summit um because
they're like performing there or because
there were judges there and so on for
you know it's a
big big event
[Music]
foreign
cause they have like the world i i think
however you know it's like if you get in
for something like that
whatever you do also has to be related
to it so it's not like you have all
kinds of freedoms
to do whatever the hell you want
like um
the tokyo game show one
from what i heard from that um friend
even though she thinks that probably
nobody is gonna really you know check
what you're up to
you're supposed to do business related
stuff you know you're not supposed to go
there for sightseeing and if you do side
seeing
and they catch you
then you're gonna get
problems
um
but yeah you can stay there for a while
you don't even have to have a booth at
tokyo game show but the deadline now is
over anyway
yeah
yeah but yeah
you just need to
have
you need to you just need to in the
application write down
a company
in japan
could even be a one-man company of a
friend you don't even have to work for
them
just write that down as in that person
that company in japan needs you to to be
there
and then
that's it
that's all we needed
you don't have to write down any
specific kind of
i don't know conferences or meetings or
whatever
it was it apparently was really easy
[Music]
to
[Laughter]
but it has to be kind of tokyo game show
related you know like the whole purpose
of you coming
so
it was it's not like i could take that
and do all my you know streaming things
so but just saying you know the fact
that they do that for world cosplay
summit and for tokyo game show
makes me wonder
it makes me wonder
[Music]
yeah
as as much as i love poker game show and
would love to be there
because i miss it
uh i i'm just gonna wait and wait and
wait until we can get in there
for whole life related things
[Music]
djs would like to always good e3
really
like i don't really go there for game
announcements but
the one time i
one time only but one time or even two
times or two times maybe i
uh
had the pleasure
of getting into tokyo game show with a
what do you call it
exhibitor
pass
because i
was helping out at an indie game booth
not gonna say which one but yeah that
was fun
and also kind of exhausting because i
was standing the whole day and my back
was killing me
standing on those tiny boobs trying to
get people to play the game and [\h__\h]
it was [\h__\h] exhausting i did like i
don't know eight hours or so
[Music]
but then i did that for like two days
and because they were like um there were
business days and then there's public
days i think i did it for the business
days and then in exchange for doing that
i could still use my exhibitors pass to
enter early without going through the
lines in lines with people
on the on the public days and that's
basically why i did it because i didn't
want to stand in line and i just wanted
to enter backstage and and use the
backstage changing room instead of the
the public changing room where you have
to stand in line again it's
i i saved myself
hours and hours
of standing in line in the hot hot humid
summer
of japan
so
i think it was worth it
merry smartshow i did that one year and
i really really thought it was so worth
it that i did it in the like was it the
following year i'm not sure but i did it
in another year then as well
just because i on the public days i
wanted that pass
didn't want the normal visit to pass not
good enough for me anymore and now that
i've i've tasted this luxury ones
i don't think i can go back to normal
anymore
i need
those passes i need the exhibitive
passes so if i ever go to pgs again
i hope especially with the contacts that
i have now
now i should know a couple of gaming
companies that will give me an exhibitor
pass right
please
let me
i will actually not work for you this
time but please let me and please give
me one of your passes
and now i don't want to work for them
like at their
booths but i just want to have the pass
please that's
[Music]
i mean they gave me a piece fine so
i think they'll give me a pass
[Music]
time
no i already have my wish you know the
cat toilets um
by the way they're working on it i
hopefully will be getting it sometime in
the next couple months
i don't want to do my cat's toilet
anymore give me that toilet
give me that magical toilet but the
thing is still
i don't even know if my cats are going
to use it could be very much that they
reject using it
i really want to see your cat in mecca
yeah
get into the [\h__\h] robot junkers
please i have a bad feeling about
chunkers i don't think she wants to use
it so we'll see we'll see i'll force her
she has to
realize
[Music]
okay
there you have a little tangent
now let's read super chat
[Music]
yeah i'll keep it
and then if she doesn't use it i guess
i'll keep it forever
maybe one of them uses it
yeah
okay okay i'm still scrolling there we
go
and looking for the top-down kitchen
what
i missed rooting for you oh wait okay
part of the super chats are
mario kart related because i just
recycled the stream
because i i was
i don't know
i i was scared that if i delete the
stream
i will lose um the
text messages from the super chats
and it will be a pain to find them again
and
it's just easier so i just recycled it
so some of these are mario kart related
i'm looking for the top thank you soon
master in thank you james jackson thank
you thank you i'm not wearing this
already
it's over okay it was only two mario
kart related super chips
apparently
uh
[Music]
reminds me of the neighbor thing
i can update you i wanted to update you
guys
nothing special but i did go
to um buy some
some simple yummy
chocolate
uh
like that said thank you soon thank you
on top of it
um
and put it in front of her door i didn't
want to ring it because i didn't want to
be confronted
like that i just put it in front of the
door and was hoping
that at some point she would see it
i kept on
looking through my picky
poke hole
of my door seeing if it's still there in
the hallway
eventually it disappeared
so she did get it
and then later on when i was like
leaving my apartment i noticed a post-it
on my door that said thank you soon as
well
so we are currently in an endless
dunkish loop no no no i think it ended
there
but yeah i said donkey shin
and then i got a duncan posted
yeah
very taping
yeah i made an acquaintance yeah that's
nice it's nice to
have someone i guess if i need some milk
or salt or pepper
or
mental support when my kitchen is on
fire
yeah so
i have thanked
her properly
[Music]
with some yummy chocolates
for the pokeball
[Music]
yeah all good all good
blue ducky and stable bread thank you
and mrs thank you
it was super stressful
your video
made me laugh
silly being speed speeds down
as long as you and the cats are okay
almost okay
my brother once started the fire by
microwaving easy mac without water easy
mac is that like instant mac and cheese
oh
silent fire
in the microwave
that sounds
dangerous and scary
in my pro tip don't microwave dry pasta
yeah i wasn't planning on it but good to
know
i've blown out the microwave microwaves
are very good at starting really thank
god that never happened to me
[Music]
my dad wants microwave a steel pot and
the plastic handles melted and caught
fire
huh
how hot was your macaroon i once
microwaved the potato for so long it
became charcoal why would you do that
and let's open what the [\h__\h]
you guys are worse than me
[Laughter]
[Music]
i
feel better now
i wanted a baked potato well now i want
one too i feel you but what
oh man beginners
this is why i am the tencho and you guys
are the chickens
my co-workers started a fire at the
client's house he left his jacket on top
of the stove
and accidentally turned it on while
replacing some of the lights in the
cabinets oh my god
well r.i.p jacket
you know what i might play tunic
tomorrow because i i enjoyed it so
[\h__\h] much i want to play more do you
guys know
can you like estimate how far i got
in percentage
i wonder if i could finish it tomorrow
if i go a little bit longer
want one or two hours longer
maybe not
a quarter
i felt like i got pretty far
one
one four
i guess okay four hours
[Music]
eight twelve sixteen that makes sense
in terms of how long the game is
supposed to be i guess that makes sense
but i can definitely do longer than four
hours next time
so maybe two more parts we could do like
six hours or seven tomorrow
get really deep into it
yeah i did eat a lot
and i i stood in one spot telling
crunchyroll stories for a
while speedrun is 24 minutes is there
like bugs that you can exploit for that
or what
not that i want to do it but how is that
even possible
your secret
[Music]
bugged speed run wow okay then i don't
have any respect for that because as i
said before to me a speed run
only really makes sense if you're
actually like
not bugging for the whole game i mean
like all those super mario 64 speedruns
they're impressive because you know they
do all these backwards jumps and they're
so
exactly positioned that's okay that's
like holy [\h__\h]
it takes so much practice
but i'm i don't know i'm more impressed
by speedruns that
actually
make you play the game
instead of i don't know glitching
through
the floors and walls of games
generally talking more about other game
speed runs than mario 64 though because
those backwards jumps
i really must say holy macaroni
holy macaroni in the microwave explosion
roni
oh my god
[Music]
backwards
yeah
impressive man
portal speed run
whoa
[Music]
insane how they pull that off yeah
i could never do that
mario games are
the end of me
like it's like
how do i how do i explain this my
relationship with mario games is like
i want to be the person that's good at
them
and i do like them
in i like the
the thought
of mario games the vision
and the thought of me playing them
but then when i play them
i suck so much at them but i don't want
to
i don't want to dislike them
i don't want to hate them
i want to be good at them i know i will
never be good at them
but
i like the
i like the thought of me in another
dimension being good at them
mario galaxy
i've heard now several times that's
easier
well maybe
if you kept going you'd be good
oh hey did i just say i like them i
don't want to hate them
oh yeah maybe we'll give mario galaxy a
try sometime
okay
give it another chance um
german channel content oh i'm actually
like waiting on um
some
um
streaming layouts
i've commissioned
something and it's
i didn't give like a super harsh
deadline i guess so
it's it's taking some time and also for
holo talk
and
i'm working on a renovation
that's also taking some time
uh
yeah sorry guys it's taking a bit more
time than
expected sorry sorry
but i also found somebody who can clip
for me um not only clip but also
translate
uh from english to gym and i found
someone who would be willing to do it
like on a regular basis
so then i will have clip content for my
german channel as well
i'm preparing things behind the scenes
but it takes a while
[Music]
but i have to say the whole talk
studio
wow
i'm so excited for it because
let's be spoiled let me let me let you
in a little bit on something we are
renovating it but we're building it you
know how the current studio is
rendered 3d
but
i i only have you know this 2d version
of it now what we're doing next is
we're making it so that i can actually
also use it in 3d if i wanted to
if i ever
you know want to use it in vr or so for
example
yeah which will not be the norm though
because it's just easier for me to
control everything and translate
maybe maybe what i could do is that if i
do you know japanese members i have to
translate so
it's easier for me to do it not in vr
but if i do an interview with
someday as i planned like en members or
id members
maybe i can do those
in 3d
well
i'm not quite sure i just wanted the
option you know to have
the possibility
so
that's being worked on right now
[Music]
yeah intervention
it's a special episodes will be done in
3d maybe
[Music]
ah
let me see i actually wanted to check
something like that um
[Music]
i did let me check
can i
can i quickly check somebody asked about
gothic
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
okay
a while ago actually
like a month ago i requested gothic but
i haven't heard anything back so now i'm
gonna try to
poke poke pockety poke
i'm trying guys i'm trying if i get
permission we'll play it in german
on my german channel
yes the way it's supposed to be
[Music]
today i feel so chill man
yeah i'm gonna do the original yeah
cause you guys were like oh original
play the original
okay
[Music]
no
you can't it's not about piranha but
it's because they're the developer we
need to ask the publisher
it's not about the developer even when a
developer says yeah go ahead do what you
want it's about the publisher
and even a statement from them on
twitter like play it
does not help
it needs to be on the record
written
directly to
um
cover so
yeah it's not that easy
i want to see gothic
i know you do
actually
oh [\h__\h]
ah
sure bro go ahead yeah it doesn't work
like that
anyway uh slippers beat sanchez onions
[Music]
phoenix too hot for real though glad
you're okay don't let it distillate you
from cooking all the best chefs have a
few flare-ups from time to time
yeah just like gordon
i was watching all those videos and
holy [\h__\h] why did he put the
why did he put it into the sink did he
think there was no water in it maybe
because otherwise i can't explain it to
myself
or or did he think there was water and
that's why he did it
did he forget how can he forget
for dramatic effect for entertainment
[Music]
i didn't find the original video though
so i i didn't see any
any of his reaction because it literally
ends when he puts it into the sink
and it catches fire
it it literally ends there but i want to
see his reaction i want to see his
explanation he had a smile on his face
really afterwards though
not spread extra damage
but like he would know how to deal with
it just put a [\h__\h] lid or one of
those i don't know other blankets on it
there were so many options
like he didn't need to do that
it makes no sense for his character to
be honest
hmm
anyway
for the lulls i don't know
and then there were all these other
videos
other clips where just generally
kitchens
uh kitchen stoves would be on fire
because someone spilled a [\h__\h] ton of
oil on it or so and then gordon would be
like
don't you dare post water on it or don't
you don't dumb just let it go let it go
he was always screaming just let it go
for [\h__\h] sake he was so mad all the
time
just let it go you donkey
yeah it's um i guess that's you know if
i had gordon with me
in that moment and he told me to let it
go
then i would have also just let go but
in that moment i was like i need to do
something i need to do something
i did not realize that i i can just let
it go let it go
but i mean also the fire alarm was
already on the whole time
[Music]
and i i i felt like just letting it go
there
was not the option i need to i need to
stop it
oh well
because i found in my line of gold the
fire's friends
i i i didn't think it would just be
contained in the frying pan but now we
know now we know
yeah if i um blow on it in front of
gordon
he would be like that [\h__\h] won't work
and then i would blow it out and he will
be like shook
shook it
i can detention for weeks
i'm excited
[Music]
thank you so much for voting for me and
bounce to be
guests at popcorn
exciting
[Music]
i was
i was so
like surprised when i first got the
message
hey kiwala
popcorn wants you to be there again
i was like what it actually happened
are you for real
it's actually happening i was waiting
for this but i did not think it would
happen because i thought it was too late
because
it's at the end of august
and i just recently got the notice about
it
it kind of happened very last minute too
but i am blessed that that happened
surprised and blessed
wow what a nice surprise democracy
yeah
power of kf koreans yeah they're strong
freaking strong man thank you very much
um
yeah but normally it's not that last
minute no
just just crunchy bowl and popcorn
like several things were kind of last
minute
yeah but it worked out well crunchyroll
worked out well it was worth it
uh
a lot of last minute recordings but it
was worth it
it was freaking worth it
it was basically hololive convention
holocorn
uh north america
holofesa
it just needed one big concert that's it
that's all we needed holo expo oh i've
expo
in n a
[Music]
who knows maybe that's what we'll do
next year
[Music]
maybe we will do our own whole life expo
in america
maybe we will
i hope you guys will come
let's go
fun
seriously glad that nothing too bad
happened i remember the last time i had
a fire related accident in the kitchen
my eyebrows took weeks to grow back so
don't beat yourself up too hard well
thankfully i didn't lose any hairs i i
blew at it but at a safe distance i
guess
yeah just close enough to blow it but
far enough to not have my eyebrows
burned up
thank you
yeah it is hard to think clear
enders
thank you this is a name
section
thank you
[Music]
i believe i speak for okay when i say
we're also happy that you're safe and
that you're comfortable coming to talk
to us about your problems we're so
grateful to have you in our life
thank you
yeah i just needed to talk about it let
it all out so
yeah thank you guys for listening it did
help a lot so
i felt better after that
i'm sure that's what caused are you not
are you sure that's not what caused your
spite here yeah no i'm sure
looks like there's a flame on my head
yeah
kind of nikki thank you
[Music]
very
thank you guys that's it
nice stuff
you're genuinely huh you want that hair
don't ya that's fluffy hair i know i
know i know you do
[Music]
i'm rocking it
kono kamigawa yamashinda
[Music]
okay next up we have my genius stream
hollow
back i'm i'm so happy with this stream
everything about it
i'm also so glad you guys enjoyed it so
much
[Music]
yeah not too soon but at some point
we'll do a part two
not too soon because i want it to be
special still
[Music]
at some point we'll do a part two
yeah
hello fridges maybe
i don't want to do anything that's too
intrusive you know like obviously
we're not gonna do a like uh
i don't know
show your whole kitchen stream
myself um
because of safety reasons and all that
yeah
um but i think a fridge should be okay
to show
i thought you know the bags
like if they don't want to show their
bags it's totally fine but they can show
me the contents
but or they can put a bag up that they
don't normally use or something like
that but generally i think the whole
bags idea works well
because it also gives you
like a feeling of
um personality and also shows your
slides that you may have not known about
that member before so i think it's
genius
absolutely genius for no idea
[Music]
stop talking about the credit card
numbers
you're not getting our credit card
numbers because i don't even have a
credit card but anyway
hello baxter sprint thank you i agree i
agree
[Music]
thank you for the pinkie give our today
marks a year since the best msu video
premiered what
and with international owl awareness day
aka my birthday
oh that's why she chose
[Laughter]
wait no wait is the abs i wait are you
just joking is it actually
international owl awareness day
wait does such a day exist actually
and maybe maybe you're just [\h__\h] with
me
[Music]
it's true okay okay okay i thought you
were just you know
maybe that was just your way of saying
mummy birthday
okay now that makes a lot of sense
as much sense as how my my birthday is
on the national fried chicken day mm-hmm
why do we need to be aware of owls i'm
already aware about
but okay i am gladly more aware of
vowels
cute
you dropped an impeccable sequel
i've lived with the shame of missing
part one's premiere and that still
hounds me to this day oh
yeah
doesn't matter
it still hurts thinking about it but
parts two's owl winnie
what reminds me of a tiny owl
what
it was so cute
it washed away my pain you were just too
sweet i'm cute
wait what
what is he talking about
you just want to cute wow i love you and
have fun taking a peek into all those
hollow bags thank you
i love you too
what do you mean though the cry you made
the moment video okay okay okay
ah i thought you meant like my second m2
video and i was like did i do an owl
before
it sounded like a different owl
reminds me of a tony
[Music]
i looked up you know
i'll noises on youtube and try to
recreate them but i could definitely use
some practice
i did do ml before
i forgot did i really
maybe i did
keanu mo
oh my god i did
[Music]
i sound
like a pigeon
i'm out
you're not now you're a pigeon honestly
my impression for mummy sounded better i
would say
what do you think trevor
i think i improved actually
i could still make it better i could
still improve but
but
it's a year ago
it is exactly one year ago
oh that was definitely a pigeon
that's a screech owl
huh
yeah
could very much be that i took a screech
owl as a sample for this one and then i
took a different owl
for
mumma's impression
yeah they make a lot of different noises
huh
i guess so
i forgot huh i even used the same image
even though there were so many other
images on on that website that has all
these images that i could have used and
i'm like oh i think i'll go with this
one
why did i not go for a different one at
least
my
my my my lower
my lower consciousness
con
my uh what do you call it
yeah
no i didn't mean to do that my
subconscious yes
my subconscious chose the same picture
one year later
[Laughter]
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
okay
thank you for
watching me remember this trevor g
here's a case for you
[Music]
i appreciate it
glad you liked my owl noises
and thank you for coming to crunchyroll
expo
hope you enjoyed it hope you had a great
time
maybe this time you socialized a bit
more than the last time did you i wonder
is that dokomi i know you were shy
did you did you talk to some kf people
no you didn't oh man
shy owl oh
oh man
oh it's so sad
owl in the shadows shadow
you should change your name from
clientele to shadow
[Music]
so cool that's so
it's so edgy yeah
[Music]
he just wants to talk oh can we just
talk
can we just talk talk about where we're
going before we grow
[Music]
like this up
i apologize i
apologize if i'm going too far
and we just song
now we just
[Music]
oh yeah done clones are scary
you know i saw a lot of like fun looking
clips though like i saw
the takodachis building towers
running around carrying those huge
bean bags in the air bringing them to
the taco duchy totem tower and building
it making it higher
i am surprised so many of them brought
those big ass beanbags to the convention
what the hell
but they had fun it was cute
very cute
anyway
thank you
[Music]
4.5 million
apparently
the other day recently
nice little thank you very much for
listening listen to people night 2
though please
youtube algorithm
hates fever9
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you algorithm
open on my tongue
thank you for the red super chat
thank you thank you what's in your bag
huh
and why is it a kiwawa kitchen
[Music]
it is pinned to the top of the channel
but when you're subscribed as far as i
know
once you watched the pinned video once
it does not show it to you anymore
when you come back to the channel i
think
and uh
as a non-subscribed person you still
should be seeing it every time i think
so it is pinned you just don't see it
because you already saw
it favor night isn't my music playlist
but
it's um on first look it only shows like
oldest to to newest so i was thinking of
making a new playlist where
i add them in the order of newest to
oldest
i guess
but it's not gonna
create any miracles
and suddenly give it five million views
so
i don't know
it's okay
it's all right
thank you
[Music]
yeah i should be able to read that
okay
[Music]
oh
yeah people night had um i think more
remixes than sparks actually i don't
even understand why fifa night is
getting so many remixes but it makes me
happy
because they're all pretty good too
[Music]
instrumental easy to find
maybe that's it yeah maybe
[Music]
i'm not sure about spikes
i don't remember
some guy called blake thank you
thank you
get yourself a fire extinguisher on me
or a new bag or a fire extinguisher for
your bag
is there such a tiny tiny tiny tiny by
extinguisher like a
travel fire extinguisher
i would have never seen one of those
before
thank you thank you very much
i might actually get myself one of those
blankets yeah
i don't think that it will happen again
anytime soon probably not even in the
next five years judging by my records so
far that it was the first time now
but
good to have it i guess when you need it
yeah
no
and then i just need to remember where i
put it in case it happens again
and have it somewhere easily accessible
yeah
yeah yeah thank you chunk rain thank you
for the super attraction thank you
nervous thank you soon thank you
come sanita for the pink super chat
thank you so i'm back looter i'm not a
bag looter i'm just a bad inspector if
anything
you know
who actually sent me
oh bad
no okay i won't say i won't spoil it
because i might show it next time but
somebody sent me somebody very special
sent me a photo of their bad contents
after the stream
and maybe i will keep that until
the next
time we do it
[Music]
but i thought it was so cute
that this person participated
wanted to participate
well you'll see it'll take a while until
i do it again though
that was a fantastic idea genius
yes yes i know thank you
for telling me the obvious
learning so much about the hollomans and
loving all the cat accessories
yes me too
i guess i should have had more
accessories too huh hmm
surprising huh
don't worry all the cat hair on my
clothes at any given time
are the accessory
of my cats so
you just don't see it on the photo or on
the back but i have it on my clothes at
all times
accessorized
yeah
[Music]
i don't know what you're talking about
shocking i showed every single picture
that i received
at that point of time of the stream i
showed it on on stream it's not like i
like kept anything from you guys
whatever came in just came in afterwards
although like mata my senpai for example
messaged me afterwards like oh sorry i
didn't make it in time can i
like do it next time i was like hell
yeah
tell me about the mistake
[Music]
yeah next time i'm gonna ask a lot more
people i think like next time we might
have um uh way more japanese member bags
because
i already
like this time i only asked like a very
few of them
but next time i will ask so many more of
them yeah
yeah
uh thank you spaghetti
[Music]
what
what is that super chat about
[Music]
the gamer great thank you soon
hey
back to you
how are you doing
one i stand for the earlier one
ah
so many weddings man
nice i've never been at a wedding before
so fast
[Music]
i've read all those already
pink super chat this is so sweet
uh i mean a certain pee bag
pummel bag
i blessed a lot of people with that
apparently phoenix very shiny hunter
thank you soon
thank you
thank
[Music]
uh
japanese bros like fans of the other
girls like energy fans because she
advertised the stream beforehand
uh who were like tweeting about it on
twitter the whole time and they were so
happy to see nana's back but they also
immediately knew that it was hers before
i revealed anything
damn
them and fu cookies as well immediately
like they know their oshes very well
and they were very happy to see the
the
um
bags of their ashes i'm glad to make all
these fans very happy
give them a little insight
into
[Music]
okay
i'm
actually
thinking of ending it here
let me check something
oh no i could go longer
[Music]
i'm thinking about dinner
i might be able to go a bit longer let
me see
[Music]
oh
let me see opening times
okay i think i can still go
[Music]
i will read the tunic superchatters
no no i'm still going i'm still going
yeah i shouldn't be too many
yeah
cute face cute face of chihuahua
oh
all right my hair looks so funny
my hair looks so funny
oh my god
thank you
hey any anime recommendation that is a
really weird thing to ask but you're
welcome to check out my top 10 animes
uh the crunchyroll website
i gave them my top 10 anime
recommendations so just look at that
also i've been called based by a lot of
people
about that
on twitter
and but a lot of people said based
except for the zeon tsukayama um
mention and i'm like what why
i think dinner not sugar is based too
that is not necessarily the type of
anime that i would enjoy the most now
but to me back then i was into that kind
of animes too and it just has a big
nostalgia factor to me
and it's so fun and cute and the music
is great
yeah
it's cute
okay
and to me i mean it just as i said has
this huge
nostalgia
factor i was thinking of putting in
uh
a different
anime at that slot but
yeah i ended up going for that one i was
also i don't know considering um
and i was trying to remember at that
point i had troubles remembering what i
even watched even though i surely
watched a million more animes
i had troubles remembering
yeah
i like that anime
the opening opening or ending song was
good too
[Music]
something like that
i love that one so much
[Music]
but yeah
working so good yes
working is so fun
so much fun
i was also thinking of lucky star
i don't know i like i like nichijouke
anime
nichijou every day size of life animes i
love them
[Music]
lucky side in the angel really i need to
re-watch it
i haven't seen it in a million years
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay sorry
couldn't stop myself i'd never watch
demon player no
sermon in service
i mean uh wasn't that
boku sss
the actual title i watched it but now it
would be too cringe for me oh i was also
thinking of putting in yule yuri instead
uh of uh video not skyma it was a tough
choice i almost put yuri yuri in there
would i have still been been called um
based except for that one or would you
uni have been acceptable huh
it was a hard choice
it was a hard choice okay but i love you
yuri
[Music]
okay that would have been based really
goddammit i was close to close to
perfection apparently according to you
guys
why
why was you that you knew okay and they
don't know i know
i love kyogre i love
hyoko kyoko was my favorite character
she's such a
baka such an idiot
such dork
love sashi no kyoko
[Music]
is
yeah railgun
[\h__\h] amazing anime
[Music]
one of the pro totes
prototypes
i was also thinking of
putting in rate zero but i wasn't sure
if i was in being influenced by the fact
that it's just a really popular anime
or if i actually really genuinely
enjoyed it
i do think i genuinely enjoyed it until
a certain
point
i don't however remember if i even
finished the last season i remember
starting to watch it on leicester unless
there has been a new
last season since then uh but you know
this the season that starts with this
like icy
place i see cold
and i don't remember if i finished it
i think maybe read zero had the
for me from my point of view the same
issue that sort of online had
then
it maybe got drunk on its popularity and
then went into
paths that i did not enjoy
like start out online i can tell you i
like the first season
but
kitty kitty's second season okay
but then after that it's just
no i need no more of this
and i think i i barely remember my
feelings towards it or my criticism
but i
i don't know i just thought it was
starting to get cringe
don't let akula simply hear this yeah
[Laughter]
i know
bleach for me drop the dang thing
yeah i think green zero is better though
that sort for me
better than sword at online also better
at keeping its quality over time
[Music]
you know what i i don't think it's not
it's not so much the you know being
influenced by popularity i think it was
genuinely
a good
anime
yes
love the character designs
so much
[Music]
i was also thinking about uh what was it
um
jellyfish princess
for example
and i don't know
i thought of a couple ones but it was
it's hard to put them together into a
list because it's easy to choose your
top three or a top five but choosing a
top ten
is tough because at a certain point
they're all
you know about the same kind of
mediocre goodness
i enjoyed so many
around the same level
but i did put in i think mama do penguin
drum because that one was insanely good
[Music]
we need to talk more about anime if only
i
watched more animated past years
i should get back into it there is this
one anime that my um friends
two of my friends they just [\h__\h] love
it so much and they are pushing it on to
me so much
what was it called again the one with
the blonde girl
um that's like kind of poppy and cute
and then there's this dude it's kind of
like a dj thing and um
i don't know
it's the most one of the most recent
ones
no not my dress-up darling
uh
potty pee dummy
apparently that one is insanely good and
i need to watch it i think i would
probably enjoy it
i should watch it
foreign
[Music]
yeah so um by it's not on the normal
disney yet isn't it
no it's just japanese's name and
man
maybe
whenever i get to japan we can do a like
a speed run watch along for all the
episodes
then i can reach disney plus in japan
you guys will have to do whatever you
need to do to get to the episodes
you do what you need to do
how many times i have to say my [\h__\h]
vpn doesn't work on it
anyway continuing
where was i
[Music]
did i
what i didn't even start reading that's
the thing
thank you for the red super chat
i haven't seen you in a while where were
you
you didn't forget about quinoa right
you didn't forget about me right you
were watching still right
function for the red super chat
[Music]
for the pink super chat
what does it say
let's go
let's go let's go
korean writing yeah let's go
thank you
hope you liked the game today
i think it is so charming and fun
it's really fun to explore because
there's like so many secrets scattered
everywhere it's really motivating me to
look into every corner
i like it so much
could end up being one of my favorite
games especially considering like
how good the quality is even though one
person made it like you don't even
notice it
like you would never think
one person made the game
[Music]
crazy
it's an elderly that's more your style
exactly
yeah
first like night thank you in the game
thank you for the pinky does the tension
fry the chicken because she's a fox
hmm
[Music]
i wonder also i just noticed i still
have my
tail
even though
i have i don't have my ears on anymore
oh well
nothing weird about this right all
normal
so um
no i am a phoenix about it i'm pretty
sure about that
i'm pretty sure
i think
don't cast like me
fancy thank you
for thank you soon
no that's a that's a wolf
wait there's a fox also sometimes i will
otherwise
there's some that's some noises that the
fox makes i think
that's what the fox says
[Laughter]
[Music]
the year the eureka you get from this
game is just off the charts and this
discovery is three fourths of the
experience
yeah i agree
looking for
[Music]
well since when did fookie have a cute
orange little sister
also thank you for the amazing panel and
fun recordings you did for crx i had a
blast cheering for you during your
sparks performance and things so much
kiwawa tv
love you and take care
thank you so much i'm glad you enjoyed
it even though you didn't make it into
the meet and greet which is unfortunate
but you still have a chance you know for
like the the birthday
yeah actually you're running out of time
so but i'm sure you signed up for it but
just telling everybody who did want to
participate in a meet and greet or buy
my merchandise for the from my birthday
merchandise
the clock is ticking i think there's um
maybe about uh
12 hours or so left maybe
yeah
so if you want that go go go go go go
but i'm sure most of you who wanted it
already got it for all of you who wanted
it probably already got it yeah
so
anyway
thank you chris hopefully the next meet
and greet you made it in
i believe i believe
i hope
yeah and thank you for cheering for me
and supporting me
at crunchyroll i hope you had a great
time hope you had a blast
yeah
on to a next time i'm glad that it was
apparently close
to where you live so
that made it easy for you to get there
how was the food by the way what's your
rating on the kfp food
10 out of 10.
i heard the sliders were amazing
and they gave you two not just one nice
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
i like the fries oh i'm hungry right now
oh thank you and thank you my kitchen
kitchen
thank you for the red super chat
i love our whole life but i only have
one hottie i tried to praise and
encourage you always but i do have some
criticism
you are too hard on yourself please
remember that everyone makes mistakes
even you i'm glad you're okay and two
viva la chiara has to focus you can't be
forever
thank
you referencing to
the kitchen incident or to something
else
[Music]
yeah mom i mean i was you know
i felt stupid
but i'm okay now
it's all right you know it was just the
initial reaction i guess but
i'm okay
because you guys also made me feel
better
you know why i felt especially stupid
because i thought you guys would be
telling me i'm stupid for that because
you guys often tell me oh my god you're
so stupid when i do some when i don't
get something in games or so
[Music]
when i didn't know about bismarck or
what was not what it wasn't even was it
disliked
oh my god how the [\h__\h] do you not notice
so stupid
you definitely have moments where you're
thinking lava is stupid
that's different that's not different
amazing thing that you guys always think
i'm stupid
even though i'm not
i think he's so smart
so then when the fire happens i'm like
okay if he's gonna think i'm stupid
again
just teasing yeah i hope so
i hope so
i call you smart show a lot
thank you
[Music]
well you you would have called me stupid
if i would have put water on it wouldn't
you
don't take it seriously i'm not sure no
you sound serious about it sometimes you
guys
[Music]
yes
well yeah
well thank god i didn't do that
yeah thank god my kitchen would have
been on fire if i would have done that
probably
i would have probably dropped the frying
pan in shock
and then it would have spread
oh thank you thank you thank you for the
sweet ones
please somebody
somebody who believes in me
thank you
i am
kind of work you know at least the work
keeps your mind off of sad things
that was the same for me
every now and then thanks for the thank
you for the pinky
attention the meet and greet felt like a
fever dream
your presence boiled my chicken brain
making me forget what i was going to say
any interesting interaction you had at
the meet and greet that you can tell us
oh yeah as i as i said already
i thought the
the ahmed gosling moment was fun
and and also
it was a
surprisingly big amount of girls
showing up at the meet and greet
like i was so surprised
it felt like 50 50
even
so many girls
so many cutie patooties
yeah
i was
shocked
[Music]
women love you
okay
jeffy has a lot of women well you say
that but it's it's still not a 50 50 or
anything but at the meeting great it was
just like unusually
balanced you know what i mean
so it had quite a quite the variety
at my meet and greet
jimmy frank penguin thank you for the
pinky tomorrow's my birthday and can you
notify other employees i'm not that
miserable chicken jimmy i'm a majestic
penguin yeah i told them well somebody
else so much people make fun of me and
by jimmy mim i'm sorry by the way i'm
serving in the military so i can't
catch your stream so i miss you oh
i miss you too
don't worry i'm gonna i'm gonna repair
your reputation i'm gonna make it right
this is not the jimmy that has been
eaten
okay i mean you see him here writing a
superchat he couldn't do that if he was
taken apart by thousands of people
congoers
yes
final
please fight them and watch my votes
every now and then to cheer up
thank you soon for your support lunchbox
thank you ultra noob
thank you for the pinky
it feels good to see keanu and kfb
developing and growing day by day
yeah
it does i hope we can grow bigger and
bigger and bigger
[Music]
yeah
and i want to improve
better and better and better
um
thank you let's get em
thank you for the pinky hey i'm going on
vacation with my family to europe for
two weeks so it might be mia any tips on
how to show up to all the
european hens for self-validation
purposes only all my time is already
dedicated to kfp
you're going to europe for two weeks are
you staying in one country or are you
traveling around
i hope you're gonna have lots of fun
show off the european hens
i think i think you don't have to show
up you're automatically charming and
what's the right word
dashing dashing that's the word i look
for
yes you don't need to do anything just
you showing up there everybody's gonna
fall over you like oh look at him
beautiful
male chicken
so get those get those hands go get them
go get them
oh there was that word oh i thought of
the other one couldn't think of rooster
you got this yeah
yeah i hope you enjoy it tell me about
your trip when you're there
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat pretty
fire stream guy
hi
guy
i mean you're you're complimenting my
last stream so i'll take that
i'm a bit confused but you've got the
spirit question mark
thank you very much mwah hope you
enjoyed it i might continue tomorrow
i might continue tomorrow yeah
i want to
hmm
if you guys don't mind that is
thanks for the flush chats
yeah i'm having a good time
nice stream dude
thanks dude
oh thanks girl
[Music]
cool stream bro
thanks
thanks peach
[Music]
i honestly don't really have the energy
for this anymore
what is quickly super chats i like them
but i don't have the energy for it right
now
i'll read it but i might not bless you
with much of an interaction
i found that i found a secret in kfc
that fired chicken boss will not be
happy i found that this secret has so
much power it might grant me forgiveness
from mama inna but i couldn't
unintentionally change kfp
must choose my next step carefully
change how
change
oh you know what i'm interested try me
try us
it's not just me
it's all of us that you're going up
against good luck
[Music]
maxwell the first ancient
uh what same
probably
uh
yeah i think actually yeah the amount of
letters makes sense too i think
thank you for the rest of the chat
i came to lead i was really in a hurry
to drive fast with leading a fire truck
in an ambulance a little ago what
after all work resting with watching you
is calming me down this
agent though
this this asian thought i wish i could
love you forever
but
leading a fire truck and ambulance like
for real why are you like
making something up
but don't take him to a normal room
chicken boss don't take him to a normal
room
lance in room of truth now the normal
oh i guess usual room is kind of i i can
see how a language translator would
translate it to usual usual to normal i
guess i guess i can see that yeah
it's just a normal room
oh what is this room that you're
bringing me to
oh oh just just a normal room
sounds less threatening than the usual
room
which is a good disguise i guess
it's just just a normal room man
just a normal room that normal room
thank you about sam i think i think i
think if i'm wrong i'm sorry but you're
confusing me it's your fault thank you
should be what same
month
go for it spanking hand thank you soon
for the red super chat thanks for
sending me down yet another rabbit hole
i think i'll be having fun with this
game for a while assuming the cartoons
don't need me to hold them
maybe maybe they'll be
staring at the screen when you play it
looking at that cute box and they will
be asking you
why can that fox stand on two legs and
we can't huh
they'll be jealous they might be jealous
understandable they deserve and they can
only if you like
only momentarily you know yeah not
really
[Music]
i woke up bit earlier than i wanted
today because smoothie was in my face
saying meow
meow meow meow meow meow
and then and then we just cuddled for
two hours and then i just focused on
cuddling instead of sleeping again
she's so cute she's so soft oh
yeah she wakes me up with the meow meows
right in my face
this is so cute
it's so cute quality time yeah and
quality time with this movie
the chokers recently
i have a problem
i recently replaced
shonker's sleeping box you know she had
a cardboard box that she liked to sleep
in on my bed
that was perfectly her size but it was
falling apart and i i bought um some
shoes that came with a perfectly nice
new fresh box
that was only like maybe two centimeters
or so bigger than the old box so it was
still the perfect size because it always
looked like chunkers had
you know a trouble with the old box
because she was over spilling
and i gave her the new box but
she tested it but she didn't seem to
like it
she didn't really use it
and now
she sleeps at the height
like the hmm
the position around you know
around where my head is
but on the floor
right next to the bed
on the floor under my night table
[Music]
under my bedside table thingy
she sleeps exactly under it
right next to the bed like she's
yeah touching the bed
she's there the whole night and i keep
on trying to pick her up put her on the
bed make her sleep on the bed
maybe especially also because of the
heat wave because it was [\h__\h] hot
but yeah recently she
she's just sleeping right there
she didn't like the
new box i thought you know she would
accept any kind of cardboard box but no
she likes the cardboard box that was
falling apart and that she threw up a
hairball into one time that i cleaned
out but still i mean you can kind of see
it's a mess
she liked that box
that was her box
[Music]
did not want the fresh box
boxes full of memories
yeah
maybe i'll find a similar box and then
i'll try to
stretch it out and rip it a little bit
so that she would
feel like it's used
she maybe just doesn't like new boxes
no
normally not
it's also not the first time that i
changed her box i think
i think
now i'll test out some things because i
want her to sleep on my bed again not on
the floor
i can't reach her i can't give her pets
while i'm sleeping
when she's down there
she keeps on going back there
man chunky come back to me
[Music]
she prefers to scuff
anyway thank you thank you
speaking time thank you
mr sanchez
i'm more skilled at ellen ring than
mario games
that that sounds about right
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
i like sausage
i'll never get that out of my mind now
kiki master guy
i like sausage so you're pretty good
[Music]
and one
last one from franklin
right yeah
thank you for the rest of the chat
one of the lucky chickens who made it to
the meet and greet super surprise i won
your meet and greet when i only signed
up for you
lucky you didn't even choose any other
options i thought you had to
oh i want to praise you more you're
awesome and i'm super proud of you oh
yeah we talked about a certain game
that was nice talking about that having
similar
interests hopefully addressed make it
clear that kiwawa is my aussie
this is my first ever super chat it's
long overdue franklin thank you so much
first i was super chat but i did
immediately know
who you were
when you showed me um that badge with
your
like your twitter icon
um
see you don't have to
super chat to get remembered
you have to spam me on twitter just
kidding dude you didn't spam me but
yeah some of you guys i know by
like it helps me to see your twitter
icon because
i memorized
partially i remember you guys
with the name partial i remember you
guys with an uh with the icon that's why
i also notice it when it changes
on twitter or on
super chats
yeah
it'd be like that right franklin
says
first super chat and yet he can
uh confirm that
i knew who he was
when he showed up on my i mean he first
had to tell me you know
i didn't recognize his real face
but
after i saw the twitter icon
i knew what was up
very stalkative excuse me
yeah
thank you so much it was a pleasure i'm
glad you made it in thank you thank you
very much we had a nice talk i enjoyed
it
i hope you did too
yeah
hope you enjoyed the rest of the
convention too and the food and
everything was a pleasure
thank you very much
[Music]
so now i will go and get some food
because i am done
[Music]
first of all as i said there will not be
a schedule
um
for the coming week
[Music]
you guys i will i will also
you know
try to keep my
plants secret and not too obvious
at least until i arrive
i'll keep an eye out
yeah i'll just put up reservations
[Music]
okay all right thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you very much guys for watching
today
uh
i had fun but now i'm very tired i need
food thank you so much i love you guys
and in german we say
[Music]
auf wiedersehen
no energy left
[Music]
you