[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
key
K oh I'm quiet
uh it's so hot what the [\h__\h] why is it
so hot
[Music]
H am I okay I am worried because I I
woke up I had breakfast and then I
immediately started the
dungeon and I
was I was partially even playing during
a
meeting but don't worry I was paying
attention more to the meeting than to
the dungeon don't
worry I was even still translating
things during the meeting for others so
don't worry I was paying attention but I
just needed to get this done and I
wouldn't have gotten it done probably
otherwise um it took more than an hour
it took quite a while
um the it was okay until the boss and I
did not I died I died I was so close to
killing the boss but in the end like
with his burn and every attack of him
hitting so hard that I need to heal one
of us and then he has so many turns his
agility is crazy the boss of the third
level of the dungeon his agility is
crazy he gets a turn all the time like
every second turn is his turn and then
he hits so hard that I usually have to
heal especially ichang cuz that's too
dangerous I can't risk it and then and
then I died I had no choice I had like
two people dead I was like ah y okay I'm
going to revive ADI and then he does
another one of his beams which are also
really strong
and ichan survived with like a few HP
but then he died through the burn sick
burn uh it was rough I was so close and
it really pissed me off and then I was
like damn I only have like 20 minutes
left and I didn't even get the
boss so what do I do now and then I I I
looked through the list of things I
should be
doing yeah I might try again I guess if
it's worth it but anyway I got like I
got one CP drop I put on the fair relay
I only had like two fights anyway to be
honest I didn't have time for
more like yesterday last night after the
stream I just got uh some food and then
then I went to oh no do you even drop
cough BLS I kind of drop cough BL cough
drop kind of doubt it you don't drop it
either do
you the boss gives you the best armor
for
each so you're saying I should try again
but the question is do we have time for
that we have time for found you
don't I already got a cough drop here a
wait it's too loud
me come on bring it yeah I don't know 10
hours or so but I'm sure we can do it
right in 10 hours I hope
so um I'm just like
[Music]
oh the [\h__\h] boss I spent like two and
a half hours on the [\h__\h]
dungeon and then I didn't do it oh man
so
annoying and every every one of these
stupid fights just take so much
time every Bonnie is such a [\h__\h]
damage
sponge is that the only fire attack oh
we have we have
this no not worth it wait wait fire
breaking never
mind than for the membership
[Music]
simply yay
well oh wait I'm way too big I'm way too
big but as you can tell I quickly am
getting to business because we don't
have time I mean I don't know maybe we
do have time we'll see in the end how
much time I'll be have I have spent on
this it's hard to say
now get low the
difficulty uh
yes I mean I wouldn't mind doing it for
these [\h__\h] low Bobs did I even get
the oh hi dude it's
you it's him did we what what was I
going to say did we even get a cough
drop just
now I mean I got one so I can do
something with
that I I I would hope they let me
re-enter at the boss room
I did the bonds before the stream at
least so you guys don't have to listen
to
that hey oh you want to eat something no
I know no I already spent so many items
on the boss
fight yeah last yapping last yapping
both from me and from the characters uh
I I got some stuff I got a new
I don't know if we're going to keep that
but I bought this stupid bat six-star
bat k k this one I got in the dungeon
this one I got in the
dungeon it was better than the Hat he
already had and it recovers MP not bad
this one causes bleed which is pretty
sick but only sometimes that's um pretty
much what I've changed oh yeah and I
gave him the jeweled bracelets
from from uh our other buddy had it um
okay do we do we want to try it all
right let's try it you guys can help me
through this although it's really rough
it's really [\h__\h] rough might want to
stock up
on
um
f uh
food can you build a her is bad um not
at the moment currently I don't have
what it takes
I don't
have yeah well anyway
[Music]
um so this one there that was so rough
it was so
[Music]
rough it was so rough guys too you have
no
idea I don't know if I can do it on
second try that's stupid ass boss
man maybe one of my mistakes was waiting
too long to activate the the four people
special attack
when
like it didn't even do that much
damage it didn't even do that
much wait where am I going I I want to
go to that coffee
o you got this B you come my Japan trip
made me realize that I can't sleep well
without bre
really you brought free F
bling of course of course they will
protect
you because they're not real if they
were real then they would kill you oh
[Music]
no oh baby a triple
Bingo that means
I can't get in you guys are so
[Music]
rude
nice I'll take them I'll I'll take them
almost
all Bingo b Bond Bingo Bond
Bingo um boogy woie bum
BM ooh what do the asai balls
do oh oh I would love to have an as side
bowl for breakfast
man wait was that
here that sounds so
refreshing ooh oh
yum ooh okay I'll buy thank you but 250
honestly during the fight is already too
little I need I need stronger healing
items um
I wonder what even is an as you don't
know do you know what asai is what the
part what the main part is it's like a a
berry but it's like it's kind of like
ice cream because they always serve it
so ice cold and it's like creamy and
it's
Berry and then yeah they they make it
like a cereal bowl with like fruit they
top it with
fruit and it's really healthy fruit and
N some stuff I
think oh
[Applause]
wait [\h__\h] you speaking of
fruit well I guess that was my fault for
running over the street like that
like do we have can I
make nice nice we can make some culinar
te
thank you thank you got five out of five
again you only sell watermelons right oh
wait sometimes you sell something
else a it's different for
day the
banana
Aloha what do I need
for passion for a mango thank you and
pineapple whatever um
ah no not
that no not that I want to whatever I
want to look what they
sell
uh was I here yeah ah sorry
I'm I have like no plan
like I want to I want to get more like
good food that heals a lot but I don't
know where to go uh because I have the
items maxed out you know so it's like
let's just let's just go
here let
here oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my
God yeah one thing at a time let's just
do one wi at of time I think we're going
to be okay I'm not as like pessimistic
about it as you guys but you guys so
many of you are like you're going to
take like 10 or 12 hours but others are
like it's going to be fine it's going to
be like 4
hours uh so I don't know what to think
personally I I don't believe that it's
going to take endless amount ofs yeah
Blind Faith that's the way to go oh
that's interesting mat milk tea oh
sounds good I'll take it thank you for
stopping not what I wanted I wanted food
though you will not be far us cuz the
final is well yeah four is maybe a
little bit too
Aloha uh ah there we go this is oh thank
you this is what I need thank you with
800 yeah sure this is what I want thank
you that's what I'm looking for just
stocking up on all that food okay at
least that's one thing we have behind us
now cuz I'm sure we should have done
that too stocking up on food and MP and
stuff that's good
and
then oh wait there's a
case okay we might be able to create one
thing with a I have one drop one cough
drop let me see which one we want to
give
priority okay both of these need cough
drop uh
I I would want to aim for this one shark
fin I know I can
buy uh can't I buy it actually at the
dungeon or was it the dungeon in Tokyo
Yokohama and then electric crystals I
can easily buy I know I can also get the
shark fins elsewhere but if it's just
one might as well just buy it at the
beach at the Hawaii
dungeon we're in Hawaii I can fish for
them fish
how do I fish you mean
dive you can fish for them by the
harbor huh maybe that's
relaxing how how to fish anakonda Harbor
Park Y and I will make his extreme bat
and then he'll hit so
hard I'll Be So Satisfied with his hard-
hitting bat
that will never be asking for anything
else ever
again okay where where do you fish I
don't think I ever fished in this
game wait wouldn't it be more like over
here on the
beach ask a dude to use his
Rod actually at the
harbor there's a guy right next to me
me this one no that's
Su I'm close to one right
[Music]
now I see
one he'll just give me his
oh okay whatever that is I think it's
some important item but we need H for
those not going to happen Okay $1
wow how high are the chances
h
k shark fin oh [\h__\h] I pressed the wrong
I pressed the wrong
button okay now now I understand what
you got to do
sh sh oh wait now it's X oh it's not
always the same [\h__\h]
bamboozle okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay what is
it oh come on at least it's
cheap now it must be triangle
it's got to be triangle
now ah it's not oh I do only got one try
okay I see I thought it might go back to
the other side I'm learning with every
single
try up for the
bait yes there we go shark please M Okay
cooking ingred what can I cook with that
I only know I can do stuff with fruit
haven't seen anything with like
fish yeah you have to react really fast
basically you have to immediately
register nice what sign it is and then
hit the middle only one
chance hot
pots eh I can make a hot pot is that
what you're
saying HP MP crafting P oh
nice right in the middle but it's only
[\h__\h]
seaweed okay okay okay I'll believe in
the shark fin it will happen it will
happen come on come
on today's goal is finishing the game I
will not be satisfied with anything
less we are going to finish it no matter
what it takes worst case we're worst
case we're going to turn the game on
easy mode I forgot that that was an
option that we could do
that we'll see we'll
see not for the boss fight though I
wouldn't oh Bullseye I would not do that
for the boss
fight any boss
fight come on is it location
or does it not matter oh look at that
Bull's Eye ooh squid tentacles for
weapons come on come on come
on one more one more it's just no one
hard though isn't it oh [\h__\h] is it oh
then
[Music]
Bulls getting really good at this
fishing super
unreliable exchange is not that slow and
it's sure I'll give it a few more
tce I'll give it a few D May might need
the other things anyway too maybe maybe
maybe
no oops almost missed
it does it matter I wonder so far even
when I had Bullseye I still got stupid
ass seaweed so I think it doesn't matter
I'm finally learning where the buttons
are on my controller without looking
isn't that
nice what
[Music]
what I give it five more tries
one
two kindness points oh
really not that I really need it anymore
at this point I think I
mean uh free
yeah y y uh-huh
four real
success wait I kind of want ah I didn't
look oh my god oh that was fast reaction
I was going to say I kind of want to get
all
30 to get that pun and another p and get
the
achievements I don't know probably not
worth
it I lost pounds is this the fifth or
the
fourth should we can we go for the 30
let's go for the
30 it's just five more or so okay maybe
eight more I don't
know sorry brain brain hurts for a
moment
there
fre does it count when I don't catch a
fish probably not right or maybe
[Music]
see yeah I'm okay I
had I made breakfast today eggs
bacon and some fresh herbs and spring
onion and stuff in there
and some
cucumber so I would think that's a
little bit more energizing than my usual
breakfast which is something with
chocolate a lot at the time so hopefully
that helps because I did not have time
to buy an energy drink but I have green
tea green
tea next to
me yeah and then if we get hungry later
I have um again fresh grapes
uh and then otherwise I if I want
something Savory me I'm going to
quickly go and make a sandwich but I'll
have to put the bread into the
oven for a little
bit and then make a sandwich but then
then I'll have something really
satisfying to
eat it's okay 10 minutes in a 10 hour
stream at this point is like whatever
yeah the grapes should be
nice but I I ate all my chocolate last
night so no chocolate for me today
probably oh how many more tries is
it no chocolate for
Me Maybe I mean I probably still have
some chocolate somewhere in my home but
not the not the kind that I want to eat
probably
H how much chocolate hey was just
maybe four of those chocolate
cookies
maybe I I wanted some dessert you
know come
on
what hasn't wasn't this also just
already 10 tries how are we not at 30
yet oh I did get it oh I I got it I
missed it okay well
[Music]
done okay what do you even get from the
achievements more personality
boosts oh you know what we can do we can
make the weapon first and then I can
rechallenge
the oh nice
Divine protection then we can challenge
the boss
again so do you sell yes you
do oh it's that
expensive oh then I maybe have to do the
boss
first never mind 15,000
discs
dude all right
all right I'm going in uh let's see
where we
can
continue from the boss
okay Y what wait do I have to save
outside first you get some by diving for
trash at this point both fishing and
Diving is probably
uh really not
oh say save point I guess don't do not
have wait I'll just save out here maybe
I don't have to
save M you think I get can get one
easily by picking up trash on the
[Music]
beach okay I'll try I'll
try I just don't want to I already
fished for a while I don't want to waste
too many minutes with this
but I know it's not trash but I want
P I got the [\h__\h] Pineapple yo free
pineapples free the
pineapples pineapple so uh diving for
trash right there pineapple Mar okay I'm
going cute okay
Nancy if it's you then I'll
listen Nancy Fancy
Nancy she'll be yeah she'll be F well
maybe not but if he just goes in and
dies and each one's like
no and cries and cries and [\h__\h]
depressed shouldn't have trusted oh
she's
gone we're just going to look for her
now
oh oh wait I know this I think from the
screenshot that that oh she has a fancy
oh
oh be
dazzled it's a Hermit
CRA wait what what if it's like like I
fought with narissa like oh so wholesome
crab with no shell and crab with shell
and oh oh oh crab wants shell but crab
with shell attacks non shell crab and
tries to kill him and eat him and that
is not that wholesome after all ichan is
just me observing this thinking first
naively it's it's it's a nice scene but
then turns out it's not at all and then
they kill each other and then Nancy is
dead why the [\h__\h] is there like a a
dolphin right at the
beach you
good I don't think they're good
ah Tak the Z Island
ah ah first try sh
no but I prefer this a little bit over
fishing wait did you just say trash wait
is this why Al could got the shark pin
or is it on the beach not in the water
did you guys say I should go into the
water it's a turn the trash into the
ah yeah I think you wrote about that
[Music]
too where is that
NPC they need
trash do I even have enough
trash what even is considered
trash where it the
side check the check them out
um this
one I don't
know I don't know the orange arrow icon
ohing Center
okay let's
check it's not a [\h__\h] it's not a show
[\h__\h] headit
Kim me mango maruya mysterious food
huh can I
even can I even make something out of
that at the juice stand but I'm guessing
that's kind of
[Music]
rare oh thank you not many people love
my voice thank you
Natalie seashell
[Music]
mystery for is rare oh no go away go
away go away go away go away go away go
away go
away coconut jump that's the only good
thing about you is that your name is
amazing
oh it's actually decent damage even
though it's
weak and it raes my
agility at least you guys you guys like
me oh yeah I switched him to hero and he
has the suit on
now looking good
looking
fancy the yokoh fit yeah I like the I
mean ah [\h__\h] the Hawaii shirt is nice
too but damn he looks so good in the red
suit doesn't
[Music]
he okay so over
here is the recycling
[Music]
center okay A bit more I
mean we need like oh my god what
happened with the sand so suddenly e we
need a bit
more wait what do we what do uh what do
we need what kind of trash not much more
yeah then we'll get the bat then we we
challenge the the dungeon boss and then
we'll do the story I guess for
now and then we might do another break
to upgrade equipment again I don't know
we'll
see yeah I'll I'll bring it up to plus
that looks like trash to
me you don't think I need to do that
yeah I know people have said just buy
six-star weapons from the shop there'll
be
enough but the stronger the weapons are
that I have at least the easier all the
Sponge Bob fights are we should just
call them SpongeBob fights because
they're low Bobs and they're damag
damage sponges so they're literally
SpongeBobs SP on I love
you I love
you how much trash do I need for like
200 points
approximately they go down fast with
proper
attacks ow holy
[\h__\h] there's a juicer here what what
kind of
juicer talk to me
Aloha ah you're not a juicer at all
thank you you're a
liar but that is insane what just
happened I want to SW your ass I totally
should holy
[\h__\h] no they're still spongy also
because there's like so
many I'm glad you guys agreed that last
time like the
fights where like there was this one
part where you have to run through the
whole city do all these little lowbob
SpongeBob fights that that's just so
unnecessary what's the
point CH is dead on stream why why you
taking a break who told you you can take
a
break who told
you come back
you think you're not it looks like a
break to
me chat revive but only due to my
power me slapping you
waake okay I'm I'm going check how
much how much that
is where's the trash lady where am I
when you swim you get lost how
realistic I like the reality of
that where is she ah right over there
okay oh I didn't get that
lost actually not
bad huh do you want those briefs as well
m
I got them points nice keep up the
Trashy work all right we can make we can
make the but uh I still
need
some some Stones I
think yeah electric crystals
13 eh no uh wait
oh
not eight eight eight eight eight eight
eight I got it I got it I got
it shut up shut up eight electric
crystals which I can get to the at the
dungeon
this d
d
eight eight electric
crystals it's kind of C crazy that the
shark fin is so expensive
here I barely spent my points so far and
this is
like like the amount you get from like
two dungeon runs oopsie
basically the points I have or if not
even pretty much free three of them it's
a huge
scam 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
8 duai so I'm guessing it's going to be
electric
element let's make sick ass bat one of
the best bats in the game I would say
right best choices for end
game true Legendary Heroes bat I mean
even the name says it's just
insane plus 44 and additional electric
damage to down enemies it looks
amazing it looks
amazing it's upgrade value will decrease
and brands that don't meet the EXP needs
may be removed oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah we'll brand it
too oh my God s
[Music]
used it for like 2
hours no I I'll keep you for now I'll
keep you for now we'll see maybe I'll
sell you maybe I'll go broke and need to
sell you probably not um a yeah wait
ah plus 10
brand big blump
damage this
one
[Music]
y okay what are we doing
for a cuz he still has a five star the
others have already have six stars so
I'd like to at least increase his Bat
before I go back into the dungeon maybe
uh increase what am I saying I don't
know craft
something it's a weapon I don't know if
I can
[Music]
though yeah it's not
uh I could relatively quickly get all
these things I think even this
one oh it's I already have the squid
tentacles I could get a cough drop
tin just to just by going to that Harbor
again I got that first try last time buy
a few rainbow crystals buy the Samurai
Katana wait is that also
like a weapon I can buy right
samai is a
drop
oh Sam
[Music]
by uh
wait
infinite
wealth someone
[Music]
like don't tell me it's in the
dungeon keepers of the
city on the foot bridge to the left of
hakita Park wait is that even in
Hawaii no it's in what you looking
at maybe in Japan huh all right whatever
then I'll go to the dungeon first I
guess uh I can't think too much
you look
which so what it's not a specific
one it's confusing
me that is confusing me right now five
star weapon okay for now well he kicked
my [\h__\h] ass so
H but at least I got one more upgrade
now
so
so to did we switch it
nope also let me switch this
again
the what was it the shiny bracelet
thingy what is this by the
way whoa
I'll give it to someone
else maybe heral
why do you have Co
ey
recycling uh
ah uh there is a safe Point inside right
and a heal Point too but well whatever
just in
case okay third
level gain oh there's second clear
reward as well
oh wizard boots oh
cool oh well we need the true Hero's
armor so second try for me I tried off
screen and I
died around the
end cuz you will see he hits so
hard it's kind of crazy
but on stream it's first try so if I win
it first try then it's first try
officially yeah it's on by the way like
a malfunction
version of that
[Music]
P I can never block this and see half of
his [\h__\h] HP which means I have to
heal him because if he dies then [\h__\h]
and you see he's next he already next
turn is already his [\h__\h] turn can you
[\h__\h] believe it although I had the
feeling that his aggro is kind of always
on the one who last hit him which is
probably just my imagination but so what
the [\h__\h] am I supposed to already heal
him I guess so
no I'm going try this
now oh okay okay you're just readying it
that's good that's good you're already
going easier on me than last
[Music]
time
okay so if you guys are
close please get everybody
uh yeah that's the thing the cleansing
skill would have been useful but that's
on in the other group the Japan group
has
that
um buff buff buff buff buff
buff oh yeah I forgot about pound mates
H thanks for reminding me I forgot about
that
completely so his weakness is water
generally just so you know I wonder if I
should switch although Inon is kind
[Music]
of I could fix him but you know what
I'll just I'm just going to
it's going to buff a bit
more yeah you has I know I know I was
using that all the time my one only hope
uh-oh
who oh that's huge that's actually
huge
OMG okay it's as weakness is water but
I'm I'm kind of ah he resisted never
mind okay other has a an an attack that
hits every round would have been
nice but we have this attack I I did
this off stream I uh went to the Aloha
thingy and I um added some attacks here
and
there and this is actually really good
to bring along I miss though because I'm
an
idiot I cannot block Lo this for some
reason I really
try yeah oh yeah especially with his
electric bat now
yeah kind of
good
a when the [\h__\h] is he going to wake the
[\h__\h]
up I cannot wait for
him is he still B is not a paralysis and
that those two are so similar I think
it's a paralysis
right oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I right paralysis is the the has
the electric
icon I actually am pretty good at
blocking that
so that's
[Music]
unfortunate going to actually heal
because he doesn't even have a good
attack right now against
him if I use pound
mate I still get to attack as well
right are they affected by the grapple
doesn't matter to them
right or should I undo his guard
first depends on the
oppon doesn't cost her turn doesn't cost
her turn yeah just wonder if the I think
his blocking wouldn't M his guarding
doesn't matter does it or does it ah
man also a Aloha doesn't have grapple I
got to do merciless Mele
man oh that's good damage
1,800
uh-oh I guarded it oh it's a little bit
earlier than I fought okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay
okay let's do mask of fertility that's
something I could have done last time
better okay that might be although like
with every hit he gets like half of each
person's HP usually half or at least a
third so his little heal is
but it's okay it'll still be helpful I
think
[Music]
um I I didn't do this in my first try
substitution JSU but right now I want to
because of
this just want to get this out now
oh it's so weak actually what the
[\h__\h] H that was
weak
that but yeah so the good thing is the
scrub down thingy his electricity thing
is lowered so I can do all my cool
attacks now don't even have to do AI
aloha
anything with the bat I
guess medium
[Music]
medium
heavy yeah but what does it mean he
resists it but he's also weak to it now
is he still like is it just like me
I don't know if it's
even like we may have lowered his
resistance but he's still resisting it
just not as much maybe it's better to go
with water
then
good oh nice thank God what even D it so
much the heal is good though if I block
everything then it's just a third of my
health if I don't block it then it's
half of my health that's
gone got to try to inflict
bleed didn't work but good damage and a
follow up
nice tuna strong man tuna is my real
OSI tuna be my real ay for real for
real I'm going to help a bit what the
hell ah but he's that might work that
might work want to get both of them
please please please please
okay Mio is
next
oh same
should I should I should I do
it that's
okay critical hit rate
[Music]
buff
honestly this might be a good strategy
reducing his defense and attack
constantly yeah I like the
idea
oh a [\h__\h] almost I almost blocked
it see half half of his HP is gone you
know what's going to happen if he dies
game over so and next turn is him
again so my only choice to be safe is
heal each
B
[\h__\h] somehow I'm too stupid to block
that
now glory
[Music]
to glory to Wawa
yeah look at all those Puffs look at
them you should keep using substitution
juu
[Music]
okay actually he's already down half uh
oopsie half of his HP that's good that's
good that's
good H where halfway there oh Living on
a
[Music]
Prayer oh he's guarding again so this is
perfect my problem is eventually oh my
god there was a lag whoa eventually I'm
going to run out of MP for everybody I'm
going to have to give everybody M and
then at the same time he's going to do
so much damage and then I have to give
everybody HP and it's going to just all
be a big [\h__\h] mess actually let's
switch
[Music]
[Applause]
a so now he would need
MP oh my God it
lags please don't oh the beam the beam
but it's already so much better than
last
time that was uh big but uh
it will
be I
think damn
it I wish you had an immediate group
here sheos I didn't even get the heal or
it's already gone or so should I just
scub down
I'm going to risk this one ah no yeah
actually yeah Ian needs the MP so I'm
going to give him a little MP
HP I think that's the smartest
yeah good
thinking would like to heal the other
but oh no no no no not the
Ali ah [\h__\h] yeah and now this gives us a
burn that's the [\h__\h] up thing and
she's KO
[Music]
see that's my problem that's my [\h__\h]
problem he doesn't do this beam until
like later on I think that's that's
where you know until now everything was
okay at least he's not it's not his turn
yet so I can
revive ichiban's turn ichun has a revive
skill
but I want to I want him to
attack but now it's me if he does that
[\h__\h] beam
again what the chances that he's going
to do it again huh but I'm just reducing
reducing his attack again with this
so okay
okay please please please be be nice I
turn the beam
no oh God
[Music]
I don't think I have an all all people
heal I think I used that up previous no
okay I still have it cuz I died I
guess oh that [\h__\h] burn thank God it
was an ad's turn because he would have
died from the
burn no he's doing it again
oh my [\h__\h]
god see how stupid this
is you [\h__\h] oh my
[Music]
God and it's his turn again next
time oh my [\h__\h] god need that don't
do it don't do it no does he just do
that every [\h__\h] time
now oh my is that
just no no yeah go [\h__\h] yourself go [\h__\h]
yourself I want to cry that sucks so
much h
he's so
[\h__\h] oh my God [\h__\h]
[Music]
him when it gets to that
point yeah it's it's it's a rush rush
rush at D point
almost makes me consider putting a
burn amulet or so if I have one on
somebody
but I'll try one more time
I know we didn't make progress thanks
for telling
me what's the
point why yall so far away from each
other huh
I don't I even doubt that the boss fight
will be this
[Applause]
difficult
wow kept taunting and debuffing with
other team
taunting what is that an attack that he
has
for yeah perfect guard still loses
almost half Health insane right oops ah
oh she's
stunned
um oh his face Clash oh
this part is still
okay
manageable yeah dropping his agility
might be actually pretty
big O
h
[Music]
me's Fang girl yeah she could get him
back to his senses for
sure um well we definitely need to heal
what who's next oh her she's kind of
stunned maybe she's un stunned when it
gets to her turn
H 330 oh
well nope nope was not the
case can we get a
bleed yeah picking up Hero's gut as
well didn't get a bleed okay
uh-oh
[\h__\h] I misclicked
what oh what did I do
what I gave him a heal what with what
skill what what did that what oh
well Bo do I have any
agility debuff for
them no but I mean it could also be a
paralysis it could be a stun it could be
anything anything would help
honestly but anyway we'll need a little
heal over
here what item did I
use what how did that happen
Oh you mean when I tried to heal ichan I
healed Tommy back then oh the the
previous turn you mean oh you you
confused
me not
[Music]
a [\h__\h] oh well it
worked n
nice
440 or should I wait for this
until cuz it's more expensive right when
I do it again but should I wait for this
until the rush starts yeah the laser
phase I think so too
[Music]
I found what a still wa 2,300 anyway
sheesh how much would would that have
been if I would have hit the Triangle
Man okay he's
next maybe go safe
[Music]
[\h__\h] I
was so on time that it was too late
[Music]
I heal ich
b or buff or
attack he doesn't care about fire it's
not a resist but it's just like
me okay
okay at least he'll be able to spam
merciless melee again and again and
again I swear I'm blocking it but my
timing is just too
good
um so I was thinking when I did the the
scrubbing that I could add a mask of
punishment onto it afterwards
he's still resisting it but at least
it's like turn
turn based
damage or should I wait for
it I'll I'll try let's see how much
damage it
does but doesn't happen first uh round I
think just this next
round yeah okay it'san turn and then
still not his turn okay okay okay we're
entering the 50% Rush phase soon oh does
it start at
50 yes okay
2,400 and an extra follow up I love
you he's next nuke time has
[Music]
begun I think our tag team attacks
aren't even so good so I better
substitute to
[Music]
Ichiban that's the best I can do and
then attack with merciless melee
again HP HP looking good right
now oh why is it so much
less but his attack is free times de upu
okay here it goes
i' like my my heal on everybody now
but when it's Tommy's
turn [\h__\h] this is already dangerous this
is already
dangerous no it's a It's Magic damage ah
ah should I use my cup
again I only have that one
cup I thought she had a group here on
his
own oh he's doing battery
shock but okay cool something different
I didn't know oh it's not even his turn
next it's not even his turn next what
what's what's
happening okay it is small smaller
smaller damage smaller smaller
damage no I'm doing this for
safety and now substitute to ichan it's
not even his turn next oh my God okay
okay I don't know why because we didn't
lower his agility but okay
huh pound mates and uh the
thing
750 what at least I mean better than
nothing better than nothing it's not
even a St I keep on saying it but I'm
like genuinely surprised
oh we can do this nice follow we can do
this we can do this okay next turn is
this turn and you know what this means
substitution
J substitution
j a surprise [\h__\h] it's me
again yeah
I was so lucky this
time
why off screen and the previous try both
were way more difficult maybe he had
mercy on
me essence of Buster Geer
we take
those yep yep yep no thank
you you stupid piece of [\h__\h] I swear to
God we should probably get him out of
here yeah damn
it we're making out of attention at this
one that was a tough bus and that was
definitely tougher than the final bus
we're getting I'm I just have this
feeling
I hope you're satisfied with my
services satisfied you could have
obliterated us down there if my B logs
are correct you say your objective was
to test your skills and get stronger I
not
assist sh figes you've got a literal
silver
tongue
compation forgiving my and your entire
wait is that yeah that's me I have sound
effect on oh I get the boots after all
Oh I thought I wouldn't get them let's
go
e thank
[Music]
you never again do I want to see your
face never again
[Music]
oh
oh at low HP Buffs all stats at the
start of your turn and this
Stacks what is considered low HP though
I wonder and oh my god
wow that is
crazy
oh aha
no uh sounds nice but I'm actually going
to keep the Cyber boots and give these
to someone
else makes sense with him
right physical attack damage is derived
from willpower instead of defense and
his willpower is then stronger
so yo yo yo oh wait oh no never
mind we're good we're good yo okay I
mean so much Seven Star stuff
we are so
ready we are so
ready should I go to main story or
should I try to improve equipment for
other G I think we can do a little bit
main story got to get into it now where
is main story oh right over
here
well
what you didn't even recognize me you
even thought it was voice acted by the
game ah
[\h__\h] what I'm not going to replace Ali
with who with
jongi hell
no not at this point then I have to get
him all kinds of good weapons
stuff not worth my time
pure steel just like ichiban's
ABS ah that reminds
me I've got some growth
items gangster cabby housekeeper Geo
dancer actually GE dancer
I think that's
it yeah he joins way too late but as we
have found out they're just here to
please the fans really remember anybody
here could be one of br's people then we
shouldn't waste time first stop cloes
for uh Mr Han
here do I actually have to buy something
for
him what if I have already sufficiently
close
him have I clothed him at all I don't
think I actually did wait where am I
going maybe I don't have to maybe they
just want me to go there and then we'll
be interrupted
or leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone oh take a
[Music]
break uhhuh oh yeah he gets like I have
proper like Hawaii clothes yeah oh yeah
okay that I
welcome their stuck does seem as though
it would lend itself some Mobility okay
let's take a
look how about
this are you joking that crap's like 10
years out of fashion now get our man
something like this these are all the
same yeah you're crazy that's probably
the oldest thing in the whole mall
that's because it's Timeless ah just
like me what would you
suggest thought you'd never ask a load
of this baby oh that is
spish they'll be outd in 2 minutes after
they ring you you're idiots we're trying
to make him look less
noticeable e yeah I guess I feel like
maybe outside of Hawaii a Hawaii shirt
will make you more noticeable but in
Hawaii everybody wearing this kind of
stuff so then it's okay guess I kind of
forgot that part oh dear so do you want
something easy to move in and in
inconspicuous right precisely and fabric
that breathes well preferably how about
this I'm bad yeah yeah okay
okay what he's what is the same same
color same Vibe does not have Hawai
pattern I I hate it there is there are
literally I think black Hawaii shirts
for the super cool people so just get
that no
[Music]
way
yeah this is not even main story it's
not even dubb
hey
oh this is so so
unimportant oh my God okay okay
okay you're so happy for what cuz we
sold you a little we bought you a little
black
T-shirt well good for you oh my God we
can give a ball a beach
ball oh I
you
yay I want to play beach ball with Al
team Aloha oopsie
thank you for
stopping yeah $5 t-shirt and he's in
love with
me I mean you know it's the thought that
count so okay okay okay but calm down
hey what is this a Side Story wa that's
slow motion we get it we get it we see
what's
happening I get
it yeah okay
what we do this
one
[Music]
save
okay what kind of sub story is
this wait I can't go I can't do like a
shortcut
oh so I didn't even have a choice to not
do that
I have to do this
Quest he still bumps into
them what's the
point oh
shees that was unnecessary and
amazing wait how's how is it making
these
curves is someone remote controlling it
or what how how is this
possible why is it making
curves
unrealistic come on a there we go unless
suddenly it jumps over the
fence who the [\h__\h] is in here
here
[Music]
no yeah I remember him
I did do
thisly there was no need to save this
guy
guys look at those huge feet they're
bigger than my
face you're the
kid I'd be so embarrassed if I was your
child I would go to court and emancipate
that's the word
right so he was steering
it well I guess it would have been no
problem if you would have wet yourself
she's your
Nanny wa
what is she paying you or are you paying
her for this
deal
what what
misunderstanding I saved
him
what you're role playing too hard
dude
[Music]
for what level
1 I am 16 going on
[Music]
babies makes
sense you happy
[Music]
now what happened uh rise and joh
yeah sorry I always chck her out after I
get my
milk did I miss anything you mean
besides all your men taking me for a
baby
Napper baby Napper what you
say she brains i s here just save my
powdered ass that's sorry
Buzz stop your sories up your diapers
get out of here and get me some more
milk oh my God you
freak been really hard to find fresh
milk around here if nowadays there's
like people selling their
milk online because they're producing
too much you know or wait if it doesn't
have to be human
milk then just go to the store I mean
but do you want human milk
dudes very concerning very
concerning
oh uhuh
coconuts movie huh hey I C the line old
man I'm sorry it's an emergency I just
need to buy some ice ice
guy what are you doing here
Orlando Oh course I can
explain what is this
connected so your wife is sick and once
you see snow this is
connected huh is this just a natural
continuation of the ice Quest the snow
Quest doctor said tonight's going to be
she might not make it through this one
no more time to wait for other option
damn it I said I'd help you but I've
been so caught up and everything
else
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh all right all right
E I still look appreciate knowing that
you
care that is totally snow
whoa what's
up does this really what that's what
that doesn't happen that doesn't look
like this when you drop
ice it's beautiful almost looks like so
no no no no
no oh that diaper absorbent must be
reacted to the water from the Shave Ice
wonder how it got here uh maybe when you
beat up my idiot kids some of their
diapers ripped open what what what what
no what what what are you talking about
it came from the ice what does he mean
it came from the diaper what oh the
powder the baby pow it means it's like
baby powder
right but why why is it coming from the
ice cream I'm confused I used oh it's
like the the coldness from the oh the
water apparently from the ice mixed with
the baby powder or
so
okay diapers get this coton powder in
them to absorb liquid once it's wet it
flops up like snow you disgust me wait a
sec like snow
huh
OMG we found it science maybe we could
use this I mean it's basically as good
as real SN right not much of it don't
you worry about that my crew left Japan
with a full assload of dipes we've got
stuck for
days an
assload clean diaper happy baby had to
make sure we were prepared case cuz we
wanted to extend our stay in case guess
that makes
sense you could have also bought them
here but I guess they're cheaper in
Japan but are you sure about this those
divers are important to you all
right baby play is about the joy of
reverting back to a time when you had no
cares no obligations but the end of the
day we know that's just a fantasy We're
Men Men of Honor and we respect people's
dying dreams ain't that right boys yes
sir I'm giving him this voice by the way
to humiliate him K Wan you're a real man
after
all Mr gond water I don't know what to
say you heard the boss go be with your
wife and leave the snow to us we'll give
her a winter wonderland trust me thank
you thank you so much so is there a
third part or is this just does this end
here have to admit I've never been sure
what to make of youan you've definitely
earned my respect though mm- no you have
not no
no respect for what for having diapers
with you and accidentally finding like a
solution to someone else's problem huh H
I've got admit tearing tearing up fresh
diaper is a tant of blasphemy would
never considered it otherwise but seeing
the lengths that man was willing to go
for his wife I can't be a baby in the
face of that it's time to grow
up
uh-huh yeah yeah get your diapers you
little
shits from the back it just looks like
normal panties
honestly okay we're staying at the hotel
near Seaside Avenue meet us down you're
ready I'm never ready for you never also
now I have to go all the way
back I guess we need to see the action
right wait where this is the main quest
right at the
hotel which
hotel where where is this
K hotel is it
this embrace your Wild Side
no yeah no blue dialogue but which one
ah this
one uh closest
taxi I know it's a size but they want me
to do
it what are youing at I have a feeling
we're going to experience something
similar as to what we
experienced before when we found those
men in the
diapers in in that place
before kill number two kill the
second I have no
more bird food or do you just eat
fruit is that the
case guess you could have a
coconut maybe this one wants
specifically fruit saying
a let me
in we're all diped up here ready to make
snow
e yeah oh Do We Fight to get the diapers
all like puff puff puff puff
puff is that why you asking
me
for Prince I'm a hero
[Music]
that's not
good don't work too much you have to
live life guys
[Music]
is this like plant scripted oh snow is
coming
[Music]
in
for foree
[Music]
here comes the
snow
[Music]
oh let's not tell her where it comes
from nice nice looks
good
[Music]
what please no foreign
fore
foree
foreign
fore speech
[Music]
fore
foree
foreign foreign
speee
[Music]
spee
for
Fore
fore sweet you
good
night oh
[Music]
no no
know if it wants to be funny or
emotional make up your
mind no I'm never going to call you ever
in my whole life never
again
OE Ollie wait ol wait ol wait you just
missed an incredible Side
Story incredible it was indeed so
incredible that we honestly could just
take this as our ending
today very suitable for an ending I
would say
right that was crazy almost as crazy as
Ollie
yeah all right K if everything's checked
off we Bound for District 5 I'm Flying
Blind what that part of the city you
guys take the lead no problem but none
of us exactly have been there before
so yeah that's true we should expect
trouble huh and then we'll make it
yeah not yet we're not ending yet oh
adti has a bond oh no okay quick quick
make it fast
adti make it fast
[Music]
spe
did she remember
[Music]
you she didn't a
they're working together probably
yeah
for
what
preparing g
g
just when two games Worlds Collide
okay so we're going to help out with
that let's catch the robbers you and
me you told her
mad this time we we show we will show
that we're confident
[Music]
well then we got to prove her with and
save her save fix the problem before
even you
know feels anything from
it we'll fix it before she can be
bothered by it and then we'll show her
see we helped
you don't worry don't worry don't worry
we'll fix it we'll fix it we'll fix it
you I get it so probably next uh Bond
conversation will be us going to the
store and like you
know punching those sussy bastards in
their faces I will not do his bom
conversation don't have time for
jungi n hold oh by the way I did uh the
the Tommy one I had a fight here in the
street uh before the stream started
really
quickly it was really easy they're
really low bop SpongeBob
weak now we're going back to Barracuda
territory like the good old days isn't
this
nostalgic remember when I was like
really freaked out by all the strong
enemies in this
area the pinkies the pinkies and the
Brain Brain Brain Brain Brain Brain
Brain
Brain yeah the pinkies were scaring
me
huh that was really nostalgic right nice
reference
woo
mus enter District 5 are we in The
Hunger Games
gra are
crunch
hello wow what a
welcome no survivors I want every one of
them gutted and left rot in
the why are they so mad
you have no business here
jungi he looks cool though I like his
new fit you don't want to mess with me
should have been a black ha shirt though
kind of
disappointed excuse me coming through
oh that actually killed some of them wow
weak weak weak weak weak weak weak weak
weak
weak oh I'm too strong oh [\h__\h] they're
not even that low
level you
want oh you
resist n yeah
oh ni I'm the right level of strong
where is this full full HP dude where is
he I can't see him oh there you
are V Quest how do you say this name
Vasquez vquez
Vasquez
Vasquez do you need me to I'm just going
to attack
I got
it
nice all right we may
enter got to look out for
items
nothing but they want another
fight Bring It
On on this current
free time that we have I shall share
with
you an incident little
tangent you guys remember you know the
story lady that I really
like and then there was the dude who
while while she was gone like I
asked if she quit or
something and then they told me
no no she's actually just you know on a
break
I'm put on you taking your time and I'm
like oh okay that's fine but ever since
then this guy has been teasing me yeah
and oh my God I swear every time I go
there he smiles at me like a [\h__\h]
teenager he's like are you sad do you
need a hug from the girl do you want to
see her what would you do if she
actually did quit a one time actually
like trying to prank me saying she did
actually quit I'm like well that makes
no sense yesterday you say she just uh
has an injury today you say she did quit
no makes no
sense yeah it's just so immature the
first times I was laughing
along and then the next couple times I
was like dude not just I don't care that
much about her she was just nice to
me but then and he still continued and
it's just so
annoying that
yesterday uh so I walk into the store
and the guy is there again and I'm
already like he's got that stupid grin
on his face
again so obnoxious already I know
exactly what he's going to say I swear
there's not a single time where he did
not say something like that making
stupid jokes like a [\h__\h] high
schooler
so I I couldn't control myself like he
he asks me are you sad and I'm like no
I'm fine what cuz I don't know maybe it
looked sad to him or so but no he just
assumes it like it
was can move in on us that I might be
sad because the lady is not here today
again you're outnumbered better start
I'm players and he just had this stupid
gr and he grins at me and so I was like
okay I'm going to say it
now I tell him dude you actually pissing
me off at this
point I said that in German pretty much
that way I was I actually was pissed so
I
said I said you you actually pissing me
off you know he's like with a stupid
grin he keeps on the stupid grin the
whole time and and uh he's like oh what
do you mean h
why I said well you know you always make
those hints about that lady it's just
just stop it's annoying me at this point
and he's like what do you mean what did
I say I didn't say anything this time
did I and I'm like yeah maybe maybe not
so much this time even though that I'm
pretty sure that was a reference you
saying oh you said that stupid
smile um but every other time
and it's just
unnecessary I said that in a pretty
serious tone he was still like oh do I
don't know what you mean play
stupid still of that stupid
smile and I said okay just just stop
okay I don't need this every time I come
in here you're making these stupid
jokes and now now now he's playing foror
fool didn't say that so but that's how
it
felt his colleague was listening by the
way while we were having this
conversation
[\h__\h] no mercy yeah I could get him in
trouble I could tell his boss or his
Superior or
so but I told him to stop from now on
and then we'll be good okay thanks good
night good day sir
yeah so
annoying like we're adults okay I
don't you can do that joke maybe you
know one or two times but I swear it was
like at this
point minimum 10 times like every time
every time I see
him was so immature I I need to ask like
how old are you because I I'm I'm
baffled like I like that lady but like I
feel like he was at some point like
making jokes that cuz he was asking me
if I want to have her number and I'm
like what the [\h__\h] like dude you guys
joke about that kind of stuff too in
chat but I think y'all know you know I I
well actually it's just different I
don't want to be treated like that when
I'm just minding my own business buying
a freaking
qu in the supermarket that's I don't
want to be confronted with that kind of
[\h__\h] in that
moment you guys make fun of me on that
topic too but I don't need that from an
IRL person a store
clerk I'm I'm not in the mood every time
I see you to joke about that like
sometimes I just want to go buy my
[\h__\h] quason and that's it
I was so pissed I was so
pissed it just makes it uncomfortable
it's like he's he's just like making fun
of me like why do you have no respect
for me I'm spending money here so and I
don't even think this is Karen behavi
Behavior this was just me trying to be
treated like a normal customer I I'm I
can be fun you know and I can I can
accept these kind of jokes a few times I
was playing
along more or less I was like funny
no
yeah yeah it's just n stop stop stop
stop I just don't like it when people
are too immature you
know sounds very annoying
right really so true
[Music]
if if he had anything else to
say the other people are really nice
there I like talking to anybody else
except for the angry
dude there's so many
Personalities in this
store maybe the grocery store lady can
give him an
earful well no not her let's see if he
says something
again then I'll I might tell I might
tell his
boss unfortunately it seems like I have
to quite the
C can we get a a nice knock back to the
other side no
can we get a knock back to the
right damn
it I've come to a point in this game
where I even understand how the
knockback works and I'm so proud of
myself like I see the arrow on the
ground and I realize aha if there's an
enemy behind that Arrow like a second
enemy and I knock back the first enemy
the front enemy towards that other enemy
see the arrow here you're go it kind of
even locks on to people if I knock them
against an enemy then you know there
will be lots of collateral damage if I
knock him toward ichan he will do
this amazing
amazing but I actually already knew that
like a couple streams ago like maybe two
streams
ago now I'm like trying to actively
[Music]
oh that sounded
bloody oh doesn't that go
underground but that's where we wanted
to go anyway
right oh oh you think I need a heal oh
there's a boss
coming but like I'm
fine oh am I supposed to be like
exhausted am I supposed to be like in
pain low HP low MP I'm so D oh dear this
is
concerning and to the underground we go
[Music]
oh were you below
sorry not
good I'm going to put you in your
place oh what are you doing on the
ground what's your weakness guys oh you
have a knife weakness beautiful
screw you okay these are a bit stronger
this isn't even a boss why did I get a
heal
come is he weak to Fire and
th combo no wait I was too far away for
combo is it dungeon time
even my no skill attacks are so
strong
yo so when I attack with a weapon like
this but he
has it literally just showed me he has
the the weakness for knives right does
the weapon still count as a knife no
matter what it
is does the weapon just count as the
actual weapon that I
have okay I'm supposed to have five
stars
here but I'm sick of taking 10 minutes
for every fight you
know the weapon does change it there's a
bit of delay ah okay okay okay okay but
generally weapon attacks are pretty
effective
so oh he's weak to
[Music]
fire
nice did I actually do damage on him
what
[Music]
what yo oh he did have thunder and fire
weakness they're giving me too
much too
much
playground too
easy
up what the back to the light follow the
light kfp no don't don't don't follow it
oh this is this is just like the ghost
game I played with
waya oh
it's so small the corns are so
small make it
bigger I need more space ooh sheesh nice
boots six star boots
style pirate boots already have good six
star boots though I think on
everybody oh wait six star boots oh I
guess wait everybody's F has five star
boots I want to keep those though
um H does EV is that evasion or
agility wait let's let's give this to
him agility yeah we don't want to lose
agility on her uh what you looking at
what you looking at what what you
looking at what you looking at what what
you pissing me
off
I'm do your
worst your time what let's
go L seraphim is a big Topic at
Coachella right
now so this is even I'm going with the
time with the HP IC of the
world go where are my K-pop fans here
where are they where are they where are
you it's a cute room by the
way I'm so trendy
yeah Cella has a lot of big names lately
yeah but they're missing
me they'll never make me hate them you
mean Lu
seraphim been listening to qu lately
what this being a fan of Chima count
yeah well that's kiata pop you know I'm
talking about Korean pop
close enough though close
[Music]
enough I would abuse of a I'm just too
lazy to even choose and look for the
skills there the lists are so
long I'm just like brainlessly
mindlessly
using basic normal skills they're good
enough to ah again
no not this time what would have
happened if I would have not P pushed
that would I have fallen down and then
what it's not a
[\h__\h] I'll you
[Music]
nice so strong Seven Star bad crazy
we got two of these rainbow crystals
guys nice Italian
ring you know what also has an Italian
ring
my
name oh get it K there's a lot kadas in
Italy I think it's like quite the
Italian
name come
on there's a famous Kiana with ch
literally in it
as far as I know was it Italy I think it
was
Italy not close
enough wouldn't make a difference in
Japanese writing if it's with ch or with
K it's still going to be
kada so ooh 700
HP don't you go
buiness so
[Music]
I missed
there are a lot of K in Bollywood oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah true true true
true so
[Music]
many Ice Ice
Baby boxing suck box suck in German we
say
boxu what the [\h__\h] this
place holy
[\h__\h] box
suck didn't think you'd make it this
far w w t
as my beloved Kon would
say yeah that's what I that's what I
think you should go back take those
steps back my
friend you have no business in the back
lines let's go of my team back lines as
in the back of the team as opposed to
front lines
yeah Oh I thought that would maybe kill
you screw you
[Music]
CH oh oh hi I didn't see you there I
legit didn't see
you I like his
fit burn byab burn
yes un
chainsaw but that's just a s
is it broken do you need a
chain do I need to help you find the you
think I'm stupid repair
store oh I didn't get the other one I
thought I could get the one behind you
too damn it that was smaller smaller
damage small small damage
I didn't see it
[Music]
coming he didn't see it coming either
I have the same attack I think on
ony combo AI doesn't want to combo with
me oh wait oh they do never
mind oh God I'm bleeding oh God I'm
bleeding
oh yeah today I showed you right I got
new
AES for Tommy I wonder if I can make
something with that something
new that's a base for a different
item different craft weapon you think
stupid I think I think it
is
actually
[Music]
actually well
actually can you imagine Tommy like
pulling a pun like that like he'll try
to correct someone and he he'll pull out
his axe and be like actually and
everybody will be like oh not
again just stop Tommy
I can totally imagine
it m me
please call me
please also don't don't shake your axe
around like that so
aggressively I know you think you're
funny but you're hurting us o that's for
H right I only saw it for an instant but
I saw it said
detective weapon uh uh
armor ooh
Seven
Stars yo
crazy kind of crazy his best armor y
wait so we have his best armor and
ichiban's best armor
and ah the others were from the other
team huh her best armor his best armor
not a
h maybe we'll get another one
they're nice for gifting it yeah I mean
I wouldn't mind if they sold it too but
not this is just making it faster easier
actually no it would be faster if
they're selling it maybe they're just
trying to gatekeep us from it so that we
wouldn't buy it too
early then it's not so based anymore
that they're doing that it's smart
though ah
God I keep on going
uh-oh they're not going to like make the
water flow out of this
right to kill us be too
easy hold still all
right I don't go away go back go Back
Sir go back to your place
a you Rin
winded maybe
two
yeah at least
wow that's air vent
oh that's a big El
vent
wow stks not stks
stks I made up new word when too much
strong that means strongs
by the way yesterday I was recording
motion
right and I was I danced I recorded BB
DEA and the N Dance I had some troubles
at first but it turned out actually all
right like uh too easy it's not finished
yet because it has like there has to be
added the physics and everything from my
skirt
ET uh on my model but chy put the motion
of the BB daa dance on me and it already
looked pretty
good look pretty
[Music]
good
so I'm
I'm okay I'm I'm happy with it for now I
didn't see the nii dance yet but the N
Dance was so exhausting if you guys need
a good workout
routine do the n dance the fun music
meeting is wa if you do it properly holy
[\h__\h] all the jumps and the there's a lot
of movements with your arms lifted above
your head whoa it's it's really a
workout I have really sore
muscles more sore than usual like this
is like workout sore
on my
shoulders Oh yay Tom let's go so can you
imagine I just did like the chorus can
you imagine how exhausting the whole
song must be to do for her she got a lot
of energy but still even if you have a
lot of energy I think it's still
exhausting
damn boost damage to enemy weaknesses
what oh does it mean like if he attacks
with thunder to a thunder weakness then
it's even
stronger and NY
NY n energy
NY yeah it's like having such an
energetic exhausting choreography is
very NY uh like very fitting for her I
would say all right who's the
boss
boss maybe a machine again do we get a
machine
[Music]
fight I already I'm fast I'm zooming
just dead
fast for
I like this moral ethical
[Music]
talk always like you don't have to do
this you don't have to be evil you're
just the
pawn what do you get from it nothing
Broke Free that
easily damn good job
though you need courage for
that ah oh he's going to make a
[Music]
pun why because they're the Sharks
they're the baracudas
guys his joke he didn't make it very
clear you can't get away from
me that's on him he could have probably
phrased it
better ah hey
dude keep no stop moving
M thanks for clearing it up
welcome you're so
welcome sick music yo yo yo yo
[Music]
yo
maybe I don't think it's that necessary
to buff
ourselves oh I got all of them but I
don't know I'm feeling like scre you
being properly
prepared what's your weakness it's water
all right all right and a nice knock
back shall
we yeah yeah yeah nice Tommy tommmy got
Yoo oh there's ooh water and cables on
the ground
H oh he's way too fire too
fire fire light the fire I'm actually
going to shoot here
first because I want the little box to
disappear the
[Music]
SpongeBob Tommy has eyes on his back too
yeah
I thought she doesn't nice blocks though
right she's got a [\h__\h]
grenade you think I'm
[Music]
stupid w
I thought that would be
enough okay we're not that strong
anymore he is
guarding and he's weak to water this
attack is
perfect now he's weak to electricity too
a little
bit got to give him a nice SpongeBob
bath SpongeBob and
spongebath these SpongeBobs want a
SpongeBob too maybe but you're not
getting it no no actually I was going to
do uh this and see how much damage we
do I I was planning on doing this was
waiting for his
turn big damage please
big interesting how they're showing d
only but I'm attacking all of them how
did they know that he's my main
target nice good holy [\h__\h]
3,299
oh he's gone dude he's dead he cannot be
in the cut
scene
oh oh
I don't get to do a prompt input oh oh
it's a Gren
oh I did not realized this was going to
happen oh look at all the things on the
ground maybe I should try using
it it's fire
huh
1,100 not so
bad w
barrels go t it's not a barrel though is
it is this considered a a
[Music]
barrel
no
no you think I'm St o
no one got
blinded ooh
nice what I pressed
it Li Li Li Li lies lies lies lies
lies these are just lies in
Disguise but I will expose
them you think I'm
stupid oh that's so
weak it's so sad
let's
go blade resist
has so much stuff to work
with that is a t if I've ever seen one t
he got a Death Wish oh don't wor uh I
will make that wish come true he's
charging
something early
delivery Amazon Prime one day delivery
for your death wish
[Music]
yeah do not touch Lonnie ever again
thank
you Alexa play reunion
play reun by
H
fore
foree
[Music]
fore fore
don't say thank you to me with tears
going down your face
what does k want to say to
[Music]
n let's go to
Japan fore
[Music]
yeah we're not going to merge you guys
told me we're not
merging think about
it no
please
yes come
on just the way he
Peaks he's so funny
suddenly
appears and saves
everything she would never want mock us
this is G
why does he not trust yam
yet after all
this I
mean oh I know they have a
pass but
still about
what kind of
boat CH
boat T
about that doesn't sound very
good yeah that's what I'm thinking
[Music]
clot holes
no it's real
guys obviously he's trying to help
us yeah does he look like he makes jokes
mm
spee
fore
fore foree
ki's fake
Pirates that's what we call this game
damn it I always forget my
team K's feathery Pirates a that's
cute little chickens with pirate hats
cute boat stocked by Ware House West of
Harbor Street I can take the woman there
while you keep poana distracted the
women okay but don't take Cheeto from
me and just in case we get overwhelmed
by Haku or whatever you'll see the
things through right [\h__\h] that make it
to the boat I don't care if you got to
crawl to get
there okay
whatever what
what what
I don't know how smart it is to like
separate again but it's just so that uh
we don't have them running around with
us just for the sake
of game
play
right that's
it this is the point of no return for
ichi's
crew well I'm
okay point of no return though until the
final battles with VII oh it's not true
okay cuz I thought I thought that might
be kind of
early that sounds a little bit
early
[Music]
okay let's go get a oh wait the someone
I ah right [\h__\h] that Katana I don't know
where I get
it you guys confused
me said Google it then I Googled it but
chat said something else than what
Google
said I'll come back yeah but still maybe
I want to get this
[Music]
before six stars would have to do yeah
but like might as
well if if the Samurai Katana is like
somewhere
where I can reach it I was a crowned
enemy in Japan only in
[Music]
Japan
okay okay then this will do
um I will keep in keep him as a samurai
until the end of the game just
because just because he looks nice and I
like it so uh usak Katana I'm sure I can
just
buy Rainbow crystals I need nine more
and one cough
drop cough drop let's do that
first oh we're actually oh we're right
across the
street get it we got it we get it I'mma
get it I'mma go get it I'm a go get her
go get her
hello oh he needs help no no no no no no
no no no no not
today not
[Music]
tomorrow let's see what you've got
just to make extra
sure
uh really pissing me
off a final P what what do you mean what
does that mean final pin what
kak
what what
what yeah I'm getting just one one
Clough drop for
now you know exactly what I'm up to
huh his plane seems to be famous for
that the enemies here the pin is just to
try what pin I have no idea what you're
talking
about what what pin the
pin
what what
um um are you talking in riddles or am
I
oh oh so are you telling me to go get
the cough drops
what but isn't it isn't it a
tin was a
tin I thought it was a tin not a ptin
why are we confusing each
other ah it's a tin
see it's a
tin we're confusing each
other for for
what why do we confuse each other just
to
suffer yeah but I I it's small and it
could very well be a pin I get it don't
worry don't worry
mistakes can be made uh the
yaku samurai
sword a first try it should be here
right let's go from
here have you been to the shrine oh yeah
uh last time we played I'm here again
um but I don't know the next things
don't seem so
[Music]
interesting can't afford anything
anyway
bye-bye I already picked up so
many o a
rake
okay man my shoulders
hurt I danced
so much actually not even that much and
then she dance was Next
Level my shoulders I need a massage I
don't have time for
massage short
sword it was this right yaku Katana
right has to
be pretty sure it was this
and she dance dance dance with her hands
[Applause]
[Music]
hands
sorry sorry about
[Music]
that yeah yum what hey huh
wrong way why would you have time for
massage not today not tomorrow tomorrow
I'm kind
of
busy um for like almost the whole
day
uh and
then the the wait tomorrow is thur day
yeah and then Friday before like I
stream in the evening right the member
stream but then the whole day before
that I'm also
busy
what you call
R didn't know it was used like this
[Music]
a that's why that
idle um music Idol groups music uh Envy
has rain in it because it's called final
Squall from cute
C makes
sense but I'm probably still missing um
some ingredients
the rainbow crystals I need nine they're
probably
expensive um why did I come here when I
still didn't have the crystals I'm so
stupid uh go to
dungeon the good thing is now I should
have a good amount of money cuz I didn't
spend everything on the shark
[Music]
fin nine
n99 n rainbow
crystals no I was
mistake hope we meet you again I really
hope we wouldn't meet you
again rainbow G Don't
Nine yes I can
afford good
amount nice
when will the waa get a chance to relax
good question because oh my God it
continues I'm really kind of like
mentally already stressed out by
thinking about the next couple of
days
M Saturday might be
okayish U before but I have to prepare
Girls
Talk um
Sunday busy Monday busy busy I'm out of
out of
town just going to be in busy days busy
busy
busy busy busy very busy
moonflower so cool but it has no element
that's so sad I wish it had an element
or does it does it have maybe water no
right it doesn't
show keep schedule light next week that
was the plan probably only three streams
I it's I I would have liked to do more
but it's impossible
actually cuz I'll uh I'll leave the
country uh next week for a few
days I'm going on a vacation
let's call it a vacation okay what am I
doing I'll tell you about it
afterwards oh my God
POG yeah it not it will not even be a
full week so don't
worry no
okay maybe one
extra what be relaxing uh generally
no it'll probably be Nerf racking
racking as
well can I take the brand out
no can I
not um but it will be fun
too I think I'll get a massage there but
until then no massage uh what should I
give
him
H something
expensive success rate of debuffs so I
could give bleed more often more easily
probably critical hit rate
10% that is good hope it's a good one oh
I hope so too otherwise I'll get another
one and another one and another
one more business than pleasure yeah
it's a mix though fire attacks we do a
lot of fire attacks oh actually wait I
guess they won't be fired not some of
them will still be fired but not all of
them right huh H I don't
know I think there were some where the
attacks were fire and the others were
just fire because of my
weapon I would do blade seal of
Blade
what huh didn't find it
H you could get the SE
ah my chat full memory reload I would
get you could get the seal that makes it
more likely to trigger Rand above Rand s
of
Steel yeah I like the debuff
idea gun
attacks wa SE
Seance what
a seance or
steel
what here this one blade
attacks all
right so what is it looking like now
seven star weapon plus 10
six-star weapon plus nothing yeah but I
was going to look if maybe I can make
something out of that more crafting more
crafting but you're going to be so
overpowered cuz I think I'm going to
keep him in this class also until the
end I don't want to change anything at
this point here this is the one I have
the the main the basic base weapon oh I
just need another cough drop 10 and 19
electri crystals that that's very doable
and but then it's not even that much
stronger it's
just should I do this
even it's not even that much
stronger I mean I can still upgrade it
but plus 1 but at least it has thunder
in it I like to have one more Thunder
weapon I'm probably
fine should I upgrade the one he has now
a little bit I'll I'll do that I'll do
that that will be
good this one oh wait no Fang axe I
think the other one was based on this
one yeah there's nothing based on the
Fang axe I guess I didn't see
anything huh oh well I'll upgrade it a
little bit this at least is fast and I
do like this one cuz it causes bleed
it's actually
op it's actually quite op
already
yeah
yeah brand let's get a brand deal
sponsorship let's
go debuffs
increases MP
absorption of basic
attacks I don't think I have anything
that absorbs
MP I could do electric
attacks cuz no wait no he doesn't have
electric
Bloodshed yo but not that one right
what there stronger
Bloodshed what just this
one you want me to put this one the $5
one I mean yeah it increases the success
rate even more that makes sense in
combination but maybe this like bleed is
a debuff so basically I can put this one
on right then it increas es it
greatly or does this not count for bleed
oh I guess it's not a debuff it's an a
is it an a is that
wait a wait is it the same thing in the
game or are
ailments and debuffs separate but which
one is ailman and which one ailman
is
Al debuff is lower stats okay is
bleeding an
ailment right I'll give him the bloody
one he likes to make people
bleed he's so hungry for
Bloodshed he's out for blood what is uh
Cheeto
carrying oh she's fine but we could
bring it up to
10 yo
I'm so
strong so
out what do we give
her fire attacks ice attacks electric
attacks blade she does do blade attacks
a lot but also gun attacks both I gave
the blade one to uh someone else so
maybe we can give her the gun
one or even the crit why not give
somebody the crit though maybe 10% isn't
so
much she does apply debuff debuff
seal debuff what are we debuffing them
with makes me think again if what's the
Deep she she we like to inflict B
no the
bees just for the bees
ah ah cuz of her weapon effect attacks
and weapon skills May debuff random
right does that work together to though
I don't know does
it cuz you know what I'm thinking is if
the game is programmed like this success
rate only counting for debuffs that are
part of her skills or if it's properly
programmed to also work together with
the special effect of the
weapon I don't know if they were smart
enough to program that or if that's even
like what they would want but I guess we
can
try
okay let's hope it works we'll never
know we'll never
know let's go
story
time
so I going to check this out really
quickly
OHA ichan special cute it's so weak
though adult oh trucker hat I
need oh this is cute too oh I like this
gift
[Music]
set shaved eyes H thanks very looks
good but too weak at this point in the
game but it's so close to the bar that
you probably were supposed to find this
place earlier
can I not buy anything for my buddies
directly in here no looks like the kind
of place where that would be
possible okay into or which one is this
Survivor or revolve revolve into
rol TR
w n I have to go
sleep everybody sleepy time
recently I'm falling asleep every night
while watching Family
Guy Family Guy and I noticed in the most
recent two
seasons they make so many references to
The Marvelous Mrs masil and it gets me
so excited don't judge me it's pretty
funny every now and then yeah I'm I I I
really fall asleep so fast watching it I
just need you know like a little bit
blah blah blah blah blah in the
background I'm sorry it's mostly for
falling asleep but it is funny a little
bit and and and I'm just so excited
because of the marvelous Mrs Mel
references and the only reason they're
doing those references is because um L
Griffin her voice actress is the same as
the one of the main characters in The
marel Mrs masel so they're making like
so many reference it's so funny it's so
funny it makes me feel so like oh my God
I I actually get this joke I feel like a
lot of Family Guy Watchers probably did
not watch The Marvelous Mrs masel so
they don't get it but I get
it yeah Alex Borstein borin Borstein
English pronunciation
borin
bin oh we're going to the Pierre
again people are judging me for liking
guy
there there's some like cringy jokes
here and there but I think it can also
be very funny for like
brainless mindless
jokes we get another cough drop here
while we're here maybe I'll need one I I
just do this one fight just this one
fight you've liked
worse thank you do your work
nobody got
paralyzed would you look at
that I heard the new episodes are
bad I didn't think they were
bad but I also don't remember them
anymore come
on nice and brainless sometimes gring at
some of their dumb
jokes yeah
pretty much but actually surprisingly
there are
some very rarely but there are some
wholesome moments too
sometimes there was one episode in the
most recent episodes where Stewie was
apparently finally saying his very first
word and they were like until
now how was this not your first word
and yeah it's just like the first words
that the people surrounding him besides
the dog actually registered as a word
and not just like baby words you know
and the Word was [\h__\h] and they were
like ah no the the mom she was like L
was like ah no I failed as a mom because
his first word was that and then they
went on the journey to to find out like
why uh where he learned it from
and did I get a cough drop I don't know
doesn't matter so they went on a
journey to figure that out and then they
realized it was from her and she was
like oh damn I got some anger issues
because I curs so much around you I feel
so bad and yeah she she felt so bad as a
mom and then like later on he learns his
second word and he says he says it to Lo
and it's Mommy and that's like it turns
into a surprisingly wholesome moment
where she's like oh I guess it's okay
you said Mommy I was your first seconden
word so I guess I'm not such a bad mom
after all it was actually wholesome
okay it was
cute let's go
yay wait that's a t boat or
that's actually not so bad I expected
something very
different
chill they running
along cute it's like his
children they love
no no I need
you I just buffed your
weapons
[Music]
forever no but what the
[\h__\h] what I don't have weapons or [\h__\h]
for jungi
Tommy
jump
Tommy oh thank God I actually believed
it because someone in the chat wrote
gone for one
chapter no
way cute
oh my God you you really worried
me you gave me a big concern
[Music]
there one
guide such a drama queen for real for
real
oh this reminds me of handmaid's
tail
oh not you
again have killed him when we had the
chance ah
welcome on
board oh
no don't worry you're not going to get
abducted
again
oh oh okay
oh I
[Music]
see oh interesting o I like the
predicament maybe they'll finally die
because they'll become f for the
Sharks
[Music]
uhhuh yeah
right we have a picture of
him that's right
Tommy
[Music]
for how much stronger did they get
oh
what what was that
Mega
what
huge I thought they just feed on jump to
the water but they
literally jumping up
here is only Dwight
left I don't know about that why you're
you're standing closer to the Sharkies
there okay he still got some
buddies
jeez why waterers oh oh look at the sh
in the background
zooming I have to pay attention to the
[Music]
Sharks okay I can't get too close to
that then I'll probably get damaged by
AOE let's go
I'm
so
shees
shees sheesh finally some
violence on the starting with already
some HP gone what happened you think
I'm if I send them that way
yeah w w w w w wow wow
wow go away Tommy what should I do oh
W screw you let's get rid of the small
boys
first like
here nice
oh let me see
okay ah danger danger Z danger Z
well that was worst timing
ever holy
[\h__\h]
you you ichon you
good
um this is actually terrifying
yo
damn I know I could use them to buy
Advantage too
but
seems
difficult ow no no Tommy Tommy Tommy
Tommy Tommy tomm Tommy move away Tommy
Tommy
Tommy okay okay he's fine he's fine he's
fine call it kak who you going to call
shark
Buster oh that reminds me I listened to
colon Empire's new song oh are they
going to get him come on come on you got
to get him you got to go get
him K new song kind of reminds me a lot
of that Ghostbuster song sharks are
closing in
uh-oh what does that
mean yeah travel Wonder it's so cute and
so funny but I feel like the first part
of the song um showcases
her English word choices more in the
second part of the song There were some
there was some vocabulary chosen that I
thought
uh oh not written by her for
sure was still really cute funny wait uh
m
I shouldn't have hesitated so much I
could have sent him over
there possibly oh oh oh yeah oh I didn't
think it would happen oh yeah okay okay
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
[Music]
nice
hello the one thing I'll give him if T
was on our side then
his his way of
uh just never giving up and risking
everything
wow oh no is uh
definitely
[\h__\h] oh it's okay it's definitely
something that you would want for your
um nakama
like he's very very tenacious very
persistent very
passionate doesn't give a [\h__\h] about how
dangerous stuff is she's not a chicken
not one of
us screw
you let's go
I want to try
this haven't done it in a while oh
nice nice
eyes oh
already
uh-oh this time I cannot deliver your
death wish so early unless you step a
few steps
back you want to you want
to show me what
[Music]
you here food is ready dinner
[Laughter]
Ser 168 extra
damage not even that
good but it works it works
it
works
nice yeah it totally shouldn't flick
bleed maybe it does but there's only a
small chance but it totally should
nice
Tommy my brain is so empty right now
guys come over
here this is really scary
is he going to come
[Music]
yeah oh y
it
y y ah he ready is an enormous
jump does that mean his reach is going
to be
bigger a little bit of heal
Dwight is asking for this to happen
don't know what's wrong with
him let's do another Thro
punch into another fro from one throat
to
another Hello Kitty oi hell
kitty oh no oh no oh it's so over for
other
oh he resisted he got
healed wait a second
what wait does do he heal from attacks
that he resists
what oh it was his MP oh yeah okay
that's how that works ah
or is
good
wow
wow you want you want you want some
merciless
melee all right just for
you just for you
making every chicken's dream come true
at
kfp for you and for
me I don't know that's kind of
fitting
interesting sounds like a
slogan that's my old [\h__\h] right there oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] it's like you wanted to say Ohi
but then you saw the shark and you're
like oh
[\h__\h] oh he's Ling
cute oh
nice easy easy easy easy easy easy easy
easy I'm make it look
[Music]
EAS Luc serim I keep on quoting them
they're so good to quote
stop oh
no it's the memory
recently I don't need his forgiveness he
need
M
uhuh
fore
fore that might be
true
for Oh I thought he would jump into a
shark's mouth he like
[Music]
whatever you won't get there with these
with this boat
for you think you frake is going to chop
anyway oh oh oh oh 3 two
one finally WI
let's
go poor
[Music]
boat Karma
I mean it's useless
now I must have felt so stupid like so
cocky driving off pushing someone into
the shark water too
and then he gets caught but like not
enough time to even feel regret
anyway what an
idiot he was so
confident oh something's going to happen
something's going to happen something's
going to happen
or is there we just had a boss
fight maybe
not
dude wait are you going to arrest me
[Music]
I guess
not the police scares
me I'm going to wait you're nice
right I know he
[Music]
good oh he's going to oh he made a deal
he's turning himself in
oh no no no no if I never unstop the
game then it won't
happen
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no oh but maybe if I quickly tell him
how to break
out I know how it works I know where the
keys
are no
no
no what the chat
though for
[Music]
us that's why he didn't want to tell us
because we would have stopped him
turning him in
probably maybe
[Music]
spee
to keep his Co
damn
[Music]
spee
fore
[Music]
fore foreign
foree fore speech
huh oh okay I thought he would like stab
him he
just ran
fast this is too
easy
[Music]
easy peace out
what what are you trying to say
fore
fore kind of late
fore fore
[Music]
foreign
foree
speech oh
that they always talk so
much same
name wait he killed someone his last
name was
Tabata but he was in love with was she
the wife of the dude he
killed he's joking because he's just
trying to say wa this is how much time
we'll have was like why the [\h__\h] is he
talking about like that he has
diarrhea why is he what what he's giving
us
time is your tmy
okay he's got tubby
hor that's
funny
nice that's exactly what I was hoping
that we would leave him behind if anyone
maybe jungi had a purpose after all not
just for fans she needed to be the
babysitter for these people where else
would they have
[Music]
gone we're back
in we
how the [\h__\h] are we not merging teams
when we're
here now this takes me back you're
telling me no time to reminisce though
we've got to find
yay so he's looking for somebody named
Tata if we can find out where she is
we'll know where he's hi it yeah must be
some folk in town who remember the top
of the family just have to get him to
talk where would people I got even be
don't suppose you know where the to of
the family's office was
that I got to mind like a seil trap for
the stuff come building number three
pink Street pink at least that's where
it was 30 years ago it's probably empty
now but they'll probably be able to tell
us where to look
next let's go
outside
neon we're back in glorious Neon
on now this is where I would get that
weapon I
suppose but I'm happy now I
think
with my whole get
up might check out the convenience store
though chiy py chicky k
oh oh we got it all
oh oh
okay no wait they don't have
Nikon
[Music]
Nik they have
Oden it always looks so nice but most of
the ingredients I don't really like
sadly
they have the Fried Chicken they have
Coro on the bottom and meni KATU and
stuff like that I think K you know it's
just cro just the fried fried mashed
potatoes and then minatu and and all
those kind of others are like meat we
breaded fried coating yeah yeah yeah
yeah but often they have nion and pizon
like any kind of like meat buns
but they don't have it here what the
[\h__\h] why
[Music]
not are we oh look at Tommy Tommy's the
first one to have over a thousand HP I
was just going to ask uh are we in that
last chapter yet or are we still in the
chapter where I started off today cuz I
know there was one and a half chapters
left but the last one is two chapters
length
pretty much still the same oh dear okay
it's probably going to end
soon tap family is been gone a long time
doubt there's much left of their office
inside what about other tenants or
neighbors might be some other oldtimers
like Adai who still remember them if
we're
lucky um excuse me I couldn't help but
over here you all a moment ago keep
moving GRS we're
busy uh sorry it's just been a long long
time since anyone has mentioned the top
of the family around here but do you
know them they went under decades P they
went under decades past but yes I worked
in this area back when they controlled
it h that didn't take take long no
kidding so are the four of you looking
for
them mostly story nice I kind of want to
make new
tea
anyway not them exactly they're
matriarch mat matriarch so to speak you
eat tapata do you know her matri Arch
goodness that's another name I haven't
heard in
ages no no no I'm going to
wait awesome well coms info she was
practically a local celebrity story go
some young gun actually killed the patri
to win love
yeah what a poor young idiot he must
have been no one could caged that
canery she just laughs about it that's
what led to the family's collapse back
it's too bad they were so good for
business back in the day so where is she
now I'd have no way of knowing that last
I heard the boy who shot her husband
fled overseas and that was all although
I do sometimes see a former Tabata
member around you could ask
him uh in the Pachinko parlor on
Nakamichi street I hear he lives for
that stuff
he's likely past his 60s by now but
still trots around in that old gangster
top even has some dimwit lack he not
hard to miss
[Music]
interesting one last thing I wouldn't
hold on to Old stories like that for so
long time has a way of wearing down the
truth in
them wouldn't even blame it on time
would just say the story may have had
some missing details to begin
with but yeah well you actually should
be thankful that he's holding on to that
story until now cuz otherwise we would
be
lost
so he would not have talked to us
otherwise I
think ichan you ungrateful little prick
[Music]
where is
k
k why are we not meeting up with
them it's a rare chance to meet up maybe
even just not for merging just for like
having lunch dinner
together come
on oh that's him another bull slum sixs
gangster top di with flunkies I think we
might have
[Music]
Bingo NOS like it to me why is this not
voiced this main story voice
it hey excuse me you have a
second
Yeah by your chance were you ever with
the Tabata family old man on pink Street
said
uh old man know I know who you mean so
what's it to you it's a long story but
right now it's pretty important we find
you a toas on your old matri The
Matriarch what the hell is this about I
only I I don't I know of no matriarch I
only
know mariachi
band I will not tell you anything about
the metri only mariachi
band don't fo me that was funny
I'm sorry but there's really no time to
explain I don't care about your mariachi
band please tell me about the marriage
don't treat me like some B you want
information but can't say
why I got the feeling this guy's brick
Walling
us
[\h__\h] he's back in Japan
what we think he has unfinished business
with her like making babies we're trying
to find him and the best way to do that
is to reach you was
on you his crew and so many words what
what and he's really back in town yeah
never thought I'd ever have to think
about that piece of [\h__\h]
again bring the car around we got to get
to master the
hospital y's [\h__\h] dead man
oh wait I've been waiting a long time
trust me leave y to us we're trying to
get him to turn himself in I'm sorry but
we owe him that he probably will turn
himself in afterwards anyway I think
he's just trying to get something done
before they put him away for
good he just wants to get this done yeah
and then he he'll be like I don't know
why you're trying to get me to turn
myself in I'm going to do that
anyway I'm going on my own shut up go
away he probably just has to say
something to her maybe there's like
something unspoken that has to be
cleared
up you know h
because he the only reason we got aanan
and Landing back to Japan safely come on
I have no idea who the [\h__\h] those people
are but not only did y might kill my
boss he s our whole family under look at
me my life went straight into the gutter
because of that prak he doesn't deserve
a good damn scrap of Mercy you huh
excuse me it's been 30 years if you
seriously blame yamay for all your
failures since then that's pathetic even
if without a family you can still make a
life for
yourself huh me she knows what she's
talking about that's it okay
fine could have who would have thought
that this would uh turn into a little
fight I had no idea
I thought he was going to be
stronger was I
just wait
what cuz he's
old these dudes are stronger than him
I can't believe they're actually made it
realistic
[Music]
what oh why are you still
alive
maker I beat up the senior citizen you
don't understand he wanted to beat me I
I was
scared no VA for
reason if I were
years 30 years you need 30 years to kick
ass yeah look at kasuga look at kidu
they're old as [\h__\h] and they're still
kicking ass we're both wasting each
other's time so I'll only ask once you
at Mas hospital is that what I heard you
say yeah I appreciate it now be smart
and don't turn this into another grud
you keep for a Life Time Stick it to
pinko
I hear
you okay Master the
hospital take a cab oh take a cab from a
specific point oh
okay uh I can take a cab to the
cab double
cabbing n I'll
[Music]
walk T step
don't think about
it I'm just running cuz I'm um I feel
like maybe I'll find something
interesting but no nope nope not
really
okay uh
can I teach
you Japanese okay one thing before this
starts so B and be sounds so similar
even I don't even know what I'm saying
sometimes one is hair salon and one is
Hospital very Musashi you can tell by
the Kani it sounded like I said the same
thing right yeah is BU and
beIN bin and be be but sometimes people
say it so fast it just sounds like
bu confus
[Music]
Areno I got that always wrong in my
Japanese
lesson I can imagine I even now
sometimes as I said I don't know which
one I'm actually saying
oh yeah yeah it's so empty did he kill
everybody that that ruthless bastard
no why so
empty no budget for more
models yeah this
is oh emotional scene
oh she's
old
W they try to make you think like he's
going to kill her but that's not the
case we know he's a
sweetheart we have some
snow oh that
hurts oh she's too too old too far
gone why is it so
empty why
no
Tommy Tommy
you yeah well that was [\h__\h] if we he
if he really did
that Tommy is just what's the
word he has
a oh 57
only
for
for Fore
[Music]
I want to see her when she's younger
oh the the boss is her
husband and the
captain
is like his groups are there two
different people right
H okay so yamay wasn't the the lover
[Music]
they're young both them
he must have been freezing back
[Music]
then she wasn't wearing a
coat
[Music]
for
foree fore
[Music]
smart I guess from
her she got away with it until now I
mean even now
should never carry the consequences of
that
[Music]
fore foreign
y y
[Music]
oh he's going to give her her is
cold oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah he looks so what
like malnourished now the Cod did
everything for
him he looks so like poor and like not
poor from like a money perspective but
like you
know oh
wa this is
so
um what's the words
so everything's so
um what's the word everything about that
was
so deep
and
no symbolic thanks yeah the moment you
wrote it I thought of it too it's so
symbolic like what he says what he
does how he looks like after he gives
her the
cat
damn oh that whoa
whoa
a
yum
damn I wonder if he gets for life
I mean he's already old
anyway but
like man I
wonder if it can at least still be
proven
somehow that he got set up but I mean it
doesn't change that he killed someone so
and I mean yaku's
a de the deep deep reasonings of why
Yakuza do things at the end doesn't
matter
yeah and I think he's probably also at
this point he's like Okay I accept it
I'mma do what needs to be
done at this point I'm done like he's
closing the
chapter he's changed he had character
development a lot of it he may have had
more character development than any of
the main characters
[Music]
damn
damn If I Can Dream
finally the
finale it's already 8:00 p.m. I'm I'm
okay I'm
okay it's going to be okay
[Music]
for
yeah we're
strong even if if
it's
we're stks
[Music]
snor that's
sneak this is so this sounds so
like this is so
unnatural this is so unnatural this
conversation
the bald Dude Looks more important than
the others look at his baldness and his
suit what kind of bow is that do do you
[Music]
he looks like a
biker he looks like he drives one of
those really wide Fick
bikes it's for low rank Yakuza oh I was
wondering yeah if that was like a
specific
Yakuza
fore
[Music]
foree she
no no
no he watched
that oh my God this is a
psychopath it's going to burn the
body and the whole place I guess
oh my
God s he's not been nice to
S oh we're
here
wait this scene we just
watched happened like I guess right
after the stream that they
did
huh huh
man
sheesh that's what's happening in there
now we're going to notice while it's
streaming that the but aren't they in a
different building isn't that what they
said
though oh we're actually not even
here but
like
oh one
I
wased that's
right for
someh that's funny to
me for
no that looks so
cool oh son he is K now
why does she look like a
Cy fore
both
wrong you don't know what you're
saying fake news
fake
news
dude now one thing I said in Japanese
was asking Japanese people like is this
even something that Japanese media would
realistically cover cuz Yakuza is such a
real problem I don't know if they would
actually put that in their new
and talk so openly about it like I don't
know you know seems like a maybe
something they they just want to
ignore not necessarily talk about it but
well we are not in the reality and this
is a very specific special situation
[Music]
anyway is a really a big problem iel
like in the
game h
yeah I don't know if they ever
wear such a big
problem hard to say no
idea I
mean mostly you would think they're just
like causing troubles among themselves
mostly
mostly but damn I'm still so shocked and
I feel so bad for SA I want a free sa #
free SA
he has such a baby face
actually compared to others
pure baby
face not just because he looks young but
his facial structure his eyes his eyes
are poppy eyes just like ich buns
[Music]
for he sounds
scary just like
geralt at least he has a nose
I have one
too
motion damn [\h__\h] E [\h__\h] E EA and
AG they should marry and kiss oh no oh
no oh no oh
no fore
[Music]
[Laughter]
he
[Music]
spoke yeah finally we
did
fore
fore for
huh to go him oh he sends a photo no I
no for
[Music]
is it even Bait when you say bait and
you show it like this it's just an
invitation it's not
bait no
[Music]
okay no I'll take it as an
invitation I'm not going to be baited
oh my God what are you wearing
to is also wearing with jacket
mhm
oh first
Chipman
fore foree
foreign
spee k
uhuh we're just not allowed to merge
we're going back to Hawaii already I
just
arrived that wasn't even a full chapter
[Music]
damn well I guess Hawai is
nicer every no
ped
ah yo grapes are [\h__\h]
goat grapes goat
groat who's
whistling
you K just not the type to whistle
right talk to cyle
ah you're right right
right such uh hey
son
yeah how is this the first come on they
got to have some proper like scene for
this
meeting come
on hey
oh I uh uh I just want to say uh thanks
for sticking
by no it was nothing I wanted to anyhow
all right still thank
you didn't K I want to talk to you by
the way go away go away he needs you oh
yeah okay see you
is it D who's
whistling no his lips are not
moving
oh oh did you stop cuz I came
closer you guys hear the whistle oh it's
back maybe they
stop when you get closer cuz I didn't
want to animate the
mouth but it's definitely him cuz yeah
still here I can tell he's not uh moving
his
lips but when you get get closer he
stops and it's the loudest though around
him not hold all he seems like the kind
of person to whistle in this
situation he doesn't want to whistle in
front of me why why is he so embarrassed
what's so embarrassing about whistling H
he's not even bad at it
isn't this a place where that dude is
under the
bridge you wanted to
talk that was going to take a while uh
you good on time if you even warn me
about it should I get like
snacks I wonder if my my peanut snacks
are still good I kept them open for like
what a week
now
hi I could have gotten the tea though
let me
test they still have a
crunch
oh yeah it's a different kind of
crunch is this really such a long
talk thanks for for the membership gift
I could make sandwich and
tea not that long if the game just warns
me maybe it's because the the
conversation leads directly to a fight
or
so I'm thinking too much about
it not even that hungry
actually okay we're good
oh oh that's what you want to say
what's
wrong she's like looking
around where is my
brother
already
M no no I didn't forget about
[Music]
for
oh
fore fore
[Music]
I would have preferred to see a ichan
now show down
[Music]
fore
ohe wow
she in that moment sorry in that moment
he didn't only asked ichan that question
he asked every Yakuza fan who plays
these games as well if it's okay for
ichan to take over as a protagonist
to handle the future
[Music]
games ah good old
times he passed the
torch thanks for the ra
[Music]
ohe I could have said it
better
[Music]
for so cute
this is how you pass the
T
[Music]
yeah prepared to get
mad
[Music]
fore
for Fore foreign speee
[Music]
[Applause]
I love this
exchange for status you probably didn't
say it on the first
date prop
[Music]
for oh no no no no no no
no for
[Laughter]
okay wow wow wow wow that was some
strong strong cutcenes
I need
to oh he's getting in
[Music]
trouble you don't
understand whatever what if he doesn't
want to be
dead he was just told to live
yes is he going to be supportive of
it oh
what
[Music]
for
okay fore
[Music]
he just saying get out of the country
now it's kicking me out for
[Music]
wait did we ever find out why the crew
want
[Music]
it so I'm not forgetting
okay time to go back to the warm Hawaii
oh no oh no
[Music]
for
it [\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
this gets me
pumped but I also feel like I need to
take this all in
like oh it's not dinner it's just drinks
I thought we're going to have at least
one dinner
together [\h__\h] beer
[Music]
damn that's a
lot bit
[Music]
expensive looks like a boy right now
cute boy oh the
smile
a so many
clicks why can't we all sit together
[Music]
a
nice
T
ooh a
a so clicky
though a these poor people they work so
hard and they got to sleep on the
[\h__\h]
floor
[Music]
concrete at least each one has something
like a
pillow and a
blanket honey
[Music]
can you
g why where'd she go got somehow oh wait
okay so we're going to look for we're
going to get one a on scene with her now
okay okay I got to find her okay oh is
she on the roof go have that talk it
says it says go have that talk behind uh
the chest
that talk all
right that kind of talk there it is I
thought I'd have to run for the city to
find
her okay she's just on the Roof then oh
more more cutcenes that are so much to
take in is he going to say it but you
said I have to get ready to to be angry
at him again is he going to [\h__\h] it up
again
is she oh she's not at the
top she not at the
top
[\h__\h] she's just [\h__\h]
there he's
so he's so
embarrassing he's drunk yeah he is
oh left me on
[Music]
unread she looks cter than usual
it reminds me of
someone oh they're so nervous
[Music]
don't announce
it just say it
[Music]
now M cattle
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait is this is this a death flag
speee
[Music]
I can't I
can't oh she going to give her like like
leadership thingy to
her
[Music]
a don't call me a
oh
man wholesome
[Music]
overload
can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I
can't
oh be
careful be
careful no more
lesbian be careful okay be
careful no more lesbian
no
more oh my oh
she
no really so in future games will never
go there
again
what
what that was a like playground for so
many games
right oh oh oh oh I thought it was
peeing whoa
whoa she
oh is he going to go
Bal
no did he change his hair I can't
tell I think he did
right I think it
[Music]
did he look so
different are you
okay wow he's so motivated K is so
motivated wow even his shoes are silver
or light gray I don't know about that I
feel like they should have been
different color but
okay wow no more reunion now is re
disbandment okay I'm not going to do it
I'm not going to do
it could have been
better
goodbye Japan
[Music]
goodbye
damn that was so
much so many
emotions maybe I should make it M cattle
video doesn't always have to be animals
right if I can make such a good cattle I
I swear that was like I just I just that
was the only noise I could produce in
that moment I was not able to
speak it's kind of empty where are we is
this not is this the usual
Beach usual room usual
Beach the oh there it is the famous one
and only point of no
return
wow time to clean out all the substance
hell no
this is the final
warning double check your gears and
skills and we are ready for the final
dungeon dungeon oh you don't mean the
okay for a moment I thought you meant
the Hawaii dungeon I think my gears in
everything is fine but this will be the
last period of free time available in
Hawaii it is recommended that you
replenish your healing items and save
your get yeah I'll check my items if you
advance the story from here you cannot
complete any unresolved uh subsidies or
drink link so don't leave anything
unfinished
yeah it's okay
um guess of dond Island uh yeah I'm I'm
sorry
I you know this is already going to take
a long time so I'm not going to work on
any of the side stuff anymore I'm sorry
uh if you would have liked to see more
of that but that is up to you if you
want to see more then I think that's a
good opportunity for you guys to get the
game yourself and complete everything
you feel like you're
missing and you know you know this game
is
already long as hell on its own so I got
to you know make it compact as a
streamer you already 100 pered it well
that's great then I hope you don't
expect me to do the
same and my my weapons I think are fine
[Music]
gear I mean I don't
see oh yeah you you're whatever oh he's
got the wizard set oh that's not even
bad
wow should I take it from
him willpower buff at the start of your
turn
but I mean they all they
all n everybody except
Cho chosa doesn't have her own armor yet
I guess she's going to get it
soon oh yeah that was a nice sub Story
the one we
did the
one this has no special effect should I
at least like take this H not this this
one syet
oh yeah I'll find hers I thought
[Music]
so did I
switch no you just took it from there
[Music]
low is the damage taken when
guarding that
is
good should I just give her the full set
for now I she has the old
weapon ah yeah cuz
uh wait did I
not the fights with
Dwight could I have done that with this
and I didn't
OMG OMG I could have done even more
[Music]
damage
I
okay um items I think I have like a good
amount of
everything if I'd remember where the
sandwiches are from I'd buy B more but I
have
this I have
these I have this
big I have a lot of the smaller ones and
I have I I might want to buy some
alcohol yeah that's the one thing
because I like to combine the alcohol
ones with the smaller ones to get the
drunkenness go away these are these are
actually Overkill
like even this already is a little bit
Overkill how how when am I going to use
this oh also I it would be nice to have
okay what we might want to
do I don't know if you guys think it's
necessary but what I might want to
do is
um get some of those fruit cups and teas
te's actually I think I'm good on those
I have five I think oh no no wait maybe
I don't actually I don't I don't have
five do
I um wait I want to maybe get some fruit
and stuff to get a few
more oh is it closed right
now know I got to sleep so we can listen
to One Bond link I
guess I'm
overpreparing okay I just want to make
like one okay it will save our but just
one just one fruit cup would be nice if
I can make one that's the HP for all we
might need
it you're not looking at the
team what do you
mean what do you
mean what what do you
mean you just mean because Tommy isn't
there there oh that's okay that's okay I
mean I would have done that
eventually I was
aware ah oh the bond is just with him ah
I know what one okay okay okay okay what
do you want I already did like all of
your
story what do you
want wait why are you here
didn't
she wa didn't she run
off why she my
team didn't she run oh wait she already
did that and that was when we were still
in Japan right then we flew
to happen
so I thought we'd have to go and save
her for
[Music]
T the
tacy
fore spee
[Music]
oh what a service we're getting Uber
today
now I kind of want a
sandwich the tackles got to
me
Jeff
for
foree
fore foree
[Music]
you concerned us you worried
us
[Music]
for
spe
[Music]
Brothers for
that's how you going to start a
fight
understanding you're so late with that
news
for is
it oh
[Music]
no bring it bring it
on they just really can't help but put a
fight every single corner of the
street level 3 free oh I feel
[Music]
bad why are we having her fight against
them oh come
on Rian perfect oh my
God no we we should have mercy I can't
just not have mercy oh he's weak to
water oh here's some tuna
oh
God yeah
this oh he's already he's already
stepping back he's like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] my oi is hurting me
I appreciate how far you would go to
protect your
lady Butler no you were not
[Music]
strong I wonder if he would have felt
more strong if we were lower
level but
like what can I
do foree
[Music]
yeah they would be low
level no matter
[Music]
what she's a
to
not
like uses blackmail material now against
her like maybe she's not so important to
him anymore but he's very very evil and
just for fun it seems like he would you
think he'll do it now
oh you probably know you probably know
maybe he forgot maybe there was just so
much other plot to get through
first like what if he just doxes her can
you
imagine like he has other blackmail but
what if he what he does is like he doxes
he says this vtuber is
her and blackmail the other stuff too
okay we'll see we'll see we'll see we'll
see
I mean you could also think that maybe
she's really
[Music]
not oh really oh
a good
[Music]
part is it you
Grandpa must be you
[Music]
then for
I think the Cheeto said Bond stories are
the
most important to the plot and
interesting
anyway so it's good that we're doing
[Music]
these
for
[Music]
fore
for he thinks he's Putin or
something do I deserve this one is that
funny is what I said funny I think it
was
[Music]
funny something about
Bears what was that like something like
he rode on a bear I don't [\h__\h]
[Music]
know who
f
for foreign
speech foree speech
what are you here
for yeah same fore
[Music]
oh
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice she'll chain attack down
enemies more often let's go rest
assured no
well that was
that I I wanted to say something but I
forgot what it
was we're going to go to the beach now
get one fruit cup and then I'm going to
go hopefully hopefully I can get one
food
cup excuse me
please but probably not honestly cuz I
need if I'm lucky the one of the fruits
they're s selling daily will be the one
that I
need we'll
see what I can make it in the
bar but maybe I can't buy the fruit I
might need to buy
one wait where is it yeah
that oh hello
richardo well hello
there passion FR okay okay okay wait
for my 21st
birthday are
super
coconut okay what are you looking at no
no
no what are you staring at what are you
staring
at I would have liked something that's
not a coconut
there's other what there's others other
Fruit
markets knock it off with the
SC Not staring I'm not
staring I really did not want to see
anything hey you guys look
weird wait where is it where am I where
am
I
ah these [\h__\h] are so confusing to
me God damn it want
go oh wait daily
fruit uh nah not the [\h__\h] water
Melon No I probably don't have
enough I
do oh even for the better one the best
one what oh cuz of the mysterious fruit
and it doesn't have like
mango but it has the
pineapple oh
wait if I had a [\h__\h] ton more coconuts I
could make another one of
these what the [\h__\h] is
this
oh nice the fishing was so worth
it 300
part okay
oh that's
amazing thank
you oh let's go that is I'm I'm prepared
I'm so
prepared do you think I'm
prepared what do you think am I
good that's amazing unkillable
now yeah all
right I mean you know if I was playing
this privately I would look at the other
stuff I would I actually would you know
how addicted I am to like getting all
these Hearts all these
bingos I want to get this
one
but it's already almost half 9 p.m.
so sheesh I got to
go okay just run past him no no what are
you
look hey you
there all
right
okay
okay oh I forgot to save it's okay
it's
okay
oh how much longer do you think I need
guys do I need a
snack oh go [\h__\h] yourself
not six you what why are you teasing me
why would you say that why would you say
that 6 to8 you no what in what world do
you live in why are you so
pessimistic nah you joking right please
tell me you're joking most other people
say 3 to 4
hours what kind of sick joke is that
why you laughing was it a joke yeah
thees weren't even so
good depends on the situation I
guess we can use up all our money
now
for attack the
movie is this
a right no real
sh the remote control
CH oh no wait look kind of real
[Music]
punch the mouth is
Big okay he's going to fight like that
with his head on top
okay Tyrant of the
[Laughter]
ties do you want me to use this game
really is it worth it are you saying
it's worth wor it I don't know is it
really worth
it wait where are these weapons
[Music]
here I prefer to do something else
maybe level 46 by the
way one level above
[Music]
us
uh what is
your do you have a
[Music]
weakness he's dancing on the gas tank
whatever that is
we against
[Music]
math well electricity is kind of great
with my final
bat ultimate the ultimate in baseball
bat heroics damages enemies with an
earth shattering slam and applies your
weapons
[Music]
attributes I could do
anything there's too much
choice I want to try
[Music]
this what why are we not on the
ocean is it all my hallucination again
oh okay almost a
thousand okay oh not so
bad I love how just we get some MP heal
out of damage just feels so in your face
you can't hurt
[Music]
me okay
uh ah
uh ah she's so farak
[Music]
ohuh why does it is it the
grapple can't grab them
ah I can't
[Music]
decide it's just all the
same it's kind of all the same can we
get a paralyzation or are you immune to
that a he he does get paralyzed I
[\h__\h] nailed
it yo yo yo yo yo yo ooh you you missed
half of the team cool cool cool cool
kind of close kind of
[Music]
close wa that's like 900 damage in total
or what did that add up
[Music]
h no wait I think was adding up to
539 yeah uh uh uh where are we okay um
[Music]
should I debuff
actually fear fear Fe fear wait
fear
[Music]
Burns
fear I not have it
hm uh let's give it to
her or is there no medicine for
fearing yeah yeah you can't Mo what you
going to do he's shaking I actually feel
bad we shouldn't hurt sharks but he's
hurting me look how Bloody his mouth is
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
agility guys is it better to use the tag
team always when I'm on ichan or is it
okay to use them on the others you know
what I mean
[Music]
oh sh oh I can't what about this
one I
can't too bad
[Music]
okay why is there a shot for boss fight
don't question it don't question it
[Music]
oh sick damage oh let's go let's
[Applause]
go only when the whole team has I don't
know maybe not
necessarily give me
agility got to go
fast nice
fer was a good idea how long is it going
to go
on or was this the last already wait
when I do this do I get a little like
icon over Tommy so is it gone now did I
is it gone should I do it
[Music]
again actually that's not even worth it
he's so
weak maybe he wouldn't be so weak if he
actually got to attack but
huh the higher your current HP the more
damage but his dark technique damage you
as
well thanks for the wa we are having a
weird
fight sharks this
big I think only
existed long long long long time ago
right this is not realistic hi toonic
what
wow
weak but I need
[Music]
MP need
MP too
[Music]
bad I'd like to do something flashy
but let's get drunk or no take a
[Music]
too and
then uh
God damn it God damn it these fast boys
are way too fast for me nice block
W oh wait I
see I should have noticed because I
didn't get to fight with him at all he
finally came back he's not scared
anymore
that took him a while I didn't even
realize now I feel
bad oh this is so
easy still not his turn next is her then
I'll heal with her
oh that's it that's
it
[Music]
okay okay shark fin now we get the shark
fin well I'm not even surprised that is
very
fitting J defeated with the
jawbreaker no I was
I was ready I was bored
ready in the past three and a half years
I've observed charts a
lot and
learned how to work with
them to my advantage now
yeah that would make sense
[Music]
what what is he saying that the purpose
the plan is to send all the Yakuza there
but have them eaten by the
shark the plan isn't to get to n Island
no okay okay that's not the plan okay
oh just to keep the people away
okay damn how does the shark know which
people are good and which people are bad
I guess they have a different
route we found it I found land
n Island
discovered this is my Island
now I'mma take it away from you
[Music]
guys wait why is he wearing
that the story forced me to
get new clothes
we're so
confident the proper hero attire
you're telling me we're going to spend
three hours in here
sorry I didn't hear the last
one something T
[Music]
right here we go fight fight fight fight
fight fight beat your whole
ass I'm hungry
oh don't
move I almost got everybody only one
left
out OU sh
good AO e though
right ow what
[Music]
[\h__\h] no time to
waste
die yeah you suck by the way I'll kill
you before you can take your pill
[Music]
you got to just
stand I will be the end of
you too bad that before they
die they will never come to their
senses they'll die stupid as [\h__\h]
your and using count mates for these
little
fights I mean I could but not
every would I not actually run out of
money I don't
know maybe not
[Music]
okay I might do that
then oh there's a church is thing oh wow
wait that looks actually kind of crazy
already from here look really
detailed BR is just lingering there
waiting like it looks like that Tower is
where we we're headed hopefully not
beheaded just heading there not beheaded
ah
okay this is so RPG
[Music]
let me just quickly run and turn on the
the oven for the
bread just really
quickly my ass hurts
okay was that so loud don't worry I
didn't drop anything
oh he's in a rush just like me he's in
[Music]
a Bring It On
oh only only
[Music]
five oh wait uh oh I thought I was on
ichun for some
[Music]
reason I'll make quick of
them don't worry don't worry ni follow I
need to see more of those more those
follows please
[Music]
making F of
me join
KF yeah we should just tell them the P
stands for
Pana maybe then they'll join us
go ahead
all they're so stupid
anyway we can totally manipulate them
[Music]
right let the bodies hit the floor
uh what song was
that a Lady song What
name
save it's just saving brain
cells oh bodies by Drowning Pool aha
never heard of that oh there's mines on
the ground I got to disarm
[Music]
them that's easy walk around you even
see them so
easily don't St on them
okay just means don't run
through it's
okay
oh oh so the the the the barrels can
touch
it it wouldn't it like normally
[Music]
oh F that really scared
me I can't even defend myself but
wouldn't the the barrels normally
uh
indeed
the make it go off as
well wow what's with you
[Music]
depends on the weight it would make them
all go up yeah probably uh okay I'm
ready does it have to be the expensive
one I guess I can avoid
it they're not even
[Music]
dead what
oh that was underwhelming well it still
kind of helps I guess so it's
okay you better
just skip it all please left or
right
oh oh there's a safe thingy yay
yay there we go oh wait that's for jungi
isn't it
need for
him
right I I'll I'll let him wear it
though yeah looks fancy though all those
armor artworks look really flashy
nice
what what that's a that's a that's a
trap let me
try oh
what why did I burn just because I I
picked up the the lava
Crystal from in between oh the the
candles there was a mine oh right in
front of
it they did bait
me what are you looking at I'll kick you
down or
not wait they were so busy did I have to
fight
them uh
oh my my oven is
ready he
made have to oh Dam
it thought they were going to attack me
anyway
[Music]
that was
good they seemed to have
been affected by it more than the
previous
ones all right all right all right all
right quick
business I saw it but it was too
late hey
[\h__\h] y now
how should I end
you
funny like why does eachone keep on
losing oh HP why does he have such low
HP and now I just realize oh keep
through the
landmines he is such a
dork but that's what I love about
[Music]
him
totally buts come up
don't miss save
[Music]
save
oh where
but I went this far for [\h__\h]
seaweed I don't need your stupid
seaweed [\h__\h] Divine water actually
pretty good 100 180
MP did I miss
a a
safe I got one
died we saw W oh my God another wave
thank you yo you guys have no idea
yesterday I was literally a jail
bird bird in jail but then I'll let you
die Unleashed myself I flew
out I just un jailed
myself is that
easy if you ever need help to get out of
jail let me know I can help you
that and all kinds of
things s spoilers spoilers well right
now not necessarily we're probably just
going to have a million fights right now
until there danger for
spoilers but yeah unfortunately just the
last stream of this
game so
yeah maybe a little
bit why are they so strong
you're going to just stand there get out
of the
way stole half of the Stu in the jail
it's so cool hi
very that was actually oh what am I
doing that was actually so much fun
yesterday oh they're really strong
she went to rest her
boys see rest in
[Music]
peace does anybody ever say that in a
different
[Music]
context yo they're actually strong
that's why it's only two people
pepperoni is this Blood N the
[Music]
pepperoni we have stolen so many Souls
with Tommy right now you going to just
stand you may think he's a colleague of
Mor how dare you P that blood
her successor
perhaps I guess he steals them she reaps
them that was a
joke y
oh I
think easier to get there from the other
side
rainbow what
these what who should
I what is this rainbow
[Music]
hat a mysterious hat filled with every
color
imaginable cute it's a bucket hat too oh
oh it gives a lot of uh magic stuff
should I give it
to Tommy
he already has the wizard hat though my
eyes it's a very good hat
yeah all right you'll get oh wait I
didn't see we had this one
too he
yo do you want the wizard hat what's
this no it's
good I keep on running into them
I in the beginning I was like haha this
is going to so easy you guys are
just wasting my time you don't even have
to explain
the the traps I I don't what the point
but yeah turns out
um turns out they're a little bit
Troublesome why did I do that because I
want to immediately go to
this this is how you get Ichiban to do
the first turn number Ichiban
oh
big
big what's with you how dare she didn't
how dare she take the first turn from
Ichiban it's in his name he's got to be
number one oh we have a little boss
[Music]
here you think I'm a fool
just try yeah it's good to have the
pound M although this one was was that
one even on datan I think this one we
got on our own
no was
that
sheesh he might be strong
oh he's strong yeah the oven after this
fight I'm going to go put the bread into
the oven
[Music]
okay
nice jawbreaker Thro
nice
skills that looked more powerful than it
actually was you disappoint me every
single
[Music]
day
hello are you back
I thought the chat was dead but uh all
of OBS were
dead for a moment I was confused
hello hi guys hey
guys oo so 8 to 10 minutes can you guys
keep
count now it's 7
to oh no it's it's it's it's
7 is this music really fitting
he spot a
scratch
for a child
she won't fight us
[Music]
right this is sothy
I don't trust the child
e out
for they're going to help us they didn't
get the memo did
[Music]
they it's a trap or or they didn't get
the
memo
for even here they just they just speak
Japanese to each other
[Music]
ooh we can see
the church Castle thing properly
now ooh we're so close what are you
going to provide
healing jumbo egg let's go and chicken
cute so many you grow your own
food so many beautiful chickens
oh cow
move Jo this is how your cow is going to
look like one
day hope you stay for dinner you freak
me
out I'm fine I have my
bread chto set Dr
finally that looks
nice yeah what does it do recover and
pee when you receive a b
H okay it looks
nice I wish she was actually wearing
that like on her
character that would look so
good such a
waste the sage praised my drawings I'm
going to be an artist when I grow
up
M you better leave this island then
then you might have better
chances which of you have been injured
you should treat them quickly now should
we get JY treated in the
shed uh oh does it trigger an
[Music]
event I don't know if I'll get my hands
on this
otherwise oh what what are these sick
RGB
shoes I see I see we're getting all
kinds of RGB stuff
now wait is it also
like uh oh okay
agility I'll take
[Music]
them yeah I think it's time for him to
also switch shoes
y o more Divine b
h might actually take it or are they
going to heal me if they're like I mean
n they probably are they are they is the
game going to heal
me cuz I want to heal my
mp what if does somebody know if you get
healed
here when jungi gets fixed up if he gets
fixed up at all how many minutes have
passed no we're probably there soon is
there a healing station here maybe but I
don't really even need it I just need it
for my mp and I have this feeling that a
battle is going to
happen
so yeah I'll I'll just give myself a
little bit
[Music]
spin seven
minutes
H okay let me check the
bread I'll might make the sandwich right
away and then I'll be
[Music]
back
for
for for
I'm B
snacked on some cucumbers
already okay smaller smaller sandwich
with some cheese some pepponi kind of
thing cold cuts and the Cucumber I hope
we have a cut scene now so I can devour
this partially
does this mean I'm going to get healed
for
real if you heal me I'm going to be so
[Music]
mad they're burning it down
no
way these bastards
This Can't
Stop we fought a huge [\h__\h]
shark come on
everybody
go
easy for
[Music]
I'll jump your body into
the that was kind of a weak attempt of
them better kind of
lame y this is so good yum
also can they please stop wasting my
time oh wow stop wasting my time and let
me go straight to Bry please we all know
that's where we're heading we all know
that's where I'll end up
[Music]
at
wow they started a fire today are you
scared they probably start many many
many fir
today they are cry
people we have to destroy
them what is the meaning of
life wow do you want a serious
answer oh oh this maybe that's the
meaning of life I'm super straighted but
to some people only 420 is the meing of
life or 42
yeah either way whatever you want really
up
feel oop I missed no I could have been
dead
[\h__\h] no
probably have cat hairs in the sandwich
cuz I tried so hard to make it fast
[Music]
that's not
important I don't
differentiate in that
way but probably smoothie hairs cuz hers
are smaller and less hard to
notice um
sorry brains
though
um
[Music]
uhy is the fire
why oh that's weak
[Music]
it'san time to waste some money
oh there's one strong one among them
it's the bald one it's always the bald
ones
guys be
careful it when lag I I 100% should have
gotten that prompt
right it was
lagging so mean
I think the house the fire maybe is
making the game lag what do you think
could it
be
yes God Dam it lazy Divine Nation for
tells the Doom future oh my God can we
sit down have some tea and like Doom
post together I totally dig that I would
love that right
now hey it lag again it doesn't take my
input so
annoying [\h__\h] this leg
no
really fore
don't say he's not here
okay for
oh oh I forgot about that she
remembered all of you for
probably
[Applause]
foree
fine
okay
fore
fore fore
[Music]
that poor boy he has no
father no prob
[Music]
where's he going to
go h
foree foreign fore
foreign mmm
[Music]
is there going to be a
heal H maybe
not ah okay I'm
done M that was good smaller smaller
sandwich but very very
good m
good
point near the entrance to the camp
there should what I
what
huh I hear wow that's pretty
[Music]
hidden at least it healed my mp
damn sounded really yummy it had a great
crunch I like these breads that you can
bake in the
oven finish baking them so it's like
quany and warm
m going to make one for dinner too
probably cuz I have nothing else
oh oh they're all like fighing each
other are they
suiciding
why what's happening
yeah that seems like a cult thing to
do how do you know we
speak how does he know
okay hope you're ready to
die how do they always know that we
hongo
actually what do you think can we get
them
all with one
call you
here's my number so call me
maybe yeah okay we got them all in one
[Music]
go it might be a little bit boring this
way but I think we're all okay with this
are
[Music]
we I could have
got getting all for all right all right
you're okay with it right yeah just run
oh oh my how can you do this to me you
know I'm
hungry
he he is torturing me
[Music]
psychological warfare there
put ah yeah yeah okay I'll do that I'll
do that sounds
good oh does he have
a it lag holy mother of legs
what restart my PlayStation or something
this is
crazy frame rate strling too yeah here
and there a little
bit going stand there
huge lag my input is just not registered
at
all
W when I miss I miss but I swear I
should have been I I'm pretty
sure
[Music]
overheating oh it feels normal
it's
okay you're going to be fine you're the
last one have you're and you're taking
us right to Bry yeah you
better are you really
really is
time no way these people would rather
kill themselves than to lead
us to Bry and trouble him
no what untypical what's with the cold
Fe there's something you
uh-huh uh-huh I know he already took the
pill or so probably he's dying now no
no okay never mind it's a
trap you shall never set your wicked
Eyes Upon Our stage the local Guardian
has blessed us with Divine protection
your ultimate fate is to offer yourself
up as sacrifices don't care if it's some
guardian or Madame Nell herself nothing
can protect your stage from what's
coming well no choice but to move
forward
and another a little
dungeon no
problem easy we're going to zoom through
this is it RGB
again no top grade Mas that's Talk of
the time special prot
no what's
next maybe another shark
this place looks cool and what's the
Trap here this getting creepy and
creepier maybe we ought to take five in
the room we're just add in case oh he's
warning me
again no I'm
good I'm ready to go but I wonder if the
if the mask is a sign that we might need
it give us a cold all the
time weak sh
again really
oh wait it's something very different
let
Leia okay this is going too
far what are you
doing those tentacles better never touch
my
Cheeto what's going on there's free
enemies what is this
can I uh get both perhaps
[Music]
no no grapples either well that's
okay maybe a b first
you know there was something suspicious
that uh ichan said on the
boat about like haha no way
like no way what did he say like
something
like no no way he could like use magic
or whatever
like oh oh that's what
uh also the tentacles
okay
now now I'm wondering
maybe yeah it's a tame a shark maybe
that's like maybe that joke was
actually rather close to
reality but I just generally feel like
this is not that type of
game I mean we're hallucinating at all
oh ooh oh nice but even with the
hallucination I feel like they wouldn't
cross that but maybe they will maybe
they
will go Tommy go Tommy go Tommy let's go
Tommy go Tommy go Tommy go Tommy
strength yay wa that's
cool H only 700 in 9 what the
[\h__\h] Aqua breath I am honored to be
breed upon by Aqua seai please
more that's his weakness I thought it
was
fire good stuff good stuff is he going
to bring back his tentacles maybe after
50%
electricity I thought it was fire I
misremember whoa
[Music]
it doesn't say
weak but oh
[Music]
well it would be stronger with a
merciless
melee these supposedly strong attacks
are not this strong after all
do you even have a jaw let's see let's
check that was leg I
think oh she's blinded oh
no uh what do I need to heal can she
heal herself if she's
[Music]
blinded yes you
can okay okay come on wa can we for one
going to
Triple
no [\h__\h]
man oh regeneration how
much ah okay that's what you mean with
regeneration okay no problem no problem
no problem uh oh two of them okay okay
okay okay yeah that's exactly what I
said was going to happen so
[Music]
[Applause]
oh she's so blinded oh
no
ah I'm going
to we don't have that thing anymore that
heals them all right
[\h__\h] she has a
a cold right and
blindness well I I'll say let's get rid
of the
blindness don't know how important that
was but you know why
not oh that could get n Maybe not maybe
that wouldn't get all of them
H aha this tentacles weak to electricity
all
right okay okay okay the tentacles
really aren't so
bad maybe a little bit of these oh he's
blind though please don't
miss he can't miss right with this he
can't I don't think he
can the
taku
taku he a squid not a tacle different
things
right octopus and squid close enough
it's it's
a it's a distance
family of oh no oh dear oh these debuffs
oh
[\h__\h] I wish I had sat right
now oh cute miror Dimension Ena he
a disgusting what I do I should probably
heal
[Music]
actually ah I think I wait I think I
figured it out it's not that he um
something that the dude knows how to use
magic what the
[\h__\h] um I think the reason why he's able
to so to say control all these big ass
what the
[\h__\h] animals what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what what the
my my freaking fun came with me what the
actual [\h__\h] so what I was going to say
this is not happening your
playr did I miss a
prompt and ended up in here what the fu
wait I'm
too baffled I can't I can't give you my
my theory my game
theory okay but okay my my game my game
Fury is
that um it's not like he's controlling
them it's that he is you know uh
dropping all that um
uh uh uh what's the word Atomic not
Atomic what's the word that trash the
from the nuclear the nuclear trash or
whatever he's dropping it in the in the
ocean the nuclear waste yeah and that
makes the animals in the water
aggressive that's why they're bigger
than usual and more aggressive than
usual oh my God I [\h__\h] figured it out
yeah it's mutating them that makes so
much holy [\h__\h] my big brain solved it a
little bit too early
get
it that just Fallout lore what no that's
going to be it I'm
[Music]
sure I'm so
sure H Tommy too bad I can't he Tommy
will we when it's Tommy's turn are we
switching into the
belly I'm ironically fall oh my God then
I don't need to play the game anymore
right I we figured it
out I already know it all I know it all
Tommy can you come out now maybe I I
shall slit the throat and then he will
come out
no
um I might actually do that I don't
know oh no I want to raise my agility
again
[Music]
what it just feels like um ni I didn't
do anything I still get a turn right
that was not part of my
turn uh this feels very
[Music]
um
uh what's the game what's the game we
played with uh oh my God I'm [\h__\h]
around like uh the game we played with c
and Nissa and
p b
g this this is just Ballers gate to me
right now oh my God stop
shaking stop
shaking
lag dear Lord the agility is [\h__\h]
can I raise my agility uh was that a
thing
no all
right oh
no the final episode
yeah kind of expected that to happen
no grapple
right I don't know she doesn't seem to
have a
weakness but he's also not resistant so
let's do the the
[Music]
tuna well I'd love to have played the
whole thing but in a group it's just
difficult especially when it's such an
international
grip um I think if I would have played
it solo I would have probably finished
it well that would have been a long play
through especially cuz I I really
enjoyed like looking at all the
details in that
game would have taken me a
while could have had it as like a Skyrim
Style game now I wouldn't want to pick
it up again now I feel like this is like
it would be so out of
nowhere
um but yeah maybe one day you know when
I have too much time in my
life I might play it
privately I think I will really it's a
great
game and it's really great when you have
a lot of
time I
am very looking
forward to that
future when I can play that game finish
it for real for real but then uh I still
need your
help I need your
[Music]
help oh no not again what
not at the very
[Music]
end so
annoying why must you do this to me
[Music]
does this
no oh doesn't work anyway um might do
beach beach side
Prof go for the kill I might be able to
but I don't want to risk it oh I want do
the tentacles die if the squid dies they
have to
right they have to wait he's bleeding
he's bleeding
this is the
one prom
do did it die before the promt
inut and hey yeah the tentacles went
down with the main uh
body why did attack have no prompt
or
dead I don't remember using that attack
before so
anyway what the
[\h__\h] what the hell was that everyone all
right yeah apart from being covered in
squids not you so that was their faved
Guardian huh not the nicest thing to
believe in and I'd rather not deal of it
again let's hurry up and get going
H I'm sure we'd all love that too but
the path's
blocked
swim oh yeah we are swimming
home but it's
radioactive
probably you mean we have to get into
that Lake that thing won't pop up again
right if it does we just knock it out
again it gets uh under the ocean and
then back up again we a never going to
knock it down
oh
oh tentacles right oh no I feel like at
least one of these is those
tentacles but I don't need them
anymore there they
[Music]
are beautiful sapply
water oh you
know if they dump it anywhere here in
this island around the island I'm
sure that it spreads
in ooh in quite the
distance water moves after all as
well I will stay with my Fury oo
medieval knights that looks like a
phoenix on the
armor who should I give this to do we
even need us
do we even need
it wait we swam but like oh over
there ah if someone is missing an armor
if I missed it I guess there's a chance
you miss
it how I feel like they' have been very
obvious but you could miss it I guess if
you play with one eye closed
can I get a
heal surely you you'll heal me somewhere
right game before you let me move on to
Bryce CH oh CH got it very
recently half an hour
ago oh hello
come I'll turn you into a fish
[Music]
face you know what's going to happen
guys wait it's only free right
now bring the
[Music]
others bring the others
why hi he's blue what do you
mean kak on
speed
people I don't even know how to use
speed di oh outfit
is I wouldn't even know you think I'm a
fool
only
two I'm being
sabotaged this game is sabotaging
[Music]
me you all saw it was going to hit four
people
thanks for swooping into the
Zone welcome to the
[Music]
O area 05 I prefer area
E15 is that what it was
called I say it right
there it is there's the
heal
[Music]
15 this might be the last for Ichibon
right let's go
[Music]
do not have mercy on him holy
[\h__\h]
for oh
yeah for
hi no let's bring him straight to to
grave yard
old before
[Music]
before in
his own
tox I like
that I want to know why
[Music]
how he became a cult
leader
god well some kind of God
[Music]
he doesn't give a
[\h__\h] we're different me and
him psychopath I want to know why he
became a Psy
shut up I won't let him say that
[Music]
well maybe I don't
I would
[Music]
think
huh huh
nice excuses yeah it's their choice Yeah
well yeah but
[Music]
the problem is once you're in there's no
easy way out of a
cult all the manipulating and mind
breaking brainwashing
starts once you're in
[Music]
uhuh maybe
that's a
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's Mafia ex Mafia
no maybe not
y y y y yep yep
y y y y y
[Music]
in a place like this filled of all this
[\h__\h] I Aspire the same thing
this is like a ticking Time Bomb this
place imagine if someone drops a bom
from an airplane down on this
island happens
gu this is underground I wonder if it
would be
safe maybe it would be
safe yeah earthquake earthquake could be
enough be plenty to mess this up
for
spee
spee fore
[Laughter]
yeah can I beat you up now
huh
for so you killed him
[Music]
right oh for
oh we only saw
that but dear I did want to talk about
[Music]
Pryce fore
yeah probably
yeah oh he's angry
roll eyes so
[Applause]
good can we fight now
yeah
please I don't give a [\h__\h] about you N I
only care about
n here we
go show us that beautiful
back and I will fight back with n's
Divine
ref let's make this
quick I need to finish kido's chapter
P
Warriors why did they make the last
chapter just one chapter they could have
split it in two chapters if we even
split it uh changing locations
too what's the
point of making just like two chapters
in one
chapter maybe they're maybe they
couldn't count
anymore all
right looking good with no cloes on
top it's run it's
run can we get them all in one go please
please please
please would be too easy right oh no
actually okay there's just one that's
stronger than the
others okay here we go guys here we
[\h__\h]
go what's your weakness is it water it
is
water
yeah cute girl best
girl oh bath bup yo recently I've been
taking so many baths with bath
bombs because you know know that time I
told you I went to the spa with my mommy
recently turns out I forgot
all all like my my shampoo and my my
shower
gel now I shampoos but that was my only
gel so these days I've just been taking
bath bom
baths cuz I have so
many I just have so many of them
so many like from Gib I also have a lot
of uh bathrooms that are supposedly
expired I don't believe in the
expiration and I I even look it up like
uh like should the expiration on the
bathrooms be taken seriously and I was
like no you can still like use it even
months
later but then I
wonder what's the
point what's the point of the expiration
date
oh dear they're too far
apart apparently yeah honestly all Rush
uh ah damn it only two all Lush
products okay the
fck like have pretty early expiration
dates from what I've
noticed what is he
doing over
there oh
wait uh oh
well that is a
grapple but I don't think it
matters
nice the expiration I don't think it
matters so I I've been using it and it's
been fine so
far yeah maybe but there's nothing that
should actually like go bad as in like
molding or so maybe some Sands will just
be less
strong I
think does this count as a new fight can
I call
again can
I I guess wait maybe it doesn't count as
any fight because we didn't get the
EXP
ah um then something like
this oh
[Music]
just a bit faded yeah and oh normally
you know I'm a shower type of
person just because when I sit on the
bathtub I'm like what the [\h__\h] I'm so
bored what do I
do
but
more even with the i and watching stuff
on the iPad even then I get super bored
but actually these past days they have
been pretty relaxing and I've been
staying in the bathtub for like 20 to 30
minutes
[Music]
even so I think I'm becoming more and
more of a bath person
[Laughter]
sheesh I'm so
good use the time to relax and
thing I think too much all the
[Music]
time now my bathtub after each bath I
have to clean it because those B bath
bombs especially the Lush ones they
leave so much
glitter so much
[Music]
glitter you would take naps and
B I I wouldn't to me it's not that uh
comfortable uh Jordan or gram
Graham
weakness why is there so much glitter
don't ask
me ask
Lush but they make nice bath boms
they're so fancy I like
them yeah you shouldn't do that be
careful guys some fall asleep in
bathtubs unless they're empty
oh
more oh
no oh no another
one
oh well there he goes wasn't much of a
concern was not a big
concern for real
yo I'm playing for real yo
something Wai for real yo oh for real
for real we need a band
a I always have
Band-Aids but I'll just wrap you in a
[\h__\h] ton of toilet paper like a
mummy I'll mommy rise you
alive like being buried
alive close enough
oh you want to be okay
wow how how how how does a human brain
mind become like
this how can you be so
susceptible yeah it's really not rare I
know insanity
[Music]
stop running away why the [\h__\h] are you
guys all so far
[Music]
away didn't even get a heal after all of
this well whatever oh it doesn't even
count as a new fight either I cannot get
the the the
cheap thing and
you going have some
fun
get little
B Des for sense of purpose yeah that's
also what I learned
in
documentaries that's what I've heard
some f
why you why you so
lonely why you such a
loner you're
fin the money won't transfer
[Music]
game
over
ow ow you going to just stand
there okay okay enough now enough enough
you're going to just stand there
your your ass is
gr are
Heist what is
weakness grass grass
[Music]
your
is uh
so can of want to go to
ichang and make a little call
[Music]
now okay that's
fine got to spend the money I guess oh
you you
back you guys need to stop panicking
you're usually back right away after a
moment you got to stop
panicking go here
no ah
okay yeah if your YouTube lags close the
chat I don't know if that's still an
issue but oh Bryce is stuned he actually
got stunned from that call that I made
oh let's
go oh she come on you're going to just
stand there
I feel like bosses generally have a
lower chance of getting to debuffs I
might be wrong but that's just how it
feels so I wasn't even I didn't even
have high hopes for
it okay we're going to um do mask of
punishment and mask of fertility first
uh fertility maybe you're going to just
stand there first mask of punishment
[Music]
yeah you would think that you have
higher resistances I assume
so a no he's already
back what each has 999
HP you
this one has so
many of these area attacks
huh he loves AOE
what do you love dude what do
you may inflict bleed let's try come
on
what wait did I do it I did it on The
Wrong
Enemy No wait I didn't it's random
enemies it just went from him to him to
him I
guess I was like for a moment I was like
I'm so stupid no why am I so stupid
Bry is
[Music]
next I wish I could maybe paralyze him
again
or kind of want to try
it oh he's
bleeding oh that will be replaced
H but it failed
anyway well him bleeding profusely is
good for Adai but Adai needs
to get a hold of
himself nice to nice
321 not bad not
bad oh I didn't see because my phone is
right in front of his
MP
um this
[Music]
next time to drink those yummy yummy
copy luu are they still 100 th oh no
it's even more expensive now okay maybe
not that's a bit too
much maybe I still need money for K I
don't
know OMG
OMG okay he's really really buff
he loves using that he loves using his
guns you need a bunch of money for for
real why did you tell me that
earlier why you letting me use all my
money up oh wait but don't they
have wait they have different money
right they have different wallets
right it doesn't
just does it just get uh uh um
like uh exchanged from yen to EUR it's
uh shared money okay okay well then I I
need to be careful
um she's next
okay is this better on the solo Enemy No
I can just
Sol I'm a little bit more careless about
my HP just because I've
noticed he's not he may be buff himself
but he
doesn't
uh he do a lot but he's not not that
[Music]
strong so far he's scaring me that
much just going to take a
while to get this over
with keep
bleeding bleeding please keep
bleeding keep bleeding please
beding beding please
for he is he stn or
paralyzed I'll never know I think it's
paralyzed
right man dude please
recover recover soon please
funny a
no why would you stoping stop
stoping man why didn't you come back one
turn earlier
[Applause]
kind of
[Music]
[Applause]
rude we are so back with
other let see
um is my my fonder isn't happening
anymore right might as well throw a new
one in
okay I'm going to check now do I get a
little
icon
no no I don't how do I know if my
thunder is still happening gu I got to
pay
attention each round if it's happening
or
not fund weapon I think it's good to
have
nice reaction
[Music]
everybody yeah I don't know his
defense never gets
lowered but attack or defense isn't it
sometimes even low in
both what's been doing more damage the
tuna or the
Mele
50% oh okay but I like to keep up uh you
know attack defense very useful
to get
that I'm going to wait for Adai to fill
up his gge and then I'm going to blast
him with tag
team why do only two people have the
heal the heal
buff why does it run out on others
earlier
H I want to do it again but I wonder why
they don't have does he cancel
it R out in their turn okay then maybe I
don't know if I should do it now or next
turn I guess it will run out
now in this very turn
so I guess I could do it now
[Music]
okay we need to make him bleed
power he
yeah that's what I'm talking you talking
about you were so far from
him what are you
doing dorky little
man you know what I'm going to do I'm
going to do a smart thing here I don't
know is smart might be smart I'll go to
Al let him Attack One More Time ich is
next then if he attacks one more time
thenan can do the attack
team just like that and he immediately
gets to act upon the
bleeding all right now we'll see this
attack for real for real oh oh wait what
it was square square square square
square I didn't get the square squ speci
square prompt did did
I when I used this against the
squid huh but yeah here's my smart
move here it is how much will it
[Music]
be
3,300 W that was a huge
chunk that was worth waiting for
actually and we get all those knif
bubs yeah
[Music]
yeah thanks guys thank you so
much yeah that was that was really good
wasn't it
mhm going to just do something super
small
[Music]
small and next
yeah yeah he's almost dead
[Music]
soon soon we'll do our little switcher r
yeah look at all those beautiful PS oh
is it
over
oh prompt incoming uhoh pay attention
get new
face full HP bar oh no okay no we good
ah easy
EAS he's even still bleeding
oh
way oh no he's going down he's going
down what you going to do I it would be
so funny he almost died from
bleeding a that would have been so lame
for
him
ah who said we might not need the
lightning who said is the lightning even
worth
I mean it wasn't
necessary but the lightning wanted to
give you a
message the lightning has left you a
message on your
phone it says
Dr what I can do I can kill
people Jud
[Music]
kind of f with the Divine
punishment as he is a a god apparently
he must be punished by divine
[Music]
intervention
for
Fore for
it doesn't matter if you're
dead but we don't want to bring him to
jail so boring let's just kill
him wait maybe her business that she did
is going
to the thing that she did CH Chan what
Chi Chan what' you do what' you do
oh she got the
[Music]
channel amazing
finally we're using this to our
[Music]
Advance yeah keep on talking keep on
talking
[Music]
Savage R safe
today save the world
[Music]
what if he takes her foot phone and
turns it around and shows
[Music]
her so she's pretty what you going to
do uhhuh got nothing to say now
[Music]
huh oh
speee
Dad I think it's her dad right
[Music]
for daughter
exposing her dad what
[Music]
oh no mercy
he's covering up the
[Music]
camera girl
I was going to
say he really said
go
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah nice chichan
one
more expose yourself Show
Yourself she's going to do it isn't
she
[Applause]
oh I'm so proud of her
[Music]
actually for
I'm proud of her
for not letting them have power over her
for taking it into her own hands
[Music]
[Applause]
she's my
o that's
my the [\h__\h] do you want
huh
yeah that doesn't mean that it's right
I think there's no better way to get rid
of this kind of track I
think this is a good
idea but this is not the way to do
it foree
[Music]
all right
bye no let is
go let him
go
e
spee foreign
[Music]
our local police
officer maybe I'll got his drob bag
no not
[Music]
yet
exactly fourth wall breaking
[Music]
I can't do
it he already did he pulled it
up do I have to upgrade their
weapons what what state are our is our
equipment
then com point of no
return hi
hi well but we're switching him back
right we we are switching him
back
um for now take
this um
[Music]
um one more big dungeon easy is it as
big as the island no problem then that
wasn't even so
bad that was not even so
bad about the same mhm
why do I have this on
him damn so
powerful got to protect him at all cost
so for now I'm going to give him this
but we're going to switch
him
right or contractually obligated to go
back to the Millennium Tower
i b it slightly hot than it one's side
but I think you'll be fine
okay W look we need she has only five oh
God do we have to craft
[Music]
again you know I have to get up in 9
hours at the
latest but I still will would have to
eat one more time
better get to it then uh take
this take
this wizard she's becoming a
wizard oh does she have better
shoes there is so much snot in my throat
now God damn it
[Music]
she needs willpower
right I would
think
40 you're a wizard now no more
Idol oh yeah okay she already has her
seven star
armor I guess the others don't
uh what do you
need ooh give me those
boots no I'm not doing part two this is
already later than I thought we were
going to do the finale
[Music]
nice
okay okay so we
have wait him as well damn it uh he's
got a six-star weapon already okay and
he's got his
armor good good good
[Music]
good oh
wait
okay we're going to change that
[Music]
to what would be good
this can have
that a [\h__\h] snot e okay we need a new
weapon for those
two these two these two and then kidu
just has no weapons right he just has
fists right does he have no
weapons then got a switch it's actually
pretty
close take a tissue no tissue close by
I hope Whatever item we got to make we
can or wait maybe we don't craft maybe
we just buy I don't
know yeah buy one and then
upgrade MH
okay it is time to you are you ready to
return to Dragon of dojima oh he's
actually locked into wearing this
current
one skill
inheritance what are we going to bring
along I like this and I don't even use
this so much you guys like this one but
I don't even like it that
much do we want one of these twoo
they're not that good the heal is pretty
good
though I think Kido has no heal
otherwise right
um and maybe the
buff I don't
know right it's a good buff I think so
too
and the rest stays what they
are then where do I buy these
weapons uh we need an Idol microphone
thingy
uh and assassin right is she an assassin
no is
she God damn
it I don't where is Idol I here I no
she's the night Queen we have an idol
and a night Queen yeah okay okay then we
got to go to love magic which is around
the
corner is this a what somehow I thought
this is the dude that we
saw the one single dude that was
watching the stream alone on his
own he kind of look like him to me right
now
you also fought
that one brain
cell if we're both thinking that way I'm
sure there's many people who fought that
way and then it might just be true might
just be common might just be on
purpose cuz they know maybe we're going
to pass by
here all right
uh this is is the strongest you have
okay back
breaker
sounds perfect for what I'm about to do
and a winked microphone cute too cute
these whole names for her weapons are
too
wholesome too sweet too wholesome too
cute okay and
now je oh she's oh everything's so close
by let's
[Music]
go do you think I need to buy any more
items I didn't even use up so many
healing
items didn't even use my fruit
platter so maybe we're
good
ah yeah no more need it we're good uh
Julie
you're not
Julie you're a faker
impostor mhm I can make it I have four
cough drop tints and I have enough lava
oh I can actually craft it guys okay I
mean I got
to if I can then I got to oh W nice
what about
hers we're just I'm going to make it
we're just missing one lava
crystal that's all I'm making anyway
right Z was
fine one lava I'm I'm going to quickly
get that that's going to be worth it I
think dungeon dungeon dungeon dungeon
dungeon dungeon dungeon
herey two fire weapons yeah I
mean the other one like Z has an icy one
so T has ice and kidu has nothing kidu
just has neutral
fists uh that's from
you no but
I I guess it this from
you oh oh thanks oh huh five star
spatula
cry I'm so excited we can actually craft
something is f a weapon enough well we
have buffed his emotes sufficiently all
of them I think they're all like equally
good now
your brawler blue not I think all of
them do
no can we see
um oh yeah H oh his blue one is the
strongest but the others aren't bad
either Beast for AOE oh okay so
generally blue
okay
[Music]
y uh
here oh that one looks so nice oh
well this is
perfect
yeah oh perfect all right I'm going to
upgrade
it both of them
to 10 as per
usual
brand what would be
good success rate of
debuffs M P up absorption of basic
attacks critical hit
rate I could boost fire attacks but she
normally I don't know if she'll attack
that
much use all the
medals I might I might let me do this
first
though blade attacks gun attacks blond
attacks success rate of stat I think uh
maybe this is
[Music]
okay she's the Healer yeah but like I
don't
know success rate of debuffs
or that would
work buff your I don't know I'm just
going to do this we'll
see and night
Queen yes Queen oh wait I forgot
strengthen okay nice uh
observe brand
uh ooh attacks and weapon skills may
burn
y burn this car
is that a
debuff I still don't
know Flames
X
okay uh are the other weapons also plus
no plus
zero
okay ah
I'm actually missing it I actually don't
have enough okay oh well that's good
that's whatever wait I can exchange some
materials I don't need this
anymore I hope I I hope Namba doesn't
have to
fight cute perfect pause
that should
be
already good
amount let me
check uh who El was ah for
you oh yes
y you can use other medals to upgrade
them they were also on zero
they were all on
zero so confusing to me that ice and
water is like the
same the the water drop to me means
water and not ice attack but anyway okay
is is Kido automatically not wearing a
weapon anymore yeah okay look at his
cute hands are these actually his hands
wow he's a hand model
okay we're going to go we're going to go
no time to
waste uh
car maybe a little bit just a little
bit hands yeah why do people not react
about hands as much as they do with feet
eh do his hands mean nothing to you he
protects you with those
why not TV isn't there like a healing
thing
here did you save no I didn't but I was
do that last time when I went on that
boat but is she paying for SP
is this main
story it's a side thing
thank
you is this a side
C man man ah it's a
[Music]
memoir which aren't the Memoirs just his
side
quests on this side of the
world wasn't there always a healing
thing over here I guess I was just in
like a dragon number
one
Uno thank you
m oh sorry I'm like too rush my brain is
like I got to go I got to go I got to
go millenum Tower
[Music]
not five
hours
hi you miss me
exactly you know we're in this
together oh I didn't equip the weapons
did
I or did they get equ Auto I don't know
are we going straight into a
fight
[Music]
for you guys remember that one from my
fre
deut
oh I'm going to go easy on you guys cuz
half of my team is not wearing the right
weapons you're so lucky
so so
lucky we can't call pound mates right on
T sir can
we certain things I can't do here like
tag
[Music]
uh oh is the perfect time for some
pounding
Banger Al it does sound like a banger
already
oh I wiped out half of them thanks for
[Music]
membership let's let's P it it might not
be worth it but at least I can
probably clean up
a I thought I could get all of them
damn our fists aren't so
strong I'm disappointed
T he's just warming up yeah okay okay
okay
understandable on me I love
her uh it's on you
apparently wait isn't that our
new uh s
has
fire let me
check if they let me do they let
me Jew break is stronger okay okay okay
okay they won't let me check
[Music]
you're not going to say it okay this is
some welcome you ready let's go
oh
so oh
[Music]
oh
nice oh my God please turn off that
sound it's actually kind of bothering me
oh remember our spinning Queen our fun
times
together my one of my best openers
not on my cutie
P what can you hurt an
idol like
[Music]
her she's standing in front of them
she's giving them even a primate
performance like that and they still
hurt her with the
chainsaws wow
[Music]
I have something
bigger not
[Music]
really Al this one's probably
stronger and D they moved already
I forgot it was
twice somehow these fights already like
feel more difficult
than on ichiban's
side wow nice
hit what's this bazooka do doing down
[Music]
here what's this ha you doing down here
what's Booka doing down here same thing
same question
oh that's where that came
from Lev below
them wa I did uh all the free levels of
the dungeon I think on this side as
well
so not much I can do now
[Music]
but I should have
called you think I'll be fine yeah it
was too easy anyway on the other
[Music]
side Mommy's going to be swiming a
little bit
longer does she have better Heels by the
way or is this my best anyway ah K is so
far
[Music]
uh please leave him
alone they're creep creeping up to him
smaller smaller
he should be
enough if this takes 2 hours then I I'll
be done at 2 a.m.
[Music]
yeah no I'm not I'm not
quitting and I'm I'm fine of it taking
longer I'm not exhausted or anything
it's just uh if only I didn't have to
get up so
early if only
[Music]
oh
nice I didn't think it would knock back
to there
[Music]
let leave the stream on well that won't
work we all
know hours maximum sadly kid
you can you stop just being the punching
back right now
please oh thanks for the
[Music]
membership oh checky did I see I see you
sent something didn't you
oh I'll check it
later rocket
launcher
no
no quick quick quick quick now let me
please adjust my weapons I think uh sat
maybe might be wearing the right
no that's the third fight in a
row I mean if they're all coming to me
does that mean that I don't have to run
for the whole building and they'll just
we'll do all the battles
here no no thank
God yeah the chainsaw gu is gone hallelu
Look Who's Back
please help me out here do
something look how little that did
actually these enemies are really kind
of
[Music]
tough don't sh don't sh you just hit is
it okay to really just hit with no
skills is it okay
I guess it did kill a but oh so these
were just the stronger ones yeah you're
right you're right it did kill a couple
of
them yeah
really violently rolls
Nar so he violently
rolles no attacks are mainly okay well
why is your Keo doing so I don't know
actually his level on the blue one is
seven I don't know if this is normal
feels
weak because all he gets all his damage
from levels and you didn't level his job
[Music]
oh okay he'll probably get a lot of
levels after we finally get the EXP from
this fight
oh right oh my God that's not true is
not
[Music]
true I forgot that was a fast boy
H yeah you would think if he has no
weapons
then his base attack has got to be
already strong enough in this class and
then I would think that's true like the
higher his class is the more damage he
does right that would makes sense I
think
um so for
now I'm going
to use some Essences
[Music]
maybe maybe that will help
I [\h__\h] missed but it even so it did a
good damage 500 is good I'm somewhat
happy with
that I did I did as much as I can for
his personality
nice you know maybe it's just his
age maybe it's just his age I give him a
break man
[Music]
ah d uh you don't need to heal that much
so I'm going to oh they're also so far
away from each
[Music]
other come
onoc on killing one enemy it's okay it's
going to be all right
he fighting back he's not taking your
[\h__\h] any
longer how dare you make a man with
cancer
bled I missed it's
okay please let me switch weapons after
this for s at
least please please please please please
please please please
please this one on point
[Music]
he resists
knives oh don't worry about it me being
good at this because I had a lot of time
to practice with son he
you okay please let me take a break game
please or like what do I need to
do need to become a break dancer
that's so bad so so not funny I know I
know how many level UPS did teachers get
didn't pay attention probably a
lot uh
ah no they had their things okay never
mind never
mind well their damage was honestly fine
anyway pretty good
K is the only one worrying me right
now all
right elevator oh look get to take the
elevator
Wow have I been in this area before uh
the in in different L game I don't
remember
this this particular
wait I don't have to fight them but wait
pink is super [\h__\h]
weak right thinkink is uh behind
Red in terms of
strength or was it better a pink is
stronger
oh right right right right in the
dungeon I red was there also at the end
oh
yeah oh not the chainsaw again
[Music]
um I should have used pound Mees first
God damn
it always remember use pound M first
both please them please
triple
yeah can't punch them through the window
unrealistic I mean surely those windows
are very strong but but in this kind of
game you should allow it
[Music]
always in most really in so
many like
[Music]
tradition I love this attack when the
enemies do it because so many times they
just fall backwards it's so funny when
they fail
okay 887 just because these enemies are
less
defensive it's a reference an Easter
egg that poor poor man did you see how
he was laying on the
ground look how dead he
is
oh why the [\h__\h] do we get so many keys
in this
game I'm opening so many
saves who needs shoes
you what do they do
evasion oh right that was
[Music]
evasion but doesn't she also need
agility
should I really switch it I mean it's
five star versus
six-star oh that just made me think of
something do I still have any
magazines gangster cabby housekeeper
no didn't get any new ones wait where
are
we oh I kind of have to didn't have to
run over here I have to get for these
enemies
oh I the the power booster do I
have invasion is better I think it might
be yeah do I have
any wouldn't they be in the same no just
ignore me just ignore me look at their
formation like there's some kind of
dance
cre oh thank
God I would like to see more of that
thank you
what are these ASMR
heads for real for
real oh there's are lamps they look like
those ASMR microphones the cool 100 or
so am I good on money
guys I'm overly
concerned I'm being taken over by the
yeah I'm fine okay I get to sing Lily
Allen and reference to what's happening
in the
[Music]
game a why you not big enough for all of
them
[Music]
okay normal I'll give you another chance
but this is a weapon attack
so it negates the really you did the
map show me the
RE defense down and
fear wor what what does Fear do she can
still attack right seemingly
if I get to sat I'm going to do the
debuff
thingy thank God we have that on
[Music]
here what it kills me when the number
reaches oh [\h__\h] oh like for real oh dear
okay okay okay okay it count as the
status ailment right or is this a DE
bu just disg oh okay it only got rid of
the the curse okay that's the one I
wanted to get rid of the most
[Music]
so
nice
nice this is the only enemy in the game
but will this enemy be in the other
fights too or just this one single
fight good damage okay decent decent
decent
maybe that screwed me bad the first time
I got figur it was just
fear screwed
you were you were you okay did you die
brain too empty to become creative
always use the same
skill whatever
damn we could have killed
him
oh
turn come on I don't have time for
it I don't have time to dance around o
numo a little
safe who needs this
now oh I'll take the
alcohol Ultra flash six
600 electric
damage base damage could be higher right
so that's not
bad oh I remember this curve isn't that
a restaurant here or was that on a
different floor now I remember the
restaurant thing the the curved
restaurant that was in the millenum
tower too right ah uhhuh uhhuh oh yeah
good times good times oh we're in the oh
swi
squ we're in the
restaurant
[Music]
yo I'm behind you
Yeah I broke
everything the enemies are different
though probably right or were they just
suited sadio clan members back then
too drunk
people friend s let's some really game
but also makes people nostalgic yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
honestly I think they're not doing it
doesn't feel so much like
recy that kind of realistic to come back
to places like
this also it doesn't look outdated in
terms of Graphics
either don't they polish
everything a little bit or is just like
absolute same
Graphics I'm not sure I feel like like
both games look really good they polish
it
right areed but the engine is upgraded
every time
oh so that doesn't really polish the
graphics does
[Music]
it I mean at some point they have to
upgrade the graphics they can't be the
same for like eight
games right
[Music]
compar it to zero it looks
better I don't remember like when I
think back of anything like
from 15 years ago or
so like back then the graphics felt the
same as these Graphics feel like now you
know what I mean
right they have the same kind of wow
effects back then because back then
shitty
Graphics were already in and life
changing and
nerving I love that feeling but then you
get back oopsie wow what's going on you
get back to that game maybe 15 years
later and you realize
oh somehow I just broke an illusion of
mine this looked so different in my
memory I don't know if I liked what if I
if I like what I just did with my memory
I ruined
it so I want to go back to like really
really old games that I
liked and and and check if they still
hold up but at the same time I don't
want to be
disappointed yeah not just due to
Nostalgia just to due to the standard
shirts that
were back then normal or already super
evolved
oo look at what a
feast who left that here for
me thank
you the games didn't change really no no
I think the games
changed I think the
changed well our standards changed too
but at that time that was the highest
standard whatever was created
then maybe the standards changed and and
we just evolved in how much we could
polish these games
huh IEM missed I'm sure it wasn't
important unless uh unless it was like
an exclusive armor did I miss an
exclusive armor
oh look at all these s clan members
welcome welcome
welcome n
okay wait didn't did I even put no we
got the one for number and that was it
right that was it I think
[Music]
sat still missing sat is the only one
what about K he's just wearing the night
armor does he not get anything
else as far as I remember he only has
that
one I did do the third floor
I gasl myself
then
H
H well all of this would be even easier
if I have done that huh but doesn't seem
necessary I
see that's how it
is combo attack go combo
ah he's poisoned you good
bro I'm excited to see
you didn't you just watch My Stream
yesterday too
[Music]
yeah I mean another dungeon run would
have been insane especially if the the
boss fight of that one is as crazy as
the Ono one [\h__\h] no leave me
alone not wasting my time with that if
this
[Music]
works oh
oh didn't realize he was going to take
that weapon but okay good night good
night sleep well I wish I could go too
are you in my
[Music]
time but I feel it I feel it it's
already been 40 minutes
so we're like almost halfway through
please don't correct my wishful face
even if I'm very far
off please don't do this to
me more or
l i missed no
no oh
man [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] sh sh
I will know when I'm in the final
stretch this is not the final stretch
this is not the final is the final
stretch final Str started
when the stream started
cover
Fire cover
fire can you guys attack faster oh my
God he's
dying Beach bro be oh they're so far
away
I'm all
[Music]
alone imagine if I just accidentally
died right
now I know I can Target but I wanted to
heal on him more than anything
else y
okay I'll heal the
SAT
[Music]
soon do something got to get some good
AOE come on
die why can't she not heal his cancer
guys why not
[Applause]
nice
you [\h__\h] video game
logic always like that
[Music]
no that's not what was supposed to
happen I was supposed to kill the other
with the
knockback oh oh thank God the bleeding
the bleeding did it for
me I can my brother not be here right
now so I can give him the
controller and just let him do it why
let's find out what's your weekend is it
fire it's it's
fire great I have
this huh what what's with this
evasion doesn't even have a
above stream
[Music]
die die die die
die come on
least one guy
[Music]
died
oh nice
just with one of these
[Music]
items also have
fire how much damage does this
do oh okay well I mean that was a
collaboration effort but that was pretty
good
wait was that the right
attack yeah yeah yeah
yeah is is this new furniture by the
way you probably already broke all this
furniture previously is it new is it
different who missed what
missed use rainbow
skills
okay why
[Music]
he don't miss oh
okay ah rainbow always
wear why is she so
evasive what I mean that's not going to
work on a boss but she has an attack
that's May instant
KO can it work on a boss I mean if other
enemies can use it on us it should work
the other way around
too
W kinky I don't know is this kinky
sheesh 800
[Laughter]
I I respect that you immediately want to
do your homework appreciate
[Music]
that that was weaker than
expected he really
does not want to die he's like a real
boss stop
[Music]
please yeah the rocket
launcher but I need to
heal here maybe
now how long
oo oh
finally
suddenly
suddenly friend put into my brain fall
guys I don't even really know that but
it's a musical
right go back to
is kind
of Fall Guys what Family Guys Family
Guys family
you should have corrected that
automatically in your
[Applause]
[Music]
brain FAS faster FAS come on come on
Family Guys ultimate
[Music]
do oh
nice yo this restaurant is so sick ah
wait the safe the safe the safe
no go down go
down no go down can I still go
down was the armor in
there you missed it
to
for oh well don't mind don't
mind
com
[Music]
for
Fore
fore
for they look so
[Music]
young are
they they just
sh oh my
God oh my
God thank you
[Music]
they're going to take care of this fight
so I can move on
probably right
[Music]
I can't believe majima still has that
when he was so
done with
everything oh oh
there
also what
what
what what's the
point emotional
nice
feelings what is the point
need
this for old time's sake where they a
gang that fought together as these four
at some point or is this just a mish
mash mix
Max fake fan
moment
nice you still got it he's fighting
better than when I fought him in that
boss fight
fan
service it do be nice it do be
nice only one time this exact
combination together that's what I
wanted to know I
see that must have been epic how did
that
happen how did that happen
if it's only one
time then maybe it was a situation just
like
[Music]
this he's so
hyped he's so
excited he just can't hide
it wasn't in
GID oh that's relatively recent
right that was the one before
[Music]
M
nice that's it that's all we get or do
we get the another fight yeah yeah we
get another fight okay okay okay
[Music]
okay I don't have to do anything I don't
even have to make choices I love it I
love it I love
it little break for my brain
punch punch punch punch punch punch
P hey I did the ground work on that
[Music]
one a maim
I'm feeling more excited towards him
because I actually play the game with
him careful now I'm standing
there try another alien
huh
[\h__\h] didn't I choose the this the green
guy green yellow what olive olive I
guess good
Y game fast sliding me again
one wouldn't believe that he has cancer
and that he's like 60 years
old and that kidu is like 80 years H not
kidu majima is like 80 years old
exaggerating on
purpose w w w
wo oh nice
[Music]
entrance why is my team not helping why
are they so
useless to give them the wholesome
teamwork moment
maima oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
woohoo
oh does only K you get exp for
that not
dead I think I see her panties oh Jee
sorry skipped one
[Music]
line more oh no we're okay now we're
leaving them behind yep yep yep yep is
that kind of moment happens in every RPG
game happened in
in uh breath of the wild too
forgot the
name happened in that one as well and
wait can I actually not go
back yeah I can't I
cannot tears of the Kingdom yeah while I
was playing it I did get used to calling
it tears of the Kingdom but now I
already forgot it's kind of sad because
they just didn't have a title for it for
so long so everybody just kept on
calling it breath of the Wild too it
just burnt into my
brain got to call some
[Music]
P okay okay okay okay
oh God there's so many and they all look
the same why do they all have to have
like half of the same
name why cannot can it not be sorted by
power or they should give me a choice of
what I wanted to be sorted by
that would be
[Music]
nice
falling I don't mean the enemies I mean
the skills have the same names for
K which is confusing actually
[Music]
strike maybe
enough music is good
yeah me like
like like like
like I want to go to
[Music]
bed I'm getting closer and closer to PS
prime time
it scares
[Music]
me the [\h__\h] what was
that no I really cannot be that much
[Music]
more it can't except there's more
there's always
more I wish they would separate it in
two different fights they know exactly
what they're doing they know that I want
to
use my
uh my
phone what was that
damage H is it is it because no weapons
or this kind of attack is SH now oh
what Well if I knew how many fights
there are left then I would be less
hesitant to use it the second time in
the battle cuz that takes a lot of
money they are strong
off avoid spamming P to win but it's
ingame money does it even count then
uh I'm not going
to I'm not going to heal him someone
else is going to handle that what if I
what was I do
uh oh yeah a grapple here
okay okay guys okay
[Music]
okaye
interest yeah
I'm going to wait for maybe I'm going to
wait depends how much longer is this
fight it looks like it's might going to
be pretty
long
[Music]
oh cuz I'm thinking waiting for
zi to load up her tack team she's so
close might be where we're going
finish yeah that's what the that's what
foro
attack monoto
AO attack
oh [\h__\h] he did it he actually did it oh
that mad lad no please don't go please
don't please don't hurt out please hurt
kid you instead
y
yum
okay but that's that's see I have 80
million I'm using I'm using 10 million
of
that that's quite
okay oh wait oh wait he
doesn't right full tag
team
[Music]
not
for
[Music]
foree Fore spe
um I'm I'm good I'm just getting
bored I'm just so
bored my neck and my shoulders are so
bad from dancing
[Music]
please tell me the boss is coming
soon I can't handle any more of these
SpongeBob fights
[Music]
[\h__\h] next for the and then there's a
shitty minii
boss and then a
boss I don't it's okay I don't need I
don't need than it's
[Music]
okay
wait
this he resisted
[\h__\h] I'm blaming that one on
sneezing may
I thank you TR thank
you should have sneeze with eyes open
apparently that's
[Music]
impossible I don't believe in the eyes
popping out but
whatever see how much damage that
does okay I should not have done
[Music]
it
wow die
please die die die die
[Music]
die I think that's my problem I'm not
actively looking for their weaknesses
anymore also cuz because I realiz this
team
[Music]
is not as versatile as the other
team
yeah yay that fight is
over uh is there a heal soon or should I
heal myself
thanks for the
membership
no I prefer not to
bye-bye so oh they're
back oh they're not giving up you're
[\h__\h] destroying the Millennium
Millennium Tower that's going to cost
you Millions
you missed
though
a going to try again on this
floor oh thank God I can skip these I
think I don't need the
exp right now right I'm good
[Music]
right this is the equivalent of the of
the traps chocolate
banana oh po plant oh what is this can I
buy
something rainbow bag wait there's
something
there silver bracelet I'm scared I'm
scared I it oh okay it doesn't go that
far far the reach is relatively
small oh they force you to
go to the front of the window is this
the silly
Part A
man was that the silly
[Music]
Part
okay oh it's the fear
guy is that the fear guy
[Music]
oh pound for
pound do I mean money for pounding pound
pounds but we're using we're using yendo
[Music]
wow that's
fast
what
[Music]
rudal what's the rating of this game in
terms of age restrictions
kind of crazy
sometimes do I need to heal her because
she doesn't look so good right
now M
mature maybe she'll
survive
it should have killed the smaller one
[Applause]
man wa what's your
weakness she's not nice
oo hey this group doesn't even have a a
real boss this should be a
quick quick and easy fight no no no
no it's okay as long as it's not
you she I will was kind of yeah bounc to
[Music]
happen dude you've been stunned for like
the whole
fight we're getting spammed with cough
drop tins
sheesh as if anybody needs them
now okay what that's too
much yeah it's always too late oh
helicopter
oo this is really silly they're making
each level a little bit more ooh a
little bit
more get out come
[Music]
on please oh it was the last one I
think all yeah uh I mean n one more oh
looks like a completely open
area oh never mind I don't think they'll
shoot us anymore maybe there's going to
be a cool cut scene now yep yep yeah
running running oh oh they're coming in
oh that's
new that's
new is this the mini
boss that might
all
right oh I'm a VIP
pounder I get
[Music]
this
peace gun no you don't care huh you just
don't
care oh that's um
[Music]
out there's a safe point
after yeah I saw the heal at the safe
Point yeah I already saw it on the map
[Music]
what oh he Wast his turn by
releasing releasing releasing his
rage hold
on massage I'd like a little massage
right now Hey where's the what you guys
are being scammed by the the zones of
this
game absolute scam
W who
W you
volunteer it's so respectable of you to
do volunteer work not many people do
that even though they should I know what
you mean I'm joking
[Music]
ooh triple defense well okay I'll focus
on your little
buddies wait they're all strong they're
they're all like they have the boss
health
bar I thought
oh I just made that
realization oh H yeah no time for
soundboard time for a little
buff haven't buffed in a
while might help
[Music]
us W was that a
SL can we instantly K them
please please please please please
please that would be too good to be
[Music]
true fire fire fire
no knife knife knife
no I have this feeling they have
[Music]
weaknesses good damage good
damage good damage good
damage what's Powderpuff dress again a
medium medium
medium well I'd like to have the
critical hit
I thought that was a
crit yellow is
crit oh
no
what
huh
full oh I want to hurt somebody really
badly
[Music]
what which guy is that which one is
that do you guys know the
name oh my God I didn't know it was like
one specifically if anything I would
think they can all do
it oh my
god oh there
[Music]
enemy area
medium
[Music]
oh wow
wow stop it you [\h__\h] ass oh my God I
am already focusing on him but like he's
doing it again he's undoing all my
[\h__\h] hard
work OMG that should be
illegal that should be
[Music]
illegal kind of need to heal
no my attack my Alpha not even that bad
I think it's okay it's actually pretty
good what
[Music]
oh come on come on come on come on come
on come on
[Music]
can I get a
hallelujah
hallelujah hallelujah
hallelu thank you thank
you I think this is partially cuz his
defense is triple lowered holy [\h__\h]
2,300
W oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] don't
[Music]
me come on
what am I doing what am I
[Music]
doing oh had triple raised attack back
then
already
she oh running out of MP
[Music]
now I'll still go for it one more
time worth
it C and he has it right now got to make
use of it and now we can drink one of
our beloved
[Music]
teas
is [\h__\h]
[Music]
we all have what's the other dude's
weaknesses must be like water or
[Music]
something if I don't have
it actually I should finish the other
one off
[Music]
thank God for her
existence
[Music]
okay is your weakness I'll never know
are you the defense
expert what's your expertise opinion on
this defense lowering technique
[Music]
H I got any comments about this one any
knowledge you can
care get up
yeah don't worry you you'll get healing
from sat in a moment
there Dragon
attention oh leg what the that still H
damage this where did he get this much
attack B
from did I do
that I do not break
call can I buff myself oh yeah the
attack keeps on buffing himself the same
attack
huh well well well well if it isn't the
consequences of my own
choices and we welcome
that oh we're so
close she did oh he double buffed him uh
self okay
well let's watch this actually I didn't
see this
yet I think did
I sake you're so
cool knock out all his [\h__\h] teeth and
now oh yeah it's this one it's this one
the
triple yeah all his stances I remember
now yeah what
what two
two extreme attack
200 what that was maybe the the damage
of the third Punch or or or what
what that can't be
right cuz
like even with the defense
really so
done what do you
want oh
oh oh he's going to throw it at the
helicopter K but that probably is going
to kill
him
okay think that may killed
him if it wasn't the bomb then it was
the fall dude I mean
I think we have to retract the statement
of Kido Never Kills it's it has become
incredibly
unrealistic it it was a grenade it
wasn't
k k you threw it
though okay whatever this is another
boss
fight did I save properly just now
is it oh is it f is it
time seems to be the
time it's the time
confirmed oh B Japan looks like
[\h__\h]
for Fore
weird flex but
okay trying to put on
the
fore
fore speee
[Music]
is he
dead he looks
dead I think he's [\h__\h] dead
this
[Music]
fore
for
fore wow
I already turned into a psychopath
there those
[Music]
eyes
for oh my
God oh my God
thank you Mr Game Boy
[Music]
look at him
going he's
moring stand back he's moring
[Laughter]
I think it's good that
we imagine him hearing
this
[Music]
fore
for can't
look
[Laughter]
[Music]
for um can we shut him up
yet
please for
[Music]
tldr
but that's over
now
over
AG do we still have to
fight please
know
[Music]
for
Fore
for you right you're not saying you're
the other
one yeah yeah yeah yeah that would be
delusional for
[Music]
yeah but I think this dude doesn't care
what you're
saying don't think he gives a [\h__\h]
it's for us
yeah
fore fore
stop showing
so please the eye hurts
me breaks my
heart I really liked him
[Music]
oh you got hats dude
like is there a cooler
right
obviously I don't want to be too loud
it's so late almost 2
a.m. wow wow six packs this is like 12
packs there so
many Z has so that's 18
packs unless they're actually not six
packs but eight packs then it's
different math can you do the
map I got to fight you do the
map is it six or eight tacks these
dudes oh he has no like little
SpongeBobs just one
enemy but like why do we have to do they
really are [\h__\h] hurting me with Sao
in the
background oh this is actually fine this
is fine there's no other enemy
here yeah he's still
there I shall see if I can buff
something or does she not well actually
she doesn't have anything interesting
could do the gas grenade
but no I'm going to aim for something
else maybe defense oh he's weak to
[Music]
electricity hey nice 887
what do I do um I think yeah I
think uh I can't think what what what
um maybe wait he doesn't have any real
debuffs on its own got to use an attack
maybe bleed can we get him to bleed ah
he's weak to to knives is he just weak
to everything or
what no he's bleeding
good
try he's
[Music]
bleeding all
right shall we buff or sh we debuff she
a buff don't
remember might have the
deff
uh if it was Charmed not reducing a
defense if it was charm then it replaces
the bleeding right I kind of want the
defense
[Music]
deu ah he's immune to CH Okay then if
anything it's going to be
defense don't know if this if this is
worth it but here we go oh we got it we
got
it we got it we got
it okay okay okay
but that would have hit hard if I didn't
block it and missed it once
sheesh
[Music]
sheesh here of
okay wait do we have
[Music]
um boosting my
attack might even try something like
that a little a little
fun [\h__\h] I was way too early ah no boost
for
me oh did it say it has to KO okay at
this point I'm like so useless
sorry okay let's get that triple boost
or wait did he have something that's
nice when it
bleeds yeah this one for example
I'mma do
it uh is that agility or is agility
right he his agility is triple lower
now that's good he gets less turns
right he is up next but
still um
I almost got
yes B
mhm no again uh yeah would have been
good my rage is gone so what I do now
I'm going to call palmes I could call
them like 50
[Music]
times oh wait oh does it matter when
he's ah
it might have mattered it might have
mattered
oopsie oops oops oops oops
[Music]
oops cuz he's
guarding grapple is that the only no
K have full
HP he's St his next
[Music]
even oh I have no choice but to
heal perhaps um the big cup it's time
for the cup
[Music]
damn the order of this is so
stupid okay cup is at the bottom I guess
okay 800
yeah the big one not the the fruit
bladder what no don't make it
f that sucks
he's
[Music]
next could try to Blind
him that might make him miss the any
attack he does or stun
[Music]
him lower lower attack
or yeah I think I'll try lowering his
[Music]
attack I know the tag te him I was
thinking about using it
but but I thought it might not be so
strong
actually um
oh my
[Music]
God oh my God [\h__\h] this
menu to in
[Music]
mhm that barely did anything let's
go
[Music]
I blind please
no B it was
[Music]
clut the first
uh he's next what the [\h__\h] happened his
agility buff is gone but even before
that he was attacking all the time what
the hell
man kind of need
to oh man oh man oh man oh man oh man oh
man oh
man that's that he is so small I should
just stop doing that
[Music]
he's next again guys is this [\h__\h]
onoo or
[Music]
what what do you think he'll do maybe
he'll bust himself I not going heal
again I need to do
[\h__\h] I miss no but I his defense is oh
is going for tow oh no oh he's doing a
oh he's doing a debuff just like I said
just like I predicted oh that's fine you
wasted the turn
sir you have wasted the
turn the
gamble see I may not have played uh
blackjack or whatever in this play
through but I'm still gambling
if he resists it then I think it might
not be worth doing it but it does also
bring a little a little buff
right I
[Music]
think well
I will never
learn what that uh what that prompt is
always taking me by
[Music]
surprise is he guarding
again that piece of [\h__\h] sure she did
but the thing is I have to attack uh I
have to send the the the pound mates
first otherwise I don't get to call them
if I attack normally
first it does my thing my my dragon
thingy R2 does that
ignore uh or like does it break his
guard
[Music]
what do you mean just use
o for for him for K because he fights
back or what don't use it yet
[Music]
up you can grab them with Oh Oh you mean
uh in R2
oh
[Music]
oh I know style breaks guard but um I
don't know if it's I don't have much
confidence in its strength to be
honest I'd rather do something like this
or like actually
above I know they're kind of
[Music]
far we got to get good we got to get
strong
oh not
[Music]
again damn he really likes that
skill he's next again
a oh
[Music]
man he did Miss a lot
yeah lucky
me
ouch good
night same same
dbh her tag team was a full heal right I
don't I don't feel like doing
that
uh going
on I need to heal
D kind of want to wake up too I wish you
had like a a decent heal that also gets
rid of the
[Music]
he ATT does all of that
oh is he is he is he he's not guarding
right
50,000 now do I need I don't even need I
don't need money anymore
right I don't need it anymore
right like for real for
[Music]
real it's still only a th000 she did
capped get up
where are you I wish like we would just
stay in the same place why do we got to
go to all kinds of
places from Tokyo to Hawaii
[Music]
literally no no
I hope it's uh uh Satan's turn next I
hope
so 50% pretty
much I want to at least he woke up okay
he woke up
now then I don't need to De up
him I'll just heal
[Music]
then
yeah Z
thankfully isn't
solo okay halfway through bed is calling
me soonm
[Music]
was this
good a thousand oh now we're halfway
[Music]
through what oh sh
oh I was like scratching my
my Mas Mas Mas oh
I thought we were doing a fist
fight you ke was also just doing with
[Music]
fists
what why okay just a f okay okay okay
okay I mean otherwise it would be kind
of insane wake
up oh a jine throwing on its own all
right need a grapple
applies your weapons
attributes uh fire is weak to
[Music]
fire recover cycle andp before it hit
zero I might just uh yeah generally use
a t cuz everybody's kind of low right
now
[Music]
wa how much MP do we have anyway 100 is
still almost
maxed what chill the [\h__\h] out dude
oh why are we so spread out no c yeah go
go there go
there go back go back go go
maybe no no no yes no [\h__\h] I swear to
God I swe I know you want to go
there
come Tag Team tag
team [\h__\h] tag
team triggering me right now
wait he switched his weakness it wasn't
fire before because uh his flying frying
Inferno didn't work otherwise yep yep y
[Music]
see look at all these naked
man that's my strongest one right yeah
okay it's pretty good
[Applause]
he completely switched it
up so much Dynamic y oh his turn is next
again
[Music]
so I'm sorry
dude does dou weakness do anything if
like cuz it's was fire and gun both of
his weaknesses
whoa
no sad that was my
tank was that a what was that a
b never seen that
before I was about to do
that I have pretty good Buffs on the
whole whole group right now o o o but
I'm having no debuffs at all is kind of
rough what can we
[Music]
do he doesn't care about knives
anymore um
I don't want to use anything that's
light
power maybe maybe we can hope for stun
or wait
um this doesn't give him anything but at
least it should be
strong
yeah yeah yeah
1,800 okay okay try healing
that I just got to I just got to go all
out
even if he has no
Debs it's going to be okay although this
is a lot weaker
[Music]
now HP looking very good huh maybe
another but would be
[Music]
niceas easy easy easy
oh my oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my
[Music]
God damage Rising
almost
there almost
[Music]
there y y y y y y
y y y y y y y y
y now now I'm just speed running it
let's go
ah no
no a loud sound oh no cover up her
panties
[Music]
somebody we are gentle men and gentle
women
here it's like when the [\h__\h] do iess
oh thanks for 10 memberships thank you
oh oh [\h__\h] no
heal
oh oh oh I I was ready to say goodbye
right
now uh you don't have a Healer oh you
[Music]
do oh wait was that
immediate no it was oh
[\h__\h]
sorry
tired tired very tired
this we're almost there Z can die
oh uh just just healing he's desperate
very desperate he wants me to stay awake
he wants me suffer tomorrow I have to
get up in 7 hours and I still have to
eat
dinner
sat really okay then k is going to be
the one who finishes uh hopefully
[Music]
okay I wasn't sure if he could do
it to press the button is it not over
yet maybe maybe there's another
face o ooh ooh ooh
ooh
oh how
that is a lot of
time that they were giving me there that
was
slow [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah it's been 10 hours and I did not go
to the idol meeting a single time
huh respect to me
so off topic I just
[Music]
noticed um please
don't go so hard
you
do
careful he look so
dead He's Alive
[Music]
thank God how I mean he might still die
but
yeah
[Music]
for foree
I think we should kill
him he's asking for
it yeah
see oh
you think
so what's is his what what what's in his
brain
you got to meet your bro oh oh
[Music]
what is this F
service why
[Music]
do not take screenshot out of
context I
think I think he's feeling
it what he's trying to
say
please don't disappoint us
[Music]
he won't die he won't die he won't
die he won't
die oh [\h__\h]
off oh my God this is a real
cancer what did he just
say oh it's the dude wait that's
Oh Oh that's oh oh that's
a now he now I get it that's the scene
that we
saw I didn't recognize
him oh he's a broken leg he has a broken
leg did I do that
time to face the
consequences how do you know
stalker you hate this cut
scene what's going to
happen
for what would his charge be
you're right I I I can't even think of
him as the guy in the wheelchair
[Music]
anymore accomplice
conspiracy being a piece of
[Music]
[\h__\h] kidnapping too I would say so
no idea
man I see why you hate it I
think cuz each one's just too
nice
dude you [\h__\h]
idiot remember what he did do you need
to
or play the
game two nice can definitely be a
character
FL I
think I mean
this is probably the right thing to do
but it's where I guess I
[Music]
guess that's kind of a stretch
too nobody would be this
nice
IRL you'd be more on your
[Music]
own people might not kill you but You'
be more on your own and suffer
alone with your things you did with
your conscious
[Music]
yep yep yep yep yep yep I
agree now both of
[Music]
you small problem
he
doesn't he that dude didn't do anything
to to deserve this kindness right
now we're it's it's nice that we're
doing this thing that's the right thing
maybe we're babying him prepare to mute
[Music]
fore fore
speech to nice
[Music]
man should have just sent the police
straight there he couldn't have done
anything he has a broken
foot but yeah we we made him
more like open to do it I guess I don't
know
[Music]
whatever he s said have cannot be
seen
yay oops no where's my here uh where's
my where's
my where
my I can't find I I don't have my thing
the world is full of
jealously
[Music]
who wa I can hear it actually if I mute
it for you okay oh
[Music]
are we helping him
too okay K first what about
[Music]
sa I'm singing it just for you
wait I have
this can you hear
that that doesn't f
[Music]
bring out the
tomatoes wow
[Music]
k
k what about s
[Music]
this so
awkward a oh he's like a [\h__\h] baby
[Music]
ah what's up I shya this
shya it looks like sh for a
moment no wait it's not it's not it's
just
Kam what is
it oh my God [\h__\h] off
guys punch it punch punch punch
unbelievable
unbelievable oh my oh my
huh what
holy
[\h__\h] this
Jesus yeah there's still music Sorry is
ending
though yeah what the
[\h__\h]
oh
dude work is
done what the
[\h__\h] I'm so mad I'm so mad so
angry
[Music]
foree
foree fore
[Music]
[\h__\h] you you're not going to make me
like you you're not going to make me
like you I hate you I will not forget
what you did unlike
ichan no not that easily you have to
atone for your
sins you need a Redemption Arc
you didn't do anything to redeem
yourself nothing
nothing yeah we're besties so
what so
what not the person thing he didn't even
have a choice we didn't have to be so
nice
hey he would have gone anyway
but forced
otherwise
dude what is this
[Music]
ending it's
like makes me mad so
unsatisfying that's it no last like
merger pulse CR oh they
better just sounds
familiar do I mute
[Music]
this sounds so familiar I'm going to
skip
this post credit scene
please
fore
for
Fore thank
[Music]
you for
no no
[Music]
oh that's nice they're doing it
together
[Music]
a that's great
speee
foree
spee thank you
guys
[Music]
for
ya fore
indeed is he going to come come here or
[Music]
what he wrote something
down oh my God
oh my
God oh my
God
shees marry me no don't do
it oh
[Music]
fore fore
he's yapping
again here we go here we
go oh that's a bit too much though
oh oh okay he likes it he likes
it he doubled down yeah
[Music]
I'm going to Kettle
again my water's
cooking no I'm good I'm good
[Music]
oh my God please
don't she
so oh
[Music]
it's cute
oh that's a bit dumb
oh the other side was kind of aary
yeah oh
man you
oh is
oh they're still so
young she looks like 12
what
what what
what what the
[\h__\h] what what
what I'm going to throw
up what the [\h__\h] they looked like
daughter and uh brother and sister
oh
Chad don't tell me they're not going to
wait for
him he aged
kill you
oh well that's no surprise why did they
make it like it's such a
surprise I love pyo shirt
[Music]
well I did it uh
I I did
it I
liked the like some aspects of the
ending
the Satan ichan part was cute um
drinking in the bar was cute um but no
matter like how nice we are I think we
didn't have to be this
nice to people who were brutally
evil I think I don't know I don't
remember it being
this bad in terms of us being too nice
in the games maybe it was and I just
don't remember it but it's it's just a
little bit too nice we're just too
babying we're too
forgiving that you know how angry I was
at Ag More than I was at anybody else in
any other video game I've ever played I
think to spark such a an anger in
me even if you want to be that kind of
game that like never kills people and
just gives people a second chance and
all
that this this just goes a bit too far
in my opinion that we could have done it
a little bit less nice I mean We R
treating everybody like their angels and
um going I thought like um what's his
name I now um I can see how his
character was like would be moved from
that speech
Etc and that definitely hit hard when I
was listening to it I was like oh that's
going to hit hard for
him but still
the was it was it free 80
160 from absolute insane world
destruction psychopath
have
to I love you
is for both both of them were
Psychopaths both E and A and if this is
all that it took then I feel like you
wouldn't go that deep into
psychopathy I think it wouldn't be quite
that easy we saw how crazy he was and
with his actions as well
no matter how hard that hits that one
talk changing
everything don't know about
that so those parts really bothered me
there at the end it's just like they
took the easy way out like yeah we're
just going to say some nice things and
then everybody's fixed everybody's nice
like happy and everybody's feeling
remorseful like man like for for
Cho ch ch was punished way more I mean
she punished herself she did some [\h__\h]
she felt extremely remorseful and then
she worked so hard to redeem herself
even though we already forgave
her but she actually did that
[Music]
in contrast to that why do we let the
real evil people go that easily I don't
understand chy wony but anyway I have to
pet my cats and eat some food at 3:00
a.m. and go to sleep and wake up in 6
hours from
now should they have killed them I mean
you know it's just like with uh that one
guy was got who got eaten by a shark it
could have been something like that just
like fall down the mill Millennium Tower
or so and then you couldn't blame us
then then we didn't kill
anyone
um man Dwight as well but
Dwight
Dwight wait did Dwight end up being like
I don't think Dwight
changed his mindset in did he I think he
did so at least he stayed in character
DWI
just do just stay
[Music]
Dwight no wait not Dwight I mean uh
Bryce I'm talking about Bryce sorry
Dwight the names have merged in my
[Music]
brain no I'm talking about Bryce Sam
Bryce Bryce didn't like change his
mindset right yeah he also just stayed
EV
I don't know that's my
opinion
yeah there were some really good moments
that those moments where I turned into a
kettle
today those were amazing
scenes and there were other moments
throughout the game play throughout the
11 or whatever episodes we had that were
pretty good too but that was a it felt
like there was
[Music]
some some dragging out like but I
understand why they did it they want
to you know the legacy of kidu you know
I get it I get it I get it I get
[Music]
it uh but I think as a as a streamer it
was a bit painful uh
to do all of that cuz also I want to do
it justice cuz like
I'm sure there's a lot of big fans in
the chat and I want to do it justice for
you guys as
well not sure um if you guys are happy
with the whole playthrough but yeah I'm
not saying I didn't have fun I
definitely had fun with it a lot of time
and
um I don't regret playing
it but I think um there were definitely
some points to
critique m
[Music]
yeah I'm curious
how how it's going to
continue if kidu is going to recover
properly or if he's like for real for
real
retired
now in the end these people just like
just like uh EV said these dudes they
always make a comeback they say they're
retired they say they're gone they
always come back back anyway so
[Music]
H he's doing camo ah so he probably is
going to recover as
he
damn well I'm going to go I I can't I'd
like to Yap a bit more but I can't I got
to go thank you for watching today and
all the previous times as
well oh my head
I appreciate you guys being here with me
another
Yakuza game has been defeated but yours
truly was a good
time thank you so much for sharing this
with me thank you for helping thank you
for everybody who helped me gave me tips
and tricks and cheered me
on it was long our next long
RPG will come after little bit of a
break probably I I'll play some shorter
games and stuff and I'm also going on a
little trip for a few days as you
know so yeah okay I'm I'm falling asleep
right now and my face hurts and my head
hurts so it's 3:00
a.m. started at 400 p.m. ended at 3:00
a.m. goodbye guys and hope he does in
war in German we say good enough mhm
[Music]
thank
you almost 11
hours
yeah bye IE wish me luck that I won't be
too [\h__\h] tired but it's okay the the
the thing I have to wake up for I don't
really I'm not really going to do
anything like physically exhausting not
really
bye-bye bye
[Music]
little tired I'm so
tired maybe I just won't
eat no I
should just a small
sandwich
n ah my face
[Music]
love you guys thank you so much thank
you thank
you love love love