[Music]
fire
down
he
[Music]
a
k Katy key
hello yeah I started
early sometimes I'm
impatient
hello uh sorry uh
wait okay okay okay I muted my
microphone to move my microphone for
once aren't too happy about that that
you don't have to hear
the yeah uh I had a nap
so I'm probably going to be okay I'm
also drinking a little bit of
Coca-Cola it's 2
a.m. at least an hour earlier than
yesterday
Hallelujah the nap was good way better
than yesterday yesterday I was kind of
nervous and didn't have quite enough
time to like really fall asleep for my
nap but yeah I had a nap and also slept
like8 or 9 hours
before that no probably eight
hours um so
sleepwise I'm fine but I have to say it
did feel weird like yesterday today
today but yesterday but
today last night I woke up at
like 5:00
p.m. little bit 5:30 maybe and it just
feels so [\h__\h] weird
especially now that uh it gets darker
earlier as winter is coming yeah it's
disorienting and I'm
like like I normally already don't get
up early but still it's it's weird
and I don't like
it I cannot imagine doing
this like permanently or
so like I I I like how do you even like
if somebody if I'm sleeping until 5:00
p.m. or so like normally I um I would
like to not be disturbed in my sleep so
if somebody Rings my doorbell to deliver
something I would probably ignore it but
like if if I'm awakened at like 3 a 3
p.m. or so I'll be like [\h__\h]
off I'm not going to open the door so
how many packages would I been missing
and and like any kind of appointments or
so or like I don't know so many things
you miss if you like sleep the whole day
so it's really not convenient
[Music]
huh I want to say one
thing smoking is bad don't smoke I do
not support like or try to um uh
motivate people to
smoke I hate smoking and alcohol H and
all that kind of
[\h__\h] but
apparently apparently whatever I said uh
in my bag stream sounded like I
was uh supportive of Ren smoking or like
more like not supportive of her quitting
which is [\h__\h] people don't
understand jokes ah you guys I think
understood it in the live
chat oh I don't man sometimes I really
don't know what to do man like I feel
like people purposefully want to
misunderstand me it is what it
is today today today we're going to play
this game again and I uh am scared
because there will be a
zombie invasion rush and Kelly talked
about um like we should
fortify sorry the Coca-Cola coming up
fortify our bases base but we have two
bases now so how that's going to work
I'm guessing that the zombies will go to
wherever they like they're programmed
probably to know where the players are
and they'll just go wherever the players
are so do we have
to uh yeah but if we abandon the house
and go to the main base will the zombies
just go to the main base does anybody
know like if we all just gather in one
place will they not attack our second
house cuz I don't
know like protecting our warehous will
be a bit difficult with just me FAA and
gigy maybe Gigi is not even here now but
I think she'll join later they spawn on
each player they go okay they spawn
where players are okay then I think
we're just going to ignore the second
house that me and Fa and giggy built so
to say say okay okay
okay all right that's good cuz I also
didn't want to move things we put a lot
of stuff there um okay well then
um seems like for now it's uh CI FAA bio
Shi me and da and I think they're I
think giggy joins later and CeCe joins
later uh I don't know if the other girls
fok is not here today I don't know but
crony and Bae apparently dropped out I
was wondering like I was like oh where
is she where is she
yesterday oh yeah gigy has a collab of
with so she'll she said she'll join
afterwards crony will be joining later
oh okay did she say
so ah after family dinner I see okay
hopefully she'll make it in time to
die with us together all right yippy Cay
or whatever let's
go let's go in
baby I think I'm in the second house oh
[Laughter]
God that's a nice thing to wake up
to hi hi Kelly hi
sorry why are you sorry cuz I
accidentally punched fa in the face just
because I tapped into the game I tried
to oh I'm sure she forgives
you f surely she forgives
you oh she gave me something cornbread
she made cornbread Kelly I need to
update
you because I think you know yesterday
we kind of like all ended up going like
separating into two groups two groups
yeah me geky and fauna we we basically
got ourselves a house closer to the
Trader which anybody's welcome to use
but uh I've heard from the chat that the
the zombies uh for the invasion will
only attack where players are so if we
just abandon our house for the zombie
attack and go to the main house where we
all started off uh then they will ignore
a house so I think that's what we're
going to do I think that's a good idea
that's a great idea so that we don't
have to protect two
houses exactly yeah cuz this one will
get all beaten up and broken then we
have that one for the Traer just move
there oh yeah can oh yeah that will be a
great opportunity to
move yeah exactly I think that's that's
the better way for sure let do it and
then oh my
God yo I'm home hello hello welcome home
ladies here meeting it's a very short
meeting yep I'm here for the meet and
greet meet and greet uh I was I just
wanted to also add that um fauna became
really good at cooking because we
couldn't rely too much on bio with her
being in a different team yesterday nice
so yeah is good FAA is cooking a lot of
stuff up nice nice oh we can use that's
good of her yeah two SH now we can have
double the charred meat yeah no no she's
she cooked oh corn bread cornbread yeah
oh uhhuh finally some darn good food
yeah good food and I think we're cooking
like water and stuff cuz we got a
cooking pot and the grill both of those
things oh oh yeah that's true that's
true very expensive we just have to not
lose it now can imagine oh oh no worry
we will not use it our our house will
not get attacked we'll focus on the
other
house oh are we getting another Base by
the way or is this like our zone now
well they found a new one right near
near the tra yeah we're kind of prepared
we prepared a second base so to say
that's closer to the Traders is the one
you're in right now uh yeah yeah yeah so
if the other house goes down you all can
just go here this is the backup
house the main sorry FAA for punching
you by the way it happens when I tab
into the
game I'm sorry I'm sorry I have your
cornbread right here just don't
again no I wasn't trying to say give me
the cornbread or
else I see so that is why you are
cooking
that kind of
yeah it's so cozy by the
fire love the carbon
monoxide it's nice it it adds to the
atmosphere it
does did did you guys also get a cooking
pot and
Grill uh we found a grill you found one
and the pot's still here yeah yeah I
mean I left them with beibs I just don't
know where it is I think it's
here we had to buy both of
them oh man from the uh the old
something that was so
expensive but it's worth
it trying to figure out how to get a
workshop bench so that we can make ammo
at some point here I don't even know
what to put away I have Rotting
Flesh yeah yummy toss that out out to
the wild I'm just putting everything in
this box if it fits it's good enough if
it fits it sits fits I
sits were thinking the same thing
yeah let me try to finish all right I
got ammo and a gun nice now we will not
use it apparently there's a flashlight
schematic I should just read okay I'll
read it we could use a flashlight oh I
got raw meat oh guess I'll
cook guess I'll cook oh I guess that's
it it it just gives you exp oh oh I hope
you're ready for some charred meat yum
yum hey you know what if it's all we got
it's all we got that's
true can't believe our characters don't
even know how to cook actually
yeah yeah I can though to be honest I
don't think any of us are exceptional
Cooks maybe a couple people I think we
could at least manage to make some
cornbread if anything cornbread
oh true
enough let's see I wonder how making the
workbench is the biggest thing that we
need to try and what do you need for it
hello find out
hello I made it what's up my Gordon
ramsy I made
here hello
hello Chef oh that's good hold up it
takes me apparently 1 minute to make
charred meat we need me cook I have a
grill but can you cook cornbread I'm
dropping my meat here our FAA can cook
cornbread oh well we need to cook off
between fauna and
B I'm down I'm down the I'm down you
want to do Che battle Let's do an IR I'm
not confident you not conf I've never
cooked a steak in my
life I'm going to burn it sure do you
know do you know the the trick to steak
where like you use the texture of your
hand to tell the dness of the steak
what I have an advantage here I haven't
even heard of that before that sounds
crazy I just try to make sure it's
edible Dody it's a little
dodgy all right so I wonder I think a
lot of people are here I wanted to
mention just briefly what we're going to
do so we have um we're going to get
attacked really really hard for in like
in 3 hours I'm excited what we need to
do is try our best to there are three
things fify the house as much as we can
mhm um collect ammo and medicine and
then
strategize right oh which house do you
want to defend though the new one old
onee the new one B destroyed yeah this
one will get destroyed so I thought
we'll just one afterward this this one's
going to get destroyed huh know they're
probably house is kind of
small yeah which house our oh yeah it is
it is small the old one oh the old one
oh our was a
smaller yeah I think wait yours a
smaller is defense no no but the thing
is we don't have to defend it as long as
we are not there the the NPCs will not
go towards us they will just go wherever
we are the sacrificial house I guess so
we just meant to die I see see the decoy
base the decoy base but my streamer set
up man it's okay didn't want destroy it
they also want to be a streamer yeah
maybe they're your fans you never know
yeah I thought you were a
zombie hell arve to the base who is
putting feathers and mechanical Parts
into the food storage huh who's not
organizing you guys got to organize dang
it Jang it dang it
good morning good morning oh who's
grunting oh sorry sorry you scared me
for you scared me I'm not a zombie what
the heck is wrong I'm sorry you were
grunting in my ear something was
grunting someone's grunting actually I
do have a sprained leg I probably should
try and fix that you were probably
grunting in my ear it caused me to
defend myself I am so
sorry fine I'll forgive you for
now for now in the meantime I will yeah
hello I think we should really try to
get the uh the thing that collects water
because that way we can get an active we
need to have about let me see what how
much was it um we need about 100 scrap
polymers so if any we should all pull
our scrap polymers together to make that
water collecting thing so we can have
fresh water instead of diarrhea water
yeah yeah how do you unlock a
workstation do you need a level of
Robotics or
engineering um I thought that you needed
at least one in the advanced engineering
um which one was it let me look up what
it was called there's a specific one um
yeah in advanced engineering I'm pretty
sure that you need like one you need to
just be like Apprentice or so and then
you can make a
workbench oh yeah no actually I not
understand but I figure it out
I tried to advance in an engineer but it
still doesn't make me do the workbench
for some reason really strange that's
not what the guide told me yeah I can I
don't know if I am missing
something cloth and glue will make duct
tape I try my best to understand I
wanted to make the workbench before
but very yeah it's still locked maybe I
need to read a
magazine yeah you have to find stacks
of I'm putting stacks of cooked corn in
the in the food container so if you need
we got plenty of corn so nice thank you
all right I guess someone should
specialize I have almost 100 scrap
polymer I have 87 oh that's big oh I
have 12 so weit we're almost
there we need we need one more we need
one more cuz 87 + 12 one more one more
no I have no
cloth is this something I can do by the
way or I can help with I have 15 scrap
polymers okay let's see what we need to
make the the water collecting thing I'll
carry it over to you girls you guys
don't need nitrate powder right cuz I'm
about to take it for a farm plot you
good yeah I'm pretty sure you're good oh
nitrate
powder actually I also would like to
make a plot for for growing things is
that what you need uh I'm making three
Farm plot blocks so we should be good
there I assuming nothing destroys it oh
does anybody have duct tape I have three
du thing we need four duct tape for the
Dual collector oh I think I have some
duct tape let me check I have I can
craft them oh screwed
Upton's very easy to get I'm going to
get cotton so I'm going to be putting SP
uh Spikes all around the base and trying
to fortify the base personally okay two
duct tap one duct tape here yeah there's
one duct tape in here I'll just drop it
for you I'll you no
problems then what else do I
need all right I guess this is good
enough for me I'm coming to Kara to
collect my taxes oh okay I was coming
your way yeah taxes
taxes aka the the be tax
yeah can have fresh
water okay our old base is going to have
the farm because they're going to be
like away from here is that okay with
everyone yeah yeah that's
fine this point and then all of a sudden
my guess I'll just leave it here who
knows maybe the old base will not get
that messed up anyway maybe maybe we'll
be fine as long as you stay away from it
I think I'm going to go try to find the
workbench uh sorry yeah the workbench
the workstation uh magazine but maybe I
need to do oh my gosh it's me I keep
hurting myself on the spikes that's what
it is yeah same the other spikes are
doing are doing a lot of harm
to good at the same timey at least it's
working for the farm we know how it
works I have some Alo Vera seed maybe we
should plant that on the farm
too oh we only have three plots um what
can you do with aloe vera is that for
drinking I think
medic very important okay we can plant
one okay I have the aloe vera
seeds Okay what else blueberries can
have blueberri I want something uh let
me see hold up where' go yeah if you
guys have like nitrate that's useful
nitrate oh I have a bunch of nitrate
should have brought that good now we
just need Rotting Flesh okay I have I'll
do aloe vera here B I'm going towards
you by the way we don't have a lot of
plots okay
let's do blueberry
slow ow the
spikes spikes are working it
seems Yay good they're I'm testing them
they're working do you have to water
this I hope you don't have to water the
plants do you have any recommendation to
what I can focus on today because I'm a
little lost and I don't know like what
to do exactly so see if you can find
as much ammo as possible right and
medical supplies so if you can raid
little places that might be good or you
can focus on fortifying the base which
is you make a bunch of spikes or like a
bunch of wooden blocks and try and
encapsulate the house in them so it
makes it hard for the zombies to come
and get us and then what I hope we can
do is get on the roof and shoot them
from there okay we'll try to filter them
slowly
inside so well any of those things is
fine whatever you like to do if you want
to scavenge that would be great okay
raid some but if you're going to raid a
place make sure that it's maybe like one
skull or so cuz otherwise it'll be too
difficult for you mhm
yeah I think I'll try to
fortify the B I think it's a fa saer for
me I don't actually have
many good weapons right now probably uh
do you want a shotgun shotgun bundle no
no no it's fine
ah I hear them I think I I got a shotgun
Sho if you want a shotgun I have one
it's okay I got it just let me know
um go ahead go
ahead we'll make this a weapons crate
that's got store uh fresh weapons I'm
going to head to the
the uh take take yes here you
go oh night TR my favorite oh oh Ry
flesh my favorite yeah your favorite
faite yeah thank you what a good
girl wow she called me a good
girl what the best
girl I hear
them they do be crawling out
there
crawling these on they will not heal
again I swear to God so Spike strap are
good right yeah I would say yeah yeah
they're good okay oh you can also
upgrade it to iron assuming you have
enough iron for that I don't actually
have a forge I think or armor I think
that's my door I don't have a forge yet
so I don't think I
can oh I have arrived at the old house
that is currently the current
house I'm scared of the
spikes
the
get make a
ofap or find ACH of ta you say yeah here
scrap polymers and some duct tape and
what there anything else I think that
was it not turn into anything
darn you know what's weird you can like
pick up I was going to say does anybody
have medical um so they can make a bunch
of first aid bandages by chance H I
think CE was working on medical but I I
put medical book into the uh magazine
store so if somebody else wants to work
on medical they can use that it might be
a good idea I don't know if she'll
always be here to play so yeah we can
have like multiple people on the same
trait just in case people aren't here as
backup blueberry
pumpkin can I can I um check uh on the
magazine uh storage as well yeah what
you looking for go ahead oh yeah go for
it yeah whatever you want to
do all right thank you you're welcome I
like how I still prefer archery over
guns do you guys have any St we had no
guns uh 7.62
ammo there might be some we have we have
an ammo case but there's no ammo in
there at the moment um yeah we should
take note of like what ammo everybody
uses cuz I know Calli uses shotgun I use
9 mm and then which one you as
well I use 7.6 to okay the golden
one if we can start up yet a little farm
then we can probably provide biu and
fauna a lot of stuff to cook with a yeah
wise right now I'm cooking a bunch of
meat and a bunch of corn nice we need a
yeah we have lots of food right now
refrigerator
okay cornbread yum yum yum yum oh that's
a lot
of all right our Harvest Moon is uh
finally
starting how wholesome a now you just
got to find like the cute the zomie to
yeah yeah zombie to Mar yeah yeah keep
in a cage like the real
is it okay if I surround the house with
spikes like actually the
outside yep I oh oh are you doing the
spikes in the old house or the new house
wait there is a new house yeah yeah yeah
we're doing like um what do you call it
uh a red herring house oh what was that
sound yeah we're leading the zombies to
our old home so it's just an excuse for
us to move well the old home is what I
think R knows as the the real current
home
yes yeah what is what is the new one um
if you press M I think you can see no
we're not there right now but TR yeah me
gigy and fauna yesterday we found a
house where we just like made a second
base uh that is closer to the trader so
that we don't have to run back and forth
all the time um but it will not get
attacked if me if if nobody's in the
house then it won't get attacked so
we'll all just gather in the same house
which is the current house the old house
to say and if that house will get like
absolutely destroyed by the end of the
day we'll just move into the new Giga
Kiana house that we
found okay sounds good okay so do I um
uh upgrade like protect this one right
the old one yeah spikes here okay just
you know spikes we still want to protect
it make it
spiky don't let them touch anything oh
okay protect us I protect okay protect
even from
ourselves yeah we could turn into
zombies and attack each other maybe yeah
you can get infected and if you let the
infection go to 100% you turn don't
trust no
one oh my gosh I've never been so luy to
live that
longie head to the new house to put
spikes there then
okay yeah lots of do I have to do I have
to build spikes on the old or the new
house I'm a little confused I probably
the new house since that's where we're
going to die Oh I thought we were
defending the old house I thought we
were defending the old house yeah oh
we're doing the old house oh the new
house is for later yeah yeah okay I just
thought all of that stuff is like our
inventory is already there is what I
thought I it'll take a while to move but
it is what it is okay can we can we like
take the boxes full of stuff instead of
just stuff no yeah have to move it one
by one I
think I wish that would be amazing it's
okay like maybe it we'll survive maybe
we can keep it and have two bases I
believe we got to try our best
apparently the first Rush is not that
difficult is what I'm being told but
we'll see I hope so I would really like
a way for us to like craft bullets
because I feel like that's yeah that's
the main thing yeah I really need
bullets
workbench get the workbench but I'm
having a trouble figuring out what
exactly is necessary I guess it's a
magazine but is the rush I don't find it
either is the rush 24 hours long like
the whole day on the 7th Day or is it
like only at night on the seventh day I
think it's at night it's at night okay
okay that makes sense
yeah and basically it's it's the blood
moon they show up and they make a SED
oh I hope they leave our farm alone I
just worked hard on this in one day I
don't know about that put some spikes
around the
farm
I'll I should have put it at the corn
farm I don't think they would have
gone can I rebuild
this my God hello you scared me
I'm come to collect my T this is not the
house and I do not have this
stuff it's with
kiaha what the the the polymer
yes oh I thought she only gave me like
10 yes I thought you had like 80 oh it
was in the crate at that house oh I only
brought her like 15 that I had in my own
crate
I more back in the crate okay where's
the house well I have 15 it's I think
Kar is still in it no I'm at the Traer I
see it I'm I'm at the Traer um the house
is uh maybe you can make a screenshot
and you can post even for other so
like yeah I'm I'm going towards there
now so you can see though uh wait I'll
be
there in a minut the one with the
bed carry on we need to make a new chest
over there I guess wait bio come back
yes yes yes check the closet look in the
closet
closet is that you're
like oh
[Music]
uh wait what bullets do you
like this gu strong right is there
bullets there where you
are if you guys yes you guys do a quest
let me know I want to do a quest yeah I
could use a little more
money but we also got to prepare so yeah
yeah like later if I'm I'm currently
building stuff but if you guys go I'm
sorry I killed your pet that's okay he
was being rowdy I more people I'm at the
house now if you want to check the map
that's where it
is okay so it's just down the road okay
got it I'm going to check it out wait do
you like 9 M thank you yes yes thank you
very
much do you are you using [\h__\h] a
b can you mod your something with
that okay I think you need a workstation
to to mod
it but I'll hold on to it thank you very
much wait wait take this
too take take all my stuff take
this the house I'll put way point there
Mar yes Market Market you want you want
coffee
seeds or a lead car
battery I'll yes sure I'll take peasants
yes oh I can mod it okay I a wood
splitter
mod they may have found some good
stuff how do I'm about to die
nobe I should just do this on my
own I can do it I can take it
okay thank you you're
welcome nitrate powder is all you need
for making a farm plot
right yes I just gave St a bunch of
nitrate powder
cool wow I like your outfit thank
you my new hat that I just found yeah I
like your hat thank
you maybe if we do a ton of quests we
can get a bunch of money and then buy a
bunch of things to save ourselves from
the from the trader not save ourselves
from the trader like he's going to kill
us but like you know buy them from the
trader so that we can save ourselves I
have to
clarify the Traer is so
rude what I mean
mean to beat myself all the time it's
really me yeah trying to get our streams
demonetized yeah yeah how dare he yeah I
mean an f word so quick in there like I
I booted up the game in the Traer and he
immediately starts flying off the handle
with f bombs like watch
him what a jerk
yeah biggest order of business is
definitely finding a way to craft the
workbench but I just think that we need
the knowledge and I don't see anything
that might help uh if you keep doing
quests from him there is it there is a
probability that the reward will be like
random skill books so okay just Quest a
lot and then maybe you'll get lucky and
gotcha the right magazine
okay do we know which one it
is which magazine yeah that's the
problem is we got to know which
one oh is it the workstations one
probably I mean that sounds like it to
be right I've read three of those oh I'm
sorry I think I was reading all the
magazines I found that's okay do you
think you can makeing the knowledge um I
think I can if I get seven more books oh
my God that's a lot all right we'll
leave it to you then fauna I like this
house better it's like
emo the new one yeah yeah it's emo oh
I'm happy you like it it's a little bit
like narrow but you know it's cozy
where's the storage it uh like right by
the
entrance oh
oops I can't move
back yes I make more
spikes get her one more I hope you guys
don't like run into the spikes though
yeah we're just going to have to get
used to that you know it's a necessary
form of protection in my H what by the
way they oh go ahead first uh you might
want to put spikes on the sides of the
house because they'll try to break down
the weaker blocks they're not going to
go in just at the
entrance oh that's it go ahead oh would
you guys rather have the water collector
at the old base or the new one
H probably old ones for now right since
we're cooking all the
stuff can always move it right but you
should put it like away from our base
even if you have to run just a little
bit for it because I don't want them
attracted to it and destroying it that's
true okay did I did I glitch him oh no
sorry I'm I'm a bit far away
I'm getting some work done we can dig
like a mount here or
something is that call it a
trench okay I'm heading back and then
we'll have
a out of the word for oh okay yeah I
went I got out of the map for a moment
now I'm back oh well welcome back a
little buggy not just zombies we're
dealing with we're also dealing with
some bugs that's okay oh it's thundering
boom
yeah the most emo of weather love
weather I love the
[Music]
rain so
cool more I'm going to do some Quest
okay try to get money and try to get
ammo I need
ammo so if anybody finds
762 ammo and doesn't need it I'll gladly
take it for you you're so
lovely
yeah I still don't know what kind of
weapon I want to use I like their bow
but I don't know if it's too weak
um you should try use a weapon based on
what stat you are raising for example if
you are doing strength
shotgun skills scale with strength um
and like same thing with agility since
I'm upping agility
pistols skills up with agility too so
I'm going to use long to reload what ups
with bows is that a agility or a
strength thing um let me see cuz
otherwise I can just go OAB boonga with
a
spear archery is agility yes okay I
guess we're going OAB
boonga chicken
soup
yes on you have some for me thank you oh
you too oh my God so many m donations
yeah presents for Kiara I appreciate
it what's that I need to drop my stuff
off then do Quest if you want okay I'm
on my way to a really close clo close
fetch Quest and then we can do maybe
some fighting
Quest if you want to if you want to can
come with the quest do I would like to
as well I want to kill
things blood
first also happy to help
ooh uh do we want to meet
somewhere uh uh yeah the trader maybe
okay I'll head there after I drop off
the D the DU collector at the house Okie
I'm a bit far away so please put me at
home it's okay I'm still doing something
small something else and then I'm coming
drop my stuff off good good good it's
good to do Quest together because we all
get the reward so that's like four times
the money for one Quest oh true okay
yeah yeah
yeah we're going to steal all of his
money to bankrupt
him we're going to drain his assets and
replace him with f Mar
yes why do we need money during the
zombie apocalypse
anyway cuz cooking pots are so rare
a monopoly on cooking pots how
dare I
know zombies are
funny these sure are silly
guys I don't understand
arrows all right if I run it really
hurts my broken leg so no oh I have a
broken leg do you need do you need a
what are they called splint splint I
just
might I have one but
I'm probably
far um I'm near the trader actually well
not near the trader I'm actually very
far from the trader oh I'm doing a fetch
Quest right now but then I'm going to
the trader so we can meet up there there
okay we got a water collecting thing
going on now so we have fresh
water I put it a little bit away from
the house so it won't get destroy just
in case mhm didn't clear it no way I'm
like legol L man I
need I don't know how to make the iron
Arrow
Head
go check the
magazine oh wait I didn't start the
quest please die there we go thanks for
letting me know Chad maybe this one
okay yeah I'm a mix between Legolas and
gimy wait is do they call him legless
cuz he doesn't have legs no he does have
legs
though him legless call cuz he has no
legs we got to watch have you not seen
Lord of the Rings huh when I was very
young I forget all of it oh it's time to
watch it again
[Music]
yeah let's do it come in also I'm going
to run on a broken leg sorry guys I'm
going to run you're going to make it
worse yeah does anybody uh people do you
can you cook grow meat right yes there I
actually just cooked some grilled meat
it is in the
cooking I give you room meat if you want
yeah go ahead and just put it in the
food box and then I'll just pick up any
food that's in there and cook it
okay also X oh can I have a party invite
please for the for the hunt Quest gang I
want to do some Quest too well if
everybody wants to do Quest maybe we
should do two groups I don't
know yeah I think two groups is
good
yeah divide and conquer
yeah sounds good to me boom head
[Music]
a let's start um but let's let's uh go
ahead and try to start the um the
process of like really getting ready for
The Rush about 30 minutes beforehand all
right okay oh what time is
the oh no it's in two days okay yeah
seventh day I guess at the night
time yeah I think 10 p.m. to 4:00 a.m.
they show up oh okay it's pretty soon
that's but it wasn't a shared Quest
what no wait did I fail the quest
because I tried to join a different
party oh no at least are you okay though
I always did you die by Spike
yeah me but that means it's
working for me he
working I better fix this spike it was a
downed up in health I see that you ran
into two of them
perhaps maybe a little bit
[Music]
more it works that's
great my back again oh God it's working
yay oh it bre
to help help help me wait your right
there
help me
him what do you
help
help just try walking very slowly when
you're going through the
spikes
okay okay I'll
try yeah yeah but the problem is on my
backpack is stuck here right it's
actually into spikes can you break it
for me
you want me to break my heart earned
spikes okay can can you not interact
with it from pet no it doesn't make me
interact I need to get
cler each other okay you can break my
spikes here here I break for you okay
you're you're welcome hold up oh no
still oh my God I canot get my backpack
back
I'm trying I'm trying okay okay your
backpack is ready just don't go into the
spike
what really good spikes though good job
I love it but I'm out of Amo me okay
okay you might want to exit through the
other side of the house just to be safe
they don't have spikes yet I just want
my
backpack you can get your backpack soon
there you go I got it
okay I'm spikes back there don't fall
into it thank you you're
[Laughter]
welcome I like how difficult is to
actually enter your own house got a
bunch of magazin plums you little
gals is there anybody I got two home
cooking weekly anyone who is using a
rifle right now by
chance uh what am I using I'm using a
pipe no I'm using good job I got to make
more hard I'm using a pipe rifle and a
pipe machine gun but mostly the machine
gun okay well if you want to use a rifle
at all you can have
that you want to
go yeah let's go I'm going to in the
VC if you you guys want to join
yes I want to join yeah I'm in okay I
sent you a party invite but oh what's
your quest right now by the way I do
need to level
up oh thank
you we're going to the trailer to do
questy
quests
okay I have a quest at the pier by the
way I don't know if it's shared however
Shar no it is it is shared I see it we
can meet at yours then we'll me that
yours yeah okay it's a level one uh
thing okay
we move to different voice chat which
one do you want
UHS and two let's go to two Okay okay
good luck
ladies good luck hold up hold up it's
only you guys just the two of you maybe
I'll stick with you guys you can stick
with us is more more
balanced okay I'm almost done with my
fetching Quest I
think okay I'm just about ready to okay
well I guess if you accept the quest we
can just go to the Final
Destination yes okay sounds
good so whoever's first at the trader
let me know okay okay I'm there at the
trader right now actually drinking out
of the pond okay just take any Quest
that you think is good Callie I don't
mind see what we
got can't find the supplies hit the
locked crate locked crate K are you in a
different party right now maybe we
should join the same party I sent you
guys a request but maybe you guys need
to send me I'll invite her yeah get me
in that party okay I'm ready to party
yay okay I'm in I'm
cucumber you're cucumber go drop some of
that cucumber off yeah that's the true
boss of this game is managing your
inventory truly oh buried supplies is
actually pretty close let's do that one
oo why do I hear so many oh no so many
zombies oh why are they fighting each
other oh oh they learned how to climb
ladders the zombies you're smarter than
we
think what so many I'm going to die no
no I'm legitimately going to die oh no
in the Attic no no no oh no oh no it's
so I'm running to you but I'm 400 me
away I died oh
no yeah like four zombies suddenly came
all towards me in the attic and I was
stuck there they wanted to have a
sleepover with
you be
nice um I'll have to retrieve my f but
father if you can help me I'll I'll run
to you than you
were you just raing a random Place Kiara
no I went to a fetch Quest but uh it
wasn't just fetching let me tell you
that they misrepresent
it where is it where's my
body and so you lose the quest when you
die huh yes
wonderful results in losing yeah it is
what it is well then what where's my
body I'm blind do you see on the map
where your bag is you do yeah oh wait
that there it
is
okay ah okay now I see it I'm
blind that's okay you got this you'll be
fine I got this no I didn't I didn't got
this
but you perished right you
died but you've learned right h you'll
never get stuck in that attic ever again
with four zombies ideally
yeah I still hear them feasting on my
body snowy over here yeah it gets snowy
like a little bit past the house okay
I'm back in the house uh I I'll wait
outside I can't do this alone as long as
I don't have my face I'm almost here
back strong
FAA yes I my punching got better
oh all right then please punch them yeah
punch them as hard as you can they're
they're right
here they're right there oh God I hear
them go go Goa go oh she's so
cool oh yeah oh yeah oh wow wow we're
bad that's impressive she got some power
in her
fists I do punch of Z Right Hook from
below oh yeah yeah uppercut or something
like that that's what you say right
uppercut yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah the
old one too some ravioli here ravioli
you deserve that Chef Boyd yeah Chef boy
Rd love that Chef boy Rd so oh oh my
backpack fell down that's good at least
um I hear a lot of zombies yeah but I
don't think now with the quest being
gone I don't think I have to go up there
anymore but we could still go up if
there's something good up there though I
I already looted it but maybe it's like
go com down yeah yeah they all came
towards me can you
imagine oh you guys aren't too far from
me actually oh come over lady if you
want to what don't die
Anna am I dying I don't know uh-oh are
you there's a lot of them in here yeah I
know I think that's up a little bit that
should be oh I'm infected o oh no I have
some
antibiotics at the house we don't have
to just eat honey all the time now wait
does honey cure your infection yes yes
oh well we have honey too another
one okay that that has to be the last
one slap him slap
him I am back down to 20 hp it's not
good I know I'm I'm at
34 okay everything's empty treasure
quests are usually like only a couple
zombies spawn so F that's empty it's
empty okay I'll Trust
you okay let's uh check down
here oh yeah I checked I checked almost
night time I think I checked everything
any
bookshelves uh I I don't think I saw a
bookshelf
I might need to just do this real quick
do what you got to do we all got to do
what we got to
do yeah but yeah should we go back for
the
antibiotics yeah I want to fix my oh uh
gloves too okay oh Celly by the way
how's your broken
leg uh 28 minutes to heal oh could be
worse maybe it'll be done before the it
arrives yeah I think it will be as long
as I don't run too much but if I died it
might you know disappear immediately
that's
[Music]
true oh I'm cucumber dang it cucumber
yay F did you run off oh I went back in
the house okay okay okay for a
second oh I see you looked in the toilet
already
yes that Mery no I now I have
diarrhea oh no we have tea at home yeah
tea at home yeah uh the sandwich don't
eat the sandwiches guys I thought I
learned my
lesson the sand yeah the Sham
sandwich it looks so tasty you know
simple s you want to raid that house get
you or just the mailbox good mag I mean
the the mailboxes are really good M we
could probably make our way back yeah I
have 13 HP
yeah what is
this sports bag oh cornmeal more
cornmeal for the cornbread
goddess is that me
yes you who else would have Miss Goddess
of course I don't know I heard I heard
bi boo is pretty great
chef N I think I think FAA is where it's
at for
me no chefs can work together chefs can
do chefs ever collab you think that
chefs do collabs together they do right
I'm sure they do I don't
know either of you watched the show The
Bear the bear no I haven't watched it
either but it's about a kitchen like
chefs in a kitchen and apparently I
don't know there's this subreddit that I
like called Kitchen Confidential which
is basically like line Cooks posting
about all the crazy stuff that happened
in their kitchens and I don't know
there's just something about it that
like I really
like it's like they're it's like they're
Pirates together on a pirate ship
working through these tough conditions
all
together and like at the end of their
their 12-hour shifts they'll like cook
food for each other like that could be
you yeah yeah it could be they put the
the most love into the food they get to
cook for their like
coworkers why am I so slow does diarrhea
make you slower God oh no it's cuz I'm
cucumber
OHS uh oh I can carry some stuff for you
oh no it's okay but are we going the
right
way um I think so right this way uh I
didn't check the map see how lost we are
without
gigy I
know GG come back she will I think she
will join after her
collab oh yeah this road just straight
should be
it straight ahead I want to surprise her
by getting her like a really nice weapon
or something a shotguns all right I got
a fire but I don't know if we could get
a a good
shotgun a good shotgun I might get lucky
do you also use shotguns Celly I do but
oh it's a pipe shotgun and it's
very you know we'll have to find a bunch
of shotguns I believe we can be
productive we can be
efficient
absolutely we have to be we must m we
must
be at least the good thing is we know
they're coming we know they'll be there
on the seventh day yeah in a real zombie
apocalypse we wouldn't have this
knowledge
true do you need any food kiaha uh right
now I'm actually really fine all I need
is the tea and the antibiotics okay
especially the tea right now it's
hurting stomachs hurting it's rough
23% of
diarrhea I know this pretty yucky yes
yes uh
man I'm so sad I failed the quest oh why
why okay we can't win all of them I
know the very first thing I did when I
spawned into this game yesterday was eat
an old sandwich mhm and iately got the
debuff but I didn't know what it was and
I thought my character needed to use the
bathroom trying to use a toilet
it didn't work
a well the world is your bathroom in
this game it seems yeah the whole world
I guess so we're home yepe so I made
this food and Medicine Chest here okay
okay wait one second I'll just load off
some my foot like
stuff what's the button
to uh
bring uh the combine like put something
in the box and then automatically have
it combined with another stack you know
what I mean it's the box with the
small the one Arrow the one arrow on
your
inventory oh but now I guess it went
into my inventory other I wanted to to
ah ah there's another one on your
inventory ah oh
okay and is there a button um where I
can like single items I don't have to
like like in Minecraft I think it's like
double click or to put something quickly
into the chest without having to drag it
over
shift yeah oh yeah thank you finally I
noed shift click oh Hallelujah things
are so much easier
now please let me put this in my
inventory I got some shotgun shells do
we have a a box for like
ammo we should make one oh I see some of
the same ammo I'm just going to combine
it
[Music]
yeah pain
killers Salvage tool crafting running
affects your splint time oh I
know I
know I got to run okay antibiotics in
here the
Suka do oh they're in on this chest oh
nice no it's knuckle wraps um hey fauna
if you like punching things you can have
some knuckle wraps if you want ooh I
have some already what level are they I
wonder oh they're just silly level one
knuckle wraps maybe somebody else you
can always yeah you could always scrap
it or yeah o you know what I'll put it
in the weapons chest because there is a
weapons chest if people are out of
weapons they can use
it am I blind I don't see antibio are do
they have a different name is it oh the
vitamin
maybe the vitamins are
antibiotics I I think they get rid of
your oh the SE resist I'll take the
vitamins I should
anyway
oh something I got some buff but don't
know if it's doing that oh no they don't
get rid of infection oh well then I'll
take the honey I thought I had something
that had rid of infection maybe not well
the vitamins are nice to have
okay the honey worked so I'm put the
other honey back
[Music]
and
um maybe I'll just keep saving my
[Music]
money H the armor parts how do you use
armor parts again are they for
crafting I'm not sure oh armor crafting
kits I I
see can I make this I could make it but
I have no more duct tape armor
book no I think I can already make it if
I have the right ingredients I'll steal
some duct
tape M I want to try making this and see
what it
is sing kit W this guy sucks no aloe
vera seeds really kidding me what do you
need Aloe Vera seeds I have one maybe we
have more in total in our house
and I think Shi we have three oh in the
old house they also had some and shieldy
was saying she'll plant it so excellent
then I can make a ton of bandages mod
axe if you mod an axe or so and it's
like broken is that even worth it
modding it I think you can get the mod
back or can you not oh oh well that
would be good
come what how do you
ah there we go okay how does this work
forging armor forging hope one piece at
a time use to craft light medium and
heavy
armors
ooh oh but I still need the skill huh
aha so I still need the books or Chad
tell
me more
books Robotics and armor uh yeah I think
armor books have one armor book and one
robotic book I think I'll I'll read them
if it's
okay yes go
ahead robotics
armor crafting noise damn I've never
read so much in my whole
life yeah you had to get good at
reading uh then I guess next is is
reading Lord of the Rings yeah true why
they make people read magazines in this
game to learn things though it's very
realistic yeah magazines especially I
feel like when I was younger magazines
were still like a popular thing but
nowadays do people still Buy and read
magazines like those celebrity gossip
magazines and stuff maybe if I'm getting
my hair done I'll read one for like five
minutes if it's already there but you
wouldn't buy it on your own and put it
on your coffee table would you no I kind
of miss those days though I used to get
like animal magazines as a kid and I
would always like look forward to
getting them every month and reading the
monthly issue a actually very
cute oh or like wait you probably know
Kiara like those uh old Japanese fashion
magazines oh
yeah and there others too yeah yeah it's
really nostalgic my favorite magazine
however was and I think this is not
really well known in America maybe but
it's
witch what's that it's a it's a magazine
but it's at the same time like a Manga
comic and it was I think it's made in
Italy so it was very popular in Europe
it's like it's like uh winks
Club oh similar to that similar it's
like w.i dot doc do h i remember that
you know it wait I feel like you're
unlocking a core memory did I know this
I have to Google it it was so good I
think they ended up making an anime so
to say too but the magazines were just
the best and I don't or was it yes I did
watch this my gosh this is like
unlocking core memories I think every
every teenage girl like chose one that
they like most connected with and felt
like that's me that's me I'm this girl
I'm that girl and you could never
overlap with your friends oh yeah no no
hell no of course
[Laughter]
not would never yeah good memories
fcking a
day so wholesome good times it is oh my
gosh I used to love roller skating so me
and my my one single friend I had like
in junior high school or even before
Junior High School we were like roller
scho skating through the park and with
the roller skates we felt even more so
that we had magical powers so we were
like just pretending that we had magical
powers from witch or like Charmed and
then we were just like skating around
being like fire
magic it's actually really cute to
imagine good times I want to be a witch
again I know simpler
times a Hol witch Ian Branch back then
nobody had Tik
Tok Tik Tok didn't exist those were
better
times times
indeed what has happened what where are
we now why is it likeu and
everything okay man I wish we got those
Club Penguin perms Club Penguin I never
got into that
Club Penguin was so good CL penguin
would pop off on stream not it really
would maybe it would is it did we did
somebody try maybe we can get it if we
try harder penguin itself is already
dead right yeah there's a fan server
that's still up and going though that's
copy of the original even though I
didn't play it I watched this whole like
deep dive about what happened to Club
Penguin and how the last day went like
all kinds of footage screen recording
yeah yeah
people were so sad and celebrating
beautiful documentaries about about Club
Penguin did you guys uh you guys ever
played Toontown back in the day yeah I
played Toontown yeah Toontown wonder I
just remember the name generation cuz
you couldn't choose your own name right
you had to pick like three mine was like
princess puffy pants or
something they were so silly and I hated
all of them I could never decide on to
name
I
cute uh do we want to go to the trader
now yes I'm ready okay um my only
problem is I have 40 HP I don't want to
waste my one uh first a bandage we
really do painkillers help you
regain HP or not I don't think so I
think they just let you run on like a
sprained leg or something like that that
would make sense oh need someone pain we
need someone to make like to learn first
aidid stuff that' be yeah I learn how to
make
bandages yeah I need Alo Vera so I can
make real bandages to help people I've
been collecting cotton so I can make
cloth okay wa do you need the seeds of
the aloe vera or the aloe vera itself um
aloe vera itself but if I have seeds
then I can grow a bunch of it so okay I
can bring you some seeds yeah I'm going
back to the old house but if you guys
want want to do a quest or something
since you're so close to the trader it's
all good okay okay okay I'll just be
chilling here trying to make cloth I
have no be
careful oh okay pops off at night it
really does
really I have no ammo what am I
blind oh well okay maybe I
food H what ammo you have ammo
do you have no ammo I thought no I don't
know I've used it up in that house I
think
oh and then failed the
quest do you want I have this
knife that people are saying is good the
bone knife knife I have the bone knife
too hunting
knife it's okay I still have my
sledgehammer okay and I could can I make
a better one no iron let me see if I can
figure out what put this skill point
man chat does this mean I need to read
six more of those Sledgehammer
magazines that's so
much yeah okay wow yeah we should just
do a bunch of quests find more magazines
find more ammo find all kinds of things
we got to do a bit of grinding is the
thing mhm yeah I think that's what we've
been kind of missing out on is grinding
a
bunch I can make a level free Sledge is
a is this level oh I see so current one
currently is level
[Music]
one then I shall make one quickly as a
backup
okay I need these fibers and
wood and small stones
okay uh
okay I'm
gonna explore a little
explore you can't hold it in can you I
can't I need to
loot loot Goblin Goblin Instinct kicking
in
yeah reading the magazines is just so
satisfying for some reason yeah it is
yeah I'm going to read the vehicle wait
let me go with you fa okay but then you
can't be too much of a loot
G build something where'd she
go you think we can take a three
skull yeah I mean no maybe not I don't
know I feel like yesterday we were in
the fre skull were we oh yeah were we I
think this place was a three skull oh
yeah right even even the old house was a
free skull yep oh we took it though if
you really want it you can get it I feel
like we're strong I just upgraded my
weapon I'm feeling strong okay okay yeah
I got a I got an upgraded the
sledgehammer now too but 50 HP so I hope
you have full HP I have 105 HP H okay
okay so you're full and but then Kelly
what are you doing right now um I'm
organizing my inventory putting some
weapons away okay uh making some cloths
and then hopefully growing some aloe
vera soon I hope oh that'll oh do you
need the seeds yeah but go ahead and do
your quest first it's not even a quest
she's just being loot Goblin yeah what
is this a corn behind a
wow it's like a holy holy corn maybe oh
watch out watch out watch out watch
out oh there is some aloe vera seeds
nice they're coming out oh real grilled
meat I won't eat all this corn don't
worry I'll
some ah he's kissing my feet FAA yes
he's graveling e e
e I mean I like to make kfp gravel in
front of me but this no no
[Music]
no I'll break this thing down the corn
really I need to know what's what's
what's it about this
corn all right I guess we're drinking
murky water can't be helped oh this is a
lot team
what is this destroyed chemistries what
oh yeah I loed that there wasn't
anything too exciting though just
plastic sorry I punched you I'm soorry
now I'm at 12
hp I'm so sorry it's okay I'll stay with
the
[Laughter]
fire yeah this house is weird
sh
died uhoh
understandable I I get it release the
corn free the corn freedom for the
corn why did they imprison the
corn yeah what's so special about this
corn
oh uh oh super corn seed recipe
really look oh yeah super corn like when
I opened it the imprisoned corn it gives
me a super corn seed recipe and the
super corn seed
itself nice we can make super
cornbread yeah dirty water
no super
coin I should just die I want to go up
or down there's a scary basement okay
but I will not be a much help really
with 14 HP
oh yeah you stay you stay back
okay okay there's a fast
one I'll meet up with you
[Applause]
guys back it
up you're like you're like on a roll you
won't let them oh I leveled up wow let's
go on let me oh I have I have stuff too
I want to use my skill
[Music]
point is there is there a
base
water
think I'm going to start tanking tank
build oh I have no point tank oh
yeah I didn't quite see you as a tank
originally but I think you were destined
for
it I'm ready to smack
them yeah spank them yeah I
will what was that no
I'm
scared maybe my game oh is she dead oh
am I am I I think she's dead oh I had a
huge
lag me too oh then hopefully she was
lagging
too would only be
fair hey what
the was
that you can search the shoes stinky
socks oh don't look at the shoes the
shoes are not worth
it
water oh what my gosh is this super
lettuce oh no way press e to activate
switch
what's what the hope I die from it why
is Cecilia Oh wait she's in the in the
voice chat too oh hello what did did me
wait wait wait did me activate the the
switch create cicilia out of fin
air yeah you called me thank you so can
I make
more no can you make more
one I'm cloned hi I was wondering
through the darkness and I saw you guys
here let me what what's going on what
are you doing we're harvesting a super
plants just raiding o
nice oh dang it that did not give me any
super
lettuce but maybe the super lettuce is
somewhere
else nope I'm not healed are we lagging
R just so you guys know you retain your
broken limbs even if you die oh really
oh really
no can't escape the broken limbs you
can't escape it funa what are you
thinking about sweet release of oh I'm
just thinking about my
XP my sweet sweet
XP should we go up uh yeah I'm I'm still
very curious about this fire in here but
uh oh I think we can well it just leads
to the super corn
right oh I guess so
science I think we should turn it off oh
it's off yeah ah was that the super corn
yeah the non Brute Force way but FR you
turned on the fire again cuz it became
so bright oh
no I wouldn't do
that messed up can't believe you did
that
almost oh how could you how could you
the beautiful sounds I feel really
strong all of a sudden
oh dead corn not super corn because of
the super corn
yeah
nice can we go on to the roof oh more
spikes I didn't see those it's so
dark I don't know if there's any point
to going on the roof but it's found
P
yeah
yeah uh okay well I think I'll bring the
super corn home to be
safe yes you want want to go to the
scary basement oh
yeah oh there's a lady out here yeah
there's a zombie at the entrance did you
oh you are so wonderful fauna oh the way
you just smash her freaking
skull that's right I've never seen you
like this before Faun of it's kind of
hot I like someone who can protect me
more silorn stay back more silorn
protector my gosh there's like a secret
area down here with a lot of zombies and
more Super
corn yeah maybe more Super corn
M okay I i' I got more Super
corn get that are you are you trying to
prevent people from making more Super
corn by destroying these things yes this
is our
recipe yes no one shall copy this now
oh working stiff seal shipping
crate I feel like this corn has a Better
Living environment than we have so far
look at this so pretty this would be a
good house to take
over's working on a de collector right
now A a do do collector ah the the yeah
so we can get water easily
she's thinking ahead she's playing the
long
game
box
cute got a radiator there's a lot of
dead people you you guys killed a lot of
zombies FAA killed a lot of
zombies I think these guys were not mind
doing maybe experim on zombies maybe
this was no they were using that as
fertilizer oh they were
take the CN stop I Really Turn us into
zombies I think so wait there's a
there's a another path
down this is a whole cult keep going and
going it is it's crazy oh H is this a
dead oh it goes even even more
down should we jump um I'm
scared I'll jump first careful your legs
I'm fine I I landed on mattresses is it
safe uh there is a zombie looking giant
boar but it is currently
sleeping there's also around 30
corpses oh my oh it's like a boss Faun
this was so wrong we shouldn't have gone
here it's a freaking boss fight well
there doesn't seem to be any other way
out probably like Dark Souls DLC or
something like that okay I I'll kind it
around I don't do that much damage wait
there is there's a path here okay I
won't detect it I W which is maybe the
maybe it's that's a idea Emer SE path oh
I'm sorry I hit you so
sorry it's okay it's okay you have
aggressions and they need to be let
out
yes okay there so much free XP lying
around what the goat I mean boar should
we try to fight the more we can always
run away right or come back here if we
die yeah okay okay I I I I'll I'll I'll
poke it oh food crafting magazine for
you FAA I took it for you for now are
you fighting the bo oh no oh
no fire fire oh
no died I'm scared I'm running I'm
running I'm running get out of
there R run run run having a hard
time it it Sur won't maybe we can shoot
it from here yeah but I have no ammo and
no AR
arrows but that would be probably a good
strategy for sure yeah maybe we can come
back here eventually with more skill and
more Health oh we can mark it on the map
like a boss I'll once my ankle we get
the loot anyway though
yeah also kiaha can you invite
CeCe I think you're the
leader armor
magazine oh yeah some holes H fun let me
drop you the cooking magazine here oh
thank you this place seems messed up mhm
I'm sure there's some L today the
apocalypse there's a cage with a bunch
of
people run run run run
oh no what was that
sound
away what is I screamed so hard I broke
my microphone and I
I I'm so dead take some trenches how am
I going to get back my backpack Faun did
you
die no h just spawn near your backpack
grab it and leave yeah but it's like you
don't understand cie it's like so deep
in the boy is right there be
careful it's right
there it's hitting me ow I have three HP
wait do you have B Arrow I don't have
any arrows we need yeah we need ranged
and we can kill it h where okay can you
do you remember where the entrance was I
don't I can't find it cuz I go from the
other way I think I can get my
backpack oh true yeah
I mean I think it's you have to go down
the basement and you'll find it okay
I'll
try oh
I you digging a mo yeah I am oh okay I
found it I think the way I found one
backpack is that Cecilia's backpack I
guess um yours should be lighting blue
yeah so it's not lighting blue then
that's mine okay uh but is I no no no no
no how am I ever going to get my
backpack is it still there yeah the bo
is right where my backpack is I can try
to distract
it wait somebody's backpack is right
here oh it's oh ce's got hers back
now back exactly yeah that the other
one's
mine oh okay okay I'm going to get it
I'm going to get it don't come down here
don't come down here your backpack's by
the ladder I think okay
okay he's through the
wall he's like in the wall I got it I
got my backpack I'm and I'm out I'm out
is he in the wall yeah he's like half in
the wall okay okay okay because he was
no don't fall down don't go out he's not
stuck he was just like I sprained my leg
why did you go down oh
no yay we got a backp back well now we
know if we see a house with free skulls
it might have a boss fight
yeah that's crazy but it's crazy that
you did it with just the two of you it's
crazy just that was fun it was mostly
just her really I didn't do
anything doing your best don't sell
yourself short Kiara no really I I
really wasn't doing
anything okay well we should really
start doing Trader
quests I'm coming yeah I'm going to help
you guys it's so bright out here is it
bright for everybody else it's nice
really bright foggy oh I shouldn't jump
this wait do painkillers
help my ankley try it out now is the
time for experiments wait I can make a
splint for
you oh wait does that help sprain or
only in broken leg I I still have a
finished splint with me do you have any
it helps I'll give it to you and you can
try I have an El seed Kelly still one
just one though I have a ton of bandages
and we're GNA need health oh bandages or
the normal ones or the first a ones
normal ones I want to make first a
ones need I don't want to waste it I I
can make those I found they're very easy
to make I found another room where it's
there's like a tiny boar in here I guess
they're experimenting that too a tiny Bo
wait CE are you a doctor yeah wait come
here I have have a book for you then
this is so messed up I love learning oh
but this boy is kind of friendly oh I
can't use it here take your splint back
oh oh I'm a terrible doctor oh you have
a here's here's a piece of wood
here I don't have anything else sorry so
here's the the way that painkillers work
is that you can eat them and it heals HP
over time but it takes a big chunk of
water and they don't heal broken legs
you know if you're just not feeling so
good I is see why is it so bright in
here am I
sick wait I can just is your spray ankle
it's like making everything
brighter me you
guys let's all try to not oh there's
another boar okay I'm going to try
killing it wait no I'll leave it be no
this one's like suffering oh I feel bad
for
them let let them roam free maybe
these are fine these are not
experimented on yet they're they they
seem nice they haven't been
attacking
a man this place is so messed up it
doesn't seem to be Want to Be Free it's
like I like it here wait are you guys
corn and bores yes oh it does have Bo in
the name doesn't it oh that was
foreshadowing
corn and bors those aren't going to to
be very
nice oh to be very nice it's free
XP it's free
XP weirdo she's doing what she has to do
no I'm
kidding oh we even get the shared XP do
we yeah so don't
complain sorry you're right wait it's
that alive I'm sorry I punched it I
thought it was dead no no oh baby
no now we hey it's free XP it's okay
it's
free the apocalypse has changed me well
I'm getting some steak at least we can't
let it go to waste but what if it's like
poison zombie steak because they're like
no no no no this one's fine oh okay this
one's not
yet have you seen have you seen the boar
where that was killing us that one's
poison yeah yeah is it a zombie boar
yeah yeah was green oh cool very green
seems like being green is a trend
nowadays huh Green
Girls Green's great Green's great
actually what sometimes how big is this
place ah sorry I thought it was dead too
oh my God no no
so it's not just
me
help the boy is
so
what no I had like 4 HP for the last 20
minutes it's oh
no one shot me too strong kill it all
right I'm here ladies with my shotgun oh
okay how much ammo do you have I have 37
rounds you want to kill the big Bo the
big Bo it just it takes a long time to
reload so I'll need some distractions
yeah a
ker okay that might be possible of
Callie help what is this all right I'm
ready is it Smokey in here or is it just
me I feel like I'm going crazy the area
is foggy but it it's inside as well for
some reason I thought it was just me
graphic macular degeneration or
something K what did you say it's
because you GRE guys are underground no
currently we were on like I think the
first level we were underground but
uh uh let's see where are you I can't
find my way back to you oh aloe vera
nice e to pick up the a plant I'm going
to scrap that
ow oh there's a lot of boes in here
still were they here before I don't
think so were we in here before I think
we were but this house is huge it's
confusing
yeah this is a really big house I can't
even find you guys wait you guys either
I found you hello there you are lead me
to the
enemy all
right fa yeah but the back uh I guess
the exit is the better entry now wa yeah
where is the the boar is it over here
it's in the big cage I think down is
probably the easiest way to get to it
it's over here one moment hold on just a
sec let me scrap this really quick see
if I get some aloe vera dang it I don't
have any aloe that's fine I'm coming
let's do it oh wait I have seeds for you
yeah key this one is also seeds seeds
thank you here I have some ammo for you
really here let's go then I'll help I'll
try to help what typ of ammo do you need
rifle world oh thank you I have 7.8 62 I
don't know what that is uh I need um yes
that exactly one oh okay wait then take
it y now we're looking a little bit
better ladies for the boy Mission if
only don't you think I wonder if there's
an actual quest for this or is this just
no Quest oh there might be a quest I'm
pretty sure that like Quest stuff is
separate from General exploring we just
killing him for fun do you want rotten
flesh cat
I'm good thank you I can I'll pass on
that somebody said you wanted rotten
flesh oh what what was it really this
way I thought it was the other one to
get directly to the board a big cage
right yeah the big big the
Grace Grace cage in a cage but he was
still hurting you no no no he the big
one was out of the cage uh there was no
be careful you'll break your angle if
you don't use the ladder sh oh how I use
it dang it no I didn't break anything
thank god oh good all righty he's right
there come down girls you think the Bo's
name is
GRA oh
he's that would be kind of
nice
uhoh do it do it k i all I think I'm oh
God I only have 40 HP I'm alive that's a
two shot nice nice I think that the the
boar lost track of me
I still have six ammo
okay I'm afraid of this ladder yeah the
ladder is the scariest part to be honest
yeah oh oh God oh
God got to try and get the backpack
somehow is this the right gun to shoot
him from here chat is this what this
[Laughter]
be I wish I could see how much HP he has
I know where's his boss bar
we don't get any loot from killing this
guy though do we I think we'll get a lot
of meat maybe we'll get Super
Meat I'm running okay
bye click right click
to what but doesn't lock on him
right oh he's there he's there good I'm
glad there now I can cheese him heck
yeah you can cheese him oh yeah I can
okay I'm shooting to in his ass don't
let him
move
[Music]
yeah oh there's a zombie up
here no help no please don't no no no
okay I'll try to distract him
him okay come
on he's got a lot of H
rattle this pig huh I'm out of
ammo is this even worth
it it has to be oh I think what you can
do K you can go through this hole and
then you can kite him through it oh yeah
you see the hole to your left and jump
let me get out of here first real quick
oh the ladder's broken that's no good
well
like
through what like for real
oh super broken he's eating my body so
hurry kill him super punches we got a
super punch oh he's my body I'm down
here with him he doesn't seem to attack
unless we attack him first no no no no
no no he will attack he wants to he's
eager to no no he's got our
number um well I I have nothing I'm not
going to go down
there um wait how do I get out now if
the if the but is broken is It Broken Oh
I thought you said it was it seems to be
fine down but getting out's a little
hard oh I
okay okay got my backpack didn't intend
to do this but
uhoh sir can you not do well at
least no I can try to land a few more
hits with my
sledgehammer that exp dead is going to
be popping off oh nice oh he's not
attacking oh now he's attacking okay all
right Ro he's done
burning oh no I think it's going to be
hard to get my backpack until until
maybe uh he's let away from that area n
you just got to like surprise him yeah
CC's soloing him H what if we uh place
place blocks around BL there's like
holes there's holes and if you jump down
the Hol he can't get through the hole
and then you can just kind of circle him
but I don't have a gun so I can't
really do a lot of damage but it's it's
pretty
safe if we just keep on clearly Landing
a few hits and then dying and then
Landing a few hits and then dying we'll
make it eventually yeah we'll kill him
eventually true come on come on get down
only problem is if the ladder is broken
how do we get back out again I think
it's not really broken you just jump up
to oh okay okay you just keep circling
him right um no okay maybe up here it
might be jump through this hole this
this hole here is he did you kill him I
killed
him e it's yucky looking you son of a
bacon eater what did you drop let's see
what he dropped um ton of stuff
really okay um yeah you guys this is you
guys' fine so you guys can look through
the
loot oh vehicle crafting skill oh armor
crafting SK
hello hey he gives back my ammo there's
shotgun ammo too guys found a nice house
oh shotgun ammo I'll take that take it
take it and then there's there's some
medicine and stuff and some food you
guys are in the the boar
area we killed the
barar nice a big poisonous experimented
boar was there the vehicle
if somebody wants to
learn I want to learn I already have
one okay I'll leave the food and the
medicine if anyone wants it w I have
bullets for you thank you oh wait do you
need um I have a to
digest yeah that's what I thought you
say it kind of the same way I
guess okay for it's wow wow
and wow it's getting difficult I can
totally tell the difference a chest
locked does anyone have a lock oh
destroy it with your Hammer yeah we can
I have a sledgehammer magazine if anyone
wants oh I've been using those I've been
learning okay I'm going to leave it at
the new house I'll just make like a
storage bin and leave stuff in there
thank
you yep yeah I'm looking for oh
someone's hitting me someone someone's
stop oh my sledgehammer is too big I'm
sorry who is it is this a new house
probably
me I don't know what I'm
hitting I do big AOE damage okay okay to
open if we all work together there go oh
there's a big
here once this chest is open must have
given us a lot of food no a lot of meat
yeah yeah I got a a lot of steaks in
total from this adventure I got 58
steaks and
80 80 Le levers and we got the super
corn seeds so we can grow super corn
super corn M and I got an an ear of
super corn and the super corn seed
recipe so we can make more Super
corns wow
love this is so stupid all the sakks
it's worth it it's going to be worth it
super corn is super
rare oh my God look at thisa caveman oh
hello what's happening would you like to
join us yeah
sure hit it hit
it wait is someone
healing super corn is used for most high
tier food stuff
let
me and there there are only five spots
on the whole map where super corn spawns
it's super rare and it's used for high
teer look at
you my little corn
expert chat is the corn expert here guys
where are you can I please have the pre
we should be heading to the old house
right everything else please can I wear
it really quick so I can show you guys
what I took here let me yeah do it
[Applause]
wow amazing OHL
finally worth it all guys can you hear
me yeah yeah can hear you I I I cannot
find you I'm right now they went they
went underground look for a cage and
then there's a hole in the
cage strug over here oh there's 9 mm Amo
oh I can use that here oh is it here and
other stuff I won't take anything oh it
is is it possible get back out maybe you
can jump on me can I I can actually but
how are you going to get
out you can dig your way out you can
climb I think I was thinking maybe
placing a building block Maybe
this still there you go
fix there you go
prob she's so
smart okay oh did your girls like did
your girls finish making like finish
doing your quest uh yeah we did a bunch
of yeah we did some we didn't we still
didn't do a single
one wow we killed the bo yeah that's
good I hope you make bacon out of stuff
so yeah I'm I'm going to go bring all
the steaks and the super corn to our new
house I haven't seen our new house yet
where is that me neither new house it's
near this area
actually oh that's nice then we could
couldn't we use the super corn thingy
and actually plant stuff and then use it
and harvest it we should you get seeds
out of it I think they did they I might
be able to get seeds if I eat some
uh no I I have seeds and I have the
recipe for the seeds so oh that's good
that's big chicken who the new home then
I will follow I'm not sure who's yes um
I'm on the way to problem is solved okay
okay I need to go to the new home to
because I'm I'm also going to store some
things we make that the water problem
I'll just learn
it just going to follow you guys so did
what happened to the old house that we
just saw did you abandon it or is there
still stuff there I think you're
supposed to spike it up cuz we're still
going to use it as sacrifice we're going
to use it as a sacrificial house when
the
H what time is that going to happen how
long 10 p.m. to 4:00
a.m. 10 minutes hour 10 minutes yeah to
prepare good luck then we should
probably do the reinforcement of the
house maybe with traps and stuff yeah
yeah yeah yes yes I a bunch of spes and
I dug a moat
Mo it's so cool so I think we should
probably have um one person collect wood
and then like others can make spikes and
all that mm I have tons of wood I also
have tons of wood I'm making a bunch of
spikes okay so we head to the old house
no correct yeah right now we're at the
new house I think
okay what you need to
do uh
[Music]
okay um okay how about like um someone
gets wood someone gets iron from Cars
cuz that can be used to reinforce wooden
spikes and turn them
into
really do you just like destroy the car
how does it work yeah you use your axe
on it and that should be giving you uh I
think iron
Parts yeah yeah it does walk got so much
now I'm going to take this hunting knife
if that's okay since I use knives M
yes I'm just going to put all the stuff
like in
hereand I'm
destroying oh f i put all the meat did
you see it oh I think you saw it okay
good good cooking that meat for our
special night our special zombie night
date
night night with zombies yippee yeah of
course like prom
night it's basically the same maybe we
can dance if we kite around them then
it's kind of like a dance yeah and it's
kind and you have to be distant you know
I've seen a lot of um uh Hollywood
movies and it's like children at high
school and there's like the the teachers
no you have to be more dist from each
other so it's basically oh man when I
went to prom they were just like
twerking and I was surprised no one
stopped that's not what the movie Tau me
I know that's not what Hollywood showed
we have like 2,000 wood here should we
take that to the new
house um yeah I think new house or old
house old house probably you oh old
house old house and we also have 390
iron so should I
probably I think I need to like move
everything uh
still I don't have time I'm so weak no
you're fine you're fine maybe we should
designate who want to collect
what are there some workstation
magazines in the old house by any
chance or does some did somebody
make what kind of magazines workstation
magazines or did somebody make a
workbench already perhaps they're super
rare I was looking for it I don't think
anybody can make one yet I have I have
free on it but just free and if I get a
workbench I already leveled up my armor
stuff to the next level so I can make
heavy armor and mid armor and so all
that apparently oh nice uh what type of
magazine do you need for that but first
I need workstation magazines then with
the workbench I can make the new armor
it
seems okay okay got to get workbench if
I find any I want you know okay oh the
hous is are far okay yeah
I just want to be able to make ammo
that's the main thing oh I have a
shotgun magazine for you oh thank you so
hopefully maybe it'll help yes thank you
so much I'll take I need to die
again I'm I'm
dead probably should get a run dids no
my legs is break is broken like oh you
need
aint do you need me if anybody can craft
for me but I'm pretty far away from home
so there's a there's a cast in um the
new
house if feel like the problem is that
um I have a broken leg and I'm in the
middle of nowhere no I I have a splint I
can make splints I don't know if where
you are or you could just die oh you can
wait for me I'm on my way where you are
or you okay I mean I'm very slow so it
takes going to take a while yeah just
keep
break your
leg if you break your leg you guys um
and then you die you keep the broken leg
what are your intrusive thoughts telling
you to
do what what are your intrusive thoughts
telling you to do oh to go out and loot
stuff no we're going to do a quest VA
we're going to do a
quest no more BS Quest okay okay no more
bores you caught me trying to sneak out
yeah I noticed I have an ey eat
this do we want to do we want to go into
voice chat and then do quests yeah yeah
okay okay oh can I do a quest with you I
would like to get a couple more money
for um sure sure for Papa for a armor I
okay yes I'm not gonna lie I actually
want to go do a quest with you guys too
F okay well oh sorry sorry damn it I
keep on tapping in um yeah if everybody
wants to do quests again I think like
separate groups would be good again but
if it is just if it's just do for then
that's fine I
think I mean me broken leg I don't know
if I can okay I be at the old house
trying to reinforce the old house
I I've changed my mind I'll go no no no
no no no vc2 for Quest make Quest doers
don't where am I I feel like I'm now far
away
from let's see let's see how do I tab
into this game without punching people
yeah I'm afraid I'm afraid when I tab
back in K's gonna get punched with
my wait but punching is punching left
click and right click yeah damn it I
can't T into the game oh wait I can just
T I want to get punched okay stay right
in front of you I did oh I didn't punch
you you still want to be punched I'm
pretty
[Music]
strong she's she's good
wait that was like 40 of my
health H wait C I'm low don't punch me
people I sent you an invite Oh yay okay
and I got it I think Cecil is in a
different group or like is a different
VC so okay this group four people sounds
good okay let's do
it let's go to the trader and find
hold on let me get some food food oh
yeah me too me too a little
bit um yeah I think we have time for
like a quest or two and then we probably
need to head back to start fortifying
the base okay as much as we can but I
believe that the folks back there will
do a good
job
yes I'm close to my next level too is
that pizza no how fast does this thing
cook it's kind of slow
H I still have one skill point available
but I don't know what to put it in maybe
shotgun is the Sham for cooking too the
can of sham you can eat it okay just for
emergency all right yeah I'll I'll
already go towards the trader and look
at what quests he has yeah okay Trader
out something nice for us yeah we want
do we want uh one of those fetching
quests or one of those um
I like the clear out Quest I know you do
I know you do you already
know I just want to punch
stuff that's fine we can do
that are we going the right way yeah
right just down the
road fall no
punch I'm getting stronger yesterday I
wasn't that strong with my punches yeah
you took out 40 of my
health that was a really strong punch
what with one punch 40 one she's one
punch woman girl yeah wow yeah one punch
girl cute imagine how much health the
zombies have though it takes me like six
punches oh man yeah you just need like
the right wraps around your fists I
think or like a stronger
weapon yeah I need more magazines before
I can make the next weapon for fist
magazines are so important okay there's
cleared zombies not so far away actually
434 M away that seems good I'll take it
okay I'm going towards the quest and I
will not start it until all of you are
there
okay it's over oh okay A bit of a run it
is it is
like a little bit past the uh Traer
sorry can't get out
here need more
stamina right yeah have SK I wish it was
like GTA where like the more you run the
better your stamina becomes I know
right punch what's the what's the skill
point skill thing for
stamina is is there which one which one
is it agility is there even one
um agility
well maybe not no it's it's just um
stamina of jumping for
agility oh oh well I'll put it
into something else need to try and
craft as much tea as
possible damage tea is good for you
gives you like Buffs and stuff like that
which
tea both uh the red tea especially and
and the Golden Rod as well oh the Golden
Rod very good I've drunken drunk drunk
that a few times they're familiar with
that one yeah it's a blessing a big
blessing all right didn't use my skill
point cuz I can't decide but we're going
towards the I think for is stamina
fortitude fortitude huh
M
fortitude for fortitude
fortitude ah it's a okay but probably
like you don't always get it with each
level huh because this time it says
stuff you get
different oh ah oh the bonus is
different but you still get like
physical resilience whatever that means
I guess okay oh I think cardio rule one
cardio gives you cardio stamina region
oh
yeah I did see that it's probably good
well it's gone
now that's fine you can get next time
I'm sure we'll level up
again a fortitude doesn't give stamina
it's the it's the running perk thingy
under
fortitude m running perk I don't I don't
I will never understand I think even
after seven days I will never understand
this whole skill it's the it's the
recovery perk rule one cardio under 42
tab okay well my point is gone so maybe
next time I get a level
up all right I'm I'm coming up on the
place
okay H do you see it on your map yep oh
nice a big orange exclamation point
freaking mushroom mining company again
again okay well we should try to nice
yeah it's fun if we do different ones
though then we unlock more different
ones yeah I have a quest at the at the
cafe so I have one a different place
Cafe
yeah well should we do the mushroom
first and then go to the cafe yeah that
SS a good idea all right I'm at the
entrance uh is this are you close enough
okay start starting now oh yes let's go
ladies got a big number two Club we're
coming in like a wrecking
ball I got a knife I got a knife I have
fists let's speedrun this
out uh-oh ah I'm Bing oh wait that's
when you got it
I wonder if the number of zombies
increases depending upon the people
thank
you people involved I feel like it might
I got too excited there were only a few
zombies when I did it alone oh really oh
that's good that's good that they take
that into account yeah I know how
considerate of
them
consideres yeah teing up get
okay we got a couple I hear them
Yep they're like turkeys turkey noises
gobble
gobble you uhoh oh there's another doer
get
ready
nice good job
team that sound so
satisfying she's brutal with that
[Music]
knife hello
oh stay this is a stronger Club quite
stronger these ones are like so
terrifying but they remind me of
mermaids super
tanky do they I guess
so not the
they just want to be Ariel you
know can't blame them oh some of the
stuff that bi boo wants ammo wise is in
here oh 9 mm nightstalker I'm going to
take this meat stew yeah and then oh
some of the ammo that Kiara wants is in
this wooden crate
oh yippee oh night stalk what that do
extra damage for
fun if anybody wants scrapping for fun
what's wrapping for fun Salvage tool
crafting
[Music]
skill I wish take the N9 M of
meat do like the scavenge
oh I will use the
nightstalker what is the
nightstalker doing damage to sleeping
victims I'm going to slice their throat
at night
okay all right bio yeah sounds good is
there a quicker way out of here you can
jump if you use the ladder you can jump
over here it's kind of
scary I didn't do that
before now it's the T ah no no no
no oh I have a broken leg by the time
the zombies come but I have a splint I
have a
splint no not again not
[Applause]
again oh right it went down to 37
minutes okay okay well only 37 minutes
only
37 I wish you guys could carry
me I
wish put you on my back how are you
going get out of there kiar good
question good question I don't know I
was thinking the same thing just
now you watching me ohaha there's got to
be a way out what if you place a bunch
of blocks and make some STS yeah I feel
like we know the way out oh can I do
it you get it you get my
joke you you want me to kill you no
because years ago we played a way out
together we play way
out you're being silly I many many a
years ago Pat you on the face not hard
enough to be a slap but not soft enough
to be a caress you want to slap me B
soft one you know why those were the
good times
that was the one of the Connect Four
right yeah I love how that's the wa I
don't know where what way I'm going oh
oh oh you guys are out there already you
are yeah oh we finished itar thank and
go to the bio Quest that's across the
lake oh but do don't do we have to give
the quest back first in order to accept
a new one I don't know
no you can do multiple yeah you can turn
multiple Quest at one so we can go to
the other one and then go back all right
I'll follow you okay you lead the way uh
it is
west
west not not W West does anybody have
any snacks only the Sham wrong way I
have I have one meat snack here you go I
have snack thank you maybe we'll find
more food for the Traer so let me go
turn around yeah I'm coming I'm
coming I'm going to I'm going to walk a
little bit here and there so that I
don't make my leg
worse whatever works for
you should be healed by the time the
horde comes hopefully the hoorde the
hoorde for the hoorde they do be
coming and it's very scary apparently is
it very scary yeah it becomes red it's
like a red blood moon yeah that sounds
great just
like oh yeah be fine though I mean we
have a ton of you know ammo and such we
just need to work on our strategy we can
probably do it the last 30 minutes
before is their strategy punch them
punch their heads couple ideas which is
you know maybe try and get high ground
and such or just don't die strategies
trying to punch a plant don't die you
did punch a plant sorry I did punch a
are you are you girls purposefully
walking slow for me yeah I want you want
to
cry you
[Music]
too we're here for you everybody
together in the apocalypse oh yeah I'm
totally here for you oh yeah babo you're
far away just scouting scouting ahead to
scouting I'm scouting ahead that's
perfectly fine make sure the make sure
the the your path is clear because of me
I've been killing them
okay crony joined the
game she made it maybe she can go
fortify the base a little bit oh yeah oh
true fortify the base she's good at base
building why does this phrase sound so I
don't know it rings a bell with me
fortify the base fortif fortify it's
like a keyword or some secret have you
ever played DOTA too
no your base is now
fortified wow that was a great announc
of voice you should you should you
should narate a a what was it a what
league is called am MOA there we go you
should narrate a MOA I want to
yeah am I sprinting but I'm not
sprinting are you sure I don't think
so we're great swimmers
I'm a little scared I might not be able
to make it across I think you'll be okay
you'll be
fine recover your recover your stamina
under the water and then come back up to
breathe it's
okay you'll be fine I just realiz my
character's nails are painted apocal oh
yeah wow mine too they're really pretty
they're better than my IRL Nails fresh
manicure even in the
apocalypse wow prior
I know this is why this is why I should
never play Guy characters I miss out on
the cutesy girly stuff yeah exactly dang
it I feel you only female characters
from now
on I want to be a Burly mustached
apocalypse man that's what I was
thinking but I now I missed out on the
painted nails it's like I can't be that
in real life so like in my fantasy game
I kind of want to try it you
know understandable be what you want to
be
yeah where are my ladies at where my
ladies go us we're still swimming yeah
we're still swimming across the the lake
oh I think it's over there I'm not going
to swim I'm going to run around I think
it'll take a am of
time wait where where exactly what it
might not
actually oh wait there's more
go hey people are you already there are
you house still swimming wait I think
we've been in that house before fauno
yeah we have I think I guess the zombies
respawn yeah yeah if if it's a new Quest
the zombies will just respawn again
beautiful
memories I am thirsty in the
water oh do you want to wear my hat for
a minute it lets you drink Lake water
magic hat really oh a magical hat it is
a magical hat it works it works I can I
can tell you she's not
lying she ain't a big fat liar unlike
me or uh oh he knows crony who lied
about drinking from the
sky can you not drink from the sky if
it's raining no just open your mouth but
honestly if you're like like so thirsty
lost in the Sahara Desert or so I feel
like if it's raining from the sky that's
your last resort and you probably are
going to look up and try to catch some
rain water you better you better true
enough I would do it I would be that
desperate
yeah all right good job
[Music]
yippee here we go into the quest think
it's okay going a little bit oh that way
oh yeah no it's a little bit farther
oh leave it to you
B well it is going to be night time
pretty soon so we'll have
to we got
this yeah we might have to turn it in
tomorrow morning tomorrow yeah
armed that dude's armed in dangerous the
biker
again oh biker again yeah he looks like
a GTA biker yeah look at us all beating
him up in a
circle I'm 10
HP oh yikes I know I'm pretty low too
you have any bandages I wonder um I have
regular bandages I have a regular
bandage just got to hope for that
natural healing
vitamins need to level up for more
natural
healing o hiker I got the cardio stamina
up yeah is this it I think this is it B
painkillers apparently those heal you
yeah they just make you thirsty is the
thing if I'm near a lake I can drink the
lake
yeah you should be
fine it's okay worst case I'll just die
and then it'll be back to full
health true oh is it Bobs huh is it this
place the Bob's Place yeah Bobs what are
we doing here people we clearing we fing
yeah we're clearing the area oh easy
enough F wait is FIA here I'm here okay
hold on let me make sure I'm here boom
okay here we go
oh the door's locked Infiltrate The
System oh you
respawned
whoa
onward zombos hello zombone oh sorry
sorry this
now I don't want to use my sledgehammer
when you girls are so
close I know the friendly fire was funny
at first now I'm kind of like H maybe we
should turn it off
this is silly
though brass is actually good you can do
stuff with brass so I'll pick it
up what are you using the toilet foror H
just looking for the murky
water we can change murky water to good
water right yeah yeah
you 8 HP sorry okay you're okay you're
going to be okay death is imminent about
fighting too much Kiara we got you we
got you all right I'm chilling if you
see trouble you just feel free to
run I'm I'm going to loot Goblin my
friends are I'm looting
too blueberry pie cash oh cooking
magazine
F what's up here here for my for my
personal private Chef uhoh um I found a
rooftop guys but there's there are dudes
oh there's a lot of zombies there's a
lot of great crates though so you want
to climb the ladder there's a ton of
loot but there's also a ton of dudes
where's the
ladder in another back room it's a red
you're in the
room oh there's on your head watch out
oh no I appreciate dying
honestly then I'm back to full health
this
better yeah but the quest oh well you
can have some of the loot how about that
oh
no oh did the quest we give you some
nice loot wait my other one too is gone
because it's not on my top should be
fine I think but it's not on my top
right anymore it doesn't say anymore
like give it back maybe when you talk to
the traitor it will work I hope
so please my other one's fine okay wants
here my ammo yeah there's some ammo for
you up here hey didn't somebody say leg
uh does not get healed by dying but is
healed oh oh I got C hey that's no fair
game appreciate that game it's messed up
yours didn't heal cie no damn rude the
heck what next time I'll just
die why why wait literally what's the
point to wait if you're level six ah
after level six your leg will get healed
when you die I'm no no cat food
interesting tasty yum yum cat food
interesting
chilly oh
yummy well I mean I guess we cleared
this one too huh bio did you you think
we cleared it yeah I got I got the done
we were so close to clearing it before I
died if only I had held on a little bit
longer it's okay let's do another
Quest yeah I can run now we might have
time for one more I think we have time
for one more more Quest I think so too
is he closed now the guy he's closed
okay okay all right we can do quest in
the do we have a quest do we does
anybody have one oh Callie uh take this
oh thank you
boom Oh something for me oh it's the
other way
around oh what level I am am I how do
you level six what I get exp punishment
thank you
exp punishment exp penalty when you die
after level six oh we're in the you got
to be
careful maybe we should head back to the
base for now if it's going to be night
because then what if okay then we lose
the class are definitely harder at night
time yeah no easy outs by die the B
shall we yeah uh let's go back it's very
far away but we can make it
let's have a nice nice walk yeah a nice
night time walk maybe we can stay at the
new house to be honest cuz that might be
better oh yeah we could stand there yeah
let's go there I have also pretty far
but yeah but it's not as far as the new
the old house so this way this way
careful lots of zombies spawn at night
so just run from them run run run run
run run run run run or stab them yeah
stabbing is good too it's just just
they're very feral and
strong so you know if their eyes are not
glowing they're not too bad
yeah the glowy eye ones though you want
to get away from right yeah those ones
are
scary yeah should we oh can I can I
borrow your hat to drink from the water
real your hat too I'm going to die I
also oh if you want a painkiller
too if you're weak here let me throw
some painkillers
around all right you need got the pain
killer hookups and and then I think the
vitamins will be useful to use during
the there's Hat zombie attack give it
back yeah cuz it gives you disease
resist so oh that's good yeah I'll take
him down HP cie get to the edge oh my HP
is all right I'm at 71 press
e The Edge have empty hands too Zip Zip
Zip Zip Zip I'll take the hat too z z
Zip Zip Zip Zip Zip Zip okay I'm here's
the Hat it's a really good hat I'm going
to Bor real quick it's like the best hat
in the game yeah not as good as your hat
Callie okay there you go I preach your
hat mhm at least style
wise it is not bad I'm not going to lie
did I accidentally make another oh some
scary sounds happening yeah uh oh hang
on I heard it
too at Le Luffy take some sips real
quick come on drink aren't you drinking
drink yeah at the edge oh empty sorry
empty hands all right let's do it m
I'm sipping I do be
sipping uh yeah why is where' you find
this hat fun this is broken there's a
there's a mod in it a water purifier mod
that I just
found you can mod your
stuff interesting on my machine gun okay
thank you I think I'm I think I'm all
good with
water okay let me drop the hat thank you
so much f
[Music]
go
anytime Big
Ups all right I guess we got to swim
back huh mm trigger what does this mean
chat what does this do increase rate of
fire never mind I know
it I I made my machine gun
better
nice yeah I guess we can modify our
weapons huh mhm you can
okay it fires a burst is that good or
bad can add spikes to my club let's go
right click for what for
aiming all right I'm going to swim swim
swim me
too
swimming in I guess in 4 hours or so it
opens again but then we're already at
day seven H maybe one more quest one or
two one more Quest I mean they don't
come until late evening we can still do
more right and maybe with all my money I
can just buy the magazines that I need
for the
workbench cuz he sells he sells
magazines right yeah you get money for
doing quests yes you do it's the um but
the Duke's Casino token those are the
money he
accepts is he
Duke he doesn't look like a Duke to me
magazines cost 300 Dukes
W he also sells armor which is what I'm
trying to go for right now hold
on okay modifi drag and drop the spikes
okay got
it okay I'm modifying my club really
quick
what the heck modifiers there we
go it is done are we going
across I got it though but B um you
maybe you don't have to waste your money
on the on buying armor cuz like I'm
aiming for the workbench to make armor
oh okay that' be nice my armor is broken
right now so I'm like defenseless oh oh
how's my armor doing
doing oh that's fine your armor the same
way nice okay okay I'll just get some
repair I have uh one two repair kits oh
on me right now even wow oh I could use
that okay if you don't mind yeah I'll
give it to you once I'm out of the
water drowning drowning
drowning right click for power attacks
okay you can make all the armors when
you have the workbench let's go okay o
yay I just need a couple more
magazines 300 for one magazine what's
the magazine that you wanted I think
it's something called like like it will
say something about workstations okay is
it Forge ahead is it that one I don't no
I don't remember does it say something
about
workstations it does oh do you have one
with you right now no but I ate some a
long time ago wait how many do you have
then like in your skill thing I think
three oh same okay I wish we could
combine it okay know I
[Music]
know do you need one or two I need two
okay then I'll give you
both thank you welcome Forge ahead gets
workbench chemistry bench and Forge oh
it gets everything
fou trash
well let's hope we find
more when we make more quests when we do
maybe while we wait FAA while we wait
for the guy to open up again we can we
can raid some some
houses yes look for magazines yeah we
need more I wish there was like a
library we could ra that would be too
easy though would be too
easy oh yeah I'll hang out with you
guys we wait for the Trader to
open but then once we turn in these
quests I'm probably going to head back
and start reinforcements M okay the you
guys can keep doing quests if you want
just remember to be back around actually
it is probably getting pretty close to
when we need to get
ready we cutting it close here yes time
to
assemble yep the night of the seventh
day is mail
boxes mail boxes apparently mailboxes
have books quite
often oh
yeah mailboxes and then there are
bookshelves inside I feel like the forge
ahead is often in garages though oh a
that maybe I'm making that up could be
could be
mhm I think no I'm not
home where is this house any place of
interest that has any form of
construction will have broken
workbenches but I wonder if we can use
them can you can you fix them or
anything I wonder funny you want to raid
this house are there zombies I had
zombies there when I went in we can go
in together it's mima's house oh hello
oh that's you I hear one I almost I
almost your throat no oh a cooking
pot oh man we could have had a free
cooking pot from there I know I found a
bunch of like grills too spent 600 coins
on that cooking pot ow oh I'm dying I'm
just letting this guy punch me while I'm
looting yay is he he dead oh he's not
dead
nice stay down stay
down oh I can make boiled meat and you
could juice now boiled
meat my armor doesn't taste very good I
think yeah same with me I think boiled
meat is better broiled or boiled boiled
who needs boiled meat boiled
meat o it sounds kind of
yucky not much interesting stuff in here
who is boiled meat they say yeah that's
why there was no like skeleton Mark no
real reward gu they're not big readers
around here H guess not not it I found a
hobo
stew hobo stew hobo stew what's in
here shotgun let me read shotgun weekly
why not yay pipe shotgun quality too I
already have one y
nice more shotgun mags all right I'm
cucumber again yeah me too I'm cucumber
I can carry some stuff nice okay I'm
heading towards the home again oh
there's a mailbox do you want to just so
we destroy the mailbox or is it no
normally you just open it so if there's
nothing inside then the that's why you
can't open it I think oh
[Music]
okay does anybody do wiring I have
wiring 101 no I don't think so what does
it say does it do in wiring improves
electrical crafting
skill oh I have five in that oh
already
yeah I think I have something in it too
but not enough start making new shotguns
tomorrow which one is
it oh they're ahead okay whoops I don't
know I need have this get it
H different
tab oh F let me drop it for you I'm
cucumber cucumber going on thank you
free
fre 11 that Trader open soon gosh dang
it
robotic is upon us
robot hope they're growing some aloe
vera Can you steal it Oh you mean at
home yeah yeah I wonder what they're up
to me too any any spies in chat have
Intel what are they up
to you see like there are
enemy I have been a little bit every
time someone's not in my group I'm like
weirdly hostile towards this I know
right it's just the the zombie mindset
yeah it's just the environment that we
live in huh humans are just as scary as
the zombies in this
world maybe we should find a quick house
to raid
yeah an easy one an easy one one loting
let's find a house that looks like it
has smart well- R people live there yes
there's a whole neighborhood past the
new house so all right
[Music]
oh chicken
soup oh I have chicken
soup
yum a manifestation of our time together
FAA is that house is that house smart
people that's our house so yes so yes is
smartest
people the Clements living
here
clementines all right let's drop some
stuff what is sp CRA tool
crafting
uhoh r
crafting armor
crafting any bandages around here by
chance ladies normal bandage I have I
also have normal medical right may be
painkillers oh my painkillers
then a to use where does this I don't
know how this is separated this makes me
thirsty
nice oh you know you can label them if
you um if you hold e and then click on
the pencil oh label the boxes yeah yeah
what
amazing things you can do
yeah a whole new world love organiz
sorry I love organizing things whoa you
guys have a lot of stuff in
here yeah we've got some good stuff some
good things yeah what the heck steel
tool Parts secret W
watchest there's some good stuff in here
oh there's a first aid bandage oh you
guys have shot shs may I take these or
do you guys have a shotgun wielder on
your we do have a shotgun wielder but
I'm sure you I don't know if she's going
to be here today she did say she will be
but by now is there collab over the
Nissa giggy collab all right I'll just
take can I take the first day B you
might as well take it since we we might
want them for the hoorde ah true we can
always get more later if she logs on
then I'll go ahead and split my ammo
with
her coffee too that seems
fair what was I going to do
uh I put murky water into the food chest
maybe that can be cleaned oh where is it
I will clean it oh it's in the food
chest like next to the
fire okay I will process that yay
awesome
aome how do I repair my clothes uh you
have to use a repair
kit she's looking good she look good
though don't don't look don't
look green eyes and green hair I'm
really up in your up in your schneer
right
there hello M checking for B in the cave
you know my gloves and shoes don't do
anything they just make me
weak oh you want to to punch with your
bare fist I don't know but the gloves
are maybe it's fine I guess I can make
new ones you don't think your wraps are
very helpful no my wraps are are helpful
but I've got these old gloves
on cheap old gloves
H is he open yet at 4:00 a.m. or was it
6:00 a.m. I'm not sure anymore isn't it
410 sorry I don't mean to St oh look
looking nice there yeah okay I'll go
there I'm going to go check and I'll buy
one magazine if he has one yeah I'll go
with you okay see if we can turn in
our hey yeah turn in quest and take one
more just one more maybe
just one more one more this time I won't
die maybe okay
okay I believe
you yeah maybe I should scrap
them brother the ridiculous no why is my
armor still weak even though I made a
brand new one that's very
strange maybe you got hurt or died too
many times I don't know
I wonder well do you make all new pieces
cuz if one piece is like hurt then it'll
just be like beep beep beep beep maybe
it's not just the Torso maybe it's like
the other pieces are damaged I see
that'll do it huh
okay yeah even your shoes
will P I could get moloto five Molotov
cocktails from
him maybe that maybe that'll be useful
be helpful yeah it's the ho for
sure uh craping arrows and
crossb maybe I should go for that though
chat what do you think this magazine or
the molotov
cocktails I'm I'm getting molotovs oh
give me okay
[Music]
spicy that's a spicy moloto
okay yeah some weapons would be good to
prepare mhm
magazines
um which one was it food
crafting can you not go behind his
thing no it doesn't seem like you can
wait he doesn't have the magazine that I
need
walls oh he is giving me a bicycle what
really
[Music]
yeah wonder I'm taking it
let's
go get that bike oh it doesn't someone
use 9
mm I do okay I'll get you some ammo oh
thank
you
after I'll be right
back
any here enjoy
than okay I'll keep my money you guys
did you guys figure out what fetch
quests are like how do you do that oh
it's basically it's just pretty much the
same as a clear Quest cuz I did one and
there were enemies in there too so okay
I'll just take a fetch Quest then
Okay add a chance to St slow victims H
that's pretty good wait I want I want to
use this what do you guys think is
better this is probably pretty good
right I'll do this when I'm when I have
some
timea though it's not the actual so
we should do that one together right I
could use all this the one you just
accepted yeah okay oh you also you guys
also accepted wait did you have to press
something to accept the quest that I
accepted girls cuz I just oh no it just
if you were in a party you'll
automatically accept it for everybody I
just took a buried supplies quest for
later when I
some yeah it's close and it's just like
digging something up I think how do I
use this
bike maybe I have to use it flex your
bike if you do 10 missions we get bikes
if we do 10 missions you do 10 missions
apparently okay
oh does it have an
[Music]
invent Look at Her Go
cute she's
zooming Zoom
me all right I I'm going to I don't know
should we go towards the people Quest or
quickly dig up the thing let's quickly
dig up the thing I think that'll be good
how how do I get off the bike I can make
armor quality 3 hey fauna I have a fist
magazine you want
it I don't think I have a shovel or fist
never mind okay I'm going towards the
digging Place yeah I hear it I'll go
with you does that one also have to be
like activated together I guess hello
did you get a quest yes we're going to
the digging Quest and then
to okay come on yeah I'll give it to her
later
I'll give it to you when I see you fauna
it's also in a neighborhood with lots of
houses a fist magazine oh my gosh you a
bike can I get on the back oh can you
that'd be so cute I don't think so
though that' be I don't think so I
should be able to that's
awesome an old movie apparently if you
do if you do 10 quests you can get a
bike really yeah we should be
closed o Bob's
Boris and cars where are we going
towards digging Quest we're heading
towards the digging Quest digging Quest
that Kiara got yeah and then we'll do
the one that the fetch Quest that b
accepted oh the bike cannot climb Hills
surprise it's not a mountain
bike okay I'm already there it's the
hink residence no the McMillan residence
two skulls okay I'm coming it's like
next to
it almost there I'm on my way me
too I hear
the I really hope I don't crash and die
I hope that's not possible oh yeah Ru
yourik been
here oh is it like
inside there is a vehicle mod that will
let two people sit on it
really
mhm
awesome need the back of my bike lady
will'll go on a little Park
date there's nothing I want
more you surprised
me sorry about
that wait what I don't get it is it down
there I think it's in the
basement oh how do we get to the
basement where is
it maybe have to destroy the floor oh
yeah break it actually no it doesn't
look like there's anything down
there maybe we ENT from the outside
maybe maybe
garage that's well hidden there you
are I skirted the outside but it doesn't
seem like there's a way to get down
below oh wait here here it is Kiara come
to where I am it's right outside the
residence uhoh
ah well done hope you're ready to dig
accept and get
digging digging lady I don't do I have a
shovel I didn't bring a
shovel I might have one it's okay you
can be our moral support yeah yeah we
have never mind work where' did I go you
see
Circle oh wait I wonder if it's really
big because there's just a ton of us the
quest might have bugged out
uh yeah normally there should be a
yellow circle yeah I don't see the
circle Quest failed it bugged out what
we failed what do you mean it fails the
quest that's crazy oh no we're here it
bugged out oh it did fail why it makes
no
sense are they only for one
person that's lame is your is your quest
still on C nope yeah all right let's go
to the bibu crust
wait let me give you your ammo oh okay
does anyone have handy skills handy I'm
not sure where is that um here fauna
this is for
you thank you you're welcome oh gosh two
of
them yeah this a bundle best present
ever yay I'm G to get naked really quick
don't worry about me though
scrapping
stuff uh it's repair tools is Handy land
repair tools what is that in the in the
books that one would learn or I I have
one out of for I also have one out of 50
oh I have three out of 50 in it oh you
should take this
okay nice handy
land f thank you now I have
four okay
bio lead us oh okay
um oh level up I'm level seven I'm
really close
too okay we are
going
directly
west quickly where was that stamina
thing the stamina skill thing cardio
it's under fortitude which is the it's
the cross there's like a cross and then
you scroll down in the skill
tree and then it says
cardio and under fortitude skill yes
fortitude is the cross oh at the bottom
okay I see it at the bottom this is Rule
one cardio thank
you you're
welcome follow the jingle
jingle the jingle hey when I Sprint I'm
as fast as you
almost oh bunny cute oh
bunny a
bunny we're having rabbit tonight rabbit
stew Oh
yay Ste okay we just follow the road
pretty much no distractions no
distractions no distractions very you
see how the the number seven is
red oh means it's hello I up no
distractions no
distractions
unless my God a pink
minivan no
okay he's trying his best run know is
that you don't need stamina for
bike unless you do yeah it's really nice
I just you can use stamina for bike to
go up like hills and stuff bu you just
let it
Cru what kind of quest do you have here
able uh a fet quest
okay well you know we all want bikes
so I know it's so nice I want a
helicopter please does he also just give
you a helicopter I
wonder in the end maybe after like aund
quests oh this would be an amazing place
to raid we should Mark this on the M
yeah the bear D oh it's a three it's a
three skull oh God maybe it'll have a
boss oo oh yeah they surely are hiding
some crazy stuff in
here you think a bear is in there a
bear I'm I'm going to mark that too yeah
definitely mark
it save
it shots how do just for rating
later oh
Las Vegas Los Angeles Phoenix oh are we
on the west coast is that where we're
located must be West Coast I guess
[Music]
so how did you
know cuz there's a sign that says Las
Vegas Los
Angeles they kind of far though yeah a
bit far away but still probably West
Coast
is Phoenix Phoenix is the closest phix
doesn't really look like Arizona though
Phoenix is indeed yeah it's it's too uh
it's too grassy yeah it's too green
where it's supposed to be
dry and there's that whole snowy area
too well they just want to you know give
us some
variety yeah it's not realistic Northern
Arizona yeah whoo oh wow I was really
try out my new
F I had
to gigy will be so proud of you yeah she
comes
back you are now the fish star
mhm how did Cecilia die so many times is
she okay I'm worried about
it maybe they made some really potent
spikes Ah that's good I mean hey that's
great actually
not going to stand a chance they're not
even going to be able to enter the house
yeah so it might be kind of a boring
Rush wait where me and Fa are a little
bit
behind that's okay it's kind of I'm
always this very far away wow this guy's
strong yeah it's okay it's a little
morning stroll before the storm that's
kind of owning me actually okay oh my
God he's still alive he lost his lag
still alive
what oh my gosh okay we got
him
675 yeah
Wow worth it okay I will await you at
the spot okay okay we're running we're
running and then after this Quest we got
to go prepare yeah we got to prepare
okay if Callie says so got to listen to
cie she's a
leader
please I beg we got to try and save
ourselves
okay but you said first time food oh um
I need food I have raw steak and a can
of dog
food I'll eat the dog food better better
than
nothing woof woof woof woof bark bark
woof woof bow bow
me I have a raw meat do you think
that'll hurt me if I eat it I mean for
an emergency I think you can eat it in
Japan it would be no problem oh yeah
we're not in Japan we're in
Arizona that actually helped a little
bit I got lucky that
time Pho where are you I'm coming
okay I'm hungry hry
IRL IRL too yeah I'm kind
of how long are we playing today by the
way uh just until after the raid right
correct okay so like four four stream
hours or so cuz now it's fre three okay
free okay now it's it's already been
three yeah W it's already been
three interesting well just until the
raid's over I suppose okay
okay well um just awaiting for I'm here
okay I'm going to get started no
cancellation please okay cancel the
quest okay find White River supplies is
all right let's sweep it sweep the
[Music]
area oh that's a lot of dudes hello oh
there's a there's an Angry Bird uh
outside
vulture it's better to shoot them he's
dead he's
dead
nice come on
who hey he dropped a a loot
Cali oh really a handgun crafting skill
magazine and a lot of 9 mm ammo I'll
I'll take I'll you take it I'll take
those yeah I'll take them I need take it
all if you want destroyed
workbench what is it usable it's
destroyed though he can't use it it's
just being destroyed
sadly oh is this the red dress zombie
yeah I
see damn we supposed to break down this
door I
wonder I might have to yeah I think so
otherwise we could place wait there's
there's a Swit
no there's a switch on the
inside oh oh I guess yeah we could try
to get up there okay time to break the
door maybe it's on the
roof swing it e take a
swing oh cie I
see just using my noodle let's go Callie
let's see who's faster at the top one
more C might
be the stairs have been completed way up
oh
oh who
[Music]
hello big chest in
here oh God help oh jeez oh I with all
oh we found the
thing oh the thing I got you I got
you yeah we got it we got the it it was
over the workbench on the second
floor oh then what's this Rando chest I
wonder something nice I found a bunch of
books Let's see magazines shotgun weekly
and bow Hunters no sorry does anybody
have a honey I'm infected
honey no at home we have honey oh I
found I found the supplies okay the
thing is done nice fetch Quest finished
yeah I wonder why I
didn't didn't Advance oh
boy
uh oh there's a medical journal too oh
wait we all have our own surise oh wait
I think we all have our own I see yeah
cuz there was a different one here ah um
Kiara there's some uh ammo old cash what
the heck okay let's see
sick does anybody use assault
rifles uh I use only machine rifle and
pipe rifle okay how do you find the
supplies I just found it in a box yeah
it seems like everybody has it in a
different location what does it look
like it's like this like bag this like
this this one bag Satchel over here it
looks like that an orang there's nothing
inside it says it's
what does it say return the traitor
already no it says it's one meter away
though ah there's no one here no never
mind never mind oh Callie uh here take
this like take this and take this shot
oh nice thank you I would probably see
hers too
right yes thank you not with a touch
option uh where is
oh wait there's like a map is
there I don't know where is fa it's on
the roof it's on the roof okay on the
roof as long as we got
it you know how to get up building
blocks I might needly blocks uhoh all
right I got to f
there here try climbing up there with
this and then let me make another one
for okay thank you I got you leave it to
my to help Mor help so we'll start with
that and then to get on that one put oh
whoopsie doodle that's not very good
actually isn't here to help uh wait wait
I got it I got it thank you so much oh
yeah you're
welcome if anyone has a
short near was broken
short IR I think we have short iron
pipes at home we do we do yes we have a
lot cuz I need to repair my machine gun
it's very broken oh yeah well we'll
definitely need to do that uh let's run
back to the trader I think how long will
it take yeah I think it should be fine
and then we head right back home bladies
you no distractions no
distractions okay oh this is good if
you're a cucumber you can just go on a
bike oh W HT or anything that's
awesome is that the Right
Way Stone ax in the bag what pick your
blocks back up no I'm okay I don't
really need
them it's just wood the bike has
inventory space too oh does
it wow I love the
bike good bike he's not so bad that guy
giving you fre bike people ha him but
he's nice maybe he's just like a little
tnd you just need to prove yourself
worthy and then he rewards you yeah I
think that's that's fine that's
legitimate biking around in a zombie
apocalypse seems almost too too Blissful
and yeah right happy Something Beautiful
about it you know sounds like an anime
biking away from the zombies biking away
from the problems yeah my new life as a
as a biker delivery guy in the zombie
apocalypse season 2 yeah deliver some
food I would watch it I feel like it's
better than a car cuz the bike is like
way easier to fix right and it doesn't
need need fuel need gas
I guess so but maybe later in the game
maybe there'll be quests really far in
like you know the the snowy areas and so
on and then you want to go like safely
with the car for some reason because
it's faster need to be and then you can
bring probably a lot more loot through
the car Supply runs true I want to go on
Supply runs with I know I hope I hope we
get get to that point I don't know how
days we just got to keep doing quests
well did you say there's a helicopter
that you can get yeah it's like the
final I want to see that yeah cuz even
the Traer he has a he has a helicopter
pad the
Traer so I guess you can go really far a
helicopter
pad no no I mean for landing at his
place oh oh oh I see he has it Outdoors
oh she look
good m
best land vehicle is a motorcycle oo
motorcycle
motorcycle imagine slaying zombies on a
motorcycle with like a big
driveby that'd be pretty cool someone
needs to specialize in vehicles I've
read two magazines about Vehicles so far
I'll try to keep reading I think I also
read a few but yeah I also have two in
vehicle how much do I have
I think in general it's good for us to
to just have skills basic skills and
everything I have four foreign vehicle
but it goes up to 100 so I guess we need
100 for a
helicopter ooh that's rough that's a lot
can you even
find
damn wouldn't it be great if you could
craft
magazines right yeah just write your own
yeah write them yourself MH just going
to make up some
stuff okay I'm almost
home hope there's some water at
home oh yeah there's my hat again it's
very nice I appreciate
that we'll see we'll see how we
feel chicken soup
again CU I am over level six so you know
penalties if I die
what kind of penalty you lose XP or what
does what happens exactly XP debt
basically I think I think you don't gain
exp until you work off your
debt wait wait there's debt yeah if you
die okay I'll be careful try be careful
ladies be careful after level six so try
not to
die pretty sure everyone is I think I
want to make some extra arrows just in
case I run out of ammo backup yeah not a
bad
idea honestly yeah not a bad idea at
all hello traditor do you have something
nice for
me ooh XP let see oh yay you were faster
than me I went for the water guess I was
a bad
choice travel 50 k
does anybody specialize in
traps I don't someone should specialize
in traps I will
say I have one in traps that's like
nothing Urban combat sneaking of a trash
makes she doesn't want to trade with
me wonder why that's not very nice I
know his rewards are
bad what should I do sometimes they're
really good yeah sometimes like I just
got um crafting
things bad
RNG shotgun parts I'm just going to buy
those for when it's
time take the wood I get the corn it's
just two corn two grilled
corn I know sometimes it's real stingy
sometimes it gives you a whole bike this
guy sucks I didn't get a bike what the
heck me
neither guess we still are a quest or
Too Short huh yeah yeah I did quite a
bit with the other group too so maybe
instead of just fighting the boar for an
hour have done
Quest we'll get it tomorrow
surely surely does he change his
[Music]
lineup
nice okay it's it's like 300 p.m.
yeah let's head back
zombies are you at home yeah I'm going
home cuz I'm really hungry I have a
another cooking magazine for you oh
thank
you personal
chef you you will make the food for me
with an extra pinch of love right yeah I
do just for you if I just eat honey will
I not be infected anymore yeah okay
oh no no no honey is good love
honey yay okay all
better you got food back at home be okay
uh more more food in general like how
much are we have cooked up right now we
don't have that much I think we got to
get the stove and the old house going
too then yeah I I had it going in the
old house okay um but it might shot need
a refresh now yeah we need more I think
zomes in the house no behind I saw it uh
when I came in there's there's like oh
is it it's h I think [\h__\h] it's happening
is this happening because there's like a
ton coming oh no oh I see no oh my God
we didn't we wanted this house to be
left alone we're not ready night right
oh this is just a normal
they say in chat um is that a thing I've
never seen that before all kinds of
things happen on the last day I
guess oh God yeah sometimes they're just
random hordes but that's okay it's just
don't worry ladies just head to the old
house you can okay
I we all got to stick
together the real one comes at Night
Don't You Worry okay this is a warm up
tce as big it is is yeah it's not bad
it's not bad actually
warm they're at least not so
buff yeah she still alive this out of
here okay
fun cooking magazine yeah we did it see
easy
welcome all right um yeah learn how to
make bacon and eggs okay well you
learned it low on
ingredients hm oh okay there's some me
to drink the water some steak in
here I need five I'll make it don't
worry guys five what cooking magazines
steaks okay there are more I think in
the oh you're right there
are oh we've got some food well not too
much I don't are the higher I'm guessing
the higher level cooking recipes are
worth making
mhm yeah bacon and eggs probably get
like Buffs and such
[Music]
yeah was iron Arrow the most basic AR
arrow that you can make wasn't there a
most more basic one I think no there was
a stone one wasn't there oh yeah right
oh there it is uh small
Stone s Safe House s you want to share
some things with me
stone stone
stone yeah we really need a workstation
we have all these parts that we can
build how
many oh I see it do show you what the H
what are you okay oh you died the zombie
didn't make a noise or
anything make a noise I just went and
looked in the pile I was like oh you
sleeping okay okay he didn't even make a
sound that's fine I love being at death
store knock knock knocking on death's St
knock knock that's what I do it's fine
I'll get
him a pumpkin I can make pumpkin bread I
think pumpkin bread that sounds yummy
why'd you get
pumpkins I don't know there were just
some in
the and the kill the chest
H oh you know can't we just put the
second cooking pot we have up and cook
simultaneously fauna yes we can we also
have another yeah let's do it we do yeah
yeah
[Music]
efficiency oh lots of eggs yeah I put
some extra ones in make
egg egg blueberries egg cornmeal anim
animal anime fat animal fat
anime just
cursed use this later
probably um steel arrowe head that seems
nice does anybody have cloth
fragment Lots I do oh boy do I can I
have five if possible yeah of course
when I meet up with you at the house a f
i got thank you people check the food
chest there's another murky water in
there okay I have oh the pipe iron pipe
iron definitely find a better water
source tomorrow oh we need we need to
check my my water collector thing cuz
it's been going on for a while maybe it
got some we'll check at the old house
yeah you actually left it out huh yeah I
did they're like you guys coming back
soon oh God they want food oh no they
don't have food
either uh
oh um uh I can't see any pipe pipe iron
ah never mind found it I think this
should do the trick
we have em moat and spikes let's go was
how was it going to do it again I knew
they'd be able to do it oh oh there we
go okay machine gun
repaired can I repair this should I make
another fire how do
I another fire a couple of fires at the
old house too stronger shot oh we could
bring it over there the new cooking pot
or we could the the old house has both a
cooking pot and a grill so I think one
there and one here is fine okay well we
can make another one here oh yeah I
guess I guess make it here because here
is safer since we're not doing the thing
over here oh my God
H they really fortified this place good
good to see that we have a chance after
all we
might this is very
nice Stone
I'm so
blind do you know where we have
Stones wait small stones yeah oh I I I
took them but also I made a new fire I
just need like two or free I don't know
okay I put some in the top chest
thans other
okay is coal fuel oh it is
this is a lot they really went to town
do you think we're safe cie with all
that I'm excited to see
it this is overboard
okay the more the
better I hope the zombies don't have
Direction sense and just crawl on the
cement it's quite the side okay I'm
going to go get into their call real
quick mhm
okay the food in this game is making me
hungry pumpkin bread looks so good I
want pumpkin bread oh we have super corn
super yeah yeah there the super corn but
I I don't know if we should just eat
those oh should we make seeds from it
yeah I have also the seed crafting
recipe already learned so I can make
more seeds it seems whenever we want
good yeah and the ear of super corn I
guess we can grill that I don't know if
you need a recipe for it
oh do you make seeds from the corn
itself or uh I don't how where do I
check that chat where do I see how to
make the seeds that I supposedly can
make never mind I find it yeah oh it
okay I need five ears of super corn to
make a super corn seed one SE we should
so we should not eat the super corns
yeah but I I guess like once we have it
plant it it will you know create more
corn so we should just plant those seeds
maybe after the apocalypse we should
plant the seeds
yeah I don't know how planting works so
I'll leave that to someone to someone
else I think sh has points in
farming
okay
nice um do we have
any yes we do we have water nice I'll
take one one turn this
off maybe I'll drink one more oh
stormy oh is it getting scary it's
getting spooky maybe we should go to the
other place so they don't attack here
yeah I just want to make sure I got
everything that I need
[Music]
I guess we'll be fine huh we'll be fine
yeah should we bring all the
food yeah yeah yeah I'm just eating this
sorry I ate both of the pumpkin breads
because I'm hungry yeah they're yummy
I'm your first taste tester good good
I'm glad you liked it wait can I make
mushroom soup or something mushroom soup
we have so many mushrooms I hope we can
make something out of it
boom oh I'm not smart enough to make
mushroom soup you have to be smart can't
be that I guess so because you have to
know which mushroom poison or not it's
almost 700 p.m. oh God okay we should we
should go I think yeah okay do you do
you want to take the food uh we don't
really have much food but I'll take what
we have
okay I have a golden RW tea in case I
get diarrhea in the
apocalypse okay yeah let's go all
right here we go okay I'm gonna pop over
I still
hungry oh my
god oh see to what's the wait till you
guys come see
this on our way coming H should we go
into the VC yes we
should oh we're coming welcome the
hello let's go you can't get back up
I've heard you if I can you fortified
the bases
girls oh this is so
dangerous okay make sure you close the
door behind
you I'm going to stand here this is
going to be my fighting position so I
can be like an angry old dude saying get
off my lawn to the zombies
strategy yeah uh we should probably try
to make a cat walk and then shoot from
afar if you can I think we can shoot
through the the windows as
well yeah or just like just uh destroy a
hole at the second
floor okay seems
good the weather is so bad this is like
on purpose there are windows on the
second floor so there is a window if
anyone wants to
like uh I thank God there's zombies in
the water cling this door
there are three doors okay okay good
sorry oh maybe I'll make one more
door I don't think we'll see any
cop cop zombies can shoot cop zombies
that's crazy cop zombies oh yeah please
stay away is that real or are you
[Music]
trolling in the front and I'll chill in
the back like are you sure you're fixing
it I don't know you have to right click
to
fix this is going to be interesting no
cop zombies yet okay so every raid will
be harder I
suppose yeah okay okay so who's behind
you sure you're fixing it yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah don't worry I can't rep what
do you think shotgun should be CeCe in
your I'll do it now Prof stupid but what
shotgun should be yeah like front or
like back do you think um I think what
we should do is we everyone looks
together and we check they go because
they're going to try going where there's
like the least the least resistance
right so once we realize that that might
be the front or the back and then once
we realize we uh you should go where
it's the less probably back because the
front has the big fence so the back
might be better we should probably close
out the window
here probably I don't think they can oh
the window
yeah big window up here you might
someone might be able to snipe from if
we use this one for my bow and arrow I
can snipe with pistol
maybe oops EXC I I found a pipe rifle
but I don't know what that is so don't
forget to turn off I use pipe rifle but
oh they're not good okay yeah but it's
all that we have little bit back oh here
can you make us some meat whoever's
cooking here oh okay I have a pistol
with a scope so I can snipe okay okay
then you should go upstairs there's
stairs you don't want to use the
ladder I'm trying to now how do how do
the friendly members get inside before
you
I be careful the door oh you can fix the
windows too oh
yeah okay I'm going
to I'm going to destroy this don't break
leg don't break leg no you can't shoot
one of the windows can go don't
Dy you don't want it it be better there
is oh okay that's a good point sorry
yeah because we have a roof here yeah
yeah you're you're right sorry that's
okay and then we should probably uh do
this for other areas that could be
useful what time does
this uh on the second floor there's also
a ledge right above the back entrance
where someone can snipe from as well oh
nice does anybody happen to have a
repair kit no no more
uh we have a repair kit in the bottom
boxes bottom boxes there might only be
first floor boxes there's a couple
repair kits I think
in this one maybe uh building block a
good vantage point for Sho
can building like a a walkway it's kind
of dumb looking but maybe it'll be
helpful all right with my shotgun I need
to be up close personal so I'm going to
take the
porch
nice okay I will go to my sniper spot
you you can if you want Bes what was
that um try to look for me if you can is
that
it I made it how do I get behind you uh
let me look for you I'm upstairs I'm the
second floor here
BS go here that scary and then maybe you
can go through here but be
careful
[Music]
yeah how
I fell no this is so smart this is so
good yes okay yeah just be careful
okay oh a sledgehammer nice traversing
this is okay thank you do you have some
food we're ready we got this there's
food in the chest in here thank
you here which
one uh there should be there should be
some meat cooking so if you want food
there's meat there okay nice I put in
the food chest I guess it wasn't at 8:00
p.m. I thought
apparent oh 10 oh that's
good yeah we still have like two more
hours but I don't want to get wet H it's
over healing items how's our healing put
I need more wood yeah I think I have one
in here but does it disappear when you
put one somewhere else okay oh he one
you must repair this before picking it
up how do I repair it is this mine okay
so we can go the you can right click it
with your Hammer equipped whoa I don't
have a
hammer okay I'll I can come and do it
where are
you come
downstairs I don't think this is mine
though okay but owned by anybody do we
have some IED it you should be able to
pick it up now plant fibers in here oh
I'm not sure I have some plant fibers in
the bi boo chest B boo chest it says b
boo box I think I saw it
somewhere yes take as much as you want
Oh ladders nice no it doesn't work I
need to put them like oh the ladder yeah
like here okay and then okay I have 55
as as well K if you need some Oh no I
got it already I will protect you with
my life I I'll be right back there you
go much better it's almost time minutes
this
okay exciting
y if we die we die together the sky is
turning red we did our
best station where should I go CH this
are there any good spots here like yeah
chill next to me with a shotgun on the
ride at the main entrance we'll be the
first line of defense I want to punch
him okay
okay our tank oh no I'm worried for you
I'm very
concerned don't worry remember Friendly
Fire is on so just be careful not to
hurt each other I will try not to shoot
you I'm going where wear your wear your
farmer hat so I can tell that's you okay
if there's an arrow that flies just it
wasn't me it wasn't
me I need more wood you look so you guys
are looking cool up there
yeah going to snip oh wait shouldn't we
block off the stairs
here I don't think they're going to
enter
inside damn it's a lot of
spikes oh boy here we go here we go no
please I'm not mentally
ready what to
expect oh boy what if they come from the
back I hear
spooky is that is that oh there oh they
are on on the time oh they're appearing
anybody has any wood do you have any
wood spes are
working do we have to do anything thank
you go away okay so mostly coming from
the West a lot let me see they're all
coming from the West right now there's
no one else oh they're from the spikes
what does this remind me of oh they are
dropping spes oh okay I'm going to go
down so I can fix spikes actually oh you
got fix them right oh I'll join you sure
care let me let me put away my items
that I don't
need maybe I can save my ammo it's
really dark oh my God
yeah what do I not need spikes are
paying off oh they're chilling the
spikes are doing
work that's good make sure to fix them
oh gosh does the loot disappear
chat does it uh I plan on dying so I
don't really care about these right now
F you going I too plan on dying the
spikes will take care of it the loot
yeah I don't know okay I plan on dying
it seems like they don't disappear the
loot bags so we can keep them until it's
over good yeah we'll get later everybody
gets
them mhm by the way since everybody's
here if anybody finds or has any
workstation uh magazines I think I'm the
furest with workstation stuff uh I would
love to get one if you find one oh this
okay there's some from South oh South is
that behind the house
just will do it South is the left of the
house if you look on your the little
line on top it's it it has the lettuce
in your map thingy oh
I I can't remember cardinal directions
right now I can't no it says like s yeah
they're coming from the front again okay
from the front Southwest Front North sou
Southwest
yeah oh they're still they're still
dying from
spikes we're not doing
anything in order you need wood in order
to repair them
no yeah I did equip some wood
but I guess I already used
theck I think I'd rather live yeah I
mean you can kill them from AF far if
you want the
XP that's true maybe just like one hit
through the spikes wow they are dying in
one hit yeah I get a little bit maybe
for fauna punching them go fauna go
fauna I'm thirsty can I go I kind of
want a piece of the if you want to have
some fun
did you just jump yeah I'm here though
oh we really fortified huh yeah we did
really good I know good job I feel like
let's go team it's okay I'm covering you
I'm covering you are you covering me I'm
covering you we're covering you we're
covering you I don't think I've landed a
single hit with too good I don't want to
die yeah we did really good yeah oh this
one's about to break yeah I don't have
enough to fix
this wait where are you I'm near the the
front like right here jumping up and
down oh where you so fast near near the
Mount I don't know West North oh I see
you I can come I'll come down and repair
which one which one oh yeah yeah yeah
okay which one any of these
really okay they seem to be like almost
breaking some ow I took some damage I we
could probably make towers and then like
shoot from there in the future okay I I
only have like nine wood left so that's
okay that's okay oh reinforce the bag
since some are still there
nice here we go okay there we go oh that
was weird what was that lag maybe we
should make a big party ni yeah maybe we
should although isn't there a maximum
party yeah you can split we have a small
party with CI biu and and me I'll just
invite anyone who's like wait I think I
guess we're full
g a man I want some exp too I know I'm
not getting
any yeah it's okay oh yeah shared exp
isn't Ah that's true oh should we just
span our party and join you guys I mean
I can step out what's the maximum again
okay six six we're we're four right now
in our party I am treat yeah you guys
can
join oh no it's okay you can join seven
no it's okay it's okay n n no no it's
okay it's
okay don't fauna you can always come
back to
us oh I think I hit I like when they
fall down they look kind of silly like
they walk you just like out there I
might as well just join you
this is I just want toch
amazing is so cool I want to be cool in
case anyone wants to just like
jumps there oh Calli behind you you're
kind of in a
nice whoops of them yay yeah with
clubs out of stamina oh I'm out of
stamina see I'm out of stamina I'm tired
me to I think when aim you use a stamina
while you're
aiming oh
yeah well I guess I'm not losing
much oh my God Callie you're getting oh
you're popular you
[Music]
P oh Myler nice super
Smasher I'm infected
[Music]
uhoh I honey
uhoh
can and use my spear as well ah I'm low
I'm low I'm leaving me too
understandable feel like Lord of the
Rings right
now use my stuff which character
specifically
Legolas
hey best boy best boy although gim is
best Boy and Sam is best boy Sam is best
boy for real I'm so tired
fire the oh nice one yeah oh thank you
for
saying
better oh shoot she can
climb get out of my car wait who can
climb I want to go the zombies can climb
out on the car oh okay I thought you
meant like have some fun or something
Faun can you move for a second I don't
want to push you but however I can use
this to my advantage I want to have some
fun I'm going out in the field yeah y
too powerful
[Laughter]
hey I'm scared
actually I'll back you up I'll back you
up
okay
okay just I don't want to punch you by
accident though hey oh someone needs
help over there about to have the first
casualty oh no I am
sprained no youant it's okay
away nice now
cry oh
no going too soon I remember all the
[Music]
time we were digging a hole together I
remember when
we and then when we made
spikes and then when we're taking
another
keep her
hole and when she said that she digs
you that was
ro oh yeah if I stay
close oh God oh God it's time to go back
home ah no
God am I going
to this on fire so much loot oh my God
the loot bags I know I want to look at
the loot so bad this my stuff this stuff
okay safe safe safe
safe nice a lot of zombies congre there
I died here is there one
open okay ra just out there setting the
fields a
blade let's
go I liked it how long is this by the
way until like I am okay yeah oh man I
guess it must have been my stuff this is
fun I didn't go my I guess I picked it
up it doesn't look my
backpack oh you died as well right yeah
yeah yeah see I see it was it was her
crony it was
her yeah but oh ra died yeah I don't
have my stuff maybe maybe did you have
the fire upgrade on your spear yeah I
think might have picked your stuff up
cuz we died at the same area maybe oh
can you give my stuff I I think maybe
you picked up my stuff yeah if I die you
can have your stuff cuz uh I'm I'm dying
where where are you I'm near the car I
think you might have picked up my
backpack yeah I mean where are you now
uh still near the car okay I come next
to you then okay I will I will die here
soon so you may pick up your stuff then
after I killed some things I feel like
for the next raid this will already
still be strong enough to cover for the
next it's so good yeah I mean at some
point maybe after the fifth ra this
might be rough but for the next on um
actually wrong I have I will have to
look for my backpack I guess it wasn't
there cuz I behind you behind you watch
out thank
you I no I didn't what okay done um it's
near the car
thir w we W have a marker on it cuz we
picked up each other's backpack I think
I don't but we'll be stronger too
confirm one shotgun kill I guess I'll go
in punch and everything so you can grab
your backpack and inside the house we
exchange stuff
huh you put my
backpack I haven't got my backpack yet
where are you ra let me leave I am
outside but I can go
inside uh it's okay out behind you watch
out watch outy I think I can just die at
this point no don't die don't give up
it's don't give up I
got zombie on my giggy is here oh oh no
did she spawn did giggy spawn in our
house
no what's up where are you just look for
I I'm naked right now just look for me
I'm naked
hurry up please I'm getting chased my
every oh my gosh I got you I got you
thanks I'm hiding at top a car hurry I
think they could jump I got I got you
guys are saing me hi Cy Kitty you Arrow
My Savior I could cry from happiness at
last it's hard to tell which ones are
our players and which ones are zombies
sometimes especially if you're running
around naked
ouch soor almost dead
already oh my goodness what is happen
over there doing to you this one this
one
perect
okay for
both thank you no problem no problem I
can still Lo this upgrade
it
yes just going to use it for some
p i can get some
trees because I feel like they just
aren't breaking really we're so fine
it's only like an hour left they get
tougher though yeah but second ra second
R will still be fine let's keep these
spikes until next
time I hear something
gross like
work nice what's going on over there
oh I'm almost out was that a zombie or a
person they really wrangling the zombies
out there oh
gosh oh my God are you good o look at
you okay
yay should do
the defense game we love it
fire fire fire die okay this one's after
me so someone can chase
it I want to be a hero
too okay sick you hurt hey I don't want
this to end
yet fun we can go longer why oh no
iion it's okay I got
you nice help my
friends one more
hour okay helping my friends that's a
lot and then Traer
opens
nice
fire
fire fire oh God oh God she oh we got a
pyromaniac
here and it's not
me is
addicted oh
God away foul Beast nice job nice job
yeah strong don't touch
me oh thank you oh no don't
touch okay I'm R to you
guys thank you car method car method no
problem oh they're so fast oh did I I
know
running so close to being deathless at
the end of the hey no touchy okay uhoh
not
work oh oh that's SI oh I really
likie a bad place to be right
now it doesn't say it was me we took a
mo
together for you could not
come here you come here you going
Adventure spes are
so come I love how I love how we're
mingling even though the spikes would do
everything we
love yeah even though dying loses
XP
no oh that poor deer over
there oh sorry oh
wow it's free food it's the
apocalypse that's
true
yes oh my
friends hey
hey oh I can't
see hey no touchy no touchy no
touchy I'm so scared of accidentally
shooting one of them yeah right
so close
[Applause]
complete guys we're the
zombies made
it thank you I did did it
te
loading we killed the zombies
together where were you
[Music]
I wonder we have to destroy okay it's
time to loot
guys time for me to loot but there is so
much the treasures did it
disappear oh there's a treasure
map someone dropped a treasure map I'm
just going to bring this in why can I
get
this let me know if anybody finds
punching magazine
okay so great gigy is the house okay
yeah sorry have one HP and a dream hey
giggy our house is okay our normal house
is completely fine thank God okay I'll
probably bage wo that was so good
yeah good job GL we work together so
hard to do this yeah yeah we are
survivors hard together yes thanks you
did so good thank you did you like that
[\h__\h] how I saved you just there oh yeah
that was crazy I took that bik you can I
bring jackter I didn't even use my gun
it's so cute the jackter is so cute
yes lot for
Morel okay I'm going to die now yeah we
didn't end up using the moat though
because they just couldn't even get past
the first line of defense oh hey um I
have uh two magazines if you want to
make a bike
y you don't need you don't need to make
a bike uh if you apparently do 10 quests
the guy will give you a bike he gave me
oh can your bike break no I it's in my
inventory you can put it in your
inventory that's yeah you can you can
take it you can pick it up and put it
down right whenever you want I want them
though shy really cool seed C oh where
are you here I'll drop it on the ground
here here you go that might be good for
the corn I'm debating if I want it I'm
dropping medical journals if anybody
wants medical journals I'm
Dr okay I'm armor the armor Journal I'm
going to drop some I guess
I'll here's another
medical okay I currently have I think
medical wise I'm at
five oh I have stuff for Forge so
for is
good um where did you put the oh maybe
someone else
put for you I I I put the medical stuff
in the in the Box I'd love to get uh
armor journals if anybody
has oh I have I have
three okay here you go I'll drop
it
put I put four in the B box k I have
thank you Ang I thought it accumulate
shotgun weekly don't mind if I do I'm
going to take this if that's
okay is there somebody else that's doing
shotgun GG do you want the shotgun
magazine okay here here you go must be
put this to
use here I have a a scrappy magazine I
just dropped it someone can take the
other one I'll do some s and uh here
just take another vehicle one someone
else can do that yeah many vehicles I'll
take the vehicle one and then somebody
else take I'm I'm vehicle four by the
way oh well there okay maybe then you
should take the vehicle because we can
open this now I'll make cars for
everybody you get a car and you get a
car I'll
be you will make me a car I will make
you the nicest car who can make better
clothes yeah clo car I'll put them into
B box as well and then you can have my
armor level is 19 now it's pretty good D
I'll make you some good armor for the
next
raids everybody will do for cosplay
yay yay very nice Straw Hat FAA it's
like the one piece is real yeah it's the
water hat
piece very nice by the way guys I have
to leave I'll see you tonight I think
tonight right yeah yeah yeah whoever's
playing tonight I will play tonight um
okay see you later see you later see
l i I'm probably heading for the night
since we have overcome the obstacle so
I'll see you guys so whenever byebye bye
byee okay i' say we did a really a
really good job yeah that was a good day
but I feel like we needed them
considering how many of us there are
which means I think there's like eight
zombies per player or something like
that well now we have a feeling for it
yes
exactly I'm thinking there will be
another raid uh tomorrow because if
we're playing tonight
then yeah oh Oh you mean tomorrow so is
there a session tonight and then also
tomorrow morning correct okay oh yep you
don't have to join the night session
though that's happening I'm going to
play I'm not going to stream but I will
be playing to help anyone who's playing
at night tonight yeah I guess if
I I'll try maybe I won't be there from
the beginning but I'll try to I'll try
to be awake for it it's difficult to
join both
slots yeah kind tough exactly 12 hours
apart to play every single time or
anything like that you do not get to
sleep you have to
protect I'm sleeping we could discuss it
in in Discord in a bit as well if you
guys want
to Fig it out yeah I I want to do more
quests that's for sure I know I'm like
getting adct this game it's addicting
isn't it yeah it is I feel like there's
so much I don't know yet but still like
I want to
play well I guess that's it for today I
too will be kind of signing off for now
all right I'll catch you guys later
[Music]
good holding off the hoorde
everyone good job
everyone the moral support I was there I
was providing physical
supportal all
around phisical support bye-bye myal
support byebye byebye
wait so in order to not is everybody
leaving in order to not like let the
clock go by too far I
guess oh oh I think so oh
quani hey I missed you today by the way
I'm still streaming I guess I should
leave
too oh you're still streaming yeah I'm
still they they still hear
you but oh crowny while I got you here
yes let's see how far we are from the
special crony Wawa dance
short oh Milestone we
are
uh oh 2K 2,000 views away until you guys
get a nice quason K dance short of
Mirage oh it's beautiful I'm going to
retweet it just so that it's going to
give you a little cick thank you oh
thank
you yeah guys
Mirage cron is the first the first uh
experiment I I love being an
experiment yeah all right I'll I'll mute
myself and say goodbye to my
viewers
Bye Bye
[Music]
Bye by the way crony
crony uh I just I just I I saw your
Tweet and I don't know if if that was
your impression from the uh the the
comments or so but I think you're fine
just having two things in your
bag it was just really funny it's it's a
nice contrast to some other
bags no no no no like I thought it was
pretty funny that's why I was I wasn't
annoying I just thought it was funny
okay I just need to know one
thing uhhuh you wear it over your chest
not over your headp
right yeah okay thank
God
why cuz like those bags like you know
fanny packs I just have a a personal pet
peeve against fanny packs when they're
not used as cross body bags like cross
body bags are fine but those you know
what I mean the ones like around the hip
yeah yeah I used to wear those when I
was like
11 oh so you think they're kind of
outdated yeah I don't know I mean maybe
there are some cool ones that you can
wear in a cool way if you are cool
yourself you could
probably wear it in a cool
way yeah yeah cool by default
so
oh
no I
wish okay over the over the the cross
body oh that that's a good relief thank
you so much for that yeah of course man
now you go to sleep girl ah all right
you too maybe sometime
later yeah I hope so I got to fix my
sleep
schedule I know I it's it's I can't
really say that to
you no no no we I think we all we all
got to fix our sleep schedules don't
we
yeah all right see you later good
night uh you guys said B box has armor
thingies oh ah and the car ones oh did
you put those there so I could use them
all right all right all right all right
oh we I have unlocked armor light armor
is quality to sick and I still don't
have a freaking workbench but that is
fine okay I'm out of the game no time is
to be passed but wasn't laa Still
Standing There
AFK I I hope she she remembers to log
out yeah ah I'm excited I think I don't
know uh if the short is finished I think
it's
like pretty much
finished uh yeah I think it's finished
but my
mic ah it's got some uh problem s with
the cable um but yeah we're so close to
the Milestone I don't know if I'll put
it up now or after I I wake up but this
ended a little bit earlier today than
yesterday thank God so I'll eat some
dinner at 6:00 a.m. now I don't know
what and then I'll try to sleep maybe or
I'll put up the I don't
know I don't know maybe after I wake up
give the other short a little bit more
time to grow watch my solo short guys my
solo short where I'm dancing
alone cereal for dinner no I know it's 6
now this is the one time where I can go
and get myself a quasa and not get
judged cuz with my normal sleep schedule
when I wake up at like noon or so and I
go get a quasa they always look at me
and like they're like oh good morning
they're so judgmental I'm like
cuz they know like I always get my ques
at like 100 p.m. or so and they know I
just woke
up um but they know by now that I just
like work weird hours and sleep weird
hours they should not judge me but now I
can go there and not get judged but I'm
not in the mood for a
quasa plus is for every
hour no honestly personally I love quos
but I would only eat them really for
breakfast in the morning like whenever
morning is for me I I as much as I love
quos they're not like an any time of the
day food for me but yeah this was a lot
of fun I think the spikes didn't even
break
so we can totally keep this until next
time it will always be a little bit
difficult to enter the house now
but the spikes held up crazy and then
for the next raid this still seems like
no effort maybe the third raid maybe
they can start breaking through some of
them but we're also getting stronger
we're going to get stronger weapons and
stronger armor so honestly that's that's
uh kind of crazy you're sure seem super
seem hyper from it I'm energetic still
yeah I had a nap even before like I I
adjusted my sleep schedule and I had a
nap I got up at halfast 5:00 p.m. then I
had a nap from like 11:00 p.m.
to 2 a. no no 1 a.m. or so I'm like I
could play for another 5
hours but yeah no I I I if I can sleep a
little bit early so to say like maybe in
the next 3 hours then I'll try to be in
the next time slot which is like 300
p.m. my time I think
um then I will see how many people have
a streaming slot streaming thing
up uh and I'll spontaneously decide if
I'll put up one too uh and if I'll
stream but I
think I'll probably show up at least for
2 hours or so because I think I'll be
awake should be all right yeah this is
getting fun and I I mean uh today our
group was a little bit more chill but I
still have a lot of fun and and this
gives me a surprising good amount of
like bonding time with FAA chicken soup
guys chicken soup I'm telling you the
STS are
rising I didn't expect that either
that's
a un unexpected development a chicken
salad was it damn it ah wait was there
chicken soup oh
uh ah was chicken soup someone
else was that someone else's
name a [\h__\h] that's me and Nissa [\h__\h] ah
no no no I'm embarrassed I need to write
a message to F F fun my brain was so
empty I
fought how do you write
F I F chick t h o u g h t is that right
I F chicken soup was our name but it was
it was chicken
salad
oops F okay I write it correctly good
good good ah I just want I don't know
weird funny
name chicken and something that reminds
me of chicken
salad damn it yeah but even normally
when when I think of me and or Isa I
don't think I call it chicken soup I
don't call it anything generally I don't
think every couple needs a name like
that necessarily but it it's funny it's
funny to have something I guess to refer
to it yeah I guess I just refer to it as
karisa or honestly I don't refer to it
as anything at all usually but if
anything it's probably
Kissa
H chicken soup and chicken salad is too
similar
oh my head hurts a little
bit um what should I eat I have some
stuff that I could cook but I don't want
to cook at 6:00 a.m. you know it just
n it just feels
wrong man this sucks it's so weird to
have this sleep schedule Pizza I'm not
really in the mood of for pizza
either maybe I'll just eat some fruit I
don't know how hungry I am I have some
bananas and kiwi
[Music]
H maybe I will eat a
qule today I
ate two uh of the like Vice worst
sausages with the sweet mustard I ate
that before the
stream and for breakfast I
had two slices of like milk bread with
Nutella and butter
not very healthy today not very healthy
at all oh and one kiwi I had one kiwi so
I barely ate [\h__\h]
today two slices of bread with Nutella
one kiwi two sausages that's all I ate
today very
light go eat but I don't know I'm lazy I
don't want to cook I turned off helloof
fresh for this week this coming week the
like the my delivery day I think would
be like tomorrow or so I turned it off
so I just want to Freestyle some stuff
maybe I could throw some pesto together
I still have some pesto sauce I I didn't
really like this one though yeah sorry
I'm just yapping I feel like it's weird
to end my stream
already yeah but guys make sure to
stream Mirage please please please on
streaming services I I would really
appreciate it if you can at least give
it one listen per day on streaming
services whatever you use and on YouTube
the music video One and perhaps the
YouTube shirt I'm going to continuously
I need to make a graphic but I need I'm
going to uh continuously upload shorts
now I got a couple planned I got a
couple in the pipelines I'm doing one
with uh quason first and then should I
spoiler I'm not going to spoiler the
rest you know what I'll keep them to
myself I'll tell you which one will be
the next Once I have the crony one
out yeah you got it set on autop playay
Wow thank
you yeah let's not spoil it mon Stone so
close
though what color is the next one I
actually haven't decided like I got a
couple lined up you
know haven't decided which one to put
next but maybe
um maybe red
I don't know could be
anything
yeah what else anything else I got to
say anything else I need to get out of
my
[Music]
system
diarhea no
a yeah I already got my Lord of the
Rings ran out of my system in the
pre-at and I was ranting about how this
generation this new the newer
Generations are so like we're doomed
because they refuse to watch Lo of the
Rings if if if the new generations don't
know and don't watch not of the Rings
and nobody makes them watch all the
Rings we are so
doomed like there's no point like I
don't want to live in a world like that
and and they don't understand like how
how much of a legendary treasure that is
that needs to be handed down for
Generations no I don't we can as I said
we can be split uh on our opinions when
it comes to The Hobbit movies but the
Lord of the Rings
movies you got to watch it it's such a
like treasure that needs to be cherished
and
shared yeah I watched I watched a video
today of like um Frodo's last day
shooting and how you know the director
really wanted to keep it going it was
kind of wholesome and and Pippins was
there and um you know Mary was there
watching and I was just
thinking this is so wholesome like this
show this these movies are
like so how to say there's so much heart
and love in that and the whole premise
of the movies it just makes you feel
good doesn't it it's so innocent too in
a
way I do want to do another watch along
but I've already done Lord of the Rings
watch longest twice of all movies and
Hobbit
once and we're currently watching bakat
all the seasons so we got to finish
those before we watch L of drinks with
Cali all right I'm going to like make an
open call anybody who didn't watch them
before raise your
hands hold the whole of members in the
end and then I'm forcing them to watch
it with me one of these
days first
experiences I shall take them
watch along number free but I feel like
just for the sake of their time it
shouldn't be the extended one we already
watched the extended one members only
before um but they're very it's very
time consuming so maybe just for the
sake of their time it shouldn't be the
extent you think it should be I don't
know like that adds like another free
hours or so
I don't mind
but okay okay but not not so
soon not so soon I wonder who else
didn't watch it
yet remember the book book club of yeah
and honestly more and more I really want
to get it going but it's I it's
difficult like I
feel it's a bit difficult I want to I
want to restart girls talk again and
maybe bringing bringing fauna back
because it was always supposed to be
like um moonay and fauna like kind of
uh
switching every other time
uh maybe we can have a girls talk
episode with me fauna and someone
else more girls talk yes yes yes
yes Irish girl Su I didn't have Irish
yet huh
fun and gigy uh our little Clement house
group yeah yeah
yeah sounds
good WIA too
yeah wha is
demure she's not like the overthe toop
girly girly but she has she's she's
definitely girly and demure and very
mindful
no she's not she is she is have you seen
the back review it was very obvious that
she was very
demure Midwest
girly sounds about
right have you seen her tweets about
about what about like anything you mean
generally I mean in the end all of these
girls are girls so in theend we can get
all of them into girl talk and even the
ones that don't strike you as like the
most girly you know they might have some
surprisingly girly things about them
H we can feature all of them at some
point oh the one with the
tattoo that twet with the well I mean
what's not girly about that huh I don't
know all right I'll try to find some
food for for thought and hopefully I
left you with some food for thought too
stream Mirage please support
Mirage and I'll see you in a couple
hours like I don't know 9 hours from now
I guess is when it would
be I think ooh oh No 9 hours [\h__\h]
that I'll see you
J byebye
do you see the top right yeah that's my
fourth year anniversary merchandise if
you're interested in any of these
marvelous things well just check the
description there's a link there that
will lead you to the merchandise sales
page it's also on geek Jack even though
the link is not in the description I
think but if you're from Europe you can
check out GJ yay please consider it
thank
you oh am myth myth merch myth
anniversary General merch is also ending
soon I think today or tomorrow one of
these days is maybe the last
day if you were still thinking about it
but didn't make a decision
yet think about it
[Music]
n