[Applause]
I have already given up on my dream of saying goodbye. I am lured by a smell that I have
known for a long time, and I fall in. I am
afraid to fulfill my assigned role, and I
cry every day. Only my heart has been clouded by the answers.  What's
inside the box is a dull loneliness that feels a little cheap,
but I thought I hid it without knowing it.Those
eyes that lurk deep inside I know it's just a joke.  Let's
fly away with all the thoughts I can't see
anymore.I won't let go of you, who I've locked away without hesitation.And eventually,
even if I say it's a lie, I'll start to flutter away.I've given up
on the white dream.I've been doing it for a long time, but I'm
touched by a smell and fall.  I was struggling, feeling like I was going to
collapse under the weight of the words that were clinging to me, even though they didn't mean anything.I
didn't realize that I was doing it.I was trying to destroy everything.  That's
all there is to the great compensation of the sweetness of the
sweetness that swoops down
and doesn't get lost, and you don't let go.It turns out to be a lie, but the
white dream that flutters and wakes up has already
given up.It's a scent that won't bring me back.  When I touch you, I'm
falling, and I can't get out. I've
locked you up. I
won't talk about it. Even if I end up going home, I'll
say goodbye. I've
already stopped dreaming.
[Music]
Oh, mom, pong, there's already two pons,
there's already two pons, tch, and the current pons are
already too many
haloes, too.
I tried my best. I
came to see that guy's cat.
Yay, the cat that came to me is cute. I've
been really into cats for a long time now. I'm
petting the pooping cat, which is really bad.  Well,
my cat seems to be
smaller than Kiawan's,
so I'm starting to think that Japanese cats
are basically smaller.
Yeah, it's true. That's true even in a child like that,
right? Girl.  Well, when I look at the other members' cats,
they all seem so small.By the way,
everyone is curious and Japanese people
say that my room is dirty.
Chiara hasn't told me about it. I don't think it's dirty. I do
n't think there are many things like that. But I don't really think it's dirty. I do
n't think so. I don't think
so.  I'm sure there are a lot of them, but
someone said they were dirty. It's Chloe,
right? It's Louis. It's Choco-sensei. There's a lot of them. It's
embarrassing. Yes, it's embarrassing when people say that.
But today, I'm going to be beautiful for Kiara.  I guess that's
true to a certain extent,
but it's true that there may be a little too much stuff,
but I guess that can't be helped.If I
could do it without advance notice, I'd scream a little,
so I might not be able to do it.No, it's okay, it's
okay, it's pretty.  Okay, and then Robo-senpai and
I were on the way there, and I had a
dance lesson the other day before I started streaming, so I didn't have
time to eat in between,
so I asked if I had any snacks.  They
made a lot of food, but when I
looked at it, I saw that there were so many things I couldn't eat.Well,
Chiara and I don't have the same taste in food, so we
don't fit together.Yes, I was in the mood for raw fish today,
but oh, and there are mushrooms.  I was in the mood for mushrooms,
but both of them have a strong dislike for each other.
But they made me some frozen Chiha instead. I'm
glad they ate delicious food. Chan-
chan has a cat room. She's so
cute, she's so cute.
Take it easy, take it easy, I'm
playing alone right now, and my mom and dad have been playing together for a
long time, so I gave Mitsume, that's
dangerous, that's dangerous, that
Roboko-senpai, the tea that I love the most.
However, we had a drink together,
and what was it like? It was really
delicious, and it was really fashionable, but it was already cold. It was
cold, but I was
really drinking it.  It's so
easy to drink this winter,
please drink a lot.I'm drinking too much.I
was thirsty again today, but yeah, I'm
feeling a lot better.Good.What flavor is this?I
mean, Christmas flavor
Christmas.Christmas Flavor Tea Christmas
Revati.  I bought a lot for the members I'll be meeting this time,
about
15 boxes, and it
was really delicious for Roboku-senpai: oranges
, apples, cinnamon, and that star.
Everybody knows the spice that looks like
this.What's the name of it
? It's like an apple with a star on it. Well, that's okay. Basically, it doesn't have a star on it,
but it's just on that photo. But it's on the photo.
That's right, Star
Anise, what is that? Yes, there is such a thing. Yes, this is the
first time I've heard of it, but Cinnamo and Star
Anise are very Christmas-like. I
didn't know about the spices, but I didn't know about them. Yes,
Christmas spices have been discovered.  That's what I
wanted to say, but I do
n't know. I don't know. Isn't that what Star Anis is all about?
That's Star Anis. That's
what Star Anis was trying to say. Yes,
there's English. It's always like that.
Thank you for giving me that.
KP
for the helpful Mangu
Mangu Hanka Solo-chi.
Meaning, I always say it, I always say it, ah,
thank you very much. It's like
Sorochi. It's so cute that it's no good. It's already cute.
Well, I've been scared all this time,
but I'm sure it's getting across what I'm trying to say.It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I've
changed my mind, and I've already come to the orchestra.  I'm about to take my
clothes off, so cute.
Chachacha, sit on my lap. Do you
want to ride on my lap? It's really nice, though.
My cat won't sit on my lap. Since I graduated
from being a cat, I won't sit on my lap anymore.
Yeah, but it's really low over there. There's a
hole in there. Yeah, come on over there and
listen to our song. Listen to our song. Come with us. Oooh,
boing boing ass. [Music] Soooo, are you going to get off?  Don't get down,
don't get down, don't get down, go up. You can go up and down.
Yeah, oh, Kia's body is
okay. It's close. It's close. Today
, I chose a lot.
Singing By the way, I wonder if the volume is okay right now Audio I was
playing it even though I was listening to Ocho, but
what do you think? I wonder if it's okay now I
think Ah, senpai, okay, okay Audio
Balance Balance Balance By
Violence Violence You
know what balance is, right?
Balance balance I understand balance I understand balance
More English.  In other words, balance
balance balance
balance okay okay okay a little
variolint It's like variont, it's like variont
Bambabarang violence violence is
violence that
fighting that attacking attack
Um, what's going on?
Violence, violence, violence, violence, it's
scary, stop it, don't mess up
. If you make a mistake, it'll make all the difference, so be
careful.
From now on, I'll call Roboko-senpai and Ponko-senpai.
Okay,
hey, that's not true, isn't it? That's a senior, but yeah, that's
strange. What do you start singing? What do you start singing?
Which seems like the beginning? It seems like the beginning.
Today, I chose some pretty cute ones,
right? Let's call this the
last part. Let's call this the finish.  It's been a long time since I've been doing a
stream where I don't have any archives because I sing English songs,
but yeah, yeah, it's
been a long time since I've streamed a song in Japanese.  You
might think that you can't read all of Higara.
Well, I can read that. By the way,
there aren't that many songs that meet Yukata.
Ah, this is so true, that's all. Maybe, maybe,
this is also, maybe, that's true. Yeah, that's
true,
a little.  It's not good, even if it doesn't fit, it's
fine.I was in the mood for a yukata.I don't
really have a lot of costumes that can be used in 3D,
so that's why they matched me today.
Yeah, that's right, it's good to match Yukata It's a yukata, how cute, isn't it? It's
cute, cute, isn't it? It's been a while since I've seen it in a
while Kyukyu D Wawa I don't use 3D too much It's
super rare, yeah, rare Rare
Leaza Leaza Rare So from now on
Let's do this. Chiara
said that it looked very Japanese yukata. Yeah, this is it. I'm copying it. It's
not a little messed up, it's a little messed up, it's
a bit of a one.  I wonder if it's true?
Oh yeah, this is so nostalgic. I'm going to play this nostalgic song. [Music] [Music] Let's go. I wonder if the volume is okay. I
wonder about everyone. I don't know who my overthinking message might reach.
I'll be singing the next Ruta beat, yeah, I'm really
nostalgic for the summer. No
one else
will tell me how long the needle will be, and the world will turn upside down.  I
feel like I'm going to die, so I'm going to throw away all my greed for money, and I'm going to go deep into this world, and I'm going to wait a little longer. Please play the quince and tell me what to do with these feelings. Let's just
laugh at everything and
dance.  ] I do
n't care if you're the kid who came to me with all the adjustments and put your hands on me. The temperature of the world is
melting. You and I have a rendezvous. See?
Ranbu was flying, and the bunch was
enough, so I took it all in. Take it in with those two hands. So, listen to me for a second. I
can't say anything big or big. Do
n't cry, it hurts, it hurts, ballet dress.
Hit me harder.
It's hard to wait before I'm all alone
[Music]
Hey, I'm choosing you and I, look what I'm doing. My
legs are so twisted, my legs are so distorted, I'm
singing.
Well, I've come and gone again today. Please
bring me more. Please give me
some more. Play Marinke and tell me what to do with these feelings.
Let's hit Kanroy and laugh at everything. Let's
dance quickly.
[Music]  ]
Hey, it's Inu-inu who has become a father.
[Music] It
was Masika.
Ugh, stop it, spoiler, oh my gosh. I
spoiled it. No, no, no, no, I can't believe I'm singing. No, no, no, that's not true.
Hey, I heard you can do it up to 5 times now, so it's
okay Who said that?
It's already the 4th time, it's already the 5th time. Is it
dangerous? Be careful, be careful
Richi By the way, yes, we are.
Yeah, Kia has been with Hololive for over three years,
but we haven't really
gotten involved much, right? We haven't gotten involved until now.
But why are we suddenly doing this off-club thing?  Well, I
guess there's a reason why. We've become
good friends since we met at the recent La Sports Festival and Sports Festival.
No, that's right. We didn't get along that much. Well, I don't know
much about Chiara.
Now that it's public, we've become good friends.  Really cute pike
We were in the white group at a festival, and at that time,
almost all the pairs were the same or all of them were already together.Oh yes,
yes, they were together for a long time.They
said things like follow-up and battle.
Yes, they were all the same, but we were a good match,
right? We were a good match, but I
was worried. Roboco-senpai wasn't there at that practice, right? Well, I
couldn't do it in the beginning, so I was the one who practiced,
and in the second half I packed everything in.
In between, Chiara was there, so we learned everything together, so we were
able to do it, but even so, there was one time when we didn't have an
eco-echo.  I
learned how to do follow-ups, etc. I was
a little worried, wondering if my travel senpai would be okay, so I
had to teach him a little bit, but I was panicking
because I thought I wouldn't be able to teach him anything if I didn't have that much time.
Yeah, I was probably more panicked than I was.Hara, I
guess I
didn't have to practice at all
after that.It was already the actual performance.I didn't have time to practice, so I guess I was alone.  We'll be
doing it together for the first time soon.  It
went well, but in the actual game, I
didn't know that there were 3 times, so I didn't really understand it the first time,
but I understood everything about this game the first time, and I
understood it from the second time.  He
did it all, and then he got better and better. He
was really good at it, right? He's a genius.
Yeah, well, if he had been practicing first, he would have bought everything. Seriously, he
might have been too good from that first match.
No, that's right, yes, but somehow
that third match was a bit of a hit.
2000 was too good, but
3000 was too strong, and
everyone was scared. Yeah,
yeah.  If we had put that out there from the beginning, everyone would have
wondered if they were protecting themselves more.
Well, it's only at the end that they were more aggressive.  It
might have been good to go to the beat-
up.I'm glad I got beat-up.If you
look at the ranking board and see your name listed, you
must have checked it.It's a 1.2 That's really
good.That's from my house.  There
was one member of the white team who had a lot of kills,
but we
defeated that general, so we did 3 at first,
so our overall points were high.  Right?
Yes, yes, we were strong and strong. We
realized that it would be a
waste if we didn't do more things together. Yes, we
can do it. We can be aggressive. We said
yes, so it became a karaoke off-collaboration,
and that's how they came.  Right, you
just suddenly said you were coming, and
thank you very much for letting me into your house.I can come, but I
have a cat who is okay with coming, which is great.It's a great
environment, and the moment I arrive, I'm on the sofa.  I've been
flirting with my cat for a long time, so when he comes to me, he's so
kind to me. He's
like a human, so yeah, yeah, I want to get even closer to him. Let's get along
better with the cat and Roboco-senpai. The
cat will sleep with me. That's good.
Okay, okay, let's sing the second part.Sing, you're
not in a good mood right now.I
see, you're in a good mood.There
's something infinite about that robot-senpai and I.  Do
n't you think it's possible? It's
not like I'm forcing myself. First, I
'd like to say that I
'm used to the German version of this song, so I'm
probably a little confused about that character in Japanese. I'm
sorry, but in German.  You
have to look at the lyrics to remember it. It's
probably difficult to read the lyrics. But
yeah, yeah, but Robok-senpai's language is
impossible. It's impossible, so it's fine in Japanese. It's
okay, it's okay. All I can say is uh.
If you sing it in Japanese once, yeah yeah yeah, one chorus I'll sing it in
German,
really. I want to hear it, I want to hear it, listen to it. Well then, let's try singing it
in Japanese once. Okay, let's go
butterfly. Butterfly chichichichichi.  Chochochocho
Feel a little good, feel good, feel
good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel
good, feel like you're going crazy  It's
better to forget all the unnecessary things about your robot. I
don't have time to waste any more. I
'm sure it will reach my sky, but
I don't know what tomorrow's plans are. In this
empty world after an endless dream, it's just
manipulation and thoughts.  I feel like I'm about to lose, but
even though I have reliable wings that are just screws, Hibel
-
san is so good, I can't do it even when I'm hooked. I'm
going crazy.  I'm
going all the way to meet you, and I'm listening to the song where you're shouting ambiguous words.I
guess it's hard to keep up with this,
but in a
world where dreams don't come true, I
guess it's not bad to be manipulative and ignorant.
Even with dyed wings
[Music] I'm
going to go here, I don't know what to do
[Music]
Nauuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu canu
[music]
[applause]
Hey
It's nice, it's nice, it's
still a long time, it's still a long time,
then I'll go.In the
empty world after a modern dream, I
feel like I'm about to give up, but
with only my unreliable wings, I'm in the middle of
nothing.  Is
n't it bad to be ignorant? Even if you
dye your eyes and
don't have wings, I'm sure
it will come.
Well, something must have come. It's difficult. I
can hear you saying it. There's a lot of ribbing.
There are so much, but it's
okay.
It's a lie, thank you so much! It's true what I
just said. There's a lot of
it. I think I'll look into the German part.
Oh, Germany, oh,
Germany. Germany, Germany.  I
can't read it anymore, I'll sing it
to you
[Music]
I'll sing a song
No
[Music]
Best Den
yo
PASSde
TRder
[Music]
allmenDENDU [Music]  [
Music]
BALonmylove This is the
same as onmy love and Seb Saib Saib
Sub-licenser Sub-License
[Music]
Yes
A little Hmm Everyone says German is quite difficult.
But to be honest, in terms of pronunciation, I think it's
easier for people to understand German pronunciation than English.It's probably a lot of
that stuff, I guess.That hiragana-
like thing is similar to
Japanese Natsu
Hidaka.  It's still the same, right? That's
a little different, but no matter what the ref is, it doesn't matter what the
ref is or what it is. Basically, the ``dotsu'' is
better.  That's
right, that's what I
want to say. Thank you, genius. I
see. To be honest, my English is pretty
fluent, but at home, it's a
lot of
things. That's how it's pronounced in English.  However, the
person who created the English language is a bit strange,
so the pronunciation is unexpected.  It's
better to memorize this one, yeah,
yeah, that one. It's better to remember this one, senpai. [
Music]
Rep
wegstelleSTder
gef
All.  I'm
fluent in basic 3 Korean, and since I
started learning Korean this year, I've been able to respond one-on-one for about six months, which is
amazing.  I
only understand FPS terminology.Oh
but it's so confusing, it's possible.I
tried to provoke Nano and say it, and it's
like, ``Ochirago''.I understand.  I'm
babbling about stupid things,
remembering poop, nice, nice,
nice, nice, engineering, nice exchange, who
taught me who taught me that little bit?  Thank you for
teaching me about Korea, thank you, Ka. That's nice
. Yeah, I don't really use this much. I feel like I only use it in FPS like that. Ah, yeah, that's right. International.  I do
n't even know how to read this lol
lol It's like this one that's also laughing Oh yeah
yeah yeah Korean I wonder what I'm going to read about
this LOL LOL lol lol That's it.  I wonder if the
pronunciation of Kakaka Kakaka Kakaka is good.Yeah,
Akukuku Kuku Kuku Kuku.
Kuku, that's right, it looks a little like that Japanese.Ah, it's
like that Japanese word,
LOL, I want to smile.Everyone has their own way of laughing.Yeah, I
like this.  Let's sing, sing,
Nexon,
what should we do next? Should I
go to Jobane? Should I go to this? Yeah, this
is it. It's already over, and there's a sequel recently.English  It's
not English, it's not English, it's not English, it's not
English, it's about the movie, it's about that, it's about the movie, it
's about that.  Hmm, I'm
curious, I'm curious.
[Music] That's the
first time.
The reverb is
okay. The promise we exchanged won't be broken. I'll close it up and make sure.
Shaking off the darkness, I'll
move on. Yes, yes, yes, yes, please listen to it.
Ah, I wonder if I've been raided. There's someone out there who's been raided. Yes,
there's someone out there. The
shadow of my anxiety blooms over and over again as I
walk through this world. The
time is now engraved with no end in sight. It's beginning now, and I'm
carrying unchanging feelings.
Open the door that was aimed at me. My heart has just started running,
so even if I stop on a difficult path, it will
be beautiful. You will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid. No matter
what happens, I won't be able to do it.
Yes, yes, where are you?  I'm
probably somewhere out there.
When I look back, I see my companions. Before I know it, I'm
being held gently. In a world where everything is distorted, oh so
cute.
My red eyes.
Joy,
sadness.
If this growing voice can reach me, I'm sure we can
make a miracle happen.  I
won't forget what I've lost. I'll
check the screws. I'll shake off the burden and move on. No matter how big the wall is, I'll
overcome it, so believe in tomorrow.  Come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
I'm drawn to you. My
awakened heart has begun running to draw a future.
Even if I stop on a difficult road, it's still
beautiful. I've always been waiting for you to do it. I'm not afraid anymore.
Even if there is, I can't wait forever for tomorrow.  Oh my
gosh, cute, small, small, small, small, small, small, small, small, cat, small, small cat, small cat, cute, cute, cute little boy, little boy, little boy.  Yeah, I do
n't like it when we're not in the same space together, so when I close the door, I open it and open it.
Basically, my cat also wants to stay in the same place all the time.
Just be careful and go to another room.
As soon as it stops, it will come. It's really smart.
This guy is already recording and is sleeping without any questions and answers. Oh, he
doesn't really care. It's the sound of it, so sometimes
when he's recording, he'll say something.  If you cry,
no, no, it's easy to do healing work. He's sleeping. Yeah, that's
nice. I love cats.
Baba,
Baba, Nya
[Music]
Nya, I won't scare that cat. So I'll pet him.
Teun  I've been with a
cat who probably gets scared when that dog is around, but this one runs away from high places, so dogs can't jump high, so it's a win for this cat.  Well, that's right.
Cats can certainly run away easier than dogs,
so it's a bit of a pain. Yeah, dogs were
coming to play, and right now they're at my parents' house, and yeah, yeah, yeah, they're
tiny dogs.
I'm a cat person,
so if I were to buy a dog, I'd go with a Corgi
or that Samo.I know, I know, I know, a fluffy
one.I want one of them.It
's so cute, I know, but
Samo is a bit difficult, isn't it?  Seriously,
that hair is too difficult, isn't it amazing?
I just watched some videos and it's pretty amazing. It's the
same with Go, but Samuel seems to be more difficult.
Moel's are more dangerous because they
have so many layers of hair, so
yeah, it takes a whole day to groom them.
Sometimes I watch
videos of people giving their dogs a bath or getting their hair cut.  Look,
it's okay to be fluffy once in a while.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I thought it was okay for me to do it myself.It's
tough, but it's wrong.But I definitely like cats and
dogs with long hair.Yeah, yeah, I get it, I
get it, I get it, but once, I
gave this guy a haircut and shaved off all of his hair.
It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time, but I'm still normal right now. Hey, it's going to be 1 month soon. It's going to be back in 1 month. It's going to be back soon even after everything is processed. It was so cute.
If that's the case, I'm
going to give you a lion cut. I want to see a
lion
cut. I don't like a lion cut for a cat. I don't like it. Look at it later. It's
surprisingly cute. It's surprisingly ok. The lion
cut is tight. It's
nice and fluffy.  I want you to like me, I
know that, I understand that too, but yes, it
was surprisingly cute. Is it
true? And it was really easy. Oh, that's right. The hairballs
come out so much. When I touched it, it was...
Surprisingly, Cha-chan's hair doesn't fall out. I
was surprised. Yes, my cat is really dangerous.
Yo, it's about 10 times worse than Un-
Un-chan's hair, which is so bad. You don't shed hair? Surprisingly, the hair doesn't fall out. It's easy to leak,
isn't it?  Hey, I'm glad it's easy.
First of all, it's huge. Yeah, it's
getting cold, but next star. Well then, let's
sing a little bit over there, okay?  Let's
sing here, here, here, here, let's
sing each other's songs as well. It's a little
bit, I think this is difficult for me too,
but I have to sing the God station, okay, okay,
okay, let's give it a try. Let's talk about God again.
That's what Japanese viewers say all the time. That's
what I like about Japanese viewers. It's
good, it's interesting, right?
There's a certain way to answer it, right? Anything.  I
said I'd do it. I'll do it now, but I
said I'd do it. I
like it, so I'll sing the music video that I released recently.
Wait, wait, just one thing I
want to hear.
In that English.  Can you sing it in English? No, it's
different. When you say the word "graduation" in English,
everyone panics, but in Japanese, everyone
panics, but
maybe they're all excited.
For some reason, all the English viewers
start crying because they're talking about things that have nothing to do
with them, and when they say they're graduating, they're not talking about themselves.For
example,
when they talk about graduating from school, they don't say, "I'm graduating."
Everyone's heart hurts and they're really panicking. Maybe the
listeners of ``UnV'' are panicking,
and there may be quite a few of them.  I
'm scared of big news, I'm scared,
it's pitch black, I'm afraid of important news, it's important, yeah, that's
true, yeah, yeah, that's what makes my heart pounding, oh, this is what
I wrote, it's so cute the other day, it's cute, it's so cute, it's so
cute, it made me cry,
that's what I heard.  Okay, as much as I wanted, then let's go. Let's
try the challenge.
Okay, okay, yeah, this is good. You
memorized it. You did your best. Let's go.
I've been listening to it many times for a long time, so let's go to love.  I'm invited and I'm
falling
[Music] I'm
afraid to go to the role I've been given, so the only thing I've chosen as an answer to the passing days is my heart.I'm feeling
a little lonely without being left in the designated box.  I
don't know
[Music] I
know it's
not
true, but I can't help but fly away. I've trapped you in my confused eyebrows. I won't
let go of you. Eventually, you'll call it a lie, but I've already given up on this painful dream. I'm forever
away.
[Applause]
[Music] Even though I have
no words to say to you, I'm being
chased by you.
I'm drifting away, throwing away my hesitation, and you don't talk anymore.
Even if I lie eventually,
I've given up on my dream. I'm sure I'll never come back. I've been
exposed to the scent, and I'm falling in.
I'm trapped in my hesitation, and I won't talk anymore.
When I heard that I was losing weight, I
felt so refreshed that I stopped dreaming. Even when I was wearing it, it smelled and fell off.
That's right, I like
it, I really like it, but it's mixed with EDM. That's right, Chikakko. It's
good. This is really good at first.
Hey, by the way, why did you release the MV now
? This
is an original song that I originally did individually.  I didn't have that
CD, but I worked with a company called Upro to
make it into an album, so at
first I wondered if it was okay to release it in full or
if I could release a video of it.  I
didn't know, so I put it down for
a while, and Ami also wanted to put out a PV if I had the
chance.I got bored so I talked to her about it and let her release it.Naaah, I heard it was good, so it's been a while since I last saw her.  I
was surprised. My senior said something like this. He
was advertising this. He said he was going to release M.
That's not
new. I've heard of it before, so I don't think so.  I was
a little confused as to what was going on. Yeah, yeah, I've
heard that before
. It's hard to understand, right? I was
a little surprised. Yeah, I took a lot of time to put
everything to sleep. Well, with this music video, it's
even easier to make it easier for a lot of people.
Please listen to it if you can. Yes,
I've heard that I'm from the future. I'm from the future. I
made that. Where
did I hear that? Oh yeah, I do
n't understand how it feels, but it's normal.  I
bet they played it at that festival too. That was
impressive. I'm
glad you're watching it. Of course, kami kami,
kaka kami kami kami kami zaza kami za kami emo. This song is
fine, though.  Personally, I think there are a lot of people who find foreign meat appealing.Yeah,
definitely, that's right, Robo-senpai is Ro-senpai's
voice, and the voice itself really hits overseas 2.It really hits home for me.  I
can't get
too excited about it, it's okay, yeah, I guess that's just how I like it, yeah, yeah, that's what I like about it,
yeah,
yeah, whisper voice, oh, no, no, yeah, like, like, senkyu somachi chiara, it
said that there were no new songs, but
there are, but they're all in English, no, no,
actually.  I also like Chiara's English stuff,
but I can't sing it in English. Maybe
Lubo-senpai needs a lot of practice.
Yeah, I really like the rhythm of the new song.  I've
been listening to so many songs, trying to figure out who to sing them, but it's so bad that I
can't remember the lyrics every day.U I
really loved winter, and everything is difficult.Yeah, it's
really difficult, right?If I were
to sing it,  My first two songs in Japan,
that first song and the second song,
yeah, that's the one.Personally,
I quite like this and watched it.
Yeah, it really does look like Kiara. I was
thinking, ``This is
cute.'' The music video is really cute.
But what are they talking about? They're
talking about Heart Changja right now, but yeah,
that's Japanese.  I
said to my civil engineer senior, ``Let's choose which song,'' and he
was surprised to hear that he chose Heart Challenger.Basically,
all of them had to choose one song or another.
Yo, fans, I think the other members are too. I
feel like I haven't gotten all the compliments for singing Heart Challenge up until now.
But personally, this is the one that's easier to sing. I
thought, Oh, I'm so glad. I'm so happy.  I
feel like I'm more of a heart challenger,
and I want everyone to listen to it.It's a great song to listen to.It's
cute.The MV is really cute.That's because
it's a song and MV for Valentine's Day.  It
's telling the story of that amazing Valentine's Day.It's
got everything from the super cute title to the cute thank you and stuff like that.Sometimes
fans forget the Heart Challenger's name.
Hmm, for
example, I guess it's uh-na.
[Music]
Hahaha
Well, instead of that challenge, I'm going to put in another word.
There's a completely different story like Love Kankara in KFP.Nya, I
take it every time, but I guess
that's what it is.When I hear the word heart,
Hachama immediately comes out and I just
bought it.  What happened to Niehachamahachama? I was
really worried about that. No, no, but before that broadcast,
Ro-senpai mentioned Heart Challenger's
name once, but actually...
It's not a challenger, it's a different word.It's a different word, but I didn't say anything.I thought I'd leave it at that.Somewhere along the way, I also realized it and thought, ``I can't give up'' and realized, ``Okay, I'm a heart challenger.''  I
thought you were saying that, right? No, let's
go. Let's
do our best. Let's do our best.
Is that Japanese? Hey,
cute! Let's go! Yes, yes, yes, papan.
Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yeah,
yeah
[Music] My heart ca
n't stop pounding. I'm about to have a maiden's bravery.
When I need Valentine's Day, I'm so sad. I'm changing clothes, and I'm changing clothes. I'm going to change clothes, and I'm going to
make a start. Let's start with a heart-pounding song.
Before I can taste the fullness of love between Chire and Tarashi, it's the
sound of music. I
have to say it quickly, but I love
you.  I
wasn't able to read the report. It's
been a long time since I've been in school. It's definitely
nostalgic. Yeah, I
can't eat the feeling of moving forward. I
plucked up the courage to be late. I
love you.
No childcare, isn't it?
When I see you, I want to
be cute. Let's go in front of the mirror. I
want to wear a different outfit than usual. I want to look cute.
Even if I try to change things round and round, nothing will happen, but it's a confession
simulation.
[Applause]
[Music] A
one-shot battle for the moon. I hope tomorrow will
definitely be sunny.
[Music] Oh, English is okay.  [
Music]
Oh my
God
[Music] I burnt my
full love.
Before I go, I can hear it
echoing
in the window. I have to say it quickly or I'll fall asleep,
but I still love you.
Well, I remember that ``love'' goes in there, even though ``nice'' does
n't go in.
Nanasunas Daiki
[Music]
[Applause]
Seriously, cute goes up, too.  It really
came to my mind, it's true.It was unexpected.It seems
like a cool song.I prefer cool, cute songs.Basically, the
songs don't suit me.  I do
n't really care about Ami or Libby Kakko, it's okay, the atmosphere is so different, it's really difficult to make it feel different.For me, it doesn't matter if it's a cool song or the date, if I think I can sing it well, I'll practice.  Please sing that English song that everyone has been singing over and over again. I
'll leave it to you. Wait, I want to learn English normally. I
want to learn English. Yes, I want to learn English.
Hey, have you released a new album?  I
released my first album, and in it I
wrote a song that sounds a bit like Suzuki's Heart Challenger, and
it's in English, but
after Heart Challenger,
there's a song called Love Rush, look at the title.  Yes, it's a
continuation of a song that goes in the same direction, but it's a cute one. So, let's
sing it. It might be easy to sing.
If anything,
Love Rush is the most popular song among these English songs. It's a
cheap song.  I have to try to remember it
Yeah, I'm going to practice singing so I can sing, please. Echa-chan is
sitting in front of that door, but it's hard to sing. I feel like she wants to perform. I just
trained a little bit, so it's
okay. I want you to sing.
Cue.  That's right,
you can tell me what color it
is. It's brown. It
's an orange. It's an orange. It's an orange. It
's an orange. It's not a chai. It's an orange. It's not a chai. It's an orange.
It's an orange cat.
Orange would say PER
orang It's
nonono orange, yes, yes, I'm sure the
viewers have seen the photo, right? Yes,
yes, it's just an orange.
Everyone's different. There's a Japanese called Chishi.
Brown, seashells, seashells, and oranges. Yeah,
it looks a little like the best,
but it's orange.
Cats are orange, yeah, and their personalities are orange,
too.  hand
What does orange mean? Chiara.
No, it's not, but it's different. Orange
cats are seriously a little crazy,
but that's what makes them interesting. Orang
CSareHowdescribeThe
OforangHere is also an orange cat.
Hey, you can be an orange cat.
But I have a
bright and
active personality,
and I'm so strange that I'm so strange.
I like lasagna, that girl who said I was weird, that girl who knows Galfie.
Orange cat Galfie Galfie I do
n't know Garfie I don't know Garfie I don't know Garfie I don't know
Garfie I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel I don't
know Garfiel I don't know Garfiel.  No, that photo is
a bit too bright. The
crow color has changed. The color has changed. Wait a minute. It's a scam that has been rejected. It looks like it's been scammed. It looks like it's been scammed. Gargal Girl  I'll
show you, I think
you'll understand. Alright, I'm brightening
this too. It's bright too. That doesn't change either. The
colors are a little off. This photo is
n't a scam or a scam. I don't know this cat. Oh, I
get it.  I understand, I didn't know the name.
This is orange. This is
orange. This is this. This is a microwave. This is okay. I
think I can show you this. I've been given permission to show you this. It's
bigger and fatter.
This is fat, this is not 3,
it's allowed, this is allowed, this
is orange, right? I think Air's is even better than this.
Look at it, look at it, it's cute.
Orange. Orange. That fishing rod over there
is orange.  Yeah, yeah, see, oh no,
well, cats
can't really eat that amazing orange.Oh, English people
say the eyes are orange, orange, oh
my, this is orange.  It
's a different way of thinking, it's different,
it's something like a hospital, what color cat is written on it, so they
always write brown on it,
yeah, injapesThey would
sayThey
would say orange
Probably not in Japan.Yeah
, well, it
seems like it's pretty good.Yes, no, even that kind of orange cat has a
slightly weird personality, and it
's a dream.  I
don't like it when I'm not the number one in the room Yeah, I'm cute, so I guess I should come over, but the pickpocket who is quite cuddly won't take my advantage
Hey, I was lying on the floor, so cute.
Love your love. I'm a spoiled Chacha princess, so I'm a spoiled Chacha princess.
Yeah, Chacha princess. I have two cats at my parents' house,
but the one who stands up more than this one.
Yes, but I haven't lost to them, I'm really number one, and I'm
strong and strong-willed, so I'm pushing the two of them,
but the hair doesn't fall off at all.  You
should just go over there. Kankankan.
Eh, I
want you to go here
. Should I go here? I'll go to my senior. Chanda-
chan, you're free, aren't you? You're
sleeping.  Oh, you
ran away,
no, I went behind you,
yeah, next time, let's open up a little bit and sing.Oh,
by the way, there are throat lozenges, like last year.If you do
n't keep the surface of the water very clear, your throat gets dry
easily.I know, I know, I know.  It's so
dry, and I drank Monster today,
so it's even worse because it's so bad. My
throat is gone. I can
open it. How can I open it like that?  I
opened it, oh, can I open it? I want to open it.I
thought, cultural shock culture.
Shock, yeah, yeah, I really
like this.It tastes like lemon.It's nice.I like it.It's so good.It's
getting closer.Yo, I'll show you my belly
again.I'll keep showing my belly.Yes, my
throat hurts.  Even when I'm streaming,
my cat always goes somewhere else. I'm such a
troublesome woman. Are you
telling me to follow you?  I'm
going to go to this cute one. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go and sing a nostalgic Honey Works song.
Oh, it
's muted, let's go
[Music]
Yo, I'm
sorry for coming out of nowhere. I've loved you for a long time. Sometimes it's too much for me, isn't it? I'm a
little old.
[Music]
Confess to me. I can't believe you were serious about practicing. Do
n't look at me like that. Don't look at me like that. I'm curious.
Just stop lying. I'll just
keep it to myself and tomorrow I'll tell you what I
love.  Please support me and tell me about my mom, and
listen to me next to you
[Applause]
Yeah
Ru
[Music]  Even
though you don't always pay attention to the trip, it's
okay. Let the girl do it. I'll make you practice for the last time.
You're responding to the words of the book.
[Music]
I'm going to do my best even if it's just a trip.  I won't let you get carried away.
You're here with a smile. Let's talk about a
love story. Ca
n't you hear me when my heart is pounding
? I want you to hear the voice of my heart pounding.  It's
so exciting, isn't it? I
said it's summer with nostalgic nostalgia, so it's a
chain of nostalgic memories. Let's
sing right away. Let's go. Let's keep going.
Won-wan-mo-mo-ha-ni-wa-han-i-wa
[Music]
Hani-wa
Love,
Rayu LOVE LOVE, I love this!  I
love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I hope I can
sing it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love
it!
If you can't do anything about it, you can read it.It's
because of the winter season when I'm next to the sky, and I
remember it
even though I didn't ask for it.There's no way I can't say it out loud.
Even though I feel like I love you, it's too heavy for me to
carry alone.Even if I feel like I'm halfway through, I
can't tell who it is.I want to be more than just friends.I
push and pull, but I'm fluttering.
For example, if you fall in love with me, the
answer will be easy. Cats are weak. They're not sick, they're a bit vulnerable. It's
dangerous. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. This
love
story isn't going well. You guys are going to
break it.  I'm
really happy if I don't move on in this heartwarming autumn sky.That's why
I'm happy that someone is praising you,
but if that someone
is a girl, it's a little complicated.
I love you so much that I can't drink it all,
but I want to be excited,
and I love you so much that I want to sing the letters.
Yes, I heard it was fun,
but it was so painful. I wonder if I'll be able to open it. When I opened it, I was so
happy. It's too
heavy for me to carry alone.
When I break it down, I have to be special.  I want to
be more than just friends, no matter how hard I push or pull, you'll love
me more than anyone else. I'll show you that I'm your girlfriend.
[Music]
[Applause]
Like, like, like, whatever.
Tontotontonpa
[Music]
Nnnnnn, I love God and look at me more and
more.
In return, I throw a ball full of love. It's
not just my imagination. Our eyes meet. I
made a heart and fell in love.
Please, I'll do whatever I can.I'll
try to be the best at the end of the picture.I
know more than anyone who finds me,
but it's okay.If you stand on your hands, there's a horse.I'll
look at you more, and I'll
love you in return.  I'm
going to make a special one for you, show me more dreams, and have more fun.
Yes, yes, yes, please draw me a letter. I'll call you
again and again, and I'll
treasure it. It's still early, but I declare that I won't betray you.  It's time to do something  I don't like
it because I have the incompetent ability to not give in to the house crap.I raise my fist, sweat harder, and return it with more love.But I still have more to accept.I'm going to rebel against the stupid mommy song full of love.It's the end.  I'm getting
closer,
I'm lonely, I feel like crying even though I'm having fun Next time and next time,
I'll see you again Ah, Chachacha is
here
Tachachacha I met you, so
cute
Hey, I need words, even the words of someone who has no heart  I
need you
to say it louder and louder, yell more and
more, don't forget it more, and make it a special day, I'll sing to you all the time, I'll
always love you, and the words I love you will always show me
pictures, look at me more, and
show me more at meetings.  I'm going to show you a dream, have more fun, have more love, and
give you a
special.
Oh, I made a mistake. Why do you
think I sent it? Why did you put it out on SA?
Why, wait, wait, wait, wait.  I'm afraid I'll
make a mistake
Ah, I wonder if I'll be able to fit the body that was soloed in the comeback fansa Ah, but
I was kicked out, but I'm going to
make it again Ah, please don't look at it for a second Ah,
please don't look at it.  Hey everyone, don't look at me, do
n't
look at me, instead, look at me on location, chacha, please, chacha, please, chacha,
chacha, I'm
sitting behind the monitor, Nejiki, who's sitting down, did it.
[Music]
Hey, I don't know, I'm coming in. I'm
hot.
[Music]
[Music] I'm home. [
Music] I want to
meet you. I'm going to be a cat home. Let's
stay in Japan for a little while longer.  I'm
going back to the place Yeah, yeah,
if it happens again, let's do a
lot of crawling. You know, I might be on the phone 24 hours a day.
Instead, I'll be happy. It's a
little far away. It's a little far away.  I wish I
could sit in front of the monitor rather than behind it, right now, in that hard-to-reach place.I do like this sometimes, but
here, the keyboard turns out like this,
so my cat keeps getting in the way.
Generally, I'm going to put it here or here,
okay, so it's right in front of that keyboard,
yeah, it's in the way, and it's right here, right there, so it's
easy to touch, right, under the desk.
There's a little bit of space under the desk.  But
Yes, the cat sleeps there sometimes,
ah, it's nice and fluffy. Is it a
nuisance? It's a hindrance, but oh, I don't get mad at that cat. I definitely won't get mad. I want to be bothered by the cat. Yeah, I want to be bothered by the cat,
and then I keep getting in the way. We're
always fluffy with each other.
That's the kind of thing that gets in the way. That's what happens between cats and humans.
So let's do this song or the last one. I've
never sung it at karaoke before. In fact, even the panthers sing to each other.  You
look so good even though you're singing
Thank you, thank you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I
love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.  Let's
talk about the voice of the person who was doing it, Orangui. Well, the last song is
not the one that will save you recently.
Ah, ah, even if you drop it, you'll drop it a lot. I
wonder if you all
have Chacha
behind the monitor. And there was some kind of tape under the monitor,
and
Chicha will drop all the masking tape.  I just dropped it. There was
n't anything there, but now I'm
suddenly dropping everything. I
feel like this is in the way. No, I'm
always told not to put it down.  I
tried to sing it. Did you think it was cute? I'll be
waiting for you. Thank you, big sister. Big
sister, we
're so cute. You're so cute, but I won't call you cute. So
cute,
cute people, please get over it even more. I'll
get over it.  Big sister, big sister, what's
so cute, so cute, so cute? We're so
cute, my senpai, we haven't changed
that much. We're pretty much the same. No, we have
n't changed. No, Rocco-senpai.
What kind of encore do I want? Ah, the encore that I say.
Encore Encore What kind of encore are you doing?
Lilbin will do it or not. I may be bad at it,
but I'll do my best, Lubilbilubi. This is also chorus.
I'm singing, so yeah,
believe me. I don't believe in you. I believe in Roboko Senpai who is behind the scenes. Believe me,
believe me, no, no.  No, no, no, no, I'll
be your lover.
[Music] I want to be your lover.
This is another song. Lil Beer Bee,
Nyuroboko-san, let's go, Original Saji-san,
Lil Lil.  It's crazy, I
can't do it, I can't do it, I feel like it's going to
stop Hold on, just a
little bit, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a little
bit, make a dream Just a
little bit, just a little bit  Just a little bit,
then it'll be over soon.
[Music]
No one will
understand. There's no such thing as a dimensional curse. That's outrageous. That's
already it.
If you know what's going on, just wrap it in your hand and hold it for just a little bit.  Please
stay with me, just a little bit, just a little bit
, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a
little bit.
Yeah, but if it's just a little bit, it'll get better
soon. [Music] Mota [Music] I'm scared It's difficult to say Bibi Bibi, Momo Momo, Noeya,
etc. This is difficult, it's difficult, so it's
difficult even for Japan's Holomen JP.
But people keep saying they want to try singing. Yeah, that's good, it's a
challenge. I'm so
happy. I can't sing well,
but I'm glad that you're trying to sing at all. I
wanted to practice, but ever since I came to Japan.  Enough already  I'm so
busy, so busy, and I can
read it.I didn't wave the flag, but I
can't stop dreaming.Well, I did that research first.I
made a dream.That's the way I write it.That's
not how I write it.I don't say it because it's manufactured.Yes,
that's how it is.  I
think it's interesting how Japanese people write the lyrics,
because they don't have it in English.That's
right, even though they write kanji in kanji, they
read it in a completely different way.  There
are quite a few things that aren't the normal way to read it.Sometimes,
for
example, I've
written a book about it
and it seems like it's serious.But that's amazing.I
think it's easy to understand.  Cosmo,
oh, space cosmo, that's
okay, but
what do you say when you write ``A bubble princess''? I
understand bubble princess,
bubble princess, bubble princess, this is in Japan.  Ariel is
often referred to as Ariel, and
that's what I hear.Oh yeah, that's right, that's right.Oh yeah, that's right.It's funny.It's the
first time I've seen Princess A.I've heard of Princess Ariel.It's
often said that it's a sparkling name.Oh yeah, that's
right.  Well,
there are some Japanese people who have never heard of it before. Yes, there are people who have never seen it before.
Yes, there are people who have seen that movie of Aria recently.  I
saw it on the plane. I saw it
on the plane. It was good, it was good. It was
good. It was a long time since I saw Riel's
story. It's been a while. How many years has it been? Yeah,
what do you like about Disney?
But, I quite like
Rapunzel, huh? Lala Pontz Laponts
Yes, Rapunzel is really cute, and my mother
also liked it. Is
that it? Is that a German story?  It's
Germany, so let's look
it up. It's crazy. It's not that detailed,
but it says German fairy tales. That's
right. German caves, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
A lot of Disney movies
use the story of the Grimm brothers, so it's
fine.The Grimm brothers were German people, but there's a story like that in German.
Yeah, I wrote a lot, I know Grim Grim
, I know Shekspia, you
know Kum Videos
Yeah, it's a good
idea to be a snow princess. It looks like that yes, that's right, that's yes, that snowwight, that snowwight, that's red,
that's a story.
It's like a scary Grimm video,
so I remember it pretty well, and there's something like the behind-the-scenes setting,
right? Well, anyone can do it.  I
know about the Grimm brothers, yeah, yeah, actually
.
Glee is also a story about brothers, but Disney
doesn't want to make it too dark, so they
make a version that's a bit more sparkly.  I feel like we're getting along
even more. It's even scarier. It's
black, and it's scary. It's the first time I've learned that it
's the front, not the back. Yeah, yeah, I didn't know that. Yeah,
yeah, I learned it at Disney. It
looks so sweet.  Yeah, almost everyone  I
first learned about the story of the Gorim brothers at Disney.In Japan,
when I was little, I probably read Snow White in picture books,
so I remembered it and I
remember it as if I admired this amazing princess.  There
may be a lot of people who don't know the original version at all.
Yeah, I see. Yeah, Roboko-senpai. Yes, I like
it.
Love. It's cute. I want to do it again. Let's play again. Let's
play a lot. Even after I go back, I haven't had anything.  Let's
go play again.I'm in Japan.As a Japanese person, I
want to go to Australia, but Austria is
next to
Australia.Australia and Austria are different.No,
because Australia is like this.Australia
is an island and English is spoken.EnglishAustralia is
next to Germany, and it's Europe.
Surrounded by a country with no sea in the middle of the world, it
feels like it's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time
since I thought I was a scary person.  I
guess it's the same as Oetabe-chan,
but no, I was just making a joke about it at first,
but when I say to Japanese people,
especially Japanese people, that I'm Austrian, all they can say is
Stralia.  I've been making jokes
about it a lot since I first made my streaming debut, but there were a lot of people who seriously misunderstood me, so I stopped saying, ``Yeah, yeah, I'm already Australian.''  I
started saying that I'm Austrian,
but since we're both so
good at speaking Japanese, it's like, oh
yeah, Australia is so far away.  I
think so, when I go out to play, I
also go to see Chiara. I
said it now, so Chizu can tell.
Well, where is it
? I said, right next to Germany, next to Germany?  It
's next door, it's next to Switzerland, it's
next to Hungary, it's surrounded by
Italy, and it's shaped like a shoe facing the sea, so
yeah, it looks like
Oria is sitting on top of it, yeah, that freedom.
Please play
with me, it's been a while. I have to study a little bit. I have to study a little
bit. I have to learn a little bit. Ah, do you
know that Austrian leader? Yeah, I've
heard of Win, yeah, Win.
There's something like a singing contest, right? He's famous. I
know Mozart. I understand.
Mozart was born and
grew up in Austria, famous for classical music. Well, he's very famous for classical music.
Yes, he's famous for classical music.
There are places that are famous for music, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, I see, I see, I understand, I'm glad I understand, okay, I'm getting lost, I went there once.
Hello,
thank you for your help. Okay, senpai. Okay,
Kia, I don't know. Call me Red Bull. Oria, I'm
surprised. You're probably surprised. That looks like the one in a can. I
didn't know that.
But Leah's Red Bull is much stronger in
Japan.  There's something about Japan that seems
even worse. Energy drinks have a certain law. They don't last very well, so they
can't make them strong, but they're too weak. They're weak.
Yeah, that Japanese thing doesn't work at
all. It doesn't work. It doesn't work at all. I'm the type of person who listens even if it's just a little bit,
but I
think it's weak. It's
been nerfed, but I often drink alcohol too.  You
say it's low, but that's not true. I
wonder if it's because Japanese people
generally don't have a strong tolerance for alcohol. I do
n't drink when my friends from overseas come to Japan.  Lazy  I was
told that I could make it about twice as strong as this one, which is extremely weak,
so I thought that would be weak as well.I don't drink alcohol at all,
so I can't say much about that, but it seems
likely.
Yes, there are various laws, so it
makes sense. I see, it's interesting, but I didn't know anything about Red Bull.
There are cases like Holy Red Bull, right?
Only the Japanese members have that button. My
seniors and I are waiting for this. I
'm waiting for this. The
European version of Red Bull is
divided into different countries, isn't it?
Each company has something.
Hey, Headquarters, Ah, Headquarters is breaking up. It's like Japan. I
'm waiting for you. I'm waiting for you. I'm waiting for you.
Please. I mean, today.
So that's about it, okay?
Can we play with the cat for a little while? No, not at all. We're
playing with each other. We're flirting. What's that,
Kaenoko-senpai? What's that?
After this stream is over, just a little bit.  I
wonder if I can record it for about 10 minutes or 15 minutes.
Thank you. Yesterday, I was told
that I want this industry to be reorganized.
Even though I was told that my current situation has stopped.  hair  I do
n't have any. Oh, then please use it.
Thank you, angel. Thank you, angel. It's fine, thank you
. You can stay here at all. Yeah, I
just want to stop, but tomorrow, it's a little early tomorrow, so I'll come back and
give it to you.
[Music]  ]
Your hands are warm. You're
cold. I'm cold, so I'm cold. But my cold
heart is warm, right? These are the
eyes of Japan. It's like I'm hearing this for the first time. That's why I say
yes. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, thank you, Senkyu for
One, I'll play with you again, so please,
yeah, it's a robot, so I
want to collect it because it's a robot, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat,
robot, so my aim is to keep it
warm.  Let's go
with the robot, see you
again. I
have a strong sense of excitement. I love you
so much. I love you so much.  I love
you so much, I hate you, I love you, I hate you, I
love you so much.  You've been
watching me for a long time.Please
squeeze me. Please look at me more.I'm
lonely. Please squeeze me more.
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you
so much, I need you
to hold me so tightly, you know, everyone, don't listen to me, listen to me, listen to me properly, come on, come on, hurry up, it's cold.