Ade
[Music]
Holo Live production official app that will make you love Pipopapo Oshi even more This is
brought to you by Holo Plus.
Good morning! This is the early spring of Hololive's new staff.
This distribution is a
nurturing student created together with the fans.  Broadcasting is based on the concept,
and plans and questions can be
submitted on the official app Holoplus. We hope that with everyone's help, we and the program
can grow together,
so we are also growing in various ways, including home videos.
[Music] I hope
someday it will change into something even more wonderful. I'll do my best. I
'll send you a relaxing message, so
please watch over me warmly
. Well then, let's go, Yosei's Holo Holiday
Kakkokari
[Music]
No, this cat's oyster  Kakokari is also
starting to be quite lively, isn't it?
Look, everyone on the right.I
wanted to come to see you the other day, but I
didn't get it.  It
's still hot in August, but
since you've been so kind to me, I'd like to go to bed,
but it's almost time for today's guests to
arrive.  I'm
going to play a lot of ping pong,
please. Hey,
hey, I'm sorry to bother you. I'm sorry to bother you.
What a lively audience.
There were so many people here today. So,
Ms. Calliope, please introduce yourself.
I'm...  I'm a female
calliope and a Shinigami.Lapa
singer streamer calliope calliope
thank you very much for your support senkyu
thank you and kia sao hi kikeni
hololive english noe miss's
high character today  It's not a mayor, it's a
frog. It looks
like Nodoka-chan
likes frogs. And there are some frogs here, too.
Thank
you, and Inari-san,
please. Wow, good morning, hello, good evening, Holo.
Live, miss, two-inus.
Thank you. Please. So, welcome to
Japan.
Ah,
Uruka. Welcome back. Welcome back. Welcome back. Yes,
today.  It's been a long time
since we've had 3 customers come. Kaoa-san, it
's been a while, yes, it's been a long time, and Inas-san, it's
nice to meet
you. I'm so happy to see you. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I'm so
cute, but I'm sitting so far away from you
. I'm sure you don't want to interact with me, but I'm in a hurry to
interact with you.
Yes, everyone's close to me. I'm so excited. Are
you
enjoying Japan to the fullest? It's hot, isn't it
?  Please stop being hot, hot, hot, please. It
's the worst. I'm not really good at hot weather.
No, I love winter. Yes, everyone
loves winter. But it's still fun.
Yesterday, I still don't tell you, but I had a lot of fun.  It was
a lot of fun. I
guess I made a mistake or something, but it's
still a secret. I don't know who these three are. I don't
know, I don't know. It's cute. I'm
looking forward to it. Thank you.
So today is hot.
I'm in the middle of the day, but I'll
leave it to Nodoka, as I'm sure you'll be able to tell me exactly what you're looking for.  That's right, it's a special meeting. Three
people like this are coming all at once.
There
's some big news. I wonder what everyone is going to do. I
want to know. I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So
I'm going to the party.  Is it okay to go? It's
okay.
[Music]
Men Actually, an overseas version of Holoplus is coming out.
That's right. The
global version of Holoplus has been officially released.Tayata
English It's
helpful. Since this release, Holoplus will also be available from outside of Japan.
Plus will be available
Yes, and official news and original
content will also be available in English.
And fans will be able to interact with each other in their language.
Yes, the release is
coming soon, so stay tuned for the next news.
Please look forward to it and check out the announcements on Official X. I'm
really looking forward to it. I've been waiting for it so long.
All of you overseas who have been waiting
can also see the Hololive schedule on the app. Oh
yeah, official news,
both in Japanese and English.  I can see it, I can see
it, I can see it, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy,
finally May we use it too, so I'm
always
looking for projects to represent it in Holoplus, but this time, I'm looking
forward to the release of the global version of Holoplus.  As a test, we are
looking for projects in English.Thank
you for all the comments from Japan and overseas.  I
've prepared the five that Nodoka chose as a list, so I'm going to do as many as I can
as time allows.Yes,
toy fingers, camo,
camo, camo, oichan, icchane, why, why, why are you on
top?  I'm all alone again, and
that's not the place where tall Nodoka-chan is. I'm sure, but today Ina-san will
be the main character,
and MC-chan
won't be the MC.  This time,
in addition to comments in Japanese, there were a lot of comments from people overseas, and we
ended up with a lineup like this:
Senior/Junior ASMR tongue twister/drawing showdown
Japanpa: Yes, I see
. I see. Comments from people who want me to make a dish.  I
wanted to do it for a while, but I guess I can't cook in the studio, so I decided to go ahead and cook it for
you next time, Nodoka-
chan.  On the other hand, when I cook, the studio
explodes.If it's Sumotokai, I-chan is more like that baker than cooking.
[Laughs]
Thank you very much.I'm
looking forward to it.So, I'd like you to choose from among these,
everyone.  Which one
should we choose? Well, you can choose first.
Go ahead, Ape-san, go ahead. Okay. Well then, tongue twisters. Okay,
yes, this came from tongue twisters. So let's
take a look at the comments we received.
This is
Don, no, Japanese is not.
Twister is a Japanese-style tongue twister
showdown and
thank you for your ideas.
So this time, both in Japan and overseas, the one that
received the most posts was the pun twister
tongue twister. Everyone is
good at tongue twisters.  Well,
Mr. Kape does a lot of rapping,
so maybe he
can do it. He's a rapper,
so he said he wanted to do it.
But what about Mr. Ina? I'm
fine with those puns, but it's a joke.  It
's okay, I'm a little lazy with the words, but it's okay. I might be able to do it in German. If I were in German, I might be good at it. Today, I'll probably speak Japanese. Today, I'm going to
try to come up with some original tongue twisters for the live performance.  I
'm here, so I'm going to challenge you with an original Holo Lifetime Toys Yes Hololai Since it's Time Star, I'm trying my best to adjust to the first theme, Inanis-san, and I'll do my best.
Nice chair Ah yes, this is a tongue twister. Let's
do it 3 times 3 times.
Ah, I don't know. Well then,
3 times. 3 times. Now, it's Ina's challenge.
Twister tongue
twister. Start
Ina.  Swiss inaninis inasu
forgets to draw Inasu's nice
chair I'll do my best, do my best,
Inasu, nice
chair
nice Swiss It's cute, so it's okay Because it's cute It's
clear,
but I'll put the other cages in  Now, Akari-chan,
look at me, let's go, let's go, let's go, I'm nice, I'm nice,
I'm [ __ ], it was so smooth, so smooth, so powerful.
There are some parts that are difficult, so when you say my name, I
always say it from the beginning, so when Inanisu is in front of me, I
feel a little nervous.
Well,
yes, yes, the tongue twisters are like this, but then it goes on and on. The
second one was done by Chiara-san, Nigiwa-a-kiwawa-san. I
definitely
can do it. I'm
obviously tired of this.
Chiara is still tired of it.  I don't
think so. I see. I wonder if I can make it. I wonder if
I'll make it
or not. Let's try it three times. It's
Mr. A's challenge. It
started clearly in the fall. It was clearly
in the fall.
[Music]  ]
Thank you so much!
How about this, Masuie-chan? I'll
try it.
Obviously,
do your best, do
your best. Eh, clearly not eeooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeoutouting out there out out there out out there out out there out out there out Kiara out there
down out Chiara out there down out
Chiara out there out and down out Kiara up out and down (Kia)
out here,
that's great.  Yeah, that's fine, yes, I
can't do it.
Scary, scary, scary. If it's scary, scary, scary, it's really
embarrassing and embarrassing. Seriously, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ka-chan's stuff is super difficult. Otherwise, it
's no good.
Well, let's take a look at Kalio's theme.
Calliope Karaoke in Paris
Calliope Karaoke in Paris Oh, Calliope Paris
Oh yeah, but I can say it right now. Yeah, I've already said it. I can
say it. I've already said it.
Okay, let's go. It's Calliope's
challenge. I'll do my best to see if I can make it.
Start
Calliope, wait a minute, I'm nervous, I'm
nervous. Fall, wait a minute, one time later. Calliope, then I'll go back to
Paris. Oh yeah, that sounds good.
Calliope, call
it in Paris. Calliope, call it in Paris.  Calliope on location,
calliope in Paris, paris,
time, callo, Paris,
time.  Is it okay to stop this? Is it
OK? Is it okay? Daio
Official
Stream embarrassed Shame Offshart
Throb  Well,
Mr. Kao was a success.
[Music]
Yes, it was difficult.Japanese was difficult.Yes, English was
difficult.There is one more difficult word for everyone,
but it seems like there is a tongue twister.Yes, let's
do it.Oh, this is that.  Is
that so? That's it, hehe hehe
everyone. This is all a bit too complicated, so here
's a suggestion from Kia. Let's
go to Zimantan Star.
These are the German tongue twisters that are difficult for me too.  But,
erm, I came up with it at the last minute,
so it doesn't appear on that screen.
But I'll say it once again, please.
Hehehehehehehehehehe it's
impossible, yes, so I
want everyone to try this.  I see, I
wrote Fisher's Fritz Fish and Fritz Fish in katakana,
but first, let's start with Kari-chan, who seems to be good at it.
Do your best, Ka-chan. Let's
do it in an American pronunciation. Let's go
to Kao-san.
Let's
start.  Fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish.
Can you say this?
By the way, what does it mean? Kae, what does it mean? The
person who catches that fish, the angler, the angler, the person who catches that fish, the angler, the angler, the person who
catches that fish.
Fish and Flitch I
have hookers, but I don't think they'll be quick enough if I call them,
so please listen to my voice as much as possible and
try it.
Wow, this is the most
difficult one.
Thank you very much for making this. Thank you very much for
making Nice and Nice Stan.
Well done. Machi. That's a tongue twister.
Thank you
very much. Thank you. Thank you.
Well then, planning.  Let's go back to choosing.Next,
what should we do?
Hmm, then I'll choose.Yes, hmm.Next, let's have a
drawing competition.Here
is the post that I received.Yes, all three of us can draw.  I'm good at it, so I
'd like you to try the illustration quiz.Ina-
chan will finally appear on Flo's Holiday, so I
'm really looking forward to it.So,
let's eat some Japanese sweets and see each other.  I'd like to see a stream of drawings,
but for some reason we
used to do this as a collaboration in the early days.I
remember the illustrations we did, so much
so that I wanted to do that
project again.  So once again, let's
draw each other
on your tablet. Calliope is
Kia next door, Kia is next door Enari, and Eri is next door. Let
's draw Calliope. Let's spend some
time.  It takes about 10 minutes to
make a presentation.If the person who wrote it
likes it, it's
passed, so let's go.Ah, yes, ok.Let's get started.I'll
show you how you draw.  Let's
not show it.
So, Ki is now a frog. Yes, a frog is
shown, and Calliope
is shown. Ah, he has that face.
Orange, uh, he has bangs. What
is
that, everyone?  Yes, this shark is
good at drawing, and each person has their own taste.I
get the impression that they don't draw well, but
when did you start drawing?A
long time ago, when I was little, I used to draw a lot,
but yeah, that's right.  Oh, I say when I was little,
but it wasn't that small, but I've completely
given up on it, so I haven't written much about it. It's
amazing. Inanis-san is already
progressing so fast. We've got
10 minutes, so
ten minutes is enough, Ina-chan.  Ha, that one minute
is enough. No, no, Hae-san is the type of person who draws
quickly. He's pretty fast. He's very fast
. Just like that kid doesn't know, it's the best. Oh,
and Mr. Galio isn't even here. Mr. Kia of this frog.
And what's her cute hair style?
What
's the name of the Blaze book? What's the name Brayle? Oh yeah,
yeah, yeah, wait a minute, right now,
Ah, Chorogi Wow, and I'm also pretty Ako-
chan. I can see A-san.  I'm here
Nesan
[Music]
Ah,
wow,
this is amazing, it's so fast Ina-chan This is so fast!
Wait, Te-chan
[Music]
Oh, it's not just the speed, it's the
high quality, so it's
amazing. That's amazing, by the way.  I guess I'm the only one left-handed among them.
Hey, don't look at that cute girl. Don't look at her. Don't look at her. It's okay. Do
n't look at her. To everyone, she has
pointed ears and a round sound.
Yes, I'm writing it down too.
Ha, it's a little cute. I have it. I
have a KFP. I actually have it. It's
cute, it's cute. Ah, so
yes, I'm currently asking everyone to enjoy it.  I'm wondering if you're all making something,
and seeing what you're writing makes us want to make something too.We
have a little news for you.This is a temporary
program called Holo's Holidays, which is currently being streamed.  We
recently started recruiting logos on Holoplus, and they said
yes, so it was adopted.It's been a long time
since Holo's holidays, so why
don't we have a logo yet?We don't have the budget,
so we decided to make it together and distribute it.
We are currently looking for logos, so please
take a look at Holoplus for the details of the recruitment trip. Isn't this even in English
? How do you say it, please?
[Music]
Thank you for planning this project. Thank you for your help.
If you say yes, please take a look at the details on Holoplus.Each
person can apply as many times as they like.Okay,
everyone, please
send us your logo.Please
give us your logo.What
kind of logo would you like Nodoka-chan to have?What
is your ideal logo?  Yeah, but I like that frog, so I
think it would be nice to have something like the one with the frog in it, or something like that.I think it would be nice to have a handmade character that looks like something I would see on this program.I
certainly think it would be good to go home.  Oh
yeah, I'll be waiting for you.
[Music]
Okay, by the way, how are you all far?
Oh, by the way, see you then. The picture is being completed, and I wonder if
everyone is writing. By the way, I wonder
what happens when you draw something like
this manga or anime.  I was influenced by this
anime, and I like this anime.Hello,
I watch a lot of anime,
so what do you watch?
What do you like?Ina-san, I
like all of them.I like them all.I like them all.  I
watch a lot of series like Enen, so
yeah, yeah, I like fantasy, etc. I
like Kado Hunter, yeah,
Adventure and Bechi, yeah, that's
Swiss Bifu, yeah,
yeah, yeah, that's all, really. Do you
like Japanese anime?  Yes, I
like it. Yes, yes, I might like it.
Can I say your name? I think it's okay. I
think it's okay. I like that Bakemonogatari
series the most.
Apparently, there's a new one coming out now.  I
'm currently watching that Megee from beginning to end at the same time.We've all
seen it before, but I'm
watching it again to remember it, and it
's longer than I expected.  It's true that I
watched the first movie from the beginning,
but I haven't gotten all the way to the end
and haven't been able to watch the new one yet.
Is there something like that?
I've been a fan of Nako-chan
for a long time, but now that I'm watching her again for the first time in a long time, I can't help but feel that
Hanekawa and
Kano-chan love her too. Wow, I get
it, I'm Shinobu Shinobu I.
Yeah, I watched
Kizumonogatari and I'm like, ``Yeah, I like it.''
Which version of Shinobu do you
like best? Yes, there are a lot of different ones,
Otone or teenager. Yeah,
I like the smaller one.  Yeah, it's
cute, right? Yes, it's difficult, but I've seen her become a teenager for some time. When I say teenager, I feel like she's a 17-year-old. Oh, she's so cute. They're all so cute. I like Calliope. I
like Aga.  Actually, I like
dark fantasy the most,
but I really don't like it.There's a
manga called Acta that I like the most.It
's quite new, but there's an anime
coming out next year.  Ah, the anime has been decided. Yes, it's
been decided, it's been decided, yeah, I'm
really looking forward to it. It's a series that I really
love. What do I like about it? The
art style is so incredible
that it's impossible to imagine. The design is
a bit like Japanese candy.
Usu has a little bit of overseas style.The
action scenes are the best.It
's the best gacha, interesting, and really interesting.It's trash that makes you understand the actors.Yes, it's
really
trash.That's what I mean.
That's right, everyone. It's a really
good story.
Well, I
have one more thing I'd like to ask Kao-san. Speaking of anime, you
were in charge of the ending of Isekai Suicide Squat.  I
made it.Oh yeah, how did it feel to be in charge of the theme song for the anime?No, I
still ca
n't believe it.Yeah, I can't believe it right now, so when I got the offer, I
couldn't believe what happened.  I don't
feel like I'm feeling happy or surprised.Actually, I feel like, ``Oh, I see.''But I can't believe it.It's true, isn't it
?Is it true?Is
it true?  I'm so happy. That's
so precious. Thank
you so much. Everyone, please check out Isekai Susite
Squat Ending Theme.
Please, everyone. I wonder if it's
time to put it on. I wonder if it's
really in this.  I'm the slowest, it
's okay, it's okay, I'm probably cute, I'm
nervous, my hands are sweaty, that's no good, no, no, no,
no, I'm putting pressure on Gai-chan because of Gai-chan's past,
everyone is good at it, so it's definitely me.  Do you really
like the picture? I'll come back for more, okay. It's okay.
[Music] The
picture is a bit too simple, but the one
you wrote earlier was also
amazing. Thank you. It's hard to write.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's okay.
But I don't know what to do.
It's Kia-chan, who was so
cute. Thank you. I drew her so cute. Well then, there's
still a little more to see. Since you're all having fun, me too. Nenodoka also just before we met.
Actually, it's a little embarrassing to see everyone's drawings.I
want to see them.It's
embarrassing.I want to see it.I
want to see it.It
's a happy welcome holoro holiday, so it
's the best.I'm so
happy.Thank you very much.  I'm
a bit nervous about this, right now.There
's a Hololive game on that island, and there's all sorts of
treasures around.It's just a face, and it's just a head,
and it's round and squishy, ​​so yeah, that's right, it's
added to Taka Mountain.  It looks like it will
be added I want it to be added It's true that it is as it is I
tried to write it in a slightly squishy way.
Really
cute UNto
Thank you very much, thank you so much.
How about you, Calliope? I
thought, oh, let's take a look. Let's
take a look at what Calliope wrote. Yes,
this
is
old man and
cute Kasan's chin.  The cute touch is
amazing.It's so cute.Thank you Kiri-chan.I
tried my best.Yes, it looks like this.Yara-
chan is cute, so it's nice.It's a delicious
naori.Umee.This is a decoration.Alright, the next person is
Chiara.Let's move on to the next one.Kaeun
Wait, let's go together for a moment. Haha,
that's nice. I want to decorate this.
Naomaikaun ITreallyBad.
Cute Tsukyuo. It's finally here.
Okay, Kia-san. Mr.
Su here
. Thank you. Add some color. It's
amazing.  This pose is cute, is
n't it?
[Music]
Wow, this is all decoration.
Thank you so much for being cute. Now, that's the end. Wow,
Ms. Innis is back, Ms. Calliope.
Ms. Kao, who wrote to the last minute about me.
Look good.  Let's go ahead.Okay,
here it is.Usu's
favorite piece.Also,
I want to be written by Ina-chan.  She's
so cute, she's cute, she's so
cute I feel like she's writing something like this.This is really
sexy.It's true.Oh, I'm so
happy, but I
want to sign something like "Thank you, Shinigami."  I'm
a little confused when I sign Karademona-chan.
No, this is me
cosplaying as Paris-chan. Ah yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes this is so
thank you everyone for drawing this.
Thank you very much. It's been a while since I
last wrote anything. Yeah, I'm glad you saw it too.
Okay, let's move on
to the next one. There's only one more left, I guess. Okay, finally,
Mr. Nijaine, let me choose which one.  Let's do it,
then I'll be Tepa junior.
Oh nice. Let's see what this is.
Here's the benefit you received.
Yes, please tell me as much as you can about each of the Holo men.
Episodes with the good friends of the Holo men will
be included in Hololive.  If there are any JP Holomen who joined before, I
would like you to let me know,
so I
asked everyone.It seems like I'm curious about the relationship with the members of Hololive JP today.Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.  Well,
I don't know what to do first. Let's do it first. Let's talk about it. Please
tell me some stories. Well, I'm surprised. There's a
junior colleague with whom I get along very well.
Who is he?  He
's my junior, so I've only recently been
with him, but I've become really good friends with Raden from Lee Cross, and I'm hoping we can do one more collaboration all at once.I've
been good friends with Ririka
for quite some time now, so
Raden.  During our last collaboration, I
learned a lot about her love for art, and she said that she
loves not only Japanese art, but art from all over the world, and she
showed me all kinds of books.  I
was shown all kinds of art techniques and things like that, and I thought, oh, this kid was
really serious about something, and surprisingly, I
started talking about that topic,
and for some reason I became interested in that pretty Loppa art
museum.  I don't think we'll
be together in history or
anything like that.That's why
every time I collaborate with a Japanese member, I
go on a trip and I'd love to
go to Austria next time.  When I
said yes, everyone said they were going, but they didn't come,
but Lale-chan was pretty serious about it and
said yes, she wanted to go. She's currently in the
process of getting a passport and things like that, which is great. She seems to be
making progress.  I'm really excited to live there,
and I'd like to go on a little trip around Europe with Lyrica-chan
and me.  I'll
be waiting for the next update. But it's okay. There are so many museums in the world
that you can visit. Come on, Ka-
chan. I need
to get a passport, so
please let me know. If you're going, thank you.
Please, please! Oh, how about this?  There are also
seniors and juniors who like episodes,
things like this that happened in the future, things
like this I'd like to do with the JP members,
things I'd like to do with this person.Yes, that's
right.
I
talked about how I met a senior I liked, and I remember when I
met everyone for the first time,
there was this aura of manager-like aura about them.Oh yeah, that's
right,
when I met Rene for the first time.  Yeah, yeah yeah, Kia-chan
was there too, right? That was quite a while ago. It
was quite a while ago, really. No, yeah, that's right. Even when we were talking, it
was like the manager's gigi, and
Ina-chan and Gai-chan
did a prank on her.  That's like a prank. He was
pretending to be that manager. Yeah, that
's right. It was so funny.
Then he
said he was a fan of ``Yeah.''
Please sign it. Was it a mobile phone? It was an
iPad. It was a case.  Hey
Mr. Anochi, if you'd like, I can give you a
thumbs up.I asked him if it was ok, and he said yes,
but I couldn't believe he didn't know that much.So I
asked him to please write my name as well.  Well, I was
surprised when I said that I was going to go to Inanis,
and it was a huge success.Yes, it was a huge success.It's good, but
it happens all the time.When I came to the studio, I met that senior and I had never met before.  Yeah, when I
first meet you, I think you're a staff member, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, when I come here, I just say thank you for your hard work, but when I meet A-senpai for the first time, I think I'm a staff member, and I'm like,
oh, thank you for your hard work.
As I was walking, I went to
say hello and realized that it was Ahhua-senpai, which was a little
embarrassing. Na-chan didn't realize that,
but she
thought that someone was a staff member.  My name is Pria,
and I thought the senior was that staff member, but I
don't think so.Yes, yes, that
's a problem of communication.But some
people wear hats, so they wear
hats and masks, and yes,
yes, it's difficult.
It's right, Kari-chan, Kari-chan, yeah, it's
embarrassing, it's embarrassing,
it's a recent story, but we're going
to have a live show soon, we're going to have a live show, yeah, yeah, we're going to have a live show, yeah, yeah, we're going to have a live show, and yeah, we're going to have some
English speakers,
and there's going to be some guests, JP.  I
'm going to have a member's guest, uh,
and I think there's someone who's
currently on Hololive, and there's someone who's
recommended by Holo, and I don't
really know if that person can speak English,
but I don't know if that person
can speak English.  I was told that I don't have much confidence,
but I gathered up some courage and
decided to ask someone who is cute.If you
have any questions or English questions, please
let me know and DM me.  I
'm sure there are people who speak English better than I do in Japanese, but you
can tell that I want to help somehow. I'm going to
send you a DM and start going around again. That's cute.
Yeah, I got a reply. I got a reply. I came. Please help
me.  That's good, that
might be a recommendation, maybe it's a good idea, maybe it's
embarrassing, embarrassing, embarrassing, embarrassing recent stories,
yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, yesterday's
stories, just yesterday, and I really collaborated with Mizu-senpai on a lot of things,
but that's kind of amazing.  I don't want to because he's someone I look up to,
but I understand that
when I met CC-senpai at the studio, my face turned really red.
Well, I get nervous every time, too. I'm kind of
nervous, so I wonder what people think of me.
That's how kind you are, too.  I helped you, I
helped you in America, please help me a little bit in America. I
still have to study Japanese,
but I'm good at it. It
's too good. By the way, is there
anything you'd like to do with Mr. Mizuo? There's more.
Kakari-chan is the one who
wants to take me out to a restaurant.
I'm the one who's going to take her on a cool date or something.  That's so nice, it makes me feel so warm. I
'm praying that all of your dreams will come true. Thank you very much. Yes, the
light is coming out. My heart is pounding. That's
all there is to that wonderful, wonderful place.  Now that I've heard the story, it's
almost time to say goodbye.
Everyone, it's early. We've been talking about this for
a while. I'd like to ask you what you like about it.  Well, I have other projects that I want to do
, so I really
want to listen to ASMR,
so I'm wondering if I can do it.I
wonder if I can do calliope, so after this, I'm thinking of doing it through membership distribution.
Yes, I thought I'd do it in both English and Japanese. Yeah, I
think
this is my second or third time participating in ASR in my life.
Unless I have experience in ASR, I haven't done much.
Haneka-chan is
doing quite a lot of things, but the only thing that makes her hurt
is the one that
doesn't hurt anymore. I'd like her to do something that hasn't hurt her lately. Well then, I'll
see you later on the membership-only broadcast,
but that's the last thing.
Nie I heard that Calliup and Chiara have some news
for you.Okay, then Calliope, please.Hey, Mina,
Calliope recently released a new album.Yes,
it's called Phantomime.Yes, it
's Phantomime.Ah, it looks amazing.Yes,
this one.  We worked really hard on the album,
and there are a lot of wonderful collaborations,
so please give it a listen.Just
yesterday, it
reached number 4 on the iTunes chart.In
total, the album is currently at number 7 or so.
Everyone who wants to be 4 again, please.
Chan's favorite
44. I like Shinigami, so God's 4. Yeah, that's
for sure. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Everyone, please listen to it on some streaming
platform, uh,
Spotify, iTunes,
etc.  Well, I want you to buy the CD too.
Please buy it from Tower Records or other stores. There are various
scoring goods, so yes,
yes, you can get a lot of goodies. The goods are nice, everyone is nice. Everyone, yes, yes, it's pretty good. The songs are
also a mess.  I've been listening to it today. It's
full of really cool songs, so please
listen to it. I'm really happy for you. Please,
thank you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Next, Mr. Kia, I'd
like to hear from you.  This is also a
message from Nekari-chan and Hi-chan, who are currently with us,
but that's why August
2425 Eko This week, the
entire 2nd episode of Wae Love English
Local Live Breaking Daishi will be held.  It's cool.
It's cool, but it's cool. It's so bad. It's so cool.
This week is amazing. It's
amazing. Everyone's got a visual right now,
but it's really cool, and the number of
guests has increased. Since the last live show, there have been more guests.  There
are no local tickets available anymore, but there
is a Moe Online Ticket, which is on sale right now.
There is a Japanese version and an English version, so everyone,
please support us at Flori Wings. Thank you
very much for this weekend. I'm so excited.
Everyone, it's not bad, it's not bad, it's okay.
But we're all doing our best, so we're doing our
best, and we're
really looking forward to it.It's going to be held at the King Theater.Thank you very much.  I'm
going to love Holo even more Hollow Live
Production's official app
will be celebrating its 1st anniversary next week on August 29th.It's the 1st anniversary of its official release.Here we go,
congratulations!  I
would like to ask everyone to take this opportunity to
download it.
Thank you very much for your support.
Yes, please download it. Yes, everyone. I would like to ask you to
download it once again. And as I
mentioned earlier, there is
also a Holoplus Global version.  The
official release will be coming soon, so check out the announcements here on Official
Please apply. I'll be
waiting. Wait.
Yes. So,
thank you very much for coming to visit us today.
Thank you very much. It was a lot of fun. Thank you very much.
No, I'm happy.
So, after this, I'm going to become an official
member.  Limited to the Ship Deluxe Plan, I'm
going to try it out for ASMR who couldn't do it this time with the unlisted deck.
[Music]
Well, that's it for Holo's holiday. That's all
for today. Well then, everyone.  Otsuflo
Plus
Plus Bye
Bye See You Bye
[Music]
Bye
OGJA