[Music]
for
hello okay uh one
sec I don't hear anything oh there we go
hello okay um okay
[Music]
yay oh
oops hello okay so I will we we we
playing League they we have a full team
yay so there will be four other people
um so please help me with the audio in
the
beginning uh and other than that I will
click and then I will win and uh
that's that's that's it that's going to
be it's going to be the game no problem
okay okay okay um okay let's move
over um where did I set this up I set
this up but I didn't think it I kind of
thought it through is this
hidden me yeah
[Music]
okay I might have to make this
smaller let me like
this I I thought it would be nice to
have the names of everyone's character
otherwise it gets really confusing like
when I was watching The V I was like
who's who so maybe this will help we'll
see okay yeah K is also here today yay
okay okay I'm going to go back into
voice
[Music]
U Elizabeth and I don't know who
Elizabeth and K are going to play
yet I just I just kept their names oh
wait where's the leak
[Music]
thingy leak
launcher K is playing k
oh okay okay okay so please help me with
audio in the
beginning yummy
ma
okay
um okay I'm going to go back into voice
hello wonderful hello okay I'm back okay
hello
hello what are we
what what
what WEA wants to steal my cats even
though she has her own now messed up no
Raa no messed up messed up
indeed get yourself more then don't take
mine away steal them steal them you
should have gotten two minimum anyway
narissa I could have told you that
no why no you just want to steal are you
kto Maniac are we ready to play some
League of L can we do can we do an can
we do an audio check can we do g go yeah
everyone introduce yourselves
oh
okay amazing silence G mood League of
Legends Cecilia
spin League of
Legends don't think that's the game name
Elizabeth oh League of
[Music]
Legends Nissa Raven crop spin a wind
leak of
less it sound like ner nerv if you're
nervous I am she
is uh Top Lane uh and and Heimerdinger
checking my ass out w why Legends why is
he what is he doing ready to find a
match thumnail he's taking my ass out I
am
too CeCe you ready are we matching am I
ready um yeah I think so
yes
found loud it is very
loud but I have to switch the window
anyway is do I choose a character here
yeah I can just
byy exciting
yeah yeah whoever you want we
okay I'm going to start
off with a clever Fox is never caught
rat rats we are the
rats rats stop fighting rat rat we are
the rats rats rats rats
rats ooh wiard choosing seraphine I see
I see I'm your support
wait I'm I didn't pick
yet uh you got to I picked you click
lock in I think you have already locked
didn't have any oh it
says
uh uh select your runes oh
God I have no runes okay there we go got
the
ruins okay okay I
think I think it's good now okay okay
sorry guys I'm I'm struggling with uh
audio balancing my biggest
weakness it's okay okay window
switch oh my God I love your re
skin wow hot KDA k
k down down down down down down
down down down down should I buy this
world atlas I know this place good luck
welcome I buy did your girls not buy
items have
it buy the little red potion K I think
forget what what sorry what buy the
little red potion I think that's a nice
starting item okay why is the camera so
weird oh you the camera the click the
camera at the bottom and it will follow
you oh thank you you hit why and it'll
follow and unfollow you you'll have to
answer a lot of beginner questions it's
okay you want W Senpai um thank
you so we end the shop W Senpai it does
give you suggestions so I mean I buy the
little starter that it pops up with at
the at the start when you open it
initially okay I did that too Gigi and
narissa are the peeps like that know it
inside out yeah careful with the
tower and say kill
everyone and and and and kill the
minions and okay and don't K me don't
die yeah die a distanced attack more a
ranged attack I like the way you said
minions
to oh wait let me change my thing I'm
going to make fet of them H yes yes oh
God goodbye thank you
goodbye goodbye and I click and then oh
and click and click click the things and
press the buttons yes yes yes I'm here
for you m lean I have fed the Enemy No
it's okay do that they're Bots oh oh
what what would be oh what would B
do B is to go back to base to go home
like
teleportation yeah yeah
oh what it has a channel time and people
can cancel it by hitting
you
oh
uh-oh am i al
the oh than keeps making me think I've
accidentally got dmca music on or
something no I'm so sorry like I'm
always like did I leave a tab on no just
you're listening to leak of
Legends the thing that I struggle the
most with in the game is like the camera
to just like have to hold it down and I
keep
forgetting I die again hold it down how
like
space
oh you don't have to if you don't want
to you can press y to keep it fixed oh
really oh
[Music]
yeah let's go let's go oh a Shar oopsie
uhoh I'm dead it's
okay press y to
lock going home she was waiting for me
even even
now here I'll
come thank you are You The Bard yes I
pressed the wrong button please avenge
me that snake lady has been bullying
me thank you that was
good why did the they have a
jungler is that a jungle character okay
they have a
jungler why you leave her I thought she
was doing
fine I guess not
you must live
rat I am rat let hey turn get
her okay okay are you ready getting
better CeCe what CeCe right here this
guy right here yes yes she is so
confused she has no I thank you she's
dead we did it buff
transfer buff
What in in short words because I can't
look at the text what does w do in this
case it's a passive it breaks armor okay
wait now I can
read on the
same I don't have to do anything it's
just always
working what's always working my passive
yes
nice we got her yeah yeah yeah don't
reset rats we are the rats we are the
rats we are the rat world of
Atlas the legacy of the
V yeah I think the way Vice works is you
hit something three times and then they
take more damage and then her que goes
through terrain and walls charge it up
and she has one more skill forgot what
it does but
something it like does AOE
stuffs Sor it's a bit much though I
don't understand there's a snake no
that's
okay yeah why have a snake here snake
void grubs grub
grub I don't understand does that mean
we got to eat the grubs
she shot my
[Music]
booty too late
okay did I not sell it did I sell the
wrong
thing but you s I want
to an item that I didn't need I guess
but uh whatever an enemy has been I sold
and I bought it okay
yay you
skin what is she up
to what are you doing see I can take
grubs leave leub where's your mid laner
what how where are
they yeah where are they hold C to fly
longer the mid Lina is here it's a woman
Fortune oh I get it their jungle bot
takes void
grubs
ew is this an objective I just can't
believe the b in this game take
objectives they're
annoying
uhoh n
so how what how many times have you
girls played this as a collab already
three time three yeah hey you're in
bottom Lane mother trucker I remember
you I'm
dead don't die help don't
die help me Liz kill them Liz no no wait
come back Liz
no don't do it oh the dear is here the
deare is here oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
dear oh dear W oh dear
thank you she's being really
mean screw
that you got this that is a deer wait
that's the one you sent me is is that
the one you sent me the skin lit dear
that's a
dear it's okay I'm almost back blz I'll
support you she's Charmed she's charm
kill her I'm asleep run from Tower okay
what get away from
me what oops I ran me oh oh I'm Char too
where are my minions minions they
they're dead that's messed
up don't worry I'm here to take your
farm why would you do that to me I'll
leave I'm coming back narissa spots are
kind of crazy all the things are doing
what is this don't be afraid Don't Be
Afraid go my little minions go minions
kute kill
kill oh
no Cecilia is Brew
now how do I buy
that no CL probably oh there's another
one I didn't even see that one
uhoh watch out if you see that white
thing around her it means the next spell
she hits you with you'll get stunned oh
okay I see I see level
eight go blood flame go blood
flame uh-oh uhoh a queen get
dragon thank you for indulging me walked
into a tower what an idiot
be back true what an
idiot an eny is unstable uhoh is there
like did you set these Bots to a high
difficulty or so they're
normal could they be easier
yes I a bad
matchup no you're
okay wait what is difficulty is it
normal intermediate normal why is the
horse on our side horse kill the horse
oh she's running away never mind what is
that uh she's like um oh the the dragon
I still don't know I'm going to die did
just explained it like a million times
to me I still don't understand explain
what what the what the
um Drake
Drake um gives us gold gold and gives us
some passive stuff so it's a good
objective to get wow it's an enemy we
have to kill or yeah it's a jungle mob
don't worry God usually in like actual
games people fight around this and then
you have to be aware but we're just
playing Bots doesn't matter too much I I
got
this you sound like you totally got this
I got this got I'm going to go top a
little
bit you going to be good down
here I cannot tell the one thing I can't
tell in these games it's like if you're
winning on up evil jungler just took my
my my
Raptors your Raptors yeah I can't
believe that bot's counter jungle you I
just just can't believe it it's weird
it's weird right yeah it's so strange
that that b will counter jungle
you so should I CH choose someone that's
far away chat
probably yes run after me you
fool an
enemy Never Let You Suffer get out of
there nice FL thank you oh get all these
before I kill that ma'am get out of here
what the freak are you doing in here I'm
here no go in the forest careful careful
careful get a B I'm
running oh that completely missed that
was nowhere near her where did she go
wait where is she KAIT yeah maybe I want
r o Caitlyn is the blue one I think
goodbye
is the one is not little m-m I said
blue yeah blue blue blue blue did you
watch Arcane did everybody watch Arcane
I haven't seen the second season yet but
I've seen the first one
okay like it I watched both finish my
Twitter feed has seen all the second
season of I led it although the second
season was bit rushed yeah a lot of
things that they were she Charmed she's
Charmed getting down
mhm nice thank you copia is going back
so you should be able to get the tower
pretty much undisturbed mhm another one
charm she's Charmed she's
Charmed oops you did not run where I
wanted her to run ow ow good
job oh I'm turning I'm
[Music]
turning she stunned she stunned owie
an enemy has
been andk gosh damn you're having a
party there are you a
DJ yeah it's a it's a it's a party
remind me of
home oh the snake is back that's
okay oh careful back up a little
bit I wanted to use my old te yeah
did I use it oh my God leave me
alone all right
let's
mother stay here if they stay we can
kill them okay
okay okay let's just kill
her watch out she knows how to
combo oops that's that's a
minion oh you here
care she chared she's chared she's
chared careful careful I'm dead wow kill
her kill her kill her G yay
okay I'll kill her for you thank you
good job see have gone in there I didn't
see the second
enemy how do I do that she's JL again
and he's G back to Jungle ah no she's
not okay I've got her back good luck
Kiara
I get
this I may have
Nils oh
no Ari has nine tails huh is she related
to Naruto back off buddy no she's a GMI
ho well she is a ninetail block so yeah
the question oh gho like the Korean
Legend yeah oh
no regrets just
say no
no thank
you unstable yay come back come back
come back
[Laughter]
nice you're getting toxic you're
learning the ways of League of Legends
yes it's true I'm I shouldn't I
shouldn't I mean no you got this enemy
bot you you go come here
J wonderful
bot let's go out of
range I don't I'm going to try a
different
character I can't get that all right
team
destroyed remember which
boots there's so many boots which boots
should I buy
I'm sorry I didn't have my heal up you
can get
the I can't afford I need the basic
boots you are Gucci I was being py oh
there's three why are there three people
in mid that's not this is not fair guys
this is not
fair obsessed with you yeah not fair
they just you just are very intimidating
s oops your
St on my way oh on my way M never mind
everyone left you yeah I she one
died
please one
Legend leg of
leg leg
okay I really like um like I don't know
if this is like the character always if
it's just a skin but when she teleports
home she like creates a oh that's the
skin yeah it's really
coola she creates invisible stairs and
then she sits on the
throne of
Le Throne of legal lean legs of
thr my favorite top Champion was always
Riven Riven cuz she's voiced by
Christina V yeah
can't fight her suffering sounds
great press the wrong button dang it oh
what's that what's that what the
infernal blazes what does it mean what
was that they took the dragon so now
there's things that'll pop up on this
the map oh
okay nice nice job yay
God I'm zoning
out like mentally or in the game yeah
in my brain I wish I could zone out but
I can't even Zone
in just chilling playing league with the
ladies we
vibing you got this you got this you got
this yay
ah yes yes iome C look at you oh you're
so good it's thanks to
narissa she to go it's all because of
narissa I'm going to die no you're
not I I'm I'm going back got this no
you're not you got this you're so
strong oh my god let's push the tower
push the tower yeah yeah get the tower
I guess I'll push a tower too she's
behind
you your team has destroyed a turret
don't worry oh oh oh you're you're going
crazy you're going crazy you're crazy
you're crazy you're crazy you're crazy
and and because of that yes in a good
way and we have a friend and I'm going
to bring you a friend and then don't
worry where am I going why am I running
this way cute friend he's also crazy I
died oh no oh no oh no well I sacrificed
myself for a
good yeah yeah yeah I'm going to go
crazy again my first successful die why
am I
turning i di
wow without my diving license can't
believe it hey you're doing really good
no I'm not don't liea you're you got
this you got this
sure first time is V this is great I
sucked this high when I first played by
C
oh F looks
difficult let's go okay I one shot these
now
no is really hard yeah she's really
really difficult I thought she was going
to people were saying she's like one of
the easier ones she no they lied to in
Jungle she's a pretty simple jungler
[Music]
yeah a tower is
destroyed unfortunate o
speed
wow I'm here no I shouldn't I miss I
shouldn't it's okay like this Forest I
am wild let's scatter her let's scatter
her you got this yeah get the kill get
the kill nice you're so good look at
you sure you did it you did it it's two
get her two get her
two oh an oh you got you got this you
got this you're crazy you're crazy she's
sleeping you oh oh no oh no
I was trying to figure how to make my
how to make my L work but I think I have
to stand still to use it or what I don't
think you have to stand still I was
pressing it the whole time you have to
press and then click
again on the person you want to use it
on or if you press um in the settings of
in um there's like these little arrows
that you can if you just hover over a
person you can use them instead of
having to click on them
I
okay hey if if someone can help me just
get the inhibitor
bottom Mega creeps and we can abandon
Lane Hi Li thank you
hello thank you thank you um everything
seems to be right click in this game is
it left
click it's it's left click I don't
actually I don't remember I just do it
by muscle memory I have no
clue
yay woo uhoh huh
okay uhoh try again
[Music]
noedy wo greedy too greedy to every time
I'm too greedy okay too greedy
but it worked this
time an enemy has
oh it's fine no it's just
me how dare you kill
narissa how dare you take her away from
us nice Liz how do I
killing here uh you're dead
okay what are we doing
team um what do I buy when I'm out of
stuff from the list you just push me
what do you mean whatever whatever makes
you happy I always like to go for a
rabadon death cat a a hat rabadon's Des
C okay I clicked it I forg if your
ability power
yeah I
forgot recommend there's a recommend
list okay don't kill so you ran out of
recommended things to buy um no I ran
out of the things on that one list that
you sent me like the three main items
you lived by this and then I did rubiton
hi
amazing
hello nice strong I thought the was in
she's charm she's charm nice okay get
her too get her too get her get her get
her forever she's so
fast don't worry we're here get her get
her nice nice nice
nice get the
tower
okay
oo get the
inhib what is that called what did you
call it inhib in it's an inhibitor
okayest
inh now what my please now what keep
going here oh behind behind two behind
us ah oh I'm
dead no you're not thank you Liz no kill
her kill her
[Applause]
nice
soara if you attack
uh if you attack them
over when when there's not Creeps in
front of you or if you attack someone
over a
tower like the the tower will start
attacking you so if you're in the
tower's vicinity don't attack one of the
enemy
Champions
okay and if there's no creep don't don't
go up by the
tower no creep yeah what's the
creep is the AIO off the game by the way
yeah can you hear the game is it like
too isn't I don't want it to be too loud
I rather want it to be too quiet and too
loud I'm muted yes yes all sounds good
okay live live live it's okay to end
fine it's
fine okay I'll end the game don't
worry okay
okay yay easy easiest game of our
Liv so easy so easy easiest game
easy winners we're winning we are
winners win we
winners
dinner y first win of the day amazing
our first win of our lives so
easy so
easy you guys want to do intro Bots or
real people oh actually Ki should pick
what pick what do you want to play
against real people or do you want to do
bots all the real people going to be
easier than the
Bots depends also there might be a
chance that if we go with real people we
still get bots like inter I'll be right
back you guys talk about what you want
and then tell me when I get back okay
can we do easy
Bots I mean I I I don't mind either way
I like playing against real people
I'm not sure if we can play against real
people yet since K is on a new account
we might have to do more games right
right before but we can see if we can go
into Quick
Play
yeah maybe we should do bots first and
then uh well right now we did Med medium
Bots and we won uh so either we should
do maybe we should do hard Bots to see
if we can keep up against hard bot
before real people M mhm
mhm maybe maybe can I do Caitlyn and Top
Lane you can play yeah whoever
wherever yeah okay be whoever you want
to be just have just yeah just mix it up
okay I want to try her Kaitlyn Kaitlyn
yeah that's the blue one PE Pew
PE Caitlyn and VI perfect match
all these discounted skins
purchase purchase I'm
back welcome back thank you okay what
did we decide on what are we up
to and Bots okay Bots and do you just
want to do beginner Bots I'm not sure
what was the
conclusion we'll
do oh I feel like we can handle the same
level of bots you did really well yeah
yeah we did beginner Bots we were
playing beginner Bots oh we W playing
beginner Bots Oh I thought we were
continue okay
okay okay down with anything an
intermediate I'll do
whatever same okay continue are we all
ready mhm we're waiting on kiar okay I'm
pressing button okay you're already
perfect at the game accept I don't like
how fast accept Caitlyn let's go lock
let's lock in our
relationship yeah let's I try she's like
a narissa but with a gun what if we all
made a star Guardian team who is that do
I need to buy a skin for that I have so
much star Guardian Star Guardian Ari
how much cost are usually like I think
star Guardian skin would be around
$15 15 or 15 yes
15 I get to use
my SK if I want to invest into this game
by giving it money I will decide after
the stream that is
fair yay when I do want to look pretty
in the star Guardian skin why are you
Sona wait let's talk real quick what's
What's Happening Here for
funes okay we'll win yeah is a
problem for both supports is the only
issue just one of you you can build
AP go carry yeah you can be anyone
anything okay
so anything you
want okay what do we have
are we already running yeah can we do
the thing G where we like kill them in
the in the in the bushes yeah we can
we'll have to go over here I'm so
fast I'm F to sponge boy yeah I'm
speeding okay okay let's
go I like your hat thank you I like your
oh no not the snake again why do we get
same there's everyone here they killed
my War messed up we can try killing them
I'm they rata is just she
running kill her kill her is it a her I
can't tell yes yes get she almost dead
get her get her get her get her first
yeah first
Blood get him oh I'm dead I'm dead no no
no help me help me you're not you're not
I stuned him thank you unap too okay
yay what is this strong tower this I'll
take this this is mine
now the minions are here you guys can go
to your
lane
goodbye you're welcome
thank it was all it was all us yes
yes oh we kill them tried being through
that wall
Sona can't believe you're here with
us
yay
eia I running but I am low in health
where are you running to what do you
mean you
better you sound like you're directly
out of the game like I wasn't sure if
that was a game Voice or
not she should voice all the characters
game Let's mute the game and just have
her do it yeah can you make the noises
Bard makes can you make my orb noises
sounds like he sounds like
Windchimes her scream when she dies
[Music]
czy
anyway
beautiful pushing
[Laughter]
the Hun always missed the last hit on
these stupid
minions no you're so
good not bad though I don't know how to
ad0 carry seraphine you don't have to
ad0 carry just AP carry I don't know
what that means oh just just build like
normal AP items I don't know how to AP
carry
your
abdons r i just my rabadons yeah you
rabons where she
going she's a coward she's a coward kill
her she's Charmed she's Charmed going
back on be to heal as normal what she
doing I'm out of
Mana if we can just keep getting them to
go back even it's not too bad because
then they they don't get to level I need
healing thank you everything no Mana
don't you think no Mana no Mana of Mana
can't do anything she's so low but I
can't do it I'm out of Mana no Mana no
Mana guess I shouldn't have used all the
Mana on the minions
minions no Mana no man
has
serious oh you can hide in the bush too
like in the in the Pokmon game too like
you disaar when you're in the
bushes what's happening here you can
become stealth going on an assassin of
the Night Dragon I won what it
dragon dragon wear Dragon
wear Where Are You Dragon you know
kill what happening here
how do I are we still on beginner Bots
[\h__\h] yeah they're very
strange she keeps like zooming behind me
it's so
frustrating what if I what if I what if
I what if you want what if you want what
have you want nothing nothing nothing
nothing
nothing nothing what do you what what do
you want though what do you what
oh rest in
peace ma'am stop it ma'am stop it
ma'am let us kill
you Yay good
kill so if I don't get the kill if the
tower gets the kill I don't get any like
X anything from work on
leveling oh you're only level never mind
I'll stay you back there's Beauty in
even the smallest moments out of
here
oh how does she know I'm
here I don't
know secret
Ward yeah I'm just trying to hit this
how does she have the knowledge that I'm
here these Bots are
cheating of course they are are always
cheating
who there stream snip I heal I heal I
heal I heal y
y thanks G how could they stream snipe
that's so rude I know it's so cringe of
these boss to
stream oh have minions
now minions minions minions minions
minions me a I hear then I go Backes
thank you Liz thank
you thank you for the assist
me n should I go back for it
really L I'm I mean I'm fighting your
mirror
match oh mirror match It's s
double dou whoops do
that nah
nice one thanks you're the best you're
the best
music
[Music]
oo what why are they getting
these how do the Bots know to get this
it's
over no it's not over it's over I died I
died said it's over there's somebody in
the bushes BF sword what sorry BF big
[\h__\h]
sword know buy is is that what I got oh
I did get the BF sword nothing wrong
with the BF sword
mhm best friend sword no she's running
away I hate her oh oh that's not what I
wanted to flash
oops
big big large wall wall big very large
wall I don't like
a no she keeps like she keeps like I'm
about to charm her and then she
teleports behind me and she goes nothing
personel kid and I don't appreciate
that person
now yay I got
her
yay Oh My Stream died my bad how does
that happen happen because I'm I'm
connected to League internet so
why your stream died yeah oh my God
that's really weird it's okay your
stream died yeah yeah rest in peace OBS
it's okay it's back it's back but
yay welcome back from the day ow ow ow
ow I'm my best life oh sorry well you
missed me killing 20 enemies so yeah all
of them all of
them killed every single one of
them believe don't kill me this is
mine an enemy has been
slain oopsie I forgot if you hit
someone it was okay ah
oh I'm going he confused he lacks
critical knowledge
what out played
her I went into Caitlyn I sent Caitlyn
back into her closet she was
invisible you what what you heard her
yeah you heard
me let me kill you let me I don't think
we should do that no I got her oh God
oh let's go
minions oh my let's eat more Snake
flesh snake for dinner snake
sausage snake sausage I already ate six
sausages today
six yeah pretty
impressive
impressive impressive display impressive
display of uhoh very unlike of Caitlyn o
I should have done
the uhoh what's
this woven into everything I got a
back
[Music]
okay can we have a Like A League of
Legends voice pack from Elizabeth yeah
we made
one oh oh go she's going into the bushes
you're not going to escape me ha imagine
running away from a Healer how close do
I have to be before
ignite why how close do I have to be
before ignite I feel like often I press
it nothing happens come here come here
come here if you hover over it you can
see the range oh another one
FR and another one you'll be fine you're
Sona another one okay okay okay I need
to
go she leaves oh no we
running maybe not
one maybe
not so many unactivated traps
sad what do I do okay don't
die on a hover board okay
okay oh God how low are you very my God
I am at 26
HP I died to
seraphine oh no he aled
me how could she do this you're the
seraphine though I know how could she I
have
a yes get hit by the turret yes
fool
yay these Bots are awesome I like yeah I
like when they run into the turrets
because it's like I would do that but
mother you would do that yeah
but I haven't today but oh yeah I
remember last week I kept getting
confused which one which which which
Towers were ours so I kept running into
the
wrong I think I think Le Riot gave me
free RP so I did buy more seraphine
skins nice I want stuff too we we can
ask there's two of them why are they two
what am I going to do okay one ran away
no she's back boots oh next
time Riot give me free stuff or I'm I'm
going to Riot I'm going to
Riot yeah before we start
rioting just kidding just kidding I'm
sorry Riot I have so much respect for
you sorry Mr Riot never R what get away
from from
me good trade it's good if I if I die
and I say good trade is that like does
it nullify any negativity I've created
yeah good trade good trade good trade it
creates space for my skill level trade
space for your skill good trade good
trade good trade your team has destroyed
a tret nice go team finally nice the
turret is
gone we can now move on with our lives
for the next turet on with our lives and
then the next
turret Target the
Aurelia level 10 is no come why would
you come here Aurelia I'm trying to get
this Rift
heral
yes my Rift I work so hard
on an enemy has been SL I'm a little bit
too happy when I uh killed a champion as
you should that's good that's your life
blood uh oh come over
here walk over here I'm so
low your
little watch brain wants me so bad I'm
so
low walk over here just walk over here
delicious delicious
yeah come get
me come on over here D nothing happen so
annoying I don't get it give me a look
closer do you also have it quick
casted yes
am walk up here I okay I'll CH her I'll
CH her I'll CH her I'll CH her o charm
she's charm awesome yay that'll show her
for trying to take my Rift Herald Rift
I toal life wonder I can get it
now it's okay it's okay my 3,000 gold
it's
okay
uh-oh a fool this one got to get a
needlessly large
Rod needlessly large
yeah needless it's so needlessly large
huh that's why I need it
okay necessary necessarily large
Rod yeah uh-oh uhoh I've been slowed
okay I'm fine live live I live I lived
totally ignored me no
respect yes come here sarap yes yes you
want me you want to eat oh she ran away
yes walk over here you want us yes come
on
over don't you
think
damn okay Retreat tactical Retreat
tactical
retreating leaving my minions
behind for a better time and I'm going
to buy boots boot boots
boots
boots maybe can buy a potion too your
team has destroyed a
turret here we
go killing killing ooh nice n get her
let get her get her get her get you get
her you get her I'm letting you get her
yay crazy you guys are really
pushing right into their base
shall we go and help mid your team desty
an inhibitor inhibitor I thought you
said that an inhibitor oh that's okay an
inhibitor an inhibitor oh an inhibitor
destroy an inhibitor uhoh Goodbye Oh
don't die dude stop following me dude
dude attack them attack them
oh yeah I keep forgetting about my old
oop see oh hi hi hi I'm here to
[Music]
help
hi hi everyone oh I'm standing in it how
am I standing in it help help thank
you o green or what's everyone screaming
about okay okay okay okay she's charm
she's charm kill her czy
y yay
yay yipp
yipp you're on a ramp page Ki you're
crazy
rage crazy oh that's
fine I'll avenge
you I won't let them get away with
this uhoh uhoh uhoh
uhoh oh why did you run over here
yes yes you're
crazy uhoh oops I didn't mean to do that
run away run away run
away no I'll avenge you too I meant to
go here but I clicked I clicked on oh my
God let me out let me out let me
outon am I clicking I think the hardest
part is like to moving with the mouse
because like I you you you click because
you're trying to get away but your mouse
is completely in a different
you it was and then you always walk into
wrong
areas
hi
hi hi thanks for the
heal GG you got
this I think I do like I scrolled over
to you and I just see like four
enemies walk up why this if I had more
Mana I could have done it you can do it
you got this you can still do it nice
nice nice say Sol one
more wind
s y we're having like positive music is
it because we're winning
star what music I hear positive music it
goes like maybe it's the star
Guardian it's so
pretty
Godlike God F walk back over
here yeah don't be a coward Bots come on
yeah come on walk over here we're just
beginners just beginner Bots
owie
healing get them now we're winning
yay we did it
[Music]
easiest game easiest game of our lives
so easy
no I think we're ready for intermediate
Bots what I need to get water okay me
too actually I'll get water sorry I'm
like since I'm sick I'm drinking so much
water that's good drink more yes drink
more water
girl I am so thirsty do I still not have
this skin oh I just need the icon
I was about to kill myself okay don't do
it do it okay okay I'll be be um yeah
I'll be or be mhm you guys are still on
my
stream water KDA
KDA KD you know how it is around again
was it me K A KD a what does it
mean it look within you
doggy
animals oh so they saying it's kill
theist yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wow you
got that way faster than me and Cecilia
did really really I don't know if that's
really fast yeah yeah yeah I didn't
notice until Cecilia brought up she was
like oh killed death like a Cy and I was
like why is this why is this yellow are
they telling me I did bad for what my
character could do
potentially or is it just because that's
me what's yellow my damage dealt to
Champions is it just because it's me
okay okay yeah yeah yeah I thought they
were dissing
me can you get skins with the blue stuff
or not um there's the they sometimes
bring back like a blue Essence store but
it's usually a lot of blue Essence it
was here
recently don't know where it went I
don't know if it's still here what are
these mystery boxes oh that's here oh
the mystery which
one what when what you need I want can
you explain them to me like these loot
Loot Crate Box thingies are they one in
your inventory I'm back inventory is it
in your inventory in my inventory Sor
sometimes you get these like chest that
you can use and they give you character
shards or skin shards or um Wards and
stuff but you have to unlock it
with this other currency that you get
from breaking down what you get from
boxes stupid okay okay I'll
unmute I maybe
see so none of these loot boxes have
skins the loot boxes have skins
if you buy a loot box you can get a
skin there will go too right no where
there's these
blue band City mystery mini icon icons
welcome
back welcome back how are we doing
amers good
good yeah good are you ready do we want
to up the bot
difficulty sure by one maybe there's
only one more to go let's go nice okay
search we got this we got it let's
search let's search for Bots that want
to play against us yeah I hope we find
some I am seeking Bots a clever Fox is
never change the
world let change okay KDA skin time yay
woo for me flexing so
hard bro I had to play to unlock this
skin I'm not flexing
still a flex no I had to play so much to
unlock her we'll get you a pretty skin
too K don't worry next
[Music]
time I don't know who this guy is but he
reminds me of like someone from Myspace
so I'm going to try he look beautifully
sad yeah yeah he looks like a nice SP
guy oh sorry I don't
know not sure pool party Kaitlyn p p
pool party party pool party cool party I
cool
party yay know snake this time oh
there's a
cow cute oh there's like a little
guy and and a fairy fairy cart Lux oh
it's Lux oh no I hate Lu oh it's
over oh I feel like I heard some bad
things about Lux but did not understand
the context she what do you mean evil
she evil
do um her bot AI is really good because
she's really good at aiming skill shots
because robot yeah can we kill them all
in the bushes again yeah over here thank
you wind oh this guy has a big
paintbrush let's go seconds until minion
SP okay I'll wait
n you look so cute thank you we match
now yay Spar yeah I'm ready ready to
press the one button I
have I'm just going to look up this
guy I'm in the ow you got this you got
this why did he
flash don't
flash oh you thank you for the heal yeah
you're welcome thank you everyone
goodbye goodbye not here I'll just go
back to
my oh no look Lux is in the middle it's
over she's in the middle she's always
there she's a lck since she's in the
middle I hate
her she's Lo it's okay I'm not the same
person I was two weeks ago I will not
lose to this spot this time yeah you are
not the same person what did I do he's
like the guy
from uh from Naruto which
one
sa his name
s who
drew right he he drew stuff yes
Artist Artist yeah how does he see me in
the
bushes if you hit him and then the
minions aggro you they'll reveal your
location in the bush oh
yeah so if you're agroed by something
it'll show
yourself no
no he's so
cool
yeah
yeah cannot outrun your crimes as what I
want to say to Walter White
don't are you planning on watching sa
after yeah
totally so awesome so excited good
halfway through the last season of
Breaking Bad you're so CL I think I'm
going to finish it tonight maybe
o also I saw I saw I was in a museum
yesterday and
um I saw a painting that really looked
like Walter White I took a picture of it
I need to show it to you guys later
anybody who understands what he looks
like in the first place it looks so much
like like him bald and and glasses and
everything and depressed fa not really
depressed deed push me in push me in no
just like his face just says he's got
issues wow I agree he kicked me into the
the thing he's
rude
[Music]
wow I'm a cute Myspace boy that draw
come
on I never used my space yeah s even
though it was popular when I was smaller
uh-oh uhoh Fair my space was too for me
you run into our Tower no but I I should
have gone home like ages ago and I kept
thinking I should use my Mana before
going home and then I even CL erase that
memory oops wrong button
oh a pot of
tea a bottle of water a Bott of
water bottle of water bottle of water
bottle of water here I'm ready for you
oh really yeah I'm here I'm here charm
her charm she's Charmed she's Charmed
she's Charmed all right all right I'm on
her I'm on her I'm on top of her I'm on
top of her okay thanks J
I feel like when it's two versus one it
becomes a little bit unfair why why
shouldn't come here little cow what do
you do when you're not like what do you
do in the jungle ideally in the game
you're not you have like a better
understanding or like you you know where
the jungler is and you know when to not
overextend so she wouldn't have been in
that position in the first place if she
was watching a map she when I'm in the
middle should I you are close to the
middle should I tell
you when I'm about to engage I think
it's up to the jungler because it's like
um they usually evaluate the kill
potential if you if like if they went
mid would you guys be able to get a kill
mhm or if there's like other objectives
cuz even though you might engage they
like oh it's not worth it cuz I have to
go to this other place right now and it
would waste too much time here I wanted
to in a game though but since just a
black game I can just
commit I wonder what skins he
[Music]
has oh you're so Mana poor good thing
she's not level six
yet oh I'm dead no I got her don't worry
don't wor I'm going home I'm going home
go home go home go
home yes go
home oh zigs is missing any minute now
oh there we
go can you believe that airplan why is
he here in the night sky or like
shooting stars yeah I can't believe
it nice I'm in a back oh Liz you sound
Rob I he robot yeah you sound very
roboty right
now guys oh oh you oh intentional I'm
almost there I'm almost there oh I
do is it the pain okay charm charm charm
yeah yeah yeah yeah
awesome I'll fix it in a moment
okay am I W am I Wally can I do the W
thing that was really
good like like he you sounding really
good yeah you just sounded really
good is there no Mana
potions no in the shop no oh in the shop
I actually don't
know there's like a refillable potion
but
people don't usually get it or it
depends on what Champion you're
playing can't buy it oh why is it locked
they used be but removed yeah the
cookies give Mana
uhhuh I
love have you girls had some Christmas
evil I thought it was nice no not yet
have you girls been to some Christmas
markets yet no not yet I did in a voice
pack not yet yeah right it's so it's all
just a lie I did in a voice pack
together in the last 3 days I went to
like six Christmas markets
running Christmas markers she's a
competitive Christmas mark and it made
it even more obvious like I never
noticed how like all the shops are so
repetitive in the Christmas Market but
it's still nice but it's really nice
what's your favorite Christmas Market uh
snack this will decide everything
K get him get him
[Music]
okay
fair talking about German
Things o yummy
yummy those are like Candi almonds
they're like they're like um roasted
candied Alm caramelized roasted yeah
they're really good they B they sell
them at the Christmas markets I Leta eat
them and she was so fascinated she was
like oh my God this is the [\h__\h] yeah a
really good it's like just the right
amount of super sweet you know mhm and
crunchy and crunchy
yeah maybe I should go oh he pushed me
away thank goodness
o I'm going to heal up o yep go ahead uh
level 88 I'm strut
away oh he's
painting he's
painting he's a
painter he's a
painter M
don't attack me little Min do I still
sound like a robot you no you're F sound
noral oh it fixed itself cool you didn't
even have to do anything you sound so I
didn't even touch
it Elizabeth Rose blood flame oh wait
did my flash and my fire
switch oh that's why I keep flashing why
would they do why would the game do that
to me that's messed up why would they
yeah why would they do that I had it I
had it rebound and it it reset
itself oh my God Darius is not
interested in me anymore he realized I
am uh not interested in him
either good good go somewhere else there
is just stop
moving where' he go what oh he channeled
so fast oh I lost the eye that was the
your team has destroyed a turret
sympy uh-oh an ult oh my
God okay
there
damn my aim is so bad man come
back stay
here no F should be Flash Flash no no
it's spash it's
I'll remember that you know flash I
can't give up I can't give
up no for
[Laughter]
Flash everyone's crunchy
uhoh only on my side look
now oh I got I fix
it live with good now okay okay see if I
can get this guy with this this time f f
launches a
vision that sticks to an enemy Champion
for 3 seconds
oh
level top like a boss I've had this real
weird issue recently it's happened like
start a week AG where my audio just
becomes like really roboty but I can't
hear like it hears sounds normal in my
my ears audio jungle are you jungle you
came to the wrong
neighborhood are you
jungle you cow J come here come here cow
nice let's get this mid
turret this game is teaching me
restraint oh I'm
uh-oh wow he's so good he's scripting
this
scripting yeah kill him kill him kill
him kill him kill him kill him you so
fast you got die from the
ignite y I'm going home oh should I stay
with you I don't know n I'm afraid of
this L killing you
[Laughter]
oh I should have gone home GD should
should got home I never bought this oh
oops just
runs let's go Tower
two gone
home I'm here no Dar is oh oh let's get
the
rumble Rumble come
what but I have no no
no no no no please darious please have
let me go let me
go let me go little hi Hi H Binger
that's zigs Dragon
spawned he does look like hinger though
I thought the same when I was watching
the show I was like is this character
going to turn into digs or
what no no they they're their own people
oh
unstable y an enemy are they
related no they're just little just the
same they're just are they
yeah oh that's what I meant are they the
same species oh yeah yeah
yeah is crazy
cousin yes there's another guy down here
Rumble
world it's who is ready to
rumble
dominating wow you're Domin back
up get the to Let's finally get someone
with this let's go Oh yay
finally everybody's like Yay I'm like no
no
no out they are celebrating my death
they're cheating up there celebrating
your death yeah
yay wa dies let's go it's okay cuz she's
a phoenix she'll be back yeah it'll be
back
[Music]
BRB I just wanted to go shopping anyway
get her uh-oh I'm dead Oh no you're not
we'll get her we'll get her flash for
her oh I don't do enough
damage it's okay we got him we got him
we got him we got him we got him oh he
oh my God so annoying come back come
back oh God come back okay we got him we
got him we got him
yay
wow shut down you know we were ambitious
yeah I mean we have three people against
yeah yeah yeah yeah we did really well
yeah what is
that it's no issue
what I'm a beautiful my space boy so she
came back and then killed you that's
rude kind of mean yeah it's very there
was like this giant arrow on the map and
I was like what could that be but it was
on top of an enemy so I thought the
enemy was doing something but it was her
teleporting I understand now at least
now I know what it looks like you get it
you I get it now I get it now does your
guy have a Santa skin I feel like he's
suit
one I don't think he has a Santa skin
this is his winter one right
now he would look really cool as Santa
yeah he'd be really
cute not
my please have mercy
Rumble I'm on my way I'm on my way G so
okay okay okay don't let her kill me
Top Lane is so
depressing you got this be
careful that hit me ient you she knows
it you didn't I pressed the wrong flash
yes yes yes I your flash crazy well
she's dead you did
it it's on the wrong button okay it's
not my fault you did
it yay you're
[Music]
crazy
yo an enemy spp snipe no don't let me
kill you please let me kill you give me
the
satisfaction
whoops you scared
me turret wa has been SL you
coward
no oh
no nature is too quiet I'm weak again
who is this rum where did he come
from kill this
Rumble Rumble can you come control your
jungle he's just chilling he lost his
jungle he has no idea what's going on
you know oh oh is that a
Teleport that is a Teleport okay I I see
it now I see it
now uhoh
uhoh there he is there he is please
should have done anything when there's
two so lesson I have to learn when
there's more than one
enemy full health I should not tickle
them cuz they will St kill me tickle
them you out play them no I died no no
next time they St me and them next time
okay okay I see yeah yeah see what of
you what if youall play them for next
time that's a good stes actually I
didn't think bit about it that way okay
okay thanks
teacher not even Cloud fruit could erase
that
memory get away from
me we got them you got
this are we I can't
tell so much I want to see for
myself there just one okay I can take on
one
y an enemy has been slain took me long
enough SL he's too
strong team she's a singer she's a
singer she's working late singer cuz
she's a singer
listen to Espresso out nowy thank you
Chas wreting listen to Blackbird out now
on Spotify list black out now on
Spotify I'll remember that your team has
destroyed a turret I'm on a roll look at
you Kiara you're slaying you're crazy
all alone baby all alone
no your team destroyed an inhib H it's
okay it's like it's it's a character
development for your my space
character it like The Angst fuels him
probably what's that why is that a red
circle around me what does that mean oh
no no no it's a buff it's a buff okay
okay okay it's good good okay okay yeah
good good good good good okay you got
red buff from Jungle no if you have a I
I'll protect I'll protect you thank you
ow oh they're all here oh there's so
many of them yeah leave leave uhoh
uhoh wa I was about to dodge that but
that came fast this just happened she
just got the both of us I'm glad we died
together yeah at least we're here
together she's
uh-oh ooh thank you oh there's three of
of them um get him okay okay he's he's
Charmed he's not Charmed never mind I
lied I flashed again damn it you're
okay every
time o the music cute your character
makes cute music thank
you as the change
she's a singer she's working
late uh oh there's two left
left he's Charmed he's
Charmed nice he's dead he's dead kill
him kill him I'm trying it's okay it's
okay I'm running oh I'm dead you're all
alone it's
okay over dominating ooh nice dominating
dominating dominating
um yeah
[Music]
teesty destroyed a tret and this
one
yes these guys are
[Music]
crazy oh I'm going to
die that damn LS
all her
fault us apart lay in the cloud Drake
nice honestly when we played her against
the ls the first time I thought she
would be like super toxic character like
um you know like no no the way her
character is like her characteristics
and then I played her she all positivity
yeah she's like super positive in
somehow that makes it worse I don't know
why someone that's like peace and love
stuns you and then like ults you in a
line H nothing personal
yeah nothing personal at all
yeah doesn't mean it he just
joking I see I see
uhoh my
wall go g go kill her kill it R LS get
LS oh this there there's like the five
of
them go k go a wait no run
run nice are those the flowers from the
No No o look it's a CO wheel I got it I
got it I got
it
oo I can just figure out how to drive
this
thing I'll hit there I'll hit it I'll
hit it what this way did you be I'm
driving here has dest did you become the
thing yeah yeah you can drive it that
didn't look like driving it seemed like
you possessed it no you're driving it
destroy
[Music]
inor every animal hungers for something
what is
this only the spawn was closer that's
confusing an enemy
has we can end yeah you right
now the game we're
waiting we're so
[Music]
glad easy easy easy easy easy easy easy
well your first time playing that guy
Liz how did you like him I loved him I
thought he was really
cool nice I'm going to see if he has
skins oh
yeah can he be part of pop
stars we doing
time I get more more gold all of a
sudden malfunction describes it well
I got more RP too yeah how do we huh
yay thank you ran I can get my
my I can buy more
sarap my space boy skin here we did I
also get stuff I don't know they give me
stuff yeah we need to we need to submit
to them your username and stuff but I
got some stuff how did I know my oh you
did like you got wait how how can I wait
I also got some blessed okay it's time
for a new skin how do I buy thank you Le
how do you know Le of
egg uh cuz they can probably see it on
my stream
oh oh it's here thank you Riot I guess I
won't Riot then you get away SC
free luy gray gray has a winter
skin I'm going to get it yay how much is
that like the the how much is 3,600 is
that a lot it's it's quite a bit you can
buy a skin where do I buy skins go go to
the right by the RP there's like coins
stacked up you click
there uh uh-huh uh-huh and then you you
and buy stuff there okay
o short hair one skin I think he only
has one skin W and it's winter I love
winter oh oh requ Champion I don't have
Caitlyn yet even though I'm playing her
she's she's probably free this week get
her with your your blue stuff my blue
stuff yeah in game in game go buy her if
you like her
okay I do like
her you know sarapen has a skin called
graceful Phoenix
ooh is it red orange or is it fire it's
nice
perfect they don't have a lot of green
skins I'm a little bit annoyed I doesn't
have a single green type
skin it cannot believe messed up
am I still in your party I can't tell
yeah uh probably maybe I'm not in it
right now so I'm buying things you're
buying things oh you're not in here I'll
invite you to the game thanks don't know
why get in here something wrong hi
guys okay money is gone Riot thank you
thank you Riot thank you money is I
spent
it I had a billion
but I I spent it all A Milli billion
dollars
wow very
based what is chroma what does that mean
it's different color variations so if
you go to chroma and you look up the
champion you like they might have
different variation like color
variations for the Skins you already
have oh so it's like in skins chroma oh
chromas yeah oh AR so for example yeah
if you go into chroma and go Ari she has
green here yeah then you can buy the
chroma and then you can use that
one instead you
know this is
green yeah she has literally an emerald
KDA skin that's nice yeah purchase it
bye bye bye bye bye now bye now wait I
have to pick I'm going to get the the
the oama it's time to go
to it's time to bed to go to bed it's
time to go to bed it's time to go to
bed that one that's green so we're
ending the stream no no what everybody's
saying bye to go to bed
byee Jo summer so if I it should always
prioritize using the blue ones right
since those are in game uhhuh okay yeah
I know those think I did wrong when I
first like got got characters and stuff
okay I got a green
one y are we going to try real people
now or can we still not what do you want
to do what is this looks cool sesors can
we play against real people it would be
I'm so ready I feel extremely prepared
for the
challenge I
believe nothing can stop me nothing can
stop you uh I'm going to change my thing
you need to select uh Top
Lane Cosmetics winter he has multiple
apparently everyone wants me to tell you
about
aniva I've been seeing in my chat too I
don't care I just invested in hot
outfits for Caitlyn play Kaitlyn she's
locked in okay where do I select oliv is
a bird I don't know uh right under your
character
icon character icon there like a little
square that you
can and then oh you click on the
character and then you click okay got it
okay okay is it possible to change the
skin now no MM in cosme yes yes
okay okay hot
cute hell yeah hell yeah how do I change
the color of my skin oh I found it you
hit the little chroma button okay okay
you can use the blue stuff woo I got it
I got it I got it let me know when we're
all ready spash I did flash flash flash
flash flash
flash bottom
W the blue stuff use the blue stuff the
blue stuff the blue stuff 99%
point6
Purity okay use the blue stuff female
dog you're ready everyone ready I'm
ready I'm
ready Mr we're looking we're going to
play people we're going to play people
I'm so scared don't worry they might be
Bots too they'll think I I I'm just the
like five years we 5 years old with how
bad I'm playing we're all you're doing
so good you're pushing top you're okay
because we're together with you so
you're not going to get
reported oh okay yeah that's what
matters it's okay even if they reported
me I have Riot on my side what can they
do a
lot it's fine oh it's fine
and a no there's a lock no that might
this seems like a bot team you know oh
okay okay that's good yeah yeah I bet I
bet they're I bet they're
Bots I'm a star Guardian look I'm green
and gold my or is gold green
yay I'll charm them with my green with
like Bish hair
[Music]
[Applause]
oh do we do the bush thing doesn't work
I don't
know are these real people or are they
not real people we'll see I guess should
I walk in if I walk in and I see them
maybe they are not real people check
this out everyone I'm about to face
check to see if they're real people do
it holding it they might be Bots that's
fine
oops I hope they're
Bots who's pinging me yeah who's pinging
us what's P someone's someone's oh the
robot oh who's
that oh no are the is the robot
intentional
again how do you even do
that robot maybe it is intentional no I
don't think so
roboz in the house Robo Liz am I back
robot again yes you're robot what who's
do the
exterminate BOS
exterminate terminate exterminate o it's
red I'm so
exterminate
exterminate forgot I can Auto attack for
a moment CU I'm
nervous there's a guy
come
here
[Music]
exterminate I see right through you
can't tell if this is bot or not ow I've
been
roed okay youve you've been don't worry
she's a bot she's a bot okay maybe she
will walk into the thingy then that's
good all right all right you ready for
this get her get her get her ah okay she
flashed I'm leaving goodbye I'll take
some of this this while I leave they're
so nice take this while I leave no don't
eat
them I'm going to die I'm out of
here believe
it blood oh nice First Blood oh you back
thank
God
uhoh Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum don't worry
nice nice good
job okay CeCe in in about
um in about 10 seconds I will come to
you
okay
yes no more no
less I'm vanished all right all right
make her come back make her come
back okay she will never expect this she
will never expect this she's not
expecting this one what is
that my snowball goodbye thank you wait
who are
you nooo okay and will and oh sorry
sorry you two people and will and will
okay okay oh no
oh no I'm so scared no I'm in a bad be
scared you're beautiful I all you are I
am
retreating that's a jungle okay oh no
how do you know don't hurt me I am just
a Noo-noo and Willam
nooo and will
world oh Liz what are you doing by the
tower okay that's I'm reading uh some
bits to do with um this skin makes my
weapon like super super visible compared
to before it's crazy super visible yeah
it's it's nice it's kind of nice
actually super super
visible super visible so
slow I am so
slow I car the oh God
on help
minions so
visible super
visible I'm going
home oh let's see what animation she has
here okay guys I'm going to run it down
bot Lane are you
ready have fun okay well I hope you're
ready for me to run it down bot
Lane an enemy has been W take him down w
y come
[Music]
back oh thank you thank you I did how
did you know she how did she know I want
her to come back an enemy has been SL
goodbye Hi
Li hello I'll help you with this guy for
a moment thank you okay okay okay okay
okay okay
oh I love playing people or totally
people not I love to playing against
people yeah these people I love playing
against
them I get it oh I
believe oh she's
here oh there's two of them uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh yeah I heal there you go is it
yours ooh cool oh she's sharp nice oh no
my guy's not a Healer I just had that on
me okay I might have to retweet here
retweet retweet retweet like and retweet
get oh I just ran to the wall never mind
I know oh no oh no oh I need to run run
run run run run run
run okay we going going home we're going
home after ret the skin is like she has
like cards and stuff it's kind of like
an
astrologian kind of
cool hi don't know
why poo is freaking
out a little
Dan I'm a noob
might be outside today is my first time
you'll be fine you're doing nice don't
worry yeah you're doing great yeah is it
easy to stream snipe in this
game we're probably against mods right
now
yeah but is it easy to stream snipe no
look
like
UT down oh NOA you look like s V thank
you I am a magical
girl wait higher
L
for oh there's a guy there's a guy
here kill him no I'm not worried about
it if anything I would have welcomed it
getting stream sniped why maybe they
maybe they would be nicer to me
feed or I'll ban you yeah they'll just
kiss my feet my beautiful bare
[Music]
feet please stream snipe us oh
God I'm so sorry it's okay shut down
it's okay I died too in solidarity down
solidarity yeah I'm slowly but surely
overcoming greed that's good no you
should keep being greedy oh really yes
continue your greed okay okay continue
your greed be greedy okay okay okay oh
they're they're right here why are they
right here okay wow I'm coming top oh
welcome to come as long as you don't
steal my kill okay I'll let you have it
I'm going to set it up so you can get
him where's he going why is he leaving
okay
okay he's never going to expect this if
he just walks up okay okay okay snowball
get him get him get him get him get him
I'm not ready okay get him get him get
him get him get him get
him I took it oh it's okay it feels like
I did it okay we did that together oh no
why is there there's like four of them
what three three just three oh that's
just okay so you're telling me if
there's two people I should still attack
them yes you should kill
them you got this
okay I'm
rooted oh there's someone else
teleporting in so three people should I
still yes you should kill them okay okay
okay okay don't be a coward kill them
live with no out of my way nocturn got a
blue buff to get yay I killed her I'm
running home yeah see green is good
who's pinging what did I say I don't
know it's not me unless I not I it's not
us it's not me I don't even know how to
Ping what the heck I don't know how to
Ping either which means maybe it is us
what's
pinging I didn't I didn't click anywhere
there so um out
by ow come back hit me under
Tower okay okay are you
ready are you ready go in go in okay
he's charm he's charm he's charm you're
crazy CRA he's charmed's Charmed oh
you're crazy he's
dead okay I'm going
home I will also go home I
suppose focus on completing one
doesn't work guys I was writing to my
chat because they were like popo box I'm
like he's a
parrot he's a coao
actually well he's a type of parrot he's
a
Kakao so like and parrots can like you
know mimic a lot of can you make a a dog
sound impressive if dogs really do sound
like that
an enemy has SL nice y I got
kill
nice
thanks oh
nine
yes I let out an alt and it did
absolutely nothing it was so bad hey the
thought is what counts
sometimes my aim is so [\h__\h] man
spooked
him
what what is that what is that what is
that what is that why are they all doing
the
apocal US um nocturns thing ow why are
they why are they all
here they want you and they what they're
crazy oh BS are crazy I want to take it
and walk up is it dead is it
gone oh oh it reset okay I'll
leave you got this there two of
them
yummy no come
back where is she where is she come here
no that didn't hit
her m
o oh that doesn't go over there yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum okay yum yum yum
yum
yum I'm going home there okay come to
SES with me will they hit
[Music]
me
yay uh shoes
your team has
desty turet kill her kill her yay the
toad the toad killed her nice walk up to
me walk up to me okay you don't need you
don't need you don't need to do that
Liz no it's that oh we got a mountain
Drake
ow ow well I got Dragon the champ plants
bloom so where's worth
it exeed what does it
mean what does it mean what does it all
mean don't me you doing what the what
waa what was that he does a little
dance run he was teleporting uh-huh come
back come the
minion somehow that's just what you have
to do
[Music]
uhoh biscuits heal you oh I didn't even
realize I had biscuits in my inventory
oh yeah
biscuits oh that's why you guys
a I didn't realize I had any
biscuits with
me I thought you guys were cuz you got
guys like cookies that's what I cookie
cookie sometimes you just wait why did I
leave I can buy more stuff oh my
God yay I got
her you got
her yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
um well if if okay so I am spending a
lot of time barely killing the the the
Bots and then going home should I rather
play it safe so I don't go home and push
the lane instead n kill nah no you
should kill them yeah kill them okay oh
what is that that's the
nocturnal okay K are you dead no I'm
alive I came to help you oh oh no I K
him he's gone now don't worry okay I
just did what Chad told
me more mins oh she's singing don't sing
why is she singing y she's dead I don't
sing okay okay I'm I'm roll I'm rolling
I'm rolling okay she's Charmed she's
Charmed ring he's Char okay okay
C There Go My
Hero level 12 is this
one okay I'm just a
girl I don't know
the I'm just a
girl I'm going to go mid I don't know if
I'll survive a dive no not just so do I
hello
welcome my Lane thank you hello please
assist me get away from her oh oh
oh oh oh
wa what happened push the tower down yes
thank you
help can you just
Mor I mean kind of worked you should Mor
more almost dead she's almost dead she's
almost dead
is it the power of women that compelled
you to do this it was the power of woman
that really pushed me into doing that
that's so
strong there's one more on the right
side okay I'll charm her she's Charmed
oh I'm inside that's okay we're fine
okay she's Charmed yeah kill kill you
got it any
heals it's okay you got her you got her
kill her kill her no no you got her no
it's okay it's
okay oh keep chasing me sarapen come on
what are you doing
yeah nice try Lux your aim is as bad as
mine all right I'm here for you I'm here
for you I'm rolling I'm rolling it down
I'm rolling it down go go go get him get
him no I ran to the wall I ran to the
wall oh nice nice nice you got it nice
double double kill um now I buy this guy
oh yeah oh yeah oh
[Music]
noturno windows I don't know what that
means I
scared you win you win them you know you
Windows no minion don't kill me yeah you
wi you
Windows oh God team has destroyed window
you window and you lose those that's
okay sometimes you have to lose in order
to activation key does have the same as
me I right behind
you he's Charmed he's Charmed he's going
to come out he's come
out nice nice nice nice nice nice he's
low smoking he's low there's another one
coming from Top jungle I guess
okay did not in in fact come it was too
scary oh here he's there he's there oh
more friendly people oh
hi okay behind I'm going I'm going
behind yeah I brought them over sorry
about that it's okay it's okay Charmed
Charmed Nice kill kill kill kill kill
kill kill
kill nice nice nice nice nice to the
thingy
finally I to nice
oo let's get this Tower let me kill you
okay okay okay y to Tower I forgot about
him do you have your ult
kiaha yes if you use it it's like a
sniping if I can get him low enough you
can can kill him get away from her
Inhibitors
inhibit get
away I I I don't know I I'm
sorry y she just walked into
it but she's she's showing me her pretty
butt get her get her get
him goodbye
come back come back he's dead
yay come here seraphine be Charmed Yum
Yum Yum Yum
Yum oops I'm in
there walked into their
home oops you walked into their home and
died yeah
oopsie it's it's okay okay guys guys
kill them all it's fine I planted my ass
there worse yeah yeah yeah worse worse
worse
oo we're so good at this game y y not
bad not bad you're
slaying no right now I'm just running
because I died I have been slayed though
you're
so good though I'll remember that you
know that is
questionable why am I here where is
everybody Ally has been SL mother
trucker we're on our way away
away will I die to this no nice I did a
thing nice I got rooted I did a
uh guys's right behind
you your team has destroyed a
turret don't die
Kiara an ambush a
stampede oh I hey I was here physically
I we were here we
were we're winners
this was us leveling up huh does honor
players just never show yourself
or yeah you can't honor yourself it's
just the others oh oh this is a screen
where you
choose why would you yourself no no I
thought this was showing the the good
players of the game already no no no no
you get to pick oh I haven't seen that
when do I skip it by accident I don't
know um I just want to go get another
drink be right back
okay we're doing it wow we're so good
yeah we're doing we're doing a League of
Legends with the with the
professionals um quick say like some
terms the only professionals would
know
um I think I need to restart my League
of Legends
that's what only professionals would say
that is what a professional would say to
restart my League of Legends yeah I see
I see I'm going to yeah I'm going to I'm
going to restart League GG I'm going to
Lane Swap and then I'll I'll mid Gap and
then I'll wave state and split push and
then oh okay and then
I'll Tower tower Tower tower Tower to
tower Tower
Sol Baron Sol Baron uh um um um um flash
yes what what about your mic Ros oh all
of them
yeah I I got it I understood get what I
meant yeah I I got it I I understood
that solo bolo jungle uninstall un
jungle uninstall yeah yeah that is what
League of Legends Pros would say proxy
proxy I am just very confused about all
the words that are being thrown around
um um they're good words jungle jungle
diff What does diff mean difference diff
diff diff yeah it basically if you say
it to someone it's like you're
complimenting them jungle diff G so if
you go into a normal game you should say
that and you're complimenting them
you're lying to me I can hear from your
tone of voice don't try gaslighting me I
if you say don't even try your gas
it's a compliment gamer oh I see I see
so make sure to use that in your next
leag Legend teach me more what else
should I say so so yeah because I want
to be a good player a positive mindset
what should I say okay okay okay so next
time you go into a normal game just go
just say like pick any role and say like
I don't know mid
Canyon yeah can someone tell me why I
got promoted to bronze
yay she's
bronze okay I'll do that thanks for the
hints I've invited you back oh you
invited me game I just checked their
streams they made it for the
queue damn how did they do that did they
cheat they made what did they cheat the
poe girls got for the like bibu and Kyla
got uh into their they did nice
yeah I'm trying to get in and it's
telling me that I need to purchase a
code but I purchased a code huh so what
does it want for me why is it l bu
another one want more codes what's more
of it that's all you had to do wait damn
ex
you it's okay it's okay K this this is
worth you right no it's okay it took
them it took them 3 hours they waited
three hours that's crazy that is crazy
I'm glad I
hello
I'm welcome back
many Exile too or I have partially
regrets but mostly no regrets no regrets
no regrets
regret yes none of No
Regrets absolutely no none
regrets no regrets allowed in this
household none of that
no none of that no
IA yes you jump scared me are we in are
we ready for Q don't know yeah oh I
haven't said anything in like a while
you did you did something oh getting
ready for
kill sorry oh are we are we in oh okay
okay
okay we're queuing we're queuing we're
going to queue six people I see I see
that's fun we're queuing except queing
are we doing yeah we we'll do real
people yes yes yes yes I
believe I like real people me do
sometimes ooh heart
throb Warwick oh heart throb
nowi War
[Music]
wig I a heart robing at the end yeah
remember darling you you'll love her be
on that one
k for me yeah does she do something
special you'll see I wouldn't
spoiler I'm so fast do we go into the
bushes seconds we can check we can see
if they're real people I'm big how do we
know if they're real people um
Instinct yeah okay I think they're
Bots that's a
bot I I don't have any CC I didn't start
with it myself oh thank
you B they won't judge me too
hard
damn why are we get on my Lane hello no
you look so different how could you
running double
you it's okay we'll avenge you double
you oh the music's cute he's inviting me
okay never
mind get them get some stupid go Nissa
it's worth it I can't get
anymore
annoying crash man oh nice that looks
cool Liz yeah okay by hi
guys Goode see see didn't even heal up I
miss
you really really
really you little [\h__\h] they're low
there's two that are low here guys get
him okay I'm
running worry
not oh
there okay I'm I'm here for to harass
her
jungle okay okay
okay y that was totally worth it I'm
going to die for leave leave leave run
away run
away it's okay the minions are keeping
everything up I don't even have to do
anything
yay
yay you can go home you should go home
I'm going
home he going home she said she's a
woman who's beautiful she's a woman wo
wo wo I said she's a woman who's
beautiful she's going home cuz she's a
woman what are you tried to say huh oh
my God W I didn't know we were like that
I didn't know we were that kind of
League of
Legends I oh that's the leak experience
that I was looking forward to wow she
has to heal
uh what's that what's what's his
name uh
ow got
Gallo
galloo Gallo I hate that guy hate him
okay I hit him down but he has a chicken
costume and I'm aware of it kfp I'm
aware she's
aware there everybody told me to look at
it I've seen it
oh right I
back nice where are you running charm
charm charm where are you running
to he gave me a kill for free he's so
nice
yay paid
actor all right he working
lck my head forever
it's hard to get
out cuz she's
a singer beautiful woman
singer I'll switch the order
now cuz he's himer
Dinger oh my god oh there was a sparkle
in the
world wait why are there two of them
that's not fair that's a bot you know
she just doesn't know what's going
oning her I'm going to
die you're not going to die not today
not
today look at this guy what is he doing
he keeps going back and forth what is is
that what's the they're doing their best
their best is not good enough to die
they're trying really hard B are going
to kill you or the
minion m to oh God I'm going to die no
okay now so you're going to Flame the
bot are you saying I deserve this yes
you deserved that you deserved what was
coming for you you know what flaming the
Bots you know what maybe you're
right once yeah maybe I shouldn't have
Flame the weird Ming B this is what you
get for being toxic and this is a lesson
you should all learn
early okay oh
the that's so
cute biggest snowball ever I
learned okay okay okay okay he's charm
he's charm he's charm I'm killing
thisall oo kill him yay we did it get
the other one get the other
one
okay shut down okay I she's Charmed it's
Charmed it's Charmed charm okay okay
okay no don't go in oh did you get him
oh no wait there's another one
behind I'm going to get this dragon
now get
it he could have killed me if he wanted
to I think he's in love with me I think
the only logical yeah makes
sense I have my ult now I'm unkillable
because I can run
away oh I will just I'm leaving over
sorry wait there two there three it's
over sniff sniff I'm doing my best
sniffin you're doing greata you're doing
fantastic you're doing great I lost my
lane and it's it's 100% because of the
jungler yeah because g wow wow
GG my bad it's just how it is
sometimes I'm
going I'm out of Mana I mean I can charm
him for you okay I'm going I'm I'm TR
okay okay okay okay he's charm he's
charm all I can do now I have to leave
okay I'm running away too oh he's
confused he confused hit him hit him
awesome okay okay he's Charmed he's
Charmed I have no Mana kill him kill him
go in go in yay it's it's easy good job
Easy E easy easiest game okay now I'm
home nice
yay I've been around for a
while did you use your ult already no
yes oh oh you're not asking I know who
you asking I no
one really are you sure because I know
I'm alone here so no one's talking to me
no I I I watch I'm looking I'm watching
you yeah if he's really low like that
and he's far away you can save your ult
for last and you should be able to kill
him you actually talked to
me I want I have my eye on you you
watching me I'm watching you I'm
Charmed
W thank
you we go
damn uh-oh
do you have my stream open in the second
screen I am no I just I click on the map
and I look at
you why I why you even have time for
that wait can you do that I'm losing my
Lane because of you you should focus on
your lane you don't want you don't want
to watch Pros they they're like crazy
with doing that
yeah I can imagine they got their eyes
everywhere I cannot be and there's one
guy here up here
G there there there there there okay
okay I'm Charming him he's
Charmed okay let's get get him get
him Miss make him regret
living okay okay there's another one
there's another one right here Warick
okay never mind it's too far waa is
dying I'm going to kill that Warwick no
don't steal my kill don't die don't die
kill I'm going into my locker bye no no
no here I'll set up this kill for you
I'll set up this kill for you I'm
already gone I'll get this kill I'll
I'll avenge you okay oh my God he feared
me he
knew are you seeing what she takes out
of the locker what does she take out of
the locker it's a picture of VI really
rolling the ball I'm rolling the ball
wait are they can idea what's going onil
it's fine I haven't seen yeah don't
spoil
please what I don't know anything what
it's the animation in the the be no no
no I didn't mean that I was asking
follow-up questions and then I I took it
back oh don't
worry oh you stand no chance I killed
him I see he's dead you you did that
because I said that I lost my Lane
because of you previously huh yeah I had
to I had to get rid of him I I really
got it
back they don't care
chat we care no no no no uh
I I don't mean
you it's okay of course we care about
you no no no no we love you we care I'll
come back and kill him again no don't do
that I'll make him regret he kill oh
someone's
teleporting who's
teleporting tell him not to okay
I'll do that next
time oh yeah I need the eat the cookies
eat the cookies eat the cookies gy my
ALT is ready okay I'm like lowkey dying
though it's okay he's leaving I don't
know what he's doing over
here stop fearing me I keep forgetting
to eat my
biscuits at least you have biscuit
goodbye
un we got this all right good Tower oh
that's true y there's some people up
here but I don't think they're coming up
here yet I not mean the flash fat
fingered
that dude right here right here it's
okay don't die to her I can do an ALT
almost dead y
okay
okay oh God oh God we can do this
yeah doing
it give me the kill give me the K get it
get it get it oh
no no yum I'm I'm going to leave right
here right
here let look picture time one I carry
the legacy of
the
no yay close that was
close oh just a little bit of power so
none of my letter abilities work on the
tower what the hell was that that
sucks oh he has a lot of Health no weird
he's a tanky he's tanky don't appreciate
it quite
tanky wow what's she doing over there
going home home there you are charm the
tower the tower starts walking towards
you yeah like
uproots oh byy stuff I forgot where' he
go there he is bye I came for you
Warwick I'm getting my kill one way or
another your team has destroyed gross
leg and then he starts walking towards
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] I be
cute and then my
[Music]
own we got him good job not good I need
more damage I need more damage good it
doesn't matter who gets him as long as
he dies
right oh I mean no I me I me I don't
know how I got him
good oh back I I didn't mind to tower
Tower kill
him no come back come back come back
come back ride come back come back oh
no get
her all right all right I'm here he has
no Mana he has no Mana to keep going
keep going
yay Mormon your team has destroyed a
turret you certainly let an interesting
oh he's behind
me who's behind you oh it's a toad why
is the toad attack a toad I mean just
kill
himy how are you attacking us Mr Toad
that's not very nice a toad a
toad I but I'm I'm coming
jungle coming
jungle I'm welcome what is that what was
that oh is that a buff okay yes Hi Li
thank
you okay okay okay let's go get him I'm
leaving oh wait this K I'm stupid hi k
because C played played last time so I
was like oh oh down down he's trying
he's charm
oh I'm dying it's okay run it's fine
it's fine I'll stop them oh waa okay
he's still run he's I missed him he's
not Charmed I'm wrong I'm
lying oo oops I didn't mean to attack oh
oh no it's okay you got this the dream
he's running at me we all here though
come back mid we're all here
okay
nice nice nice nice nice
nice get the turret okay awesome
[Music]
nice oh oh what oh I died from the tower
my
bad my
bad oopsie
y oh you think he'll walk out over here
yeah yeah he's coming your way oh he's
going back walk over here come
back no he's not I think he's so scared
he's too scared of you what is he scared
of he's coming back
nice nice
nice
Gallo no you got him you're two people
and there's gig right behind
[Music]
you what is that is that an elephant no
tiger Bo I'm not sure an animal
time is never over Mony welcome to the
table I guess hello fluffy monster a boy
she wants to play
league is she only she thinks I'm done
streaming cuz I'm so
quiet girl I'm still streaming let's get
top
Tower guess I should talk more this is
my it's okay we're all locked we're all
locked in so hard
ah ah ah ah
lock not protecting
the goodbye chunky
wonky okay
uh I am here but I am
low a
shoot okay we did get two shut it was
worse it was worse was worth
worse worth wor
worse okay he's almost dead do you see
him the on the right yes oh it's
you nice nice nice
nice
legendary charm
Charmed nah
nice I'm going back she's going back
where's my bouse oh oops I'm
coming uh-oh not again not again I
almost died I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine get
get goodbye everyone good job Ending
game
[Music]
a you got him nice uh-oh uh-oh I'm
dead it's fine you guys can finish it
I'm course nice you got this last one
last
one a triple kill triple kill he so good
he's so Goods no no live she's weak you
can get her
no you you you got triple kill you got
triple
kill look at you
Kiara
yay thanks to the question marks League
of Legends
Pro League of leing pro
g
g good
work
GW oh my God I can honor more than one
person I can just honor all of you yeah
oh
oops not biased do you
think would would Liz be okay going top
does wa want to bot
oh yeah you want to support what the
hell is bot Lan or she can still play
Kaitlyn yeah Kaitlyn is I spot I don't
mind uh doing
whatever okay don't bother me I mean I
love I I love
youa I mind switching up oh bottom L I
thought everywhere is bot Ling cuz the
Bots are everywhere
no what so should I go bottom yeah go
bottom
oh I'll I'll see a different scenery for
once mhm okay
okay yeah and then narissa will set up
all the kills for you
yeah okay oh she will steal them all is
that what I hear from that
giggle I I nothing
intentional I believe okay one second
I'm just getting water up but I'm still
like here one sec okay you will steal
them it's okay okay like if I don't she
can't steal anything that doesn't exist
there are no kills in the first place
with me no she she's going to set them
up and then you're going to kill steal
her it's probably more like she's
setting them up and she's killing
them both I'm just there for mental
support we have to do it together
okay can't play play again okay I'm here
okay okay let's go I'm
baby I'm
baby I'm baby I'm
bab I'm sorry I'm
not where are you Liz we need you oh
mine's still mine's still loading uh
yeah loading back into the thing yeah
now it's doing it well I've recently met
a baby so I think I'm pretty good with
you know you Rec
a baby mystical creature the
baby and I get I I I uh it it pulled my
hair it was pretty fascinated with me I
gave it an elephant it like the elephant
yeah kid I think it was in love with
me was
baby baby do I need to click something
different now no okay no you can just
swap you can go top
baby was cute don't have to swap the
thingy you pulled my hair
yeah and I didn't mind I would like to
go back botom after this game though
okay it's just a test
yeah with
gr so I'm going to go Bottom now yeah go
bot wa Fair cool just looks like vior I
know it's so pretty the
guy oh we on the oh no we on the other
side oh no oh no it's over oh no is that
bad it's just it confuses me personally
it doesn't change anything but it gets
really confusing for me no it is
confusing
yeah let's see if they're real people so
is my bottom the top now because we're
the other way around yeah go this way
right
here uh wait wait wait why is the view
always so weird in the beginning why do
I always have to change it I don't know
are we going into the into the into the
bushes G we can see if they're real I'll
hook my head
over should I follow you are we going
into the
bush yeah we might die I don't see them
they might be starting blue
blue should I walk over there just look
yeah I'm behind you I'm behind you okay
oh are are you guys real are you guys
bot guys are you real are you bot yeah
are you real people you going Sarah are
you real
theying own person wait there's someone
there are they real are they real get
him I'm too used there's another one
behind oh no that's that's this get come
hurry we'll just go to L are they
real yay he's dead it's
okay oh they're here W hey wait that's a
real person
really that's a real person okay I'm
running away bye a real person back to
the tower back to the tower wow okay I'm
at the tower you're playing against a
real person F who the Lux is real the
Lux is real no
bot Lane is definitely real
people it's okay I got this we've
trained for this
guys no we haven't yes we what yes we
have
sorry oh hey what ELO are we playing
against What's Happening
Here what's the best thing to do now ah
wow
um you just are supposed to kill kill
the minions last hit them you get money
so when you die or go back you can um
you know that's a buy thing okay to get
stronger
yeah I me running away from me why she
running away from me scared
uh I mean there is no retreat we just
have to keep doing it if you're
struggling you can come back by the
tower okay I carry the legacy of the I
carry the Legacy blah blah Ari blah blah
blah she's telling us our entire life
story blah blah blah blah blah
blah
okay this Lux is being
careful whoops what the
hell come here CC where is here up up
okay okay yeah where I am I'm
coming okay Charmed good good kill him
kill him kill him I don't have a ward
I'm afraid of walking in I'm very
low no I have okay there's two now I
can't do it
I die to this oh might die to this just
a taste cookie
owie the music is so peaceful it has to
go know all
peaceful ow ow ow ow
ow I prefer playing against bots no no
it'll be okay I like I like I feel more
fulfilled when it's a real person than a
bot yeah you feel learning it's how you
learn it's how you actually get
better dying from B I mean from like
minions oh I'll use all my man and then
yummy yum yum yum no no I'm going to die
have confidence bye have
confidence an ally she a high hello oh
no oh no oh no I am dead oh no oh no no
no no it's only to see how far I've
come all right okay I will come smack
him soon
Liz maybe let me kill all these little
tiny
[Music]
babies he leaving they're pretty good
they're pretty good bot that's a little
guy good luck GG you're going to have to
carry I'm I KN okay okay I'm here Liz
I'm
here okay I'm going to
uh I need to get closer to be able to do
what I want to do oh no where' he go no
he healed oh I shouldn't have
flashed I don't know where they are well
nice try
there they
are
place oh no okay she has no Mana I'm
running up oh okay go go go go
go nice P she can I blame the Ping have
170 ping blame the Ping thank you though
okay it's that goddamn pain every time
maybe I can maybe if I charm
her ow ow he's hurting
me I'm going to go back let's go I can
walk
bottom wow he's ice sking with himself
it's so cute I'm going for the Draven or
the Jin go on okay well I hit them but I
have leave they're they're leaving back
up back
up I want to go get grubs so
careful b side
okay
is grubs grubs grubs grubs just back up
we're really low
mhm right you
nice
thanks go my minions oh your minions oh
uhoh what was that does this music come
from you I don't
know uh yeah the music comes from
nissa's so
calming double kill
uhoh
ouch
uh-oh got you [\h__\h] female
dog
meber I can't I can't I can't fight this
Warick no she's level seven okay got
scar I can't fight this
Warick where are
you it's okay he's on grubs
can't really can't do anything
here I got you biscuit an experience not
my no Lux leave leave my tower alone you
fiend oh I'm back yeah leave it
alone I can't take my jumper off it's
hot we can go kill Warwick if you
want I don't think we can kill Warwick
people two versus one should we
win oh he's just standing there we can
walk towards him I don't think we'll
make it there in time is the only
problem by the time he leaves he's very
fast they're already level six we're
screwed he's right there I see him they
have alts we don't oh I'm coming it's
okay wait there's two of them there's
two of them I'm dead I'm so dead I'm
walking to you oh
no go the wall I'm too I'm too behind
it's okay it's okay sorry it's
okay let me grab
this please stop pinging
randomly ma'am um I've been told it's a
polite thing to do if you do it
correctly oh I think retreating was the
correct thing to do it was just too
late would you agree chat
no she rooted me she always Roots me no
he rolled at you that's rude I hate
her goodbye what the
heck oh my
God okay so that one is like a is that
the stun I can't tell
[Music]
this oh he's just walking past oh he's
just walking okay I'm coming from
behind might come back I'm dead I'm I'm
running away no I missed I missed don't
worry I scared her I scared what are you
doing with the scar
there's another one oh no oh no oh no oh
no I'm going to be more careful wo it's
good go go go go you got
him you ow okay never mind it's okay
it's okay no you got this oh no I I was
trying to W the bush no wait that's
messed up only the bear dies and the
girl still lives and then she just like
lays next to him on the floor what do
you mean the bear which bear Noo-noo and
which one I don't know the your animal
your pets oh he dies you're mourning and
she's fine and then she just lays down
on the
floor she's living that's messed up she
dies of
grief a it's a Yeti Yeti a Yeti is a
bear if you think about
it okay we can still turn this right
guys yes we can still turn this around
yeah yeah yeah yeah turn this around we
can do it
duh I should have just played
team melted
bottomy oh my God okay what Strat do we
do quick do the Strat number seven I
think and then we got this number seven
if we do seven I think we got this so
can you tell me CU it's my first day
was of course I can tell you um else
knows but you explain it to me yeah so
the Strat is you didn't read the manual
on the strats yeah you didn't read all
the man behind me he coming out behind
me he's behind me he's behind me oh
behind you okay I'll charm him I'll
charm him yeah he's over here where yeah
he's over here somewhere and by he was
behind okay I'm running away again
please okay running back to my
minions your turret has destroyed uh-oh
that's not
good oh he's here oh wait okay okay
okay he's Charmed he's Charmed oh I'm
going to try coming Mondo's on his way
Mondo's on his way I'm going to try
coming but we're both dead okay that's
fine we tried that was a good try I'm
here for the Gin oh he
flash I mean I need help top I'm not
bottom anymore we need to help top okay
yeah I need help help for a moment watch
out for this Warwick Let's Get
Him whoa what is
oh actually as Mr
Mundo what is this what is all this fire
everywhere fire fire the fire fire
fire fire fire like the fire fire Bri a
high as you desire who very
collector an enemy is no not legendary
that's fine you got executed greedy nice
what what a fool what a loser what a
fool just kidding he's kicking our asses
no no he's a fool he's a loser and a
fool a
fool I have to learn how to dodge
that let's go where am I to go
we're getting stomped no we're not no
it's okay it's okay we're fine we're
fine yeah we can turn this
around I don't know I don't know just
has to come up with some Strat and tell
us what to do that like really confuses
they have 21 kills and we have two are
you
sure uhoh uh-oh uhoh I got that they're
all here I the war and the freaking M
got me am
G can you come up with like a cool Strat
like twist don't die we going to bite
them okay that's a good idea I
think that is my plan
mhm we will bite them okay what if we
just went next you know like a reset
okay okay and where what like like we go
to the next next
[Music]
game
that's what if we went to the next game
thats like surrend winning that feels
like the opposite of winning no it's
winning it's
winning I can't get this ow they're all
here I'm coming I'm coming I'm coming
bring them
mid uhoh there's so oh my god oh no your
dead body and the dead child like so
many stop the dead child
too we can we can go next to reset and
maybe we'll get worse people you know
they're going they're going mid I think
they're all going mid
hooray
surrender
what dang
[Music]
it it's tried who voted no wait early
surrender who voted people do have to
have to vote is it like it has to be
unanimous for early surrender unanimous
oh
man oh if only that was if only we knew
who that was too bad we can't figure it
out wait what oh it's only oh it is
unanimous I
suppose that's the first time I see that
today it's very depressing no it's okay
the d stands for done well
done well e f e a t yeah yeah uh I
finished my second lader of water give
me a sec I need to grab
more I'll me I'll
BRB BRB okay
BRB okay you are still not muted on my
screen just you know okay
okay hm
[Music]
H 13 kills from that cloudy Jester
Jin
13 oh speaking of Jester I want to try
shako shako shako
shako um let's see do I even have him
[Music]
yet we fed him to too
early but I am a fast food restaurant
owner so I'm here to feed people no
that's
true I need to feed them you need Fe
hungry I would be evil if I would let
people
hunger yeah you're just so kind and
giving I I I do like to receive too but
that's in my private life I suppose as a
professional businesswoman I like to
give
M
yeah yeah what's your love language or
what's my love language
[Music]
uh
uh we should all take one of these
quizzes yeah I feel like I'm the only
person who didn't take this like Omega
quiz thing oh I haven't done it yet do
you want to everybody was taking it I is
it that short no well I don't know we
can we can still look at it afterwards
after stream after after stream cuz
everybody was taking and posting the
results while I was busy with Lady and
uh I don't even understand still what a
mega verse means it's it's
important it's important apparently it's
very
important H it has 40 questions
oh that should
Beed hello did you take theega quiz
Cecilia no not
yet I also didn't I haven't yet wow yeah
I should I should I haven't what's your
excuse I forgot about it I saw it I was
I should do this and I forgot about it
really how can you forget about it when
it's been going on for like 3 Days Every
posting it goldish memory her and me
haven't done it yet so I see I see we
have a good excuse what is your excuse
yeah I was busy the past three days with
in my in my should I have picked that
one yes ladies did you have ladies in
your house I'm a
lady I
mean
ladies there's too many ladies my mom's
a lady have you been having a nice
time yeah me and the ladies or and the
ladies me and the ladies we had what a
nice time very nice time and magnificent
marvelous time that's not oh
beautiful they love Austria it's very
everyone Austria Austria is very two out
of five of us here have taken the O
Omega quiz I will say one thing
yes how much longer do you girls want to
play because one person in this room has
a uh thing to do I can't even get on
don't even worry I want to apply uh not
pressure but I want to remind a who is
it who has the thing to do
a someone sounds very
guilty I
see it's practically done it's just I
whether I whether I want to add a cherry
on top you should you should
okay you
know sure I'll add the cherry on top add
the cherry on top and I will eat it
should we play another one yeah yeah we
can play one how long does the Cherry
take um shouldn't take too long all
right if we do one more then yeah I'll
have I'll have time all
[Music]
right oh my runes correct okay finding
match Comfort P t-o oh you're doing P
Teo this time okay comt demo I oh I want
to change my catak oh
everybody Discord room has participated
in the Advent calendar already except
for one
person who could it be I declined it you
can switch your character thank you
sorry I can try try Lilia actual jungler
look herb oh my God Teo with the be skin
is called
beo so
cute beo I love beo
beo beo wait who are you aist CH a can I
go top again bottom was stressful yeah
you're going top why are you say that
like you want to get rid of me you are
not a good
goodbye I know how do I learn then how
will I ever learn you're Li you need to
read how to play it read how to play it
and then try
again hey I I am sensing some
hostility micity that I have hearding
over the report button
[Laughter]
I'm I'm ready now I don't care either
way but you it's okay I broke up before
you broke up with me I already said I'm
going back up good she already sent a
letter before good fine then good I hope
you'll have fun down there being bottom
lovep yeah I already
have who's who's joining you down there
H herb me
a h I said off I said before the last
game I want to go back you want to go oh
okay I wish you two happiness I see I've
seen this coming in the past weeks and
months anyway the signs were all over
signs oh my goodness gracious well you
knew that that we would be like pairing
in the in the bot Lan she knew leg was
com seen this paing since the very
beginning I've seen the Synergy in your
colors and your designs
mhm well she's monitoring me you know
yeah I mean I'm monitoring yeah I mean
Cecilia and Gigi also monitor Thea too
so
yeah oh I'm ready I don't see us oh
there I'm
green are we checking if they're real
people again they're real people I'm
sure no I hear KDA music
[Music]
are we going into the bushes or not nah
that's the most fun part of the game
Run I'm fine on my own
H me and my minions we're going to guys
you want to you want to you want to see
this oh my God you're my goodness your
little
Crown who are you playing against is
that lux okay no Lux it's okay good what
is
this have SK smolder smolder is that a
character oh what do I need to know J
quick I know nothing about him I I I
think it takes him a really long time to
ramp up he needs a lot of farm oh okay
so I his old is this big line and he
flies around and he's
like okay and he throws a ball at
you smolder from a
cane
hello of that's crazy Wawa turn turn on
your screen question mark someone
is okay I kill tell me what to do okay
okay do whatever makes you happy that's
fine I have to I have to task manager my
way out of it why is it not Window mode
anymore what happened actually
wait why is he doing more damage than me
m
up he's going to farm
huh oh W just for you so nice to see you
you thought I was alone did you
oh you are wrong yes you are wrong I
think bot is real
people I'm pretty sure they're real
people this still
uhoh Warwick behaves just the way I like
it so I think he's a
botor can the team be like half bot half
real people yes sure I think that's what
happened last the first time we
played yeah I think if they don't have
like a full
team and there's like not a good amount
of people who can join with them they'll
just like supplement with Bots that
would be evil
oh it's okay she's
back is it like common that the Top Lane
is always played a load and the bottom
is always double
yeah Bottom's not as aggressive as last
time which is
good maybe maybe maybe they are Bots
maybe maybe they are you should you
shouldn't have judged Me by One game
against players
I'm not judging you I would do better
now
perhaps I'm not judging you just bot bot
all the lanes in all the different areas
play differently oh they're all Bots wow
they're Bots for Wheels is mine bot guys
yeah they're all Bots my
[Music]
boty
of the jokes on you getting very
conflicting come to come to where I am
you me yeah okay I'm coming yeah oh
guys
come oh don't run up to him though he's
melee oh don't run up to him he's he's a
melee range champ too late sorry I was I
wasn't looking at my HP that well you
got him you got him you got him you got
no confusing I feel I don't know what
about champ
messed
up no his life
steal well an enemy it's okay they're
Bots it's okay it's okay nothing wrong
with a little
feeding I see right through you I see
right through
you she's so close so close to death I'm
dead why' you die I I thought she was
going to die awkward she's so weird I
thought she was going to die
narissa oh God I'm going to die wait
wait wait yeah kill him kill the bot
kill the bot oh he just left yeah he
teleported
away oh he went bot MH oh what that's a
skill Oh I thought he was going home if
it's purple it's teleport I think it was
gold don't
remember what oh if it's blue it's the
back oh I see
okay get her get her get her go
minions an enemy has been slain thanks
G that was very very productive no
problem uh
uh
thanks no problem thanks GG just doing
my part
than oh nor I'm out of
Mana
ow I'm living my best life I'm living my
best life she says don't one of these by
okay goodbye
[Music]
oh I can zoom
in I'm
coming oh God oh God looks
funny jungle
attacks is that what you is that what
you
need was that what it was GG jungle
attacks yeah yeah is thatt of League
yeah it's part of the league you know
it's normal you should get used to it
yeah it's a normal thing that everyone
does all right all right all right I
understand now here I don't think so I
don't think the Bots are intelligent
enough for that oh stop him stop him oh
oh wait there's so many of them there's
three people in the
jungle it's okay you distracted them I'm
sure that they won't get the last grub
they're going to go to KI though
woo okay I'm running oh my God they
killed my God you got him kill him kill
him kill him GG jungle tax jungle tax GG
jungle tax jungle tax jungle ta jungle
tax jungle ta J I'm getting the jungler
the jungle TXS a
owie he's
Charmed okay you're crazy do it again uh
give me like five
seconds nice okay bye goodbye you like a
heal or something nah okay that's fine
it is what it is that's fine so when
they do damage to the to the Jungle
people jungle animals don't die can you
like kill kill them and then steal their
kill yeah you can steal the the jungle
animal M that's a
strat well that's why you always want to
fight objectives and take it from
them yeah level seven let me have your
let me have this no
please let me have your
blue oh where is he oh he's right there
hit hit it take it
take your blue they're weak we'll fight
it together Voli bear
weak goodbye I'm going this
together okay chunky
wony oh s's also
here hi oh my do that
here oh he's he's flying he's flying oh
oops he's flying
did you hear that so cute she just
jumped up chiring home oops don't press
buttons thank
you she wants me to watch the
enemy she's so the enemy oh everybody
wants to be my
enemy want to be my enemy she's an
Arcane
hater don't be a hater from League of
Legends yeah from League of Legends from
you know they made a game based off
Arcane oh my
God is to
me you're fake fan fake League fan they
made they made a game based off you
never played this game joining you guys
of course with fake fans what do you
think I'm an Arcane what that sorry
Riot it's my
so come here you little bot got him
clone into get
him
aim whoa what was that he killed you
take away my skins that was like a
wave that's old oh that's his old yeah
uh level eight I love taking your farm I
appreciate that you know someone should
take it I never hit the last hit anyway
so might as
well are you dead no I'm running
down oh are they leaving oh what is he
oh no oh no you don't you don't see me I
I see you though I'm helping I'm helping
I'm helping you're helping you're cra
I'm helping I'm helping ping
nice oh nice nice nice you guys are so
strong oh there's two oh
no no but Gigi said engage even if it's
two at full health don't be afraid do
not be afraid always always greed I'm
not hitting any of my shots that's
fine come be here now okay okay okay
okay ow cleaning up yeah it's my job H
perfectly
plan get almost oh my God nice nice nice
nice nice what who the heck is
that worth G wor what did you do with
war worth let him die that he's a bear
now what really is that still Warwick
yeah that that's still him no it's a
bear why is he AAR
right are they
[Laughter]
Bas fine I'm fine I'm
fine I'll scare him away from the
lane thank you please continue doing so
trying I'm fixing
it
okay is it
fixed ma'am stop it
okay I don't know why that
is are we sure they're Bots yeah we're
sure they're Bots m I'm not sure if I
was a
b an enemy has been
SL pretty
flowers
a what that
do soon okay sorry about the audio
stuff maybe I should reinstall like all
my audio drivers or something yeah ow ow
ow every every single one each one of
them
what's your audio problem every once in
a while since like last week every once
in a while my audio just becomes like
super crunchy but I can't hear it only
chat can hear it for some reason so it's
like what is you know it must be OBS I
don't
know that's interesting oh go go get him
get him get him he'll walk back to
us now it's this good time is any nice
SL live with no
regets so now G when I have like this
much health should I still go home what
is happen to my hold on something is
going on with my computer uh something
very terrible is Happ I admitted
something bad my I think what is
happening my second monitor is
flickering oh God maybe the cable is is
loose crunchy it's it's like look let me
take a video of this so you can see how
cursed this is be so funny if you like
screen
record I'm going to start screen
recording what no that's not going to
work if it's the
monitor okay let me send this to you
uh-oh what what is happening
my computer Al what the hell is
this has problems with conne let me
upload and then send
this
oops speed it up he's at my tower your
team
destroyed there he goes
where' It Go J on
you oh my my goodness what is going on
yay towel broken
finally ooh I don't have boots yet I'm
slow put it here and then I'll also send
to kiaha so you can see thank
you check after the game I I did have a
lot of uh flickering issues yeah do you
see that like what is what is
that's fine just hit it once I'm sure
it's fine oh I'm sure you're okay o yeah
yeah yeah it's fine it's fine don't
worry don't worry no it's fine it's fine
I think it's okay it's fine I'm pretty
sure it's fine yeah yeah we're
winning I'm glad it's okay and nothing
as bad bad as happening no no it's
fine I don't
like what are these circles and question
marks and x's on my
screen what let me know if it turns into
a blue screen I had that
before I think I can make it through
this League of Legends game yeah yeah be
we'll we'll make it to this I bet it's
Path of Exile it's mad at me oh you are
you do you have Roblox on in this side
as well that's no I don't have Roblox on
today I don't believe that no
very
surprising what it became dark what's
going on my greed I will die now oh my
God down I deserved
it I deserved it for my greed what is
that oh that's his that's pretty
bad
die your
team accidentally flashed I'm already in
the middle I no longer have second
monitor like at all no it's still
flickering but I I just can't use it you
know oh that's okay you don't need a
second I don't need a second monitor you
feel it you
know yeah I feel it I don't need to read
chat
y all right an ally has been slain
what is oh God we're do well is that
Twitter that's flickering on my page
what is oh my God takes another
video puing what is happening be
AF this
enemy hey looks fun
you what do we want to do we're all
we're all doing pretty well there's a
bear you want to do beautiful lady do we
want to go mid and push mid do we want
to push bottom what do we want to do oh
this wait they're all here no I don't
I'm here
I'm I'm here let's go let's go let's go
okay okay okay I'm going let's go go
[Music]
in okay I'll get him I'm pressing get
him yay you got it
nice get this one get G I'm dead you got
this though you got it yeah good job
okay okay Quadra kill wo wo wo the panta
the P being left over what the
hell what's going on what he run to wait
guys oh yeah you you got him everyone
running you all running
behind no keep oh nice shot
G I'm too far I'm too slow still running
he's just baiting you
goodbye my War your team has
destroyed very nice you guys are just in
their base destroying things it's
amazing that's
beautiful would it make sense like if
you just kill one lane and then ignore
the other turrets and then you go into
the base you could do that but um why
don't people do that that should be a
thing oh the more people that are in a
lane the you have to split XP with them
I just put that on the outside so if
everyone went mid and tried to push
mid in theory it sounds like a great
idea it sounds like a great idea yeah
but if you're all level one oh the the
the single person in that lane on their
side is going to level faster than you
and everyone else is getting lots of exp
free fire
wow good job my poor poor
computer oh no I did my thing chat it's
okay we've almost
W yes oh what's this it's so it's
fine will I ever hit and ignite I don't
think so wait how
W she's singing oh that's you right I
was like am I singing yeah she's a
singer he's Charming he's Charmed
Charmed
[Music]
y's hey
SN she's a singer himer
Dinger nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice
nice this is so nice we're so good oh
here we can end yay end
yay come out twin she's a
singer we won yay
we Yi my was
too my
clone good job y good work everyone
good keep up the good work all right I
got a dash nice game byee for thanks for
playing
everyone byebye bye-bye bye-bye bye is
everybody just is this that's the same
one for oops what yeah I think I need to
restart my computer I really don't know
what is going on it really is not having
a good time
I mean you played really well all things
considered yeah yeah it's just it's just
my second monitor something's happening
to
it I can't explain your
problem I can't either I can't explain
my problem either have you tried turning
it off and on again yeah to help you've
got it good job today got
yay thanks for joining PR you save the
day
thanks k for joining thank you for
playing with us
did she's like in a coma she Wes up what
did I do
what I mean it would have just been a
bot otherwise right no it would have
been a random person yeah I think it's
it was very nice that you join I love
playing with you yeah join us again
sometime sure thank you
for we can we can Bot game
your hand and I can teach you
yeah the noncom
sure okay bye everyone thanks for
playing
bye byee
bye oh that's turning is that normal
well how do I make it go away there we
go
okay there we go thanks for
watching wait did I leave yes okay um
that was
that wait no the game's still going stop
stop stop kill it exit now do you want
yes exit Okay um thanks for the thank
you for watching um
um that
was uh I had a fun time was nice I like
playing with the other girls um um
that's that's what I'm
thinking I do think that I am not that
good so but you know it's fine we're
just playing for
fun it's very not serious I think today
before the stream started I had
completely forgotten how to play it so I
did like a bot game and the Bots were
killing me so you know it's uh um but
yeah I have learned no not too much
greed unless I listen to Gigi and I have
learned certain
I have not learned how to use ignite I
don't get it I feel like very of maybe
I'm pressing the wrong button but very
often I feel like I'm pressing it and
they're in my range and just nothing
happens I don't know and sometimes I use
it by accident oh in my GRE flows
through you yes yes yeah what thank you
thank youas thank you very much for
hanging out I know these type of like
like a I feel like bigger collab games
in general I kind of can't really look
at chat that much but thank you for
helping me with the audio issues I don't
know what to do I will probably
reinstall my audio drivers and see if
that fixes it it must be OBS because
first I thought it was my first it was
always the game audio right so I thought
it was maybe the the the the my game
like the way I captured the screen of my
gaming PC but today it was Discord as
well um so yeah must be OB or something
in my main PC so yeah I'll I'll I'll see
what it is maybe o yeah but I don't
really have any audio stuff on OBS so
that's weird maybe it's the go XLR when
in doubt always blame no I don't think
it's the go XLR has nothing to do with
it okay I'll figure it out and um thank
you very much I have to reinstall my I
have to do fresh install on my PC
anyways to be honest I got like a bunch
of new parts I mean it's basically a new
pc My Stream at PC not my gaming PC and
and I was so lazy and I had so much to
do so I was just like I'll just use what
I have but I should probably do a fresh
in so oh well have you been chewing
cables no no no no of course no how did
you know no no I have not that's not
been it but there is a lot of my setup
is a little bit scuffy just because of
the way it is maybe I'll try fixing it
okay I see you all tomorrow
for uh I don't remember what time I
think 8:00 p.m. c will be doing a movie
watch along M stream of I eat eat your I
am eating
H loving eating let me eat your pancreas
that's that's the real name of the movie
and then I have never seen it I don't I
don't know anything about it I just know
that it's always been uh I wanted to
watch a
movie no I wanted to watch an anime and
then I I wanted to watch like a
emotional thingy and then I just picked
suggestions off of air you know air
200 five and then uh that one came up
yeah so we'll see apparently it's really
good I've only heard good things and
when I say heard I mean I've looked at
the review which we'll see and then
after that at midnight I will Justice
will be joining Minecraft and we have
some tour guides that will show us the
Ian Minecraft server so that's nice nice
so I'll see you then thank you very much
for hanging out and
byebye my tummy hurts I'm
hungry byebye
[Music]