[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
hello
oh sure
Barbie
[Music]
ah chat
foreign
[Music]
because
I don't know
I have very very rarely feel like it but
today I felt like wow I'm announcing
something
you know
how you guys doing
you know you you are all here today to
hear an announcement from me possibly
um however I will only be able to
announce it if I
uh can clear stage three and four
apparently
well you know even if I can't clear it
uh by midnight I will announce it so
[\h__\h] it
um
uh I just tried
um a little test uh money run because I
thought I might wanna buy even more
stop asking about the second hat
I burnt it
it wasn't as much as other people are
getting but I only played on stage two
so maybe that's why but I had I had
everything you know I was playing with
Reina and I had I had the green sticker
and I had the super tattoo timer and I
had
um another thing that's like for Super
Chat for for coins I think I had like
free free
passive skills for coins I had
everything
um
oh we have a problem the latency you
know when I make a new stream instead of
copying the settings
it always changes back to normal latency
ex instead of extremely low latency and
normally yeah piggy bank I also had that
instead of
ah the extremely low latency I forgot it
I forgot to change it
today you have to change it before
starting the stream which why why can I
not
change it anymore missing hello
I may have been missing Hollow yeah
but I also I have again I I gave myself
like haste and stuff
um this and that I think it was an
interesting combination of things
um
uh but drop the piggy bank what do you
mean I did have a piggy bank
I did use the piggy bank
are you why are you saying dad like drop
the piggy bank give me your money or are
you saying like Piggy Bank not good
you can make an instrument and rate it I
saw it didn't work nah I don't want to
do it we'll stay here it's okay like I
mean you know I shouldn't always be so
dependent anyway
uh coin upgrade from shop I don't know
no wait let me let me show you again
let's see I I made a little bit of money
okay not like in the millions by far I
made just a little bit of money and
we'll get some upgrades of that and
we'll see how it goes
yes yes
uh uh
oh
turn on the fan too
nice nice
[Music]
there it is
spicy oh we want it to be smaller
[Music]
somewhere here okay
well the house makes a [\h__\h] ton of money
I saw that you can make a lot of money
with fishing apparently
[Applause]
anyway
[Music]
shiny spicy story
strong Independence what but I had it it
was good it was good it came kind of
late but still an eight-chunk killed me
it was going so well and then suddenly
didn't I kill hm before though this time
I couldn't handle her
I was not able to hmm
anyway let's see yeah okay 23 000 that's
like I expected a million like in all
those money Strat videos they promised
me a million and I only got like 24K huh
what the first one is maybe we'll spend
the whole stream fishing no wait it's
not about making money it's not about
making money it's about clearing stage
three and four
[Music]
anyway because I I still need to try out
new characters
um so yeah
so yeah I can still wow
maybe before going into money game one
more I think I should upgrade some of
the smaller ones because
I I need to I need to it's not about the
money that much it's about clearing free
and foreign money
no wait wait maybe not no no no no no no
no we got time we got time
we've got all time of the day maybe uh
one of the speeds
and
um
25 holy [\h__\h]
and then some cheaper ones
sure uh three thousand
foreign okay
okay
yeah
let's check out the whole house haven't
been here in a while
hold a house
hello oh my God they're all dead
no do I have food still
manage okay so clownfish
I don't have
but can I feed them something else no oh
wait I do I do oopsie I thought the zero
was I don't have it he needs 11.
no thank God okay uh how does this look
again how do I ah okay
oh level up okay you need shrimps
okay you need wheat I don't have that
much but it's enough
ah tomato
oh wait I'm looking at
I'm looking at the EXP right now I
thought I was looking at I'm so confused
who's exhausted you waffle waffle waffle
we kind of feed the waffle man so that
he continues to provide us waffles
I wonder
what the kfb who weren't here last time
by now heard about them being my workers
in the game
like one of the man spade Cinder Heidi
17 are you here
are you here guys how can you not be
here when you're literally working for
me
should be here
are you stuck in the game Spade is here
and hello at least one person
oh hello say something
say something I'm giving up on you I
don't see you
where are you
stayed at my blind
they can't type their work
okay I guess I mean it makes a lot of
sense
good to know
oh
okay
lurkers lurkers are also welcome of
course now
uh damn
how's this work again I can fish right
how do I fish I forgot let's not miss
another shiny shall we
uh
what uh
sorry I I needed to um
I needed to
remember how this works
I I can't [\h__\h] believe that I got a
shiny on my first try when I still
didn't know how this game works
so then I obviously missed the shiny
like that makes me so mad that I wanna
ask Caillou to give me another shiny
because like come on come on where's the
tutorial huh before giving me a shiny
it's not fair it's like literally
taunting and teasing me
that was fast
tuna
we got the only kind of fish a little
bit for the food for the chickens you
know
English also because I'm low-key
stalling
took you six hours
same habit the solar Senpai no way eh
her first fish was also shiny
hey come on
that can't be
a thing that happens so easily tell the
fishes gives you good money
oh yeah true even these normal fishings
should I not feed them to the chicken so
the chickens suffer
well I should I should honestly just get
higher chickens is that the Strat I
should only hire chickens who
um
who eat wheat and tomatoes and stuff so
no fish no fish liking chickens Maybe
is the way to go
so that I can sell all my fish
um
it always changes oh really I didn't
notice oh my God that one's fast
ah
why is this one so fast when does it end
why is this why was this so difficult
the food changes per level
I'm not good at this stuff man bye-bye
Wayne
imagine gives you a lot of coins too oh
really
because I'm using a video oh yeah how do
I get the better rods hmm
does it cost money
[Music]
when you feel
at least it's not shiny you know wait
how do I know that again I don't even
remember what made it look like a shiny
I love tuna though I don't mind just
getting normal sooner I like tuna
tuna
together with salmon is like my favorite
fish I think to eat
what do you say
for me the favorite way to eat Tunas on
a pizza I think two
Pizza I know I know some people think
it's weird because you've never had it
before but it's amazing
Luna's all right eh
oh God
of someone
um
purposefully lagging their PC
opening a million windows
[Music]
so that it would lack whole look here
did you see that so that they wouldn't
have such a hard time anymore
uh with this rhythm game
I had like maybe oh my God this is so
late they started to they had like maybe
five thousand no okay not five thousand
maybe like 100 windows open Maybe
big brain
oh basically
[Music]
cheating but it's a great idea so
I'll give them that
that's just that no
no big brain when you can win with your
skills you gotta use your brain you know
there's there's two different kinds of
people in this world
although with brain comes skill you know
different kind of skill
there's the big brain people and then
there's uh I don't know just I'm gonna
punch everything that's in my way and
that will fix everything in front of
people
if you know what I mean
for a piece of corn and cooking cream
what the [\h__\h]
yes okay cooking cooking your mother I
can't imagine
hey what's good so so [\h__\h] well come
on why how many
every time I get to that like whew
that like oh my God I can't I can't I
can't
uh no how would I do what do I do
what I do I need to sell a fish but I
um
how do I sell all
there we go I have 35 shrimps
okay so I sell this it gives me
[Music]
uh like 5 000 of that dust okay
change that to
whatever give me I don't know
huh I don't know give me the maximum
weird
I don't know you tell me tell me how
much I can exchange huh
the same exact thing huh
this menu is kind of weird kind of you
I'm gonna tell you that eh no
no use the center by the rod oh
okay okay just fish a bit more we'll
just fish a bit more
this menu is weird
not not user friendly
[Music]
wow this is the system of the latency
ah no idea man no idea
you're telling me
very unfortunate settings today
sand gone yeah
my Ultimate Styling techniques
stop stalling me
Starling why would I be stalling what
no no no no I don't know what you're
talking about
a little easier Over Control to navigate
the menus really
don't sell shrimps workers can't believe
them
I don't know what to prioritize man
it's confusing me when I prioritize
um I also have to buy like fruits with
my holocorn fruit or like veggies
veggies for the
some of the chickens
let her cook
foreign
yeah we might just do another money run
before we get into stage three and four
or or we can try doing a money run in
stage three and four to get you you know
to get kind of useless well who knows
who knows maybe we end up winning stage
three and four accidentally while we're
doing a money run you never know it
doesn't mean that like a a money
strategy makes you weak I mean you
literally built to kill a lot of enemies
to create a lot of coins so
it's not not necessarily a bad strap
when we saw my latency is so low no so
high and so normal today so I will see
your messages very late
keep shrimp tuna and clownfish those are
for chickens shrimp tuna and clownfish
that's all I'm getting though
that's literally all I'm getting
on clownfish oh my God
that is all I'm getting
yeah
huh
the other girls maybe can get me
something better
oh oh that was fast
and Ina is here too
this is so cute
guys did you see like this last last
yeah last weekend now it's Monday the
last couple days
there was Gamescom in Germany
big big event that I suppose it's one of
the few
events in the German speaking world
that people know of
outside of it
[Music]
I've never been there before though and
I only hear bad things about like
I mean yeah I don't actually I never
hear anything positive about it
I was like I guess it's probably like ax
level uh eight X levels of crowded
and people here really don't like it
apparently
um
yeah it's in Colonia yeah some some
people I know went there and so I was
looking at the
at their like posts social media posts
about it
that's not fair it's just not fair
I I'm bad at fishing it seems I'm bad at
fishing
I've heard good things this year
um
I don't know oopsie
I don't know I mean I'm interested to
maybe someday
checking it out but this year was
apparently not the year because I I
found out too late anyway
it was happening
um I wonder maybe at least once I want
to check it out
dream
[Music]
heck new Rod now yes okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
and then you know another cool
convention was happening that I was
thinking of going to
there was another cool convention you
know Europe has some really unique
conventions
mmm
do I still have tomatoes
ah I kind of do
there is a convention in the Netherlands
that oh that's a lot oh wow surprising
actually oh [\h__\h]
um
there's a convention in the Netherlands
that
uh
it's it's like you know there's like
this big venue where there's like a big
indoor pool
thing like that's just one pool it's
like yeah it's like huge okay
um
let's just get the normal one
and it has like a little little Huts all
over that you can stay in
a little little apartment houses
thingies
dream hack dream hacks nothing special
dreamhack sucks
dreamhacked will never invite me but
European conventions don't give a [\h__\h]
about YouTubers anyway so whatever
um yeah and uh did you hear that so fast
what I just said
I didn't say isn't so bad if you're
laughing because of my dream hack uh
statement
no but yeah it's like you know one of
these like big pool places that are I
think supposed to create some kind of
big uh tropical pool experience with
lots of different
uh lots of different uh pools and yeah
it's like really cool and they have a
convention where they
uh like yeah it's like over the weekend
you can you can stay there you have to
book one of those Huts it's I think a
little bit expensive
you cannot go to the convention unless
you book yourself the that kind of like
um apartment
and accommodation
um but yeah if you have it then you can
go there but it's like so popular it's
like quickly sold out
and I'll be honest I was thinking of
going there I I had my group even
I was gonna go there
but then I heard about the pretty strict
rules
uh
so
like during the day even though they
booked this venue for the convention
during the day they actually
um still have normal visitors okay but
because of the normal visitors during
the day they don't allow like all the
cosplayers and photographers to take
photos only in the early morning at like
what 6 a.m or something for like two or
three hours and then in the evening when
everybody's gone all the normal visitors
must be gone
so that's pretty lame because that's a
really short time window and you have to
get up really freaking early and you
know you know cosplayers take a lot of
time too to
yeah to get ready and like ah and then
so late too oh my God and then there's
only a specific area apparently where
you can take photos like uh in Cosplay
like in the water besides that you have
to take it outside the world so what's
that even what what do you think people
go there for like obviously because of
the location I think a lot of the people
who go there are less normal convention
goers and more like photographers and
cosplayer groups you know this is not I
would say it's not really a normal
convention surely there's some normal
visitors too but I think a lot of people
will go there for the location trying to
take cool pictures
um
but anyway that's kind of lame and yeah
[Music]
yeah so and yeah also it was kind of
like
stressful uh
in general with my schedule and some
other reasons why I decided not to call
[Laughter]
uh yeah so I didn't go but my friends
some of my friends are there and I I'm
still like in the Planning Group that we
had opened the planning chat
um
where they were oops [\h__\h]
where they were planning everything and
now they're like posting photos and
stuff of them having fun and they look
like they're having fun they look like
they're having a good time
good for them
good for them but even getting there
looked like a pain in the ass without
the cards like really difficult and
well not really difficult it's not
impossible dude
there's conventions I've been to that
are probably worse in terms of how to
get there
um ah what was I doing is anyone
exhausted no okay
give me that money oh this is really no
but I didn't realize when I first
started this that they actually create a
good amount of money
Can you hire new workers wait how many
Is It Anyway that how many was the
maximum I think isn't this the maximum
oh no it just costs a lot of money was
that the issue
10 is the maximum oh let's see who we
have for camping we have Annie Ming are
you here I should make a rule where if
the person isn't in the chat I'm not
hiring them
but then can I re-roll it though
anime where are you
you better be here
hmm
but if you're not in the chat I will
also fire you from Cafe just kidding you
can walk from one end of the country to
the other so nowhere is that hard to get
to I mean
uh wait are they here
I don't see any Ming in here
fine I guess I'll hire you anyway
uh can I wait let me see if I can
actually buy the rod now before I waste
all my money
rename them into someone who's actually
here but that feels kind of sad too
though
oh bye uh dad's Rod okay ah wait I need
to exchange right what it's three
thousand
and the blacksmith made Atlantean
should I just should I save up for a
better one or should I get
whatever's next you tell me
while I go to the workers again no
actually here
oh I didn't know that you can run faster
oh
um get the next one that's
sell your fish yeah okay
foreign
don't eat the tomatoes they they look
like berries but they're not really
berries
trust me
that is good get the next one okay well
we'll see how much I get if I
uh
sell the fishies but wait wait wait
first I saw someone's exhausted
this doesn't feel like we're playing
hola cure right now at all does it
okay tomatoes
brings them a level up too now he wants
two now all right
is that it yeah okay
[Music]
what do you mean this is the main game
anyway I've been seeing like lots of fun
conventions happening but speaking of
convention
um
speaking of conventions
[Music]
this weekend is a convention in Toronto
that I'm part of
okay
[Music]
uh I I scheduled Final Fantasy 16 over
it because I was not made aware of the
time there was some miscar ly or like
Miss um somebody wasn't Tagged
so uh I found out after I made the
schedule
um but I I'm trying to basically for me
the panel will end at 8pm my time and
you guys said that the first like intro
Final Fantasy 16 you can kind of play it
in four hours
so I'm thinking maybe maybe I'll just um
I'll maybe I'll play it afterwards
if the panel ends at eight maybe I can
play from 8 30
onwards I think that could work uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah
uh wait so we want if we can get 15 000
that would be good but I doubt it
I'll just get this oh wait no we could
maybe no no we can't we'll we would get
like I don't know 12 000 13 000.
makes sense it's possible
if you want of course yeah because I
feel bad for like
moving it around so much and and and
canceling it so often so will you feel
up to it afterwards sure sure I think so
oh that's fine I mean the convention the
panel is just like a little bit under an
hour anyway so it's no problem
um maybe the fishing Offspring no
no what do you mean me should I just end
my stream now and now fish and then I'll
come back later and starting my stream
again no
about what's what a stupid idea fishing
is that other people other people
literally Fish hours and hours in their
streams and you're telling me to not do
it what what
kind of double standards
are those huh
let's see how the dad Rod is different
how is it different
is it gonna make me struggle more or
what or does it just give me better fish
access to betta fish
still a clownfish
we have an announcement yeah but I'm
preparing for
good gameplay
that was fast
[Music]
it's so long I like eel I forgot to
mention eel when I said salmon and tuna
are my favorite fish because
we don't really have access to eel like
eel isn't really a common thing in an
Austrian foofs
I love to eat eel in Japan though
Lobster let's go let's go
have you guys had unagidon before
it's one of the foods I I tell you to
eat when you go to Japan I I must say
you have to eat it at least once but
it's kind of expensive usually a little
bit expensive you can get some cheaper
ones here there and they're still good
though
depending on the place you go to
depending on the restaurant hmm
I love katadon yes yes
okay
going going well let me see what you
guys got
[Music]
do I still have clownfish I do right
yeah see I left some for you just for
you oh and you're not even in the chat
second time in the row
Unforgivable
unforgiving girls
who knows the song
knows that
you got A plus point in my books if you
know it
I'm forgiving and forgiving and
believing
oh my God why does nobody know it oh my
God I need to force I need to force Cape
up down your throats
soon
at least there was like two people yes
yeah ah here they come yes
and somebody just automate this can I
upgrade Caillou you need to make an
upgrade like after like a certain amount
of effort you put into this Farm you
should be able to upgrade it so that it
happens it's like it plants everything
that you have automatically I don't mind
if it's like an expensive feature for
the player
make him spend like
um 20 000 Holo coins or or more I guess
that's fine that's fine
[Music]
while I ask you for cheats again no I'm
just enhancing the game
so far no workers asked for the other
Foods yet
I wonder
so for now I'm just
planting the usual
[Music]
no pressure yes pressure
look at the fish
[Music]
keyboard much faster but I'm using a
keyboard
tomato
I ran out of tomatoes
oh no
[Music]
we also want to hire one more here who's
gonna be
foreign
[Music]
it's a very very special honor
um
not here unbelievable
[Music]
well now you're here in my game forever
and you'll be working 24 7.
[Music]
congratulations
the problem with this is
I'm like endlessly stuck in here
I want to be recruited well you didn't
sign up for it did you huh
should have thought about that earlier
when they had a sign up form up there
very unfortunate
should have had your eyes open all the
time be ready for it hmm
I'm always rename that them no that's
just that you know when you get that
lucky to actually
oh God I was I was on edge just now holy
[\h__\h]
and when you actually get the chance
you know to put in your name and then
you actually
find yourself in my stream I think that
would make you very happy and then it
would make you very sad if I changed the
name so I'm not gonna do that
oh wow
okay I swear I'm gonna start playing
soon
TM
[Music]
m
soon not selling
[Music]
okay
let me just let me just plant a few more
Tomatoes okay just a few more just a
little bit
this is a tiny bit why why isn't there
why doesn't it take longer for
everything
like it should take longer
for the workers to become exhausted and
it should take longer for this Farm to
become anything at all
so that I can go out and play
the game without feeling
you know worried about
stuff going down here
uh
okay tomato
mm-hmm
clownfish
I only have one because I sold it
I guess you're gonna die I guess I'll
die
kfp being like yes I'll die
oh you want Tomatoes uh-huh
changing your taste buds quickly aren't
you
stardio is that how I start you what is
it stadio Valley makes you feel like
five hours later
a little bit more
even I put my name in I checked
I want to find you
and then bind you legally uh to me with
a working contract
find you and bind you and then bind you
to a chair with some ropes and I never
met you leave
[Music]
okay
ah I will go I will go okay I'm leaving
ah
so
let's go what do we do people said this
could be good for some more money
um
let's see after powerful singing the
sun's package for three seconds this was
someone's big nuts that slam down oh
come on
dealing 400 damage to all Giants around
you just want
to show that's why you said play these
two why does Lisa better at this than
others
tell me
um I guess this does not slamming I
don't know no it doesn't even say that
it gives you coins like like container
why why why why why why
[Music]
I've heard people use azuki too nowadays
yeah
Santa Claus have a circle of probably on
stage lights damaging okay why why why
why is this because okay this was fast
yeah I guess so
what makes what makes azuki
so good at this
you just have ah she does have all the
corn skills
okay
let's try
shall we right away go into
page free how do I know that I've
cleared it before
wait have I not cleared stage for free
before because like doesn't that mean
because I have stage four that I cleared
stage free I don't know
I don't know how it works did I never
clear it before like I personally feel
like I didn't but
um
I think it might have it would say
cleared below the picture
but I cleared stage one before is this
character specific
you've played stage three but not stage
four oh really uh it's character
specific okay I don't remember clearing
stage three
at all
but then let's give it a try let's see
if I can do it again haha we'll go
I've played it before because I remember
some of this
and I've never clear I don't I mean
apparently I have but I don't remember
it okay DLC gain one hollow coin every
three seconds after gaining Hollow coins
five times create another issue for 15
seconds dealing 40 of your weapon damage
so I copy paste myself
for 15 seconds
okay so I just constantly threw out the
whole
playthrough I get one hollow coin every
three seconds
change okay I don't know if this is
currently a money run I guess it is but
if we can finish the stage that would be
cool too these
inflicts internal damage
internal internal
I guess that's good
naughty this is main weapon has a 10
chance to inflict damage equal to 25
percent of a non-boss targets HP
oh is that I guess that's good like we
want her main skills and the other
typical like money Super Chat
skills I suppose if I say hello I'll
take Halu right if I see superchato time
and I see I take super time oh don't say
so again
if I see
tell me what I should be looking out for
because with these latency issues we're
gonna have some troubles guys
what I want to get the the piggy bank
and Halu and Super Chat and anything
besides that
it's not a money run if you don't have
restricted weapons
[Music]
foreign
chance
Target explodes into nuts that scattered
dealing 60 of main weapon damage each oh
sure
okay if it failed this I can do the
thing with the money restriction but why
why is it because if not money was the
weapon is searching is it because
oh wait that was credit card what does
that do again is it because if I do that
I'll only get like all the passives that
I want
instead of having all the the weapon
options is that what you you're trying
to
accomplish with that
many reasons
yeah great stamp I know about that
um oh wait my special is ready
let's do it again oh my God
okay they just fall down on like random
locations okay
that's fine that's fine uh great step
only affects Primary Weapons so you
wanted to get as many hits as possible
oh which won't happen if you collapse ah
well you can still do money runs about
it
I didn't realize that oh
[Music]
so having collabs and stuff
kind of is in the way though
number three what what did I take guys
I'm sorry you guys are so behind because
I [\h__\h] up the settings
you'll get so frustrated by my choices
uh yes
um I suppose the yes was for
you guys if you if you write something
like yes or no you have to also give me
some context there because I will forget
what I talked about 15 seconds ago
look at that
whoa nice nice crack
feels good
that's good I know I shouldn't do it so
it feels good it feels [\h__\h] good okay
oh
it's just a random [\h__\h] greed lying
around here
as if like
somebody just placed it there
purposefully
for knowing that knowing I'm doing this
wow
well we might as well take it
damage now
it doesn't really clearly say it there
huh wait I'm dying I need some HP [\h__\h]
where's food
or should I take something defensive
maybe now
man I'm dying already and there's no
food around
nice find right yo
yeah Greece said so early in my last
money run I got it like in the last five
minutes
now defensive okay thank you for giving
me context
okay I went through this too yeah
I feel very insecure right now oh my God
Square open I just realized there's like
so many squirrels around I think I know
why they're oh food I think I know why
they're trying to get me because of what
I did in Baldur's Gate oh my God
oh more food okay nice I'll keep the
other one around I'll be very aware of
its location
I'll just I'll just keep on updating
upgrading these ones for now
because I think that's good to do
did you see that no it is
I don't say it hello
everybody
let's go I'm going to die let's go let's
go
let's go let's go
it's okay if I die I'm just here to make
money oh my God
I really want soup potato time because
that one picks up the coins
automatically right I really want that
I don't have to run to them
should I oh should I go speed up maybe
I think I think you guys are telling me
yes but I don't see it yet because now
you're reacting to Halu
early hello
level two or three is already huge
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
speed up yeah oh my God thank you for
providing context so I know you were
talking about this now
you know speaking of Baldur's Gates
I wasn't
my mildly annoyed today when I watched
the comment section of about their skate
clip
um should I upgrade greed I don't know
I'll put it in a normal spot for now
there was a clip of me reacting to the
ogre scene
from like yesterday
[Music]
um
and
it's really like you guys I think you
can tell
that I was genuinely thinking they were
fighting or something
uh
or like walking around in the Huts it
took me quite a while like the narrator
has to point it out
yeah the narrative had to point it out
that there's something else going on
there and I
didn't realize I would dumped about it
okay
but then like I see the comments and
there's like somebody like this is why
not this is why I don't watch Kiara
because her reactions are so fake what
my reaction
I really didn't know
it was I was really mildly annoyed at
that and really wanted to reply like
hello how do you know if my rashes are
fake like this is legit like why would I
fake my reactions anyway
who can keep up with that [\h__\h] man I
can't stream constantly faking
everything I hate taking [\h__\h]
it's faking anything I hate lying to you
guys so much
I prefer to just if there's something I
have to lie about I prefer to just not
talk about it at all this is stressful I
don't like lying to you guys
Ah that's awakened
I guess that's what we're gonna do
wow that's a lot of nuts let's go
peanuts
it's just ah I just don't like it when
you know somebody basically claims I'm
not genuine but I'm very [\h__\h] genuine
I'm keeping it real guys you know that
right you know that
yeah yeah waking my nuts hey
uh Hollow level three let's go
[Music]
no no no no no no no no I can't I'm
scared I'm scared
yeah there were some other comments that
annoyed me too badly only mildly only
mildly of course
and I really you know it's hard to hold
back sometimes
to react to and comment on this comments
but
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh my God
the Earth is shaking from too much money
maybe I should increase my speed with a
ninja headband what do you think yeah
what the heck
I get annoyed at Clips myself
I'm not even blaming the clip of that
one because you could say oh the context
was missing maybe a little bit but I
think mostly the clip doesn't take away
too much context the clip wasn't in the
back in in the in the wrong or anything
ah
one hello
no I'm thinking the ninja yeah I'm like
wow
ninja actually with me copying
copying myself into however many wishes
actually it makes sense I feel very much
like a ninja Rider oh my God I'm dying
oh my God I can't die right now I can't
die right now I can't die right now I
want to survive I got all the hollow at
the all the money making things please
please
[Music]
how
help you guys are saying too well what
are you saying what are you saying guys
and headband is merely only what what
does that mean
s
oh wow it's too late now
it doesn't work on this so she doesn't
want me water okay
oh
my God that was food
wait so you shouldn't be throwing nuts
you should be throwing like bricks or
something else man nuts don't do damage
to people right you realize that right
peanuts are very very very
light weighted
sure okay let's let's keep the nuts
let's keep the nuts coming let's keep on
coming and they don't stop coming
let's go nuts I'm going nuts oh my God
sometimes I think I'm at a different
research it's confusing
oh oh I forgot my special
uh you you you I'm gonna wait for you
guys here I'm gonna give you some time
they do emotional damage don't you don't
they do internal damage
these
I think I know if that was for me but
yeah what do we upgrade
I'm just gonna upgrade mommy water I
don't know
grab those rock hard knots let's go
[Music]
they look like rocks in in the special
okay
they look like
um
yeah you have meter what's that mean
what does that mean
s
oh my God copies
take damage uh instead of me this is
what's happening
don't you want to upgrade your greed
uh uh maybe
idle song Too
pillow uh-huh
you used it it's okay are you mean with
Mita you mean my my special
[Applause]
no not the one thing cool I'll take it
anyway
that I
made the mistake taking
okay at least we've got some other super
cool special stuff
oh this is creating a lot of coins right
now no noise somebody's not glow stick
right
glossic and warming water is that a
collab that was possible I don't
remember actually but these
these yeah I already have the glow stick
anyway
it does make you faster at least yeah
right yeah okay see yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's what I wanted out of it anyway
the speed was the thing that spoke to me
in the first place
and you really need some help Adam okay
I'll keep my eyes out for it but damn
I'm so happy
uh let's upgrade but does it make sense
now because you guys said greeds well
it only works for melee attacks
I might as well strengthen it
yes okay
remember there's food there
it's gone somewhat well so far quite all
right
drop those nuts
no great and um
upgrading green still good
great main weapon headband is really
depends on
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and I know
about the Mad Band now
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm give me food please
somebody
[Music]
okay
I need more pool drops
[Music]
it wouldn't be so many enemies if I
wouldn't have chosen Halu huh but I'm
still handling it I'm still handling it
somewhat well
oh hey one tangent I wanted to tell you
guys about and I totally forgot about it
is I went out to see the
[Music]
oh two or three
I went to see the Barbie movie and of
course I dressed up in pink
as much as I could
looked really cute
Barbie Barbie
and then bend it
yeah and I didn't know what to expect to
be honest my I went with a friend who
already watched it like uh that was the
first time or I think at that point
she said she would watch it again and
again and again because she loves it so
much I was like okay okay I would
personally normally not really go back
into the movie theater to re-watch the
same movie that I saw like a week ago or
so
normally I wouldn't do that
four times get it over with
but I mean
that's
when you're ready to do that must be in
the movie is really good
yeah so I I don't know I expected like
something really tacky
but oh
nothing that I already have
did I re-wall maybe yeah or go for a new
collabo
where are you wrong okay
maybe idle costume
so I can spam my special more not sure
We Roll again are you saying real again
or number three
[Music]
okay one more
[Applause]
okay
and yeah so this movie oh my God it has
like so many famous actors and singers
they I don't know if it's considered a
musical but they do sing a lot in this
movie is that a musical automatically
just by them singing a lot
well not necessarily themselves singing
but just like a lot of music is being
used in it how do I reach this Anvil man
I can't reach it
and Ryan Gosling played Ken I I don't
I've seen the face of the lady who plays
Barbie the classic Barbie before but I
don't remember her name to be honest
what was it
another one
ah
can't reach it
ah there we go it's like stuck in the
middle of the between the chairs and the
table what the [\h__\h]
my good Robbie that's it yeah Margaret
she's really pretty
and she's really cute and I think she
was like the perfect
Barbie like she had the perfect face and
her acting was really good
did I upgrade the potato time no more
yeah
let's do it
um
[Music]
I don't think I ever saw that before are
you guys sure I cleared this stage
before
and then watch it you should it's
actually like I don't know the first
impression maybe tells you oh this is a
good movie but uh I've heard of you know
good good feedback from
um men as well you know
you have station long so yeah I guess so
okay okay
I guess so
um anyway what was I saying I am so oh
my God I I was so happy to see
um the actor uh I don't know his name
but the actor from
uh Arrested Development in there one of
the main characters from Arrested
Development
the the Sun
I love him and I feel like they gave him
uh the perfect role
to play oh my God
[\h__\h] Ducks everywhere dance
stop stop
you
[Music]
it's whistle is whistle
flat
not X Oxo yeah Michael Farah Michael
Sarah I love him and yeah the character
he played is so funny because like in in
the I I won't spoil anything but
basically it starts out in the Barbie
and Ken world right so basically
everybody is a some kind of Barbie and
everybody is some kind of Ken
there's supposedly nothing else there
but there's one random Allen there which
I guess was also something uh that
really existed and Alan uh oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
I didn't see this Circle anymore so I
thought it's to go in
no
but it was just the circle disappeared
and then he immediately did the big
attack no
oof one more
yeah yeah uh it's okay it's okay we're
having fun I'm having fun
yeah what the [\h__\h] I thought it was safe
to go in
the classic I blame out don't blame Alan
well Alan is like the only one who isn't
a Barbie or a Ken
and he's like
trying to fit in I guess okay we're not
We're Not Gonna Take the ninja headband
then this time okay okay
um and he just plays those really
awkward
isolated role when I really really like
him it's just like he he's
similar to
um
to his uh Arrested Development character
I think in my opinion oh turn off
weapons person shot ah okay
doesn't that cost something though
oh no it doesn't limit the max number of
weapons
this one
the max number I thought it's like no
wait which one
why why do I do this
I started limits
to not use any weapons at all
ah
I should just get all of them so I don't
get any weapons over
okay
so only like supportive items
right
okay
yeah anyway uh back to the Barbie movie
so it starts off like for the most most
of the time like really oh
really funny and comedic and they start
with this like and oh introduction song
um
that they repeat over the beginning of
the movie like three times but they
changed the lyrics each time and it's
like fitting to what's going on in the
scenes that was one of my favorite
things it's like so funny oh my God why
are all these like I guess because no
weapons
I was wondering what was appearing so
easily right away
yeah the narrator singer that was so
funny
and uh generally all the songs are
really good
uh and oh my God at home the dances were
so fun and all the all the cans and the
Barbies were so funny and then I was
shocked because when they left I don't
want to spoiler anything you know but
you know eventually they leave the
Barbie world
um they're like on the mission you know
and
uh I am I was really surprised because I
last year or so I think I binge watched
um Superstore on Netflix
you guys know Superstore
it's just another
I guess sitcom comedy American Comedy
Show about uh like a Walmart basically
no it's not real spoilers you don't know
anything about the plot really yeah
it's in a trailer there you go see it's
in the trailer it's in the trailer
yeah so there's an actress a main
actress in Superstore uh who plays one
of the main roles in the Barbie movie so
I saw so many familiar faces
in this movie is fascinating damn they
must have had an insane amount of budget
holy moly
so the acting was was really good too
let me tell you that
was so funny have you watched Parks and
Rec yes some of my favorite shows to
re-watch and binge watch I love that the
first time I saw it I still love it now
I love that kind of humor and I love
those kind of like like the office and
Parks and Rec you know they're like
these shows that
want to give you the feeling that oh you
are
um watching them work basically
what was it a mockumentary
so funny 145 million can be precise oh
my God now what I found interesting is
because when I was watching I didn't
know that the movie was actually made by
the company that's behind Barbie I
didn't know that
um but I thought that they must have at
least gotten permission from them
uh to do what they're doing
uh but then throughout the movie they
were like moments where they uh really
criticized
the Barbie company
quite seriously
um and yeah I was like yeah they can't
there's no way that they would allow
that right
so that's that's really it yeah Mattel
yeah they were they were criticizing
themselves in the movie like pointing
out
what what they're like yeah doing wrong
so take some balls to do that
surprisingly Ken's and Barbies don't
have balls well especially Barbies don't
have balls but
you know what I mean
if they seem to have balls
that's cool for them to let that in I I
thought so too
but yeah I just really loved all the
jokes and interactions what is this what
is this what is this green circle
excuse me let that beat or something
I have to go for all the time these are
all things that I want
um
now I would definitely recommend this
movie I was even I was really surprised
it was like a moment where I even cried
in the Barbie movie and I'm surely not
the only one I didn't expect that but
there was a uh okay there's just there's
the scene I won't tell you what it's
about but the the the superstore lady
she makes a speech you know anybody who
watched the movie will know probably
what I'm talking about
you
um yep I cried the Barbie it's so good
oh my god let's go
crying together
the movie theater I'm feeling awkward
about it acting like you're not crying
let's go
yeah there's this there's this scene
where
um yeah the superstore actress she puts
makes this whole speech and it kind of
oh my God it was so intense you know
that anime scene where there's this like
they were in this kitchen and people
love this anime scene because of the the
emotion in this endless dialogue from
this one character lady ranting and
ranting and ranting
um
it was kind of like Dad like she went on
an endless rant
but this one hit so hard to home to home
man it hit so hard
you want glasses Halloween nurse horns
now class is Halloween I don't have any
of that here
these
Phil and Phil Phil and and my sandwiches
uh sentences
these
[Music]
nah I don't know
I guess piggy bank
[Music]
oh
I guess that actually makes sense now
for now for now
kind of want to get pickup range up
because I I low at my pickup range with
the other thing
[Music]
is that okay I'll do it I don't care
I can't wait for your answers anyway all
day
so like you know I wanted you guys to
watch The Lord of the Rings musical but
not everybody can go there because you
gotta go there in person to watch it but
the Barbie movie is everywhere in the
cinema so please go watch it it's really
good don't be embarrassed
or I guess if you don't if you feel too
embarrassed to go to the Barbie movie as
a guy then just wait I guess for until
it's like available online
it's worth it it's so good
you know I know this is supposed to be a
planet but every time I see it maybe
it's the little cat lady brain inside of
me but I feel like it looks like a like
a wool ball that cats play with
I'm not that interested in but it's
really good
give it a chance
not for me how do you know
no you and you didn't watch it it's it's
it was very different you know from my
expectations it was it was really funny
to if you like funny movies you will
like it okay don't let yourself be
thrown off just because oh there's a
Barbie and Ken
it's genuinely a really funny
movie
period
I thought it was a yarn bowl yeah that's
what it looks like right but it's a
planet I'm pretty sure because it's a
reference to Sana
because B it makes your attacks bigger
so it's a reference to Sana
and confirm fantastic films there you go
thank you
you agree with me it's good right
foreign
yeah it's legit funny right funny as
hell
[\h__\h] yeah
and like
Ryan Gosling is playing the main camera
right I love
okay he
quite the character development
throughout the movie
um
but my God in the beginning I love I
love him the most in the beginning
it has just so much comedic effect
how he acts in the beginning
oh my God he's so dependent on Barbie
that's so funny man I love it
I want to watch it again the movie was
so funny
just bring him back on it now oh my God
oh my God
I was saying to my friend yo I want to
learn these songs
oh
I want to learn these songs
um and sing them in karaoke some of them
at least
the the song where they were playing
guitar on the beat oh my God
the whole scene oh my God therapying
they were being manipulated
all of this will make sense if you watch
the movie you have to watch a movie guys
keep up keep up guys
you gotta keep up keep up
it's definitely gonna be in counterclock
I think so
so probably if I would look now there
might already be some kind of fun and
you know what I love Dua Lipa and Dua
Lipa saying one of the
most important theme songs
oh my God oh my God
[Music]
literal Gosling
man I I don't I I know you know Ryan
Gosling like his whole existence is kind
of a meme
but uh I never really paid much
attention to this movies and and like
who he is and all that but damn this
this was a pleasure to watch
now there were many Gosling moments too
it made me really happy you don't you
don't even
understand
he's literally me is he wait
literally
what about physically
The Outfits too like I love that what is
this green line I love the outfits that
they were
wearing Barbies out to everybody's
outfits oh my God
literally me it's like me for real for
real
on the internet his existence is kind of
a meme
what's wrong me is also mean yeah yeah I
know I know I know I know oh no I
literally live on the internet
I know some things I would hope
I can't believe I'm actually like so
stable even though I
I don't I don't I I don't have any
weapons
that's actually impressive I don't have
to rely on the weapons
maybe I should get the should I get the
pill no horn
um
I am the internet literally mean but
Michael Sarah
Michael
they're so fun
if you like Michael Sarah please watch
the movie
um
chicken's better
really just in case oh you don't believe
in me do you
um
I don't know about these choices today
rainbow
I'll give you a moment I'll
um
pour some water
real world right yeah doesn't look so
good to me
I agree
can somebody say
that I should get sucker too
Michael Cena wait is that the buff guy
he was also in the movie
wanna ASMR
we need Halo for last item
okay
oh that means we gotta keep the last uh
slot open huh okay okay
this is Michael Cena the buff guy guys
he had like this like really random
appearance appearance in the movie it
was like so Random it was like literally
just
he was just there for one scene he
didn't even speak that's John Cena oh
yeah that's what I mean not my Casino
John Cena
hi guys
huh
[Music]
yeah the wrestler yeah and he was also a
Ken
oh you know it was so funny I didn't
know about this did you guys know so
apparently I learned a lot of basic
knowledge about Barbie thanks to this
movie
um
you know the there's like the default
can right the default Ken like everybody
has kind of like a job or like a purpose
right and the default Ken's job is Beach
in the beginning when they show off the
cams they're all at the beach you know
but it's not like their job is lifeguard
or anything no the job is Beach and they
make fun of this quite a lot like
you can't literally not do anything he's
just like there to be on the beat
he can't swim he can't get into the
water he can't help anyone he can't do
first aid or anything no no his job is
just Beach
hello hello don't kill me this time
please
oh God scary okay please
I hope I can kill him
like this take this take this
goodbye
oh the Earth is cracking
oh hold coins but no not worth it I
think
we should all aspire to be Beach doesn't
sound that funny
don't be such a
H what are you calling
it's really funny
if he wants the movie it's so [\h__\h]
funny
you're hitting a lot and escaping I
believe right it's going pretty decent
let's do more Hollow then
uh increase the chance of critical hits
cosplay as this weapon
this weapon what weapon this nuts these
nuts
uh
should I switch something out
10 percent
strength and solo
solo
oh God the Ducks oh no the Ducks not the
Ducks
thank God I have everybody feather
feather revives together oh that's
hopefully not revive all these ducks
though
only me
ah
it's up senses
fans they're so big
we have the face that's a super Gillian
let's go let's go
I am not sure about this I will not do
that
um well what will I do hmm
should I get another feather Maybe
yeah
and
no it's already so stressful
[Music]
birds have a better feather let's go
maybe I'll consume a hamburger
um
re-roll
one time
um
moving
you guys will tell me soon enough if
that was the wrong or the right decision
[\h__\h] that's a lot of enemies I'm not
getting another Halloween are you insane
are you insane
I'm barely surviving
Speedway right let's go
[Music]
let's go
I think I found out you know what's
important in life not the tutus
well honestly then I don't have to feel
bad about sacrificing that one
um
let's just get the whole points let's
just get the whole points because I'm
not I don't think I'll clear this I'm
I'm getting less less confidence by the
seconds of hello
yeah yeah I'm not this if you choose
hello you're not you know it's just like
you're just taunting
you were just taunting the game
okay I see that
um needs a bit of time to get there oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
uh
coins
now
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no take the stats no food or coins
okay
foreign
I don't want it I don't want it
can I drop it
may I may I may I proceed to drop it
yeah okay
leave me alone leave me alone
goodbye I'm gonna die I'm gonna die I'm
gonna die and I'm gonna die wait I have
I have I have uh the chicken feather
don't forget about the chicken feather
okay okay
you can't force me
you can't make me
I don't have a hollow problem
oh my God are these uh
are these cats
made cats is this wait who who
what do these cats belong to who let
their cats out
who let their cats out
oh yeah bye goodbye yeah bye this is
wait when you revive you kill everything
I forgot that eh
you can't take the Anvil why
I couldn't really
I only remember you know that like
scuffed cat that she always draws oh
oh
more stats more stats make me stronger I
just need stronger stats thank you thank
you thank you thank you and I'm really
not get this oh there it is
uh
I guess I'll awaken the nuts even
further
20 minutes two guys I'm getting to 15
now
I'm kind of terrified I don't believe in
winning anymore
I never did I guess
oh my God
there's not much I can do 20 oh my God
throw more nuts I need more nuts
oh there's so many
I never thought I would be
I wouldn't appreciate a huge amount of
cats
following me wherever I go
I normally appreciate it
that's normally what I dream of it's my
dream life oh god oh what do I do with
this bunch
I feel so weak right now
I don't know if I'm doing any damage at
all
can they disappear please oh my God 15
minutes I think I have to kill this like
big mob in the middle right
ghosts I think
if I'll die that's okay too that's okay
too if that's okay too that's okay too
it's fun
fun
oh hello anvil
we'll revive this damage yeah yeah true
true I still have that what how oh
let's go
kind of makes me want to activate that
and die on purpose we have like one more
now right
flower
attacks have 20 chance to reduce attack
and death of targets but oh 20 and 5.
should I maybe switch it out with the
size
one revive left
can I get another one
yeah I think I want to replace it with
the big one and then strengthen and then
we're done
oh the Anvil can I get the Anvil without
dying
success
[Music]
success uh can I get out of this alive
alive
yeah oh
what the [\h__\h]
16.
oh less than five minutes left thanks
for the membership gift yay
very much appreciated
increase the eggs
guys you think I can make it I feel like
I feel like I will I will fail I will
crumble
very close to the end
triple coins coins and uh wait wait it's
asking me first to take the hollow red
so I dropped this and then I take take
it I'm not taking that combo guys I'm
not thinking uh
but these ones aren't so bad yet
I'm gonna strengthen something here
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God
ah Yago was there but I think he died
pretty quickly
oh
the only thing they can give me almost
at this point I guess so
because in those boxes it has to be it
has to be items right it can't be like
stats great hello greed
when we're not going out do we want
great we don't do we do we want green we
want green right okay
oh
Maybe
no attack go flower
tangent harder you think that makes me
stronger three to 17 minutes kind of
late yeah we had green so early in the
previous run but now we got it so late
[Music]
um
I'll just take this one
I'm probably gonna die soon though
I haven't revived we'll have one more
about it I have one more oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God that it's making a lot of
coins right now though holy [\h__\h]
we're making bank
what is this
the first Target this weapon hits marked
the marked Target will receive okay
whatever
strength
this is just Hollow right
oh what a surprise well they want me to
hydrate right it's very important to
hydrate by the way guys did you see my
schedule for the week
today after Hollow cure after we're done
with the stages if we're ever doing that
I think we have a chance to even finish
this one
um
we're announcing something and then
tomorrow it kind of has to do with that
too uh the reason why I chose such an
early stream time for tomorrow
um is because General told me to stream
at that time because it's connected to
what's happening and what I'm announcing
today uh and then I was like well what
the [\h__\h] do I who's that baby is that
good for me
uh I was like okay what the hell do I
stream
so early for like a short amount of time
because I only want to do a short stream
[Music]
and we're just a time between attacks
I don't know
announcement announcement announcement
Reddit Nikki heals heels enemies oh [\h__\h]
him oh
it looked like he was doing something
supportive but not supportive of me huh
oh
I died
[Music]
in my [\h__\h] up again like that then I'm
[\h__\h]
oh at least I got all this yummy XP ah
there's no nothing no no no no no no no
no no they didn't kill me oh no no no no
[Music]
I could apparently in theory say though
that I cleared stage three before so
it's basically cleared but not really I
do want to clear it again today man okay
okay we're done with the money making
let's spend some money and then try a
proper run hollow hollow hollow yeah
yeah they told me to take even more
Hollow Man Without Hollow then we would
have won Maybe
the money Strat if we focus more on like
damage and all that then it couldn't be
so bad right
okay 15 1K
um
should I get the cheaper ones or the
more expensive ones
[Music]
it's you
hey
now there's just one more minute more
minute left
expand haste
oh that one is full now can I
taste increase attack speed
all right I can take the next one too
um
maybe this one I got a lot of money
let's spend it all
you fans
special cooldown reduction
[Music]
money oh now I can't afford it anymore
yeah okay
um we're fine okay so
um
one of the I wanna play one of the new
characters that I didn't play yet maybe
Muna is she strong is she really strong
do you think I have a chance at clearing
stage three or four
with one of these I played Cobra before
and I played Elena before
and pretty soon I think that's it maybe
strong
and the weapon limit
have to get rid of that how do I
I have to refund it okay okay
frozen spinning Crescent
and at an arc in front transforms into
true Moon godspeed I saw that it looks
so cool
okay let's clear Stay Free
what do you want for her guys like
what's what kind of build am I going for
a defensive one
or a very
aggressive one
oh lunar construction targets may drop
lunar blocks
at five blocks
and Luna Ramen cute
which explodes on nearby Targets dealing
300 damage if Luna rabbit defeats a
Target to gain special meat that sounds
that sounds really freaking strong
muscle
but yeah we start with a basic attack I
suppose
I'll take this now before I don't ever
see it again
the study glasses the earlier the better
right
so more exp what's this hoshinova and
moon again hoshinoa above increasing
attack by 20 if taking damage hoshinova
becomes Mona for five seconds reducing
damage taken by 15 instead what
if taking damage for five seconds
okay okay so different Buffs but no
downside to it
cool and is that blank a reference does
muna have like a split personality on
stream where
there's like hoshinova and there's Muna
that's so I didn't know about that at
all damn
[Music]
oh is it a high tide restaurant
she did for a while really
alter ego
no
let me out let me out
Muna very slow right now oh my God this
is a big difference to the speed I had
previously
okay what kind of collabs do we want to
see oh
wow pretty
that's so
bad ass beautiful damn let's go girl oh
those slashes slash me slash me up
slice me into Sashimi chicken Sashimi I
will give you I will give you
salmonella let's go
ah
Idol super collab what was the Idol
super collab
um that was it glow stick
[Music]
and then at the end an idol outfit right
but first what's the normal collab
um
[Music]
oh
you guys are so slow with reacting
glow sticks and idle thumb okay
so far
really easy
[Applause]
okay okay and then spider love or an
Uber sheep really is that a thing
Uber sheep as the
the final collab item what was it glow
stick glow stick right an idol song
Closer song
oh my God hello
we're already on level three with the
glow sticks immediately
I've never seen that before I want to
see that
you guys want to refresh your browser
then it should be gone
I know
in the beginning but I actually turned
it off
I don't know why YouTube is not updating
that on its own
but you know what I don't mind so much
honestly I feel like
if
if I wasn't such a
chicken being scared of accidents
then DVR should be on all the time
because I think that's very convenient
for viewers who just stumble into the
stream a little bit later
going jenga's content is that what is
that what that is called at the end
foreign
ER
[Music]
come here
oh don't be so ignorant call me you talk
to me I want to have a meeting with you
let's have a conversation come on
size plus 15 for the elite lava bucket
we need it later right we're gonna
we're gonna use this one too right
I still delay even if you're refreshing
too yeah there's definitely also stupid
delay
I [\h__\h] up today okay it's okay though
it's not something that's you know
that's like gonna destroy our experience
we won't let it
take it okay
oh how perfect
is part of us again so we must take this
stamp even though second hasn't been
very active
at all for a while
or half day and I just I'm just missing
out on it have they been doing anything
as us again
we have a server for us again but it
hasn't been used
since
since I think the wasn't there like us
again Summer Festival
probably since then
[Music]
concert
was really really fun to sing together
even though it was a difficult really
difficult song
okay first boss down
how about you start a new I I did say to
them I talked about this before
once we found out that we're doing
something together in the concert I said
uh should we maybe
um
uh do at least one collab stream
together before the concert but then
time went by so fast and we ended up not
doing it
unfortunately
it was just yeah I was too busy to
follow up on it it was my idea but and
then I was too busy to follow up on it
um but hey I'm not the leader of us
again
basically also
pretty much takes the lead a lot of the
time I would say
um
[Music]
yeah we got idle songs so we can work on
that collab
decreased damage of the main current
weapon
increasing speed by 20
I don't want to
should I upgrade
isn't one of the CEO yeah but in terms
of like planning things so far like I I
saw mostly like
[Music]
initiative honestly
I like this but not on Muno
I see
yeah I usually use it to upgrade okay
I shall do the same
[Music]
are we using fan beam no right
I still think that makes things just
colorful right now [\h__\h] that
ah speaking of Muna man I've been like
bonding here and there with her like you
know at the at the sports festival too
that they did
okay yeah and then you know in Japan for
all the usakan things and then also
uh
for the theme song so I don't know
Sun Moon you guys call it sun moon has
been pretty strong
wait wait
we should do a proper collab I guess
because I don't think
have have I ever done a one-on-one
collab with no no I've done like an off
collab of
some ID Girls when Luna was in there too
but I don't think I did a one-on-one
collab with Muna before today
well honestly maybe it's about time that
I started doing the the holotalk the
reverse holotalk with a translating to
Japanese instead of translating into
English
uh because I could start with Muna since
she's first gen ID
that would make the most sense
never one-on-one
maybe it's time
it might just be time for that
sounds like a good idea
yeah I mean I could like
do it simultaneously you know with the
normal
horror talk and I know I haven't been
doing the whole talk much in general
anyway which I'm sorry about
sorry I know I'm I've been busy man
I have to do one soon though so we can
at least finish the
fourth gen
with
and then I feel a little bit better a
little bit more
satisfied
completionist
there's a whole box
to the South
ah oh I don't notice that one at all
telling me
[Music]
it's more moving up of Music why did I
not get this yet that draws Targets in
slowly dealing 100 of damage per half
second
it draws them in
okay
okay let's see oh ah like this
what's going on
foreign
number one number one oh I read your
mind guys we are connected we are
intertwined it's the tadpoles in our
heads that are connecting us
[Music]
almost special time almost special time
take this take that oh you guys you know
what's weird I received a package
from cover
but I thought oh maybe this is my
I don't know my 3D merchandise my pretty
um like reveal merchandise or something
like that some something I'm still
waiting on
but no
what was inside
it's Pokemon merchandise
and I'm thinking is it because of the
Pokemon Unite
thing they they did say a thing that
they're giving us something but this
what was inside wasn't at all mentioned
that we would be getting something like
that so I'm like really confused
and it's not even really unite related
it's just like a lot of different things
from the Pokemon shop I think like uh
the one I like the most I think is the
there's like a toothbrush a Pikachu
toothbrush holder but it's a
it's I think it's a diddle Pikachu
because it has like a really goofy face
and there's like a towel and there's
some Pokemon cards
stickers or or something for Pokemon
cards like uh I think maybe it's just a
cover for them uh
and what else what else what else was
that I like some
some pins
uh with that penguin Pokemon
did I just
swap it out oh
wait I don't know which one I want
this one's already Max
wait wait wait
Maybe
which one do I like more yeah pipla
Piplup
replace flour okay
I will do that
baby I don't I have to look at it again
it's so cute though
and yeah so a bunch of things and I'm
like why did I receive this
yeah
scribbly eyes I think it was scrapply
eyes no
what's that no maybe not scribble it
looks funny in any case
well I don't know why I received this
but thank you thank you whoever decided
to send me this it did come from cover
so
somebody
you know normally when I receive things
from like game companies or something
they send it first to cover and then
cover sends it to me
um for safety you know so that as few
people as possible know my address I
guess oh okay not an ear Muna get out of
there
ah don't forget to take spiders oh oh oh
oh yes okay
butter cooking
oh another thing I received from cover
recently
is uh yeah bye you're back
I'm gonna die it rhymes
beautiful uh I need food you're buying
you bye
so might die yeah ah [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay again
ah man
God damn it oh you can only get one
super collab really
oh okay well then we might as well just
aim for one oh hey look at this it's the
idle costume I'll take it now
I feel like I was looking for it and I
could never find it in the last one
[\h__\h] that was rough
I need something
what what we learned from that is I need
something for healing me I had nothing I
think nothing at all
um
something one hammer for the super cool
only one huh
yeah
I guess we'll never hit a big
announcement
I will I will announce the announcements
I will I will no matter what
we'll just have to get good I've got
time I've got time
would be nice to get the glasses again
though
Ibrahim or defense yeah
yes
yes really I wasn't trying to run into
them
[Music]
anyway if I can use the special more
often that would actually indeed be
great because her special is saving my
butt all this time
anyway I was saying
announcement announcement I'm not
announcing anything no I am uh I was
saying I received another thing from
cover
really really really really really big
big heavy heavy heavy thing what do you
think it is
something huge and heavy what could it
be
no no no
uh actually a merchandise I I got all of
it now
a tank
a plaque and I'll already have all my
plaques
since a long time ago 3D equipment no
why would I get pretty equipment from
them
ah
what could it be
personal assistant
wouldn't this be nice
no it's no merchandise it's no no
merchandise of my own or anyone else
actually
new cat channel in a box
it is
um my birthday okay I guess it's kind of
merchandise my birthday merchandise
um postcards to sign
uh I don't know how many thousands
it's really freaking heavy and I have to
sign all of them
and my deadline to sign them is
[Music]
um in in like 16 days maybe
um
yeah bye
so I'm thinking maybe maybe I'll sign
them
well while shit's chatting
in a member stream or something
oh but I guess a lot of them like at
least maybe I don't know maybe 10 or
five percent of them at least are
um
like
throwaways like in case I make a mistake
like there's definitely a bunch of extra
ones in there
oh hi Yago
don't run away
don't be scared
let's go yeah you can basically see your
card getting signed
later when you receive it you can
compare
you can check if that was uh
when what second of my stream I signed
your cards
be mine because here she drew the
the
chicken face like this
that looks like the car that I got
a lot of work like this is the first
time that I'm um
signing for birthday or Anniversary
merchandise
um
yeah I've never done it like this I've
signed things before but like not for
you know this kind of purpose where I
would have to sign so many
it will take a while and we'll probably
use up at least three pens
oh we're loading
well we're probably back by now now that
I noticed it
oh yeah we're back
only understanding was yeah I signed
someone took me but it's like not even
not even you can't even really compare
those
because that was like how many 20 I
don't know
not many
hey I want I want the special hi
yoga this time you go
I want the special that has
um nice nice freeze
I want the skill with the idol stuff
Idol song and glow stick please
damn we're keeping this young girl alive
for a long time
but
we were keeping track of him keeping him
Frozen best Strat for Yago
oh God
no I'm not gonna die I'm not gonna die
I'm not gonna die why would I die I'm
not going to die
nah come on
the Bale sticker you for real
bye
bye bye
it doesn't even really offer me any like
healing besides the healing is doubled
item why why why why why why why why why
is it not offering me anything man
um
I feel like I want to re-roll
hey there's Idol song I guess I'll take
another song but I actually I actually
want healing
is there any food lying around please
can I eat the pumpkin I like pumpkins oh
[\h__\h]
that looks like footballzilla to me
I can't see oh yeah it's not
looked a little bit like it yeah
oh
there's there's some food
give me the food
uh ah no we're not doing a money run
hmm
wrap it's rough kind of rough oh trip
uh-huh okay okay okay I'll take it I'll
take it oh
I'll take the study glasses
well not a healing item but you gotta
take what you get
well damage not defense I need at least
a little bit that's what I died for at
the very end last time not very end
wasn't I didn't even get that far got to
11 minutes
double hit on Ollie is great nice find
what what did I find
please stop please stop
[Music]
oh my God I don't even realize my
special
loads so fast holy moly
now here we have Uber ship I will take
ubership okay
please
that's all all the healing stuff I will
take okay I'll the rest will be
focused on aggression violence oh so
much food I'm so happy oh my God I'm
dying
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
make way make way for the queen for the
moon Queen
that's once again saved my butt let's go
you need a feather
maybe maybe
[Music]
what do you think I'll be announcing
later wrong answers only I liked that I
saw it on Twitter and I thought it was
funny wrong answers only
[Music]
thank you for the special
foreign
Cafe in Australia I already have one
there
was Austria a movie four of Debbie were
retirement
one month vacation a new hat
having a new hat
I love that oh I love that oh my God
you're funny
the new athlete game yeah I'll be
announcing the new ads in your game yet
German channel 24 hours marriage with
narissa what that's real though just
kidding
a new hat
that's my favorite that's my favorite so
far
uh funny
[Music]
guys I'm just saying we're going for a
super cool app with glow sticks but so
far I've seen no glow stick
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
Dodge Dodge Dodge
[Music]
Nintendo Direct oh yes I'm announcing a
Nintendo Direct oh should I take the
researchers called coat
Return of the second hand no
had prediction tweets
[Music]
final cooking one I mean we could
because I have Uber shape too huh
[Music]
so that's why I'm wearing my my OG
outfit yeah yeah and now to Skate 4 in
GTA 6.
[Laughter]
104 okay
what would I do without my special
I am nothing without my special
I'm not so good at this character I
think there's other characters that I'm
definitely doing a better job with
this is a good character though still
I'm just not good at controlling it
okay yeah Fitness art part two uh-huh
yeah yeah
how do you say that in English triathlon
in German
are you getting your own Barbie oh my
God
I wish
no I don't wish
Bring it on Bring it on Bring it on
Bring it on
fan beam no go stick
I was waiting for you oh is he stuck oh
no he's definitely stuck now
get out of there oh my God
oh my God so close to death
I had like literally on my tongue that
fizzled my tongue
somewhere please
okay
okay ah
let's
someone else
[Applause]
[Music]
that was so stupid
that was so stupid Oh man
um
guess no announcement today
um what character was the students
remember what character was I
specifically pretty decent at using
um
I think
I don't remember
[Applause]
I heard kiwawa is still pretty good
maybe you know wouldn't it be kind of
badass to clear the state that I can't
clear with me
yeah that really easy for this
woman is great
that's the kind of
I thought you would say Kiana is great
oh wait noisa you could coach me because
you're really good at home look here
you would choose another whole verb over
me
no reason
let's try his Chihuahua I mean that
would just like be so meaningful so deep
uh Larissa do you want to go on a call
and I show you I will show you my
screens
no I wouldn't mind having like someone
to talk to me right now
and then you can also tell me if I'm
doing so
[Music]
she's really good at the look here I saw
her play it she she even she had
features that I never knew of before
I'm going into
the vce
you're welcome anytime baby
oh my God like wait I'm trying to
um
[Music]
hi yeah
it's over here how are you doing doing
good you're playing my favorite game am
I I love Hello Kitty out of all games
yeah well uh you know yeah I feel like I
have so many hours on Hollow cure that
it is not incorrect to call it that oh
okay will you guide me to win please
um okay so that I can announce questions
I actually haven't watched because I've
been playing Baldur's Gate at the same
time
so let me let me uh save my game real
quick okay
um but okay so
I the only reason I recommend
is just because she is so easy in my
opinion to like be good at even if
you're not very good at the game which
was me at first I don't remember I think
I played her before but I don't remember
how well I did with her well the nice
thing about her specifically is once you
like uh the best way to put it once you
uh
once you've leveled the weapon up all
the way her attacks are really really
good because it kind of hits everywhere
around the map for you
um I do think she got nerfed a little
bit but I don't really think she got
nerfed it seems her skills just changed
a little bit this time but I in my
opinion I think she's still pretty
broken
um iris is also really good but I um
haven't gotten to play her a ton a ton
um Miko I think is also pretty good but
I don't remember
somebody's just broke I don't play as
kiwawa anymore too easy some people say
you know Kiwa was still very good you
definitely uh because at the very very
start of the game Chihuahua was kind of
nerfed um comparatively uh that they
gave her she's stronger yeah I remember
that yeah yeah she's way stronger
um so she is she is very good I hear
Sana is easy too but admittedly I'm not
very good with Sana so yeah I think I
was pretty yeah I remember having a good
time but you know what we should just
you know wouldn't it be like you know
kind of it makes whatever yeah
how much experience do we have with me
I've I played you quite a bit I'm
actually at the super the epiget don't
you have everybody maxed out anyways no
just just in a myth and I think most of
council and a few of the random JP
members so yeah
I I need to with this with with this
character of AKA and me I have to like
constantly be on the move right
yes well honestly with any character in
this game I would highly recommend you
be on the move
really don't think it is beneficial to
not be on the moon
um my favorite method to do it uh this
map it's a little bit harder but to keep
moving in a big circle because they'll
they'll inevitably all kind of get in
one Circle and it'll be easier
I've seen that before what's my method
okay my ways to play is I will
prioritize getting all of the skills
first and I will stop
um if there's like a weapon I know I
really really want or collaboration I
know I'm Really Gonna want then I'll
like prioritize getting that but getting
all the other skills otherwise before
like leveling everything up I think is
really really important okay um as well
as Max weapon so okay
you want to ideally go for what what you
were kind of muffled there for a second
what idea
what what collaborations do you build
end games something that makes you super
cool app so I heard there's one with
Uber sheep the other one I've already
seen the one with the idol costume
what's this do again the Uber
collaboration is really really good um
that one I think is spider cooking
um I would recommend picking that up
when you see it next okay
I think it was kind of cooking and the
lava bucket right and then yeah yes um
those those are all items I usually get
in my runs anyway
um plushie is a really really good
Shield item or at least it's one I like
to get I don't actually know if it's
good I wouldn't pick up the stamp uh
just because it decreases okay but we
can like strengthen something a little
bit later I guess
so I continue with like all the all the
kiwawa specific skills right for now and
you could use the Anvil to just do your
main weapon just to like save you
okay okay
didn't I leave like a like a fire behind
me a fire Trail where is that um I don't
know if you've picked up the skill yet
you used your didn't you use your old
and that's why Ah that's why
only after you get the skill because you
need to get the level one of it
I know a shame what a shame well you
know if you if you get to Utah level you
start with all your skills maxed out
um
wait no get spider cookie get it okay
just in case I I have the worst luck
with this game that if I skip something
it never pops up for me again so that's
the only reason I usually uh it will be
like that sometimes yeah
oh girl tell me and tell me about your
father's gate solo experience who do you
like uh currently mostly bring with you
what's your favorite team members
um I really like historian because I
feel like he but he is the most helpful
now didn't you have a thing against him
first I made a bad first impression
oh you agree with me now
he's so beautiful right he is he is like
I feel like I I'm sorry Shadow heart
misses like every other attack and it
rolls me off and then like I have will
on my team and he's good too but like I
have to be close range a starian will
just like one shot people yeah I'm just
getting there are you also using this
like you hide first and then you do the
I think you've been doing that oh my god
I've just been just doing like the
regular shot and he just still like just
absolutely demolishes people
she gets it now she needed some time but
she gets it now well I I won't bring it
up too much on your stream but I had one
of the cut scenes with him and suddenly
oh yeah I had that too you mean the
vampire bites yeah yeah
that was yeah it it it is
who understands
yeah no I am
that's what changes your opinion I know
it's vampires you know yeah I don't want
to be charged by vampires but can you
it's hard it's have to resist as I think
as a woman especially
you're just like inclined to feel
something there
I would um oh no it's too late don't
worry about it should I have taken
something else
um I I really like getting uh boys love
book oh um another thing you're going to
want to try to pick up is Shield because
you don't have any yet
so you mean like the the pillow Shield
yeah yeah well just any any of the
clothing items quote unquote okay I call
them Shields yeah I'll help you don't
worry we won't be getting the Uber sheep
anyway okay what do we do well we might
we might be um uh for now let's do
Phoenix Shields just because you already
have spider cooking but we still don't
have the thing to collaborate it with
anyway so might as well wait so where
are you getting stuck here because again
I was only halfway I was I was playing
um with Muna hoping it was the first
time like I played I tried uh with her
like for like two or three times
I want to play a new character because I
haven't played everybody yet
so I just wanted to use an opportunity
but
I think around shubangelion something
always like ends up killing me like just
the explosions and yeah it's just rough
stupid alien I understand I got past him
once but
um
okay let's finish off Phoenix Shield
because I think that's I think it's the
last one you need to get all the way up
uh you could take credit card if you
want to I usually don't get it but if
you like the chance of anvils popping
back up then you can no no cutting board
is really good for a collaboration well
I'm not flat
you're not flat but you don't you don't
need to be flat to use The Cutting Board
so uh cutting board uh wait I know but
it increases the effectiveness if you're
if you're flat so um but but hear me out
so The Cutting Board collaborates uh
with the en curse have you unlocked that
item yet yes it makes bone Bros as a
collaboration it's really yeah I think I
did that before yeah yeah it looks cool
it's really good I otherwise I I agree I
don't really like the cutting but it
doesn't do a super cool app does it
uh no but we'll still we'll still be
building up to a supercloud but it's not
a bad idea to start planning your other
collaborations as well otherwise um in
this case I'd go for either that or ASA
Coco with the um now okay I'll take the
cutting board but this is one of the few
times where I wish I was flat
I assume nothing wrong with um flat
girls you know
yeah nothing I I appreciate all the
sizes
but I'm also quite happy with my
I am too wait tell me more about BG free
how far are you
um I I don't know I'm definitely way
further than we were before but I
realized I forgot to go to a crush
um
you went past the goblin Temple and
stuff yeah yeah I've already beat that I
have over like 11 hours on the game okay
because I in my two about their skates
little strains I tried to just do a lot
of side stuff and like not really go
past the goblin Temple
so that's what I've been doing
yeah I do cutting board here okay
uh I just I just focus on what you have
I I admittedly I think one of the
complaints my builds get is I'm a little
inflexible with what I like to get but
um
I have builds that I like because they
work I am and that's fine reliable
strategies
yes wait do I have a different sticker
already no man no I don't want to
strengthen something
oh there's lots a lot of things going on
yeah spread the fire spread it did you
get Carla
did you get Carlock yeah I did get
Carlock yeah did you did you enter with
her that Paladin house
no no I didn't because it's like one of
her like side quests her her own
personal story Quest thingy you know
I've been ignoring her I just I
accidentally almost lost the opportunity
to get her all together she's a really
good tank though she is also extremely
hard
so who else is on your team as Darion
and yeah a Syrian whale and Shadow heart
out
yeah I don't know
like she's a great tank although I guess
it depends on what your class is with oh
oh oh
it's okay that's okay what you did was
not wrong okay um what I usually like to
do at the start of the game is kind of
pick up the first three like items I
know I really want for collabs
um that I want to build towards uh but
did you want the nightly milk or what no
um I was going to recommend that you go
for instead the uh don't don't put
yourself into a wall yeah yeah okay I'll
go to the right side
um
let's take it for now
[Music]
okay yeah but you gotta get garlic
because she's kind of like me you know
she swears and curses a lot and and
she's she has a Burning Heart
and and she leaves fire everywhere and
and she destroys my OBS because somehow
her fire makes my OBS go crazy
um okay so here's what I'd recommend
here
um obviously we need to get the lava
bucket we need to get the en purse but
then we still need to pick a third
collab to start setting up I really like
whammy water
um and doing that with boys love book
it's a really really strong collab in my
opinion because it shoots all over I
think I saw that one too before I think
I created it if you'd like we can try to
build it
um if you don't we can go for something
else we're doing it oh nice let's go oh
spider cooking let's Max it out just so
you have one less thing that pops up
um can I mention
um
yes today me and Elisa were chatting and
I I I quoted the lyrics of the Advent
song is liar liar pants on fire is that
not the lyrics no no well this is not
it's fire fire light the fire and it
sounds like liar liar pants on fire I
mean it's honestly it would be funnier
yeah
I like that version
no it was pretty silly or pants on fire
um you have got stamps down there I I
don't think you need to pick it up but
you could
ah it's almost like that I think it's
for his MPS empty yeah okay
I usually find it has little benefit
because I fill up my weapons it has it
made sense in my um no weapon
money run
um made sense there otherwise it's kind
of it's kind of useless yeah
it's the lyrics now we changed it
officially
no we'll get in trouble we can't change
the lyrics to advent's first original
freedom
creative dumb man
oh you can't stop my creativity
okay we really need to get some Shields
because you still don't know one time
I'm a phoenix I'm a phoenix but there's
still not any good ones yeah I wish you
had uh
I guess you could
let me read Band-Aid I've never gotten
it I'm being hit you're good oh you know
that's not too bad do you want to pick
up the Band-Aid yes
I will use the bandages instead of um
usually I really like to eat the plushie
because what it does is it delays how
long it hits you so you kind of have
some time
I get that too because that makes it so
you have basically an extra buff before
so that like you get hit but you won't
get the damage until you exceed a
certain hit limit um but no the the they
work differently the the plushie makes
it so it just you will still get the
damage but it gives you basically a
buffer to go and find Health
um I would do whammy water here it
doesn't really matter though yeah since
we don't have anything for the
collaboration yeah not yet we'll get it
we'll get there ah
uh
uh whilst travel far farther
whatever it doesn't matter you know what
I will tell now
yes now that we're in the groove
uh
remember our collaborations where we
talked about similarities
and there was one thing we forgot to
mention I purposely left it out I didn't
I thought it not to put it on my knees
it would make pork Oh but BL buck
perfect and then we want to try to
prioritize the lava bucket if we see it
so that one is closer to being ready for
a collaboration and you want to try to
do the super Club okay um but yeah no I
purposely left it out because I figured
it would give us some good good content
for later but if you like to talk about
it we can yes
so how does we even find out about this
uh well I knew because I heard you talk
about it so I think I just brought it up
uh yeah yeah so it's about hair removal
guys we have we have a hair removal
similarity or like we did the same type
of hair removal and even
foreign
because there's several ways you know
normally like the most standard I guess
is like shaving yeah and then you're
like you know you get like kind of
unsatisfied by shaving because maybe it
leaves stop bowls or it's Shine for me
the problem was like it kind of shines
through because my skin is like really
light
um but my hair in for example like in
the in the wacky in the um what's called
underarm yeah the underarm area
what's the real word
armpit armpit yes it's a bit fake you
know so it shines through and I was
feeling kind of like
um
yeah insecure about it so when I was
younger you know what I did
ah wait go for plushie okay and that
flashy oh yeah uh when I was younger
like in uh
okay good in in school time back in the
day for like PE physical Sports
education
um when I I tried mostly wearing shirts
that don't show the armpits but when I
did I
I I actually I I was so insecure and I
put like some makeup foundation on my
armpits so that it wouldn't be so
visible yeah
I know what you mean though I I have
like thin skin in that area so the hair
shows through and obviously I have black
hair right so yeah yeah that also means
that that hair is pretty dark as well
um so it would always show through even
yeah we cut it down so it's like ah I
was like okay I'm just tired nurses
horns nurses horns I'll get it thank you
okay
yeah but because of those struggles I
then later tried out the the Epi later
that like fluffs out right really fast
it's like a little little device
do people do everybody does everybody
know what I'm talking about when I say
epilator
is that quite common
yeah you know what I mean right so but I
used an epilator once or for quite a
while before I hate it yeah it hurts so
much and there's like specific areas
where it oh nice well it hurts even more
I think like for example on on my lower
legs on the sides of my the inner sides
of my lower legs it just really hurts so
much do boys love books since we have
the one for the collaborate okay
um once we uh get hopefully because uh
sorry I'm trying to think how to talk
um because we already have the other two
that are like ready
um it's better to just like Max them out
uh when we get their collaborations to
try and get them closer
um
that's that's a hope all right some
people in the chat know about it okay
especially for Coco Senpai apparently
once you did the hair removal stream oh
yeah so I tried that for a while but
it's so painful and annoying but if you
rip it out you know it doesn't grow back
so fast as when you shave it obviously
so I tried that but I didn't like it and
then waxing I kind of tried but I guess
I was doing it wrong and I was using the
wrong product so waxing wasn't my thing
either yeah did you ever try it
go in and get that guy he's healing that
oh yeah yeah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] him yeah [\h__\h]
ing don't let him do that
oh I think he's gone oh okay you got him
um but yeah no I I've done it pretty
much everything uh BL book okay
uh I've done pretty much everything in
the book have you tried waxing at a
store though because I only tried doing
it myself I never tried it at the
professional place you did it I I um I I
went and I had a professional do it and
I was really disappointed because I was
wearing uh skinny jeans I don't like
jeans anyway so that was a mistake
I no it was like the fashion okay
perfect okay and now if we see Uber
sheep you want to get that no matter the
cost
[Music]
um
yeah yeah
um but yeah so it wasn't like uh it was
supposed to be like my whole like above
the knee and Below but she instead of
like the name below above the knee so
like from from the top top of the knee
to the bottom aha your leg okay okay I'm
sorry I explained it more and um the
lady so you know how most of the time
when you go into those Services they
just like have you take off your pants
and give you a little towel
um yeah she didn't want to do that for
some reason she didn't give you a towel
at all no she didn't want me to take my
pants off so I'll just take them off and
just like oh no but how are you going to
do it then she rolled it up oh
[Music]
that's that's difficult
it was very frustrating I do boys love
Books Okay um just because it's closest
to a collab okay and uh This Cloud is
pretty good so once you get it it should
help you quite a bit
um nice I like this one yeah me too
um but so she she could only roll it up
half my leg right so not even the whole
part that she was supposed to do so
instead of actually waxing the whole
area that she was even supposed to just
because she didn't want me to remove my
pants for some reason she just waxed
that small area and it was like 60 bucks
so I was really disappointed wait she
waxed less than you actually wanted to
yeah she she waxed less so she couldn't
reach it because she because she just
didn't want me to take my pants off
which would have made the area easily
accessible so weird and what can I do
when somebody wants to to wax their you
know private parts right right I was
just like it was so weird because like
even uh when I was doing laser hair
removal you know like they just have me
take everything off they'd be like just
get naked come back yeah and I was like
oh okay
meanwhile they're like
not this guy again why why why why why
you gotta always ruin everything huh is
he gone I think it's gone oh golden
anvil uh this this one's first was it
yeah yep
Frozen sea
all right very nice hopefully we see
Uber sheep sometime soon yes yes
but now you can start focusing on so the
uh lava bucket you've done the wax thing
we've done the epilating we've done the
Shaving we've done um oh you know what I
also tried the the the cream that you
put on you let it sit a little bit and
it's supposed to fall out on its own in
the chemical yeah it really work yeah I
mean the issue is because it doesn't
like penetrate into your pores so like
it really doesn't it really doesn't do
what you want it to do you know what I
mean I think it said that it works
better if your hair is like really thin
and I guess if there's not too much but
I tried it on my on my lower arm where I
had a lot of hairs and it wasn't really
really good
I wouldn't I don't I don't really care
for those kinds of those ones seem you
can get it if you want to you don't need
it
um
they're just really gimmicky to me I
think it's the best way but you know I
just felt like kind of desperate I felt
like I needed to try everything
nothing wrong with that at all find
everything I mean that's what I did
before I decided to do laser removal
um and do the bucket yeah yeah we're
close let's go
if only if only we had the Uber sheep oh
but you know you're talking about laser
removal and we just gotta make it clear
because there's like normally when
people think about the laser removal
they roll here yeah okay you could get
nice milk too though but this one I just
re-roll but
um they think of the the one that's
mostly advertised as you know laser uh
where you go in there and I don't know
maybe it's gone for a few weeks but then
it grows back but the one that we did is
actually you know with lights with
really hot hot light
um and it stays gone forever like it it
burns the root of your hair that's why
it's not growing back yeah and we did
that it's it's it's just a longer
process you have to do several sessions
you go back in like I think you know
according to the to the group the growth
schedule of your hair uh because you
can't get all of them at once so and for
me it took like two years or so two
years yeah because it was like every one
or two months or so and then sometimes
it didn't work out and I was doing a lot
of areas you know yeah yeah I know what
you mean yeah and also I moved cities in
between so then I had to go to different
office and then there I absolutely hated
the lady that did it so
um
let's go we'll just regular clam oh yeah
true not super yeah almost
uh yeah uh because she was so weird and
mean and it was so painful like I I said
oh this hurts and like in in the
previous one they would turn down the
strength because you can you can turn it
down it won't be as effective yeah but
you can still turn it down so it's less
painful and she said yeah but then we're
not getting anything and I'm like but
I'm like literally crying here right now
okay
yeah it's it's kind of frustrating I I
was told that I have a really high pain
tolerance so she she had told me
actually she's like you're really
amazing I can have yours up really
really high and you're not feeling it so
I guess I guess I was pretty lucky
um but even then I mean it definitely
does feel like getting like either like
stabbed with like a uh okay here's what
we can do here yeah get the Ian curse
okay
perfect but I feel like I have a
normally I have a pretty high uh pain
tolerance too just because of my chronic
pain that I've been dealing with for
many many years and because of
fibromyalgia and all that yeah but when
it comes to hair removal it was still
pretty rough you know I feel like it's
because it's so different from any
Sensation that like you experience that
like I can totally get where you're
coming from because it is so it is just
a weird pain yeah I feel like it's the
best way to describe it like it's very
weird yeah and I feel like you know for
or for example on my legs I could still
handle it but it was really bad on on
the armpits and maybe maybe another
certain yeah I know the point is that me
and then we started it in three
different areas that are exactly the
same matching cleaning we're twinning
yeah
no I feel you the my legs they were
pretty fine except that area is like
obviously you have thinner skin in some
parts of your legs and like that would
be really painful but I remember the
more I went through it the less it would
hurt and I mean my sessions only really
took like 15 minutes each so like 15
minutes each they were really quick oh I
feel like I was usually in there longer
well it depends how small the area is
because the leg was pretty big but
armpits really small yeah thank God
because it was so why is the armpit so
painful man
I don't know I think it's because the
skin there is so thin yeah which is one
of the same reasons the hair shows
through so easily so it's like the skin
is thin the hair is really thick and
coarse too so like you know yeah man but
no I feel you and I hated doing that
area the most because I could smell the
burning
you know
oh I guess I didn't smell it so much
because I didn't have it amped up so
high
no I I mean I never had like any issues
like my skin never looked like anything
was wrong with it yeah yeah but like I
could definitely like smell it and I was
like oh
should I be worried and they're like now
you're fine
wait uh look you've almost got the Ian
you've already got almost three
[Music]
wait ah so
yes yes okay okay I'll look out for it
I'll re-roll
um but yeah this method is like I think
also maybe the most expensive hair
removal method it was really expensive
in my uh country at least because also
it was really special like nobody no
everybody I told about it they didn't
know about it they always thought I'm
just doing normal laser ring but it
wasn't very common you know mm-hmm I
mean even I I was able to convince one
of my sisters to do it
um but like a lot I've I rarely meet
anyone who does it just because like it
is more expensive but also when I think
about like how much some of my friends
pay to like laser I'm like yeah keep on
going back there for yeah that thing
that we did you know you know it's it's
painful while you're doing it but once
you're done with it you never have to do
it again and I I have to say this is
kind of gross but you know how like the
hair falls out after yeah and like you
can kind of just like gently pull on it
and I don't really enjoyed that oh my
God it's so long ago I didn't even
remember that but that was really
satisfying yeah
yeah um just oh no no luck yeah that's
it um just do plushie uh okay just let's
just start since we already have three
clams and we're close to the end just
focus on upping your shields uh the more
you up your skills the more likely
you'll get to maybe have a new one pop
up
um because even if we re-roll like this
because you have open slots and stuff
it's gonna be all shitty should I get
speed
oh yeah why not because I'm scared at
the end I'm very scared it's always good
okay
[Laughter]
because it was just such a fun
experience
you just mean the hair falling out right
you don't mean the actual I mean all of
it is kind of fun like because you know
like it feels like it feels like
traumatizing to me like it's like it's
like something special
also I felt uncomfortable you know
during the whole experience show like my
armpit and my and my legs whatever but
you know on the other part like I just
feel so uncomfortable like uh do nurses
horns here okay being out in the open
like that in front of people so but I
guess I guess did you just say you like
it
yeah
do you like being naked in front of
other people
yeah well then it's the experience to
you
exactly and switch it out together
explosion
[Music]
Maybe
ah I don't know that's whatever at this
point yeah we're close enough to the end
that it seems we're probably not gonna
be able to get the collaboration I'm
sorry it's okay it's neither it's just
because it didn't pop up as long as I
finish this I'm happy oh 20 more seconds
what what Boss shows up at the end again
uh uh
apparently I've cleared the stage before
maybe like two one year one or two years
ago but I really don't remember it you
know you this game wasn't out two years
ago it failed like two years ago though
like it oh
just pick up something it doesn't matter
what you get just get a weapon oh okay
the the ball is so fun but I don't I
love the ball but it's difficult yeah
I'll take the tears
oh my God
we're almost there you've got this oh
there she is oh my God they're fine
running keep running
yeah perfect you have to burn the spider
with fire right that's the only way to
deal with it with a spider okay
don't don't let it live
yeah run away from this one I hate it I
hate this stuff yeah me too make it stop
making stop making stuff
okay it's over what kind of at least she
changed her pattern ah where's she [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I use my ulti at the wrong time
right there um
she'll walk through the fire
on fire
oh the boat hell again okay no problem
no problem I guess I gotta just walk
down together with it oh
oh this is too much for my brain ways to
block it but it's I mean it gets more
condensed the further down you go which
I think is what makes it at least for me
like more of a painful experience
I shall credit you in my announcement
because you're the only reason I'm gonna
be announcing anything today
stage four as well
[Applause]
oh my god let's go
let's go
don't retry characters
whenever I clear a stage like this it
feels so unsatisfying to leave all the
EXP and the Box on the floor like that
they won't let me pick it up
I'm like I know the round is ending but
like I kind of wish that Caillou would
change it so like once you get to that
point you can actually pick to keep
going and switch to endless mode oh like
I feel like that would make yeah it's
like oh I'm doing pretty well right now
this this could be an endless run yeah
exactly every every time I'm having that
sort of luck um I get really uh angry
because it always happens to me okay
let's try with lava
um here's what I was actually gonna
recommend doing uh but you already spent
all your money so I guess not uh how
many how many copies of you do you have
go to
uh none um
don't go back I don't need any more
copies of me I'm me go back to the title
screen
um a shop I think you wanna gotcha no no
no uh click back I want to check
something but I forget how to get there
uh buy upgrades
uh okay okay you do have it okay so back
back
home oh okay uh a leaderboard or
achievements it's in one of those okay
yeah no not later board hello guys
oh achievements okay fandoms
ah so here you can see the fandom levels
so the reason I was asking if you had
copies of yourself is because the more
you get the more
um the the higher your level goes and
you can Max that out 20. so once you get
21 copies of you you'll max out that
part otherwise clearing stages also
really helps yeah my priority was just
you know getting every character first
yeah I know it should be listen to me it
helps you so much it helps so much okay
okay well I mean I'm not getting there
today I think so today but just just to
know for next time we have to deal with
the way it is sadly
but now you know
uh so do you think we can clear stage
five with Wawa too
I think so let's go let's see I don't
know what one oh it is I'm not very good
at this one so I've only played it twice
and one time I lost but that's because I
was screwing around at the end
um we're gonna want to make sure we do a
really good job building everything okay
stop wait you're coming from Amelia not
the number one cause like shut up
I have actually never inside the ID
stage yet so I'm really excited to hear
the music there
[Music]
the identity song so much oh my God it
is so good
[Music]
remember be careful move in a big circle
brick Circle
um I would recommend uh walking around
also so you can see where all the limits
are on this stage because this one does
have boundaries oh yeah does it end here
oh boundary yep right there
so that that threw me off because I kept
forgetting about the different
boundaries
okay and here
oh can you walk around here oh yeah oh
yeah no wait I was I think I walked on
this one time maybe the pole okay
yeah okay
do you hear the music too uh okay
[Laughter]
plushie plushie
you need some Shield so you hear the
music I do hear it
I was testing it
I'm happy we could have the hair removal
talk
yeah me too I mean very happy it's out
there now we're so similar over so
similar when we're naked too
[Laughter]
I just yeah stick with your sword for
now
[Laughter]
you gotta run why
uh because you kept getting hit that's
fine
[Laughter]
it's still the beginning and I have I
have noisa in my pocket I I don't I
don't know if I was playing for you
maybe but the good thing is you know I
kind of messed up today
um that's a bad thing there's a good
thing and a bad thing the bad thing is I
messed up whoa
that's close okay let's get the elite uh
okay we want to try to go for the super
club we couldn't so we want to get over
sheep lava bucket
uh the spider cocaine okay if you see
any of those prioritize grabbing them
otherwise prioritize your main stuff
okay okay push it the lava and spider
cooking okay yes uh I was saying the bad
thing is I messed up today with my
YouTube settings I forgot to change uh
it's to extreme low latency or something
like that so now I just have normal
latency so when when they were in chat
if you can help me yeah okay you mean
the Phoenix better excuse me uh it's not
called that in the game excuse me
and they were they were trying to help
me but they're they're like advices came
in so late all the time so now I have
real time feedback from you which is
great
and you can trust me on like chant
yeah I think they give okay but it's
hard because
it plays differently and what's going to
be preferable to one person might not be
a good play style so I'm forcing you to
play by my play style which is also not
great mind you no no no no I was like
shocked when I saw your first spider
cooking when I saw your first hold up
your stream I was like yeah I'm just
gonna check out Naruto's holy cure
stream it must be her first time surely
and then bam
uh Phoenix Shield okay you are like
absolutely
it's just so Pro edit yeah uh scared me
even I I kept getting people complaining
at me what because you're too good or
what no because they were like your
build isn't flexible I was like yeah it
is because I win when I use this build
okay so while we're here we might as
well pick up another weapon um one of
the before don't pick anything before so
what are the one of the benefits to
picking up weapons early on is then
you'll stop getting random weapons yeah
whenever you fill everything up so I
think that's one of the should we get
Hollow bomb
um
what do you want to collab it with
there's this one thing you can collab it
with I forgot what it was
um flattening board and then it gets a
flattening board you can do it with the
asuko uh tail and you can also do it
with the X potato and that one is pretty
good
I've never seen I don't think I don't
have it yet because I've never seen it
popping up you do because yeah I haven't
seen it either uh otherwise I really
don't like Hollow bomb gotta be honest
um I usually do it with the cutting
board if I do get it but that's usually
when I get it by force and pick it up or
pick it up on accident okay personally
I'd go with boys love book again because
that has two really good collaborations
no there is that that's boring we can't
keep doing the same thing okay
with the Holo bomb I like that one I
haven't seen that one in a while let's
do it then let's pick it up we'll go for
it yes yes yes yes it's strong too it's
fun okay
now
follow me
my favorite meme of her that I'm like
constantly repeating these days is the
smartest on the top of the house
[Laughter]
do you know that one no I haven't seen
it it's so funny obviously I think for
especially Western uh audience when
first getting into Hollow I was very
crucial a lot of her memes yeah it came
from her like Super Mario English stream
um where she was trying to play Mario
game with just English and you know
obviously her vocabulary is limited so
she sees like a tattoo tattoo enemy and
she makes fun of him because he has such
a small small half Turtle house
and she just says it like so so like uh
looking down upon him like
oh my God yeah
it's it's not funny when I explain it
but it's really funny I'll send you a
clip of it please please do I have water
in the fire why I like that one too
I know that one what's like your
favorite whole life memes then
um that's hard I don't think I can pick
one uh I'm I'm a filthy Marine fan I'm
in iTune I think every Marine fan has a
little bit of filthiness in them yeah
um I just do spider cooking okay for now
we have it and we're oh yeah
yeah I feel like boxing usually yes
perfect now we just need the lava bucket
let's go
okay
we do have to Max that up so you will
have to you will have to prioritize it
over some other items oh I lined it up
with the with the Kaboom with the bumps
we are getting that announcement KFC yes
yes oh my God
oh my God
ah well you already know it anyway like
I spoil it Marissa a lot about the
announcement I don't care I I'm still
waiting I've been waiting for it to be
announced so I can stop horny gripping
my thigh horny gripping you're fine you
know like you you've seen that Meme of
the guy who's like gripping his thighs
so hard that there's blood that's that's
oh his eyes not his fives no his thighs
his thighs yeah his eyes he's gripping
it until it get trailblazing get your
get your things yeah okay I'll show you
later I never heard of that before I'm
sorry it's not because of the feelings
I'm feeling in my heart I mean maybe
kind of but like it's mostly because
people Chad is shocked about your
statements
you know as the KFC myself they they get
me they're they're gonna pretend to be
surprised but they know exactly what I
mean chat is very good at doing
something like that they they pretend
like they're shocked or whatever or yeah
or something uh
yes yeah but I I spoiled you but I
didn't spoil you completely I didn't
show you everything only a small part of
of you know yes just a little bit you
can do Uber sheep here if you wanted to
just um since it's a free one that way
uh you can focus on other things when
you actually level okay oh oh first boss
six minutes in that's uh first one this
is yuffie that must be related to EOP oh
God I'm walking so much into the enemies
because I can't help it I'm okay though
I'm okay look look I'm I'm absolutely
nailing it yes you're still alive
Marissa tell us now no she will not I
will I will I will fire her if she does
I I would not do that to Kiara something
it's Kiara's news to share so that means
Kiara should share it uh that's the most
important thing
and also I think only has one more level
so if you wanted to upgrade it just so
you stop getting it too sometimes I'll
do that when I'm like close to the last
one wait which one which one uh the
nurse this one it only goes up to three
ah okay and the nice thing about it is
is it heals you uh I believe it's
lifesteal so
oh love a bucket
get my own things up you said that
before what if you but I said if you see
a weapon you need you need to pick it up
because you might not get it again
contradicting themselves no it's it's
you pick up and just at least with the
first one but otherwise if you see your
skills you should prioritize I just
didn't want to
what the [\h__\h] look what like look you
gotta revive right out of there why did
they why did they slow me down so much
what was that I was suddenly slow like a
sloth you're just you're just slow I
don't know what to tell you no it was
like for real slower than it should be
no I don't I don't know what was
happening
uh despite the cooking uh yeah let's
finish off spider cookies I mean you
wait uh never mind if I know
um
what's your favorite type of burger to
eat when you oh God
um
I like it to have everything on it so
like I like onion onion uh and it
doesn't need to be cooked but it can be
but raw onions on Burger is good too do
you like the really static burgers
um honestly I feel like at that point it
just becomes okay some point where you
need to eat it with not your hands which
takes away the purpose yeah yeah so I
feel like it's kind of not worth it uh
to do it that way
um but I usually do like at least two
patties you know
I normally always go for one patty
because I I don't know it's well too big
and it falls apart we eat differently
yeah I only eat one meal a day so I have
to uh I I usually tend to eat more
garlic a lot and I do intermittent
fasting so I eat like a really big meal
yeah sometimes I do two instead but it
depends I just don't have time to sit
down you know
interesting
dinner or what
uh no I usually uh like to eat in the
morning
and then for the rest of the day
well if you insist
bye-bye
I want to pick up a noble feather yeah
pick up another feather uh right there
perfect
time to level up your feather let's go
oh you're good now if you die again
we're still saying yes I feel safe
and I don't want to kill the way in the
mascot do you have to no no I'm we're
not we're not killing them we're saving
them so funny though that Anya's uh
mascots are these like uh in Indonesian
daggers
they look so funny
um dancer I yeah I do dancer just
because that's the last level it needs
okay
[Music]
big bird is dead
now the biggest bird in the room is me
again let's go
[Laughter]
food food yes keep keep the burgers
coming is there like a favorite fast
food chain that you have
um
yes
it's it's located in multiple places
around the us but uh I don't I don't
know if I
um
it's it's a place called you've never
eaten there before I can guarantee but
if you ever come visit me uh I'll take
you
it's called Culver's Culvers Culver's
have you ever heard of Dairy Queen yeah
I've heard of Dairy Queen yes it's like
Dairy Queen but instead of ice cream uh
it's actually custard
so a restaurant that's focused on
custard I love custard but what yeah
it's it's really good I know it sounds
weird but so they also have like uh
cheese curds which is like squishy
cheese cheese fried no cheese curd so
it's like you know what a cheese curd is
right it's like a certain kind of it's
like a certain kind of Chet loves
Culvers and seeds thank you Culver's
Bros up so real for that Queen
get that Phoenix of butter burger what
the [\h__\h] is a butterfly
um it's it's it's the Culver's Burgers
but they call their theirs it's really
good
no I wouldn't say it's really all that
buttery but it definitely tastes
different than like your usual fast food
burgers
um it's it's definitely like way better
than like a McDonald's like in terms of
like the food quality but it's also then
the price reflects that in which the
food is more expensive expensive
you've got this I'm so scared
you've got this don't be scared you're
doing so good
There She Goes
it's okay this is just a 10 minute box
um what you could do when you get to
that is you could pick up phoenix
feather and and get it to its third
level or I would do
totally up to you whatever one you want
to do
what do we do here
um oh that's a good I would maybe
re-roll just because I don't think any
of these uh yep there you go and then
just uh you could do plushie or Uber
sheep
[Music]
and one more revive just for sale so for
safety yes yes okay perfect
uh people are bringing up in and out and
Whataburger in and out I think when I
was uh in L.A
it was pretty decent yeah I didn't
understand the fries though that was not
really
that wasn't good maybe they would be
better if they were fresh because like
we had them delivered I agree with you
uh even me and Bijou went to In and Out
together and got the animal fries and I
didn't I didn't I didn't like it yeah so
apparently uh pomu is in chat Pomeranian
eh
[Music]
Pomeranian oh it's already so far up the
high up anymore
and now my chat is slow oh but uh come
on come on come on chat come on
they said we missed her Five Guys wait
was it five guys are in and out that I
had and in and out right because that
has the animal fries
she's modded right she's investigating
me your stream randomly went okay it's
back oh ah the stream went dead for me
for a second and said offline oh it's
probably because I like camped out maybe
I see oh she likes Culvers oh my God
Culver's is so good she says
it's okay they weren't there at the same
time so basically it's a timing thing so
you just have to immediately after the
other ones go you just gotta switch okay
plushie yeah it's yeah plushie here is
good
if you see the docky come up too I would
pick that up just because it's in my
opinion one of the best slowed down
again this is happening again it's like
this okay
there you go
[Laughter]
eight minutes left man it's okay we can
do this you have two additional lives oh
look at this you almost
lava bucket lava bucket because we we
are almost almost have enough for the uh
collab if we can manage to get yeah get
that get that one it's good
uh you do Uber sheep or nurses horns
either one okay oh big carrots all right
big carrots I don't think it's called
carrots
I saw a carrots in the in the British
museum the other day a British Museum
and a British museum where they stole
everything
oh my God oh my God I mean yeah
oh it's huge have you ever been to
London
I haven't uh I want to I've actually
never been to Europe which is a crying
shame it is girl I I think it would be a
dream to backpack in Europe backpack
yeah I really I really just want to go
and like hike oh you know you know what
you could do my brother did this
um he's not religious but he did this uh
what do you call it again the religious
hike
yeah yeah yeah we call it again I have
no idea
why do I keep on forgetting it
um
Chad will tell me in five minutes
it feels like five minutes a pilgrimage
yes yes yes yes yes yes yeah and it's
like it has a set route uh throughout
Europe you can start wherever you are or
you can like go back to have an even
longer pilgrimage and my brother like
kept on updating us with like pictures
of it and videos and oh my God it was
quite something like the you get for
like mostly Countryside but like
beautiful countryside and he went
through Austria through uh Switzerland
through
um France and Spain you know a lot of
countries you get through a lot of
countries there and you meet so many
people from all kinds of countries it
honestly sounded so interesting to me
that I kind of want to do it at some
point too but apparently normal people
they don't do it all in one go my
brother did it all in one go and it was
really rough but normally people go like
maybe you know they'd only do the
pilgrimage for one country in like one
and then maybe next year they do another
pilgrimage for what'd you say lava yeah
yeah yeah they do another pilgrimage
before the next you know country until
they reach their goal eventually they do
it just like
month country by country year by year
yeah Santiago is the goal yeah yeah
we can do cutting board or plushie it
doesn't matter okay
yeah but it was it was rough because
sometimes you know it's like really
really happy and you only see cool
things but sometimes the weather is like
really [\h__\h] and maybe you're not lucky
enough to find a good accommodation
because like in this like fixed route on
the on the roads there's like a lot of
free accommodations for pilgrimmers or
not free but like really cheap and they
give you food and all that but sometimes
you're unlucky and you don't find
anything and then you've got to sleep in
the shittiest weather in the rain in the
cold somewhere in a sleeping bag and
yeah but yeah I couldn't do that and
then you know my brother told me on some
days he would be walking together with
some groups
um and that would be fun and he would
befriend them but then they want to you
know go on in different paces and
um you know they split up and then for a
while you're alone and then you go kind
of crazy because somehow you go through
this like stage where it's just lonely
you see me maybe like really boring
Countryside with nothing to see it's
just empty and gray and no people around
you until then again later on you find
more people again and maybe you you find
the same group again and you're happy
and ah oh my God reuniting so it's like
this whole like mental experience man
crazy
it sounds crazy my brother also like
injured himself at some point like he
had to be treated
because yeah no he he overdid it
definitely
[Music]
yeah but still cool experience like if
you want to go hiking anyway you could
do that but it's like hardcore hiking
yeah
that's okay
yeah you did it was like everywhere
quick get the get the get the box
uh
yep
okay let's see
I love the bird sound when I activate my
special
is Kiara strong um they're under five
minutes almost four minutes left
yep
yeah
bucket now now we just need to hit Level
50 and you can get the next Super calam
oh that's still it looks like it's still
a while to go until 10 levels we might
we might be able to do it oh yeah right
that was my issue like I I had a really
good run and was I was gonna do like
super cool ABS but I never reached level
50. I ended my stage run at like 45 or
whatever yeah I never saw the super
collab
oh hello yeah oh big fat chunky Cat
hello
be mindful of your surroundings yes
oh my God okay I'm good I'm good I'm
good we're good oh it's the wool ball
um
I'm not even paying attention much to
these stickers yes
you stamps that I like but otherwise I
tend to ignore them
so many fat cats I love them
I have a very bad cat do you know the
the palace cats the palace cats yeah p-a
oh god oh what the [\h__\h] is going on
you're good it's just a timing thing
it's showing you all when they're gonna
pop up body pillow okay oh and and then
uh you could you could do Ian curse if
you wanted to collab that with a cutting
board again
um since you want to do ASA cocoa with
the yeah cutting board right if we ever
find it I'd get Ian curse here just so
you're set up for another collaboration
okay
okay oh yeah it's like this wild cat
that
um has a really short neck it's kind of
it looks kind of chubby and I don't know
it's just really freaking cute it has
like small small legs and it's it's
p-a-l-l-a-s Palace kit
okay look it up wait wait wait wait yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Carl's cat yeah you remember yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you sent the
video again recently didn't you
it's okay revive incoming oh wait I
somehow survived how the [\h__\h] did I
survive because of the doll the the
plushie will do that to you because you
see how you you still have that uh that
buffer bar yes yes that's what's keeping
you alive that's why the doll is so
freaking good man I might still have to
end up using over five I'm not I'm not
sure but it's pretty close to the ending
so I still have to be I think it's kind
of hard you're gonna have like three
bosses I won't say who or anything but
we all have like three bosses to kill so
okay the end only gets harder okay I'm
scared to go out of the screen dude
you've got it
okay here I am once again I turn into
pieces can't deny it can't pretend I
thought you would have won broken up you
can find what you want you won't get to
hear the tears I cry
[Laughter]
was that Kelly Clarkson
I have no idea I think so I loved Kelly
Clarkson man
I don't know too much for the music what
the [\h__\h] I have to be honest you have to
love Kelly Clarkson girl I'm sorry we
can't like everything the same
no no we should otherwise don't accept
it
can't to be friends it's good to have
differences
if we were exactly the same person it
wouldn't be any fun
why would we challenge each other okay
but we are almost the same produce each
other to do things
let's go
and Fire
yeah
fire fire pants on fire
no please stop with the please stop
please stop with the spam please stop
with the spam okay you got the Uber
sheet maxed out
there's food everywhere you just got can
you take the controls but you also said
you only played this map twice
yeah but uh I lost because well I I won
the second time but I lost my first time
only because I was using uh new
new people so I didn't know how to play
them so you laughed once you won once
how come you only played it twice
um because I was just mostly focusing on
the new girls playing them and like
seeing what they're doing that was [\h__\h]
holy oh [\h__\h]
but I still haven't used the Revival
feather
[Laughter]
the red lines but then that made forced
me to go inside of a little bit of the
the mob so you don't gotta explain
yourself to me it's okay I love you
[Music]
um
[Applause]
I don't I want to switch this out and go
ahead
who cares
okay
my favorite burger by the way to go back
on that topic yes yes
um this is this is so such a basic
cheeseburger but somehow I have this
special thing oh uh oh also be careful
the slow down guy is there oh no you can
collaborate those two their
collaboration isn't bad
is that but that's not what you wanted
to see huh but I guess let's look at
this yeah but we've got we've got 30
seconds left you almost simple
something I've never seen before so
honestly I'm happy about seeing
something I haven't seen before oh there
you go
[\h__\h] you go [\h__\h] yourself get out of
here
okay so burger Burger King so the Burger
King has this yes uh Bergen has this
some this crispy crispy chicken burger
um that I absolutely love they don't
have it the same way in every country
like it depends on the country I ate it
in Japan but it was completely different
so I don't wanna I don't want people to
think that this is this is what it is
but uh oh my God what the [\h__\h] I'm gonna
[Music]
yes okay
there's a burger
okay one last remaining
[\h__\h] okay okay bosses are here and you
still have one extra life okay yeah okay
do you like chicken burgers
oh I I do but I have to admit usually I
don't really like chicken because at
fast food places here at least it's kind
of dubious meat
that's what I feel about
um minced meat Burgers a lot of the time
from the cheap restaurants because I'm
like well what are they mixing for
chicken I feel like yeah it's at least
probably mostly chicken
I would hope so but you know the crispy
chicken you know what that one looks
like
holy [\h__\h] yes
um yes you do it's like you know it has
this like almost like corn flake uh
outside like it's really crispy really
crunchy it's like very special like
normally you know when people name their
burgers crispy chicken or crispy
something crispy it's ah
uh it's it's usually not that crispy you
know the crispy chicken burgers honestly
the best crispy to ketchup was for
someone else okay I I have a reason I
don't like ketchup I shouldn't talk it's
really disgusting so I feel like it's
not something that you should repeat
okay you know like on on stream say it
say it are you sure
um
are you sure what could it possibly be
you're gonna throw up if I tell you oh
apparently stream was a little bit dead
or was it just a check it's it's back
I've got it open okay
is back now hi hi she's about to tell us
apparently something disgusting yeah
I'll have to show this on my stream
later too but basically
um
I
when I was very very little I had a
sweet tooth right and I got a cavity and
they they it was a baby tooth so it was
going to come out so they put a crown on
it but obviously as you know the crown
doesn't really stop the cavity it just
stops it from like spreading to other
teeth yeah um so they eventually oddly
enough the cap fell off which is not
supposed to happen I remember them
vividly having to go into my mouth with
a wrench
tooth out
um as a child I was awake yeah while you
were awake yeah well I was awake does
ketchup remind you of blood or something
no no no no no so
um because I was very very young you
know how sometimes they'll give you
those little tooth containers and you
happen I think I intended to throw it
away but somehow it it got lost and I
realized not in my room but in my
sister's room there was a weird smell
that smelt like oddly like ketchup right
and oh hey you got the super collab
thing how do I do it I need to need to
get to the golden animal it's in the
middle
around
okay let's try
you've got this I want the super Cola
before I die oh my God okay run fast
feline for it this is very dangerous
what I'm doing right now you've got this
um oh but so basically uh what had
happened whatever you want to get look
just pick it Yep
this is so good
oh
scan froze delicious gorilla lamp all
around standing inside the Genghis Khan
area he's free HP per second oh it heals
considers Foothills oh
yes I can't even pick up everything [\h__\h]
that dude stamp
okay cut keep keep it up keep on oh yeah
so I found I found out later that the
tooth had somehow I think my sister
stole the tooth which is why I lost it
why would she steal it I don't know and
somehow it ended up under her dresser
um and was stinking up the roof and I
realized so I eventually found it and
and grabbed it and um because it was in
my hand and kind of like close to my
face because I was a smaller
um demon than it it's wreaked of rotten
ketchup and every time now I smell
ketchup all I can think of is that smell
and why ketchup
I don't know why but it just melt that's
just what it smelled like so I was like
oh
okay
I'm gonna be wrong I'll still eat
ketchup but like especially like warm
tomato sauce I can't or like cold cold
tomato sauce I can't do it I can't do
full cold Tomatoes it's like unless it's
like fresh fresh tomatoes is fine I mean
I mostly like anything with tomatoes the
only thing I don't like that I tried the
other day because everybody does it and
I'm like why do they do it in airplane
rides you know how people go for tomato
juice
because it's good for
um something Chad will surely tell me I
forgot what it was but I think it helps
you to
um survive something and I tried it out
okay it's like really healthy in in
plain rice it makes sense somehow but
yeah I tried it out and it's disgusting
I hated it but I don't like tomato juice
but I just as I said I don't like cold
tomatoes so
you never Focus the bosses uh yeah I'm
trying man
at least I'm surviving well the issue is
if you don't kill them too fast
everything will just keep getting harder
true so you need you need to kill them
ah wait you could just pick up a weapon
and start leveling it up some people it
doesn't
make you immune to a plane crash no um
no no why don't you guys know about it
no
it's not no
no no no no no no
the taste of food changes a lot of light
no no no no no no there's an actual
effect to it
okay uh what did I even kill one of the
three bosses
I don't know if you have honestly I it's
hard to see I keep I keep seeing uh the
Muna still so I think maybe you've
gotten the others oh [\h__\h]
yeah I'm dying but it's okay yeah just
keep picking up food I have the I have
um a little red Vibe oh you need more
speed
yeah I feel like how the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to get Muna when she's like
zooming across the screen
um because she zoomed at you it's
because your movement is too good my
movement is too good oh
we're just gonna get lucky just down
we're gonna stay
um stay strong
and don't die first we'll finish off
yeah
oh okay
are we already married
this is like the emotional moment where
I must I must no matter what I must ask
you to marry me
congratulations you can make your
announcement
let's go yeah you did it you're so good
at this thing sausage
soup's a small sausage let's go
congratulations oh my God thank you so
much for being with me in these trying
times of course I look forward to more
Hollow house but for now I'll leave you
so you can make your announcement let me
tell you I want to find out because you
felt like I don't know like like oh is
this not good to tell on stream but I
think your story is totally like
understandable there's nothing to feel
embarrassed about
no I I just uh I don't want to gross
people out you know rather my my big I
don't think it grosses anyone at all
right I mean yeah
yeah you know when you know when you're
like having dinner and then somebody
talks about something that's kind of
gross and then some people will be like
oh my God can you like not what are you
the type of person you're that type of
person who says don't
yeah okay I'm like really I don't really
give a [\h__\h] about that like normally I'm
like whatever keep on talking like it
doesn't matter I can separate these two
things in my brain I think maybe maybe I
get disgusted easily but that's just me
okay okay okay I will then if we ever
eat together I will not bring up
disgusting topics thank you
um people say they heard much worse good
good yeah
good okay they're not they're not
grossed out
it would only be gross if you made them
smell it yeah that would have been yeah
I I pray to never have to smell a smell
like that again it's understandable
though that that kind of stays in your
brain in your mind and then you you like
influenced by it forever I don't know if
I have something like that but you know
yeah hopefully not it's better it's
better to not it's okay mayonnaise is
superior anyway it is mayonnaise
mayonnaise I love mayonnaise uh
specifically with mustard I really like
mustard mayonnaise with mustard
yeah it's better on sandwiches than it
is are you dipping the mayonnaise in the
mustard or the mustard into the mayor I
mix them together and then spread them
okay honestly I had that in a recipe and
it was pretty good yeah no there if you
ever uh with fries personally instead of
ketchup I really like to do mayonnaise
and then a bit of mustard and mix it
together it's really good yeah fries
with mayonnaise is my favorite toe yeah
yeah yeah that's the reveal one well no
Albertville nothing so far I'm gonna
reveal now let's go
all right congratulations I'll leave
good luck thank you bye-bye
thank you for the help I love you of
course
say bye I'm Gonna Leave This
I don't I mean I mean I feel like
eventually we could have done it without
her but thanks to her we were able to do
everything first try in the end
thank you no Issa for helping me also it
was like you know it's just so much
easier having the immediate feedback
when today I messed up with the chat uh
everything's so slow right so yeah
ah okay
um I'm nervous but kfb knows what I'm
announcing anyway so I shouldn't be
nervous oh you know what we could go
I never use this so far but we could go
here oh [\h__\h] this is where I recorded my
this is embarrassing don't look ah I
forgot that I left my SEAL costume there
that's you didn't see that
mysterious question
okay wait I have no no chat box here let
me let me move one over here
[Music]
I see Lego
the announcement is
I was never a phoenix or I'm
transitioning into a seal
yeah chat
you want to show up or so maybe no
there you are
there you go let's go where in the hell
do I put this chat I don't even know
there's no space here to chat put you
down here
okay Welcome to The kfb Newsroom with
the latest KMP news
let's go I'll keep the whole of your
music on
um I have something to announce
um
uh right
should I announce an announcement or
should I announce the thing
well if you look at this this was my
schedule for this week right
So
today we're announcing something and
then something's happening on Wednesday
hmm what's going on oh my God oh my God
so special
wow wait
what do you think it is guys what could
it be what could it be
I am very excited
to announce something to you we
are not there
no I'm not pregnant
which which graphic do I even show
at this one
okay
so the following days will all be very
exciting because because
pineapple no
but also pineapple
here comes the announcement uh
[Music]
free
two
[Music]
first album point of view with many many
artists involved available for pre-order
for physical copy
uh on August 29th 2023 jst of course
there will be digital as well
uh digital is gonna be um I think
Tuesday at midnight in every country
oh my God
and the album
will be accompanied by some envies and
so on but I'll I'll uh continue to
announce this uh you know in the coming
days
so basically uh the ring for the
adventure tomorrow the time for that is
because
um I think one hour into that stream or
no half an hour in is when the pre-order
starts for the album in case they want
to get a physical copy why do you want
to get a physical copy because the
physical copy actually comes with an
extra song that's not in the digi not
extra sound but like a remix of Special
lyrics of an existing song that won't be
in the digital and I'll say it for a
moment in nihongo as well
foreign
I have Japanese version of this graphic
too let me show the Japanese ones
um this one
[Music]
this oh my God this one even spoilers
this one doesn't say it oh my God this
One spoilers it
uh that Sparks remix
physical copy so yeah it will be a
Sparks remix with a very special one the
actual title is
wait you know what I won't spoiler it so
I will be releasing in the next three
days
um some teasers you know album teaser
and B teaser and so on so for the album
teaser
um you will see all the names of the
songs so you know what I think I'll
I already have the graphics but I think
I'll not show it yet
so that I can keep you guys on your
tippy toes for a little bit longer
um what I do want to say is that the
album does include songs that I
previously released the singles will be
making up a part of the album so
yeah because I was asked them do you
want to do this I'm like I guess why not
yeah sure
vanilla or city just City and oh yeah I
want to say you know you might be
surprised uh why I'm doing an album
cover like this
that has no image of me basically
you know I've been trying with my music
since uh do you to kind of
as much as I can make it like create
something that even like people who are
not into whole life can consume uh I
hopefully uh without like feeling like
what the [\h__\h] is this you know
um so that's why I kept the MV for do
you pretty serious like with no like
whole life references and stuff like
that
um and I felt like I wanted to continue
that for the MB uh for the not for them
for the um album cover I wanted
something that doesn't immediately
scream into your face hey anime let's go
no I wanted something more abstract and
um yeah I don't know normal looking and
you know a lot of album covers out there
that I see or like whatever CD covers
just are very simplistic and abstract
and all that so I wanted to go for
something like that instead of the
typical the typical you know anime
illustration bam there you go uh it's
just you know not only in terms of CD
covers just uh in terms of merchandise
Etc I feel like I'm doing that all the
time anyway so I thought I should just
do something more normal yeah normally
friendly
um
so maybe that way you know what you
could do if you get more than one
physical copy you can give this to an
unknowing friend who's not into her life
just give it to them they they will
think maybe it's just a normal artist
you know not anime and then they'll
listen to it unknowingly and then
they're like hey wait this is actually
pretty good stuff who is this and then
then you drag them into the rabbit hole
anyone who's maybe like a little bit
against uh you know getting into anime
stuff maybe anyone who's hesitant or so
yeah
um so yeah the artists that are named
here
um they're like uh producers at the
lyric liquor
writers and so on
um
yeah so it's a big list of people uh
participating Kira of course Moni who's
been writing actually all of the lyrics
of All of the new songs
um Johnny R uh a dial
is something who uh I've been working
with for the first time this time for a
new song
WD Martin torabian
um astrophysics pinky Kai Gojo who made
hinotori kaikojo and Shino Aya are the
ones who made uh hinotori and heart
Challenger and astrophysics and Pinky
are the ones who made uh favorite night
before you know you know and Kira before
made sparkson do you so those songs are
of course on the album yeah yeah yeah
Rabbit Hole starter pack let's go
huh
yes yes yes I'm so excited to show you
guys so basically let me tell you
tomorrow
um during ring fit
and will be the album pre-order if you
want to get a physical copy I think
uh I think it will be made to order I
have to check again
um
yeah uh
oh this is a
it's a Japanese version kind of outdated
I think
ah OBS hello hello hello are we back
it's gonna be sold out no no no no it's
not limited uh the the CD will be uh not
limited
you can order it how many you want and I
think it's you know like the usual
merchandise it should be made to order
but it will be faster I was told that it
would probably be sent out around
October or so not like half a year later
this should be definitely earlier
would sell it in a second otherwise I
don't know about that but let me let me
continue I wanted to say
um that yeah during ring fit will be the
album pre-order start and then during
ring fit we will together
look at
the album teaser I've prepared an album
teaser
and we will we will I will put up a
Premiere and we will listen to it
together once I'm done with the ring
fitting and then on the same day at
midnight like Tuesday uh midnight for
every country whatever whatever time is
midnight for you will be the digital
release on Spotify and Amazon music and
iTunes etc
etc
yes yes yes yes yes yes very exciting
I'm so excited
bye bye
are you guys excited
and then uh yeah on on ah here then
Wednesday the question mark question my
question mark is the new album
okay I'll be doing a little scuffed 3D
album karaoke
and and then at the end of it I'll be
dropping another teaser
for something yes
another I never teaser yet so I have two
teasers coming up
hi hi
I'm signing exciting pineapple what's
the pineapple but I don't know I don't
know I don't know what you guys are
going on about I just like pineapples
what do you mean
I mean
archived oh yes it will be archive
because it's my songs I'll be singing
all of my previous songs and all of my
new songs so everything that's included
in the album I'll be singing in the
karaoke for the first time and in 3D
with a special
keys are coming out afterwards and then
and then on Thursday this is not even on
the schedule but on Thursday after
Baldur's Gate and before the members
only stream
is another video coming out
but you heard what I just said about
birthday right
that uh yeah basically basically three
days in a row Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
I'm putting out some special videos that
I want you guys to watch
yes
do you guys like the look of this
you like it
do you like it
the album cover hmm
I I had I struggled with coming up with
an album name and then money helped me
and gave me some ideas and she inspired
me yeah we inspired each other
uh you like it it looks sleek it will
look so nice in your shelf guys
and point of view basically the album is
my point of view and also your point of
view
um
that's
what it means to be
the songs the lyrics
the feelings
The Vibes they're my point of view but
also your point of view
hey hey
it is divine oh thank you it's kind of
basic but elegant yeah I wanted it to be
kind of basic you know
the album cover was made by antsy who
you guys maybe saw maybe on Twitter
before making some
um you know self-made uh
a whole life like covers
for release songs like in his own style
um like this for example and it caught
my eye every now and then and I thought
hmm actually you know what instead of
going for something like
typical anime
um I think I want something stylish like
this for my album cover
um his mama totally heard it no she
hasn't heard any of the new songs
narissa heard
one or two
two maybe actually uh of the songs yeah
foreign
ERS gate group a teaser of something but
yeah besides no reason I think a myth
myth hurt uh probably two songs before
two I sent it to them uh one of them I
forced uh them to listen to like in
January
one of them eh ah come on
why does why does YouTube always die for
me like in an important moments what the
[\h__\h]
hello it's back right yeah when we were
like in Japan in January February I that
was the time where I kind of started
working on the album I think and I I had
this one song already really early on
and I
um was so happy with it so proud of it
and I had
I I had to have someone listen to it a
little bit
we're back
you're back for a while now right I'm
not talking to myself all this time
[\h__\h] owl LA palace too
ah one of the songs the early one yeah
yeah I I had her listen to it because
it's
uh very very
cool I think she I think I think uh yeah
I think I think you guys like the songs
on
them so I tried to
um basically have some songs that are
similar to what I've done before
um but also some stuff is kind of
different
um
it's been stable for a bit okay thank
God but no it has many hiccups what the
[\h__\h] YouTube why Always In important
times
so I would like you guys to be there for
all the premieres of the videos if you
can
um I'll be putting up a premiere for and
the reservation for the stream for
tomorrow the ringford stream and the
premiere of the album teaser if you
could be there you know it'll be so hype
to listen to everything together for the
first time yes yes it might be
especially the album teaser might be at
the shitty time for n a but it's really
short if you can wake up even just for a
little bit that would be cool
the extra song will not be in the album
teaser though because it's not finished
the the remix
it's not finished
that one because the CD takes a while to
reproduce anyway uh it has a further
away deadline
well any of the songs be in German no
but
every single one of the new songs is in
English
fully English 100 English
so you won't be able to understand
everything and um
let's go
yeah so I am I'm excited for you guys to
learn the songs and sing along uh when
you play them you know
and sing along maybe in my karaoke
stream that will be on
first day first day first day no
Wednesday Wednesday
yes yes yes
best myth speaker proving her
credentials
best web speaker in the en yes
we should done at least one Japan song
well but you know an album already has
Japanese songs hey hi Challenger and uh
Hino Tony so well
I know
you know I I was working on with money
this time and she wrote some really cool
lyrics for every song
and I love them all very much one of
them has
one of them has maybe too many innuendos
but that's okay I love it anyway
yeah
yeah that's the announcement for now and
the next days will be very exciting so
let's have fun together let's share this
uh together
I uh yeah I am I can't wait oh my God I
think I will read some super chats at
least because I'm kind of behind
but I'll stay in the screen okay
so you can see this up here
just give me one moment please
um
one moment please
[Music]
okay
uh
us okay
okay you gotta sleep early tonight oh
yeah [\h__\h]
oh
ah oh that's true maybe maybe after
ringford we'll read super chats Maybe
tomorrow is it 10 30. ah wait thanks for
reminding me oh no you know it
it's big thing you made my album
pre-order starting date so early and
then Gemma was like um you should stream
when this is happening and I'm like
[Music]
you will not be able to read why not of
course I will
well then I have the whole day it starts
at 10 30 a.m for me
see it's uh however EST is 4 30 so it's
kind of shitty for a lot of Na people
but it's good for sea people and Asian
countries
uh 5 30 yeah so if you can be there I'll
do my best
[Music]
you know I thought for a short stream I
need something energizing
so I thought why not do ring fit
um
why would I only get for six supers why
why why
yeah it's a um I'm sorry that's am yes
foreign
for you people who have to work I know I
know wasn't my choice I I wasn't gonna
stream at all I was just gonna throw
around the teaser and then have you guys
focus on the teaser
um
yeah
it is what it is did I miss the new hat
announcement
no new hat I'm sorry
what time is that in L.A I don't know is
it
see YouTube and OBS is constantly dying
right now anyway
so maybe it's good to leave now
it's unstable YouTube and OBS very
unstable
maybe better to go and hope for better
stability tomorrow
um
yeah hi hi it's telling me to go to
sleep yeah
ah this dude's too high for YouTube
I'm so excited for you know the album
because I can at once
shove so many new songs and your face is
yeah so I'll go prepare the streams for
tomorrow uh the stream and the video for
tomorrow and you go you go have a nice
day okay
and a nice evening and a nice night and
and and please even if you can't see all
of the streams or videos that are coming
up please make sure in any case to
listen to the album when it's out there
on the Digital streaming services please
please support my first ever album
hi
[Music]
okay okay thank you everybody for today
thank you nerissa for the big help what
would I have done without you oh my god
oh that was fun and in German we say of
Vida
um
let's go
exciting
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]