[Music]
[\h__\h]
hello hello welcome to kirby's dream
buffet
everything in this game looks so
delicious released game by the highly
acclimated
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah i was so surprised
this game is only fifteen dollars
instead of sixty dollars like every game
yeah i'm so uh we have gathered here
today because um
the moment i saw this release trail not
really australia the first trailer about
the game i was like i wanna play this
there's no release date yet but then i i
hit up these girls according to their
image colors because there's a green one
and a blue one
i was wondering how you decided that
makes sense
i thought you know i'm not pink but i
didn't want to kick myself out of my own
collapse
and i was like whatever
i'm close enough
pink is adjacent to orange right yeah
and i did manage to maybe you guys see
it on my screen i didn't manage to get
like a fire red skin already so that's
looking pretty gorgeous
in this game yeah yeah
yes there's skins and it's kind of like
fauna said fana what did you describe it
as oh it's kind of like fall guys meets
mario party meets kirby
i think
yes yes yes yes
meets fortnite with the skin
you don't have to put in fortnite
i don't know i'm getting real fortnite
vibes with this game right now
um
i'm a uk
i'm playing in handheld mode so if i'm
looking down yeah i'll fix it william
has fish on her head i wanted to ask
amen about her fist delivery tell me
about it oh yeah i got fish delivered
today i got um six clams they're little
tiny fresh water clams
uh-huh yeah i'm gonna put them they're
gonna live in the sand in my tank and
then i got a two bumble bee gobies
they're little tiny striped fish they're
very cute they're cute
you're gonna kill them
and i got um five black neon tetras and
then uh one pea puffer
one pea powder pea pea puffer fish
what is the pea puffer fish yeah oh
is it poisonous no no it's fresh water
and um they're very very very cute and
uh yeah they're acclimating right now
can you spell that one
p puffer
p p e a
like okay
is it green
peep popper
oh it's green
oh it's cute it looks like a frog
wow
[Music]
yeah it's really cute
what are you gonna name the fish peanuts
[Music]
peanut butter you got any bottom feeders
oh wow the pea puffer will attack other
fish and stuff so probably not for that
because he's just in the tank by himself
ah
what about shrimp sir oh yeah i have a
ton of shrimp they have like 30 now
because they've multiplied by themselves
oh what kind of
cherry shrimp
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah this is the it's the fish talk
the fish tank episode two everybody you
always wanted to come back here it is
don't get me started i can talk about it
for like an hour so let's move on
now you can you can talk about it if you
feel like uh
you have enough what what's the word of
yo i only know it in japanese always
why are you playing
yeah
i don't know enough spare time
it's not spare time but spare
spare
space
head space i don't know but yeah we're
going to play this game for a while it's
apparently kind of small but yeah let's
see how long it goes it looks fun
open up a room
okay
okay so you girls know the the magical
number yeah wait yes rewriting or green
grand prix
uh um
yes
okay
we don't have to push that i think
though
oh yeah maybe you do
yes
yeah
good good
do we join now
i have joined uh you can join me too i
already have
yeah i'm doing it
[Music]
i'm joining
there's no numbers shown here right i
can show now okay
girl it's time for some fun oh by the
way we didn't have self-introductions
left to right crony go
wait wait what happened
what did happen
wait are we complete even
yeah yeah okay
i think there's randoms drawing too
crowdy introduce yourself
oh yeah oh good oh god
um
i'm oral cronie i'm ward enough time and
everything oh
like i
i am like i manage time really badly
yeah
but i like manage
oh god
what's your recent uh hobby
my recent hobby
yes oh god i have a recent hug
you you did asmr recently oh yeah i
uploaded
a cover and everything yeah yeah well
that's not a hobby is that a what
why not oh my
it could be a hobby
sure that can be a hobby
singing is a hobby singing is a hobby
you sound really
curvy too much for the mental strain
[Music]
game actually i think oh i think i may
have said that too
yeah me too i never played it before
[Music]
in the practice round that i did with
fauna
it's okay you can just blame it on the
lag
yeah
[Music]
uh introduce yourself hi
i'm sarah spana i'm from holla live
council
and i like
sweets you don't seem stressed out by
this at all
i have like what's your favorite sweets
i like french toast
and i like peach pie
what french pie
peach peach pie and french toast
but i'll take a french pie and a peach
toast too
oh that smells good
i never had peach pie before really
oh i want to make one
yeah
oh
well i've been meaning to make one but
while it's still
summer
why is it so hard to control
us
it is hard oh big why are you so big
[Music]
is that good enough uh no
no
no tell us more
which fish
is your favorite so far in your whole
fish life
your life it's a fish mommy
i guess uh i like the pea puffer because
it's super cute and interactive they're
like little dogs oh
okay
oh my god like little dogs oh that's
cute
[Music]
eat the cake
eat the cake did connie win
oh my god
[Music]
why why do you say that just because you
were the pink kirby you're the main
character
no i guess maybe that's the problem
because i'm the red kirby now like maybe
i should have been the pink one
i bought strawberries at the supermarket
today i think that should give me a
bonus
i also went swimming today what did you
guys do today in terms of moving your
body mm-hmm i just woke up
[Music]
you
that will become the largest kirby
that's a lot of strawberries oh man what
the heck
finally justice has been served
i got donuts
[Music]
oh
bird
i'm also playing on handheld wait you
can play it
another way
you're pretty
yeah
very round extremely
so round oh my gosh
[Music]
but that might be the only choice
i don't know i just i just get a
different character i think this one's
messed up i just oh seconds
okay okay good luck that's a good time
and we just ended the round anyway
next minute just gonna use that as an
excuse for getting fourth place
always the excuses with this girl
i got a burger hat too
oh
did you get it maybe i got you yeah did
you get orange juice
i got orange so maybe you got it
i got the bandana waddly
and
uh
orange
finally i can be my
oh nice there's so many colors though i
wonder what other other colors are there
maybe maybe some patterns and like
rainbows
but yeah there are a ton of colors
aren't there
that's a lot of colors
so
cute even with a weapon perfect
okay i'm styling
i'm sorry already feeling the addiction
to unlocking all of the cosmetics
yeah
by far guys i always missed out on like
the cool items that i wanted yeah right
i never even got i think
when i first debuted it um the oh my god
it's just
quite nostalgic um after being awake for
i don't know how many hours 24 hours or
so because of the debut relay that we
did that was really stupid um i had a
stream plans to follow up after the the
group collab and that was fall guys and
at that point i was absolutely sleep
deprived and my goal was to get the
chicken costume back then which is one
of the first costumes that you could get
i did not get it and i sucked at four
guys on that day but
some traumatic stream
have any like
big regrets in terms of like streaming
like i shouldn't have streamed on that
day that was terrible what have i done
oh
maybe your debut
my tv no i know what
our council is about to have our
anniversary so it's about time oh did we
get kicked out
was this something you regret maybe this
stream won't be the one
one stream that i regret
um
was like the model went so wacky that
time and like taking like a clock um it
was stop talking and nobody explodes the
string with fauna and i was ticking like
a clock there
that was a cute stream
a man it wasn't that was fun cute crony
but it's so stressful it was so
stressful
this isn't stressful you were taking
another clock because game made you feel
stressed out but
[Music]
wow that was making you feel that made
you feel weird
i'm like stressed out because
i tried to get it working and it's not
so you just sometimes you have to say
[\h__\h] it i don't give a [\h__\h]
true
what about
who was that with cortana was that you
yeah
i always wondered how that happened that
was so funny i like halloween stuff i
know
i don't know whenever i
say the name too sometimes it just comes
back but i think i disabled it for now
successfully
our phone thing i'm at pc
oh yeah i've been here
oh hi
my capture card seems to have stopped
working
oh okay
why aren't collabs
lately
why not find that just
outside
the mario kart
hello
i know what's happening
maybe it's me
maybe you can't collab with me
for now well at least uh my internet's
still working
yeah that's good
but the game kept hmm
well test it out a little bit i'm gonna
ask
that you
have regretful feelings about um
maybe working on ppp minecraft or
something
why was it that it just i [\h__\h] it up
but and it i don't want to go back and
touch it i never want to go back and you
visit it so often you know people keep
kept on telling me oh just go to the
japan server everything will be easier
and i said no i'm gonna use what i'm
gonna build here because i'm gonna use
the resources that we have on this
server not cheat and go to the other one
yeah now you won't let me blow it up
i mean it's kind of iconic right
yeah yes maybe i'll turn it into a
resort on the inside thanks for the
memories even though they weren't so
great i guess
that weren't great
they were great
building the tunnel that was that was
not great
what do you mean
the tunnel was one of my biggest regrets
maybe
but that was also iconic i feel like
we're starting to realize all the
regrets are iconic streams
iconic i guess it's a
yeah i don't know chad do you think that
was iconic
the building the tunnel
itself the act of doing
it was kind of a troll troll action
[Music]
good evening we went on an adventure
a very straightforward straight
adventure straight straight sometimes
sometimes
right sometimes left but mostly straight
adventure
good times
an adventure that's for
four to six four to five blocks wide
at least now we can laugh about it yeah
yes it's a long time ago it's really ah
i like it i'm in the the second year
anniversary is coming up soon for
council first anniversary right
you guys feel like you've been around
for longer oh
hmm fonda is currently
somewhere
oh hello sorry i'm trying to fix my
capture card
oh
what could it be
can we can i'm a troubleshooter man i
think it's good now
i think
oh
okay yeah the ribbon on your neck
uh you should like have you ever heard
that horror story like the lady who
takes off the ribbon
falls out oh yeah
maybe but no it's not like that i just
have a thing for chokers
oh
yeah they're cute wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait i think
you told me about the choker
yeah
seems to have a thing for it too because
he keeps on them even though that's true
even in your normal outfit right yeah
yeah and every outfit every outfit
that does make me suspicious though if
we never see your bare neck how do you
know
how do you know
maybe i'm somewhat of a
uh
what's the word the the dude that's put
together
frankenstein
frankenstein frankenstein
a little bit of a kiara stein
[Laughter]
are you ready to do another round yeah
do you think i can rejoin her
what
what do you think i can rejoin with the
same code oh yeah yeah i think so
yeah we'll i'll do it
push play again i pushed it yeah push
push play again i pushed it in the same
lobby okay hopefully i'm did we do it
oh wait i think i'm alone wait am i
alone oh i was alone in the lobby
there's three people here i'm alone
[Music]
our secret password that we will not
share with anyone that is super secret
and super super complicated
go make home please
[Laughter]
[Music]
i see you guys
yeah everyone's here sorry
but the game wants oh wait that's what
was wrong here we go we're back
okay yay
time for more
fighting
are there different maps than the one we
were on so yeah i feel like they're all
kind of similar though maybe
the principle of what's to do is similar
but they have different designs and all
that
that's how you say that
yeah it's a german word
what is this
i'll tell you a little bit about
[Music]
at the end that's true what is this
okay so let me tell you
[Applause]
so uh
in japan because they really like they
really love bangkok i guess the
simplicity of it they really like it
there
uh but
uh i think it's a little bit too simple
for my taste i like my cake to have like
some some cream and some strawberries or
whatever is there no cream
um i mean i guess maybe you could serve
it with some cream but normally it's
just a bamboo
but it's kind of boring
but what
oh is it that in the back the ring cake
yeah it looks like a tree like the
inside of a tree if you cut up a tree
okay i'm gonna take you all apart now
take us apart
like like surgery
yes
how comforting
a [\h__\h] european pink okay
it's a it's a little rough over here too
oh bacon
you may be winning the game so far but i
won your mom eating last night
[Music]
just wait
your mommy too
[Music]
i'm not sure my mom is interested in
girls
[Laughter]
oh man
but navi mama was so sweet to me you
know
she's so cute
oh wow i bet
we talked a bit about you um
did you tell her my secrets
which one
[Music]
[Applause]
told her all your secrets
i also told you all your public stories
not only your secrets are told or
anything we just talked about your 24 7
as a joke we didn't
in the first place oh no just kidding
that's not true
[Music]
a single time and i still only have
three strawberries less than you
okay step up your game
or maybe don't don't step it up
i don't get this model
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
yeah it takes a while
i'm too small
oh gosh
at least you couldn't see who did it
finally i got a tornado
unbelievable i will not rest i will not
let you girls go today until i get first
oh god
cherries
how did you grow so large
wow
so oh so formidable
damn
[Music]
um what are the character trees
let's play again click play again
please
please ian curtis leave us alone for one
round
so i'm here with
i'm here
wait i'm here with ami
i will be there
with cronies why don't they separate us
you guys join us for now
now you join us no i joined you last
time
how do we okay we can leave
good luck finding us
yummy no i see you crony i see your
shadow
i see you
hi
hey
do we all have to press that
oh
the race is so intense man go go go yeah
this is the part that's kind of like
fall guys
but much faster oh
it looks so good it looks so tasty i
want one what are these like speed
boosts i'm scared hey what
you have to go on the sides
no oh no oh no
i don't understand ah
how do you guys all get tornadoes and
[\h__\h]
did you use the boss
yeah but i never get it
do you use it
yeah
with r right yeah
[Music]
i never said i was good
[Laughter]
[Music]
wow
oh my goodness
at least something
[Laughter]
oh
i'm sorry cronie i just wanted to be
like you
i just wanted to become round like you
but you already were in the first round
yeah
give the others something to enjoy too
huh
[Music]
what is this moon
what's happening right now i have no
idea
get everything i'm rolling
us
baby hating
she's so hungry i am
like a hungry hippo yeah
okay i don't see anyone is that a good
sign oh i'm sorry
i don't see anyone
are you
yeah
i didn't think that would happen
oh my goodness guys
it's ruthless
kirby is ruthless
[Laughter]
let me go
oh no very crony was eating blueberries
before the streets
i still am you still are
very much in the sweet berry mood oh no
oh no i'm just gonna let's go for the
middle i'm just gonna
i don't know i think it's just one
but i don't really know
yeah the fourth piece
fourth person i'm too scared to try to
test it
i hate this one this one sucks
i like this one i never get [\h__\h] and i
keep getting cut off
oh goodness
oh
[Music]
give me a box
i'm just gonna throw you guys off love
you guys
[Music]
uh-oh
oh goodness
ah give me that give me that give me
that
oh
[Music]
i don't have a strategy
i have a chance i have a chance
no you can make the most out of it
well i have to see the bonus stars
anything could happen
i know somebody looks really big
oh yes
oh
what little chunky
second kfb can you believe it
they are shook heads
shooky shook head oh kirby burger oh no
minion game course available oh so you
unlock
[Music]
i think
play again
yes
i hope they put us in the same lobby
have you ever heard the saying uh
nintendo online is four dollars a month
and it shows
oh oh
no also free oh we're all together no
cronies i'm here oh god is here
oh crony what happened to you're not
blue anymore
i want to burger brown for once
i just unlocked it it was really good
oh those donuts look so good
sheet cake
excuse me
let's go
your little [\h__\h] cake
please i'll listen to my new original
song you little [\h__\h] it's a banger can
you perform it for us
yeah
yes um do a live rendition
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] oh wait if i could
do this we're gonna get demonetized
because that's what happened to the song
not too many little little shits we have
to balance them you know
keep them balanced and a good good
amount
oh man
honey already so big
this map looks tasty it doesn't mean
[Music]
a very good question
what is this camera angle i don't know
where it goes oh
gosh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh geez this is a lot of tornadoes
yes yes
[Music]
oh nice
oh
i just want a berry
how was that
if you girls take this from me
[Music]
strawberries
[Laughter]
the only chance i have to win in life
okay
it's so depressing you're always winning
in our hearts oh my goodness fauna i
will kill you you just wait do it ah
the fritz i'm ready bring it on
yeah i'm
i'm here
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
so first still first so first
don't shoot their cube
oh
that was a decent safe
[Music]
holy mackerel
you guys know super monkey ball
oh yeah
[Music]
why did i just fall off
it's
[Music]
unless i can hit fauna with it no
you did
i need i need the strawberries all of
them
just one box is all i need
oh
[\h__\h]
there's no oh my gosh
[Music]
kirby cannot be controlled ready maybe i
can still get some extra maybe i can
still get some extra extra extra
[Laughter]
number two
it's not oh
you need to learn how to wear clothes
that are more flattering on your weight
what i think the hamburger hat is pretty
flattering the scales
oh now
the bad way out the end is a game
changer
[Music]
i think
i think i won
in
my heart
[Music]
yeah we just did that one
get mario partied
mm-hmm okay well oh wait i didn't change
[Music]
it i'm stuck
a car yeah
carbon cake
oh
what do we have hamburgers
this game is making me so hungry
probably gonna eat after night i know
yeah me too
i did order food before the stream and
it's something sweet even though i
should be eating dinner i just ordered
dessert you're so smart you knew it's
never
never too early or late dessert true
oh jesus
npcs i'm still wondering i think yeah
yeah they're random oh yeah just like
npcs
[Music]
okay platforming not bad this reminds me
a little bit of super mario sunshine
those platforming levels that they have
there
the tick tock sand sandy ones hmm
but that's the mario part of that game
traumatized me what
this sandy
no i'm talking about sunshine oh
sunshine oh
oh anyway bye-bye
how could you
business
it all gets down to business no
[Music]
go
it's too close
you just gotta go straight off
go straight that's all you need to do oh
what's your dreams
there we go
there we go crumbled crate oh
it looks so yummy
is this like mint or something
oh chocolate leaf yeah
fancy
these strawberries
okay another race here we go
matcha
oh
my
god
participated in a real like marathon in
real life no
no
only like a potato sacrifice
i did once when i was really young
get out i was i was really into running
when i was younger oh
oh i was on the like cross country team
had a nice
okay but no marathon or what no
oh no i should go on this thing a
marathon
why did i go this way
it's over
i wonder that
every day
[Music]
[Applause]
how do you stay on those
[Music]
it's a mistake
did i lose my thing
i don't think you lose your items yeah
you do you do oh
yeah
strawberry so far
oh oh
two wheels green now stay away from
them
you're dead
it's true
why am i not getting it
they're just
escaping me
i got my territory crony
i'm sorry
yeah
i was so slow oh my goodness
you were like you play more kirby games
auto missile
you're so cute
what what can i ask thank you no
[Music]
yes
yeah
i don't think no for an answer
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's time already
[Music]
good job
is it you and me who don't get wins
who i
oh curry won like twice
you mean the final win or just one like
a single pony was very large
in at least two rounds
am i the only one
you'll get it
windows
i think i only won once beginners
[Music]
i'm dead
are you are you here
oh
look at my eyes
oh did you get the the possessed see
there yeah
what
oh wow what happened to you what is that
it's like a skin
cool
blind kirby
i've never had it
i've had chocolates on you i don't think
i've had it either
i'm more of a chocolate phone you kind
of push what about like a chocolate
fountain
i feel like they're doing kind of gross
though oh
no they're not gross no
no they're not like they're a little
gross no why why why is this so rolly
oh goodness
why can't i i can't
oh everybody else is still here you guys
are so slow
what do you mean
one more good items in this round good
items also
bye oh i should have kept that one when
people are around me
i never get [\h__\h] when i get the box
strawberries
i need i need more strawberries but it's
okay just go straight to the middle
straight straight straight straight
straight
i'm eating it
[Music]
okay
i really want strawberry
i know
[Music]
you should not play this game without
desserts on hand oh
oh i see
what are we doing
i don't know i could have seen
i saw you very clearly on it i got like
one strawberry
i guess we're just ready
[Music]
wow all covered in cheese
what's your favorite cheese mine is um
cheddar maybe or mozzarella
or burgata
i like string cheese
um
cheesy strings
[Music]
cheesy strings there's one you can get
that's like a it has yellow and white
cheese
twisted
[Music]
no that one ow
oh goodness oh my god oh
oh my god how did i do that
what
oh it's very
very saucy i'm lost in the sauce
boston spouse oh
everybody's getting up
oh incredible
straight straight
i'm going
go
the caring is caring
can you actually share them
i don't think so no because kiara was in
the middle and i tried to get it but it
wouldn't let me oh it feels like you
should be able to i guess it doesn't
even matter how fast you spin
oh
mint chocolate chip cake oh it's so good
i feel
like chocolate tall
how long is that i am
i'm playing a fun game making fun
memories i don't regret any of the
memories of losing sounds like coping
i'm kidding yes
yes so what
hope in this life how can you not
it's all i have oh no
that was on purpose for now
you just have to make sure i know
it's like
oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
oh man i've thrown it all away
all down the
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
okay
cute
pixel yo-yo could be
wispy wood abilities you use ah ah
oh just the r button oh what
honey yeah
what's the free rolling thing
i think it's actually you can roll
around and get strawberries and that's
about it it's more like a practice yeah
ah
oh crony you look cute with that burger
on your hand you'll get yours too
oh i already have it as an option but i
didn't want to like copy you i didn't
want to steal your thunder
oh never had a banana no let's like do a
switcheroo
burger is kind of on the theme right for
kfp
yeah it is but uh you know i i saw how
happy cronie is with it i thought i'll
let her be maybe they have a fried
[Music]
what you can you say
i had korean fried chicken
oh how was that
it was yummy but way too big of a
serving and and then you know they serve
you the smallest serving they have is
the four people serving
and it was just me and navi mama
so
we start eating and then pretty early on
nabi mama stops eating and she says like
tiana
um i actually have to make
a confession to you and i'm like what is
this gonna be something serious what's
up what's up
and then she says i actually
can't eat fried foods very well oh
and i'm like girl you're already giving
up on eating wait
there's still like a million fried
chicken left on this plate how am i
supposed to eat all this
no yeah
yeah
doesn't it it means she was willing to
sacrifice to order the chicken for you
oh i like salads she doesn't like salads
he doesn't like fried foods
oh
i don't know where i get him from
[Music]
that's cute
oh do the cups like come up and you have
to be inside of it
yeah
i don't know i don't know this one is
it's a little slippery
yeah
it is slippery
oh yeah we got like three strawberries
what the [\h__\h]
hey i thought i was doing well what's up
with that
man
the races are so stressful
got it from my mother
from my mama
ah don't let me stand yeah how did you
miss
[Laughter]
oh goodness more like rng
[Music]
get up
back up faster you gotta
tickle the joystick just okay
don't go full throttle
don't go full throttle just go
i thought it was pressing a
[Music]
sorry
was it you
yes
sorry mommy
mommy sorry
have you been asleep for the past five
years
oh wait i've never heard that one that
cake is mine
i guess it is i'll go to the little one
yes to the left to the left
all strawberries are on the
left oh catching up
leaving me behind
yeah well i already won once unlike
somebody so now i'm just sabotaging
everyone else unleash my wage
oh my gosh she really did release her
rage
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my goodness
calm down
oh my goodness it's an intense game
no oh no
no no no oh
[Music]
kelly is like
invincibility
is it
[Music]
seems like it
i call that a mukbang
all you can eat strawberries
now don't [\h__\h] this up
i swear he always gets the extra
okay okay i got the hovering one oh oh
i i swear
[Music]
very nice i jinxed it for you
look at that let's go
actually been to an all you can eat
strawberry buffet in japan wait we have
that is it strawberries um just
strawberry oh you can use strawberries
and all you can eat
desserts of strawberries but also
a lot strawberry
desserts that made our meals with
strawberries and i think i went there
and
with money in senpai i think that was
that to say
if you if your girls go to tokyo they
have like um
uh all these like
in japan in japan in general they have
all these hotels that have like these
sweets buffets i went to so many of them
and they often have like a theme or the
one that i went to was alice in
wonderland for example you know or one
one that i went to was cats themed fauna
oh
did they have real cats
no musical cats also are you guys are we
separated again
oh i didn't join oh let's join
japan there's a mini pig cafe
oh that's so oh
wonder if they keep them all the time i
hope they treat them okay
yeah i hope so too
strawberry cup that's so cute holy [\h__\h]
oh you can use the hamburger
hamburger hamburger
okay if i have the time i'm still um
receiving my rewards okay okay i'm
coming now i'm coming now
got one minute
one minute we got plenty of time there
we go
let's see if i can
continue this saga
[Music]
i think
fast oh my this one yeah this one looks
new
looks like i wonder how many there are
ah
sorry
oh my god are you really sorry you like
totally rearranged me just a little yes
wasting my time oh my goodness oh my god
what did you just do girl that was so
rude i jumped oh that's cute that's the
new item i've never had before did you
guys have the sour candy high jump item
uh-oh
no
well i think you should do that like
near the finish line
cause you can't get a lot of
strawberries if you use the high jump
i guess so but it also gave me oh i have
a high jump now i have i jumped too why
does everyone have it now oh no we
unlocked it maybe
oh no no they're all good
job don't oh no
[Music]
little strawberries that fall out
[Laughter]
oh yeah that's good too
oh big one
i'm getting better at this
i'm getting better
robbery mountain
ah
[Music]
believe one delay
oh the candles
oh the misery oh no
i made a mistake wait maybe it's fine
wait can you just climb walls
uh you can just sort
[Music]
oh
what was that
did you see that i was just working
really hard on that wall and then she
comes there from the back out of nowhere
just
destroys every hard work i'll put into
that
it's okay life happens
it's like it makes you think you know is
it really worth trying hard in life
what's so deep polo said
don't let kirby change your whole life
mentality
oh yes
yes it's okay it wouldn't happen because
it would have been sandwiched
[Music]
i like that it's not just sweet stuff
there's savory stuff
i like to order sweet stuff first and
then savory that's that's just how i
like it oh
do it sometimes backwards
ow
how come you knock me so far but i don't
get to knock anybody back maybe it's a
waiter
[Music]
oh my goodness
bounciness it's just like a
bubble
[Music]
i'm not oh so well here oh i'm just
trying to knock you guys out
[Laughter]
all right
oh [\h__\h] oh my goodness bro
you did that oh
don't pinch me
you go
i got pinched i went from first to third
wow
that was probably
[Music]
is
oh
what it's not like it's not like we have
any of us had the same amount of
it
maybe maybe we were it was just too
close to call
[Music]
i can be put on the grill now no ahead
can't beat sometimes we have to switch
it around you know i i think today we
can
switch roles you know
um
can we have it on
can we end it on this happy note of two
wins bro
okay
[Laughter]
i don't know if i want to
be the witness to whatever whatever
you're proposing with your kfp employees
right now
oh we could we could chat for a little
bit
yeah we can do that
can i go i'll go check out my face
really quick okay yeah okay
alive the one in your plastic bag looks
um actually kind of electronic
it really looks electronic
it's so modern let's talk
can we just talk
yes
[Music]
i already pulled out so many topics
today it's your turn girls
give me something give me something
but my head is so empty
what did you do with the insides
of my head i think i spilled them out
all into building my minecraft farm and
there's nothing left oh the guardian
farm right yeah
oh you made a car i heard about that
what what what is a guardian film what
does that do i mean i know i know the
you're using like that tower thingy but
when you get out of it it's um one of
the most efficient xp farms that you can
make and it also gives you prismarine
which you can use to make
on those pretty aquatic blocks
[Music]
sea lanterns yeah sea lanterns too sea
lanterns and prismarine blocks
if you ever want to make something
turquoise blue
[Music]
but i need to make some changes to its
place
minecraft
everybody left minecraft but fauna if
you want to have somebody um i find
people have been playing a little bit
well i don't know maybe i've just been
watching id play and being inspired by
them and it's mostly id
[Laughter]
kind of i don't um why are you girls
like like playing or
a game called rest perhaps by chance i
have been a little bit i have to go feed
my house after this you have to paint
your
you have to feed your house or your
house will fall apart it's kind of like
having a
pet
don't talk don't talk
jinxed her
she said the same thing at the same time
oh at least in my timeline it lined up
are you are you eating the blueberries
why are you like gasping for words i'm
just you told me to be quiet i was like
wait what i never went
beyond that part
before like what happened to the jinx
person talks even though they're not oh
wait oh do you have to say her name
uh and then she gets unjinxed
i think that's never heard of this crony
has to buy you a soda or something yeah
like oh you owe me a coke yeah
oh
then okay you owe me a collabo
like like this one right now
not this one
collab one-on-one i want some one-on-one
time with my
[Music]
i'm feeling i'm feeling a little bit
caught up in the middle of something
here
literally
or something like that remember that
come here
i actually went to eat uh
[Music]
yeah it's fun
funny you can come back
oh sorry i just i just uh didn't want to
get in the way of anything happening
right now come here
don't worry okay okay
come here
we don't know
[Music]
your cats have also some weird affinity
to like um plastic
um they'll try to eat almost anything
really yeah that doesn't sound good i
think i'm i think i'm stuck over here
actually okay
you told us how about we have some
coffee and then you just disappear for
five minutes sorry
how are they doing
they're good one escaped into the tank
but it's looking fine
escaped oh
is is that good
yeah yeah it looks okay it looks okay
are you gonna eat the clams at some
point no no no no
could you though could you
i guess food you know what you can like
eat anything
[Music]
oh interesting yeah i guess you can eat
anything that you put your mind into it
like kirby
yeah yeah yeah kirby eats cars and stuff
be what you eat
do you have that saying in english
because we have it in german yeah you
are what you eat oh
in germany rhymes
fast to east
one more time do beast fast to east
dubies
[Music]
is
the way you pronounce the eye is cute
to leave
to eat or not to eat oh you were not to
be that is the question
[Music]
um what's the something in particular
you wanted to talk about with us
oh um
i don't know i'm not good at coming up
with topics here's the topic lady
when you were gone i asked these two
they couldn't come up with anything hey
we talked about the games
no camera
and then we talked about
coke
and going on a date
yeah yeah
wow
and the hot topic lady
oh oh i didn't want to ask uh
somebody please
introduce me to rust i need to oh
rest
yeah yeah
yes you play
can you help me
i could teach you yeah
okay so everyone playing rust running
you should play russ
rony you joined too come on join the
amateur cody i think you'd like it
really
oh yeah i think so
oh yes you would yeah the more the
merrier organizing [\h__\h]
oh yeah and you could have make your own
buncaroni again
but i have to feed it
yeah you have to feed it you do you have
to eat your bun
and the bigger it gets the more flesh it
requires
goodness what the heck
sounds morbid
that sounds weird no no it's not
actually flesh it's just if you build it
out of wood you have to keep wood inside
like a cupboard so that it it doesn't
decay yeah and if you build it out of
flesh then
you know
flesh begets flesh
oh what you can build it out of flesh
can you
maybe i shouldn't shouldn't say anything
else
[Music]
yeah you can build it at a bone do you
think
oh dear okay
can i build it
[Music]
out of gold people's ashes oh my god
i don't know
i think fauna knows more
well really you should ask me about that
kind of thing
[Music]
well she's not here right now is she
[Laughter]
hey guys
oh hi
i can't i can't do her voice that well
what's up no i can't
this is my mom
can you guys hear that
no no no i can't hear
all right it's just me
miracles i'll discord thank you thank
you discord i have a fan on too hey up
top
oh
you have brought mine here to be part of
the fan clique
from all fan club
mine's in the other room
i'm gonna not use me too
[Music]
you know
you actually have a lot of fans right
here so don't worry about it oh
[Music]
oh
oh doesn't chiara have a fan too
yeah
oh you can't pull it up
ah no don't worry ben don't worry it's
okay too much you can pour some water on
your head from my face
[Music]
it was it was
they were supposedly fish in there but
it was that's so much like a jungle you
could never see them and oh that would
i would really wonder if there's any
fish there at all anymore
they probably liked it because it felt
natural you know
yeah a lot of places to hide
a lot of green stuff everywhere very
green
fish jungle
yeah well
no well well well
we don't well well i guess does anyone
have the final tallies does anyone keep
trying oh yeah did you guys see who won
the the most
ah on the top right it does tell you
your victories from my for me it's two
oh oh i think you won the most
i
[Music]
the biggest kirby
be kirby well i mean i think that was
worth the 15 bucks
yeah
i think it's cute i want to unlock the
rest of the
cosmetics i hope they have a banana hat
yeah banana hats it seems like there's a
lot
yeah yeah
they're alive
i'll check it out again sometime i need
to get more of those
strawberries and blueberries yummy
no because all of those on my balcony
died so uh
they were growing like a [\h__\h] ton of
raspberries and another weird berry and
then and then
the heat wave came and then the wind
came and everything killed my plants and
now all i have left is one small
tiny cherry tomato oh
the plant itself is not really producing
anything but as one one tomato
maybe you should bring it inside i don't
know no those are balcony plants but
like i was when i was in america you
know
apparently it got so hot somebody took
care of my balcony and apparently also
watered them but not enough it seems and
then i came back and it was all dead and
from then from there it was all downhill
and oh can grow again after the heat
goes away
yeah
not this summer anymore and it's not
happening anymore those were like the
raspberries
you have one chance for them like in
ever
[Music]
yeah
and i had like four
four different like
thingies
um
[Music]
for a little while i felt like i had a
green bump but i guess i don't wanna
help
[Music]
approach to caretaking so
nature is like a gotcha game
just throw it out and see what happens
then i guess i have to quit the gacha
game
because i'm not carved out for it
[Music]
that's a that's a corner talk you
yeah yeah
but i have a big balcony i want to make
use of it but anyway that's okay
all it's currently growing is some
weird-ass mushrooms that no one else
came with with the earth that i put in
there the soil
that's that's nature
right there you're doing it
they look so disgusting because they
come out of nowhere okay and though the
ones that they're growing apparently you
can eat them in the very very early
stage but it after like one or two days
it already falls apart in the most
disgusting way it turns black and
it's just disgusting i'm like ew no
wonder i dislike mushrooms
it looks like a horror movie i swear
i want to see i want to see
i want to see
i probably have a picture i can send you
[Music]
i'll
try to find something but yeah
i only like enoki mushrooms oh those
ones creep me out somehow they're so
skinny and long
they're creepy
they taste good i think all mushrooms
are kind of creepy though
mushroom for me it's just a texture
thing but once you get used to it like i
kind of like it now because it has this
like moist crunch to it
[Music]
moist crunch
um
i'm eating coconut or something
mushrooms prepared by oh i never thought
of it that way
[Music]
okay yeah i made some mushrooms with
like a little bit of butter and garlic
and then a little bit of white wine it
was really tasty
garlic
anything of garlic is good
true that's true yeah
okay girls let's end it here okay all
right
thank you
thank you for answering my call to play
this game
[Music]
yeah
we're used
i have to fight back somehow you know
and i'll see you all in a roster
minecraft yeah
yeah
um and in germany we still beat us in
when you say fana
fun well
fun wow
[Music]
you