[Music]
foreign
can you wake up
wake up
[Music]
in your eyes I can't turn off my alarm
guys what's wrong
[Music]
[Laughter]
but I didn't even need to wake you up
though I'll give you that credit because
I woke up without my alarm you know I
woke up like after sleeping five hours
or so yeah naturally I woke up because I
was feeling like an idol meeting and I
looked at the time and like oh it's
already 6am all right I guess I'll stay
awake and then I wrote to Ina
and as she was awake too I can't believe
it I mean I did set alarms I did think
about you know
perhaps not opening my door
I could consider it first like oh by the
way we should say we should move this
more in the middle microphone how's the
how's this guy
yeah can you move us okay
we're in pajama by the way
okay
Nina opened the door she
she
looked like yes she woke up five seconds
ago why because I did wake up
she was like
yeah it's very early it's on before 7 00
am in Japan but isn't that 7 A.M in
Japan is your usual streaming time right
yes indeed so you have made it your goal
to continue that streaming time while
you're here right that's correct well
good luck with that I would not be able
to do that I mean may or may not be the
link to an hour later more often than I
hope you know I heard you missed your
Twitter space
I did indeed
did you miss it on purpose or by
accident ah
it's probably close because I literally
said like oh
10 alarm you're so hopeless Cena I know
I was to the point where I set my alarms
and my sleepy self learns how to turn
them off no matter what kind of alarm it
is
yeah no sleeping is a it's a force do
you recognized
I'm I'm
well then I was really lucky that you
were awake today because chances are you
wouldn't have been
I mean I didn't know Nintendo Direct was
actually happening yeah you messaged me
I was like ah okay okay I was actually
in the plane when I messaged you
oh yeah I got bored and I bought myself
some Wi-Fi in the plane Honestly though
like
just for like that whole flight
I I only bought it for one hour
um so it was less but yeah no and then
one hour I just tried to contact as many
people as possible but I didn't count I
wasn't able to contact Jenna so I asked
you to contact General your volume is
super low they're saying I see it oh no
it's because I'm so far away from
microphone I literally have to lean into
Kiara you know I can move it a little
bit no yeah
so there we go easy if you're okay with
me
actually now the Nintendo Direct is
easier for me too oh really oh okay
that's fine then that works that works
by the way uh last Nintendo Direct did
you watch it
which one the last one before this one
when was that a while ago but they
announced so many like
um RPGs jpgs back then I must have
missed that when was it the last one I
watched on stream hmm was the tomorrow
will we get uh yesterday today yesterday
I mean there's a lot six days ago for
Kirby Return to Dreamland Deluxe seeing
from the uh
Zelda
right yeah or at least like said that
they were releasing it yeah exactly I
think but I was more excited about other
things like
um like like 64 snowboarding or whatever
so six Nintendo 64 snowboarding being
brought to the Nintendo switch I was
1080 1080 snowboarding sorry I was so
excited but I was screaming I was
screaming for the top of my lungs that
was the one no no screaming this time
okay I'll try I don't want I don't want
walks in the store okay
oh I love the one thing I was really
excited about and then I was also like a
Tales of Symphonia remaster
I screamed I think I almost cried
I don't think I remember seeing your
reaction I probably slept in that day or
something no it's because I really like
loved hands off games and Tales of
Symphonia was my first one and then they
showed the remaster and I don't know why
because remaster isn't even that
special in my in my mind a remake would
have been cooler but still when I saw
that I got so excited for some reason I
mean but then like like that's the thing
about games you like hold dear to Your
Heart Right no matter if it's a reboot
or you know remake
kind of just like you hold a special
little place in your heart yeah and you
feel you feel happy and what would that
be for you you know
what would that be for you like which
game oh
I'm sorry I am him heartbreak
I was looking for the Game Boy
who knows that
that's good I'd have never heard of that
one
[Music]
Kingdom Hearts I mean Kingdom Hearts is
one thing right because I didn't have
consoles to play Kingdom Hearts with
when I was little we were talking about
games like we hold dear since you know
and in that category I have to you know
how little are we talking like
Elementary
oh that's very I did not play a tails
off in elementary but I'm I may have
played uh 1080 snowboarding in
elementary now
maybe maybe more like in junior high
ah
yeah all right I'm very excited what are
we expecting today
oh we should make like a bingo or
something
news because it's less than 100 days
till breath of the wild too
oh maybe yeah definitely I might I mean
I'm I'm hoping for some Splatoon news
you know it's been it's been a while
since
you play Splatoon yeah I feel like we
might get some update on the Nintendo
movie yeah Mario movie yeah I mean I
already I think they gave us plenty of
updates already plenty of trailers
some more news you know they gotta they
got a mark at the Moon yeah I think
we're good the movie looks really good
why is everyone saying sing song silk
song what is that Silk song that's the
sequel to Holiday ah and we we think
that's coming so like always silk song
because um was first announced with um
DLC for Pokemon oh yeah oh yeah Pokemon
DLC yeah probably yeah so someone's
probably gonna be like um
PC or Xbox release first oh you played
holiday right I did
[Music]
um
when it releases five of them DLC you
think it will be announced so early I
don't know I feel like it's too early
yeah
like a re
what should I say
the remaster of like an older one or
[Music]
um
yeah I mean that might be because they
do a lot really early oh there is so
many a DLC yeah because they released
the DLC and at the release date so I
mean I guess it's not too early to
release another DLC I've been playing I
mean I wouldn't be surprised if they
pull like uh we're adding like you know
an earlier game as like a
the master version for the switch or
something like that
or something oh I've been enjoying fine
Bloom engage I think I'll probably play
again on Sunday Sunday or so yeah have
you ever played a fire emblem game oh
really which one
um Awakening
oh
and isn't that the phone game no
Awakening is the moment Chrome
oh my first one was free houses so I
don't really know much before that
Awakening was my first time I actually
like played plate oh I forgot
wait how come
refresh that one not the refresh
behind Okay ah
get in there
one day
okay okay
what's that
that I don't hear anything real I'm
beautiful
is it okay what's that what
[Music]
I know but they have so much stuff okay
okay
[Music]
I've never played Pokemon actually
that's a Pokemon
it's a crossover oh maybe I can play
this too oh
are we we're not looking at the same
thing you're earlier
later you're ahead of me I think yeah
you're ahead of me
but just like myself
she's watching on the phone no I'm
watching this though oh audio I guess
okay you're listening to the late audio
[Music]
voice act means I didn't didn't
something Pikmin related come out
recently though am I going crazy am I
mixing something up
they announced this earlier did they not
one of the previous ones they just now
said but they didn't have a gameplay or
anything oh maybe I'm just nudging
things I think I'm I'm thinking of
something else maybe why are my eyes
dead because I'm dead inside why else
I'm kidding I'm alive now
they announced it years ago
I at least remember seeing it in one of
the previous Watchdogs so
what's this it's like a dog but yeah
it's a new friend look she's cute George
that looks pretty good
it's actually quite typical Fourth
Street
it's not a it's not a gameplay we're not
playing the game right now
no need to read
and they can also
[Music]
isn't it a flower
oh ah boss mechanics yellow
that's the most Pikmin gameplay I've
ever seen so did you see that like the
boss changed colors like depending on
which Pikmin was attacking it oh it was
like the yellows were attacking you so
the ball thing was glowing yellow maybe
it's like a mechanic
we're being abducted that's their own
Airship oh
[Laughter]
yeah when okay release date
oh that's so bad
wait I think this is still the same yeah
feel it maybe after that we gotta
release date
I'll leave it here so it looks oh my God
Eve oh there you go July 21st
what a date
hello
hello thank you
hi I just love their like English dubs
all the time
as well he also woke up at seven A.M
good for him
well they all woke up at 7am this ain't
live
got some Flawless English damn
oh
she's pretty though
yeah
I have I have Fire Emblem brain right
now
please you know play oh I like her hair
she's hot
[Laughter]
you know what else is hot
yes tell me
my my hot water kettle oh
actually it's not hot
she looked at me though but she probably
couldn't say it because I was right next
to her she can only say it when I'm like
in Discord or so I mean I don't think
there's a
what's it
like a fire
alarm I mean there might be a fire from
here
tell me why
oh British they are so British
it's beautiful
I I don't I don't [\h__\h] know
let's go suspension pass I don't want to
play Xenoblade one day it seemed to see
one but it's a big commitment yeah shake
it Amigo amigo
I'm speaking of shaken
that was very hard yesterday Kiowa
weren't you proud huh what's your day
yes
literally called me I called I'm telling
her
120 something in the morning
oh no it was one like midnight
basically one
yeah because I had a long yes dance
lesson yesterday and came out I called
me she was like I heard your word
I don't think my dancers are that hard
but my body's so slow
it looks sad to see them whenever
wherever yeah
[Music]
you can come to
you're gonna be there at the rehearsal
what's the practice together man
enough we don't know we don't know what
what are you talking about no I mean I
mean like personally use the studio
together you know oh we put the time
together we're preparing preparing
fourth Fest yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
I also have a dance lesson today
actually but I'm gonna take another nap
before what is that you forgot
you forgot she also has yes lessons no
don't forget
I don't know
I know you're good at dancing but you
still have to practice too
yeah
oh Fashion Design oh oh my gosh
no no that that iridescent shiny jacket
I'm not sure I'm feeling it
wow that belt on top of the jacket wow
slay girl I like that outfit yes
new looks
friends
what an one okay that's more like
clothes I would like to wear just like
big sweaters yeah it was even your
colors yeah
fashion dreamer wow
marvelous what other games did marvelous
do
they do a lot of like
there was a game that I knew of that was
this Dracula oh
my favorite was already do you know Ori
Oreo the blind Forest yeah did you know
it's from Austria really Austrian
developers made that game oh it's so
pretty it's so good too I played it and
it really made me better at those kind
of games I was so shitty in the
beginning
[Music]
oh yeah
I'll cross over oh oh yeah that sounds
like a different game that's why yeah
just try
oh
did you watch the movie like at least
the quote-unquote recent Tron movie
yeah no no oh yes
it's kind of fun
oh
I'm not sure about the game though
[Music]
looks fun it's like a nice sci-fi movie
to kind of watch you know oh
check
oh my god oh it's getting is it getting
a switch oh must be I love ghost tricks
oh
she's cute yeah
there's like a really cute Pomeranian
I hope so I don't remember much of the
story so maybe I can
oh that's a nice surprise
what's this trailer
Japanese
[Music]
GTA
please oh cute graphics
is this by whatchamacallit
level five I don't know it looks like
the Inazuma Eleven art Stone oh
uh I like the graphics yeah that kind of
graphics
oh cute
oh I love detective games
that was like objection
and there's like Turtle face battle too
oh
it's kind of like how am I would be
doing detective work it's not if it
doesn't work violence oh yes yes
what else does she have like a mix of
like what's it it's kind of a mix of
uh what's that one game
it's a turning oh yeah like
um like more of a battle
drpg aspect to it
we've got a ball oh why is there Subs
or autogenics Deca police
that was also in the last Nintendo
director for the first time yeah I
really like the looks of this one so
much more than the actual Bayonetta game
yeah that's why my this is her origin
story yeah oh that's so cute I still
want to play this
it's like a prequel
save upon me a lot of relaxing Mommy
[Music]
it's like Alice in Wonderland
the style is so good
oh
oh yes
I love it
[Music]
art Direction on point yes
I mean I like the looks of the original
lay on that out too but this is more of
my style all the stuff gameplay style is
kind of like Hades like oh really yeah I
haven't played that
you should play it's pretty fun
coming up too so um
oh it looks pretty did we already get
out have we stayed before
well sure I don't remember
oh yeah people are saying
yeah yeah
love it love it love it need it so good
give me um
[Music]
why must you release every all the
damages I want to play so close to one
another
never stop streaming that's what they're
saying
I'm busy
oh good for you DLC
been there I already have a million DLCs
let's set the new one oh button three oh
which they haven't had Millions yeah it
definitely is because they're going to
the subway oh
I haven't played Bud recently I should
play again
[Music]
oh
um
where are we
hmm
oh they're back cute
oh
we won
oh we're back
two waves
oh
ah we're back
yeah
cute Annie
oh
tempura
crumbs
Fred
you're sick here damn so spiky
music is so good in Splatoon yeah nice
soundtrack
I'm surviving
oh it's an idol yeah they have idle
groups
she looks like you yeah but I think her
name is
Cali what Yeah ironic yeah it's like
their name is Cali and Mari yeah so
together they're calling
Mari
[Music]
it sounds good though wait is that also
oh my God
cheese so much what's the vibe what's
the atmosphere it's so edgy emo it's
like near but
um dark oh what's this
oh what
side order
but it's a nice clean canvas
everything's White
collar on it
[Laughter]
near splatanata I have two
[Music]
um
from an outsider point of view the side
order one finally looks like something
new like everything else like Splatoon
related all looks like kind of the same
to me it's but like that's the world of
the switches it's colorful on YouTube
that's why it looks so perfect I wonder
if it's like the past or the future or
like somewhere today they said something
about today
today today what
well maybe they're releasing the first
wave today
hey headlights headlines remember that
switched to the the second part oh
Mickey oh
um you know every time I've been walking
around with a girl and we see something
Mickey I mean Michael moose related
silently we just kind of like get closer
and we're like oh
it's okay when you're outside when
you're not streaming you can
you can just be loud about it and you
can say Disney I know but the like with
the like every time we see something
like a loser really we're just like
oh
[Laughter]
wow
it looks fun player
what
I wake up late
oh yeah right let's see of course not
yeah
I mean who knows we can play offline you
know
I like the cute art style on there yeah
it's it's sort of different from their
usual you know
one but
um
Lucian Island
I guess I'll only be playing it in my
Illusions
because I'm not gonna be streaming it
sorry guys
here we go
oh yeah
I guess it's like a character expansion
because of the the mobile version when
it first released he was like the op
character hmm
let's go
more open rings for me
oh yes oh yes I'm getting her
Ramen Ramen
I don't care Robin
oh
love she's from the mobile
love love love love Veronica wait which
one is she from no idea
but she will be mine
the girls are cute wait what wave four
Casino log
new characters
those two are new
sick today
oh today
for real though today
I'm so busy with the current volume game
oh you can have them in your in your
place here now yeah
looking at them early get more op
don't nod I just started
no you can't you cannot
wait
okay objection
wait is it is it Ace uh Phoenix writes
Japanese
yeah
look it up like his Japanese name is
like something not a hula isn't it
really I'm pretty sure yeah yeah his
name is Navajo
like or his last name or whichever what
[Laughter]
yeah his name is
I laughed when I heard I was like I mean
technically Phoenix Wright is a pun
right
right correct like right but then remix
correct
I feel like there's been an octopath
like Trail like game trailer like
announcement everything and yes that is
true
and I really want to play it was the
other one called triangle strategy yeah
something like yeah similar and now it's
like wait I also wanna play on stream
both of them
no
monkey
[Music]
s
Sophie
wow
oh someone she photoshopped that with
like the taco me going okay
[Music]
game Trials oh sea of stars sabotage
that also looks like octopath traveler I
mean it's like a classic pixel yeah RPG
a cool music it's pretty nice
wow wow
it looks nice
today hmm
what what
say I've done this antenna direct a
couple days earlier so it wouldn't
everything wouldn't be today
even if it was earlier you know
I used to play Omega Strikers will
release it you know when I was younger
is this the one
were they like the interview and then
they like mentioned YouTubers for one of
the character design really
this is the one chat
I I thought wait yeah they mentioned
they mentioned the sexy octopus
I wonder who that is that looks like
coyote and a pink one yeah
[Music]
I heard this is this is the one game
that's like super difficult right yeah
or like um
what's it there's like a like a
difficulty or like a learning curve
really hmm
oh
you draw it yourself
while you're in it
but I have a lot of the art books and
games because their design is so cute
yeah so good
it looks a little different today
maybe that's her that's her let me
bought it like second cousin twice
removed
in a I hope you're eating something else
for breakfast too besides that whole
chocolate bar I'm taking a nap okay
hey I have like five crunky bars to go
through okay
like breakfast of champions
June first
oh
today three different ones yeah I mean
it's like a HD Master of the older games
so what's that is this just the fire
fighting game or the Rescue game
oh
Advance one
is it I want to consider firefight I
don't think it's firefighting but it's
like kind of like a hmm team
you know
this one has been
announced before too yeah I remember
watching it yeah
everyone everybody was like
let's go let's go
hey at the reboot yeah yeah April
um
because delayed oh okay
oh
it is oh
DLC oh
they got easy guide
save them Kirby
hey
magalore oh
weak skill issue
I just thought this is the training Arc
for the iseka you know guys when you
drop into the new world but then you
have no skills you gotta start from zero
no hold up levitation
it what if this is just like
isekai Kirby that's the whole story
maybe it is
that guy Curry just wears a hood
you said Kirby is not naked
oh oh couch Club
um we need more online please we're
streamers
oh
[Music]
so it's free
I guess nice something new
oh demo can we kill
Ed
[Music]
uh but that's local again right a code
couch
but it's like
you know like Kirby was supposed to be
just like a placeholder for testing a
game design but then curly was so cute
they like decide to keep understandable
yeah
oh new games for online new games
they did say something recently about
discounts too Nintendo Game Boy game
more Game Boy games
yes I always wanted to play those retro
Nintendo switch online games
oh Delta I played the Remake on stream
catches
[Music]
oh my goodness let's go
hell yeah
nostalgic hmm
oh
look I missed the Game Boy can we get a
Yoshi one please
wait does that mean they might you know
down the line they could totally do
Pokemon
Pokemon company to find out
I mean it would be nice it would be nice
wait that means there's so much for him
heartbreak
oh scary
I was gonna like get like a Game Boy so
I could I try to stream it
oh
they have Pokemon games on the N64
switch online apparently oh
watch it
why were you all done I want to play
that one okay
oh Kirby's debut I want the Aussie
please I love their little dance did
Yoshi not have a not have a Game Boy
game guys
maybe not
oh oh
whoa
oh online too
which ones attachments
seasons and Pokemon Trading Card Game oh
TCG I've never seen that oh
hold your horses
could it be no
no
yeah I played this one already too these
ones
I'm a rhetorical question oh which games
oh
[Music]
yeah
[Laughter]
why were you aware
can we play this online too
oh I feel like I've seen that before
yeah like a new one yeah
maybe
that would be amazing this one too can
we play this one online oh that would be
fun we've won Mario yeah
oh oh yeah I remember I don't want to
play
[Music]
online we got the the TV wait Mario guys
live tournament with this one
yes this is maximum problem oh
f2o F2 F2 oh let's go Golden Circle
in a while
that looks familiar to me yeah
what about Dark Cloud please
oh he's playing hey work work
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
trying to give like no warning they love
doing this don't they
ah a few more come on that's cool I
brought my switch maybe we can play some
and stream
together oh remastered oh
[Music]
um
people are excited oh because it's not
it's not like a
HD remaster it's a remake eh I heard
remaster but it looks like a remake yeah
it almost looks isn't it they said
remastered
looks like green it's obviously a remake
right
yes I don't think they have this graphic
back every Master remaster Port
really it looks so good yeah I I would
believe they just like you know
oh meet that it is very much oh yeah
wow
wow that looks good yeah
um that was from the GameCube oh I might
oh it's cute
I mean GameCube actually had pretty good
graphics for Buckingham yes yes yes have
you ever played Crystal Chronicles
Crystal Chronicles the final fuzzy
Crystal Chronicles on games no like I
look at like
um the
the cutscenes like right now I'm just
like hmm Graphics are pretty good yeah
console
mmm oh
black on hmm boom
boom
ah
forbidden jellyfish
oh
nice
uh-huh
that looks like really good
if they said this was a new game
hell yeah I would believe it too
good job today
again
no what
hey
what's what's happening why are they in
such a rush
oh
yeah
it looks like yeah it's it's oh maybe
it's by their um developer cute
what they're um I forgot they had they
had a different name for their Studio
but their their designs are always on
point
[Music]
oh he's bloody
nice double disguise
oh super hearing
oh
the eye is a zero
edgy
oh this is fun
[Music]
igami
wow
raincoat
that looks so fine
no hold on
what does that wig look familiar
thank you don't know this
then
I'm telling you game but it's a jrpg
again right yeah
different they're built differently
the graphics
hmm
I wonder what happened during the
GameCube and Cube goat
oh looks nice
yeah those are
Graphics that remind me of the Tales of
Symphonia on GameCube times
it's kind of like
um
cards yeah
but second
I feel like you'd like this game
I already have so many therapists for
this year though I don't know how to
like do all of them
uh like oh
nasty life
this is by um
this is another one by level five I'm
not sure well it looks like a Mario
Party map um the girls needs time
oh it is level four yeah actually girl
talked about this yesterday when people
were talking about random stuff how does
she know
what she's is she
inside
no I think we're talking about like um
anime and stuff I talked about like
ninokuni and like it's 9 11. she was
like oh have you ever played like
Fantasy Life despite the people who made
like ninokuni and stuff like
very interesting
thank you
bless you
oh Fantasy Life I wonder it's like
something about fantasy
you're for real though
I love that combo when the girl who
steals Time free this is historical um
well this one's so rough
tell me more oh
oh oh this art style
oh cause he's taking my arms
calm down calm down
a new world
focus focus
that's it that's all that's all I get
I'm satisfied I'm satisfied
oh more more maps oh no more
more maps to crash that is that the last
one
that's so because like those there was
waves and waves right that's the last
one right because I was like how many
more are you gonna add this one looks
nice still
[Music]
wait
finally berno
finally is she gonna be the new meta oh
we'll see
finally
oh
let's go
oh spring oh so one thing that's not
today
that's okay
I love that they do that with the
expansion packs like if you have the
switch online yes like it's oh I need
something
um
oh what's that game
Minecraft
on switch
yeah I was I wanted to play it like a
Minecraft
um this looks really cute that's cute
too yeah damn
oh I love this art style for this mm-hmm
beautiful oh
the Mega Man it's it's done
have a nice day oh yeah I want to play
this I actually told Kelly to play this
it looks nice yeah it looks really fun
this is for Callie
oh I I kind of want to play it have a
nice day
baseball yeah
we can call Young
sensor sensor
oh
whoa person let's just save in the Box
that's
what
well yes it's coming February 17th
I know I already knew I already knew but
yeah
ah o'clock
I want to play the remaster
my plan on my channel surely breath of
the wild too oh surely
hold me
I'm holding you yes
Nani Shirley
it is right it is
a breath of the wild thing you
has a new title does not breath of the
wild yeah everyone just calls it but I
don't know
how to get inside
then gave it away
wow
oh he's working
what's that
gun on
oh oh [\h__\h]
is he in the Sun
oh
I remember last time I saw a red loon or
son I guess it was a moon drop onto the
Earth you know everyone got isekai I
woke up like five years later
that's another world five days remain
a Minecraft
Zelda sala's voice
yeah pretty
oh
y'all so much footage
[Music]
you know how people were writing like
all kinds of stuff so they're just like
you know what let's just give them a
call
maybe you could put some luggage on it
too oh
tears of the Kingdom yeah do we already
have a date
yeah it's less than 100 days oh yeah
right
then give me your power
where me
was that the final yeah the final one
yeah that was really cool May no not me
May 12th no it's December right okay
what me
yeah I said less than 100 days that's me
it's not December huh amazing
was I aware of me I think you read the
dates backwards yeah I mean that's how
we write it in Europe May 12th
not December 5th wait I thought this fur
it's not December 5th it's May 12th
bye
okay that's [\h__\h] amazing yeah so I
got clear I gotta clear the first one
the thing is I never played the first
one but I watched um full playthroughs
of it uh including all getting all the
Crocs uh or whatever they call in
English I watched a full playthrough
four tabs
okay yeah so I might like do it like a
little bit and play a little bit but not
the whole game because I already I know
I'm sorry yeah but I I don't want to
play the new one but probably
everybody's gonna be playing it but oh
my God
until December I thought they were going
for you know the Christmas Market
because everybody can get the parents
can buy for the children for Christmas
and that's kind of a Nintendo thing to
do you know it's like a Pokemon thing to
do I guess yeah
yeah me what did I never realize that
yeah you thought it was 700 days but I
felt like yeah how many days it's a long
time to go that could be that could be
the same month that's a three months ago
so I just saw that the other day 100
days remaining and I was like oh 100
days that doesn't sound like so much but
I guess yeah that December December
yes uh closer than I thought it was oh
my god oh man what do you think about
this Nintendo Direct
last one was more exciting for me
because it was more jrpg focused right I
mean this one a lot of jrpg yeah
um but a lot of them were already
announced last time I mean
for example oh I guess I didn't watch
last one so I didn't see it yeah that
one was bad it looks really promising
yeah yeah my I guess my favorites
um probably gonna be Bayonetta and the
new breath of the wild and what else
what else was I excited for ah some of
the Nintendo switch online games
we should definitely do the the Game Boy
um
it looks like we could play up to four
people that one was four yeah it would
be like just like a small Club I have
two controllers I have uh the con I
brought two controllers Pro Controller
and another one so but you also have
your switch here right I'm the control
right there
so yes and what are you most excited for
oh hard to tell like they're a school's
trick too if you haven't played it's a
really good game congratulating I mean
this one was packed like is your tooth
expansion
yeah
many things we forgot after perhaps I
mean that was already announced on time
yeah yeah it's so exciting
oh yeah
[Applause]
if I can't play it this year I'm gonna
move I'm gonna making more of octopus
traveler or triangle strategy I don't
give a [\h__\h] I want to play one of them
I'm also um waiting for so many other
um games from that
um Corner yeah
we had some exceptions but it's a yeah
[Music]
replicant still I forgot about it oh you
wanna you wanna
the I was thinking about it but I I
decided not to oh I I have like
so I thought okay so what happened was I
was gonna get the limited edition so I
did but then I wanted to play
the game fast but my my package didn't
arrive so I bought oh I bought a steam
version too
yeah in German we say doublehead PESA
one more time natural
I should teach you German oh get me into
that German class
no no we don't say I'll be the same yet
okay we're in German we just say okay we
say a lot of things in German
[Music]
so now we're both gonna go back to sleep
right yes next time but it was fun thank
you for accepting my requests
together oh it's good to see you too
[Music]
I mean it's not too cold it's kind of
hot right now so yeah right now I'm
feeling hot yeah I can turn off the heat
later I turn off the heat when I sleep
because you sleep better when it's cold
it's scientifically proven
like around like 16 degrees Celsius not
too cold please
it's kind of like you know when you're
like like dying in the mountains like in
the snowy mountains and you kind of get
cold and you get sleepy yeah it's kind
of like that
um yeah but then you also die
wow that's just a side effect isn't it
someone needs to take care of this girl
[Laughter]
she's not okay alone her room's so messy
too excuse me
excuse me I have absolutely no time to
clean okay you knew that I was coming
over yeah
I got that like my my okay it was chat
chat Mike
like dance lesson was until like 10 11
p.m okay I got back
before I go into the lesson I was
I was sitting on things I wasn't just
lying around nothing but like
[Laughter]
I will send you a maid I'll order a maid
for you oh send one over for you oh
thank you she'll clean it and then you
open the door and it's just me in a
matrix
wow that blush is really strong are you
drunk okay
goodbye
have you been to Cafe I made Cafe yet
this is this trip no no I've never been
to a vegan
oh my God yeah
well I have been back in the day a
couple times I don't go these days
anymore because I have enough of it but
we could go
get that moment can we just have me Cafe
at home
we can't make Cafe at home
you know what I'm doing
huh but what we have Mommy can we have
makeup okay
at home
this no like I don't know what I'm
pointing it's just do you know the meme
I thought I thought you were gonna
explain what the this is
because it ends there
[Laughter]
made Cafe at the home just koala and
made out of this no um what's hand blade
omelette and a special message written
by you I can do that that's an upgrade I
mean
might fall apart when I flip it or so am
I gonna am I gonna make it out alive
you're not gonna get poisoned by my
cooking that's for sure I know you can
resurrect but I don't I don't know if I
can I give you my feather Phoenix
Feather oh you know I always wondered
it's Phoenix town like a edible item or
it's like how do I use it like it
disappears after you use it right every
Italian so uh imagine someone dead then
like you so then you take the Phoenix
down and you tickle their nose with them
and they're like
and they wake up
I am enlightened today
there you go so why does it disappear is
it because I I chew and it just like
yeah yeah or or when you go there
with the hot you like inhale the feather
oh I guess could also be a thing I've
never looked closely oh
that's why they say bless you oh
Yeah the more you know
so Phoenix Feather right hmm
any feather work
s
I'm curious I only have two
um please have to stay up here like an
apart from doesn't that mean you have
like um unlimited yeah
[Music]
I would think you would have a hard time
plucking every single one of them
and sell them effects please don't sell
my paintings better
do but it's still my butt feather yeah
this is still at the same effect does it
have like a special effect
you asking about what my butt feather
does yeah
all right guys
me too me too let's go back to bed
don't worry about the butt thing okay
anyways uh thank you guys
asking the real questions
[Music]
don't leave us hanging out I don't know
think about it think about it
no butt feather in my current form I can
yeah I'm just talking about your you
know pretty explore oh curious which is
usually have like a really long you know
um
I was like oh maybe if it's like a big
book feather maybe it has like extra
effects right I don't remember it's been
a long time since I was in my Phoenix
Farm I won't remember yeah well you know
but anyways thanks for your thanks for
joining me today no thank you for
letting me do this on your channel I
appreciate it because I haven't set up
anything yet
if I need some help I'm gonna ask you to
help oh no oh no she's gonna be like
already tweeted it she's also back in
Japan so yeah we're all here yeah we
have a oh basically Hollow and hola myth
house right now well Kelly you know
she's she's not in the same house yeah
but she's here yeah we joked that she
should just um like sleep at in our
places yeah every day someone else's
yeah
but okay so does this mean when you're
like streaming I mean I think chances
are low that I would want to be awake at
the time when you're streaming but when
you're streaming are you open to me
intruding suddenly and be like hi ain't
nothing coming in and then staying for
five minutes and leaving yeah yeah well
I'm okay with it too okay I was going to
Clash of stream yesterday but then you
ended just as I got to the train station
I was like yeah it was already over yeah
yeah my mom's house is gonna be a thing
for a while right because we're like
preparing for Halloween
yeah pretty long I'm gonna be missing my
cats so but but please look forward to
fourth class I'm so excited yes so
excited yes
I
realized this after you guys mentioned
it
very fabulous because I'm so used to
like hugging like my family and we
haven't talked to say hugs
okay hmm
[Music]
okay I think I didn't eat it
she's losing it talk about the bud
feather really got to her anyways uh
thanks for watching guys thank you I
hope you guys have a wonderful rest of
the morning afternoon evening I think I
forgot to do something that I usually do
on stream which is
okay bye hi