[Music]
I'm
Kori and I want to kill
you tonight Lads
we
[Music]
let's
I'm you know what here's a little C free
style if you want to fight me Get
Wrecked you kidding me I'm pretty good a
grim reaper what do you expect this
about sounding cool I would say so I'm
inclined to agree this is my line of
work this what everyone wants to see
bird cute kill them time to redo the
fight this is called being a Pro Gamer I
won't die right try
aiming I want to cry you off he's right
though
[Music]
die my hands
weapons of mass
[Music]
destruction half HP in a dream boys this
findest me and my Natural Essence a
workaholic by Hobby I'm cooking I need
to teach you a lesson say howy this is
the
W Sheriff's the best I'm going to get a
B jump emperess anything to achieve that
dream let's go out korei heart
palpitations on Street
just let it end just let it end my
friend plays the recorder better hey
your a
friend hey guys two quick
questions number one what the am I
looking
at number
two are you
ready
go that's AI
me the ball that's a yeah that's a check
this
out right yeah baby that's what I'm
talking
about hey everyone I'm
Kori and I want to kill you
tonight Lads we
go let's
[Music]
party
I'm you know what here's a little C free
style if you want to fight me get
wrecked you kidding me I'm pretty good a
grim reaper what do you expect about
sounded cool I would say so so I'm
inclined to agree this is my line of
work this what everyone wants to see
bird cute Ked them time to redo the
fight this is called being a Pro Gamer I
won't die right try
aiming I want to cry you off he's right
though
[Music]
Die My Hands weapons of mass destruction
half HP in a dream boys that's fine me
and my Natural Essence a workaholic by
Hobby I'm cooking I need to teach you a
listen say howy this is the
West sh the best I'm going to get a B
jump empis anything to achieve that
dream let's go Kori heart palpitations
on
stream just let it end just let it end
my friend plays the recorder better hey
your
[Music]
friend hey guys two quick
questions number one what the am I
looking
at number
two are you
[Music]
ready that's a
Mori me the ball that's a Mor yes that's
samori check this
[Music]
out what I'm
talking oh
ah
Mina perhaps I should do it more
properly
Mina clear in my throat it hurts I don't
know if I can keep doing that I don't
know if I
should the first question out the gate
they ask is how is your health good
enough good
enough good enough to be
here hey
[Music]
hi good tomorrow don't overdo it I
wanted to stream is the amount of
coughing going down oh yeah big time
when I cough it still does
hurt but it's gone down quite a bit so
I'd say that's
progress I don't know about you guys I
would say that is
progress we noticed that you wanted to
stream but did you now would that be by
the fact that maybe 10 hours worth of
streaming today M maybe no but I'm I'm
good I'm not really coughing super hard
as of right now I've been taking even
more antibiotics even though apparently
it was just damage left over I think
it's to really make sure there's nothing
bad left over in my lungs um and it's
kind of it's been nice they're very
strong though they hurt my tummy but I'm
almost done with them so I have faith I
have faith and I feel pretty good today
so but yesterday was rough for sure I'm
fine now though 70% better it's it's
hard to judge right it's just a little
difficult to judge because how to say uh
it's been going on for a while right and
I always think oh the stabbing pain is
getting better in my lung and then it
comes back so I don't know when
something like fairly permanent damage
happens to your lungs from a sickness
that you didn't even realize that you
had um that's no good
and the doctor said it might take a
couple years for those scars to fully
heal that's just what happens when you
get certain sicknesses that really mess
you up I'm certainly not the only person
this has happened to I've talked to
plenty of friends who have had similar
sickness some also without realizing it
and and they too are like ah yes lung
damage for for a while but it's not the
kind of lung damage where you can't sing
anymore or anything like that it just
it's kind of bad you know it took an
x-ray and whatnot which is crazy to see
my own skeleton for the first time in a
long time and the dock points out like
takes a a circle like a red pen and
circles around like where it looks like
there are scars and it's like yes these
are scars on your
arteries I'm like really the sickness
didn't hurt that bad when I had it did
you see a heart N I saw a faint
Shadow I was like dang all right yikes
that's rough it didn't even hurt that
when I had it like I had a little fever
and the coughing was painful but the the
really intense pain only lasted for like
a day but hey a heck of a lot can happen
in a
day so I know cut my life into pieces
this is my last resort
suffocation no breathing um we're
drawing pk5 ey today but I'll probably
just draw half and half half for this
stream half for the other hope that's
okay I just want to be able to help my
team
[Music]
so there's just not a ton of time but
pk5 ey wants like a a jailbird themed
jacket as well as of course the dead
bead hat and an open Palm don't give a
gut if a cut if I cut my own Brea I
think it's cut my arm
bleeding but close enough close enough
uh let's see I'm kind of referencing um
I've already I think I've already done a
drawing for pk5 IR this is this is based
off of that one very Loosely well not
Loosely pretty much cuz I've kind of
already drawn a dead beat Sona for pk5
but that was during the drawing request
stream now this is the full-fledged
version with pants and all cuz everybody
needs pants and you know unless you
maybe don't leave your house then you
don't need pants if you don't want them
[Music]
right yeah you know playing the server
with all of my friends has been really
good for me knock going lie you know
it's it's more of like a casual fun just
jump in whenever you want server um
which is kind of what I was hoping
for especially after you know we all did
h of GTA
together so I'm glad that it's chill and
some of the members really seem to be
having a lot of fun so I'm glad I'm glad
I really needed this though personally
you know just do something
that is just fun and I don't know gets
my mind off of off of all of the the
pressures and
such yeah you know cuz there there are
there are
some still lingering here and there but
I'll be okay it's been fun to do
something
else kar's having a really good time
yeah I was really happy she wants to do
a season two I was like oh really that's
the best thing that you can tell me is
that you want to do a season
2 she like can we keep our characters
I'm like I don't really know if we can
do that but if we're super good at it we
can speed run
it speed run it B Boo and Faun is having
a great time love when Faun is having a
great
time so that's what's going
on yeah and Kiara being able to join
every day really surprised me cuz it's
such a a tough like time slot for
her but n she she's into
it I didn't think Kiara would get into a
game about zombies you know me
neither but she's she's like taking it
like a champ and like she's she's
researching stuff my screen chat's
Frozen oh you you know what I know why
thanks for letting me know but what I
have to do is I have to pull up this
stream hold up you're going to hear
double audio okay and then I have to
pull up this chat hold up hold up hold
up pop out
chat grab link thank you very much for
the gift memberships by the way and then
paste it into this little
thingy maybe that'll work oh there he
goes sorry we're having to rework how we
do um
how we do our chats and
such I'm pretty sure this was just a
shirt
maybe and then open Palm this is open
Palm can't forget it's an open Palm
because PK
[Music]
Fire I mean pk5
IR oh man all of a sudden tummy really
hurt
from the antibiotics maybe I was waiting
for it I was like hm I wonder when my
tummy's going to start hurting
today now they kick in it feels like a
punch to the
gut I'll be
fine I'll be fine this another reason
why I feel like I might end up playing
but not
streaming s it depends I probably will
do it tomorrow but on the sixth on the
sixth day I sadly cannot because there's
another obligation that popped
up that I really kind of need to do um
but I trust everybody else will hold
down the fort and I'll be there for the
final
day they will handle it they will have
it
handled I wanted to drop in even just
for like a couple hours in the beginning
but I heard I have to be at the studio
very early for for
it it's a different stream it's a
different stream so I will be streaming
don't be jump scared by that
but um I have to go to the studio to do
it I was like dang
it maybe increase your fiber intake what
are good sources of fiber that aren't
cereal bars or like granola bars and
such there must be others I can eat
those they're just not my
fave all right we'll keep working on pk5
ir's uh dead beat Sonet at the beginning
of the Dark Souls stream but we got a
little bit teeny tiny bit done it's just
it's time to go help my friends now are
you ready Fiber Gummies veggies I love
some good veggies some grilled ones okay
okay that seems possible I can do
that
okay ah let me pull up the game
no everybody's going to get in there
before
me I got a race to everybody's going to
get in there before me all right let me
deafen and jump
into a voice
Channel
um I'm very excited for today though
because we get to do another zombie rush
and we get to see what it's
like you know I can't I can't even I
can't even blame R for yesterday's
mishap it was very silly number one
number two my OBS continued streaming
for 12 hours yesterday but it wasn't
connected to a
stream we all have those Pawn moments
can't be
helped all right pass
input I ski to 21 no no no it it wasn't
in the game though it wasn't in 7 Days
to Die it
was it was in h
OBS why if if anyone had like been in my
channel and clicked like go live or
something like that like a manager or
something you would have just seen my
outro screen for 12 hours maybe not 12
hours CU I was streaming for about I
wasn't streaming
wait was that yesterday or was it the
day before it might have been the day
before cuz I wasn't streaming yesterday
so I think it was the day
before days are blending
together days are blending together dead
Beats
oh hold
up here we go the fum pimps oh actually
hold
up never mind I can't let you see the
screen
yet never mind I can't let you see the
screen I'll let you see it in a
minute once I'm all
connected
okay all right it showed the thing you
guys can't see yeah yeah the fun pimps
that's the name of the that's the name
of the Hey look it's their their company
name not mine all right get on their get
on their case about it what happened to
your voice was sound
scratchy does it just sound very very
scratchy husky
Etc server details almost flashbanged
yeah but I was smart I didn't allow it
to happen this isn't my first
rodeo Oh well
not going to show the server IP not that
it would matter too much cuz you don't
know the
password but
still could have joined the server as
randoom yeah let's get some random NPCs
in This
Server can you imagine
that oh my gosh just invite just invite
a bunch of whole of fans to be
uh to be random MPCs that we can
interact with
password
444 they're too good they're just too
good all right hell Trel what's huh oh I
was at Trader jens's that's what it was
who's that is that oh it's
Gigi I'm not in the same VC as her am
I
oh hi oh hello hello Traveler
hello fellow
Travelers hello welcome we're Trader
Jens just going to grab a from right
away yeah oh should we start with
questing right away since we I guess
have a couple days to do Stu that might
be a good idea it happen okay I'll head
to trt Jens uh I'm going to put you all
in my party everybody get in the
party gets in your party yeah you're
allowed to be you invited me to our
party oh
shy yeah everybody get in my
party we can we can change it up later
going to be inside your
party you're welcome inside my party
anytime I give you permission you have
consent to be in my
party you have my complete consent to be
inside my party you're welcome I don't
know what I would have done without it
your consent that is not be in your
party I supp
party jeez what are we 12 Gigi my God I
should slap you with this roll slap you
with this this big bandage and wrap you
up we're in an apocalypse okay we have
to yeah it's how we C in these dark dark
times you okay I appreciate the honesty
do you like my bat I like it is it cool
what if I smash you over the head with
this G try it no I won't do that you
really want to if you didn't I would eat
this egg
do you like how
I my armor is getting shred oh Lord you
got bat I found another baseball bat I
put it in the um weapons test if you
happen to need a second basb baseball
bat is
crazy oh thank you about first
bandage it was a big chunk of HP
gone sorry about your armor you can get
it fixed
I hope so too oh my lord it's fine it's
no longer getting shredded that's good
yeah I need to keep that armor safe let
me check your inventory my girl no
problem no problem o Furious Fists fa
would like that she's the Fister in this
universe yes the fist
yeah so I wonder what we're goingon to
do today for um popping pills might have
what you're looking for what's it the
the the raid the raid I'm wondering what
we're going to do because we could use
the spikes or we could try funneling the
zombies the spikes work really really
well I don't know if they'll be able to
hold I think it I think it depends on
how many of us there are as true
well I'm heading over to Trader Trader
lady I'll be waiting for you yeah you
know I feel like um how' you
say uh let's just use the same method
until it doesn't work
anymore okay why not not broke if it
ain't broke don't fix itly that is
something
say that is a saying I wish I could
figure out how to repair my preacher
hat so is it going to be like two times
more difficult because we missed the
other one or does it still based on our
level I thought it Scale based on level
but I wouldn't be surprised if it didn't
oh well hello hello have
unmuted hello have a nice day
everybody
wow the waha armor Shop is open for
business ooh can you fix armor kits
right yeah armor kits that those can be
crafted too you can check out like uh
what do you need for it crafting armor
kit uh yeah armor crafting kit needs
okay my cat knocked over something arm
parts armor parts stealing kid and duct
tape stuff awesome I'll go get it and
I'll have you make me a nerd hat yeah
okay yeah let see what level I can make
it after today's
uh Quest currently the nerd hat that I
can make is at level three so it won't
give you the best exp buff yet but
like exp buff is a good true
agreed do you see the quest that I just
took to on your screen by
chance yes you want to just meet me it's
highlighted okay anyone who wants to
join me on the quest that's in my party
GG you're in my party oh I have a quest
near there too oh very nice wait let me
join your party yeah get in my party I
sent you an invite there you go thanks
yeah not sure where you are but I'm
going to see if we can go do the
quest y are you guys in the desert the
area right clear it's a clear Quest
okay I'm
here I'm pretty far it might take me a
while to join you guys can maybe do one
Quest without me first oh that's okay
I'm just like looting the area and
killing baddies how's that going for oh
my Lord zombies are knocking down so
much wood I'll come a little bit later
I'm a beaver oh just kidding it's you
Gigi I thought you were a
[Laughter]
zombie uhoh
okie
dokie turns out I do need the Tactical
Warfare magazines that say improves
assault rifle crafting skill because
that apparently also includes machine G
so many I put so many in the in the
magazine chest so you should check
either old house or new house I put like
seven of them in there ooh thank you
awesome nice hey Gigi and and uh bio if
you want to if you want to do a quest
with me I'm right in between you
guys okay hi yeah just meet me and
there I'm here nice nice welcome babe I
saw G over there she was knocking
entries hello
hello welcome
welcome I have lots of
magazines any shotgun
mags I have a rifle world
is that different I think Kar needs that
one different gun you see I have I have
a batter oh yeah up I need that volume
one I have handy land oo an explosive
magazine any want do Quest we're
starting and you're right next to us
wait yes where are you let's
see yeah we're in the town getting my
party that we were last
time yeah
very
excited do some other stuff right now
sure thing
yaha on my thank you for your
services
yeah very excited well you're really
looting and shooting everything
huh do you want some
wood yeah I'll take your wood okay come
here and take my
wood SAR to God
3,000 is that why
they a new one I'll get some more don't
worry she's full of wood I have so much
wood
cool
cool cool it is kind of cool I want
Grandpa's awesome sauce what the heck
okay I'm
here yo they got Grandpa's awesome sauce
oh my Lord that's awesome sauce yeah all
right ladies let's go
wait wait wait take this book oh oh is
the baseball one yes F on my you read
pool books which books Andy land
um yeah this
one oh and it's a lumberjack one too
I've been reading these ones and then
the ones that improve the club or axe
bio aren't you reading harvesting rifle
world oh no I'm a handgun oh you know
rle World I'll hold on to it CU it seems
like you really want to give it to me
and I appreciate present what does rifle
world do don't AR you
use though I don't know what does it do
makes you betterle crafting um I'll just
hold on to F sniper rifles no no I don't
need sniper rifles that's fine just the
assault rifle
magazines cuz those are for machine guns
too apparently yeah get them ladies yeah
good idea there's some spikes up here
I'm going to destroy
them I hear in the closet oh he's got
yellow eyes
he
scary hey when can this when do these
spikes go away okay
cool I didn't stab you did I no I don't
think so
okay oh
hello maybe going up this way is
better hello the spikes are popping
off remember [\h__\h]
house got rid of
all to your
head nice good job
ladies what are you doing
zombie that was aw awesome I have
something for you to read right here
that was stupid strong thank you there
is stupid strong kind of awesome this
bat's
broken I agree my sledgehammer is broken
too oh nice so you can relate feel like
we're experiencing the same things even
though we were in different places
crazy there's a lot of medical stuff in
here oh nice someone should take one of
these Med kits
oh oh the barb wire oh yeah good idea I
wonder who would be a good
choice who is our well I mean everyone
could use Med he's on fire wa yeah make
him pay the zombes on fire oh charge
zombies now
huh okay it's fine think we're good
that's enough buy
zombies how many more left I wonder oh
there's a safe
here ooh you found a
safe
yeah I have a loot I don't oh do you
yeah can I see it sure here I dropped it
on the ground ah they're all upstairs oh
yikes um oh okay it will take me 15
seconds to unlock this please defend me
I got you I'll defend you with my life
with my life bio I got your back oh dang
all right
nice
punching nice punches off
F oh boy okay I got it what's in there
it only had one molotov in it amazing
it's the saddest thing I've heard all
day and we're just getting
started pretty sad day e boo do you use
9 mm ammo I do I have some do you craft
bullets I am learning medical yes I do I
have bullet casings also I can I can
hold on to did someone pick it up huh or
did it
despawn plant fibers wait what are you
talking about what thing there was 9 mm
ammo it despawned what it was only it
was only on the ground for like a second
I thought it takes 20 minutes it's
messed up game yo fun pimps what why why
is that how it works fun pimps where did
it go wow so much fun hey underworld not
very fun from the fun pimps well we
completed is
anyone working on like medicine and
stuff I have a book of how to make oh I
bandes yeah I think a couple of us are
so maybe give it to fauna I think it
would be
good yeah I think everybody having a
little medical skills probably for the
better just to make decent bandages
yeah okay oh yeah I think
who is
that how are you going to use
sledgehammers in the future probably yes
um I don't really think sledgehammers
are in my build I'm pretty sure it's
just bats and shotguns for Str oh it's
just bats okay I have a sled Kiara is
doing hammers right okay I'll save that
for you yeah Kiara's getting hammered oh
nice o nice idea yeah now they're going
to break it
down watch out before he vomits on you
police they're police zombies though so
be
careful oh oh wow so strong This Bat is
so
broken but I'm also very high level with
the skill so you going to
move hello I think the server is lagging
oh
yeah maybe I'm dead already then help
help everybody's Moon walking in
place I'll take it
that was
silly oh
fing what's here pipes just pipes oh
there's ammo on the top of here thank
you there's an ammo pile I got it uh
shotgun and Crossbow parts but I don't
really think we need
those so
noisy you guys want to go uh turn in the
quest maybe get another one okay well
actually there's there's uh tier two
clear for G and Fa I he oh sure let's do
it very nearby Quest G is really nearby
lead the
way I think it's over
here lead the way and then both parties
split
completely oh no it's I think it's the
same house first really quick and
then can we even do it though right now
there might be a cool down so maybe we
should do the one Gigi wants to do ew I
ate a
bad sandwich and now I have
a sandwich oh I would like some tea that
would help a lot I'm on my way oh thank
you do you want any more sandwiches
before you drink the tea oh God I don't
want I didn't like it it made me sick
you can min max your sandwich
in oh gosh I also yeah eat another
sandwich no I
always no no more sandwich sandwiches I
I've been in the condition to hate
sandwiches now because they gave me
diarrhea that one time so now I hate
sandwiches better than raw
meat all I have is raw
meat yeah this Quest isn't available
until 1413 oh okay let's go to fauna's
one then yeah fa's got a
quest all right now I'm going
to wait no it's not it's somewhere
bye-bye
diarrhea that guy's freaking me out over
there let let him
see just straight Savage eating the raw
meat I've eat raw meat before in quest
ohc oh
yeah Okie doie just don't die Lady
newspapers Jacob's residence let's Ratt
wait this is crazy there's books here
huh really helpful books archery book
where archery I have it for you
yay oh here take I have a bunch of Arrow
stuff please thank
you rattle them girls let's do it here's
archery yummy yummy his Bat is so
strong oh I'm hi oh do I push it I think
so it is your
quest I've never done my own Quest
before first another people's Quest time
to kill them
all and sometimes it's forgetting Quest
zones
hello how sorry sorry please don't Smack
me oh I died what no way no way did my
bat really hurt you yeah I think you
smacked me too hard oh no maybe I should
perish too as you no no no no no no keep
your class keep your class no I think
you should we demand a fair trial tells
it how it is it's okay I needed to be
punished for all the times I've killed
everyone anyway my own you have killed a
lot of people maybe we asked them to
turn off friendly fire from here on
out we we could I know what is that it's
a little hard should n you don't think
so because sometimes people want to be
killed like when fauna killed Cecilia
because Cecilia wanted it it's true
that's true oh they there are flaming
men upstairs be careful flaming
men
Hallelujah
there's I'm glad I wasn't with you girls
cuz my internet just died and kicked me
out oh
no is fa behind me right
now don't worry I made sure to not hit
you you see how strong that bat is one
hit one hit dead if you hit them in the
Headly fire is part of the experience be
more upstairs yeah it is part of the
experience did you girls hear why CeCe
can't join us today why because she's
drunk she's to drunk so funny oh no oh
yeah she was playing SEO she she took
100 sips more than
100 I heard3 yeah 130 130 SI CE and I
can get along
I we need to hang out a little
more
incredible Jin
Jin isn't Jin really strong not not I
wouldn't really I think that whiskey
would be a little more
oh whiskey would probably be a little
more intense but itle tummy with the
poopies cuz I ate a sandwich oh no you
need need
tea I don't have need tea I have do I
have anything that helps stach there you
go that'll help you oh thank you eat
some more sandwiches first okay okay let
me sand my sandwiches and then take it
there's somea I must have you have to
Mid Max your hunger yeah yeah all
right M yummy is anybody working on
Salvage tools at all um let me
check Salvage tools I have 12 on Salvage
tools oh okay I'll give it to you um
want to go to the trader again how you
use heavy
armor oh I use heavy armor will she will
she will here you go I have heavy armor
for
you oh which one is it a helmet oh oh I
think I already have a helmet I that one
yeah you can hold on to ites anyone else
need a helmet
take the sh shells I probably should oh
thank you I probably should get rid of
my old preure hat not going to
lie but it's so dang
cool I kind of can't like an old rock
star oh I didn't know I had that did did
you guys already finish that first Quest
yeah
yes you can probably turn we have more
there's a there's a GG clear nearby oh
yeah let's we can do that really quick
I'm just going to quickly build myself a
new machine gun I think and then I'll
come over
[Music]
okay going to be
bodybuilder you think we can start your
quest now or do we have to wait we can
start it okay let's do that I should be
there
now oh she's
Speedy I want SL my what you can't pick
up a bike if it has stuff in the storage
yeah can't it's okay you can just ride
it ride it and park it um no one's going
to pick it up really what if someone
does steal it I'll take it Ste your bike
in zombie
apocalypse steal
it I'll make you a new one if someone
Tak yeah we got your bag I'll give you
mine don't worry oh we can we can share
about the wives can share a bicycle I me
lock your bicycle you can you can lock
your bicycle and enter a code for it and
I don't think people can steal your bike
lock your bike yeah there's a locking
function that's tell me your bike code
now no it's one one1 what a good bike
code the typical whole life password you
can get into all of our social media
accounts if you just type in 1111 one11
it's very secure oh yeah what a
wonderful word come on give it a try
hack
us I do still1 is the password
they're going to get us locked out of
our iPads for a
year oh no not the iPads no my iPad code
is different though it's very funny that
you guys think we're
J got to really stop hting my friends in
head with my
bat have I already finished my quest can
I give how can that be can I give you my
um a bandage if I hit you in the head
please maybe as an ingame today so then
maybe yeah cuz it was 6 a.m. when we
ended last
night oh God there's a lot of big poos
here are you kidding
me there's no way that I one shot
him oh my gosh you're a
menace it had to be a critical hit
there's wait isn't there someone in The
Walking Dead with like a terrifying
baseball bat like that there is uh a
villain was it oh yeah Negan
yeah and he kills a bunch of characters
that I love yeah yeah yeah I hate that
guy spoilers just kid well you don't
know what characters I love B silly
these trees oh yeah I'm going to call
this bat Lucille in negan's
honor yeah cuz his bat's name is lucil
ky yeah the trees you planted in front
of our house conceal our house so much
it's it's hard to find the house now and
it's hard to find an exit and an
entrance it's don't worry I'll chop them
down once I come back please
do take care of it I don't want to kill
you I also don't want to stab you is
death oh you found the fake
wall oh yeah
nice smart fa's got better eyes than I
have who has a tummy ache I hear it you
hear my tum tum
growling my tum I didn't hear anything
do it again I hear them do it again this
might be a fake wall too actually hold
up
this could be a fake wall need that
Golden Rod tea I'm okay oh hello hello I
think this is a fake this isn't a fake
is it oh ow the spikes still
[Music]
hurt let me look oh boy huh what's that
noise oh oh someone's using the
defibrator oh he after the spikes I
really
hurt you need a bandage fauna oh I had a
a kit okay so you're good I'm good for
now I can craft one oh I'm level
14 ni
well let's
see wa did it now I can get bodybuilder
yay yay
good job team let's get out of here now
we can return Yes get those tasty quests
turn in there's some farmer boots in
here if anybody wants farmer boots any
Farmers that need
boots boots and cats and boots boots and
cats boots and cats and boots and cats
yeah boots and cats and boots andat cats
and boots and cats and boots and cats
and boots and Cat boots and Cat and Cat
we're in a zombie apocalypse um it's
wait until I suck on your
lips yeah swag swag swag on you she's a
rapper chilling by a fire while we SI
fondu sip sip sip LCS that have never
been sip sip sip sip sip sip sip are you
a toilet sitter you can't be on our team
if you
are the toilet sitters my
favorite all right there's some lot up
here I have no more so if anybody wants
it feel free to take it no worries I'm
heading back to the Traer you have to go
home I have so much stuff in my pockets
I need to go home too I have like a
bunch of Band-Aids which I would like to
share ooh we will need those for The
Rush are you just offloading them on us
or you I'm worried I'm worried about
People's Health ouch are you really
sharing
them I'm worried about everyone's Health
you know how
kind I reached the Quest liit for today
too congratulations I can make my
payment to the Duke now who's the
Duke all of these kind of suck Jennifer
I'm sorry but it's kind of bad rewards
yeah but look at her chest that's the
only reward we need race mod didn't you
want her to like be into and now you're
like dissing her no she's just she gave
me some silly items and I don't really
know how I feel about
him uh let's see structural brace mod I
don't really need I don't really care
about decoration
though
Wonder
hole
n oh weighted head Mod's pretty
good what does that do um it says it
adds a chance to stun and slow
victims I already have that I'll grab it
for somebody else then if that's the
case okay we got some more
things this is good actually weapon
flashlight
mod can you put it on your bat The
Shining bat of J I
wish well maybe on the next shotgun I
can do
this seems pretty
good feeling a bit under the weather I'm
hungry is here to
help I know I need to go home to
cook
stuff yeah big
hunger
starving oh she's got grilled meat
though and Cornbread wait I'm full on
oops I bought it
inventory on
inventory thanks for the business I'm
full on
inventory I love the taste of
inventory for
despawn I feel like if we do another 10
quests with her or do all of her quests
will she give us a motorcycle
maybe that's why I kind of really want
to do Quest I don't know she'll give us
something good
though something
good it's a cooling mesh mod
good um not really because it'll take
you you're your uh so your armor only
has like a limited amount of slots
problem
so I see like Bigger Pockets mod and
stuff is better I
think wait am I not done with Quest
I think I
am I don't know if there's anything I
can really give
her not really farming these days so I
don't really need these oh I have am for
you I
you there's really no reason to even
sell her things if she can't just take
all the
inventory it's wrong wrong with you
woman my God I hate her just kidding her
no I would never say that about my wife
just knew you find something you like
give me a
sec I got to make some of those armor
kits now soon for gaha to help me would
you like a mod for melee weapons that
lower degradation by 25% I'm okay I'm
not too worried about degradation thank
you very much though I appreciate it
okay I'll put it on my axe or something
yeah yeah go for it you can definitely
make good use of it and then this I'm
going to put maybe on my current shotgun
even though it kind of
sucks
okay I am sorry you right in front of me
as I tabbed back in are you drinking
again I'm sorry dear I didn't mean to
punch you don't tell anyone okay okay I
won't you want to you want to ride home
together
okay are you coming home we are coming
home
yes what are you coming home for I to
offload stuff and cook I guess okay so
many things I will do Quest I need to go
home too as well cuz I have too much
stuff okay yeah yeah what is the best
way to get home a quick trip home might
be a good
idea
um where even is
home so nor well there's this main road
we could
take well we could take the main road
and then go west and then go
north okay where'd you go I went into
the okay let's go this way aren't you so
curious what's in here yeah I guess so
I'm working our working our legs
getting swoll ever skiing like day I'm
going to follow you guys seems fun oh
gosh well when you girls come home and
offload and you're done with everything
then I'm ready to do quests
anytime remember the day
21 which way this way probably up oh
maybe this way if the bitee can even go
up The Path can it just takes a while
you know cuz it's really it's rough I
mean but at that point why not just when
I just no no but then how will you
increase your biking skill I won't but
you guys are going up pathway okay I'll
come too I'm almost there guys CS yo can
Trader Jen get us a mountain bike please
yeah oh gosh jeez my gosh I'm just going
to run goodness gracious me sweet
Jesus this is like yoi pedal huh oh I
know you're talking what what is yoi
pedal y it's exactly what you imagine it
it's I don't know what to imagine can
you please explain in great detail so I
can visualize it in my head um bunch of
yahi and they're pedaling on bikes
that's not really what it is but I guess
no B Bo how would you explain it it's
called yoa Mushi petal and
there are a bunch of but how would you
know that it's yahi petal if that wasn't
a good description because because I how
would you know that's what she's talking
about because I know how you think it's
really
good I know how you think so there's a
dude who loves muscl y on pedals yes
yeah well no but kind of but yes I mean
if you really if you look at it that way
I guess wait can I drink from this Lake
really really quick yeah you need I will
watch you um are you
thirsty I don't think I am but I would
like a second what what is it called I
would like to share your hat as an
indirect
kiss don't worry about it does anybody
need water I'm okay I bought a couple
bottles it be fine actually I would like
to sip sip so that way I don't waste the
water that's in my inventory okay here
you go an indirect kiss
O Okay speaking of
yoi I need a
freehand take my corn
seed
delicious bikes are so silly in this
game they really aren't that much faster
but they they are funner but it saves
your stamina true my stamina is still
like zero but it's it's fine all right
be boo take this hat for drinking water
than you I will go to the exact same
spot that you drank at so it will be
more of an indirect Kissy Kissy oh wow
yeah it's more intimate she's going out
of the way see I think she sip sip like
right
here I can still I can still see the
water is still warm I don't know why
it's
warm yo you guys delicious they actually
started growing supern yummy my eyes be
hint of hint of gig this is
G it's like water it's like flavored
water where it's like you run a run a
fruit over a faucet and then that's what
it tastes like that's that's it ran over
yes a fruit and a f it I'm eating
blueberries here you go thank you thank
you annabe potato yum y y don't tell
them I'm in their fridge in their fridge
eating things right
now yo can we get some Cooks maybe
cooking some more of this meat cuz we
have a ton of raw meat we have 52 raw
meat I will cook please some more Cooks
in the kitchen great I'm going to eat
this Char we have do we have eggs cuz
it's oh there's a bird what the heck I'm
out of
there oh my God there's a lot of birds
not surprised out of
here is it really
Birds nice there zombie bird I hear I
hear more there's more oh my gosh
shooting them out of the sky get them
rattle them okay they're going to give
me a bad
[Music]
reputation we need better representation
of birds in this
game oh yeah in the game you okay yeah
I'm just taking out my anger here party
invite mailbox oh thank you you're
welcome I got kicked out twice already
out of this game and out of the internet
wait do you read Magnum enforcer I do
here you go thank you
I love how you ask as though it's like
we're subscribed to certain magazines or
something like that do you
need I to have a
you zombie Birds batter up I'm ready get
out of here before more birds
show I'm stuck on the
mailbox and I can't pick my bike up
full oh no who built this Forest yeah
who built it the fun P maybe maybe we
can we can we can smack the mailbox to
death yes okay let's smack the mailbox
wait I got it I got it oh yeah mailboxes
have magazin I don't got it all hold on
hold on I'll set I think I'm free I'm
free okay okay thank
you oh
no oh shoot I am pretty thirsty I don't
have time for this I'm
fine just open your mouth collect the
water yourself with your
mouth why is that not possible I'm very
mad about that know right I know I wish
we could turn snowballs into
water right I'm going to go get armor
plates so that I can make those armor
kits so I can get a nerd hat from
Kiara that nerd hat oh yeah we have to
prepare for the the r yeah it's on the
21st so we have like but the the old
house is pretty reinforced still I think
yeah it's going to be a tier three raid
oh
[Music]
yeah yeah I think the old base is still
pretty well reinforced you know if it
ain't broke don't fix it but I still
want to go get a little up close in
personal with some of the zombies yeah
get some XP yeah precisely we should try
to craft as many nerd hats as we can
definitely I really want make a normal
shot
Ro I'm so close Tex and ride everybody I
was to you and then I also hit the
car it's so far this
traitor I have one armor parts I think
that you just need one
uh for what for the nerd hat
yeah and let's see we need for the nerd
hat in order for me to make it on level
three it's free crafting kits if you
just want it on level one I can make it
for you for one crafting kids like
apparently it really correlates I see
yeah I think it would be better to make
it on a higher level if you can get more
armor crafting kids okay I could have
sworn we had
more you can make them but pretty simple
ingredients but we're currently always
lacking duct tape you have bird still
F I'm stealing bio's dir tape and I'm
putting it back later I get more I see
you biking with two birds overhead
another
one they really getting targeted what
this sound yesh we just brought the
desert back with
us they're knocking oh wait is this the
house really loudly oh yeah it's our
house oh get rid of those trees I free
duct tape from the old house or from the
new house
home I don't want to see these trees
anymore o it is night time can you still
make glue from Bones and duct tape
actually I'll make her some new ones
right
now
glue better just kidding
could have sworn I had
glue my iron sled was canc
why I'll take it with
me all right time for a very frightening
bike ride back to the new
house what is that does anyone have
eggs yeah that's what I was thinking we
can make bacon and eggs with all of them
I think we have a lot of eggs at the old
house m spikes did not really affect him
huh I will look for
eggs ah shiny eyed
D finally the the boat with spikes came
in handy I will if I can find the
entrance to our house I will him to it
the zombies are getting scared uhoh I
fell in some spikes I
think he's here he's here oh God he's
fast he's coming into our house
he's chasing me he's chasing
me easy I feel like I'm breaking our
house there we go mercy so
scary nothing to be scared about a spike
attack Spike P moment piss all get rid
of the
trees my character is so hungry I hope
you guys are grilling some meat
um
Chef hey
chefs we have two Chef we need egg where
are you looking I'm on the way to the
new house I guess we can make regular
grilled meat but is it worth it I don't
think it's worth it we have so many eggs
at the old house that bacon and eggs
would be so much better can we get an an
egg delivery oh God all right I'm
turning
around thank you
I'm turning
around what happened to my armor it says
crit does that mean it's critically
damaged we have some baked potatoes and
grilled corn in here that's good I might
eat some of that at least tied you over
yeah well we're waiting for the good
stuff right
[Music]
yeah hey Chef all right I'll be
waiting we have one bacon and
eggs yum
yum I guess I shouldn't have been just
fisting those eggs in my mouth I guess
still eating raw
eggs I I was doing it to prove a
point
to I asked her if she wanted to see me
at eat these six raw eggs and then I did
no that's three bacon in
eggs think of how much breakfast we
could have had we could have had so much
breakfast
Gigi that's okay I forgive you stop
eating those eggs ra you have problem I
can't help so much protein you've made
your point don't worry
G okay I'll stop eating the raw eggs
please no more this isn't Japan you
can't just do that it's not have a tummy
I'm not surprised all right 13 13 eggs
here we got 13 I'm going to go put some
of this stuff away oh you can you should
check the cooking pot uh at the house or
the one of the cooking pots cuz I think
I was cooking a bunch of bacon and eggs
before oh yeah so you might want there's
five and there's three water yeah there
you go you can go ahead and take it and
bring it over like okay I'm going to eat
one of these bacon and eggs okay just to
keep myself
okay and then I'll bring the rest of
everything over to
put how many armor parts do I need for
the
Hat uh if you want it on level three
then free I have three oh
nice what else do you need um the rest I
can take care of myself okay I'll give
it to you about to get the nerd hat it's
fine um I'm in the house in the
kitchen in the real kitchen where
there's no cooking to
done where no cooking is happening
whatsoever yeah okay and then I'll take
my forged iron and the leather nerd hat
is wait did I pick it up you gave me
free armor kits I
did where did they
go oh was it oh maybe I gave you armor
parts oops oh yeah I
guess I think that's it can have them
back okay let's see how you make armor
kits you need sewing and duct tape I
actually have some duct tape for you bi
boo I just need to get some glue first
oh no I have I I have the other things
too I'll make quickly okay okay okay wow
wow armor shop well I stole your duct
tape in the old house just so you know
so I owe you three duct
tape we need duct tape more duct tape I
can craft duct tape I have a bunch of
cloth and we just need glue I do need oh
wait I can just make duct tape too I
think yeah it's simple
ingredients yeah can never have enough
true
enough I like how this game brings you
to like even later in the game you keep
on needing simple ingredients that you
get early in the game yeah the simplest
things like cloth fragments and stuff
like that it all has a purpose
yeah which is nice I prefer that to
always learning about new items and
never needing the old
ones yeah for sure okay I'm almost there
I've got a delivery of eggs and then
bacon egg I have the kits for you okay
I'll go back to the kitchen I'm here I'm
here have to make my hat too
kiaha I think I went the wrong we all be
nerds nerds be so cute oh no I made a
mistake I went to the wrong room My
Le where did my leather
go quick there it is okay there are
zombies
here can't believe I didn't
crafting and finish you're going to look
so cute
yay where are you my creature hat I'm
here put this on oops that's fine oh
getting some air do I look cute oh wow I
didn't know you had such a beard do I
look
[Music]
cute oh my gosh you guys match look at
you look at you am I am I cute do you
think I'm
cute those
glasses perfect hey they're having a
fashion show without
me we're matching show you guys my
mustache wait I have cool facial hair
too please well I already know your
mustache it's very thick it's very cool
you know it well don't you it's so in
style yes it's very scratchy for
smooches you're such a fash all the
ladies I want the person who dug this
hole in front of the traitor
[Applause]
dead no it's
funny very you know it I want to meet
them I would love to meet them and shake
their hand and give them a smile and
tell them how good it is
the
hole Yeah the hole yes it's a good
hole is the best hole Yeah Hol are nice
you can hide in them what are you doing
now giggy oh I'm hitting trees enjoying
life
Beaver can never have too much wood I'm
looking for
nest oh somebody's screaming oh oh yeah
there's a screamer I heard that too
actually
oh whoopsies that's
me here they
come oh yeah there's a couple coming
towards our
house I will help defend the new
home let's get them
ladies help I'm out outside I'm out of
stamina thank you oh my God that's
SP think we're okay more
stamina oh there's a lot jeez
let's go oh they really are aren't they
oh my God we can take them we can take
them oh my
god oh oh hello ouch ouch
o I'm infected too a little bit a little
bit just a little bit yeah
0.44% it's not that
bad nothing a little funy
C wa see we're great team I like this
action I wanted some exp bring me more
oh there's more I hear more you asked
for more you shall receive Kiara there's
still someone
alive sounds so
close oh he's on the ground he's over
here on the ground I'm just having a
snack really quick so hard to see yeah
he's chilling in the grass sorry didn't
see you down there hey guua I have the
materials for the nerd hat you do nerd
hat so po all right yeah your special
Kiara brand nerd hat here's this I will
get to it right away thank you so that
you can show off your nerdiness proud
excited I've been a preacher for too
long let's see I also have the eggs I
don't know if we have
ingredients that's okay I got your eggs
I will just zombie it up don't don't
become a zombie no has fin finished but
then your your current hat what's going
to happen to that it's almost broken so
it's fine oh
okay well well this will be hopefully of
good use to you ooh and I can put my mod
my intelligence mod on it to make it
extra nerdy ooh intelligence
mod I
pr I don't really know what it does I
don't really know if it's even helpful
but I'll take
it
[Music]
okay byebye appre your hat let's see why
am I fatigued maybe I will make this
this is so
silly
oil hey guys why am I
fatigued are you tired you swung too
hard now you need a little nap the
bullet is eepy dang it I wonder what I
should vitamins maybe maybe vitamins
will
help oh yeah we have some I'll eat a
couple
H here's fatigue I have this for you
parts for later since I think you're
using hammers oh thank you thank you are
there steel steel
steel I get so many Steels let's my part
this if anybody finds machine gun parts
please let me know I'll let you know one
more okay I wonder if there are any at
the old house I'm pretty sure I saw them
somewhere I checked I checked no there
was
um uh not enough not enough that's rough
dang it yeah some
glue um is coffee
good um it gives you a buff I forget
what buff it gives you but it gives you
something coffee yeah coffee gives you
stamina regen 20% oh that's good stamina
regen is good does it fill your water or
does it make you dehydrated no it makes
you it fills your thirst it does
and pipe shotgun is not even worth using
maybe maybe we should be making drinks
with the with the empty water than just
drinking straight water I feel like we
need glue maybe yeah glue is what cuz I
have a ton of cloth there's like 91
cloth that's a lot of cloth I have more
glue I have a couple more glues oh nice
cuz that could make duct tape and you
really need duct tape oh glue glue is
water too while everything needs water
yeah oh
let's see I might to make some
glue
yeah
oh good
idea I have fdy glue oh you can get all
the skills one level earlier with the
intelligence mod so it's very nice mod
oo
cool I'm going to make my sledgehammer
cause some sick Burns today cuz it's
going to light zombies on fire I want to
see it in
action I want to see it too I can
actually show it off earlier probably go
advantages who cantly on
[Music]
fire ammo thank
you armor plating look PA look my
sledgehammer it's on fire oh it is
you put it in the fire yeah I I honestly
don't know why it's how it does that but
it's fun hey kiaha you're making armor
right I don't really know if this will
be useful to you but I feel like you
should you should take it and use it
it's a
schematic oh yeah I mean anybody can put
that on their armor to make their armor
stronger I think oh yeah oh another well
you can have it I don't really want oh
oh but ah this is the schematic too I
see never mind I'll I'll learn that yeah
yeah
could be helpful
learn
okay I want to do Quest okay I'll do a
quest with you I'm I'm ready for quest
really I come home drop stuff off and um
we can go to the new Trader yeah
okay she's I don't have any uh quests
personally but I'll just do whatever you
go I think there is an active Quest but
I don't know who activated it it's 88 me
away I have I have a tier 2 infestation
and then Gigi also has a tier 2
infestation oh nice well let's go do
those perfect 4:00 a.m. okay does
anybody use clubs yes Mo here I think I
have a mod that you could use o uh I
dropped it in the right here oh metal
chain ooh the chains yeah people have
been wanting me to use the chains so
thank you oh I brought
eggseggs I have five five eggs and 20
meat good job oh thank you our bread
winner providing for the family that's I
accidentally put who is it's everything
into my inventory on accident
[Music]
well
welcome we woke up on our bunk bed yeah
we're going to help but we are H baby
then it doesn't look like anybody's our
house it's clean oh we have new house
house I figured maybe everybody do you
want me to come pick you
up it's night time no it's 4:00 a.m.
you're fine yeah yeah and you guys can
be on our team and get the EXP if you
want WR demon dogs we're going to go and
find you I should if you if you look at
the map and zoom out like really far you
can see a bunch of our names on the map
and that's that's new house
location okay we'll go on a quest G you
good okay that's not that far what you
trying to do okay yeah we can all I'm
going to go towards the the tier 2
quests the okay in the desert yeah is
anyone learning how to lock pick no I I
think I would like to okay here you go
thank you but why lockpick when we can
just Brute Force open
everything apparently there are saves
that that won't work with I had to lock
pick one F so it might be nice to have
we're going to go on a journey and then
once we everybody oh is it okay I see at
the old home here there's a bunch of
magazines and animal and stuff yeah yeah
you can use whatever are they can I take
everything at Old home or is it still
we're going to going to go back there
for the raid um so maybe leave some
resources but whatever you need you can
take okay yeah just stuff that you need
good we'll go on our journey then okay
come by if we have a questions sure make
sure to take lots of quests at the
trader if you want to get a bicycle
okay good okay we
will bow
do we have any honey Now by any chance I
feel like you can get it from the Tred
too you can buy it from the trader
actually ah he just charges too much no
the lady she charges less I think oh
really she's so
nice yeah she's a nice lady she wants us
I could get used to her she wants us so
bad yeah I'll just get some tree
stumps on the way to the desert or
whatever that place is yeah I'm sure
you'll find some honey have better RNG
luck than
me have you been looking for it
too uh no I I'm good now but whenever I
do need it it just doesn't pop out of
the
stumps sadly yeah it's a little bit rare
yeah okay so I'm going to go there
whenever you girls are ready we're going
to do quests there right I'm almost
there all right yeah I'm on the way some
f
water yes yes yes so we can stay strong
for as long as possible yes and some
bandaids are there tree stumps in the
burnt area as well or should I check in
the I think I did see
some but I'm not exactly sure but
there's a lot of
trees maybe like generally surrounding
the area if I see any I'll try and break
them
okay I wonder how much percentage until
you die from
the from
the sickness illness 100 one okay well
then I got a lot of time there's a I I
found a couple stumps I'll crack them
open for you okay see if you can find
any
honey was that Honeys and stumps and
stumps yeah I need a stronger
axe I'm still on quality one axe we're
heading to the infation Plus
I have quality
5x OMG quality five wow man you're a
beaver huh I am a beaver I can make iron
tools now too but I haven't touched the
bench you're the tool
Master yeah for my Beaver activities now
you need to like truly RP and bite them
with your teeth how you yeah yeah just
like that ah
infection is everyone infected I'm good
not yet you mean you're gonna get
infected yeah once I bite
them sorry Kiara my luck is just so bad
I opened up the stumps but there was
nothing in them it's
okay I'll probably die anyway I think
after a certain percentage uh honey
doesn't work anymore and then you need
antibiotics as well oh okay oh can we
craft that well maybe
someday maybe some day I'm at the
location by the way so after
5% honey doesn't work anymore what oh oh
well then I kind of want to find honey
right now oh tree
stump I think I would like to find some
honey
too I found one a tree stump please oh
no my character's hungry and I didn't
bring any meat dang it what am I doing
I've got oh really oh chef
yes really thank you
oh also Kiara oh no it does work it just
removes 5% honey okay yay I see good job
Gua also Gua I have two Hammer magazines
for you for
Sledgehammer Yi take some thank you did
you put it in like a box or something no
I'm just waiting for you at the location
oh I'm coming now now that I have my
honey I will hurry
excited to get rid of these magazines oh
my gosh us trading magazines is so fun
yeah it everybody has like a different
specialty yeah that's why I kind of
appreciate that we're not like 20 people
or so in this collab because then I feel
like I would lose oversight of who needs
what and now we have such clear roles
and it's really comfy
yeah I like this group me too me too
yeah usually usually I don't play like a
killer in games like the the really
physically strong one so this is new for
me but I'm having fun I love clearing
what do you normally do food cooking or
something like that yes thank you how
about some bacon and eggs oh my gosh my
chef a blueberry pie yes chef thank you
Chef that sounds so good you have a
Band-Aid you just have a Band-Aid just
in case visualizing it right now in my
brain I'll take your Band-Aids phone
I'll take your Band-Aids off your hands
there snake a snake there's a snake I
think it's just an angry zombie is it
not I'm gonna punch
it I'm
thiry
snake what is that chat why why am I
laughing at my
ligma oh ligma yeah like I have an icon
that's laughing at
the
radiation I guess because I'm laughing
was because it's going
away yeah of course that's definitely
the only reason that it's it's
laughing okay it is a little weird got
[Music]
him okay I'm kind of in the area now
what's
Lima what is Lima stop you all know
exactly who it's a very serious
illness that cannot be cured
normally how do you cure
Lima yeah how do you you know
you know
it I don't think I do I've never heard
of it before
jobs who's that huh oh oh wait how do we
get huh Zoomers these days I'm missing
[Music]
something Lima balls okay I said it
someone had to say it Lima balls
Lima worse than Cobin d a this time it's
you sacrificing yourself B thank you
you're welcome do you have any
Band-Aids I do okay there's a bird watch
out whoa protect friends protect friends
sledgehammers too who is it on the roof
that over there I'm getting chased by a
hog kill it
I yeah no wonder don't
miss wait stop
R I don't want it to bite me where are
they you guys are on the road huh
yay wait are you guys going to
infestation or bio infestation cuz I
think you guys are near I'm getting
chased by a pig any of them we are at
bio infestation wait that's your arrow
there's an infestation of bi Boos yeah
infestation many of
hered yeah we can do this one real quick
and then we'll do
GG's okay and then I want to I really
want to go check on the Twins and make
sure that they're ready for the the
apocalypse so I'm going to go talk to
them after this after these Quest we
also start preparing the old house yes
we need to prepare stuff as well cuz
tomorrow is the chosen day so w The
Chosen day the dawn of the final day
this is so
strong I'm looting a pig real quick okay
I'm looting a
pig yeah so much
meat okay you don't like that I'm
looting this pig please don't Lo the
Pig please
don't I'll do my best just get the meat
just get the meat
and I'll keep my thoughts to myself why
are you thinking about the pig oh no no
they're funny share
them thought thought you didn't want me
to I only pretend like I don't want you
to it's it's really I speak in opposite
speak which is really
annoying I say that I hate want
oh yeah I'll get your bone and meat you
guys got the water yes yeah I have some
water and some tea sorry I'm going the
wrong way just
water from the tap is fine I don't want
to pay extra for water just give me tap
water thank you what does this look like
oh it's
chained all right you guys ready so
ready are you done looting the pig
yeah but now I'm lost I'm almost there
okay I think I'm almost there you're
here I'm here let's get started let's do
it finally quest Quest time yipp yippe
kill them all oh lock door oh we could
break it or we find an open door a
different door ah dang
it they really tried to board up this
house huh H why do they need us to clear
out these infestations because like no
one's there anymore what's the point the
houses don't have a point yeah we want
to make it livable again I see
insirational ow did I oh guess we're
breaking down the door does the beaver
want to break down a door oh I would
love to break down the door open we're
so in oh they're in the way there's
actually so many zombies they they're
alive they're here oh they're very much
alive
and on
fire my hammer takes so much to
[Music]
swing keep up the good work everyone
help
help help okay almost died you are you
okay oh no I'm not okay you have a
bandaid I'll try and lure them
outside I'll need a Band-Aid later
here's the bandaid oh thank
you nice see where you work
done bi Boo looks so funny with the hat
and the
beard the wood crazy zomie fear me right
I'll oh there's an AK machine
gun I picked it up I'll give it to
someone else I have no interest
close it's bleeding for
a I just opened the door you stabbed me
ladies not each other I'm bleeding
out okay do you need a bandage Instinct
take this for I have thank you I will
use this bandage too empty here and also
yeah your health is low so use a regular
bandage too hold up uh let me see all
right here's a regular bandage for you
blood from my friends thank you no
problem heal
yourself is someone up there oh bio okay
me and fine are up here I don't know if
there's any more bad guys
closed do always bad still some more
okay I have ammo for you oh wow okay
thank you I'll get shooting
then no
mercy there's an
upstairs ooh cat picture new cat I'm not
sure love the cat
pictures uh-oh I've seen that one or cat
behavior oh maybe we just see
it it's a good good
cat every cat is good cat there are no
such things as demon cats agreed I agree
they're all perfect
angels we are the ones that are not
worthy of the cats there's a hole
where's the last
zombie probably down the hole come on
zomie who's a good zombie who zompie yes
you
are oh maybe it's
no do you guys see an orange
dot I do see an orange dot that might be
where it is oh it's upstairs somewhere
cuz it's pointing up second floor maybe
ceiling
zombie oh no it's second floor second is
this second floor what I don't is the do
really going to a zombie it seems like
pointing outside yeah that's a little
strange maybe the zombie is outside oh I
think it's a bird outside yeah on top of
the
other oh boy I didn't see a bird's nest
oh there's a bird out
there yay we're
done okay this Quest is complete
complete nice job
ladies a bit
thirsty okay we're going to go straight
to the next Quest yeah uh yeah it's
right below us okay I'll follow you also
is it possible for uh Kiara to repair my
bat at a workbench
possibly H I think with a repair I think
you just need your repair kit okay just
do and you can do it yourself here let
me let me give it give you one oh you
have a repair kit bio thank you yeah
appreciate that so
prepared okay and I Ed it at a workbench
right no no you just unequipped your
weapon and there should be an option to
repair thank you bi you're lifesaver
thank you so
much nice that's huge uh which Quest are
we going to I think it's over here tier
2 infestation gigy yeah it's just down
the road
okay my way almost
there I'm almost there too I'm getting
wood oh no she loves the wood more
in case we need it you have a wood you
know serious wooded that's so
cool I'm I'm I'm there have a treeh
housee how
sweet not one I'm done with
it she's going to eviscerate it with her
Beav shers
children you're going to watch me do
this are you going to dismantle it
you're going to watch me do this
no I like this tree
house the
tree you actually hurt me look it's the
look oh look it's
back wow God is gracious should I do it
again it K me how many times do you need
to fa the tree house to be satisfied
Gigi they cannot have a tree house not
when I'm around when the beaver's
here no I can't believe you're doing
this in front of fa that's messed up GG
oh it gets so messy around she can have
some of my 7,000 like there's a lot
coming there's a lot coming mad cuz
I shooting me stop shooting
me I was I wanted to help dang gun is
crazy God being melee is
suffering it is
I've got N9
HP all right fa I have a I can blow on
it and kiss I have I have two thank
you oh my
god blowing on it does that help it
should it should thank you I hear it
helps helps me kind of house is this
what were they doing here so much
kissing
what have I done they super angry I've
lost
myself not the same person anymore this
zombie stuff is getting to me this is
their bunker huh I'm becoming one of
them it's okay I beat fa earlier
too would beat I didn't mean to I just
lost myself found a couple there are a
lot of crates down here the punching bag
take the shotgun ammo there's there's a
ton of Bio ammo and Kiara ammo in this
fested catch that's yellow up here thank
you shotgun Messiah oh God he's
big why did I miss so hard there's also
a really good pipe
machine shotgun shells I'll take them
yeah also some behind you GG do you also
use a shotgun oh my God I have some
though
okay it's so
noisy is
okay I'll make sure they get
it
oh what a big family a pipe machine gun
where's bio there's there's a ton of 9mm
ammo in this yellow crate up here I am
I'm upstairs I'll come down after you
know I'll grab it for you oh I'll just
give it there's a lot of there's a lot
of things in the house right now get
into the house
I I broke the door wow Ah that's the
best way these houses are getting more
intricate oh yeah what is this for are
they protecting themselves from us
couldn't
be un must they family that turned into
zombies oh
wow the heck is going on I want to get
rid of this oh oh oh are you guys
destroying more floors no no I'm not
trying to it's doing it on its own
really are there
upstairs I was thinking is there an
upstairs it must be there has to be one
we're not done yet no does anybody have
any dirty water I can drink murky
water water there might be some in the
toilet dirty water I checked the toilet
already okay I'm outside the
house here's some dirty water upstairs
thank you leg H you have to be able to
get upstairs like maybe yeah where's the
last zombie I'm a person who bird again
if I want to get somewhere I'm going to
get there so I'm going to make a little
makeshift
stairwell outside and climb so
good did you grab all the ammo where was
the ammo did you say I am holding on to
it now oh
okay I don't see an orange dot
anywhere where is
hiding actually why am I picking up so
many
things okay I am on the second
floor if you want to join me I made a
little stairwell out oh here we here you
are
sir ah I see I
see oh wow he's quick and he's on
fire that zombies on
fire oh is this on
[Applause]
[Music]
fire I can't jump that high I took girls
check it out there are a lot of dudes a
whole lot of dudes and they're very
strong oh really so many yeah send them
down push them down all that was it huh
good job team yeah yay more more more
more more here you guys' ammo by the way
bio and Kiara you guys want a ton of
ammo a butt ton I got a butt ton this is
for
biboo okay and this is for Kiara where
where is she where is this beautiful
pink-haired woman Oh you mean pink hair
pink mustache
lad oh are you on the roof still yeah Oh
no you're there oh oh oh are you down
there Kiara yeah all right I'll bring it
to you if you're down if you're on the
bottom floor I'm down for it yeah so I
guess the only way to get up here is by
making a
stairwell outside now leave it to
me yay all right let's
see where is Kia wow are you destroying
the car yeah what for do we get parts or
St yeah you go to k
Chum it's for
you thank you a lot of bullets so much
ammo I'm swimming in ammo all right I
need to make a new axe new stone
axe
wow anything it's just satisfying oh we
don't get to pick it up a
no I have an armor book for
you I take I take
I have a cooking book for you nice
exchange thank you thank
you I can make pumpkin
cheesecake have a cake the world is
saved let's go I'm so
happy cheesecake will be our savior
anybody find any Baseball magazine I do
love baseball baseball no I have seed
and medic
okay well if you find a baseball one you
know who to
call cool who Ghost Busters you no
mories hey o raid in the
cafe I think somebody's been here it
does seem
empty well let's see what time is it um
why so broken want to go turn in the
quest back to the Traders yeah we got to
turn in this Quest after all this dog
start preparing for the thing there's a
safe in here already oh I have lock PS
maybe we can get another Quest when we
turn it in yes more quests more Quest
okay oh I'm in the wrong house I'm
coming come to me there's a
safe I'll head back to the
the what do you mean ask for the
AK-47 have AK I do what yeah I was going
to give it as a present here wa here's a
it's a AK47 machine gun where did you
get that found it in
box thank you sick cuz mine was just
about to break my my shitty machine gun
oh
enjoy brother you in the middle of day
20 yeah we'll be fine we'll be fine it
upstairs or downstairs it's down okay I
just want to get the twins up to is
upstairs I am going to turn into
questing then go find where are you I'm
in the basement I thought you went
downstairs basement but no no it's wrong
house you're the wrong
house come to
me I'm coming I'm just a little
silly make sure they got their weapons
and
such are you two just raiding houses
over there still there's a safe I did
ask them what they want
to specialize said
shotguns shotgun everybody wants to use
shotgun awesome are you doing this on
purpose look at your map I would like to
have my map yeah still
no okay I around the edges I'm embarass
but I'm here be right back you guys I
got run I got to run real quick I'll
BRB okay just a moment guys
BRB a nothing this
time
for
for for
for e
people you should get the nail gun it's
the best building upgrade tool oh hello
I did I did get a nail gun ladies I
going to go help out the twins but feel
free to continue your journey glad to
see your
face okay all right I'll see you
later see see you byee we do more level
two bow bow
b b b hey guys what's going on we're
digging a hole we're digging a hole oh
great doing some quests yeah okay I I
would love to come be a part of your
quests if you don't mind okay of quest
yes I'm going to go to you and help you
guys do a bunch of quests get you up to
speed yeah okay let's really quick let's
make our own party um okay okay so I'm
going to so we should probably be both
party then right probably let's
see um I'm going to make Kiara the
leader of this other
one and
then leave okay now I'm inviting you to
my
party
[Music]
okayy don't get
distracted you guys are digging a hole
don't worry about it I will go find you
we'll go how do we leave the party we're
in right
now oh
yes okay definitely do
that and I will I will come to you on my
bike okay yeah it for a moment so oh we
found
oh okay those are all good did I take
all this stuff I took this stuff
I got a party invite from you guys okay
I'll accept it now we're in the same
party I think there's a zombie that
found us oh no do you guys have any
weapons I found it it's a gun gun
gun okay this distance where' she go
where she go where' she go there she
is maybe maybe I don't need to shoot her
you can shoot her I going to have to
send her
away die yeah you're going to have to
violence other another gun another gun B
is the best way this one no no bullets
okay I'm running hello running is also
okay oh
hello I I I I I saw you but then you
running away from me stop running away
from
me CE you want to get in our
party yeah I just I just spawned and I
tried I keep running for more you keep
getting further away from stop stop
running she goes to help are a
zombie
[Music]
hiie s you look
strong I bet you weak yes I very strong
I'll protect you don't worry hide behind
we're going to do a bunch of big quests
together and get you guys strong and up
up to date this is on the hill to okay
I'll kill her for you okay stay behind
stay behind stay close but not too close
I tried using my gun
has arrived hope it doesn't have
bullets
boy she looks very plasticky oh she's
not going to
roll oh no hit her hit her hit
her is that the only is that the only
weapon you have or we have guns but we
don't have bullets gun okay okay is that
I couldn't tell was that just a normal
Stone axe okay let me give you a spear
okay that's
behind you behind you there's a big
one okay okay wait come with me here
I'll I'll drop it at this smaller tree
and then you have a spear which is
better because you have more
space between you okay and then aim for
the head yes head is the best oh I had
a oh you
hady the a is to to make stuff it's like
to repair and
Stu ow he's saying ow maybe we should
stop no keep going keep going he
it it
it me they're over here I think get them
get them get him I don't know if I need
to hurt him that much okay should we go
to you Kelly or I'm on my way to you
guys I have um a special club for you
it's got chains on it it's very
effective just try and hit them in the
head with it okay is it okay if we go oh
I got
scared H here you go this is a very
special Club it's a level five Club oh
thank you thank you it's my nerd glasses
I get lots of exp you know what fumo you
guys need one of these nerd hats because
this will get you a ton of exp during
the I thought you going to say because
we're a big nerds so I can't believe you
would just say that to them that's
messed up I can't believe it that is
maximum silliness right
there kie can you invite me to your
party yes
absolutely okay now I'm going to invite
why can't I invite you that's weird very
strange um oh foko you guys are the
leaders so you have to invite
CeCe let press Tab and invite her be the
leader for once okay invited okay quick
make some call some shots give give
Tower why yay we were working on diing
and then we got scared and R away oh oh
look at Tower it's so impressive it's so
Tokyo Tower oh Tokyo Tower why is it
next to an American
flag Tower to alternate universe it
looks different oh boy to Tower I don't
know if there are going to be any good
quests in here or good loot in here
though okay okay let's do let's do
quests for you guys all right let's go
the didn't quite finish off maybe no we
did you finished it land claim block at
the top zero out of one so I have a
feeling we didn't do it I think I just
have to build
one we have to
[Music]
H yeah we're going to see if we can make
you guys a little nerd hat so you can
get exp with the raid
um so for the raid you guys um guns
might be best just because we have the
spike Fortress set up and yeah uh but
but the thing is when the zombies run
into the spikes we don't get exp from it
so we prefer to shoot them if we can the
spikes like the last line of defense I
will be going out into the the the
center of the fight with my bat cuz it's
very strong but for you guys it might be
good to choose a gun and um but the club
is also helpful so just in case can I
place my land claim block can you make
make uh
cabs uh yes you can make them yeah very
with wood easy no no I mean the you said
you have a very strong one do you have
like a special one oh yeah I gave I gave
um one with the chains to them I can
make level six I believe no level five
clubs you what you mind me you want
level five Club I got you I want I want
a weapon cuz I I'm not really wait wait
where are you going turn around
okay look look at the M look at the top
left do you see your name and Callie's
name I Follow the arrow turn around turn
around turn around look at me see this
way this way okay and then on do you see
the arrow oh
God just stay stay they around SC where'
my bike go look at me we are faster than
the zombies run with me this way I've
lost my
bike they are very slow just keep
running
and follow the blue arrow that you see
on the top of your map and where CI is
that's like it shows the arrow and then
we can follow her okay so here here CeCe
here is a a level five club for you for
me the next shotgun I can make is a
double barrel oh man I need to keep
reading shotgun weekly um also oh there
it is NI here are some bandages for you
guys three see see here's here's two
it's not that I don't don't love you any
any more than them it's just here let me
get you another one all right there you
go there you go CeCe get those
bandages all right yeah those are for
you that there yep you can take these
too it's also for you CeCe oh for me
okay now you have three
bandages mom so ready okay okay okay
okay okay now let's go do some quests to
get you guys some exp get you up to
speed maybe bikes sounds good how many
quests have you guys done n we have
whole land claim block yeah okay gotta
we were digging I think we fin did we
finish the DI the quest in the upper
right corner does it say go to the
trader oh we did that one okay you got
it okay land clean block and then it
goes Place land clean block we didn't to
place it but I think we want to place it
in a good place right I don't
know um it's good to be pretty late so
I'm not sure if if we'll be able to turn
in the quest today we can turn it in the
morning
okay okay
here yep welcome to the
Traer I'm thirsty I need a little drinky
hold on little
drink this is my favorite
trador there's some dog food in here in
the vending machine if you want some dog
food dog food yeah you guys don't like
dog food the dog food and no dog food
you don't want dog food unless the dog
for you guys yummy
yummy how do I hand him stuff go talk to
him talk to him with e he's mean by the
way and he will he will be save some
very mean things to you that's not nicey
I don't know if he wants any of my
quest oh he wants to give you quests
don't you worry he does but he's just
kind of a mean guy so just get ready for
that oh I
see machine shot machine
gun armor we sell an armor pocket mods
we have a p machine gun P machine gun
pip machine gun pip machine gun bundle
yeah I want the shotgun no no no no I
want the shotgun
shotgun yeah
should I ask him for more jobs fetch yes
you want to you want to get a job right
okay there's fetch clear
zombies that's [\h__\h] man I treat you that
good and you don't even [\h__\h] tip
me let's see I have some level two
quests that would get you guys some real
real good exp let's do okay we only
accept one Quest at a Time come to think
of it I no you can do multiple oh we'll
do just fetch one let's do the second
fetch all right so if you guys want to
follow me I can take you okay thank
shall we shall we
go go is it the one on the map that I
see as well as it your or is that 43 424
or so meters
away 4 and yep right this way that I'm
headed
y follow where's the tip well he doesn't
deserve a tip he's a mean guy that
dude's a bully just ignore him it's a
bully he told us to wipe the smile away
yeah that's not very nice smile wait are
you guys crouching are we probably oh no
we aren oh we ar okay we
just off this
couch yeah we'll do a couple quests um
although it might be night time by the
time that we finish this so we won't be
able to turn it in we'll see okay um
until tomorrow and then we'll get you
guys prepared for the raid you know
teach you some stuff well we'll see if
we can make you some strong armor too
your armor what level is it careful
coming down this hill one okay all right
I got you I'll make you some be careful
be careful be careful just just kind of
carefully scale the wall so you don't
break I like that adrenaline yeah maybe
that's how we survive in the zombie
apocalypse we're all addicted to
Adrenaline yeah it has to be it's got to
be what's your what's your favorite way
to get
adrenaline coffee mine is cough that's
not that's it's not not okay maybe it's
different oopsies what's you I might be
I have no idea roller coaster uh shaking
a a soda bottle and then like opening it
I think that's not that's really that's
bad but
cool do that inside or outside yeah
both you like
cleaning no I don't clean all right you
guys ready to
oh
crony Cron's here get in my party crony
hold up oh I have to do that crony get
oh yeah you got to invite crony there we
go should we place the L block or what's
this yellow arrow here
for uh it it'll start the
quest so I will start the quest
now all right now be very careful these
zombies will be a little stronger if you
feel like you can't win just don't try
and
W
here
yay
nice there's some fire going right now I
don't know how to turn that off why why
why I don't know that's really
horrifying I wish I could turn it off
hang on maybe we can break it oh no no
it's it's here's a there's a there's a
valve here H good thing I have smart
people with me I'm just an unab Bunga
caveman to be
honest a wrong weapon
oh he's just doing his job guys stop
yeah yeah I've
heard helping more
conru oh wow no problem this nice yay
big
exp feel free to you know look through
all the stuff and loot whatever you
want those look good F
trash see nothing in
here all right let's see what we got in
here oh this is a nice
room okay
upstairs B come down the stairs oh she
died from one hit she look good
though don't worry don't worry you'll be
fine see you're doing good good
job yeah use that
[Music]
doing great with that club oh we got to
climb up here oh I hate this one climb
up where this rope oh my God no it's I'm
Too Tall our biggest enemy yes honestly
yes freaking rope I can't there we go oh
hello jump up
the oh my Go zombie half off I did not
want to see her
pants I didn't need to see yours
I can't I'm out a stamina don't worry
don't push yourself I can handle
it I can handle it I'm just
dizzy I'm just dizzy do you happen to
have food or water uh I think so yeah
let me just really quickly heal myself
wait actually I have food I just need
water okay n chicken soup the yummies
all right we're almost done I think we
just need to do a little we're just
missing a couple a few
more all right not a lot of goodies in
there I think this one also gets turned
off somewhere some oh oh oh
here zom okay we can jump into this hole
nice all right let me kill this guy
really
quick wow zombies can climb roll now
we're looking for supplies ladies so
everybody has their own Supply cat they
have to find uhoh
I'm going to die I'm help I'm what's
going
on I went into the hall there's like a
bunch of them and okay okay okay and the
door is locked and I can't get out it's
over we're good we're good don't worry
let me just I'm bleeding
[Music]
no it's okay you got this you got this I
got you just cut him around it's okay
he's just got toite him just got to kite
[Music]
use the first items that gave
us so the area is clear it's okay we'll
do another Quest don't worry we'll do
another one died
[Music]
crony I guess it was
time for her to I get it that's very
silly that you said
that I found my my uh I found my items
my supplies everybody's is in a
different place so look for an orange
marker on your screen that has like a a
bag icon it's orange search for
that I haven't seen an orange marker yet
there it is it's far okay look we should
use another Band-Aid it could be
upstairs or up in the the attic there
are a couple different places it could
be but try and track it you guys are
dogs right you can track it oh mine's
downstairs here oh we found it nice I
don't need this right here by the orange
Mark nice Who would
know give it a sniff crazy how about you
CeCe did you find yours mine's
downstairs one sec okay
nothing oh no it's like middle it's not
downstairs what the I wonder if it's in
the
Attic gu no it's like in a vent oh yeah
there is a vent one oh my God don't
worry all the zombies are dead no I got
jump scared by the voice oh
God you're safe nothing can hurt you
hello hello I'm sorry I'll fallen
soldier it's all good it's all good did
the mission fail because of me or no no
no no no we're all okay it's just that I
don't think that you can get the rewards
sadly but we can do another one oh no no
no that's okay that's completely fine
crony what are you fighting with
kind me I'm fighting with a bone knife
oh
nice I wonder I wonder how that um I
wonder if that's a strong enough weapon
against these zombies um let me see
maybe I can make you a club uh that
might be better I can give you a level
five club that will be a bit stronger
for you um I don't know what you've been
putting points into whether it's been
strength or whatnot but this will
probably help you more than the knife um
the the the level five wooden Club we're
going to the club
this one right
here go so bless okay I found my Satchel
thingy then are already done the quest
then yes so we can go back to the trader
now and turn in the quest and maybe get
a new one and then crony can along did
you uh grab your backpack crony you got
everything yeah awesome well let's go
back then let's go back to uh the trader
if we can figure out how to leave the
house oh it's uh it's this way I think I
remember kind
of
um yeah yeah it's just this
way oh yeah it's supposed to be this way
but then the door got locked this way me
neither it's fine now it is night time
though so actually we can't uh turn in
the quests instead what I think we
should do is we should make a run to the
new
house and see if we can grab some
Provisions to take to the old house okay
oh oh oh oh have shotgun weekly you you
Ed oh yeah yeah yeah I need that yeah I
put it on the floor thank you all right
read oh I have some shotgun shells too
oh if you if you're not using them I'll
gladly take them off your hands I just
love collecting things I can make a yes
thank you you're the best oh I have one
more here we go another I can make a
double barrel shotgun this is big all
right maybe I can make some for you guys
too if I have enough stuff
so let me look it up double barrel
shotgun if we die then the mission will
fail so we got to live yes need to work
kind that's kind of that's kind of I
mean I get it but that is kind of diff
the difficult part I think have this
stuff let's make a run to the so I think
it'll be nice to go back to a house it
doesn't really matter which one I think
that we should go back to the old house
first though okay to collect materials
and then see if we can craft some stuff
at the new house so just follow me
follow my marker okay sounds good yeah
okie
dokie only we had
bicycles yeah soon enough you can get we
just need to do
quests after the raid we can speedrun a
bunch of quests if you want I think
actually shouldn't Ki be able to make
bicycles now I wonder I wonder if she's
that if she's that strong she has like I
think you only the thing is you only
need three vehicle magazines and I think
she had like 10 I think the problem was
often the not having a workstation for
everything yeah now we have a workbench
though so yeah workbench right right so
I think so we could all have bik bikes
we could be a biker gang yeah biker gang
that'd be cool there's something making
sounds maybe we can okay no worries just
keep running you're faster than them for
now zombie are we faster our stamina is
kind of low even at night I would say
yeah even at night they just get faster
but you're still faster than
them okay why are you starving cuz we
can kill
you no K the
quest oh
right thirsty always the right
option yeah we had to eat and drink we
got food at uh the new house let's
collect some materials here wonder if I
can make make guns for everyone maybe
Kiara can make some stuff
too yeah uh are we splitting up wait
wait where are you going I have no idea
I have to check the map okay if you
follow my marker it's it's to the left
uh there are a bunch of bars and it
shows some arrows that are pointing look
for the one that's pointing to myy and
just follow that
direction
okay follow Cecilia cilia probably knows
how to use the the thing yeah I'm just
sticking to the road so that we can have
that's
screaming oh no it's okay keep going
come with me scam in
un it's okay it's okay that's okay why
did it start attacking the car that's
weird it hates cars oh know I was always
standing in traffic I hate this it's
like oh cars
disgusting our cars kind of weird if you
think about it kind of weird because
it's like a house but outside of your
house and people look into it but people
act as if it's like their private space
but it's not really because I can look
into your car you know yeah
unless house yeah I think that's legal
in most count if we eat or drink
something then our stamina issues will
be solved yeah you can eat or drink do
you have food or what we have M you
water uh coffeee yeah
but's wait until we at coffee we can
drink that oh drink that yeah we have
mushrooms yummy can we eat that eat
mushrooms I also have some water and
some Golden Rod tea for you guys over
here and there's also going to be some
food in the house just when you approach
the house be careful it is very
fortified there are a lot of spes be
spikes do not run into the spikes yes
take the straight path into the house I
think at some point I think it was
yesterday started just breaking spikes
because she was so sick
done with
this no what do you mean just don't walk
into them yeah those spikes yeah I mean
we did a really good job we did yeah we
worked really hard for those spikes you
know how much wood is needed for them
yeah it's insane it's
impressive you're very careful not to
get hurt by them or when they're opening
the doors we're struggling a okay we're
crossing the
water this way what else did I need okay
I have a lot of ammo so I'm going to
drop them off here I don't want to die
in the water I think I had some shotgun
parts
somewhere
materials I'm going to make you guys
some better armor maybe I bet Kiara can
still make the better armor alog
together though
H yeah it might be nice to have now
unless it uses a lot of important
materials just so that we can like
survive until we meet them again and
then maybe tomorrow when we all like
hampered down in the base and starting
maybe she can make us some yeah did ium
big
order we jump I you as a rock to pass oh
gosh I'm ow don't hit me don't hit
me guys I'm not a zombie I'm an autot
it's different I'm alive my for iron
here Papa but you can be used as a a
Crossing block over the water yeah that
is true I can't float
okay I'm make where do we put the armor
parts um oh you have armor parts that's
huge yeah okay maybe yeah can make you a
nerd hat then I would hold on to that if
I were
you okay um and give it to how many
parts do you have by chance uh just two
okay um biu has four I wonder if she's
using them first close the door because
if you use those you can make armor kits
if you have sewing and duct tape as well
and you want to make those because you
can get stronger like pieces of armor
and clothing so if you can try and use
those armor parts with sewing and duct
tape and put them together you can make
armor kits try and make some of those if
you can okay I think
armorie what what is armored up is that
is should we use that or should we use
that or should we give that to um it
will basically make you able to make
better level armor but the thing is we
can probably like me or Kiara have been
reading a lot of those we can just make
you really strong armor instead okay I
have three I can give this to you I have
one armor part you have one armor part
okay that will help I think that will
help Kiara uh just definitely let her
know that you have an armor part and
she'll help you out Kell I'll put it
behind youp magazine what was that oh
it's a magazine a magazine and
mechanical part I'm going to give those
to Kiara actually cuz I think they'll be
in better hands with her machete PLS
I haven't really decided what I want to
go into I think I want I think I want to
go oaba I I found something it's called
Bing like bar balling like crying
balling your eyes no like like brawling
brawling braing not Bing nice oh don't
bring
the uh hey fuoka where are
you f fire with fire five based weapon
effects license o cool oh super are you
guys under are you guys in your little
room yeah it's a bunk bed okay I've got
some food for you oh thank you here I
take these and then have some of the
Golden Rod tea as well because this will
cure denter if you start having like you
know bowel problems by accident huh no
I'm sure you're fine don't worry about
it okay I'm sure you're fine okay let's
have the golden R team
yeah oh it looks like murky water but
it's that will be good for you it looks
like murky water it is not though should
I use it right now I don't do we have
this c um if you don't I mean it's still
probably it it still will cure thirst we
have some murky water that I really want
kind of we need to maybe I should learn
some cooking skills as well to boil some
water and
such let's
see I was reading vehicle Adventures I
can make bicycles y
y big okay please bicy make us bicycles
all right let me see if I can figure it
out
bicycle open I'm just going to put all
my stuff into the shared storage so that
people can take him yeah we should do
the because we don't really know what's
what honestly yeah that's a huge help
because for example if I want to make a
shotgun I need duct tape some people may
just have duct tape lying around you
know oh I have one duct tape I put it in
here oh yes let's freaking go crony
you're a legend thank
you put it where I can make a shotgun
now materials yeah in the materials box
it might be full but if it's full maybe
see if there's something that you like
in there I'm so I'll
just probably going to
use Stu put stuff people nice SW croner
this is also ammo do we have ammo
no put some of our weapons in the weapon
I'll take one of these if it's free this
one's pretty full material oh we have a
lot of feathers put the feathers FEA
pretty good part so I feel like it might
be a good idea for them to put it in the
shared container if they're not using it
like seeds for example oh seeds yeah
seeds need to be in the food
crate yeah it seems like some people uh
they have their like they have stuff in
their own boxes so maybe we can ask
later yeah good
idea I wish we had one where it's like
this is the garbage box cuz I have so
much stuff and I don't know what to do
with this you know what I'll put mine
into two yeah oh you know if you have no
idea where to put him just put it here
I'll organize it I love organizing yay
thank you okay I'll put it I'll put I'll
put it in here just put any random stuff
and I got you buddy alcohol I don't know
should take beer oh this oh take this oh
this ises this sound
bad I understand the need to organize I
agree with it okay let me
see which one's this one food food so we
can put our mushrooms in
here there's animal bat in this one too
there animal bat material and it or food
I put it in food cuz it's like animal
based
but yeah I don't really know like what
else you use it for but
yeah we also can head to the new house
as well and see what's going on there
there may be stuff that will help us out
over there too okay I recommend that we
do that since now it's about to be
morning yay yay the new house is right
next to the trader as well so we can
turn in our
Quest that one here's some murky
water multiple yeah I was going to bring
that to bi boo oh I have six murky water
to have her
boilet oh okay you can take mine too
then okay please oh wait I took I don't
want I don't
want will make it all nice and clear Sor
good thing I missed some be time of day
I'm predisposed to try and hit people oh
I'm I'm drunk in
game oh that's pretty silly like me two
hours ago yeah it's all blurry and
stuff okay wait I put my club in
the in the weapons uhoh you may need
that you may need it
we also we we have these but I don't
know if we need those we could put them
with that has handlebars material Cofe
material
maybe's got a lot of good stuff actually
I'm not going to take it though I'm just
looking at
it take it take it steal
Ste mechanical Parts is
material o I can make a land mine cool
that could be useful yeah I mean the the
whole like trap stuff sounds fun but I
guess it's not that useful if we want XP
so I'm not going to do it but it's
fun yeah for
fun okay this
better maybe I'm going to head over to
the new house whenever you guys want to
want to come over um feel free and I'll
have some stuff for you I think I'm
going to try and make armor for you guys
there yeah should we go together yeah if
you would like to come with hey
guys leave not to rush okay you can you
can drive for in front of us but it is
almost rain time so we will need to make
sure is the dawn of the 21st day
bcle yeah I'm going to figure out if I
can make a bicycle for you guys because
bib has handlebars but we need like a
chassis is what it's called a bicycle
chassis I'm going to see if we have that
at the new
place Oh I thought you could make it out
of like iron or something oh can you you
might be able to put cornmeal in the
ammo
section some food I'm going to go to the
new house so I can make armor for those
guys I'm fast right now we're hungry
though we also don't have stamina don't
go in the you have to you have to let it
go we got to go we got to go yeah sorry
sorry yeah I'm sorry I'll I'll be I'll
be right there
sorry you have to it will never be a
perfect system it's okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay thank you perfect
system okay I got it chassis it's okay
to be okayish system as long as it
okay what a Sil system is have to wait
to hit that
yeah I'm still I still believe you're
the only one that knows that that is a
thing I'm going to make them everyone I
mean we'll see once you get to the new
house you can check you can check the
boxes yeah I've already like sorted all
the boxes in that in that old house so
oh yeah you you'll get to live your
dream with a new one as well a sick yeah
the new house is full of good materials
that's why I'm running over there really
quick to grabb some stuff
and then we got to go back and make our
I don't know if we need to fortify the
house I will say that during one of the
earlier nights there was a zombie that
jumped and it could jump like 10 m so if
those zombies attack us they will get
through our def yeah so we will need to
fight is the thing that's fine we can
fight we can fight it's just cutting
down the numbers with spikes might be
very helpful yeah oh we might also maybe
at least uh we for and I maybe we should
go to the trader to give back the Quest
for yeah the tra next new house yeah
yeah yeah is that the red one so that
you if you die nothing bad happens
yeah yeah make sure you turn in that
Quest it's it is right next to the new
house though thankfully yeah yeah it's
sure it's pretty
close oh my bat's so
cool so the old house is just a
decoy yeah we use we use that as our
fortification so I I think I'm not sure
why but I think it's so that in case we
die and lose they don't destroy our all
our items and stuff it's not our main
base of operations it's to pull the
zombies over there you know we have two
houses basically yeah I I have a
question we're starving so we ate a can
of salmon but it didn't really do
anything we still starving really that's
kind of weird I feel like well if you go
to the trader he's selling a lot of food
and you'll get money for your for your
quest okay so you might be able to grab
some food also if you come to the new
house I think that there's actually a
ton of food at the new house just
kidding come to the new house please we
got bacon and
eggs bacon and eggs at the new house
it's right where I am if you look at
where I am do you think you can make
bolts at some point do you think that's
the I'm pretty sure that's possible it
would be weird if you could I make
shotgun shotgun ammo so thirsty now
thirsty and then we just drive around in
boats and run away from the zombies yeah
that's
awesome right I'm get you a
shotgun that would be nice all right
crafting shotgun
now a new house
yeah to the
tra oh there cloth nice oh 15 armor
parts yeah it looks like we we will we
should be able to make an armor kit for
you guys but I got to ask if it's okay
Y in here they we cooking three bacon
and
eggs B ba welcome so check out the food
in the food
crate uh feel free to look it's in the
cooked food and Medicine just take what
you need um okay I don't know if there's
much food in
here there should be enough if not
there's three bacon and eggs that are
cooking right now on the okay maybe time
can we try cooking eggs oh yeah there
isn't a lot of food there hold up yeah
click click on the um there dang we do
need to cook a little more huh I don't
have the skill oh I can make I can make
t meat let make the meat oh yeah you can
also just take the the bacon and eggs
that are on the the stove and eat those
okay that should help
you is there a bike chassis here by
chance than you willing to bacon and
eggs then yeah
making maybe I can make another shotgun
for
[Music]
someone we got I'm so slow my God no
worries uhoh uhoh
what what I just got a big pop up and
said I was dehydrated oh that's guys
don't forget always stay hydrated
hydration CH hydration check is
important okay I'm going to make another
shotgun to give to someone wait how come
nobody checked the cupboards here e my
oh did they not is there stuff inside
the cupboards yeah there's a book here
oh
nice wonder what it's
for uh it's for cooking I'll I'll put it
in the Box it's going to come in a half
at the bottom left this oh yeah maybe
one of our chefs could read it but our
chefs needs to cook a little more food
oh really can't believe it I would love
to do some supply stuff that would be
what would you like to do in this world
crony would you like to cook would you
like to what do you want to do for
you I I don't know if you guys have any
need for collecting materials but I
could probably do that I like that
where' the shotgun
go I don't actually yeah I I think I
think we always need materials right kie
isn't that like always need stuff to
make stuff so if you guys like going on
like little excursions and and it does
happen naturally when you do quests
where you will go to places and you can
just scavenge that right right uh it's
also farming which might be important
but I don't know I think Shi is farming
but I don't really understand how
farming Works Scavenging is really
helpful I am going to borrow these
Springs yeah if you can get a bunch of
material for example I'm going into
healing and I want to heal but like
everything I need I need uh like AO
cream for it and I need Aloe Vera and
there's no aloe vera in the world unless
I haven't seen it at least unless we
Farm it ourselves the new Trader though
the new trador has it yeah oh the trader
has it okay yeah I got to go see the new
Trader the new Traer yeah she's a
beautiful
girl give these to
Kiara with these he going
[Music]
into head on to the tra
tra where are they there the trees okay
is it is the where's the forge
cie right over here I'm just uh waiting
for a shotgun to be complete oh it's
done okay uh foko come here
please where are you guys we are going
towards the Traders oh you okay let's
both go to the trader together okay okay
we'll be at the end of the road here
okay let's go meet the trader I have a
little something for
you well heck yeah I'm going to repair
all the windows right now we're a little
bit SL Cron's Mr Fix It hey guys I have
a little
gift what here you go um this should
help you during the they should help you
wait and then here's I'll give you guys
let me give I don't know how much you
guys are going to need so let me for
now here's 65 ammo
thank probably you press R to reload
[Music]
it ooh I think I found I think I found
something that I want to do if you want
to if you want to join me with that I
need oh yeah I need five forged steel
five I need five duct tape okay yeah
find glue and cloth you guys I'm sure
that'll get you the duct tape you
need heck yeah clo you can make with the
cotton right is there anywhere we can do
like
Farming Farming is a bit difficult in
this game yeah I think farming is super
comp some I don't I don't really know
how that works also it takes really
long no gratification there it's like
here you put it in there now wait 20
years yeah it's not great right now
let's oh server lags pretty bad right
now hold
up I wonder if there is anyone has he
always
gry he's going to give you um a a gift
for completing
the so you can choose whichever one you
want I'm going to see maybe crafting
skill yeah they're just really good oh I
can do it now you get a little money too
stumbling into my shop so cornbread's
really good and yummy you can buy some
of that but also at the same time you
know fauna and bibu when they do want to
cook they they make a ton of a ton of
corn bread and such
so you may not want to spend too much of
your money on it but it's up to
you ooh lumber jack outfit if you find
glue let me know I can do all the side
jobs like if there's like nothing to do
like aside from you know looting places
or whatnot if there's anything else you
want me to
do I don't know if I got any magazines
anybody wants well which ones do you
have Sol and farming explosive magine
I'm going to go and loot houses and see
if I can find glue well you know Kiara
wants hamers so just put it in the books
box at the new house let's talk to him
again he doesn't have any job I don't
really know what other jobs there are to
be honest corny so it's kind of like
just do whatever got yeah yeah just just
just do what you want to do you guys
want to do one more quick Quest and
[Music]
then you want to come to two Quest two
Quest don't have anything do we have our
own person the second I got a buch we
use our skills or anything yet oh please
yeah allocate your skill points and
actually I would recommend putting them
into shotgun and strength okay
shot oh God the date has turned
red oh boy shotgun
strength strength shotgun there's still
food I'm going to
die oh gosh let me uh let me hit him up
let me ask really
quick food drink I don't know how many
points we have oh we don't have anymore
oh do we use them all up okay so so go
to Rally Point is that the quest you're
doing it's the orange
marker okay okay I think we can do one
more Quest and then we need to regroup
with the others and prepare okay all
right they're coming home they're
getting ready to come home our cooks are
on the way so
okay it's going to be a bloody day I do
want to mod the shotgun but I don't know
what mods I have for it I have to look
and see I'm sure I have
one oh actually we have a light I know
we have that going fast for a bit
just fixing stuff in the house cuz there
are a lot of damage stuff around here
okay nice nice extra 45 all right let's
go let's get moving and you can you guys
can try using that shotgun yeah let's
try using it Qui on the shot practice oh
really but what about my
bullets you'll get more bullets maybe
crony could learn minor skills do the
bunker Oni 2.0 oh oh mining yeah
you be a miner it's oh I like that some
holes oh I love being a hole digger oh
yeah only for the most sophisticated of
people you're a grinding
croner how should we get down from this
hill or you guys just very carefully
slowly walk down okay just yeah very
carefully you won't break your leg this
game the fall damage is like you have to
really be jumping pretty high up um but
if you can scale walls so easily in this
game that was a really bad experience oh
no yeah oh in
she it was a bad
experience we got stuck in a storm with
n being the N was a good part the storm
was the bad part of course
okay I'm let me know when you guys are
there and then I'll come back yep I'm
I'm there I'm waiting at the exclamation
point okie dokie I don't think I've done
a a clear quest to this house yet maybe
but I don't know nice I'll wait for you
guys
here out of breath here I we to eat it's
say you need to
eat
eat let eat the
sandwich oh is that a sham sandwich
yeah okay just get ready to drink some
Golden Rod tea afterward don't eat it I
ate it okay that's bad I think we drank
our tea too do we have more tea I we
have more tea okay we're going to drink
the tea okay I thought that was the one
that made us
sick all right I think we're ready to
take on the last oh wait ce's not here
oh okay I'm coming okay I'm right I'm
right here
oh owo plant there's an ow plant in the
house a part plant on
ow
oh it's a nice place the cover already
thinking about stealing it
huh why not a third base would be nice
but I think it should be more in the
burnt Forest Area or maybe the snowy
area all right we're snow area has
[Music]
a oh potato oh you the my gun you
should yeah just give just fire
away there's a food pile see what's in
there if there's any goodies oh
hello oh sorry oh I'm so sorry I thought
you were zombie I'll give you a
bandage oh my God someone shoot are you
kidding me
you have full health how what happened I
think I hit you in the head but here's
the thing you have to understand you
didn't appear on my screen until half
one frame it's okay it's okay okay one
blame the Ping it was the Ping it's okay
maybe I just jumped I usually I will
admit I at fault but that no no no no
don't worry don't worry it was probably
me I I might have just jumped into your
into your all right let's push forward
try and stay away from my friends when
I'm beating up
zombies it's okay with
my don't worry don't worry don't worry
you're good you're good I got you I got
you yeah beat her up beat her up
yeah he's
up no
problem eat the food we're hurting here
all right there's one in the washroom
here Somey liquid
people can take care of
that I'm going upstairs there's a bunch
of dudes
here that's let's go help
Kell she'll be okay I think it's just L
stuff afterwards so I don't think I
really need to use a shotgun the bat's
just the best weapon in the game
so he not done so it's fine wait wait
oh why why
you why is get get her get her crony oh
nice I oh I found
glue shotgun I can make more shotguns
for
friends what's in
there crate got some dog food strength
qu oh a batter up for me
see there's some there's some dog food
in here if you want dog food oh
dog dog
food is the strength mod this yeah just
hit it this will enhance my strength I
think that this will be
good I think this will be good for
me I'm just letting you guys know I'm
installing a strength mod on my hat
because I really think that it will
help you'll get be smart cool and strong
with each other did we do it we did it
someone wants an intelligence mod I'll
give it maybe maybe Kiara could use that
nothing there all right we did it guys
I'm sorry C we can do another Quest if
you want to get you some it's
it's nerd hats have been requested I
hear yes we just finished a quest we're
not too far from the new house but we
probably need to start working on
getting ready for the raid
anyway so we're going to go turn in a
quest and then yeah we have some hungry
folks here lots of I can now make them
on level four already but I will need
four armor crafting kits unless you
wanted on the lower level oh the nerd
hats yeah um they have they do have some
armor parts um I might actually if if
Lok wants to make a level one or so a
nerd hat I'll take it and I can give
them mine because they need exp more
than I do but we'll see we'll see how
many armor parts we have cuz I think I
think that there was a bunch in the
crate it's at the house but you might
need that for other
stuff parts we have here and there I
think biu had like four in her personal
chest at the old house so I was going to
ask her about those if she'd like to
make a
donation I I I got a couple too I just I
don't know if I can make a level four
nerd have maybe three is
fine
yeah yeah should be okay how do we make
the level one night
H I think you only need one yeah I mean
there's some extra stuff but the most
important thing is the armor crafting
kit um I'll make you actually you know
what I'll give you my level two I think
nerd
hat uh or wait wait wait wait wait
wait thank you yeah donate to the animal
shelter
get him their new armor and then I'll
try and craft I think I have enough
cloth to craft you guys some better
primitive armor it's like a higher level
I also have a ton of magazin oh yeah you
too no
problem I actually have a ton of
magazines to give Kiara
yeah like a whole bunch I need more duct
tape do I have any duct I have two duct
tape okay I that'll be enough I'll see
if he has any stuff I can use to make
duct tape if didn't we agree we're still
using the old uh base right today for
the attack yes okay hey Chad does this
increase the this doesn't increase
magazine for
shotgun glue glue we should ask for glue
right make duct tap glue yes we need
glue as much glue as possible it's not
shotgun I figured as much just get the
magazines food bundle
workbench oh wow another
workbench that's a big
reward oh they're giving you a workbench
yeah yeah it's a reward for a quest Lev
up level up
nice then we could have two next to each
other because again we can't use it at
the same time it seems right okay I
grabbed it nice and more
jobs even a dumbass like you
can you make a
bicycle
oh you you should be able to but it's
just it's a matter of we don't have the
parts is the thing yeah I would need the
parts but if you do enough quests you
get a
B
Quest okay okay let's
leave let's
go uh should we all go should we go to
the old house now or the new one
or maybe oh there's a zombie coming up
behind yeah okay okay let's go to the
old house and make you don't bu check
the spikes we don't have to make more
maybe we can like fix the ones that need
fixing yeah or should we stop by the
trader first since the Trader's nearby
one more okay okay okay okay and then we
can get some stuff there oh there some
air
drops you see air drops is that the
sound yeah you [\h__\h] off where is back to
where
is this where
is H
okay [\h__\h] man I treat you that good and
you don't even bucking
me our inventory is full again so we
should go do something about
it that's okay I now have an old level
two nerd hat that somebody can have that
might be and one new level four nerd hat
that I'll give
to how about how's crony doing crony uh
cron CC you guys probably need some exp
right um yeah yeah I can live without
too you know if
you I can even more crafting kits then I
can make more ner
okay okay I I'll see if I have some and
I I'll I'll I'll but right now I'm too
I'm a bit far away if you can put it
into a chest somewhere get a new house
uh I'll put the nerd hats that are like
free to take into the armor chest and
the new house yay thank you yeah I mean
if there are spares would love it but
otherwise you know actually it's okay
well there's still enough time I can
probably still make more I just need
more duct tape and stuff I wonder if
someone could get those supply drops
Gigi's kind of close I wonder if she's
going to get
them wow
oh it's fine we need to focus on getting
ready yeah we want to focus on getting
ready but we're not sure what getting
ready is so fortifying the base GA upgr
your armor I'll make you some armor I
said I was going to do it so let me I'm
going to make a bunch of armor with
cloth thank we have cloth I think if you
can give me some cloth that will help
me if we do have cloth oh we have a
fragments oh I see I wonder if you can
make a full cloth with the fragments you
can craft it I
[Music]
think I think cloth fragments are fine
I'll take them
okay this house is so cramped we need a
bigger one we need a number three thank
you oh perfect this is actually yeah
this will be great okay I can use that
okay we can make more so we'll make more
yeah okay and I'll see what I can do oh
oh oh oh uh Cory you should buy lucky
loot sorry guys you should buy lucky
looter let's put a magazine lucky looter
I I heard on the guide you really
shouldn't do that one for some reason
yeah why not it doesn't make much of a
difference but if you want it go for it
go for it don't let me no no no no no
okay okay I just it I was like this
would be good but if guide says no then
don't do it okay never mind all right
let's go
back feeling we're not going to survive
night don't say that I think we'll be
fine'll be okay nobody has to we will be
the one who
dies that's heroic but you know we won't
die just stay in the back a little
bit let's see armor staying in the back
naturally because we're scared but
a paper magazine let's put it old house
which is this follow me
okay I I
follow I follow you something something
baby what that song is that does it go
that way follow you into the deep sea
baby someone back me up someone
all
right come here come here f m into this
room
okay they're all kind of different
levels but it's better than what you
have right now so thank you than
you I'm in another nerd goggle level
four um you're going to wear the nerd
hat
though okay let's put this stuff on if
you're going to give if you're going to
wear the nerd hat though maybe give mask
to someone else's house okay yeah if you
can wait wait but I think hi is here so
we can can take no ah wait are you who's
we're in the in the new house we're in
front of you yeah uh yeah one of you
Cecilia crony fight for life for this
level four yep
okay you want it do you want it there a
take take the level two one of you can
take the level two one in the chest no
actually I think I think you'll benefit
more from having this here take it I'll
take the other one there's armor
I can I can probably sell like a one if
I duct tap
no huh I have the the fragment
here oh for clo this for duct tape this
actually
welcome thank you
K thank you
primitive Hood then yeah it's a level
five primitive Hood who wants the
Primitive Hood maybe give it to um I
think CeCe needed it and then oh no I I
have the I have the the I have the head
kit I made now this okay okay I'll hold
it may cron I'm going to make some more
level four do we have water she has
level two CR I'm making you some better
stuff let's get
water oh some stuff oh more plant
fiber oh we have a lot of plant fiber oh
okay nice that's that's big that's big
news yes we do that's
aw is time make gun okay okay okay no
more put away the rod and nerd hats
unless they give me ingredients yes you
got to order with
ingredients um okay crony come over here
I got some better armor for it's just
higher level armor yippe here you go uh
yippe and then yipp the the Hat I think
somebody else has the very strong face
mask who's not using the very strong
face mask you guys we have the that one
the strong the Primitive hun yeah if you
could give that to cron that would be
awesome yes here it is yipp yipp now
you're
fortified
yay look at how strong we are
hey grony you want a baseball bat
there's a baseball bat in here oh I have
a forge ahead if someone needs that yes
yes please here hold I'll give it to
you I see you I put it on my feet okay
in my on bottom there's a baseball bat
two
wonderful see what we look like nice
Bellows aim for the head by the way aim
for the aim for the head
sorry no problem it's so cramped in here
definitely also get a little bit of a
little bit more medical stuff so like
maybe everybody take like a couple
medical things like a med kit or
something which one am I making CH I'll
take one medkit for me and then maybe
everybody just you take some painkillers
or
something we should probably boil all
the murky water so I'll do that yes I
also have some as well oh we have
some put the ingredients can you oh my
god crony hold on a sec let me give you
do we have a magazine box in this space
as
well yeah the books yeah yeah books are
here right in front of the fire oh okay
thanks crony use the use use the hold on
use the painkillers
the cocky CH oh thank you where's the
you didn't have to it's okay I have
magazines for you a lot oh thank you
where's where is takak do you have any
more claw fragments by CH yeah they're
in the storage I have
10 oh really I'll give you
some the house is put on the ground here
oh thank you and this is for you 17
behind you K yo yo thank you yo so many
gifts you got to make the armor for us
you got to make the armor
okay want to spin the propeller on
that
here the armor part yeah oh yeah armor
parts will also be useful for a lot of
things okay we only have that one so and
maybe we have some more oh maybe you
should use this Kelly oh yeah KY I have
I have a since you do shotgun I have a
thing improves weapon handling while
moving or firing from the hip because
the weapon becomes more manageable in
close quarters oh really interesting let
me see me grab that from you have my
little my little hands on it let me see
what am I doing right now cuz I don't
use a gun thank you what is this here
and I think we can put the mods in the
magazine section too because um they're
like all learn
stuff manageable Close Quarters I don't
really know if you can fire a shotgun
from the HP but I think people might use
this cuz she uses a pistol see oh okay
okay I'll give it to her when I see oh
she's here okay we found some aloe vera
seeds I don't know that help at all but
um I would need like actual aloe vera
but it's so nice for the
future knows great all we do have a farm
here yeah we kind of noticed we took
down a super can scrap can I scrap all
the level one primitive outfits cuz it's
taking up space in the armor section I
think so I think you can scrap that yeah
yeah scrap
it it pretty sure we have these things H
probably not on a
string iron in my crafting book yesing
is always a good
idea unless it's something important and
it's not I have another workbench I'll
put the workbench down somewhere
else let's see
where
is so
blind don't punch yeah I am pretty blind
there it is what if I put the work bench
like
directly is bad
okay uh do you guys have murky water
yeah it's in the you put it all there
okay I'll boil all of them then that'll
be good there's a person standing there
Callie is a pipe pipe pipe pipe pipe
rifle good okay use that uh the only
good pipe weapon apparently is Machine
Gun okay but uh let's see I wonder if I
can make another Shotgun If I find
enough Springs uh does anybody have
Springs I need Seven Springs oh dang it
for my new shot uh machine gun oh dang
it you're not using the AK to find more
um I was using it it was so good but I
can already make something better now oh
why don't you give it to somebody else
maybe if you're going to make another
gun what's that there oh does somebody
else use machine guns now I wonder I
don't have any guns yeah have you
skilled into
anything no no you haven't skilled into
any weapons no cuz I can't
peek you can't peek oh yeah I'll do it
now I was waiting for well I we didn't
need it for the first round and I didn't
three available do it now okay I'll go
into I don't want to do anything
like maybe
I'll shotgun
Master I'll be right back should have
done this
one we know going to get here that's I
wonder have you put points into anything
have you picked I put them all into
Str G stage how game stage 40 okay I'll
go I'll do that B is at 45 so she's
pretty deep into
it The house's the
house I should started organizing this
chest too it's kind of getting messy the
blood moon starts at 22 by the way
ladies we have any points we could
use nobody wants robotics no the Nerds
oh I I kind of wanted to do robotics I
think fun are you sure you should there
are tons of robotic magazines cuz no one
wants to learn it
so going take this gr meat for me is
there something wrong about learning it
it's just it just seems complicated but
I'm sure it's not that
complicated all right I've taken the
food I want to
take what do we do with the freaking
Duke's Casino token you can buy things
in the
Traer yeah
oh robotic turrets are amazing yeah
people recommend making turrets
but nerd stuff but then we don't get XP
that's that's the only thing that I'm
worried about that if we go do you think
do you think they count as like I wonder
I wonder maybe chat knows if they count
as
exp mhm yep turrets give exp they
say okay I Ed all my make it yeah use
your skill points okay uh we should
probably head back to the house uh
pretty soon soon I would say
okay let me see maybe we should all get
everybody in the same voice chat let me
go see I think I'm
stuck I think we can make it down got up
here we can get down I'll send a
message right I'm going to go head
back okay I'll read the I'll read
the BLS then let's see what are
they house too okay well I don't where
did you say the robotics
was what was
that where was the robotics thingy uh
magazines in the books crate that's here
either that or in the old house there
are a ton of Robotics oh I see I see not
a ton but there's a good amount like
I'll go to the old house
yeah that was so s what was
that all right old house quick way point
okay yeah cuz it's almost
time yeah okay let's go back so exciting
yeah oh God there's still stuff to
organize it's okay it's okay next time
next time it's okay and once the raid is
over we'll still you know can go on for
like a tiny bit longer I think but I I
won't I have a different stream I'm
doing
but yeah if you want to stick around I
think that having the server open for
like a couple more hours probably
okay we just have to keep track of when
the raid is going to happen you
know the raid is happening
in very soon very very soon so yeah I'd
recommend we it's happening in at 10
p.m. in the game so in like 10 10
minutes yeah K so yes we lost track of
you
there you see me on the map yeah also
you always anytime you can't find me
look at the the left hand side and you
look for my name and there's an arrow
and it points to where I am same with
any party
member
yeah why is it so
Misty we're going to the Silent Hills
baby oh no no but then we going to have
to stop talking to each
other it's over
be kind of funny someone does a Sil Hill
in play and they just don't say anything
time they don't they don't elaborate
they don't explain they're just
quiet oh Storm's come yeah it gets super
foggy when it's close to the blood moon
and it starts
storming oh I see that makes the zombies
are coming they're coming the storm is
here uhoh the zombies are coming
oh no I want to go home we're going home
but the zombies want to come to our home
too I don't want okay heck yeah let's go
time to die time to die in
style swimming ladies yeah oh make
sure
uh make sure that there that you have a
bed roll at the old house or yes you can
well you'll SP your back you want to we
have a bed R and both okay I don't know
how it works I think you have to like
inter it'll be the most recent one I'm
not sure okay we'll interact with our
old one then or just spawn near your
backpack I think that's the best
way okay spawn near the backpack then
cilia
imig hey that's me have you decided on
your choice of
weapon um I want I think I'm going to go
stick stick stick b b stick no no club
club club oh really you just want to
focus on one I feel like I don't know if
anybody else does this but I chose like
one and one PE I think it's a good idea
do you like the assault rifle do you is
it fun it's fun for me it's like I don't
know much about guns and okay then I'll
go with that one okay uh I can give you
I can hand you down my old uh the one
that Callie gave me what I will say
though is that if if you are using clubs
and you want to level both your your
shotgun and Club strength at the same
time like they shotguns and clubs use
the same strength metric so if you
wanted to use shotgun might be a good
idea cuz you could minmax it a little
better but it's up to you okay I'll I'll
I I think I'll do one skill in into
because I don't want to go since the
weapon is already Meely then I want one
that is a little bit further so I'm
going to go with assault rifle for now
but I can do I can change my mind with
time I think one point is not going to I
would like to hand me down please sure
for now me make more spikes uh no I am
at the old house right in
the I'm making Spike TRS okay uh so the
hord is starting in 3 hours is should we
all go to the vc1 then yes I that'll be
a good idea to all get in the same VC
let's go over there to VC
one we see
Wonder hello hello brain slow do I have
any other modif too
seriously I can use my blocks in some
kind of fancy
way where are my spikes do you think
maybe we should move like most of the
materials to the new home then or do we
just have this place has a backup I
wonder I think it's nice to have a
backup but we can slowly try to move
things
over
[Music]
mhm okay so the back do
closed let's
see
thirsty can't the
front I'm going to show up last minute
again
uhoh the r is
oh let's put
magazine there some shotgun shells in
the magazine and ammo snipy
spot
okay and
then oh
nice this is
nice what is that does someone have a
higher quality shot the shotgun Maybe
oh are you using a pipe Shotgun by
chance uh yeah so I already gave uh the
double barrel shotgun that I had to F
but I wonder if I can make a shot a
shotgun double barrel quality one let me
let me look it up can I eat this right
there thank you okay too I have shotgun
parts I just need five forged iron duct
tape and spring I'll see if I can if I
can make something for you a thank you
just better quality I don't want to hurt
myself get H does anyone have wood oh
yeah the beaver has wood I don't know
where Beaver is though can can you can
you give me some I'll just make some
more spikes
of sure just a
moment okay here you go I'll give you
I'll also like help repair this spikes
yeah okay so you kept some wood because
you'll need that want to no worries I'll
go can't get I'm so hungry use this in
some claw I'll need to go back to the
old house staring going to the old
house and then I'll bring you your your
rifle nice than cute okay okay I'm going
to reput the spikes outside be careful
when coming in and out of the
[Music]
house
okay was there any fortification added
again or is it same as last time is last
time I don't think I think it's going to
be fine I don't know if I can go in time
oh gosh uh run run bicycle
bicycle a
sky it's so nice guys have two minutes
tops ow I think I'm going to die
actually you know what I can do I think
I can make you a pipe shotgun that's
higher quality it it won't be double
barrel but it'll be a higher quality
pipe shotgun oh thank you I just have a
level one is the thing so okay I can get
I can wish I scrap my level three dang
it hold on a second oh no no you don't
you don't have to like straighten
yourself cuz I already have the club
that you gave me oh yeah it is a pretty
it is a good club um okay let's see pipe
I just need glue might not work for why
not six glue really this is pretty
close does anybody have a ton of glue
let me see glue
are you in the old house or new house uh
either one I'm scared oh I think there's
some yeah in new in the new house yeah
but depends on where you are it might
take you a while any at the new house
other guns maybe other guns better I I
just left a while ago on the don't go
too far what about in the but wait are
you making it for for who uh what about
that
guy maybe we should we can check the the
boxes here there's a bunch
of maybe if bi has glue I'll just pay
her back for it later oh yeah bi's got
five glue never mind all right bio I owe
you five glue we might be overpreparing
again we might be fine I mean
overpreparing is better than under
preparing
right
pipes only three pipes I wonder if we
have more
pipes pipes in the new house there's
definitely some pipes
I have some you have time oh
no let's see need pipes you sending her
she's going to die what are pipes what
do you mean what are pipes
[Laughter]
G you know why is she so
confused pipes okay
okay surely somebody has some vies
somewhere hello
um I need them for a pipe shotgun I'm
making for crony actually I'm stealing
them from viu sorry viu I owe you six
pipes go you don't owe me anything just
take it fine are you sure G get to the
base hurry I'm trying but I went the
wrong way try
Foster the wrong way use your bike go
through the river you don't have to go
through the path go through the river
I'm trying I'm try harder don't shoot me
when i c
please try really hard not to I might
enter with the zombies oh oh oh then we
might have to I don't shoot me don't
shoot me I'm almost
there food we have 60 bullets let's make
them count go down okay yeah you guys
will be fine I'm going to show you I
made a little p that you guys can use if
you want I'm going to with an Italian
cilia and ammo oh my God this shooting
platform is so good thank you yeah
you're
welcome you're
welcome I made made it Y how going to
shoot you no shoot her shoot her no it's
not too
late it's dangerous place is dangerous
does anybody else have any pipes any
amount of pipes at all
okay it's okay I can make you a level
three I can make you a level three
shotgun and give you some bullets the
zombies are here I recommend the club
they'll be here in 20 seconds oh okay so
beautiful ites want to S it's going to
be fun and I'll give you 65 ammo as well
to help you out crony all right oh thank
you where are you I am outside oh I see
waiting for death I see everybody's
facing that way the other way I see you
okay here you go here is your gun and
here is your ammo oh my God you didn't
have to what the heck that's a lot oh my
God use them well but remember it only
it only shoots one at a time okay yeah
yeah so just be ready for that I'll make
them
count oh boy here we go oh God here we
go uhoh good luck everyone oh gosh
we got this it's easy
easy easy
game kinky can you put one more block
here for me wait a minute okay another
block I I can't jump so high
yet party they're
coming shotguns are not the best to have
at this V let me make it for you
Qui thank you oh God there's really a
lot of them oh yeah thank you oh God oh
my God no's on the shield right I'm
going to throw
Molotov okay what be
careful oh old they spit all the vomit
now oh they spitting
ew pretty
far okay seems like no one's attacking
the house from the other side it's only
the I want the other side okay okay nice
[Applause]
okay all right all right this might be
pretty by next time I forgot to put my
bed roll in here I'm oh my God it's
vomiting like
crazy scared
laggy too oh that vomit is
like vomit so
far are you
okay I need to get better I almost sh
you ow don't hurt
me
uhoh uhoh they're going to break for a
[\h__\h]
soon inside in the food chest and also
food anyone needs a break they're going
to break for the fight soon over here
are they okay
wait wait wa wait can can somebody build
more spikes I I don't have material for
it I'll build more spes I have some
spikes okay you're doing you're
doing on the left side of the house okay
okay okay I'm building right
now us I don't know where I'm looking
I'll cut this tree down too while we're
at it for more
wood but what about the natural uh uh
you know Hill ow owow ow ow zomes on the
hill on the hill
uhoh on the hill sh from the brid
zombies on the hill hill they they're
coming from the front of the house now
again from the Hill from the hill I'm
going up the stairs oh yeah they are
coming from the
hill see see right click to activate it
and then throw it with left
[Music]
click oh good we cring Dodge Dodge
backward okay
okay I thought the bomb would kid
you oh there was a bomb I didn't even
know
that yeah but it was very
very a all the birds are on there the
bird those dud are strong okay birds are
not that strong it's
okay yeah the spikes down okay I'm
putting spikes on the front I don't
right now it's kind of calm over
here watch out for the dog there are
dog I
think taking him down there's a big one
okay dog is dead it's no it's not a big
dog oh dear the dog hurts I think on
this side am we helping so just keep on
shooting am I
[Music]
helping someone's naked out there can't
reach it can't reach it's me I
think my arm is
spr all right let's do this I'm going to
try putting down more spikes oh
God I'm C more spikes oh I killed the
bird
my he's in he's in is that a person oh
did they get in okay maybe we can filter
them in in a certain way like choke them
through let's try to re forticate when
there's
time okay let me know where the chill
time right now down time healing and
food inside in the food
chest time so oh they're coming they're
coming from the left side left side
healing oh I'm going to throw a Molotov
so don't go in the field on the left
side yet okay should have brought my
moloto this is definitely different from
the first nights yeah yeah yeah this get
a little harder oh nice
fire oh God so many of them are broken
[Applause]
I'm going to throw pipe bombs also on
the left side so don't don't go out oh
watch out watch out watch out watch
out make it go boom I saw right in front
of me there's a lot going on on the left
side the left yeah there is a
lot oh nice make him go boom yeah make
him go
Bo
I okay don't worry don't worry we'll be
fine okay they're starting to come a
little bit from the left be a
bit okay it's a lot on the left
back don't mind me
I'm oh my God he's having a contion over
there down
down reloading reloading get him get him
get him right I want to set on fire
again
ni wait look look I hope he doesn't set
the spikes on fire by himself burning oh
nice get him not I think we got him
uhoh anybody over here down below much
better
shotgun there he is there he is where
are the repair kits do we have any here
side I'm pretty
sure they're coming from the Southwest
Southwest get them there's the big one
the
big throw it yeah I'm fixing
I'm I'm helping get him get him get him
yeah nice job
team
yeah oh no don't break it is Faun out
there using her Fists
yes he always does dang it I'm jealous
has no fear I'm jealous yeah I'm getting
I'm getting bonuses oh my gosh I super
jealous of funer right now I'm going to
go out and
fight she's so brave I'm brave too they
are they are I'm too scared to go out
there but I'm out of ammo soon so I'll
probably go out and die oh watch
out not to shoot okay no watch out
behind you there's a big
guy yeah that's what I thought
officer oh oh
oh in the for I don't know if we hit him
there are a lot of dudes here GRE stuff
so
weird need to be I don't know maybe I
should go outside and it's so laggy
I it's pretty
laggy I tried to hit them like face
through me oh my God
[Music]
reloading oh wow terrible swings from
me so we go
backwards
oh back
off get
trying oh that was really strong
down the orange ey on are very strong I
need to get out of here we
could I'm going to start throwing pipe
bombs watch out people on the
field I'm out of
Amry I think we're almost out of ammo
too I'm
scared who's who's outside right now
besides FAA I'm about to go back I'm
in I'm coming back
[Music]
Miss so that I can go back out and fight
again damage to me I don't know what
it's almost over no we can handle it we
can handle
[Music]
it too
bad yeah I'll make some more
spikes go back go back go
back it's the big
one there's a there's a lot Southwest
Southwest uh-oh won't let you
it's it's a zombie
is yeah hit him with the
fire
okay
stamina stamina
nice oh no I'm going to go leave leave
they are
camping nice oh love love dying oh
joyous day to die yeah Seven Days to Die
Seven Days to
Die crazy exping head
emoji shocked face oh boy oh
they
nice do
it fing we've reached the house the door
open just two I got
you I got you I got you so close
not there's one
more just one it's fine it's fine get
off my boy are they is it
D until
three I F I fought four a.m.
it seems quiet now it's they're
preparing for the next wave very quiet
recoup everybody eat some food recoup
loot get did I die last second oh it's
over for real oh man why did I last
second oh it's over it's quiet too quiet
it's too quiet I don't think it's over
ladies cuz usually there's like a happy
song or
something I thought we were leaving loot
Until the End ladies how many bullets do
we have left if we don't have9
really is it over gone there's no way
it's
over I don't know it feels over I don't
think so feels over but the but the the
the the the the the the the sky is still
red and the Happy song isn't playing
what
Happ Happy
song Can't Touch This okay you got it I
got
it okay I'm going to put stuff in the in
the storage
well too quiet wonderful we've done
we've done it once again but I think
next time maybe one more row of spikes
because they do seem to be breaking
through now yeah just one small row yeah
I worry if we're going to I I wonder if
we're going to have more like flying
type enemies as well if that's a
thing C there was only a few bir yeah
more ammo also there's spikes that you
can build now
currently it's not over not all over
it's not that's
that's me yeah did I scare you guys a
little bit it's just me oh you're such a
troll silly I get a little silly
sometimes she
getting I think it's not over yeah I
heard a weird noise it's
over there was a
lightning yeah it's over yeah apparently
you can you can uh get fredom all before
4:00 a.m. we were just back we
just okay free waves that makes sense
thank Oh yay we did it we did
[Music]
it it felt more intense than the first
time yeah it the first time was
[Music]
an we just got so much
stronger nice nice stronger together
everyone we didn't die help baby good
job you did you did you did did you guys
are doing great how do I fix the spikes
oh god oh go not with our body not with
our
body going to die I'm stuck on a spikes
oh
no can we heal now we're going to die
let's maybe maybe fix
what oh let's heal let's heal M let's
heal this kind of a weird
noise mhm I hope it's over cuz I already
left and went far away oh God yeah yeah
it's over it's over yeah it should be
done I think speaking of uh how long
maybe be online today for hours total
again or um I would I would be very
happy if if we could if people could not
play past uh 45 minutes from now if
that's okay
okay okay of course we'll play again
tomorrow of
course you know just to make sure that
everybody's got enough time to level up
and such and do a bunch of quests
together and such yeah yeah there's
shotgun ammo and uh 762 ammo in the old
house so take that before you leave the
old house is it in the ammo box
we need to end here for today but if
anybody wants our our our what's it
equipment oh cuz we have the good n
right oh yeah you can borrow to someone
else I guess where I'll drop it for now
okay
thanks ah I I was going to drop the
other ammo in the new house let's check
the current stage the game
stage uh fa is the one that's furthest
in game stage
50 what did I do how did I get of this
what's a game stage no tting so
good punching things punching I have not
been leveling very much I wonder if I
have the EXP debuff or something maybe
I'm just not doing enough quests I got
to do more quests huh if you want to gra
the N goggles again oh yeah I'll bring
it into the new house okay
okay I hope it gave you some levels
yeah nice our bun everybody looks so
nerdy
look bunch of nerds bunch of
[Music]
nerds should we put our levels into
strength again what weapon are you
enjoying using the shotgun or what are
you using shotgun strength is probably
best for that okay strength for shotguns
and clubs and bats I want to take some
of these materials like iron stuff from
the old house house to the new house
since we have a forge over there good
[Music]
idea good ide we'll see you everybody
byee see you later thank you byee bye
bye we also head out for now I have a
different stream I'm doing um but I will
see you guys tomorrow
by don't overdo it cie okay byebye all
righty I'll see you guys later take care
bye bye take care see you tomorrow
peace bye okay so that's it for 7 days
to die today but I will be playing again
tomorrow of course with everybody and uh
it's cuz I wanted to play something else
as well today uh which is why we're
playing Dark Souls so I'm going to go
send it you guys over there if you'd
like but if you'd like to keep watching
7 Days to Die there are still some other
people that are streaming right now so
go check them out but that being said
I'm your myy and I'll catch you guys in
the next one thanks for hanging out very
excited to level up a little bit more in
this game I feel like I need to level up
a little bit more I don't want to I
don't want to be super lowlevel so I'm
going to try and do a bunch of quests
tomorrow because you know we've got a
bit of time until the next raid we are
going to have to figure out how to
better fortify the base though cuz we
did have a small breach and I get the
feeling that it's going to get a little
wackier so look forward to it you guys
hope you're having fun I'm having a
great time I will catch you guys later
see you
bye-bye for