[Music]
n
la
[Music]
a
la
[Music]
ah
uh uh Kik k
KY
it's so weird
to uh not be
moving hello do you hear me
finey
wait where am I which one am I this one
k I'm in my swimsuit let's
go sorry um I wrote this in the pre-
chat um
but um when I was installing the Holo
app it needed because I'm using ena's
laptop but I'm like on
a out okay I'm on a separate
profile um is it too quiet now cuz I
don't know
man H I was I'm on a separate profile so
I need her password I guess for some
things so I was trying to install it and
it asked me for her password but she was
still sleeping so I went up I was like
N I need your password and then she came
down and she typed in the password and
then I think she went back to sleep but
then I restarted the PC because I had
some troubles with the hardware AKA
mostly the go
XLR being a [\h__\h] it's good to know it's
not just with me I mean it is with me
but I think it's good to know that it's
not just uh my own old goxlr
but yeah I restarted the PC and even
though I had the H app open before that
and I was literally like changing
outfits I remember that I remember that
it's not a fake memory I had it open I
had it installed and I had it open I
restart the PC and it's
gone it's just
gone
yeah did it kill you no cuz like the the
G that Ena is using
at her uh streaming setup cuz she has
two this one is the travel one she
doesn't seem to have issues in her
setup so maybe it is just me but anyway
yeah so I installed it but it's gone and
I looked for it in the installed
programs it was not there I looked at it
on the desktop and everywhere nope it's
never nowhere to be found so weird so I
would need her password again but I
don't want to annoy her again so we're
just going to wait eventually maybe she
will come down and I'll be like you know
actually this stuff happened um do you
want to like we can we can install it
again Midstream and get some life to D
going
uh yeah the app went out for the milk
and never came back
yo yeah but I'm still uh at ena's Place
indeed indeed I
am um some things went wrong and I'm
still here uh and I will go to Japan
soon as
well I I will be in Japan very
soon so things are very very uh
stressful but uh yeah for now I'm here
and I I made the stream reservation as
you as you can probably
tell uh this is a usual Wawa time this
is Peak WWA
hours
this is normal W hours um because I
thought I would be home right now so for
Dave the diver as you know as we tried
to play it before and then I couldn't
because I didn't make a proper
reservation and we had to cancel it so
as you know I need permissions and
beforehand I need to apply for it
beforehand so I did um and usually when
you apply for it beforehand you should
not really cancel it
you you can but it's frowned
upon so a good thing that uh even though
this is prime Wawa time it's not so bad
over here like time wise I actually woke
up earlier than I wanted to even
[Music]
M you know the best thing that there's a
water cooker right behind
me a water
cooker from Japan
[Music]
so I can
refill
endless endless tea refills Ena has like
a Japanese water cooker that has like
constantly cooked water inside a boiler
sorry sorry it do be cooking though it
do be
cooking Kettle it's not a kettle though
it's not like a typical Kettle it's like
a it looks like a rice cooker and it
just has endless cooked water in
[Music]
there water cooker excuse me that's how
we say it in German
okay and when it when it finishes
cooking the
water um then it does a really long be
melodine
like but it's not that one it's not that
Melody I forgot what it
was it's so long it's so
[Music]
long it's something like
that uh yeah maybe it's some whatever
song it is maybe it's some classic music
um person
like reincarnated and the soul is stuck
in the water boiler Kettle
[Music]
whatever so I'm still here guys um and
I'm I'm so sorry um I want to say right
away we're probably not going to play
Yakuza on the
weekend I might still stream I might I I
will probably be able to stream
something but it will have to be a
shorter stream and I don't want to do a
short Yakuza stream CU I feel like I'll
get to nothing I'll feel I will feel so
unaccomplished you
know um I'll do something short Pro
probably a member stream cuz we didn't
have one yet this week did
we probably going to do a member
stream um I'll probably need to
like throw up my
emotions anyway
so
uh
yeah but um I'll keep you
[Music]
updated you seem quite stressed I
am I am a lot of things are not going
the way they should be going a lot of
[Music]
things there was a high possibility and
I'm not actually um I'll say there still
is I'll say there still is a high
possibility that I'm not even going to
uh make a stop in
[Music]
Austria I
mean I think I'll still get to go to
Austria but there there was um yeah a
big
chance that I'll just have to go
directly to
Japan but like I I can't I can't I want
to see my cats and I needed to do some
things at home and I wanted to have some
normal streams you
know cuz I was going to be at home for a
few days but no it's okay it's okay um
FaceTime the cats I did I did very very
cute
cats very cute I'll I'll I currently it
looks like I will be getting home though
eventually so yeah I'm looking forward
to that uh even though it's going to be
kind of a crazy
[Music]
schedule now my cats my cats don't react
to I'm so sad they they hear even with
speakers they hear my voice but they
don't react to it like they don't
acknowledge my voice through the phone
speakers it's like they're not hearing
anything it's so weird even when I make
the typical sounds
[Music]
like which should be so
recognizable
[Music]
yeah I'm so sad dogs can oh man my dogs
hear my voice and he just barks cuz he's
confused okay maybe it's better if they
don't hear
me um RBF and BFF have been taking care
of my cattos and they're very very
delighted um by my cats so I think that
makes up for me being gone for longer
than expected and
yeah I think that makes up for it they
are so sweet they're enjoying my
cats they're having a good time with my
cats and they're eating my hellofresh
orders which I think is a good
compensation them having my hellofresh
orders
yeah well well that's probably enough
chitchat for the
beginning um did you read my Tweet guys
that I just tweeted did it even go out
let me double check cuz probably it
didn't let me double oh no okay it's
there it's there for once okay have you
noticed like over the past days even
I've had some incidents again where I
tweeted something twice and I
immediately deleted it but you guys
still kind of get notific a and still
notice it so you may have
seen what's the surprise the surpris is
the waas no I should I want to show them
though honestly the one with the weapon
is uh I would say still kind of
fitting p waha no that's not the
surprise there's a chance that we'll fix
it over the course of the stream and I
can basically stream long as long as uh
I don't overlap with ena's stream cuz
she needs one cable of this setup that
she made me on the kitchen table she
needs um one HDMI cable I think so
[Music]
yeah yum
yum all right guys you're in the kitchen
yes I'm in I'm in the everything I'm in
and I'm in three rooms at once
[Music]
okay Ena home has been very comfortable
I must say very
comfortable no plans today what the plan
is
streaming I do a stream and then Eno
does a
stream not in the laundry that happened
again by the way it happened
again it happened again I again I went
um to the laundry room two more
times
two more times so in a total I went to
the laundry room three
times but now now I got to figure it out
today in the morning when waking up uh
Ena I went to the right
room are you okay no
no wake up washing machine it's time to
wash my
[Music]
clothes are you sure you haven't figured
out yeah yeah I I'm sure now pretty
confident pretty
[Music]
confident uh wake up washing machine
wake up
dryer and the thing is even when I look
into the washing machine room for a
moment it's like pitch black dark so I
don't even realize it immediately I like
open the door I look into the room and
I'm like squinting and trying to
understand what I'm seeing and I'm like
like it's dark but I feel like I'm not
seeing what I should be
[Music]
seeing doesn't the noise no there's no
noise cuz it's not on there's no noise
you know of the washing
machine hello darkness my old
friend is Ena
sleeping in this
tent okay so um finally Dave the diver I
um I only saw like some stuff on what
was it like was it a Nintendo Direct or
so where I saw footage or was it the
game awards maybe
both um so I saw it's like a pixel game
where it's kind of cute and you make
sushi and you fish am I am I right am I
[Music]
right and then I I bought it on the
switch and I didn't realize we only had
perms for the steam version so we had to
wait a little bit for the switch PRS but
here they are
and let's
go
[Music]
oh okay
yeah let's
go I'm and so
excited they should be switched sound
but I think it's really
quiet yeah first time playing
so f f f first time oh wait let me mute
this
though
H
what what
what
huh oh so interesting
[Music]
oh oh oh wow that's how you start the
game oh
oh
what's going on is this
really what who cleared all of
this I told the mother there must be
something wrong with
this they can't be what can I see like
the play
time just what what let me let me let me
check
something uh where do you see the play
time again in my profile
right
oh let's
see can I show
this no that's my friend code oh play it
for 30 hours or more do you hear the
sound by the way you should be hearing
something there you hear it
right oh must have been Musta you don't
hear it of course you hear
it I hear
it
ah I what about
now Monitor and output what about
now
no okay well so yeah I wish you could
see my Expressions
guys H what should I show
you I am in I'm in chapter seven BL okay
I I actually can't turn it up but I'll
I'll put a gain on
it
is this louder is this
better oh wait wait I think I can oh did
that did that get a bit
[Music]
louder is this a surprise
yes yes how about now I made it even
louder I think I
did first time
playing is it not changing uh can you
can you guys just like deal with it
though cuz I'm kind of confused here why
it's not
changing I know I know this should this
should be
louder this is
[Music]
louder it should be quiet though like
generally this bgm is generally kind of
quiet okay so yeah my first time
playing
um yeah I have um uh I I don't know
anything about
[Music]
this about one more thing that I got
wrong
monitor off okay there you go yeah so um
I just started like this on max
level I have no
idea no so remember how after um
um
after death
account after my break I actually
immediately scheduled Dave the diver cuz
I kind of wanted to immediately surprise
you boosted the account I wanted to
immediately surprise you and be like
haha my first time playing Dave the
diver and then be like wow actually well
actually I played this during my
break I played this doing my break this
is one of the things I did during my
break I I played Dave the diver for
hours for hours and this is the game
that I even played in the spa that I had
the staff come up for to connect the
switch the HDMI cable to the uh to the
TV that is built into the
wall yeah I I played it for a long time
and I played it very furly uh
thoroughly H how did you like chapter 5
I don't remember I haven't played uh in
a while now because I was just waiting I
thought chapter 7 I think is like very
close to the end so I was like I should
stop now so that I can at least play the
end with you guys and surprise you with
it and that's also why I didn't want to
get a second uh game copy of this on
Steam because I had it on the switch yes
but also because I had so much game
progress on the
switch but it is it has been a while
since I I played it this is kind of um
weird right now especially with this
setup um but yeah let me show you like
let me show you around a little bit I
guess uh let me let's go to the farm
it's just evening so we're about to go
and make some
[\h__\h] and yeah I'm not going to lose
those hours
no yeah I just like I was kind of like
bored in my break and I was like I can't
be playing power world all the time
so wow oh there why is it all
dead oh no okay I don't think I actually
planted anything here though um I was
kind of bored and I didn't want to play
Power uh oh there's a big reflection of
the Sun in my screen oh
no kind not really the Sun but like the
light farming yeah there's
that's one thing about this game that
kind of bothered me like I had a lot of
fun with it especially in the
beginning damn the
reflections okay now it's
better and then they added so many more
things first they had a farm and I'm
like oh ew I don't want a
farm this was fine before and then they
then they add the fish tank and then
they add the second branch and I'm like
guys stop this is enough
already but I I've got I've gotten used
to the farming the cool thing is the
rice is more or less automatically you
just have to pick it up um but the other
things like uh there's some veggies that
you can plant in case you guys are not
as familiar with the game as I
am uh I guess I have to kind of like you
know help you guys out so basically you
can make some like later on you get to
make some vegetable sushi and other
vegetable stuff like um fish with
vegetable meals and so you besides the
rice you later get to grow these
vegetables and so there's like these
kind of things but I already have like a
lot of everything so I'm not growing
anything right now cuz it's annoying to
check back every single
day it's annoying so I don't want to
oopsie I went to the boat no I didn't
want to go to the
boat I wanted to go to
um wanted to go to the other thing and
and then and then when you're in the
late game you find this like underground
underwater world
um you would have liked to see it from
well excuse me I could have also just
not showed you the game at all and just
finish it off stream but I thought it
would be a
funny BM
Boozle uh if I showed you the end game
and this way I can put a a finished game
on my finished game list without having
spent 10 streams on
it getting my ratio up let's go I just
want to show you what I was up to you
know this is me just sharing my life
with you okay this is what I've been
doing oh look the fish farm they've been
making fishies so you get to like after
a while you get to get have a a fish
farm where you have to like you have to
buy you have to spend money to open up
all these
Waters and then when you fish fish
sometimes they drop eggs and then they
grow in here and then if you have two of
the same kind eventually they'll
also um make
babies and then you can send them you
can either sell them or you can sell
send them directly to your branch or to
your main
restaurant but this is also kind of like
a feature that I feel like
it's too much too much to take care
of too
much I know this game thanks to P but I
never see this end the ending so this is
perfect ah really I actually checked uh
Kyla's archive cuz I was just curious if
she finished it and I saw she also
didn't Kyla is not a game finisher h h
she only did three streams three like 5
Hour streams or so so she's like way
behind
me um but anyway artificial inflation of
the completed games list what do you
mean artificial look I have a narell
this is 540 m is like really freaking
low and in that area it's like icy so
this is really really late game we get
to go to the icy area even though this
is supposed to be tropical and tropical
fish like the whole thing about this is
like you make sushi with tropical fish
cuz like okay okay okay let me tell you
if you didn't if you don't know the game
and everything um let me tell you so
Dave is a diver and he's just like
diving for fun and he's in this tropical
area and
um he's in this tropical area and then
you know there's a restaurant there and
um I think uh it it breaks down because
of uh earthquake I think in the
beginning it's so long ago I don't even
remember and and um they build it back
up and then they kind of ask Dave to
help them get some fish cuz he Dives and
he's like uh okay I guess so he Dives
and then they ask him actually we we
need you to work for us in the in the
serving service area too because we
don't have enough St staff and he's like
uh I didn't sign up for this but okay I
guess so he does
both Dave yeah Dave the diver he Dives
but he also drives dve no no you say
like oh my God he Dives but the thing is
he doesn't only dive okay he also like
fights um people
sometimes uh but yeah wait
Branch this is so confusing to me Branch
AKA my main restaurant
right I'm too confused why can I only go
from the
boat yeah this is my Branch wait it's
been too long
this is my second Branch why is there a
thing on on
him oh a manager huh you think I can
handle it oh cuz
I promoted
him I guess I
did ah he only has that sign cuz he's
the manager okay I thought it was like I
have to talk to him oh
well okay so I have to go to the boat in
order to go no wait it's just sushi I'm
so stupid sorry it's been a while
it's been a while uh so but it's okay I
still have to kind of um did you have
save any Clips I don't think I
did I don't think I
did um but anyway I wanted to say so
then he starts working for them and yeah
so basically he's like in this tropical
area and then and then they're like you
know what we're not going to make normal
Sushi we're going to make tropical fish
sushi cuz no one else does it so so you
see all these beautiful beautiful fish
in the game and that's like funny to me
because some of the fish that I've been
catching and making sushi out of our
fish dad I saw in the
moldes
[Music]
snorkeling yeah it's so funny to
me game might be oh now it's too loud oh
now I thought so mm I thought
so I am not
surprised
okay how about
[Music]
now yeah so okay gosh I really don't
remember how to play this game but okay
here's a here's like crazy fish these
are like boss this you can see on the
left side it says rank level rank
99 um these ones are like boss monsters
that are like totally oversized crazy
monsters like this for example a truck
hermit uh a goblin
shark yeah but with these parts after
you kill the boss um monsters so to say
you get like one or two parts of their
meat of like a special part of their
meat and then you make a special dish
which sells way better than the other
dishes yeah yeah so this s but you know
these are the other things so did you
see here like now I'm like in the
Antarctica even though we started out of
like warm water tropical fish but now
it's
Antarctica it's kind of crazy I I love
getting as you can see I have a lot of
tuna because I noticed that the tuna
dishes they sell real hiccups really
well yeah oh look oh egg egg great a egg
so good and there's like a lot of basic
fish that I don't want to catch anymore
cuz they're too basic cuz the dishes the
dishes don't sell so well and it's
boring and also yeah you get to collect
um these kind of spices under water too
but U they're kind of rare uh so some
are more rare than us but you can send
people you can dispatch
people
M so let me show you my staff my staff
they're level 8 9 7 s maky maky i i
leveled her pretty pretty high uh this
should be like a pretty good level to
have them on
honestly yeah and uh here's St some
dishes that you can make and these are
dishes that I didn't research yet so I
can't make them yet um but the thing is
you you can't just learn a I have like
flame Artisan flames you know and I
don't it's hard to get you know so I
have to Choose Wisely I can't learn all
of these and and recently I just started
like learning the ones that I need for
the events cuz the events there's like
events every couple days there's an
event for example there was a tuna event
where if you make only tuna dishes but
people will come for the tuna dishes and
they'll pay more um if you serve them
tuna dishes so you want a lot of tuna
dishes and as you can see on the top
right we have an event with shrimp
coming up in two days so now I would
research ideally I would research things
that have uh shrimps in it but even in
the worst case when I can't learn these
they's still the
normal the
normal uh yeah the normal dishes um
these are some of research but these are
look at these these are just
Sushi yes yes yes yes and then for
example on this one can you see not in
the on the big menu but in the middle
menu uh there's a a ribbon on it and the
ribbon says that this would be a a a
suitable dish for the event cuz it has a
shrimp a sort of shrimp a waptia
a
really weird uh shrimp I don't know if
this even if this if it's not
actually
in Instinct
extinct you know what I mean the [\h__\h] is
a WAP Tia shrimp you know yeah uh this
one too this is a a black tiger shrimp
and yeah so what do you think guys of my
of my super Advanced
playthrough it's extinct right
yeah I was so excited I was like I
really wanted to show
you I really wanted to show
you this is the end game I've been
grinding yeah okay let me let me pour
some more
water my tea keeps on getting
cold actually there's barely
any barely any water in the tea boiler
in the hot water
maker think I'll have to drink cold
tea unless I fill it up
again so okay so I is there anyone here
who finished the
game
before
anybody
because I beat it
okay am I could I finish this today cuz
that was my goal I stopped here cuz I
thought I probably can finish this in in
one
stream that was my goal just a one
stream
series
no yes I can yes I can of course I can
but I I I like to take some time
actually I haven't been like going uh
too hard on
the
um uh like main story I've been doing
like some side quests too and I've like
sometimes I just like fish and then I
wanted to make a lot of money so I
ignored both sub Side Stories and main
story
yeah uh anyway
okay let's see let's see what are we
going to make today it's not an event
day so I just want to make money um we
don't want to use up the the the ones
with the ribbons and anything with
shrimp I want to keep aside and yeah
what could we
make it's sorted by price right
now I feel like I'm not in the groove
you know cuz normally I don't stream
this game
so it's like my com Comfort game
normally hello thank you for the
r uh what what what what what are we
going to make we want
something that I have a lot of stock for
I could make um
[Music]
this not the shrimp not the shrimp okay
let's put this in the
menu and then let's aut the
supply trust trust me just trust me bro
just trust me in the process okay I'm
I'm I'm doing the process I don't want
to do these like cuz they use up all the
veggies and I I don't know I might need
them for something else something more
simple like tuna
or the humble squid those I hate
catching
those The Humble squids are such a pain
in the ass I swear what about this ah
vegetable
Sushi 300 Let's uh Greenland shark oh
yeah let's get rid of the Greenland
shark
it's a big boy that's a real big
boy
okay and yeah we could throw in
a see this one don't CLE STS that's like
a extinct like in the end game they
bring us more and more extinct animal uh
animals fish I feel like
um but you know it it's kind of fun to
learn about fish that don't exist
anymore more it's kind of fun and I I
I've been like collecting way more like
big Sharkies and other things that you
have to fight cuz they're kind of fun
to
shoot uh yeah I don't know we don't even
need to we I usually don't fill up the
whole menu I just put in like three four
items or so in for some variety but they
I don't even think they need variety
like I haven't heard anything about the
NPC W the variety in the menu as long as
there's something they can order they're
happy I think it's really up to you what
you want
to what you want to get rid of you know
okay I think this is fine
um maybe I'll
dispatch
someone how's work oh yeah
dispatch you can
bring something we don't have have a lot
of okay we don't have much black pepper
or mayo and sesame seeds Okay then
Carolina uh dis patch for the sesame
seeds they'll eventually come
back and
then I don't know this menu kind of
confuses me cuz I I choose that NPC but
they still ask me
again so
confusing oh oopsie wait yeah this was
fine Yus is going for mayo and
Raul how did you hire what do you mean
how did I hire them this is seriously
impressive thank you I actually know you
know a
lot I played this a lot I played this so
much um I I actually I played it mostly
on my bed with my cats next to me but
like uh I had like really bad neck pain
from playing it in my bed because I was
just not sitting properly but it was so
comfortable so you like sink into the
bed but what can you do what can you
do knowledgeable wow is scary for
yapping yeah it's my first time
streaming it this is the joke I'm like
surprising you with my really Advanced
um play
through okay okay let's uh show you how
this works it's kind of chaotic I have
so many staff already so only I don't
have to do so much
but yeah it's been a while I don't know
what I'll be doing
uh so uh the staff that you hire they
can't all do the same things like one of
them can maybe uh fill in drinks oh oh
that was wrong but okay but not
everybody like some can clean the table
some
cannot H wait what get wait H wait what
how there I pressed X it didn't
work it's been a while let me bring let
me bring let me
bring and then in the late game you also
get to make like cocktails and I don't
think uh there no there might be staff
who can make cocktails but I think it's
just me oh I hate I hate doing the beer
I fail so often with the beer
give
got to do the Wasabi the
Wasabi
uh let me
check okay now we should we should still
have enough is this one out of one just
because I'm doing like all the supply
but the the day the day's end is near uh
what am I
doing the day's end is near so it's it's
all good oh he wants a cocktail okay uh
two
blue the cocktail is okay the beer I
kind of hate
doing there we go perfect cockail
perfect oh my god let's
go wow they do fresh Wasabi like that in
Japan yeah maybe in in high highend
sushi places like mine
yeah and see these are my sales I got
$8,600 profit
today
and N I earned five Artisan Flames those
things to learn learn the the recipes
remember we had no unsatisfied customers
I think so but our Branch
however oh branch had no unsatisfied
customers either but like
well I don't
know I'm not really paying much
attention to them they're just doing
like lowlevel
sushi yeah
thank you Nathan for the pinky I do
think I could probably read super chats
today I think there should be no issue
with that and if people really think I
can't finish it in one stream then then
we can do one more stream finish it in
two streams I'm I would be glad to
stream it a second time but I have to
get perms for it so I can't do it
like oh anytime
soon um yeah okay so it's another day
and the shrimps are coming closer but I
think I have enough shrimps so I don't
really need to focus on that we could do
some story we could enter the control
room that's the main story
um I think uh I have to go to the GL
glass glacial area right it's been a
while it's been a while the glacial area
isn't even like so nice to show you as
the first first look into the ocean of
this game if if it's your first one
because like it's kind of empty looking
it's not as colorful and fun as the main
tropical
[Music]
ocean yeah I think the control room is
the final mission so I'm like what do
you mean I can't finish it I'm I feel
like I'm pretty close to the end but
okay we'll
see I need to remember the controls
uh how do I go faster again I like this
okay okay I already have like a pretty
upgraded amount of uh oxygen like as you
saw it's like the maximum
and my two gold weapon is uh this one on
the top on the bottom oh you can't see
it wait let me move myself here maybe
maybe here the the laser
one what's in
here a baseball I don't know about some
of these items they're kind of like
ridiculous but let's use it I'm scared
okay I forgot how to play ah [\h__\h]
ah I forgot how to play how do I shoot
y it's been
weeks okay I'm going to get back into it
how do I shoot again I think like this
no like this
okay so my laser it has uh the the shock
the electricity in
it okay so now I'm out of shots kind of
sad I could do my other thing but there
is ammo over here and there's oxygen
don't
worry nice cing
and it's it's it's difficult cuz he's so
slow and when you go faster you lose
more oxygen there we go so for these big
boys you can like either cut their meat
or if you're advanced in the game like
me you can send a drone in the beginning
you have I think only one or two Dres
drones but I upgraded it to Max so we
have threee drones and I take the whole
thing so you don't lose any meat you get
the whole thing and now I recharge my
oxygen so we're back to the full oxygen
all good all is good in the neighborhood
I can catch these small fish too but I
don't really care for them cuz they're
small
fry oh [\h__\h] right cuz I have the
baseball [\h__\h] baseball with my normal
knife I could do it NY oh a do
a dolphin I don't know if it's my small
screen but that barely looks like a
dolphin looks more like a a manta to
me drone fish recovery yeah I'm going to
keep it like high quality a dolphin in a
place like this it must be a lisso
delish Peroni what what the [\h__\h] that's
surely also
extinct huh you f so too it looks like a
blanket I heard they're pack animals but
but that one is swimming alone is it a
photo
op sometimes these things these cut
scenes bring you to a photo op sometimes
it brings you to a boss fight um could
be anything disappeared behind the
iceberg okay sounds like it could be a
photo op photo up basically like they
make you take pictures oh you little
[\h__\h] I hate that um squid over there
there are more of them behind the ASB
okay a school of dolphins always okay
that's a photo Opia if you take a nice
picture you get some money for taking
cool pictures on the water basically
it's only like special locations
though a
a wait ah here okay oh God I always mess
this up though
uh
uh did I get
five [\h__\h] I if I cancel it now um they
might go away immediately and I don't
get a second chance to take a picture so
I'm just going to send this in whatever
sometimes they disappear really fast
look at them go look at them go those
are interesting
Dolphins those are so
cool it's difficult to take a picture
what do you think this is guys what do
you think this is It's a crab it's a
crab it's a crab I can for these ones I
can put a a crab trap for others you
have to like do something else there's
different types of crabs that you can
catch and there's different ways of
catching
them yes it's so interesting guys
actually let me ah heal little [\h__\h] I
hate you so much no
why that's not
fair honestly the aim with the joystick
is really difficult especially when
they're so
small ah you little [\h__\h] w oh I didn't
see
you
hey hit him with the baseball ah
[\h__\h] get those baseball I'll get that uh
oh what what I'll at that stingray in a
moment he scares
me he poisoned
me see in the late game these are the
creatures are like pretty like you know
they got High uh pretty
high um HP it's kind of
crazy so okay oh what the [\h__\h] is this
gravity launcher launcher modified to
utilize the suction power of a wall
field sucks in nearby creatures and then
explodes I don't think I ever had this
one before so if you find new weapons
you got to pick them up and then I see
okay it is a first time Duff is our like
guy to learn how how to make new weapons
so if you pick it up like twice in the
game on different occasions you'll have
uh found it often enough to like study
everything about it and then be able to
make it uh outside of the ocean as well
I feel like I'm holding a PowerPoint
presentation or something
here um so like in the boat you can make
your own weapons but in under the water
you can find like different weapons to
replace the one you came into the ocean
with but you don't get to keep it you
only have it under the water
okay um but if you want to have it
permanently then you got to study it and
then make it uh under yeah you know yeah
okay let me catch that stupid Stingray
where was it ah there how did I not see
it
before come
on yeah yeah I know you're coming you're
not going to surprise me this time hey y
hey come
here there you
go
no no no no no no no no no no no no if
you go too far it goes
away no I didn't take damage it's unfair
absolutely
unfair there we
go a [\h__\h] how do you cancel that
baseball going to send that with a drone
as well I guess W walk through Duff cut
scenes are the best yeah man is my drone
coming or what did I count cancel it I
cancel it oh no ah wait the Drone drone
drone drone drone
please
okay uh we got to go
deeper yeah I'm I'm trying my best to
explain the game to you guys it was a
star skate by the way a stary skate such
a funny name well these names are so
funny so here is like um other materials
that I can't pick up because I got a
stupid uh uh baseball sometimes you get
weapons that still work for collecting
these things but the baseball just does
not work so we got to go back to our
basic weapon then we no not the
baseball I don't want the baseball my
basic
uh my basic knife is fine okay it's even
upgraded I think a little
bit
toic for some curry dishes some sou bull
kelp there's different types of kelp in
the game even it's
amazing I'm running out of air cuz I'm
like wasting so much time talking
instead of moving oh the [\h__\h] ball is
there again but I just want the air
behind the
ball the what's here ah the sensor bombs
okay okay baseball and
then you know what I'll just I'll
just okay now the baseball is gone
forever I know I have to go left but
there's always something cool down here
that I want to capture cuz it's only in
this location [\h__\h] Frozen Cod
no only in this location them up there
oh actually no the stairc now now I know
usually I only thought it was here but
now I know it's in other locations too
huh wait I don't have ammo oh [\h__\h] okay
gambu oh no so see it's not a stair
skate that's what I
mean so you can try with your normal
Harpoon thingy
but they're difficult they need many
hits and
then when you get to the last
hit it it can
uh-oh H
okay [\h__\h] see see you
you come on
ah I miss I
miss but this one's so cool it's so like
old and un not existing in IRL anymore
okay now I'm prepared now I'm prepared
so I was ready to push those buttons
okay um this time I'm going to cut it I
think but this is
aanas look it up guys look it
up I love I really actually love the ECT
of learning about fish in this
game I really love learning the names of
fish that I've seen before that I've
seen in the males and all that and even
if I haven't seen in the males like you
know new fishies and their behavior and
everything and yeah it's really cool I
really enjoy it and so I've been
actually I've been waiting to tell you
guys oh ice got gun
um I don't really like the ice gun
either but I'll uh yeah this is what I
forgot last time I have to disassemble
at least um ancient you love me saying
ancient fish name new new fetish
discovered W was saying ancient fish
names oh oh wait this is the poisonous
one huh whatever I'll at it
anyway wait did I get the air up there
or I feel like I'm already out of
air this by the way leads us this is
like a shortcut to get back
home um
yeah ammo let's
go feel like I'm not ready
to go move forward in the story cuz I'm
like so out of out of it ah see so this
is where we continue in the story but
there's a cool ass
rare [\h__\h] it's cuz he
turned ah but I I have the B bombs I'm
going to use the
bombs come here come here come here yes
go off go off let's go 80
damage oh no see this is the problem I
think he took damage though on his
tail like if they Zoom too much past it
then and they don't get caught let's see
can we can we do it can we do it can we
do it can we do it it can we do it yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay yeah that boy is definitely extinct
that's the cool thing like in the end
game you actually find all these extinct
uh boss boss not boss uh just
monsters fishies cuz like it also kind
of like in the story you reach new areas
that were like you open them up then
they were thought to be like unreachable
up until that point cuz they were closed
off and you see how there's so many room
ruins here like it gets a little bit
more unrealistic in the end game but
it's really cool is there a mega loon
yes uh-oh uh-oh too close too
close oh yeah right he only takes damage
from below a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I think there's
ammo on the left side that I could
[Music]
get yes me got
done but there's this boy there too [\h__\h]
ah ammo okay
120 120 oxygen yabby yab
y all
right and wait I don't remember do I
even have to hit them from with the
actual there we go I have one more right
okay okay okay okay okay quick we got to
find some
oxygen 100 got to go
slow please don't please don't hurt me
please no no no no no no no please
ignore me he he's got his eyes on
me
uh
oxygen there must be oxygen otherwise
worst case we can take that
mirror oh there must be
oxygen in the end game there's like so
little oxygen I
swear
[\h__\h] I rarely die but okay here it is
but like sometimes an end game with so
little oxygen scattered uh uh all over
it's like really
[Music]
rough yeah there we
go buck Bean is there something down
there oh oh wait I haven't been here
before what are these TPO like creatures
are they ancient species as well what a
cute Bunch picture up photo up let's go
oh they are [\h__\h] cute what the
[\h__\h] they are like tpes take a picture
of four creatures
four
wait for
it are they suddenly going to zoom look
at
them look at them so cute okay okay one
2 three
and four [\h__\h] I did it no not a four
whatever I don't know if they come back
whatever that's okay they're so cute
they're so tiny no they're like really
fat big uh tpes what are you talking
about oh this is nice we love we love to
have that you know what I'm going to put
a fish uh trap here but uh actually oh
they do come back quite a bit man you
never know you never know let me get one
of the shms as a trap but
um the fish you can catch with your
net but I always wonder like I probably
won't get good things out of the Trap if
I put a shrimp in
there cuz it really depends actually on
the rank and
whatever but we'll
see we'll see we'll
see takes like a few seconds like maybe
a minute and then we go back and we pick
it up and see what we
get H me and the boys used to raise TPS
cuz the paddle they're born in was
drying up that's so sweet you raised
them cute make them into frog lightning
Harpoon tip level three all right thank
you that's for my main
Harpoon and upgrade for that I like to
see I don't want to go too far away soz
I got to come here anywhere so let me
let me get
you this one's also oh
God you you you you bamboozle me what a
fake
out
ah wait no so there's like different
kinds oh [\h__\h]
it die like this then okay F catus
there's different kinds of like
these like catch
thingies and some of them are really
difficult in my
opinion and if you just knife them if
you just kill them with the knife then
then you don't have to catch them like
that you can just pick them up but
generally you get Less meat I think or
less quality
meat uh if you don't catch them normally
what the [\h__\h] that's a first Doo Caris
ing what the
hell what is that I want to I want to
Google
that Dolla do what doar
Caris do
Caris
ing oh
oh it's look you guys should Google it
too it's like a weird crab with only two
sneppy snappies and like big eyes like
an alien you're telling me this existed
before holy [\h__\h] and they know this from
like the fossils but like
wao this is the cool thing about the end
game you don't get living creatures
anymore you get only like dead things
it's kind of crazy it looks like a sport
creature kind
of kind of crazy I'm just going to take
this sometimes I don't don't want to
waste them cuz they fill up um
everything and then sometimes it's kind
of a waste so I want to like first use
up the ammo and then come
back cuz it can be a
rare thing you know but okay let's get
this boy
the one thing I love about this weapon
is the reach cuz the others don't have
such a good reach and also you have a
good vision of what you will be hitting
the others don't show you the other
weapons or not they don't show you
necessarily okay
um do a big turn cuz they if you stay
too close to them they're going to get
you they're Out For Blood for Blood ha
why is still lava image
well I already told
this on once in preat on once on the
beginning of the stream I don't want to
tell the story again but it might be
fixed
Midstream we might be able to fix it
later so this is also like kind of toxic
or what why is it so toxic Ruby my first
Ruby I think my first
shell ocean quw shell
interesting
yeah my app is broken right now okay
shall we
go wait which X am I supposed to
press oh there's some riding on the sub
this is from a a boss fight that I had
this is the leftovers but I didn't click
on this
before see blue forever I guess they're
really proud of what they
do that's almost seems like some code
that I should enter somewhere to get
like a some extra special item
all right um I guess we'll go oh here's
Duff we have like a like a walkie-talkie
thing like a radio
thing I seem more static than
usual I like the music yeah the music is
really chill too for real
M it's it is a CO it is for what SE blue
forever I'll remember it even I a man
with even I a man with heart of Steel I
feel a bit nervous now May the Pixies
guide you oh God wait wait the way you
say it it really feels like okay there's
going to be a big boss fight probably oh
and I don't have the ammo a I can at
least get some
ammo usually at boss fights they have
like one oxygen refill on the ground and
one ammo
refill and the thing is it's often so
hard to get like one of my most recent
fights I had to redo it like so many
times cuz um the boss wouldn't even let
me go to the oxygen refill and all
that no one tells her thing this fight
is a bit different okay okay
interesting sometimes it's really rough
I had
um wonder if I can see it here probably
not I had one my my most recent boss
fight I want to tell you about how
[\h__\h] frustrating it was I want to
show you which one it was so maybe some
of you guys can relate to
it okay let's
go 210 oxygen I hope that's
enough yeah some of them spawn it
through their faces but even then it's
kind of hard to get I don't know the
roots have severely
mutated the door is blocked by tree sap
there should be a way to go
inside okay okay sometimes yeah it's not
like we don't go to the boss fight we're
going to some more cool areas like a
dungeon hey yo what are you what are you
I probably can't yeah I thought so what
am I going to do with
you what am I going to do with
you okay I I'll find a way to catch you
eventually but Hey where's the no
oxygen let's focus let's focus is this
yeah
come on really I have to do it like
this it's it's I don't have enough
oxygen for this no can't do it like this
wait can I pick him
up can I actually pick him up
actually I can
wait no way you're more heavy than
me but at least he can stick to it and I
had to push it okay okay
do you ever get to catch this boy he's
so cute oh there's an oxygen there don't
go away hey no you're going to get me
stuck forever no he was not
cooperating [\h__\h] oh what is this big big
scorpion underwat
scorpion I must some somehow find a way
can I catch you uh-oh uhoh he wants to
catch
me a
Too
Close y Miss they're so close I have to
shoot
fast Dam
it all right got him we got him Mega L
grabus he has a mega
grab Mega low grabus oh there's
more he wasn't so hard to catch I
y oh oh so many wait do
I if there so many do I actually like
need them to do something actually nah
why is there so many what the [\h__\h]
y oh I yeah the cool the cool thing
about this uh specific weapon is like if
they're close by they all kind of like
get some damage it's like
AOE that's pretty
dope
they're so fast
though [\h__\h] yeah chain chain
damage I'm going to get you I'm going to
get you okay one
down
okay last
one it uh it's really difficult
sometimes
H
uh-oh uh-oh oh oh nice Dodge no
why you're going to make me lose all my
oxygen
again what these obser we'll see we'll
see in a moment they're from the like
light their light fruit from the tree uh
you can use them in previous oh
[\h__\h] in previous places you could also
use them in many ways come on die my
god um [\h__\h] oxygen
y so we pull them out and we put them on
top of the jelly I think then maybe that
melts it I don't
know does
it it explodes doesn't it yeah okay do I
need more no oh I can pop the sa using
the mut mutated Divine tree fruit what
if I drop this mut mutated Divine tree
fruit onto the door I saw
earlier okay on the left side
right [\h__\h] I hope I have
enough I have enough
oxygen oh yeah apparently it's
International women's day wait what door
H
so what
door now it just exploded on me I have
to go around ah here's another boy a
hydrothermal went vent is blocking the
door is there any way to stop the water
jet yeah probably move this boy but um
do we just drop him on top of it
what how is that supposed to
work just drop in like this no way
stay buddy
stay
uh
uh oh come on the top wall looks loose
may it may collapse if the crater UPS a
little
higher what so I should go back up or
what no ah thank you I was hoping for
that ah oh oh can
I if the crater erupts a little
higher what what do you
mean ah no there's no Oxygen here either
is there am I going to
die let me see if there's something here
oh there is but I need a I need one of
the
boys Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay
Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay ah it goes
down don't go
down let's just take the air and then
think about how to do
this how the [\h__\h] do you do this if they
all wait wait there's a a tree food too
so I could make something explode like
the volcano
thingy how do you make all of them at
once if there's if I'm so
slow maybe I have to drop
them see he's already on the Move he's
already on the move don't go down don't
go down no don't go
down how do you how the
[\h__\h] no no reset
reset and quick Qui Qui quick quick
quick quick quick quick come on ah okay
I did it he was already on the
move he was already to move that sneaky
little boy it was good that I reset one
of them on the way okay nice what was
the tree for ah okay we bring it with us
going to ask what what it was
for pop pop come on what the hello
okay what it's going to explode tell me
what I need it
for I'm too scared I'm too scared I'm G
to get another one okay it's for here
but that's also so far you kidding
me
grow to the left to the
left okay fast fast can't go
faster uh-oh
hi I'm out of here okay the door's open
looks spooky inside I should be careful
I actually I already in this game I had
to deal with like underwater
zombies following me and there was even
some stealth was kind of incredible I
wonder if he's necessary for some ah
this is the
beginning
uhuh yeah underwater
zombies like uh there's mermaids in this
game and those were like underwater
zombie
mermaids ancient
ones ancient zombie mer
mermaid oh more water thank God okay I
see I see what's up okay it's like a
right timing kind of thing and I got the
right timing easy easy easy
easy all
right oh I can just go around
I
hot hot hot you can't go through in one
go here I
think a oh
no look what we're going to do to
them well I can't drop it I have to drop
it when it's
um
yeah come with
me how much time do I have for that
a got it it didn't work oh it fell in
okay now it's I don't know ah
[\h__\h] look at my oxygen look at my oxygen
I need more
oxygen they feed off of are you sure you
you w how do you know
that
oh
e I've got a
feeling that the boss fight is coming
closer yikes one of those gr looking
eggs
H why are they attached to the Divine
tree roots
m boss fight no not really but they look
like
sushi they look like
Sashimi strange creatures have hatched
from the eggs his his
statement wait those creatures I've seen
them in one of the sea people's
murals what they already had Sashimi
back
then
do these count for the shrimp event I
think they would tenin once told me that
an ancient engineer altered creatures by
infusing the Divine tree okay so this
might not be a thing that existed
IRL these maybe creatures they have
survived these may be the creatures they
have survived for such a long period of
time still breeding oh I don't know
what's
happening I like how they
flap wait
defeat that wa
to what my Harpoon didn't work
why well that certainly work my Harpoon
has to
work there we go even got
AOE there we
go I don't I'm going to take the oxygen
once
I'm done with them just want to
really save up enough
okay I just missed
really
really balloon shrimp go pop indeed all
right we have another one of my cute
what are they called they're so cute
underwater um
shne in German we
sayne what would you call
these
Kina so cute SN snail oh yeah snail
forgot forgetting simple English words
let's go there even more eggs here they
look like they're ready to hatch but I
can't go back now no it's perfect for my
AOE weapon it's generally no problem
there's a door there if I could Mount
the mucus covering the
door okay are we going to do this before
they
hatch yeah the tree fruit should I put
it in that tree Divine tree fruit device
huh what
device are there
oh hey I wouldn't mind fighting them
all come on which direction this one
huh
wa okay
okay I'm going to Bazooka
them oh it just works on its own good
the contraption is working maybe I can
melt the mucus by protecting the light
from this Divine tree
fruit protecting okay sure so it's like
a timing thing mhm oh no the eggs are
hatching I need to get rid of them
before I can melt the
mucus yeah all right uh no problem a
[\h__\h]
uh-oh oh W yo this weapon is op for this
chapter absolutely op they weren't even
that close but I guess the the closest
one the one that was closest to him and
the one that was closest to him and the
one was closest to him wasn't the
closest to the other to the first one
but they were close to each other so you
know Chain Reaction
baby let me melt the muc is covering the
door yep uh what can I control it now oh
yeah covering the door over here
okay
see this is another part of the game
that was so unexpected to
me uh-oh having
like gaming like this like
what okay uh will it stay like this
probably not oh oh but I can I can do
damage to them but I don't want to no
this is not efficient let me do it all
okay okay they pop pretty
fast I would say my weapon is better
though cuz I could do them all at once
kind of
you didn't know the game had boss
battles yeah I I have no idea I thought
it was just like a diving game no it's
everything it's farming it's cooking
like restaurant management it's it's a
lot at least the sav ammo no the Harpoon
um has no ammo so the one that I would
have used so that one's fine we can use
it
forever must open the door and Escape
quick
quick behold more balloon
shrim this time I'll eliminate them all
once and for all okay we'll see about
that I I I just oh god oh there's one at
the very top what the [\h__\h] how am I
supposed to get them
ah oh it just pops down oh wait okay I I
was able to get rid you know what if I
just oh wait if I
it
okay y y bad experience experiment bad
experiments bad experiments oh no no no
no no no no that was uh not good but
they all going uh interesting
interesting choice of path my shrimp
friend [\h__\h] come over here come over
here yeah
okay we're back on the on the
controls almost the big brain Str you
had you know what I was trying to do for
a
moment that should be the last of them
I must quickly melt the mucus covering
the door before anything else shows
up okay well that is a kind of a flag
furagu
furagu in in Japanese they say like that
I don't know if that if you say it in
English like that when there's like a
hint of something
happening in Japanese you would say a
flag was put up do you say that in
English master mucus is all gone it must
be the cord of the control room over
there you say it
oh yeah like a red
flag let's find out what it
is you sense a dangerous
oh so this is the boss fight a I know
there will be one oxygen on the ground
but I I usually like to take it like
like in the middle of the battle I like
to go in with like more o and then
refill it after taking some
damage ah it's okay even if we fail we
got uh a
retry and I think the retry is with full
o Maybe
not maybe not actually I don't
know we'll see boss fight let's
go oh
oh
oh The Offspring of that ancient
creature is clinging to something is
that the nucleus of the Divine tree
could that be why the Divine tree is
acting strange I'll need to get rid of
these creatures by the way so the Divine
tree is like the reason why we care
about the Divine
tree it's not for our Overworld life no
it's for the sea creatures uh sea people
the the mermaids that we found um when
we found
them um they didn't trust us first but
we kind of helped them and they've told
us that like um they have been
struggling cuz it's been getting colder
under the ocean on that level because of
the tree not lighting up everything and
not warming up everything so it gets
colder and colder and they don't know if
they can survive so we've been trying to
help them and by us helping them we've
been getting more access to new
creatures which is cool and yeah new
materials as well but I think we're only
helping them cuz we're
nice but also because we care about the
beings on the water we want to protect
and preserve them if it gets too cold
they'll all [\h__\h] die yeah it's global
warming or Global colding so we we're
doing it for for the sake of everybody
right yeah yeah yeah yeah not just for
the mermaids for the
sushi yes for the Delicacies delicacy
delicacy
Delicacies
so yeah that's the story
guys cause of the
earthquake okay defeat the Ancient
creature zero out of eight honestly
that's so easy with my weapon oh there
they
are nothing easier than that I wonder if
there's oxygen down there actually maybe
I should have checked first cuz this is
probably going to immediately
spawn the biggest boy of them
all
like a big version of that maybe I don't
know looks like the Divine trees nucleus
has stabilized again I guess this should
do it no no no I hope the earthquakes
will stop now no no
no I should start heading back to land
no no no it's not going to be that
easy
oh
okay this is going to sell
well the meat of that thing all I think
about is like this is going to bring the
big bucks if I kill this and cut off the
meat this is going to be a
delicacy what on Earth is that or what
underwater is that is that the mom of
the creatures I saw earlier the mommy no
wonder there were eggs everywhere ew ew
ew ew ew ew what are those flaps are
those
wings
it's so big oh [\h__\h] um I need oxygen
first otherwise I'll be like a one hit
probably yes I'm a
chef got to think like a
chef mommy came up to pick the kids oh
hello if you are coming over that means
this is a difficult situation ATT track
you Dr bacon is a
dude just a dude I checked it down in
case you needed help what's going on
here the huge monster came out from the
lava I know what that is I've seen it a
lot in the text about the ancient
civilization of the sea people looks
like the creature known as
Yari
Yari an ancient beast from Legend still
alive wait is is this Legend IRL Legend
too is there a real legend about this
thing or is this made up I wonder
it's massively bigger a [\h__\h] ah missed
ah it must have absorbed the Divine tree
and the geothermal energy to get this
big it's an actual you it's an actual
fossil okay cool cool cool that's what I
wanted to know there's a small small
real small version okay yeah that
obviously not such a big one
yeah
M that's so
amazing that's so cool oh based on a
real animal I guess so yeah we have to
defeat it to stabilize the Divine tree
Dave I'm coming on you divine just
Divine
Exquisite how can I possibly defeat such
a huge ancient creature he took down a
dinosaur just a moment ago a moment
probably a few weeks ago but
yeah no that was a different situation I
don't even have any weapons or bullets
now eh I do but but yeah maybe not
strong
enough oh Duff what are you here for
Dave isn't the weapon right here what do
you mean what what do you
mean I told you this drone has all kinds
of hidden features uh-huh I knew this
day would come but it was a bit sooner
than expected I'll inut the oh
wait I'll input the I I'll input the
activation code for the drones Attack
Mode
my nose my nose has been constantly
bleeding and then immediately drying up
I have like dried up blood in my nose
24/7 since I came
here it's really bad so I can't make the
nose voice so
[Music]
sad yeah that's really
bad it's so
dry yeah no no no humidity I die my nose
is so like red everything's red
inside my mucus is fully
red H wow I can do that the this drone
can maintain oxygen levels fire
unlimited bullets and even manipulate
time
what you mean if you press a you can
temporarily manipulate time it should
give you some time to dodge attacks of
course you need to be quick so you're
telling me this is a fast boss when are
we getting the no scopy
pics
uh
uh oh bullet
time this is all the help I can give
right now I hope oh I hope we don't we
won't we won't be saying our final
goodbyes goodbye T oh no why is this
also purple that's also a cold huh
good wait the other one the other one
was something with blue uh what I forgot
it no h ah no okay it's not a code it's
just him using his yeah Bluey forever
this is just him saying his cute anime
figure uh and and
Anime magical girl anime phrases he's
into
[Music]
that
he's just a big
aacle nothing wrong with
that okay I don't know how this is going
to go but partially I feel like the Y we
the no monster bosses are more difficult
sometimes than the monster the the story
The the no story bosses are sometimes
more difficult than the story bosses is
what I
mean
yeah I can't just run away now not after
getting this far all right let's deal
with this
hi um how wait let me get oxygen first
please hello I can't look at get oxygen
I can't uh what how does
this what how what how do I even shoot
uh fire
okay ah yeah it's not going to go
well oh yeah okay I'm going to die uh
what
Papa oh they can shoot a lot of times
okay let me redo this let me redo this
I I can I get oxygen please normally you
can get
oxygen oh this is like to whole [\h__\h]
project
now oh this is [\h__\h] to
project but like a [\h__\h] I'm dying I'm
dying I'm dying I'm dying yeah that's
fine I want to redo cuz now I
understand sudden genre shift oh full
oxygen tank okay now now we're talking
oh uh yeah z
r all
right ah
nice
[Music]
okay I got I got it figured
out okay
okay
ah okay to whole
time oh I can I can shoot them but
they're like they're over me so oh oh
okay I don't want to be here ah okay I
still have I still have bullet time do
you get this in Toho project too I don't
think so this is like the lowest level
of too project bullet
hell the easiest what are you doing oh
the
babies
okay going to have to kill them
all what now don't scream at me what did
I do I'm trying to help
you where am
I our current attack level might not be
enough this enemy is tougher than we
expected I didn't want to go this far
but let's unlock the
limiter why do you not do that from the
the
beginning yeah thank
you who brings out their trunk card
right at the beginning of a
game just watch
this
oh Kaboom I call this Stella
laser a superpowered laser combined all
our Tech never thought we'd use it on
the water where did you think we would
use it pay attention if you hold X you
can gather Stella energy okay let's go
of the button to fire easy right keep in
mind that you'll move slower while
charging so be careful good luck Dave uh
okay
uh
uh what it didn't where the [\h__\h] do I
go release to fight a oh
ah I can still shoot normally too though
might as well ah ah wait I can push both
at the same
time I missed
no oh good good good
one
time ah oh oh yep yep yep where do I go
where do I [\h__\h] go I Mak the super
chat
ah I what
the
[\h__\h] okay okay I was kind of in a sticky
situation but it's better
now uhoh okay oh I did it I was right oh
did I did I no I didn't it's just a cool
moment [\h__\h] I'm like in the middle of
all of
this maybe I should
like focus on in this oh [\h__\h] oh sh oh
sh I'm going to die I'm going to die I'm
going what the
what no no
no I'm
ding ding I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying
I'm dying I'm
dying do I restart from the beginning
y or is it like from the
middle oh I think it's
beginning is it no it's no it's
middle no that's not a good start but
okay we start with full oxygen haha
haha
[Applause]
mhm mhm
mhm
[Applause]
mhm pretty
good
uh
ah ah all the buttons are confusing
me okay let me let me go up here and
ah
ah gosh I thought it was fullly
charge now there it is how many hits do
you need
of the super
laser ah I'm in the middle of everything
again oh God oh
God
uh guys I'm not good with with bullet
dodging as you can
see
yeah please be the end to
oh wait no that felt like the end but
it's just a slow motion that makes it
feel so
satisfying
oh yikes
go
hello some go up some go down I stay
here between L the part
oh go
here oh oh it's like they're dancing
around me like those dancers in the pool
oh oh oh oh
oh ah what the
[\h__\h] why did it not hit you oh no oh no
oh go go go go go go go go go we got to
escape from it
okay okay I feel like we're back to the
beginning of his like
[Music]
pattern oh oh we're cutting with close
guys oh my
God that was so close
again close close it was so
close goodbye Big Boy goodbye mommy
sorry Mommy for hurting
you oh what is trying to run away are we
going to chase it if we don't kill it
now it will continue to cause problems
oh
no we shouldn't kill an ancient
creatures that we discover after
thousands of years we should preserve
them but at least it has a lot of babies
maybe if we find if we take some of the
eggs we can like breed them but like in
small not in big and
dangerous
perhaps what do you mean I got hit in
too skills don't make fun of me you're
lying to
me I definitely
don't
M oh H there there were similar sections
like this before Oh
God let me go here in the
middle yep do I have to charge the thing
again oh I have to oh
God while in on the
move this is not
funny ah but uh oh I will actually uh
100% die look at my oxygen guys it was
not recharged uh throughout this
okay
fine
yeah all
right let me go here should be
safe
zooming zoom
zoom zooming
backwards
uh-oh uh
concentration uhoh he's he's is he going
up or down I
wonder oh he's just going straight
okay didn't hit him
much ah ah okay okay okay stay stay here
yes okay okay
okay H oh yep I I don't know how I I
can't I
can't Dodge do oh is it laser it's Laser
Time straight laser
time no
problem no this face is actually not so
bad not the
worst oh or it was like a survive kind
of
thing just survive
until the the time is
over oh it seems like it's finally tired
now it's a chance dayve we need to end
this
now but no
oh oh no no no
no but this may be good he's opening up
a new area for us maybe a good Escape
path
mhm
go he's so angry
why wow that was
close look it's using its last bit of
strength they've moved to that path uh
that's one that's open now if won't be
able to hold much
longer oh will it drop on
on no it's following us it's it is
following
us okay now we go up but okay this is
just escape cuz I I can't shoot
backwards yeah there's no no prompts for
shooting either ah but I still have the
slow-mo
oh slowmo still works no
it oh he follows me what the [\h__\h] I
better stay here on the side so I have
enough
leeway
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
H
[\h__\h] ah
ah ah didn't he owe me to straight
forward the first time now he follows me
I'm going to die to redo this stage I
don't know why they don't let just like
recharge your oxygen automatically oh
hey that was it
actually it's a dead end what should I
do uh
shoot if it if it doesn't have much
power left then just a few more
lasers oh n hold
using its own weapon to our
[Music]
own advantage that's the
word oh ooh ah I feel
bad ha that creature's entangled in the
vine
tree this is a lucky opportunity to
finish it
off the Drone seems to be malfunctioning
I can't pick up a weapon
signal my nose well what should I do is
there anything useful around
here yeah yeah there's a huge Divine
tree fruit device over there the Divine
tree fruit seems to have returned to
normal what if I put it in there and
operate it no it's too big I can't
possibly move and aim it all by
myself
okay who's going to help us
oh so many of them even it's the king
and the princess and some guards and the
dude are you all right human yeah yeah
I'm I'm good I'm totally good I can just
recharge my oxygen if I die once I'm
fine we came down here because you
didn't come up even though the Divine
tree was stabilized kind of
sus is that Yi has grown that big over
this long period of time this is Ru
she's so cute it seems like we need to
defeat that creature to end this there
our chance well it's tied up let's
finish it off that won't be enough
unless we use a Divine tree for device
over
there this this is swam he's quite the
douche
bag he like like me and him sometimes
will be sent on like missions to fix
something and then he will be like I
totally did all of this on my own even
though we're kind of like saving his ass
all the time well given my expertise in
both physics and math it seems like we
need uh to adjust the angle of the
device
upwards that might work but it looks
incredibly heavy well we'll help if five
of us combine our strengths we can do it
somehow you bring the Divine tree food
and put it in there's no time hi you
pull I put it there
yes
yes friendship power of friendship oh oh
they're already angling
it okay while they're angling it I could
have already been on the move but okay
144 oxygen and a
dream I have a
dream shoot all right I'm Ready the
device is responding it's time to end
our long
history you py nuisance take this
Kaboom Kaboom
Kaboom
mm W
[Music]
be
W yeah it feel so bad but that's a lot
of meat we can feed like so many people
with
this my a was precise it won't recover
from dead State ah this has really been
an incredible journey you did a great
job a a great job human let's go back to
see people Village and talk I somehow
cuz I can't read I just gave him a
foreigner
accent just missing words by
accident yeah now we're in the the sea
people village town thingy you get to
see that
to the water temperature is stabilized
and the Divine TR fruit is also in good
condition the villagers who were e seem
to be slowly
improving we faced many challenges but
it's a relief that we've managed to
overcome them I think earthquakes on
Mainland will stop as well how about
going up and checking the status good
job human come and visit us
often
okay
I kind of want to make more more hot
water and more
tea so I I think I'll do that
now uh okay EP see I am like I wasn't at
the beginning of that chapter you guys
were maybe looking at how long that
chapter is generally but I was at the
end of the chapter even usually the
chapters are really long I'm in the
epilogue now know guys so I basically
finished the
game but of course you can uh from my
knowledge like play more like they were
also like DLCs right you can just play
more and like cook more and like finish
get all the recipes and everything I
I'll play more though of course we'll
see what the epilog has to
offer but I want to see is there like an
info how long the epilog is Dave the
epilog
[Music]
length friends is the epilogue and the
final chapter of Da the
diver so it is the finale but I don't
know how long it
is it doesn't say game completed in one
stream yeah it's not long right yeah you
guys who the hell said I can't can't
finish it on one stream you
underestimate me you probably don't know
the game or so let me make some more tea
though I'm right here guys I just have
to fill the the W
[Music]
cook
one
cup wow I can actually measuring
cups that's so confusing I don't know if
you can hear me but when I when I use
recipes that are from America there's
like cups measurements and we don't use
cups measurements we use milliliters in
Austria so kind of
confusing all
right boil I have to press
[Music]
something you you'll end up hearing the
melody how nice you will get
to you'll get to witness the melody
oopsie here we go ice gun okay I don't
really think I I've learned uh they
taught me in the game so many new
weapons after the laser ones but I I
keep on staying with the laser one cuz I
feel like I think it's the best at least
for how I play the game you can keep a
good distance cuz the reach is so big
thanks for the 40 months almost of
membership thank
you Fire and Ice gun we usually have
measuring cups that have both yeah yeah
that's actually uh the ENA cup that uh I
just used it also has both but when I
look at the recipe it only says cups not
Mill
so I always have to look it up like how
much is one cup or just look up for I
try to find a German menu uh recipe
instead um but
yeah water cooka melody dmca in
coming
maybe okay
so wait I didn't get
to I didn't get to take any of the meat
that's
unusual normally I get some of the meat
UD he's the picture guy oh you brought
picture of something can I see W dolphin
found among
glassier ah where have you been there
the Antarctic or something yeah it feels
like it I found it in deep Waters of the
blue hole that's amazing this blue hole
is like a gold man for our magazine yeah
that was a joke I'll put your picture to
good use I'm sure the readers will love
it money money that's not much money
though and yeah the Tad palls they were
so cute what the [\h__\h] what are those Tad
palls I think I've seen picture of them
in
book I remember now
Arandas no I can't handle Freedom Units
sorry how did you take picture where in
the world could you take this kind of
picture our readers made think will you
using fake pictures can't use no no no
freaking AI nowaday makes every picture
unbelievable
uh actually for real though like there's
some fan
art sometimes still where it's like AI
the other day I found one like even you
guys have noticed usually are able to
realize like to to see which one's Ai
and which one's normal but recently I
saw a lot of you guys like retweeting
and liking a piece of art which wasn't
tacked as Ai and it's it doesn't have
the typical AI look to it but uh I
looked at the profile and I noticed it
it was
AI so I didn't retweet it because of
that even though it was such a good
picture such a good picture but it
wasn't real and I'm not going to retweet
AI
art sadly
um yeah it was a wobble fan art it
looked so good though I wish it was real
it was so cool I think it's the the the
one um it was one where my back was
pretty
prominent uh and the back was mostly
free and the rest of uh my body was
covered in some cool like original armor
that was
AI it didn't look like it but it was Ai
and if you look at the the rest of the
profile you'll realize cuz like one of
some of the older actually like he he
doesn't tag it but like in the comments
sometimes that person leaves a comment
on their own um pictures and like
describes like whatever like some kind
of uh methods they used to create this
picture with
AI
yeah I forgot if it had my feathers but
even real uh artists forget my feathers
so that's not necessarily a giveaway
yeah the prompts but it was in Japanese
I think so um not easy to catch that
one
yeah yeah yeah it it's so sad
man at least some like some of them make
it obvious but if they don't make it
obvious it's it's kind of
shitty cuz you're like you you you think
it's real but it's not no and there's so
many other like artists whose art has
been used to feed the AI uh generators
and they're not happy with it Japanese
artists especially are not happy with it
but they can't do anything about it so
let's not support something that steals
and feeds of other people's art who are
not okay with
it
yeah Anyway dot do dot I'm just kidding
I put your picture to good use I'm sure
they will believe that it's not
[Laughter]
AI we need AI to be regulated for real
for real or like why did we even walk
down that path
[\h__\h] like at this point it's too
late we're going down a really bad path
in terms of
Technology this is the problem when we
advance too
much it becomes very problematic for
many reasons yeah the Pandora box has
been
opened there are photo spots all over
the place please take buo
okay okay wrap up your day and get
things ready bunch of sushi yeah well we
skipped uh like there's usually the the
part the day is uh separated in three
parts in this game morning time
afternoon time and evening time and
evening time you have to uh go to
restaurant but you could even skip a
part of of the evening time cuz
sometimes you want to get some nighttime
only fishies there's not too many um but
there's a couple uh and so if you do
that half of your restaurant time will
be skipped and you get a little bit less
money on that day but yeah you want to
get those exclusive animals but yeah
this time we went from morning
immediately to evening cuz I guess the
story time was really
long uh let's go cook some sushi oh
actually never mind this cuz this is the
start of the epilogue U NPC is not here
so this seems like a special special
skip oh we can't even go to any of the
other
places your scientists were so
preoccupied with whether or not they
could they didn't stop to think if they
should what an amazing
quote
bunny art of w that's AI I don't
remember
that hey there da you're finally back oh
everyone's gathered
here yeah we've heard from Dr bacon
you've accomplished a lot you did a good
job how about we all relax today oh
that's Bano you did a good job how about
we all relax today and enjoy some food
together he's the sushi chef
well awesome I was worried I might have
to get right back to work great we
should all celebrate together
a one question for people who finished
the game like I I I feed I fed the cats
so far that uh a new cat and a kitty
showed up cuz in the beginning you have
like one cat in a restaurant and you can
feed it uh during the daytime and it
will like you eventually but was there
any any further stage of cat invasion of
my
restaurant or is this like the
maximum look how
cute that's it oh is it is it cuz I kept
on still feeding them hoping that
something will
happen I got further than
you all right oh Sammy So Sammy Sammy
works at the farm he's the son of the
farmer first he's not there you get him
later on he's also one of like the the
special people that will show up in your
restaurant with a TV crew asking you for
a challenge to make some special
Sushi and yeah then you get some big
cash and he then eventually joins the
farm to uh you know have a different
lifestyle he used to be a musician a
rapper I
think yeah but now he wants to just have
uh chickens he wants to just raise
chickens it's been a while bun of sushi
how are you Sammy are you enjoying your
life here you know there are times when
I get a bit bored but it's also
incredibly inspiring
yo the new song that I recently released
farmer daddy online has been getting
great feedback you know Al so you're
still making music huh for sure the
sound of a hoe hitting the ground the CL
of a hen it all just is one big beat to
me yo oh he gets it he gets it I like
those hoes
too why didn't he come in person oh yeah
he's just
a what do you call this um um uh he's a
YouTuber now
basically because I'm waiting for an
important partial today I'm been
inspired from afar by your bravery Dave
the way you four tires Le to safe that
see people Village oh if you were a
beautiful girl I might have joined your
Phantom I'll pour all my energy into
weapon research to prepare for any
upcoming
crisis as your colleague I'm counting on
your continued efforts
Dave all
right [\h__\h] my
nose if only I was a girl if I was a
girl I'd be a popular
one I'd have so many people oring me
because they love me
so if I was a
[Music]
girl I could join whole on
life and I could go on stage with all
the cute girls and do the
drive ha true Feast you always so busy
we've hardly had the time to chat now
that things are calmer I'll have plenty
of time to share with you some of my
stories oh sorry back in my diving days
I was mostly into free driving and I
wore the necklace my father gave me but
barracudas have aend see to attack
anything that GI now out of nowhere a
school of Barun came at me even worse I
didn't even have a Haruna day I figured
fleeing might be more dangerous so I
swam straight towards the barracudas who
I think the ground is sick huh I didn't
feel
anything
what what was that interaction that's
you Dave you've worked really hard it's
gratifying to see your Venture
prospering uh I think she's the
restaurant tester that um lets me go on
a higher rank um when you get higher
rank you can make cooler recipes and
hire more staff and all
that you liked my voice acting thank you
I'm having
fun that's largy thanks to you for
providing such reliable staff you must
have had your plate full with all kinds
of things but now I hope you can support
Bano in running the restaurant
effectively Bano is a bit stubborn and
might stir up some problems if left to
his own
devices Ed uh your assistance has really
helped Elevate status at company uh we
have a new reporter now which lightens
my load a bit so I can afford to join in
this evening Gatherings yes ah since I
cannot drink beer I stick to
non-alcoholic
drinks I was helpful so you don't need
me to help with the reporting anymore
right what are you talking about I still
don't know how to dive you are da the
diver so please do you're
diving ah good job Dave I only open the
shop here because this place has plenty
of fish who knew it had such a secret
well you solved the problem and my
business is booming now I guess my
decision was right after
all that was a fun experience coming
here was a good idea I'm thinking of
seeking out never Venture what do you
think let's just rest for now
Cobra oh oh can you
[Music]
hear yeah that was
it
we
cooked we have cooked s you thought that
was your water boiler you have the same
I think a lot of them just have the same
noise the same sound
effect my froat
hurts
yeah streaming and talking so much in
without a humidifier is I'm not used to
it um although no I don't have a
humidifier in my room uh in austri e in
the streaming room but I know my throat
recently in the past
days my throat and my nose have been
[Music]
suffering now she has one but it's
like in her in her steaming streaming
room like as a
constant of um I don't know it's
constantly positioned there thank you
for the Super
Chat yeah oh you got the
Blu-ray nice
nice yeah I think I've I've seen people
receiving the Blu-ray and also um the
merchandise more merchandise the one
with the um with the backpack and the
the memo and the
pen all of that mostly first for I think
like Japan and Asian
countries be careful W you fit for all
of us I'll be fine good thing is Japan
is a humid country so m
I think my my throat will recover
fast I do have a weird stomach um pain
right now
though it arrived in na too
yo I really I have so much merch to pick
up in
Japan dating back all the way to the
[\h__\h] hot talk
merchandise I really need at least one
big empty suitcase maybe even one and a
half m
yeah which is also a reason why I don't
really want to go directly to Japan why
I would like to avoid that uh cuz right
now I only have like a medium siiz uh
suitcase with
me yeah I need to I don't want to buy
another suitcase I already have so many
suitcases at home suitcases at
home yeah they're literally
at home
so okay first time seeing you in the
shop
huh ah yeah okay uh she was um some kind
of researcher too I
think well I just finished subing my
paper so I'm a bit free good I'm glad
for you that Eco bag there I haven't
seen it before ah you have sharp eyes
it's the reward for maxing out the Eco
Watcher level I I
did I I did
when did I do that I guess I
did cute it has your face on it it's
your freaking merch that's what it
is it's a service that prints the faces
of users committed to Environmental
Protection on a
bag wait but your face is on
it you've really been putting a lot of
work in since you got some free time I
can't fall behind but I've been doing
the work and she printed her face on it
what shouldn't it be my
face
huh this guy does he remind you of
someone
huh I'm just going to give him a Mickey
voice cuz I don't know how to do a ash
voice oh sat you made it
too I heard you've been wering into
glaciers uh to collect marinka and I
thought I show some
support well that's not quite true
but oh thanks to you my world ranking
keeps getting better and
better now that big event is behind us
let's see about Gathering the remaining
Mara oops just remembered I forgot to
turn off the lights after G went to
sleep what yeah so the the the monsters
I always say Monsters the fish that you
catch uh sometimes they they are more of
a monster than a fish but yeah you get
like a an entry in your Marine card the
collection and if you get like rare ones
he gets really
happy the
cards I still can't believe what
happened not just the sea people's
civilization but the village too you
even solved the crisis good job from now
on we should keep the civilization
secret they need to maintain the peace
day we
gained I agree yeah of course let's keep
the mermaid Secret
ah she was the rich lady who um Bano was
cooking for
before and then she kind of started
hating him and now she's like actually
he's really the best aha yeah Bo
Peter Peter although it was quite a
roller coaster I School match from
B I want I wonder if I was too focused
on fancy food and missed out on what
true flavor is but I still can't get
myself to eat that grilled sharkhead
over
here anyhow please keep running the
branch smoothly and sharing more
wonderful dishes with people
Dave
Vincent wait what who was here again
Vincent
now I'm actually blanking maybe he'll
give us a
hint glorious voice acting even with
your nose FR issue thank you is he the
TV host I guess so yeah I didn't come
here to radi your restaurant today so
don't stress take it easy I see he does
give me a hand when I D in peace I can
save her intricate flavors more it's
delicious happy to hear that I guess my
Prejudice have worn off but there's no
denying that there has been a slight CH
change to taste oh it's a bit smoother
you could say softer before the dishes
were briming with the chef's strong well
style but now it feels more
accommodating to the consumer I guess
that's a good thing well that might just
be my
perception and last but not least we
talked to our partner in
crime who had rain less work than me cuz
he's just cooking and I'm doing like so
many other
things um um um I'm I'm sorry um I don't
know how to do his voice I already had
to come up with so many voices I'm sorry
I couldn't be of much help I was busy
with the
shop thank you you Lally saying what I
just
said I'm happy he's acknowledging
it
Bano oh like B I should say like B
what like how
do no I can't talk like that that's like
I don't I don't need I don't know how to
recreate
that what are you talking about the see
people love you
cooking that oh that sounds like
her just slur the [\h__\h] out of it now
that there are no more earthqu let's get
to work a I wish I could have voiced him
more say more I
my that was actually so good holy [\h__\h]
this the I can
[Applause]
do I didn't understand that
[Laughter]
perfect wait I want to talk
again no I
I
is and but I wanted to have a normal
restaurant day I only had one normal
restaurant day what am I supposed to do
sit
down wait what do I do a there's another
speech
bubble at the cocktail ah to pour myself
a
cocktail ah a lot of nice people in the
end looking back it was a fun
adventure it was really nice to um grind
this game in my break it really was I
never would have visited a place like
the sea people Village in my life where
are not given the opportunity okay let's
relax and go for another exciting
[Music]
dive wait is that the whole epilog just
talking to the
people yay come by
ah there are so many cool cutcenes and
the food art on like their own Instagram
is so cool
too
a it's a ghost there's a ghost in the
picture but wait what about shrimp day
what about shrimp
day oh they came up a he's scared but
she's happy
a pizza yummy
he's not eating sushi what the
[\h__\h]
fpi PPI he got a new
figure oh they're fixing the statue or
making no they're making a new one of
me our our cutest Helper made the best
sushi ever she's
impressed oh these are like these are
some Farmers that and other like
material people who can help you when
you get the mermaid uh Village
unlocked this lady she keeps on coming
for the TV programs meow
baby yeah my cats would not eat it they
would not eat that oh cute boat he
always arrives in this boat when we're
out in the ocean it's like hey can you
catch some cool stuff
please the final boss and yeah oh ha
funny what what oh yeah oh yeah a new
adventure
oh they finally gets to
sleep he's got a nice Ocean
View cute
feet
nice is that a goodzilla
shirt that didn't look like
Godzilla for
free that was a a shooting star oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh what the wait what what
what what the
what hey what was
that what that
flash what it's a Dream It's a
dream wa where we can dive in space Dy
astronaut oh this this credits oh score
the score
ah wait what do we shoot ah okay I
thought I could shoot the spaceship yo
yo okay that is my new favorite okay my
new favorite uh credit
screen I need more where where are the
others the
music oh it's
funky I need more
animals hey
I diving in the
space with funky news and can I shoot
this oh I can oh it explodes oh what is
this I didn't know these exce this looks
like a a thing that I've seen before yo
big big HP
[Music]
hello is the music loud enough for you
guys to enjoy because you have to enjoy
it
yo I'm I actually thought I I'd have a
little bit more content to show you guys
but hey you got to see the sushi
restaurant Thing Once you got to
see the the waters a little bit you got
to see a boss fight could be a bit
louder h it would be hard to change that
now I thought it would be long but we
can read Super Chat that's one
thing yeah there's there's several DLCs
right we can play the DLCs I know
there's a Godzilla DLC
they no that they keep on Advertising no
no no no no no no no no no don't take my
score
away
oh
God that was just one boss fight who the
hell said I can't do it in one stream
you were just coping you were like hey
she could totally do it in one stream
but let's make her think she can't and
and um hopefully we'll get a longer
stream out of
it I had a good feeling that that was
the end I was like hm this kind of you
know feel feels like it could
be one of the
last things to do in the
[Music]
game and I was right my gut feeling was
right this a perfect
bamboozle I just wanted to bamboozle you
with this I didn't even know it had a
story it does have a story and it's
quite nice the my only criticism and
here we go this is credit so let's um
talk about what I feel like what I liked
and what I didn't like uhoh if the
credits on the left side end does that
mean the game is over no no no no no no
no I want to have higher score naon naon
no no naon no I want an autograph from
naon from twice no
[Music]
naon
no sign to all no
no I didn't get that
far no
2022 that's is that when the game was
released thank you for playing you're
welcome thank you for giving me a fun
game to spend my time with on my
break oh yeah oh yeah
oh
h n so was it a dream or what obviously
it was a dream
right uh one endie of the year last year
wow did you sleep well Dave uh this game
seems perfect for switch on Steam like
no I will say that it's uh it was really
more difficult for me to play uh on the
switch when when uh you use the the
switch in a portable way so I don't
think it would be easy on the steam deck
either the best is playing it on the on
the screen and then having your Pro
Controller I
guess yeah you could probably do that
yeah but what I mean is like in handheld
mode it's not so easy cuz um of all
those like quick button
mashing um and the grip overall you you
need a little bit of a grip and you need
to have quick access to the buttons to
button
mesh I didn't like it on handheld
mode yeah anyway finally got some sound
sleep and a fun dream yeah I even
dreamed I was exploring space ah things
should calm down a bit now well then
check on any unfinished business and
let's have a blast running bnch ass okay
o reward sweet dream what is that the uh
uh uh color for the
boat hello there a wonderful Monday
thanks to your help uh we were able to
get a special in the magazine we issued
today today please keep up the good work
I'll be back on
Saturday weekly fish new fish found a
discovery of wizard Barrel jellyfish has
increased the magazine uh sales oh Udo
has sent you a monetary award the wizard
Barrel jellyfish didn't I find that a
while
ago
it's shred party today wow let's go new
content oh mini game Space
diver oh my God oh my God oh there's so
many updates on the Instagram cook
star he
son
ah this is not enough you have to do a a
a a uh a loop a loopy one for the
Cai ah this is old okay right yeah but
so one more thing I still need to do is
reach Platinum oh and
Diamond uh I've been only missing the
best taste it's kind of hard maybe we
can still reach that and then I would be
quite
satisfied what do you mean I she said I
I got the final level in E Watcher but
I'm on level four and I kind of gave up
on doing this because it was kind of
annoying
yeah I was like always collecting
something but here you can have it and
the rewords aren't even that good I
don't even use any of the rewords I
think oops
it oh she oh she got it she was just
flexing on
me
be I kind of don't want to give that to
you I want to cook those
things okay yeah well it's morning so
let me show you like the normal the non
non icy
world how about
that let me show you I can
show you the ocean that's what I'll do
American
lobster I I love this lore too I always
read it it's so
fun it's so fun going snorkling with the
w one yes I'm taking you but we're not
snuggling we're going next level
snorkeling AKA
diving so this is where you start out in
the beginning you can't go lower because
you just don't have enough oxygen and
just not enough like your equipment
isn't good enough to go lower
um but
yeah there's still manyif ficiency and
then later in the game you do kind of um
find a few new
species in the
higher uh areas as well but not too
many tuna for example is something that
shows up o nice
um in the
higher
meters not no not to impress GAA but one
thing I wanted to say when I was uh
playing this
I I was so fascinated by everything and
and since it was like immediately after
I played I played immediately after I
went to the
moldes
um
I I I
decided this
year I want
to get a DI license [\h__\h] car license who
needs a car license ah you little shits
I'm going to get a diver's license
yeah I want that diver's license you
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
shark no why he
missed I have decided cuz I'm so
fascinated and snorkeling was so much
fun to me but it's not enough for me
anymore I want to see more I want to go
deeper be careful though diving is real
serious I'm probably too much of a
chicken to go really deep anyway um but
I I do want to have the option when I go
on like holidays like the males again to
go diving instead of snow calling I want
to have that option and it's just
there's so much to see it's it's been so
fascinating to me to learn about these
fishies you know this game has been a
really really deep
eye opening experience to me it's kind
of crazy it's kind of crazy go away you
are all low tier fish I don't need
you I don't need
you yeah shallow I'll stay pretty
shallow don't don't worry well maybe I
won't maybe I'll get so good and
confident in it that I'll go really
hardcore yeah I want a deep
dive oh hello what this is this should
be a a a white reef shark or something
like that see I learned so much I'm
already ready to get my
license I'm already ready white tip
brief shark I think was it why did brief
Shar this
now
yes I remember their [\h__\h] names
guys I
know I know everything now now I've
actually learned like IRL useful
Knowledge from this
game that's the crazy thing Endless
Ocean oh yeah I heard about that I hate
this one and this one's kind of
boring that shark is kind of boring like
I I caught that one so many times I
don't care
anymore but yeah we're now at 100
m 100 m this let's catch that one no oh
wait no never mind the barracudas are
boring barracudas bore
me every time in Yakuza when we were
playing these days and every time they
mentioned the barracudas I always had to
think of Dave the diver and I always
wanted to talk to you guys about how
I've been playing Dave the diver and how
there's barracudas and Dave the diver
and they're kind of low
tier I mean they're annoying and scary
at first but then they're so low tier
and easy to cat like [\h__\h]
him I had to hold back so much oh I
really wanted to talk about Dave the
diver so yeah I'll I'll be I'll be
getting the license uh in Austria in the
lake I
suppose because um oh we I want I want
this one that one's pretty uh good um
that was a what was it called again
a valy
to to what was it tell
me Tell Me game yeah TR Val oh my God I
[\h__\h] remember the names of the
fish I learned so much yeah we have no
ocean but I think I uh I can easily get
a license in the lake and um I don't
want to get it like in in on a holiday
cuz they're usually way more expensive
over there it would be crazy too yeah I
have fish bags I do this is a like a to
toad a sea to this is a sea
toad let me show you let me prove you
it's a sea toad they're kind of annoying
they're so fast but they're cute they're
they're they're really um
cute they're cute come here SE Toad Say
out say say out come here let me catch
you a [\h__\h] oh it has this no no
[\h__\h] no
I'll
just get you with my
Katana SE to se to is now do the voice
but under
water I'm under
water help me no let's stop oh my God a
grenade
launcher we had that before huh I had
that before but uh I don't I don't want
it I'll stick with my
gun oh wait there's olive oil see this
is called olive oil also a thing I
learned while playing Dave the
diver I've learned so much thanks to
this game this one's so funny I forgot
what it was called but like it looks
like a normal fish at first but then it
looks like this it's so funny I love
this one I want to meet all these fish
under no I hate I hate this
one I hate this
pattern a [\h__\h] I can't believe it
just
die yeah Pacific fan
fish it's so funny what is this olive
oil you speak of oh Myer
mysterious very
mysterious okay I forgot a lot of names
but they're really familiar to me though
I I have to say ow ow ow ow
ow
[\h__\h] um this
one [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I swear to
God fang tooth yeah the Fang too and the
com jelly s this n s this
[Music]
n what are the requirements for the test
do you have to I actually don't know but
I think yeah it's probably like getting
a driver's license you have to take some
this is the
NP na na something na
naus a chambered naus I know that yeah
um
I was going to say yeah I'm sure there's
like you have to take lessons there's a
I think a set amount of how many lessons
you have to take with a uh a
professional
um and yeah then yeah you get a
certification and then you go you can go
diving on your
own ah [\h__\h] hell why are you so
annoying no oh open
up so I think these ones don't exist in
reality
the comp jellyfish that
explodes I don't know about
that ah let me show you if you take this
stone and you drop it on this and you
get the spider
crab see spider crab it's called SP
spider crab just so you know it's called
spider crab
woohoo only professional divers like me
know this it is true it is
known yeah I don't think they explode
IRL actually I I'll keep this
one yeah spider crab because it has big
no not the rubber chicken equipment no
has big Oh Long Legs oh hello uh this
was a funny funny shark it's called
funny shark trust
me no it's um it's the one that could ah
this is the cookie cutter shark isn't it
I remember now I
remember I'm so proud like
I I know all these names it's so cool I
actually really learned something useful
from this
game I can't believe it guys
see you will see the proof in a moment
oh the FR Chu oh [\h__\h] it wasn't the
cookie cutter shark ah it was a FR shark
a [\h__\h] I thought it was I made a mistake
but uh there's also a cookie cutter
shark I
think yeah you hear interesting cookie C
cookie cata sharks story that it's kind
of a tongue
twister the stove offer cookie
katak wrong fish identified scuba
license no more please that one looks so
interesting doesn't it that one looks so
surreal actually oh
yeah abort abort
abort so sorry this doesn't normally
happen to
me this doesn't normally happen to me I
lost track of the oxygen cuz I was
tanging
[Music]
thank God for the Escape
pod
wow yeah B so I'm going to get a license
for diving this year I'm not going to
get a driver's license I'm going to get
my driver's license before I get my
driver's license I'm so excited I I was
playing this game and I suddenly had a
new goal in life that's so exciting and
it will be so much fun you guys will
understand I have so much fun in my in
my vacations I can go snorkling and I
can go
diving
oh I can I can take like really cool
underwater footage for you guys and
maybe I'll find some maybe I'll make
some discoveries that are ground
breaking history uh changing life
changing it's going to be in the
newspapers no probably not but
yeah I'm excited for that I'll do it
sometime this year when I have time I'm
going to find Atlantis and then I'm
going to return
GAA I'm going to be like here here's
your Lost
Child uh don't know what to do with her
so please take her
back now you want to do you guys want to
see the sea people Village I I'll show
it to you
to just skip over the
afternoon
meaningful so is there an end to the
epilogue because there's no they didn't
give me any anything to
do besides just like
chilling and running my
restaurant so you can either just swim
through but you it feels so slow so you
can hire a beluga
although it makes me so mad that you
have to pay for it so most of the time I
just like really slowly make my way
through the village I don't I never want
to hire the
Beluga no I don't know I think I'll get
a driving license before I get a flying
license see I'm on the
Bela it's a pixel game but this one's
kind of pretty actually I guess
everything's pretty but like in the
pixel
looka
okay let's go so there's some places
here where you get some side quests but
also there's like some special food that
you only get here that gives you some
extra um time limited
upgrades and yeah this and that and
there's like a casino kind of thing too
oh that's
me seeing a statue of me in the sea
people Village feels kind of nice to be
honest yeah they really didn't like me
in the beginning I had to do side quests
to get them to like me in order to
proceed with the main
quest did you say Casino yeah kind of
something like that there's some
gambling there
yeah uh I think it's in
here you going to leave H for no it's
just my part-time hobby so this is uh
there's some games there's a shark
game which is kind of funny we can try
them
all bet
50 yeah you will understand in a moment
what it's
like it's it's a game that exists IRL um
so for now I'll do
free it will eventually bite but wait I
didn't pay attention it did show where
it would bite right I didn't a
[\h__\h] I didn't pay attention did you see
where it BL
blinked [\h__\h] I didn't I didn't
look did you see which one blinked I
think one
blinked top right where exactly which
one what is the
number tell me number the number of the
tooth what the [\h__\h] I'm getting WhatsApp
messages from people I don't want to
have what WhatsApp messages from don't
tell her no
no what the [\h__\h] what do you
want what do you want this
time
ah
oh
oh I don't want to answer that
now uh okay I really don't know but you
can kind of know if you pay attention in
the beginning which I feel like defeats
the purpose of the
game let just go with one
now ah
[\h__\h] have you ever gotten like a hacker
call on what's up
no no no
no but I watched a documentary recently
about how there's this thing um like
especially um in
America people are getting calls ah I'm
sure it's the next
one no it isn't people getting calls
from these like uh what a oh
what oh my God I did
it without knowing yeah the pig buter
scams I heard about that that's really
sad that that's a
thing m a it's from John oliv that's why
I know a lot of my knowledge comes from
John Oliver uh I don't know I don't we
don't know have to play again let's do
this one find the
Pearl guess what kind of game it is
let's bet uh 100
okay okay okay okay everybody look
everybody pay
attention don't
blink like at the end the first time I
played this oh god oh i l okay [\h__\h] I
lost Dr do you know first time I did it
once and I I won but I was really
unsure thanks for the raid by the way
did you lose it did anybody get it top
left top left top right top left most
people say top
left oh this one's really rough normally
these kind of games these mini games and
other games are too easy like this um
hide the the thing under the cup are
usually too easy but this one's actually
difficult so there's another one is card
matching it's all
right so here generally um in the
underwater world
you there's a different
currency so you can't use your normal
currency so this is a way to get like
more
of that currency and buy things okay
crab and that um or or famous mysterious
ore thingy or fish
starfish
shell ah I think here yes
got I got the first
one he has memory ah he opened that one
before and he was wrong jellyfish okay
jellyfish uh seahorse maybe ah that one
I think was top
Row third one or ah please mess it up
nah he stole it from
me you suck H I think
here y okay okay okay okay okay
wow I using photographic memory ah I
hope he doesn't remember cuz I remember
oh that one
I did I see that crap before or a
different one but
anyway this one I certainly do
remember Uh crap ah yeah I opened that
one before there's not much that we
didn't open
yet not a whole door did I open this one
before ah crap crap here right y crap
Connie let's
go
ah okay sasani he remembers that one cuz
he opened it himself
before
okay ah
easy oh
[\h__\h] no wait I know where that one is
top right top right yeah [\h__\h]
nah is okay I'll give that one to you
wait
to ah ah okay we win though we
win when I play
memory it's like when you open the right
one you get another turn they have
different rules in
here no no need and then there's a
seahorse racing but nah I never did that
I think and this guy plays music
when you talk to him oh oh wait he says
something new now that the Divine tree's
power is returning I feel my inspiration
coming back let me give you a sneak peek
of the piece I'm working on it's a song
dedicated to the Divine
[Music]
tree
wow
so nice that was really pretty he used
to play something
different oh yeah she gave me the beluca
whistle oh wait she has a side quest
actually Dave something wrong siio ran
away again a yes I think something
caught his attention it's like her
underwater
dog I think so I've seen one near a
glacial pass
sorry to ask you again what could you
look for SEL if he's hiding somewhere
you can learn him out of some Fe okay
I'll switch around the glacial
passage
passage go out
yes wait did she say glacial
passage did she say glacial passage I
already forgot what she said
[Music]
so this is like the second floor this is
the the Royal house where the king
is and there's like a library on the
right side but we can get a shortcut to
the glacial
passage
here oh tumia calpis an arthropod
presumed to have lived during the
Cambrian Period it has 50 legs two pins
and little eyes near its antennas it's
10 cm long ah I couldn't read the whole
thing sh jellyfish that looks like
something seld would like I should
follow it
so
wow
ah these are a lot of really cool
ancient fish in here in this section
this one looks so
funny where you
going to the
mountain
shiny fish in the water why water in the
water
why dog in the water why oh oh oh
no yeah I've been here
before we're reusing the area it seems
like the path collapsed when the giant
goddon woke up I've come this far I
can't lose it now going to keep
following it
okay let's go o I'm so close I'm f
faster than
that I'm
faster I'm just predicting the path
now is this way you want to
go probably
right ah and then
down all
right gon is uh it was like a one of
those zombies but like in really big
[Music]
wait for me wait for me can I lose it uh
I think it kind of waited for
[Music]
me
nice oh oh oh oh oh a no I'm no I'm
stuck
no okay okay ah special material got to
pick it up gives me
money okay the the fear of
losing the jellyfish was not
so beak so glad you're finally playing
this thank
you and I'm finishing now let's go I
don't even have to play this this is
just a side
quest oh the jellyfish disappeared why
don't I look around the area where it
disappeared oh I'm sure this is
connected with like a boss isn't it let
me take
the just in case get it topped up
[\h__\h] humbal squid get out of the way
I hate you so
much um was that a are these the blob
fish I forgot are there the blob
fish nah this was not the Blobfish was
it think s is hiding behind the she of
ice all right I have the ice picture she
gave me stay right here you little
rascal oh we were
gone I was just
uh saying how I hate the humal squad
squid Squad humal squid and this I think
is the Blobfish but I might be wrong
so
I was a bloodish oh my God I'm such a
genius I remember even these
insignificant looking
fish let's go the humo
Squad YouTube cannot handle the Wawa
fish
facts yo it's so fascinating to me use
an ice pick to break the ice striking
its weak points so you guys may be
surprised like what is this part there's
Parts like this uh sometimes in the game
sometimes we um use like this like kind
of like heating device to uh go through
metal under water I don't know what it
was
called okay but this is new never did
this before what where where am I
supposed to do
it
oh that was good that sounds
good oh I'm it's like it's like hot and
cold and this is like pretty
[Music]
hot judging by like the sound what ah
that surely was good uh-oh I'm okay I'll
redo I didn't really
understand I wonder if the spots are
different
now this feels like a DS
game yeah but it's fun so what about
oh
oh ah it's like M
sweeper stabby
[Music]
stabby ah nice so one
more
how many is there a way to
know stop the actual I
can't those are like I think you have to
like get free and then it will break
properly or
[Music]
what near the
cracks I think you just have to get free
random like they're just scattered you
have to find
[Music]
them oh first
try what so far on the edge
too oh aha I do understand something now
like here it didn't leave any marks so
there's nothing close probably but this
one yeah know it is really like mind
sweeper
oh
cold colder there was hotter it was
hotter there so hot
hot
[Applause]
okay there we
go okay now I should use uh the feet
Linton gave me to lure it
okay what how are feet
oh ah
[\h__\h] where where that yo I can't go
lower I can't go
[Music]
lower what take it it's up there by the
way can you see behind the ice over
there that's her underwater dog what do
you mean bad give me a different spot
he's top right I know but like I think I
have to put it where the light is
obviously
right ah like a trail ah a trail makes
sense yeah cuz it did react when my hand
got closer
but how cute I want the underwater
dog I want
one I want to have underwater
dog yeah B okay trial and error learn by
doing underwater dog tacle feed the
tacle so
cute it's such a
baby okay catch it catch it catch
it we got it s just sure is fearless
considering it came all the way here I
should go see lynchin
now
yeah it she came to
me what brings you
here oh she has like a winter hood on
now I like it cute
outfit I was so worried about sjo I
couldn't stay inside you found him come
here
Salo he's a good
boy I didn't have to go all the way back
to her thank
God Dave I owe you again nah come to the
casino later I have a small reward for
you I'll be on my way then now now I do
have to go back to her what the
hell just to get my
reward
man you know how lazy I am and the
loading screens in this game are so long
the only thing that makes me accepted is
the the
lore the fish
lore makes it acceptable otherwise ah
the funny boy the funny boy I have to
catch him he's so rare he only shows up
right
here
basically he's so thin there you go
aiming is really difficult Pelican eel
yeah yeah I remember I remember I
remember um these ones are funny too
they're like they're like really brainy
squids is so
Jupiter and four of his
moons oh that sounds
cool you're back to my stream and you
see another star
wow yes a Dumbo octopus I said big brain
but it's the
opposite it's a stupid Dumbo
octo yeah oh
this one was it like a skeleton fish or
something like that or am I making that
up right now CH W fish
facts this one they these fish they only
appear in like really cold Waters ah
Bary right yeah
Bary but you know and in the in the you
the world of the the professional divers
we have some nicknames for these fish
and it's totally skeleton fish
okay yeah this one is so funny I also
don't remember this name cuz like I
rarely come here to catch these
fishes but I feel like barel eye was
something like I heard
before the
game oh my God stop
running or
swimming there we
go peacock squid that's what it was it's
a squid it looks like a fish
though and the red one is just a stupid
ass humbled squid that I hate cuz it's
not humble at all it's just
hum
hook ah [\h__\h] wrong
direction I hate it cuz it's so fast and
the poison is really
annoying [\h__\h] I hate him so much
no [\h__\h] it wasn't the homeo squid it was
a vampire squid the homeo squid is like
bigger but it's also
red I'm so I'm so
embarrassed I'm so
[Music]
ashamed
yeah yeah it's a vampire
okay wait I don't want to go here I
don't know where do I want to go I don't
know I need to study more before my
diving exam yeah but I don't think they
ask you fish um
like species but maybe like just so you
know like the important ones that you're
not supposed to tach you're not supposed
to get close to I can imagine that that
they would want you to know like really
dangerous on
ones but like these random ones probably
not the most dangerous ones for
sure no I haven't tried diving before
besides in Dave the diver um but I
am I do be efficient in snorkeling in
the technique of the ancient snorkelers
[Music]
yes a big snorkling
fan so my next step is learning how to
dive and how to
Dave I will know how to Dave and how to
dive so true all right what's my reward
girl why did I have the all come old
what I can't talk all come all the way
here thank you for saving some it seems
he likes to wander around when there's
no one watching him there's a small gift
for you here's our friendship sa money
you could have given that to me
before okay I just want to uh do the the
shrimp
wait the shrimp day so let's go
[Music]
home I want to work in my Resto
w
please I just want to make some sushi oh
wait was over
there Mera Mera on the wall who has the
best sushi of them
all me me in my
restaurant we're going to have a EBY
party
yeah deep sea live is so interesting to
me
same
same same same
same oh see there's shrimp
fireworks good I would love to see that
I wish I could have her see this
beautiful
sight
hi hi just go again get the same
stuff okay we going to make some good
money now trust
me have you watched blue ocean by BBC I
don't know I don't think I
did like sushi now I guess it's okay K
Takashi agressively gay like sushi now I
guess that's
okay no I wouldn't eat it I just want to
dive and look at the uh fish but I don't
even want to catch them so don't worry
don't you worry what do you want to talk
about cuine made of seaweed I yeah some
side quest I didn't do
yet seaweed I think I have all of
that don't
I here's the ingredient make me
something
nice W
[Music]
so yeah I want to make insta post of
fish before Sushi here the SE people
should be satisfied with this yeah it
looks good thank you
Bano okay we bring it to the Sea people
farmer the next day but I don't even
know I'm in the epilog now and I have
like nothing specific to do like no main
quest so I don't know how long I should
play this not much longer maybe and then
I'll just read super chats but at the at
the same time I feel like I should take
this chance of doing a longer stream and
just like drag it out stop
St stall
stall stall
stall um yeah uh it is Sushi day let's
see if we have
something no no h this
one but I'm lacking cucumber no I'm
lacking black coral see I shouldn't have
given it to that uh Eco Watcher side
quest
thingy that's why I hate that Eco
Watcher thing doesn't even have good
rewards all right I have enough other
shrimp dishes though
oh wait we did get something from
yahi we can make something from ywi but
not today today we have to focus on
uh on
the shrimp let's see what do we got U we
have this humal ink pasta which
apparently has shrimp in it
too should be pretty
good other
Supply and then we
have special fried trimp
Sushi
sound could even could even upgrade
D how much will I have left no good
amount good amount
I'll do
it s
shrimp I wonder what squid ink pasta
tastes like ARL I think it's a thing I
think that's actually a
thing I feel like I've seen it
before at least like using the squid ink
like a little bit of it to color it
maybe it's not a big amount
but yeah people do use
it
M yeah I've seen
enough I've seen those cut scenes plenty
um ah
okay
um ribbon this one has a ribbon
Mia fried minc shrimp placed between
slices of square
bread okay
could upgrad too but the olive oil will
be getting less and less so maybe not
we'll get enough money even without
upgrading these
dishes
um ribbon ribbon
ribbon honestly this is already
enough yeah if the rest is just these
normal ones then I don't know if I want
to do it cuz they don't make as much
money the normal
sushi I'm money
except I feel like the tuna sushi are
really like always big money makers and
I upgraded them so much
too I should be good
enough I've cooked squid ink pasta
before I was part of an um entry for
your whole oh
damn oh
wow I don't really remember that that's
a long time ago wow 40 mths thank you T
thank you so much damn long time I did
upload the members wallpaper by the way
in case you guys haven't seen it and
also I uploaded um some Polaroids
everybody who got the diaper chicken
should be served with a polaroid now if
you check the community
post I yeah the wallpaper up to although
I don't think I'll be using it for a
schedule um next week I mean I could but
there will be not much on it I have two
streams that I know I'll be doing but
they might be the only ones and they're
even on the same day on white
day besides
that um obviously on the weekend I can't
stream um even if I wanted to stream in
the night of Japan time
I wouldn't be allowed to uh they want us
to rest which is fine it makes sense cuz
we are
performing um but yeah my chat is not
moving are you guys
listening uh
okay okay
okay
yeah
so maybe not not much going on at all
next week sadly maybe I I'll be able to
prepare some shorts still I don't know I
I will I'm pretty sure I'll do a Twitter
space though on maybe on like Tuesday or
something but we'll see we'll
see Tuesday
Tuesday no maybe not t I'm I don't even
know what day and what time I don't know
anything but I'll definitely do at least
one Twitter space
yep yep
yep yeah okay uh let's H did I auto
supply them all I don't think so oopsie
I don't think I did
[Music]
yeah oh we can start uh start the the
shrimp
party you will see they spent good money
but it's kind of
stressful so there's normal customers
too who don't even care about the sushi
but you should really just put sushi in
your
menu Fu he's so slow Dave is like so
slow he loses stamina immediately after
a few steps I wish they add so many F
facets to this game so many things you
can do oh God I have to pour some
beer um why not give Dave like a workout
mini game that gives him stamina oh my
God I did it actually not too
bad oh so far no
stamina okay uh let me get one of the
beers cuz she's get oh you got it okay I
get it I'm going to get this one I'm
running out of bab I hope I still have
enough of all the dishes this going to
be bad this is a bad beer oh it's good
really
damn hi hi hi hi hi
okay uh you get this how's the food a
looks
good oh wait I just realized something
the auto ah whatever you guys won't
understand anyway unless you play the
game cuz like
some some are like one at of one and the
others are like if you serve one it will
have like seven
portions but whatever I I yeah just just
my my faults just my faults just my
seven
cents okay that was it that was pretty
easy I got my staff really high level so
it's pretty chill
mostly mhm mhm it's much harder when
they don't have skill look at the
obviously the previous day we didn't get
to use the restaurant wait why they not
happy look at them they're making an
unhappy face but like I served everybody
properly and they got good dishes did
they want more of a variet
see what's the problem but I did make a
lot more money than
usual if you compare to the uh
12th yeah it's a day thing you wouldn't
understand I think I did pretty well but
when they look so unimpressed at the top
it means I didn't do perfectly well I
guess but why are they so
unhappy the branch no ah I guess the
branch also had shrimp day yeah I don't
give a [\h__\h] about the branch
really oh 13 13 angry what are you guys
doing in the branch I don't want to
handle the branch I have to give them
more skills and and fish
delivery oh
no it's dragging me down that's why I
don't want the brand it's dragging my
statistics
down what the hell
so
[Music]
rude okay
um
yeah yeah it's weird to play this game
without a purpose
but
H what do I do do I just end the game
well let's go to see people I have one
thing to give to them at least
I do want to minmax my business I do
kind of want to do that but not the
branch I don't care about the
[Music]
branch the end is never the end I should
have gotten one of the DLCs and we could
have gone straight into the DLC I didn't
know I would be done so
fast my bamboozle was too
good for my own
good okay I was supposed to bring this
to the
[Music]
farmer oh I don't know if I need extra
perms for the DLC I think
not and even if I I I should be able to
get him pretty
fast
yeah here this Cuisine is made from
seaweed oh what are these little round
white boy human cine I can predict the
taste but I'll give it a
try yes just
try
so a fish out of
water oh my
god oh this is a new taste W the soft
texture of seaweed and the little white
grain they go so all together this
yellow thing it has such rich flavor
they're sea urin eggs is this your first
time seeing them seea urin that spiky
creature humans eat that kind of stuff I
guess humans are able humans are able to
use various sea ingredients I'm
surprised haha B Bano is very serious
about food all right promise is a
promise I'll open up the seaweed farm
for you can you get me the black seaweed
or whatever that was I have to make a
separate form to avoid food supply
issues to the Village it's going to take
some time please
wait oh
well uh I'm curious what I can grow
there but it's nice to have a sea with
Farm yeah pretty cool kind of too late
though kind of too
late all
right do
do what does the board
say who who who
oh
clear accept Mission
a in
progress no leave me
alone those are just like more Eco
Watcher style quests I don't like
them you can't grow black cor there
nice but kind of too
late too late in the
game hi there you look cute today thank
you I'm sad I can't move and
I'm
I'm I don't know I'm I feel so
stiff but I always feel really
stiff I can't tell the
difference okay so we're done with the
game and my throat hurts so I guess
that's it oh my God no fish C I think
that's a first actually for
[Music]
me I might be just playing this a bit
more off screen like in the airplane and
whatever
yeah game
done this is going to be added to my
finished games list right I have a gun
in my hand so
right did you take a warm SI or I didn't
cuz it's already cooled down like I
think the water in North America just
cools down way
[Music]
faster
oh I topped it
up I topped it up a little bit but might
my tummy also hurts today it's so weird
have like a a
sting stingy
[Music]
feeling NY boss I'm tied up in there
guns the games list was meant to go to
meant to just be a funny thing it's not
funny it's serious business to
me oh [\h__\h] now now now I'm getting like
craps in my
tummy maybe it's because I ate something
sweet again for
dinner oh yesterday oh F A [\h__\h]
yesterday I had my first ever
tacos took me long
[Music]
enough
um yeah my first ever tacos I was always
even when the opportunity was like in
front of me I never had tacos before
because I thought that the shell was so
crunchy like uh like like
[Music]
Naturals that's just just how I imagined
it and I thought that wouldn't be fun to
eat I don't want to eat it can be but I
got a hard shell one and it wasn't like
uh oh it really hurts
it it was a hard shell but it wasn't
like a
nacho but it was yummy though it was
really small but it was yummy I want to
have that more often now
I want to make my own actually I want to
make my
own yeah do you guys prefer a soft taco
or uh a hard taco what's your choice to
go with I I wonder what's the more
popular
[Music]
choice soft soft soft so many soft soft
softt softt
soft Oh I thought I thought the hard one
are the the to go choice
but like explain to me like to me that
just seems like a not wrapped burrito
like an kind of half open
burrito when if it's a soft shell that
seems just like heart CH very messy yeah
i' I've noticed that a little bit it is
yes it is it kind of
is it kind of
is m M we're not okay I'm not wrong
small burrito small kind of open burrito
[Music]
ow OU
cheese guys I don't I haven't even
prepared a screen for Super Chat reading
so we're just going to do it here but
tummy really H
wow yeah it's pretty
bad it's really low oh sh I guess I
should okay this is going to look
[Music]
weird oh it's fine
okay ouches you can pack more yeah I
kind of I did add a little bit but I
should add even more was my conclusion
also it was kind of small I wonder if
all tacos are so
small need to go walk around no this guy
is
okay I'll
survive um
M how
how how do
I how do I get to my super chats
again I'll just go to
Hyer and don't worry guys I got it I got
it another H mom checked
off her mom is so sweet I love ena's
Mommy I love her
I need to tell you I told you already
how handy she is how skillful she is
right like with like oh she told you
also how she makes like everything
herself and um like it even looks like
store bought cuz it looks so
good yeah like this one time when she
brought us
food um it was like the the it was
wrapped in a blanket no not like a big
blanket just a small like Fabric and it
had a really nice pattern so I thought
yo this looks so nice it it looks a
little bit maybe like I was going to ask
is this self-made but I was like no way
no way that this is selfmade it's too
pretty but then later on I found out it
was self-made it's so pretty and
then we I was talking with um mam about
like all the kinds of things she she can
make and
uh how much time it takes her and like
all that we had a nice conversation and
then she showed me she showed me um
something she's been working on she
showed me really ow ouch really
proudly um a picture of
chicks that she crocheted crocheted
crocheted
crochetted little chicks yeah I was like
oh my God they're so cute can I have one
I just out of nowhere I I instinctly
instinctively I can't talk anymore asked
if I could have
one cuz I thought you might be happy if
I ask her and also genuinely cuz I have
a connection with chicks and I thought
maybe she knew um so I I also explained
to her after I asked her like oh because
you know it's just because you know I I
I I am all my fans are like chicks
and chickens and she was like ah yeah
okay okay I can give you one I can give
you one and Ena told me later that she
also thinks that Mama was really happy
to be
asked for something like that cuz like
she makes so many things herself right
and and having like someone be like oh I
want this like I actually want to have
this surely made her really happy so she
gave it to me and it's so cute and
small
yeah it's so cute it's a small yellow
crochet chick crot
chick crotch
chick a Crotched chick
M yeah really cute m is said artist
alley honestly like
yeah show us pictures we need a picture
I don't know I I I have to ask Ena if
I'm allowed to show a
picture
I have to
ask have you showed Mama any of the food
you've made any of the food I made no I
don't know I I wouldn't have thought she
would care
much hi Shi what
Shi want to see the crow chick yeah ah
there it is how did you already know was
she talking about it you knew it
beforehand you spoiled the
[Music]
raid um
welcome dear Raiders and
shiine um I I did a thing I said to my
viewers that I'm streaming Dave the
diver for the first time and then I
Bamboozled them by being in the end game
at the last chapter right before the
last boss fight so I finished the game
and now we're just vibing and
chilling it was like a surprise this is
what I've been up to during my break I
started and
finished um Dave the
diver and I just stopped right before
the end cuz I wanted to bamboozle you
guys yeah so now I'm just like chilling
and talking a little
bit cuz I'm Still Still uh
overseas in the uh North American
continent yeah I Bamboozled you
successfully did you like day to div oh
yeah so oh I I I think I ended up not
giving my real opinion so uh but I think
it was really clear for um even this one
stream uh of me like uh gushing about
how much I learned about fish in this
game and how it motivated me to um get a
a a diver license not a driver's license
I want to get a driver's
license and uh I don't know it was
really fun it was a really nice Pastime
and uh the only thing I would criticize
is it was a bit too much for me like in
terms of like extra
stuff oh is uh the chat stopped for me
are we
good
hello hey boogie boogie let's go boom
boom hey boogie boogie bum bu let's go
boom
bo hey you are my mama my body o hey you
are my mama my body o hey you are my
mama my
body o hey you are my mama my
body my body clap clap there you go you
moved again I was just waiting
for you guys I love that Pokemon song so
much so anybody who played the game
until like at least mid game or more
like end game I wonder if you would
agree with me that it was like I don't
know they added so even even in the end
game they still added new things and was
just like a lot of things to take care
of it's a bit over
whelming that that
yeah what that is a common criticism I
heard of the gamer of the game yeah okay
really yeah it becomes pretty complex
pretty
busy I'm on chapter 5 and I do agree
with you okay good then it's not just me
I was like e another thing oh please
please tell me it at least kind of
handles
itself but besides that I think the
story is really cool there's a lot of
like action too like a lot of like
chasing we even had one overwater boat
chase we chased like some people out of
a
cave and yeah there's like a lot going
on the NPCs are cool every NPC is like
really original there was even like a
flashback like a story of Banos the the
chef's
Beginnings um that was was pretty
intricate pretty well
done so yeah overall really lovely
game if it wasn't for the overwhelming
content the overwhelming amount of side
stuff I would give it a 10 out of
10 pretty
much or 9.5 out of 10 but that did kind
of annoy me and some of the fights um in
the end game were pretty difficult it
made me feel like maybe I was
underleveled but I already had almost
all of my equipment maxed or even in the
end game when I had it maxed there was
one more boss I was struggling with so I
was like why is this so difficult what
am I missing like I actually today cuz
it was the first time in a while maybe
my skills weren't as good um cuz I was
like you know not in the groove but I
when I was in the groove I was better at
the game and I still struggled with some
boss
fights so that's also a thing like why
why is it so difficult but it was so
manageable did you evolve on my guns
that's yeah maybe one thing but
uh uh where was uh
I uh
wait
here
um
yeah yeah so uh yeah I I okay I didn't
go like all the way but it was really
difficult to get these materials like
legit like impossible to get the
high-end materials especially cuz it
doesn't even tell you what you will be
needing beforehand so like I'm not sure
if I should invest into that
tree because I don't know if I'll even
be able to make what comes after and you
know what I mean it's kind of like a bet
like you you want to you think you want
to go that path but then you realize oh
this path
is how am I supposed
[Music]
to yeah I did get I guess to the end of
this one yeah and then I
tried uh
I don't
know first I think I was mostly working
with this one I don't
know the hard bosses the extra and
lightness straight up Borderlands
[Music]
gun just to get
Tuna the Tuna freaking tuna when you
play more I might play like the DLC one
of the
dlc's eventually cuz I really love the
[Music]
game I really love the
game yeah I really enjoyed it it was
such a chill game to play off
stream
yeah the Godzilla yeah I mean the most
recent one would probably be
fun
M I don't really have a favorite
character
maybe the cat's in the
[Music]
restaurant
nice
okay let me put this here and we're
going to read the super chats from the
stream for now I
guess I'm going to start now I I kind of
want to stay long but at the same time I
have throat egg and tummy egg
so Slavic fellow thank you for the pinky
W in na streaming in the middle of the
night what do you mean in the middle of
the night for who for for oh you're in
Japan now cuz you added Japan to your
name normally you're not in Japan so I
mean travel to Japan be glad that at
least you can catch the streams it's in
the middle of the night again just fry
me up at this way hey I mean I'll be in
Japan and then stream a little bit in
Japan
so don't worry you're going to get some
sea kind of streams as well don't
worry yeah a lot of you guys are already
on your way to Japan
huh nice sounds
exciting well I'll be flying on a
private
jet obviously
so I won't be seeing any of you guys on
the airplane I
hope yeah thank you slav fellow than for
the pinky and oh I'm excited to hear
like your stories afterwards about your
trip tell me all about it please tell me
please write me uh a tweet
longer uh py D thank you a you you're
welcome I I I would if it wasn't you
know if it was just me I would even tell
you more um but I I have to like
consider and respect the wishes of the
people surrounding me so I can't like
yap yap yap and blab blah blab too
much yeah but I hope the information
I've been giving you guys has been
making it somewhat clear of what's going
on and now my chat stopped moving again
and now it's no okay it's back it's back
slamic fellow thank you for the red
super chat I already see what you're
doing there I see what you're
doing I see what you're
doing uh an upgrade to Red for Pat's
Super Chat for saying what every kfp
feels and thinks wow I love thank you so
now I can read the whole
thing K thank you so much for always
being so communicative and trusting of
your fan base and apology isn't needed
but appreciated nonetheless we all see
how hard you work and I support you
wholeheartedly just keep on doing what
you love and happy because you help
bring joy to all of us thank
you it do be a busy
time not just for me but for many
others um and yeah in one
week is
fast let's
go and I am so excited for you guys
kfp I'm sure you guys are excited too
and I'm excited for your excitement I'm
excited to your
reactions and all
that I've been extremely stressed out
cuz like things are like falling apart
and not U going the way it should so I'm
really stressed out but it will calm
down once I'm in Japan I
think yeah and then I'll just be having
fun I
[Music]
hope yeah one thing I want to say I'm
not going to I have like one off collab
set
up uh with someone who I haven't off
collabed with before but besides that
I'm not going to be really chasing off
collabs this
time because it's too stressful and I
don't know what kind of off collab to
suggest and I don't know who to ask and
all that uh and yeah I'll be if anything
I'll stream solo more I don't want to
stress myself out too much with off
collabs like both the planning and the
social aspect of it is stressing me out
so yeah I have one um set up for the
week after uh
Fest yeah one one and then I have um
asked jenma to reserve the studio on the
few days for solo streams as
well yeah maybe I'll add one more off
collab or so but really no stress don't
want
to don't want to yeah Force too much
I'll be back in Japan several times this
year anyway so
whatever yeah I will probably be staying
in Japan longer than most of the others
that are um coming from
overseas because I I have something to
do so I'll be staying a bit longer but
I'm trying to stream in the
[Music]
meantime
yeah also I'll meet I'll meet a certain
Pomeranian in Japan which is really
exciting
exciting can we hope for a
Suitor uh collab I don't
know um white day stream appearance I
think
so but it's not a real collab it's just
uh you know my Valentine's stream that
has been moved to White
day
yeah and just general off
stream tit will probably
commence you'll see you'll
see foradian let's
[Music]
go let's
go so uh Slavic fell you get a kiss for
that
Mah a Chu and a ped p no no p
p
motion d j d you crazy chicken your
attire I hope you won't be in the way of
other
people oh M fist hi M
fist
you I I
am I I had to laugh at you m fist
recently you are
funny you're funny Mist
fist you know what I
[Applause]
mean don't tell
me you are
I the story was so funny to me I even
told Ena the
story cuz it was so funny to me and she
thought it was funny
[Music]
too thanks runs
[Laughter]
away
[Music]
um one of the odds like for real like I
totally
[Music]
agree okay it's it's a story that I
think
I
it's it's fourth wall breaking and meta
so I'm I won't tell it it's your story
ask Mist fist about the
storyi
Theif
Hans thank you thank you for the sweet
[Music]
words oh by the way even if I finish the
stream now I I won't have anything to do
for the rest of the day so I'll just um
sign some Polaroids I'll finish them
I'll finish them I I am glad I can
finish them after all yeah and I'll be
opening them up for a white day again
and if you honestly if you got one
before I don't care you can get another
one if you want a different
[Music]
one if you want you can get
it I'm the Polaroid
finisher
yeah yeah I got time so I'll be
finishing them up I only have a few more
um from number three and all of number
twos but that's no issue no
issue you'll buy it in pre- chat so I
don't forget yeah you guys should uh if
you want one you should try to buy it in
pre-
[Music]
chat yeah yeah yeah Cruz than um thank
you the gamer cre thank you for the
pinky I wholeheartedly agree with Psy
hardworking communicative and a deep
trust in US are some of the strongest
traits you have and some of the reasons
why we love you so dearly no matter what
we'll always be here welcoming you back
with Open Wings a thank you thank you
thank
you I I'm really happy to hear that but
at the same time I I do understand that
March generally um and ever since my
break like a lot of the unexpected
things are happening this very trip I am
on right now was also something I didn't
know would happen until
recently
so everything's kind of crazy
um I wish I wish I could be
more you know streaming streaming with a
usual schedule I really wanted to stream
in a normal manner until up to Fest so
that between my break and Fest that I
would be streaming normally that was the
plan but things don't go according to
plan sometimes so please understand
things happen and often they're out of
my hand on on the on the other side what
I was doing for this stream uh for this
uh trip you will find out soon and you
will hopefully agree that it was worth
it for me it was worth it so you'll
you'll see you'll see soon enough
soon pretty soon this month actually so
my chat stopped moving again but I'll
just keep on
going um Jacob 47 than give me your
thanks for the pinky it's my third
birthday with kfp and I wanted to thank
you Wawa for being an inspiration to me
you and kfp have given me strength to
pursue my dreams I hope I can be an even
better fan for you in the future I'll
keep drawing W I love you forever thank
you please do
keep on drawing and there will be
Improvement and you'll feel so
accomplished and happy and proud I'm
sure of it so I'm looking forward to
your improvement as well is is this my
chat is still not moving so I'm kind of
worried that maybe the stream is dead
too going to wait for the chat but you
did hear me sing the Pokmon song
huh let me pour some tea cuz it's cold
again
[Music]
I keep on topping up the
tea oh you're moving again
hi hi
guys maybe it's because I'm not using
hyper chat right
now oh
well I've been drinking so much I really
need to go idle meeting but
whatever
hi
hi yeah I'm still motionless so yeah
give me a gamb bir day I'm happy that
you're doing you know the thing that you
enjoy and you're improving and happy
birthday of course
congratulations Michael H thank you soon
Studio Rob thanks for the pinky Studio
rob you little [\h__\h] you didn't answer
about the both you and the other person
hatch that I mentioned that sent a pinky
or
more during the polar word stream and
didn't uh tell me what they
want and then I made a community post
and asked for you guys and you still
didn't tell me what you want so I really
want to do something I'm just going to
probably end up making a Polaroid with a
random chicken and write your name on
and then you may not even realize that I
did that you maybe won't even know but
I'm going to do it cuz I'm
nice yeah I'm
nice give him the
diaper okay okay
okay don't say it like it's a a
punishment
don't say it like
that but thank you Studio
Rob thank you so much I will make you a
Polaroid I would be happy if you would
check out the Polaroid when I upload it
so that I didn't make it in
vain I know you didn't ask for it but
you know you sent a Super Chat and I
feel like I need to provide the
Polaroid raldi f suan d Michael h d d h
d Michael H D BL Parky ah dang thank you
for using my Art thank you for making it
I think cuz I reused the
thumbnail uh from before I didn't see
anymore who drew the the little Dave the
diver
Wawa so I couldn't credit you but um if
you guys can help me reply to the
thumbnail uh on on my Twitter with the
this artist's name if you have it on
Twitter let me know then I can like um
still add it onto
[Music]
it
me
H I don't know how to say the the Korean
name but come thank you so
much thank you Michael H D Nathan thank
you for the pinky uh hi nential popping
in on my break to see uh that to see
that you've already Dove super deep into
this game yeah literally good luck on
flexing your fishing and Sushi skills
thank you surprise surprise surprise yes
I got so far in like when did you come
into the stream 2 hours in or something
like that totally in two hours I I made
it I made Seven chapters it's a really
short game you
know really short game
my chat stop moving again a few seconds
ago makes me
anxious guys
H thank you Nathan for the
pinky bamboozle you have been
successfully
Bamboozled Migel Duran Dan looking for
the top Dan Evolution Dan sand no thank
you for the red super chat yo what's up
hello K I wish you a good day thank you
I wish you a wonderful day too thank you
so
much oh my chat is moving again let's
go I did yeah I do think it buffered a
little bit cuz I did see the kbps go
down for a
moment oh stream hasn't stopped for me
once okay that's good to know that's
happy happy
news ah anyway sand thank
you big kiss is that a is your profile
picture Chen from Ark nuts is it is it
someone from AR nuts am I wrong or am I
right I want to be
right naruta thank you for the red chat
as well hey boss I'm a bit late but I
wanted to celebrate my free anniversary
of being
kfp I'm usually a lurker but I wanted to
thank you for being so amazing and for
putting your heart into everything you
do is it is it I guess it I was
right it's her sticker I play nice so I
recognized it for putting your heart
into everything you do thank you for
being you and for being my Kam oi thank
you for letting me be your Kam
oi in the coming weekend I hope you get
to watch even if it's just online I hope
you get to watch the concert because I'm
going to be doing Oshi kind of things
just things that oshis do you know so
please check it out and thank you for
staying with kfb for such a long time
too D soon I appreciate it big support
feel free to lurk less come out of the
Shadows a bit more often anytime I would
be happy to see your name pop up here
and there thank you so much for the
support mAh
dark Manny
Sky Daisy
toast free strap thank
you
water space
waterfall yes there's extinct
animals so much yeah cool marine biology
yeah love it Sky dang Jim Tracy dang boo
73 dang you should play the endless
ocean games I've heard about them they
were announced for switch oh yeah yeah I
saw I saw the trailer yeah in
the wasn't it in the uh in the Nintendo
partner showcase thingy GD d Sean r d
Brandon Dan G Dan Rice of fre
Dan uh pyra H thanks for the pinky not
sure what to do but I doubt I'll be able
to watch too many streams in the next
two weeks but I am looking forward to
watching your stage one performance in
Michaela for real in the wiek oh it's so
crazy to hear like from kfp people who
are making the
pilgrimage this
year I feel like with every year there's
more obviously cuz like in the first one
Co was probably still stopping people
from doing the
pilgrimage in the first one where I was
part of but in the second one it was
getting more possible and now you guys
are motivated to do the
pilgrimage yeah anyway I'll be sure to
enjoy my time in Japan to my best yeah
please have a great time in the Holy
Land in the Holy Holy life LS you can
find a lot of merchandise and stuff
there
and many other things that are unrelated
to H life so please have a great time
take care I hope your travel goes well
uh and don't worry about not being able
to watch too many streams cuz I will
probably not be making too many streams
at least not in the coming week in the
one afterwards I'll try hard really my
chat stopped again by the way but I'm
just hoping everything's okay Richard G
thanks for the pinky hey K it's almost
been a year since I first interacted
with you in kfp and I wanted to say
thank you for being
my also I'm sorry about the very first
Super Chat I sent you it really gave a
bad impression good luck at the Fest yo
you're lucky I don't remember it I'm
sorry but I don't even remember it which
is good in this
case but now I'm kind of curious but
don't worry you saying I'm your commi
already swept away any bad memories I
could ever have so it's all okay
no
problem my birth memory yes it serves us
positively
y thank you for the support over the
time and yeah it's it's only been a year
or so in the beginning I thought a year
was really long but you know now so much
time has passed so you're still a little
baby to me Richard I hope that we'll
have a great time together in the next
months or years and you'll grow up from
baby to big chick yeah looking forward
to that thank you so much and and thank
you for the good luck wishes
G I will
G and you can't just rely on calling me
Kam Oshi when you make me mad no no no I
do regret it oh don't worry I really
don't remember it it it didn't
happen you mod thank you for the red of
chat hey kiaha my brother got me
watching stars with his telescope we saw
Jupiter and four of his moons why does
Jupiter have four moons what the [\h__\h]
Stardust star thep what and Galaxy M51
now I'm back to your stream and I see
another
star wow by the way hope you had a
wonderful day happy International woman
say wow thank you that is some big Riz
right there holy [\h__\h] tuper has 20 plus
moons what why let's like give others
some moons why don't we have more than
one what the
hell what the hell that's not
[Music]
fair how is that fair how is that fair
the size is Jupiter much bigger than
Earth excuse me for asking I only know
things about the ocean not about the
space
dot dot dot I hate you guys for dot dot
dotting me mun maker okay
okay
okay I get it okay I mean yeah what
whatever I I I I heard before that Earth
is pretty
small shut
up
they're so mean to me why do I even
stream a leral gas
giant
[Music]
well
okay Earth is the fourth smallest
smallest planet well at least from the
ones that we know of that
are comprehensive whatever
whatever let's just talk ocean okay
let's not talk space let's talk ocean
talk ocean to
me average crap cor enjoyer what a
name what the [\h__\h] is
crabcore anyway thank you so much UF mod
I must say your Riz your Riz is off the
roofs today thank
you Moon thank you for the red super
chat I finally got my free Year back
badge a few days ago it will be my
birthday tomorrow oh my God I just want
to give back to say thanks for streaming
and being a great oie I wish for you to
have a lot more happiness this year
thank you I hope so too and I wish you
also happiness a lot of it let's be
happy together and happy birthday in
advance cuz I won't be streaming
tomorrow Happy Birthday
woo woo woo woo woo I need to go I don't
eating so
[Music]
bad I'm going to explode okay I'm going
to go now to idle meeting
BRB I can't hold this
[Music]
anymore
okay I'm
back why did my chat has been stopped
since before oh now it's moving since
before I went to the toilet uh idle
meeting now it's suddenly
moving H
hello I wonder if Ena is still
[Music]
sleeping it's
been a long time since I've seen her
awake she didn't she didn't come down
you guys didn't hear Tako
[Music]
toi
okay sleep well
[Music]
Ena
style apparently that uh reached another
Milestone of
views on
YouTube brain empty
Style
yeah 8 million thank you for 8 million
on brain empty
Style no tanky
style Alig
goas So yeah thank you uh to moon dog
again for three years happy birthday and
let's yeah let's have a great year
hopefully Let me refresh cuz that was
where it ended
originally Flappy boy thank you for the
re chat another Hol mom checked off Dave
the DI vanquished in record speed lots
of adorable moments to be remembered and
some new found motivation for Kiana to
get back into drawing overall this
special trip to Tacko town has been a
tremendous success already
tremendous tremendous H you sound like
Trump
thank you yeah I I I checked that one
off of my list
quickly thank God I think it would have
been a long a long series to do on
stream I probably normally I don't think
I would have considered it as a
streaming game I just kind of like one
time I was like going through the uh
Nintendo switch store I was like I need
something I wonder if there's something
that's like chill enough but not too
chill that's kind of engaging but not
too
engaging and then I went through and I I
found David the dive and I was like
maybe I can give it a try like I heard
so many good things about
it and I gave it a try and it was the
perfect game for what I needed in
my yeah off time I feel like my chat is
just constantly stopping let me
open not the studio chat but like the
the normal chat I just like YouTube is
actually crashing on Me YouTube Studio
probably the what's it
called the cash it's
over dendo is dendo has a Princess Peach
video up is it already
released I want to play princess
Beach I think oh the chat is stopping
for you
too huh nah oh the demo okay thank God 2
weeks then we can play it when I'm back
from Japan I
think immediately it will be our back
from Japan game besides Yakuza and yeah
just
yaku I want to play it right away I
don't care here peach in am's outfit
what do you mean Amy in Peach's
outfit yeah many Mario games
yeah yeah we can play Peach during the
week and Yakuza on the
[Music]
weekend I should play that game it's
her so okay well thank you uh Flappy
boy not just another Holo mom checked
off was that my first Holo dad
too did I
meet did I meet any I mean I met um Hol
dads as in like artists but when when we
talk about blood related
families I
think I think that was my first Hol
dad I've met some artists but like not
flesh
dads no no no just moms ah no actually
no coobo also didn't meet the coobo dad
no
no just coobo mama and cobal
brother flesh
[Music]
dad in the
flesh hm why are Hol dads so
rare why are why are they so
[Music]
rare
H please don't call it
FR what Hol siblings have you
met uh I I video chatted with Nissa
sister one of them um but I guess that
wouldn't count I
Met m
well kobo's a
[Music]
brother
and who
[Music]
else I didn't me ananus
m- no no no
siblings Callie siblings I didn't
meet just heard
about her sister I don't I don't think I
met
her um huh wait let me no
no oh NOP narissa almost met my
brother which uh was
interesting like was this before or
[Music]
after before we got went to the moldes
or after thanks for the raid before we
went to the mives or after we went to
the mives um my my brother he had a a
key he has a key right so he was going
to I think
uh he was it what was he going to do
pick up something or so uh and he
thought we wouldn't be there and I was
just like I think narissa was like
sleeping yeah I think she was sleeping
and then I um I was just like cleaning
the living room or something and then
suddenly I hear the door opening and I
also didn't expect anyone coming so I
was like what the [\h__\h] who is who is
opening my door right now and then it
was my brother I'm like what are you
doing here and he's like what are you
doing here I'm like well I live here
and then I was like oh you know nissa's
here right now she's sleeping so what do
you want what do you
need so he just picked up some stuff and
ah oh I think it was like
uh we weren't supposed to be there
originally but then something got
delayed and I did tell him about that
but um he didn't see that or he didn't
remember so he thought he had to come to
feed the cat but uh turns out he didn't
have to but I did update him he just
didn't see it and then he came for
nothing basically but I still gave him
some things to pick up
yeah yeah and then I didn't want to wake
up N I didn't want to make it awkward
for Nissa or for my brother so I didn't
offer anybody to meet each other I just
like gave my brother what he needed and
tried to stay somewhat quiet and then he
was gone and then then I was like hi hi
hi Nissa and she's like oh who was it
I'm like yeah that was my brother she's
like oh I thought I heard something
yeah yeah I think she was like in
pajamas and everything so
uh I don't think she would have been
ready
mentally Pro to always getting kicked
out no he was too
early he shouldn't have been
there it's okay though even like I
wouldn't have mind it my uh my mom met
narissa so it's
fine yeah bro it's only waiting outside
in the
C
wait I I don't even remember why we did
that
anymore I don't even remember that
anymore wow it's cold outside let me
in no no it's not that it's not like
that it's not so
bad I didn't I
ah was that so long ago where he was
staying over in my
place yeah cuz he didn't have an
apartment yet I think he was on the
lookout and I I needed to stream but I
also didn't want to want him to to hear
me so I always had him like go
away
yeah something like that yeah he was job
hunting and apartment
hunting after his bu that's so long ago
it doesn't feel that long ago even
though I don't remember
it it doesn't feel that long ago
what
crazy so okay enough tangent thank you
Flappy B
yeah it was a success that was very
chaotic and kind of crazy and
surreal why it was surreal you will know
more soon please look forward to the
tangent Sky thanks for the pinky Teno
can you sing poker dance I did I did so
hey Bo Bo let's
go hey boogie boogie bang bang let's go
boom boom I asked for permission to
cover it even do a dance cover or a
dance and song cover and I'm waiting to
hear
back cuz now I'm like more and more
figuring out my accent suit and the
finger tracking I got the finger
tracking
going um I just kind of need to make all
the trackers more like stable cuz yeah
the ones on my upper back apparently are
ruining some things cuz they like they
are kind of loose on the shirt
M no but generally it looks pretty
good I
think have you figured out the stream
streaming option no no idea yet I need
to like try after after the Fest
afterwards
no I'll try and maybe there will be a
gorilla stream if I can get it go
ziply D corl Dan iron V
than yeah it is a shame thank you I need
some cat time for
real I really need it Els La thank you
yeah they're making so much art some of
that I haven't even seen before the the
the kiata and MAA one I didn't see that
before they didn't show it to me I just
saw it now when I made the
Tweet but yeah so much officialish waa
art wow we're we're getting
spoiled a naan Westland thank you
g um thank you you be let's
go may go away in Japan best of luck
than thank you oh you're doing a watch
along let's go that sounds like fun I
hope I hope you'll have a good time
watching together mafin eight thanks for
the pinky I hope you can get a day with
the cats that sounds pretty stressful
yep yep yep yep but at least you got an
extra day with Ena looking forward to
fifth F sounds like this stream will end
the same as the Twitter audio Ena
uploaded when you
arrived oh no no it didn't I went I
went a few minutes ago so
[Music]
it didn't quite end like that it could
have but it didn't every cult T and back
is t r t oh there's oh there's so many
flush I haven't seen so many flush chats
in a while guys cuz you guys have been
slacking with the flush
chats wow so many flush chats in a
row
Unwritten r d just another
D um yep that's
it that's it that's it I just came back
too
quickly I
finish I probably have super chats from
the taco to stream
though we can read that but then you
guys going to add more Super chats onto
this one and I have to go back to this
[Music]
one
they're probably not going to be many
so we can finish it fast for
sure okay the Mario stream with
Ina Jacob 47 Dan Sky Dan The Gamer cre
Dan J swag book D swag B spam thanks for
the red super chat I've never been to an
idol
meeting in my life nor have my cats I've
never been invited to an idle
meeting I I I I wish I could invite you
but yeah I
shouldn't but you don't even know you're
an idol you just have to believe in it
and then it will automatically become
Idol meetings you just have to think of
yourself as an idol and then you'll be
having idle meetings all the time more
than you're asking for more than you
want so enjoy enjoy M what why you guys
so freaking out what what what what
what what I didn't I told him to have
his own Idol
meetings are you guys freaking
out rine D Elsie l d take it mon let
[Music]
love ah okay yeah that's what you meant
my line let's take the helicopter when
it's a
plane big freaking
Bamboozled they gaslighted
me so
rude thank you jail bird Lord Commander
AR Mund I am a beep actually have a
beep small XLR
beeps that are uh gentle on your
ears so
nice beep yay we miss the G our Beep
don't
we small
beep yeah I am a I am a che
Dan this is now nostalgic
almost Goose of the
small you have a goose picture cute alar
d j d m a d Cruz D and you reminded me
of the goose du du Goose or Goose goose
duck I don't know cuz I I looked up the
game and I first looked it up wrong and
uh it showed me a different game on
Steam there's Goose go duck and there's
duck duck
goose but yeah in case you guys didn't
see I uh participated
[Music]
in
I participated in that collab with
mostly ID and
am and it was fun I'm sorry I I I I I I
should have streamed but it would have
made things a bit more complicated and
stressful I was just I was just chilling
I was nice
though yeah there were some funny
moments but you guys have to look at all
povs to find them if you go check out
Way's SP I think you'll find some
moments uh as
well
yeah yeah I would have had a POV if um I
was streaming from home I would have
done it
then but you
know uh the unarchived K had one Super
Chat by the way thank you Jacob 47 for
um sending one
there and pal world I think did I have
that uh was I caught up
there oh let me see does that sound
familiar to
me oh actually that
doesn't I haven't
huh okay they're not that much either
let me do it check for the seven d l
moon thanks for the pinky for the red
one don't you hate it when your tart
comes from there oh oh it's pretty rough
you forced my hand T you I had to do it
or the voices wouldn't
stop yeah the a't a
start oh I think I'm going to eat some
Tarts but not anus Tarts obviously no
like a blueberry tart or something like
that would be nice Cy
stamps oh Lou M kissy Psy danash Cream X
Games danash your lunch money no I don't
want to take your lunch money take it
back no side
D Salah Commander d v
faction danar
danar Dan Michael H Dan H thank you for
the pinky but the message was
deleted I wonder what that said cuz I
think you were
weren't you
nice or wait wait I
can ah no the Super Chat was deleted
maybe cuz like it was originally a
wordless Super Chat I'm confused it
[Music]
says how can you delete the message from
a wordless Super
Chat was the Super Chat deleted I don't
know what this
means all of their supas get deleted
maybe it's like a card problem a card
issue
but yeah they deleted themselves right
cuz this person isn't seeing isn't
writing anything that would get them
like
[Music]
banned I wonder well thank you ah anyway
for the
[Music]
pinky he the guard Dan
a thank you that's a sweet message I'm
I'm Sorry by the way whenever like I
talk about like me feeling old I don't
want to like imply anyone else's old you
know how it is you kind of like see like
feel more like stressed out about your
own age and then you're not really you
don't really mean like anyone else is
old you just feel like stressed out cuz
you notice you're getting older and and
it's yabby it's so
stressful you're like I want to do this
and this and this I didn't get to do it
until now like you know there's certain
things in my life that I would have
wanted to do that are kind of
like time
limited kind of
so due to things like that I feel too
old now cuz those time limited things
are not really possible
anymore not I would wouldn't say I'm
generally old but you
know
yeah don't worry I only gets worse don't
say that none of us is getting any
younger why
not M told us the fres are in
theand what a
c what a cop I mean every age is in man
some
people maybe want the
30s no that's always a
demand not not in my demand though not
in my
[Music]
demand although I don't like I don't
want to
be
whatever I am in theand
yeah I mean I know I'm in demand I am in
demand I'm in your demand for example
probably I know I am in
demand what a weird
conversation I'm not worried about not
being in demand that's not my concern
it's more like a
self stress
problem like oh my God I only have so
many days in my life left that I can
cuddle with cats you
know that kind of demand and only so
many days left to you
know just like follow how the world is
progressing that's like the the biggest
fomo you could possibly
have the biggest fomo you could possibly
have is
like yeah missing out
on technological advances and whatever
and science ien ific advant advances in
life maybe in 200 300 years we don't
have to die anymore but everybody's
who's already dead missed out on
it freaking
sucks but I'm I think generally I'm
happy to live at this time um
Although our life is one big for more
yes
no I I generally am happy to live at
this time
but I would have also liked to live
[Music]
in the
hundreds in England
ideally although I would probably die
from some
plague probably would
but maybe there's a small chance that I
would have been born
as emblin although that is obviously
not the best life to live but I would
have been
fabulous I would have been
[Music]
fabulous and I would have been iconic
and I would have birthed a future Queen
that everybody would have underestimated
until she became Queen and even
after
so I'm fabulous and iconic
now thank you of course I am I guess but
I mean it would have been a different
fabulous and iconic
whatever uh melang star D thank you come
clever name thank
you you'll never forget me wow
H
maybe you for the
pinky
D and that's it for the pal World Super
chats now I'm going back to today's
super chats
so yep yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep um El name the pinky adding on to my
my load of subjects true we would add
more supp to the stream yeah there we go
um that was for science right we have
proved it thank you Nathan you're part
of science G D golden i d o o you know R
lunchbox and pudding
Channel pudding Channel you finally made
a new um clip of me thank you I enjoyed
it it was very enjoyable guys got
putting channnel Channel cuz um there's
a new hour clip so go go go go go sky
thank you than you
soon so I'll see you guys soon
[Music]
okay and I'll do some polar voids after
chilling for a little
bit yeah soon soon soon soon soon
soon today was fun thank you it was fun
for me too I'm just like really
satisfied that I have finally
accomplished the biggest bamboozle of
them all you can never say again that I
can't play games off stream I can but I
can if I have
time and if I you know find one that you
know fits the
vibe but yeah when when streaming games
is your job then you tend to not have
the mood or the time to do so off
[Music]
stream I didn't finish it off that is
true CU I did it to bamboozle
[Music]
you yeah it is true it is
true
there's nothing to prove
really there's no need for me to do this
more
often although if I go on another break
I might find another game to waste my
time
with I spent so much time with I don't
even know I feel like it's more than 30
hours I don't know why this game is
telling me I played only 30 hours I feel
like it was like 50
hours no try St your well no although I
do have the game cuz I bought it for my
mommy but then she didn't need it cuz
she already had it and yeah so I have it
in my
steam
oh n Maya in your KN has descended
descended oh what
what oh okay I think
my um is is getting a
breakfast almost Taco Time I think it's
still a little bit too early for Taco
Time can't believe it's at the very
end tell her we say
hi they say
[Music]
hi they that that mic is not picking
that
up she says hi
kfp Ina you know this whole stream I was
streaming with a
p& because uh
after you put in the password I
installed the app and I even had it open
and I even like changed costumes and
whatever but then there was some problem
with the G I had to restart the PC and
the laptop and then when I restarted it
it was as if if the program was never
installed in the first place it was gone
and I needed the password again but I
didn't want to wake you up immediately
afterwards again so I just streamed with
a PNG the whole
time
wow what did you get for
Brey a spaghetti
spaghetti spaghetti for
Brey what kind of spaghetti just spag
just spaghetti plain spaghetti no
probably not but let's
imply spaghetti
spaghetti spaghetti Italian breakfast no
no no no no no
no Squid Ink spaghetti no no no probably
not okay okay tell we say w okay they
say w w she she wed back
[Music]
W yeah she'll just uh put her own Squid
Ink onto her spaghetti that's why she
got plain
spaghetti
weird okay she's she's taking the
spaghetti and
um leaving but I'm leaving you guys
too what the hell is switch cartridge
spaghetti what what
what oh oh seems like uh Ina knowledge
secret
knowledge yeah a glimpse into ena's
morning yeah well eating breakfast
that's how I how how most people spend
their
mornings as long as you're not leaving
on a jet plane we're fine cuz I'm
[Music]
leaving on a private jet
no I wish AR's 41 months thank you k no
no oh no the
Panic the absolute
PTSD I'm
sorry
here I sneezed it to your face to make
up for
it go okay I'll be going
now
y the Elgato died
anyway 38 months thank you so much oh my
God come on buz I'm already sick I'm
sorry but then it doesn't matter right
you can't you can't put sick on sick
thank you for the Super Chat star
Creator
and today is over polar wordss
later uh I'll see you again soon enough
and in German we
say in German we
say I
[Music]
don't worry I'll be back I'll be
back byebye thank you for
watching
hey
hey boogie boogie bang bang I I I
switched the the A's and the those
hey body bang bang no hey boogie boogie
bang bang let's go
body hey Bo bang bang let's
go hey you are my M
my hey you are my M my body o hey you my
M
my you my mama my body
be my body clap clap clap be my body
come on let's
[Music]
dance no no no
hi
oo they say oo at the end of the song
please listen to it now with that
knowledge o
[Music]
bye