[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
have you ever played before
this is my first time I like just bought
the game wait like ever ever or just
online oh I've played like real Uno with
cards like in my hand was stacking
before
no I don't even know what that is so we
have stacking turned on and what that
means is that uh there's the plus two
plus four kind of thing if if Eno puts a
plus two down and Cali and I have a plus
two it'll stack to the plus four to
whoever's afterwards
are we ready ready
[Music]
like everybody looks so different but
these are all our 2022 outfits
yeah okay leave it to me my green
because green is a nice color hold on
under appreciated color
but in Japan The Color of Money is
yellow oh really oh yeah I have no
choice
huh
oh
yikes my hand is really shitty by the
way what's that means
oh how daring are you feeling
I think you get a plus four if you don't
put a blue card on it or something
I don't know
I'm just guessing I'm just guessing
let's go with the flow what do you think
I'm never gonna win this one yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah that one's good yeah yeah
okay
just for now ah you're checking if that
person is bluffing
[Music]
what I don't remember either
oh wow you blocked my turn
are we doing it one choice yeah I'd say
so we're doing it
thrown into the ice water green yeah
so is that like if
[Music]
okay
I'm reverse reverse you can only play a
plus four if you can't play anything
else oh yeah okay so it's like you're
testing if they're bluffing because if
they could have played anything else and
still played the plus four get skipped
they shouldn't be doing that yeah shut
up then
[Music]
expose them
thank you Chad for reminding us
but you probably know right you know
that's pretty good yeah yeah yeah okay
[Music]
uh wait what do I what do I do when I
get when I when I can running out of
time yeah because I can't get a card
Fine Again
card
ew okay okay it's been a while since Uno
okay yeah
why do we really want to play Uno it
doesn't let me get it
or do we have a gun yes
I panicked yeah
we don't have any green cards
challenge you because I believe it
there's
Barnacle farts I didn't mean to
oh do you think they're they're best
it's mind games yes
I guess we'll find out
[Music]
um
we'll have to pick up a card now right
stop the tablet
okay nice plate you know nice nice Kelly
it's you and me against three what the
heck
last two
oh
yay
oh the music is so Jazzy
apples
that's what we like to see we still
remember
we'll be at each other's throws in the
next round
Ian is running out of cards
oh true
[Music]
I don't know
cards
YouTube
[Music]
is there a saying in English like the
one we have in German that says
like having a special card up your
sleeve oh yeah
a trick oh okay
do something once I had a tricker please
up your sleeves
yeah
you guys are focused on trying to get up
again what happens the people who are
next to her must make sure that she
doesn't get to get rid of the cars
[Music]
oh okay makes me want to go to I got a
good one the Big M
anything uh no immediate Revenge let's
just be chill free
we're chilling oh oh the seating is the
same as before huh yeah
mmm play it safe for now
why not
[Music]
oh Tango
okay that's how you're gonna do
I'm feeling ketchup okay okay
what do you girls put on a hot dog catch
that mustard or something else
relish pickles
so much we've ever had a Chicago hot dog
it's just relish and mustard oh yeah
good I like
I like them oh
oh I saw a list of like worldwide hot
dogs and there's like some crazy ones
out there
I want to try them all yeah
oh no I know
a card for me for a hot dog
oh yeah I'm kind of getting hungry
last four okay
take it
take the plush bar what if we say to
[Laughter]
climbing
yeah
no I don't want it I'm glad we didn't
challenge them
what happens do you you have to have
four cards of the same color or
something no no no no if you want to
challenge it that means you doubt that
they had no other card to play oh
and if you were wrong then you get the
four I guess but also if you if you just
leave it the way it is
you couldn't play a different card yeah
but you didn't even know that this is
what happens yeah
but yeah seeing how it works in in
practice will make you learn how it
works easier
did you girls have okay another hot dog
question did you guys have a Korean hot
dog before because that [\h__\h] is amazing
yes
cheese inside or other things at their
top of like for example potatoes or
ramen noodles and stuff it's amazing but
I've seen it like rolled in sugar before
that's kind of yeah
oh it's so good the sweetness is really
good
oh God I wasn't paying attention
can I do this wait
wait what I don't know
you can do it she could play yeah but if
she if she could have played the other
card then it would have been okay
you have better luck challenging if they
have a ton of cards
[Music]
let's go see how it is that's how it is
probably good well I'm sorry I didn't
answer
seven lucky what color does Ina have
oh
yeah
he comes in handy having so many cards
I respect it
is playing the game very correctly right
now
that's it
[Music]
come on
wait so I have to pick one that doesn't
have uh no no did you have a green to
play before you just played this
because then you're in trouble then
you're in trouble answer that don't
answer that
don't answer it but um if you have no
other green card then
okay I think I get it now yeah
oh
it still has to draw okay so she doesn't
have yellow
[Music]
I mean you know look
I'll go for this uh-huh you say it as if
you had such a big Choice oh
yeah right
I'm giving you a chance on me
there's so many cards
yeah
thank you for changing the color color
yeah yeah yeah why is she laughing
let's go
[Music]
is
still she's down to Green again she only
has green right now so don't bring it to
Green
are you sure about that I'm pretty sure
yeah no green right and no red maybe
um
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
hey Uno I forgot there's a little button
before you play the card
yeah is it before before you played it
okay [\h__\h]
come on man you've had enough
[Music]
bad luck no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no not green
snow green
uh does she have friends wait Kelly this
is the play
yeah she doesn't have red she doesn't
have blue what the [\h__\h] it's okay
I've read no more this is still the
plate right good draw again yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
oh
[Music]
good place get back in Indiana we're not
done with you yet
not yet
no no oh no sorry I have phone it is
oh there we go okay now we have to get
Kiara bye
everyone no no
changing target shoot no oh
oh okay again yes yes yes yes
oh how the tables turn oh how to turn
tables oh
no
okay
this is nothing for us
all right absolutely nothing
[Music]
's on the table now isn't it
nothing for me what is
oh nice okay okay
there are no team ups here Lee me and
girl are the trash
hello hello not nice what's your
favorite number I'm coming back uh the
round one
down
[Applause]
I mean that one's extremely round
the Snowman double around
okay eight
[Music]
okay nice huge it's getting dangerous
oh
shoot keep keep it keep it yellow thank
you because I will help us no okay no no
okay I have something for tattoo yeah
[Music]
now I had lost track of track of what
she has no that's bad well we're going
back to green
do you like it do you like Green we love
green here
um
[Music]
okay that's that's a new color guys deal
with it deal with it okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
well green is membership color it's a
nice color I'll bring it back
[Music]
this is gonna be a plus four
okay
plus plus four okay I guess what I was
going to get
and I totally that would have been nice
wouldn't it
[Music]
um
now why am I getting all the cards again
seems like everybody's struggling right
now oh sorry except for Inno
but anyways
not again not again
blue taco
yeah yeah
she got the plus four or what
that works unless one
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
I'm not taking that I will stack yeah
[Applause]
she will never
[Music]
oh my God I feel bad
um
yeah maybe I couldn't hear you I just
think it's gonna It's Gonna Change up a
little too much someone's gonna flip the
script okay not coming back Amber what
are the odds
what are they all right damn it yeah
[Music]
I know I got green because I believe in
green green is beautiful
and green green is the color of dinosaur
yeah
why do you know we have children it was
already
[Music]
made her draw six cards
oh Emma is getting close soon
it turns tabled again
we have brains as well so we can
remember too yeah once we get a card
yeah
[Music]
look at this what
you are not done yet Madame
oh no
no no no no no no
like this
going the other way
oh
more green
it can't be anymore so much green all my
cards were green okay sorry color change
has to be are you
okay what do we do Shrek dick yeah play
it I mean screw it whatever okay
oh
Oh Mamma Mia what a surprise
oh yeah that's right okay
that's a nine okay in German we say nine
when we say no nine and I say no blue
oh wow
so you don't like yellow I'll remember
that yeah
oh time is running out you up to you
okay okay
wait is this a good idea I don't know
[Applause]
guys like my chance is this it winner is
this it
is
bring it back we're gonna top deck are
you ready for this Cali
be nice to me
doesn't she have
Kelly
Maybe
she has red I swear to God
[Music]
okay not bad not bad
don't let her
let me
please I don't think she has red is the
thing so maybe we should play a
different one I
um
[Music]
color change again
it's so colorful such a rainbow we
really the enemy right here
well me and Tina have the same amount of
cards now but not anymore
[Music]
[Applause]
I thought she wouldn't have yellow and
she'd had to take another I had two
yellows yeah
[Music]
all right that was a good sign that was
really intense really entertaining
wow that hand's got cards in it it sure
does yep a little plus four off the bat
wait what why do I pick a color what is
the point of that because
that's what that's what the car does
changes the color okay
uh
but you must have understood the meaning
of this card by now right I get it right
I get it so I'm not gonna challenge you
because I think you probably understand
I don't have any other yellow so I put
it down okay okay well then that's
correct that's correct I get it I get it
should we start this early
yeah almost started early oh thank you
yo
[Music]
yo yo soldier boy you
um
yeah I love that
you lucky number yeah
yeah it's mori's lucky number yes is you
the new tomorrow
yes oh red yeah
yeah
I like all the colors everything is fine
on my hands
hey let's go oh wow
they cannot stand kids
oh I have so many choices but I'll go
for this oh okay
yeah all right all right
[Music]
why not
but if we change it up on them
[Music]
money colors
I don't know about that oh
yellow
the color that made me win last time
I believe in it I trust it that's so
perfect
oh because I did a reverse
true take this oh my God
I hope that arrives safely
aren't those cards beautiful me okay
we'll do it we'll do this one we'll play
safe yeah yeah that seems good is that a
six okay that's a six blue
wow
did you just say blow I did oh oh my God
she's so German I know you
good good dad I didn't do German class
uh instead of my game show because you
you would be top of the class anyway
you would know it all you know even
though we have three red cards let's
just draw a card you know yeah
what we're keeping it that makes no
sense
uh-huh
uh-huh yellow look at me I'm Watson I'm
playing a yellow yellow down
why would you good Let's Line this up
huh literally the exact one yeah okay
um
we're lining up the Wombo
okay
oh nice nice
[Music]
that could have been nice
wait stop playing with the rules where
you draw until you get a playable card
huh yeah apparently not no that's fine
though that's fine that's fine that's
what got me stuck in a three-hour long
game
um
yellow top deck oh
yeah I'm sorry no no
oh no not today no
no no no no no I don't tell I refuse
it's okay I can't win twice in a row
I'll win the next time
[Music]
impossible no green what was the other
color yellow that she didn't have hey
hey what's the aggression what's the
mild aggression going on there
we have every color yeah oh yeah sure
except for great things
and there's four colors and you're
selling you're saying you have every
color yeah I really like the color green
the color of mine here
what does Kiara like green she does not
I don't know not today nice not now I
don't like I don't like blue either
damn shots
it was good but not today
unlucky color
um I'm feeling like rainbow today all
right
I want to see a color a different color
each turn I know oh no hey
what the what do they have left
what could they have oh you need to turn
this around because otherwise they're
about to win I have no choice I think I
hope they don't have red
we do
oh
yeah
keep the red keep the red I I can indeed
keep the Reds but there's uh free
players with two cards right now okay so
I don't know who I want to help okay I
don't know well I'll continue this
another card and another one
another one
and another one I
[Music]
I don't even know anymore yeah it's
whatever
[Music]
we can put this one you don't sound very
happy about the yellow just now make her
skip make her skip
does alma have yellow she doesn't okay
okay okay
are we gonna have a three-man Uno
what do we do what do we do
I don't know girl I don't know
[Music]
the second wind player how could you let
it happen
um
[Music]
can't believe we only have one color
a single color you say all green all the
greens Let's test it do you have more
greens
I mean
oh
we're thinking long term I didn't know
it lets you pull a card when you have
something anyway yeah
yeah
you can pull it you can pull it mine so
get rid of all those veggies now get
them out of the bag
[Music]
um
got more of those yellows
I think any yellows do this oh they're
struggling again
yeah the topic
[Music]
take those
those beautiful balance has been
restored uh-huh uh-huh
I don't know
do it this might be a fast game
oh [\h__\h]
which one will it be
I don't know up to you just what is it
oh you don't have any red girl what I
meant to Red
uh they're bluffing they're fluffy
[Laughter]
so they do have red right yeah
no or what surely they do who's
pretending to be super transparent are
you sure about that yes
[Applause]
[Music]
don't worry guys
one more time
[Music]
right now
get out of here
and the stream and the stream Kuda so
that's just
[Laughter]
let's just play what about this dream
that's better let's move yeah oh is it
my chair oops
all right
uh okay
okay
a fresh start
it's so nice to just start off a fresh
fresh run yeah
yeah
still has a big hand you know we're good
we're safe
don't let it go anywhere near like free
cards
Too Late by that time
I miss vibing the tropical sounds are
you guys hearing the same music
yeah tropical right yeah
what happened oh
oh you're keeping her far away from yeah
okay yeah
[Music]
let's go
we could we're relaxing we can do this
and then this and then yeah and then
this okay that's a good idea well I got
this
fudge
it doesn't change
thank you thank you okay Amy has two
Army has two okay
wait the fact that she played that I
want uh what's happening
decline I guess
I believe you I don't think that these
two cuties would lie to me yeah
of course never what the [\h__\h] they will
not please
play the card
no
yes yes no no
[Music]
do they have more blue I wonder
I'm not gonna say oh nice
they have blue they have blue
red red nice okay you better be you
better have chosen the right color there
I hope so what do we do this yeah do it
right yeah
[Music]
okay so they have blue in their hand do
we think so it could be yellow it's too
late for me to think about winning
anyway so I'll take the cards I'll take
the ball I'll take the fall until we
learned how to mind the game now
do we have
skip them
[Music]
are they gonna win
wait they they change it to Blue right
so they have blue
ah
[Music]
I'm gonna need to win guys
win one more everybody wins in in myth
let's go all the winners
no losers
great
right off the bat okay it's okay if it's
in the beginning that doesn't matter
it gives you more hands to play you know
exactly more more variety I'm a variety
streamer I love variety
[Music]
okay
that's looking at a lot of greens yeah
like all the Green in the deck yellow
I want yellow yellow
[Music]
like a pineapple no yellow on this one
okay hello
hello everybody seems to agree hey hey
and then
and then yeah
no
okay okay
all right I see
you're getting there
oh okay is that an e-guitar going crazy
there in the back or you know an e-base
okay
that's a trumpet how do we do this
[Music]
Maybe
so wait or do we want the next color
that they picked this one
yeah so the last card that they have is
green
wow it would be weird for them tonight
[Music]
supposed to be my name there's no
possibility oh that's all you guys
how could you do this to me I have the
perfect solution here
hey oh nice
no no
no no no
[Music]
sleep
no is that really the perfect solution
is cheating that she must be cheating
how is this possible this is like the
perfect win
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
oh my God
we need one more we said all the time we
have
is this the real mips
girl you have some things to say right
uh oh yeah no actually I guess no okay
okay okay sorry sorry
I'm gonna play aggressive now okay
aggressiveness okay
wait no no
I see we got skills
mm-hmm
aggressive color red hmm
yeah I think we should just aggressive
oh
you think that will help you now yeah
yeah yeah
it'll feel good having you know draw
four cards yeah
[Music]
can you really
oh
wow
not today
okay
interesting hey you still shared it even
though you were right yeah what the heck
it's rigged rigged
it's interesting
but I I respect your courage and the
guts to yes challenge here I called her
Bluff yeah
a lesson
mm-hmm
hmm
and feel like yeah
is this I feel like our game doesn't
feel like it it doesn't feel like our
game because it's Amy's game okay yeah
[Music]
my game is my game is next stream
that is that is also true yeah yeah yeah
yeah I miss game I'm his mom is the
bullying again yep yep
oh sorry
I mean
there's also this possibility
a nice team up here a nice team up yeah
yeah yeah yeah that gives me PTSD
all right
shoot I have a lot to choose let's go
why Toto
no
la la la la la what a close one okay so
she doesn't have any blue she doesn't
have any blue
no blue yellow
nice okay
get ready
oh what is it I'm hovering is it the
Duos
um
oh wait it was my turn
oh
it's okay
oh no I hope it's not yellow what do we
do yeah
uh I think I think we should
play it
[Applause]
now
[Music]
I guess that's where it ends
okay get out of this game wow now we're
in the chatting room to say goodbye
chatting room
what's next for us uh next we have the
grand finale yeah
Amelia Watson's channel is surprised
and announcements so please look forward
to them yes what announcements all right
you guys are gonna get redirected you're
gonna Zoom right over to Watson so we'll
see well we'll see yeah uh we might need
just a few minutes to set up but yeah
we'll go over there hopefully it should
work because I think I set it up right
um yeah we did we did okay okay see you
thank you
bye everyone bye bye whoa whoa whoa