[Music]
generation two
and welcome to rush stream the stream
will be very very short because
uh yeah because yeah because
i didn't stream this morning so i want
to like do a little stream
guys
[Music]
i don't know what we're gonna do today i
feel like a bunch of people are actually
streaming rusty i'm open mic so like if
if people pass by they'll be able to
hear me i mean i can turn it off but
also i'm kind of like i'm kind of like
lazy
um
i don't know guys
uh
[Laughter]
mike
okay this stream i don't know what we're
gonna do honestly
well
i think we're gonna
just
i don't know
tidy up our inventory and then i wanna
talk to you guys
yes yes yes yes yes yes
yeah guys so if you see here
in this one um my house is good for
another 10 days 10 days it's like sunday
monday
tuesday
wednesday
thursday thursday the server will be
white so this is more than enough
this is more than enough
um
i'm gonna
go uh i wanna
research stuff
i might
need to
what should i research
i have a lot of weapons yes i do i play
it offline a little bit
sponsored this is sponsored by anya
melfissa actually do you want to like
sort this first
yeah so actually yesterday
i went with anya melfissa
to
i don't know we went uh
boating
yeah and then we went to the
oil rig place essentially
i think um
we're gonna
try again because we we didn't succeed
we died at the very end
so i don't know maybe we're gonna try
again
and i found some loots
found some loots which is great
um
should i research i don't think i should
research telephone cause i'm lazy
but
my inventory is so messy
how do i
make this not messier
how do you guys how do people actually
manage their inventory i feel like you
know or maybe they use the fridge to
you know do stuff like that
i also want to upgrade my house i also
want to upgrade my house to stone while
we still have time but the thing is i
don't know how to farm for stone
like they say people say it's like oh
maybe it's near the place where
um
it's near the place where where there's
uh snow
but i don't know guys
i don't know
i just put my scraps here
what should i research i don't actually
know
long sword long sword's good right i
already researched this i already
researched the
thingy c4
like i need to research either c4 or
like one of the guns
or something
yeah
you can store the c4 in the tc god dang
okay
okay so this is gonna be like for
weapons i think weapons and clothes
so anything weapon related they go here
and i see
i think
let's just like do it like this like
cubes
these are bullets
any other
let's
[Music]
guys i'm so confused how do people like
arrange this this looks so
bad
this looks bad how how do people arrange
their inventory
we don't need blueberries
certainly not okay these are weapons so
certainly not this certainly not this
certainly not this
certainly not this either
[Music]
wait where's my hammer
oh i think i hel i left the hammer in
the tower i forgot
let's just
make hammers
let's just make a hammer
and then build hold on
and then i'm gonna make a shelf maybe
yeah
just build a new one is that a warm yeah
i don't know i forgot where i got it but
i got
on
[Music]
in india
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
um
what do we do if we want to make like
mixed shelf
steps floor floor triangle
i don't think it works that way
[Music]
foundation
half wall
window
luring well
you need to research shelves
for real yoda
i want to make a
chest
[Music]
box box
yeah
large wood box yeah
and i need to make middle middle
fragments
[Music]
metal fragments
this is my last metal fragment omg
[Music]
what what
yeah would you rather
okay
yeah we're just gonna like make boxes
i'm gonna make boxes okay the wooden box
one is finished
we're gonna
put it somewhere here
[Music]
guys
why take so long guys
why does it take so long to do this
you know we wait we wait
okay um what do we do
gun
what's this
maybe like the anti-radiation
see what the hell is this
sm
i don't even know guys what these are
the bones
like organic stuff maybe they go here
organic stuff like bones clothes leather
i think they should go here
at least they're like a gun here
why are there guns here i don't even
know
water goes here
water go here
i don't know why there's a green card
here it's okay
and then
and then i will put gun here
put gun here
clothing
c4 fuse
um
okay bullets
well let's
let's let's
hmm okay
and then
what's telephone for
medkit is green so they belong together
here
yeah
i think
see okay it's green it's green it's
green and then okay there we go that
looks nice that looks kind of nice
if you want me to be honest that looks
kind of nice
um
chainsaw i feel like i want to bring
with me but maybe later i want to sort
everything first
yeah i see
i think this looks nice
green shotgun shells moved up
guys because this needs to um
no
yeah
okay this looks better this looks better
yeah any sorting simulator yeah guys
sorting simulator okay these are
okay for example
okay wait just put just put this here
first just put put it here first because
later on we're gonna like
take them out anyways but
we're gonna take them
crude oil
let's turn this on because
because it's dark
weapons are here
oh there's also this one
um
and then there's horse dung so random
uh
ak goes here i think
oh
what about the hazmats
here
um
not this
i'll just set my automatic rifle i feel
like i should like bring one of one of
my guns anyways so
um
which one do i bring with me maybe the
thompson
yeah
and then ring one instead of bullet like
this
okay
and then it'll be okay
i think it's next week
we got our guns back
no
why would you think that
okay
okay this is like a fridge but not
really a fridge
i don't know why the green card's here
but
okay i kind of want to recycle this
i want to recycle this but that'll do
that
maybe the warm belongs here
close
yeah like maybe this one's for like raw
materials this one's for i don't know
um
this is these are both empty
just like empty these
where all this loot come from yeah uh
sponsored by anya and we've been yeah
because we've been playing off stream
and then we went to like places
we went actually to the oil rig place
yesterday but we died so we're gonna
like try that again probably on stream
or something
no funny guys
i need to sort this out because it's
driving me crazy
okay metals metals is next can i just
like put metals in the tc yes i can
right
hmm
so metals in the tc
um
okay
what else can i put in the tc
oh i can't put this in the tc that's
that's kind of amazing okay
that's kind of amazing um
and then what
you sure that tc won't eat metal um
i don't i don't have metal at my house
so it's not gonna eat it
i don't think so
at least i don't think so
what about like r and this is for
organic this is for armors maybe i wish
we could like label stuff
hmm
i gave all my cloth to anya last time
oh weird weird weird electronics go here
i picked up like another cctv but i
couldn't like really clean up
yeah weird electronics they go here that
i really don't know how
[Music]
maybe so i won't forget about them
compound bowl maybe
just to fill in the last slot they
should be here
i don't know
hmm
that's for the thompson though i don't
really care okay weird stuff basically
go here
where stuff weird stuff go here
yeah
the stuff that are weird like i don't
know what they're for they go here
and then this one goes here
this is for like the weird stuff that's
like water where's my cloth did i like
just literally give them all to anya
i guess that might be the case
and that is okay i think okay i think
it's pretty much all cleaned up
i kinda want to
[Music]
okay now we oh i can't i can't put tc
i need to kill stuff
okay
should i put like a weaker thing because
like i'm kind of i don't want to waste
my hazmat honestly
i mean i have like three hazmats
but
you clean like ocd people come on it
just looks nice that way
okay it's almost
it's almost evening anyways
maybe i should just wait wait until
sunrise
and then while we wait let's just um
i need to collect scraps
because i'm lacking like i can't even
like
or should i research bullets
maybe i should research the rifle bullet
or did i do that i forgot
[Music]
already
researched my voice
yeah i think the important one is the
pistol bullet and then this rifle bullet
so the next one is to just like either
research the guns which i can't or like
basically all the things that i need to
research they're they're they're they're
in like workbench level three so i kind
of don't know
yes yes yes yes yes
yeah so
i do not know what to do
maybe i can go to the recycling center
and just like grab some scraps
[Music]
yeah
is it is it is nighttime coming soon or
is it morning i don't actually know guys
is it morning
[Music]
oh sh
this always happens
it's morning okay
well i also want to like dig for stones
like where's stone
near there's no places
well first i want to go to the oh
what's that
i want to go to the
uh just for our survival just for meat
did you ever find your horse oh my god
is it the right time to like
revenge the scientist but honestly i
don't think it's kind of worth it
because i can just
oh my god
e
where where's the weak point
oh there we go
[Music]
nice
okay
[Music]
let's just um
see there's like a crate there
i kind of want to get it
i hope the people who are online are
like peace loving people right now
ready to fall
oh that's pretty far though
so for a query okay let's let's try to
get it let's try to get it
yes yes yes yes the whole server is
peaceful compared to rust pubs exactly
um uh you know uh there's actually some
rules
i know it's like a you know soft rules i
guess
soft rules in the game
and um
i mean it keeps order but
it's just nice i guess
for once um
you can't do stuff like offline rating
and
oh right here
helicopter over there far
yeah
uh so it's a little bit more lacks i
think but
i know like some people uh in this game
like
they play kind of um
sort of like how they would play pop
damn i don't
did i lose it
did i lose it where is it where'd it go
offline rating is like when you're
um
when for example when when you're
offline and like the people
you can't basically attack somebody's
base when they're offline
yeah
if they're both online then it's like
whatever
oh did i lose it
hmm
do you have to tell them they're
attacking that base
i kind of forgot because i um
i think you don't have to have to if
they're online
but
hmm
offline doesn't mean also streaming like
literally offline in the game
and then if it's offline like as long as
the other party is okay with it then
it's okay
but you know i guess it's just like to
um
so that you know i know this is like a
pvp game but like i feel like some
people
um enjoy
doing
[Music]
stuff like so that so people can enjoy
stuff really also guys i think i lost
like the crate thing
i don't know where it is
i'm just gonna like try to look for some
stones
anya says stones are near snow areas
but
um oh i found it
ah not bad
not bad not bad
what's this
satchel charge oh
lucky lucky
um where am i right now
so for query
power plant
i need to find stones guys do you guys
know where they are
like because i i really need i need to
like upgrade my house you know
university
[Laughter]
i know that but also not that one
search for stones in an area with stuff
okay i'll try
i don't know like how dangerous it is to
go places like this
because it's like kind of cold
oh shoot
okay never mind
mountain like area this is a mountain
like area
hmm
oh what's that is that a metal or a
stone
the helicopter is so close
but if i strip
there we go
i
these are metals
these are metals not stone they actually
don't know
are these stone
no they are metal ores
they're metal oars
the metal also gives stone really
is that cough sound yes
[Music]
foreign
mahalo
we don't even know where stone is so we
can't we can't upgrade because
we don't know where the stone is
north of amis base that's so far
i can just walk it's no big deal
go metal instead huh one piece
[Music]
just skip the sheet metal
i didn't know you could do that
but you need sheet metal right
there's the helicopter
over there
i have five
for sleeping sleeping guys
i think we need to put sleeping bags in
different places
so we can sleep
anywhere
you're gonna see
skipping to metal is a good idea i guess
so
yeah but like the thing is upgrading is
like a lot of work
server is going to be wiped soon i feel
like at least like i want to upgrade to
stone but i can't
yeah guys uh yesterday uh anya and i uh
we played a little bit of rust offline
so if you see me with like a lot of guns
uh this is like first sponsored by anya
and then we we went i went to the oil
rig place for the first time if you guys
don't know um i think today
and
they're also doing
they're also uh they also were doing the
oil rig
thingy it's basically there's a place
that you have to reach by boat
um and it brings you to this
i mean like literally an oil rig with um
scientist npcs
scientist npcs and
it's nice question mark
might as well you know because she's the
one who's giving me these like items and
stuff
and
i think it's fun to play with her
yeah
i'm not seeing me
yeah i think it's fun to play with her
and then um yeah we went upstairs and we
looted some stuff uh the c4 that you
guys saw um we took that from uh from
the from the basically one of the people
that we killed
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
so it's nice
would be a great team yeah maybe
i'm having fun so far she's like
teaching me stuff we're like we went to
the boat
and then i gave all of my low grade fuel
not that many though or her anyways so i
think it would just be kind of nice if
um
oh what
it would be kind of nice to um
do stuff
with her
nice
okay
so many metal oars
yeah let's just like collect metals i
guess because we're already not doing
anything
nice
okay
oops
but the thing is i never find it
it's so hard to find
you know
like the thing is i need to know where
they spawn like which area
you know
give me the full damage
i do dehydrate it i'm thirsty
let's steal water from kimono house
[Music]
it just rains so she should have water
oh wait shoot i think she's gonna stream
rust today
sorry for stealing your water i mean you
know
you guys could let her know probably if
like she ever runs out of water i have
water in my house
yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
yeah
because you have to offer yours i guess
so
[Music]
okay let's go home
are you gonna see her
um i don't know if we if we if we see
each other sure
[Music]
this needs to be smelted
so far
[Music]
okay
literally don't know what i'm doing
but excellent
i'm gonna cook meat
yeah i'm gonna cook meat that's that's
the announcement
[Applause]
okay
i'm just like you know putting these
like oh maybe you should do this instead
fold this okay
oh i have some clothes
i want to make a wolf skin
wolf head dress and put it somewhere
versus craps where am i
where did i
where did i put my scraps over here
yeah
oh just a hundred more
and then i can research
[Music]
hmm
okay
i guess
this is fun
oh what's this rifle for
guess hmm
hmm what do i do
let's put it here
let's put it here i don't need it
for clothes
yeah or already you know we we just like
clean we just cleaned up and now we're
already like putting whatever
we're already putting whatever in here
you know it's fine
it is fine
[Applause]
okay
i'm gonna go to the uh to the
supermarket
[Music]
oh shoot um actually i think i might
have burned my uh wolf meat
oh actually only one burnt
neat
i'm gonna eat it
eat
okay nice too i'm gonna go
to the abandoned supermarket oh hen
fibers where
where
where is it
i'm gonna craft like sleeping bags maybe
i need like 30 dang
how can i make a cloth
all right can i can literally make gloss
no okay fine
what's the sewing kit i have no idea
okay
yes yes yes yes
oh and by the way did you guys enjoy the
collaboration with the um whole little
[Music]
no kill the chicken
no kill the chicken no no no no no no no
no
yeah
yeah i'm glad you guys enjoyed it it's
actually the first time i played apex
since i don't actually know
okay um the last time i played apex was
before i changed my mouse
how about being uploading
are you aggressive no
goodbye
what's this
okay
some random barbecue place
yes yes yes yes
perhaps wait where is this
too far
minus 50 damage with silencer
really
silencer is
okay just to make people you know
just to make people not scared i guess
yeah it was pretty long ago i think like
you know the last season i went it was
like season eight or something when
valkyrie was like implemented
oh there's the supermarket there we go
oh no
that aim whatever
okay
okay there we go found the weak point
finding those
weak points is hard
yes not to spend
five minutes pickaxing them i know but i
need food guys
come back what could i see
okay nice
you
yeah sometimes it's hard to we need to
find like the soft spot like the max
amount of damage
oh
yeah oh
hey what
huh
not only
okay fine
okay um let's gather stuff let's gather
stuff
i want to go to the water treatment plan
but
i might see people there so i don't know
i don't like it
i don't like it when i like um go to the
water treatment and then i see people
it's like just kind of awkward
i don't want to socialize
because it's like listen it's clearly
like but it's clear that both of us won
the loot you know
so uh i i i will try to
check the
check the box when you know i'll try to
wake up early or something and just like
play offline oh
and see maybe when nobody is awful
nobody's online then i'll get it
[Music]
there's more yes of course of course
there's more
that's what weapons are for na
na na
no i don't think so
what the heck okay binoculars are pretty
neat
i got them once and then i i think i
died and i couldn't retrieve it anymore
hmm
but it's okay
i think i'll eat this
sheet metal
and i'll eat these beans
okay i'll just recycle first
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
nobody online when everyone's playing no
like by online i don't mean they're
streaming it's when they're like
actually offline you know
um
there's two wolf's calls so unnecessary
cycle recycle our priority here is
scraps so i'm just gonna like recycle
everything i don't need
[Music]
i can't recycle that all right
fine fine by me
[Music]
okay
i'll just um look for more
[Music]
there's a green card which is like not
very important but i guess
better than nothing
are you sure you want to recycle the
helmet i guess so
[Music]
what's this spear gun what kind of cool
pressure pad kind of cool
[Music]
there you go
a spear gun
speargun maybe for spear fishing perhaps
okay um i'm gonna just recycle
oh and then
where
where is it where's the last item that
we need to recycle
[Music]
i don't care
nothing
put this on
okay let me go upstairs
[Music]
let me go upstairs oh i think i should
scraps the rope and scraps the rope and
scraps the rope and scraps the rope
um
maybe i might stay here until the
morning because uh the day is getting
dark
[Music]
eat the apples and throw away the seeds
all right
miners hat
wow
excuse hazmat
cool
um
um should like toss the pickles
another hazmat cool
oh sheet metal not there
hi
it's so dark
the night's coming
um
i'll do this
okay
like it's apple
and
okay and then what else
what else we put in
oh here this one
what mother had kind of cute though
i want to keep it
i want to keep it cute
okay
oh this is the one with the sheet metal
i think that's all
we can take
is it
i'm not sure
[Music]
okay
and then what else
oh i forgot about these
anti-radiation bottles
[Applause]
there we go
[Music]
okay
cool
okay i think that is all from the
supermarket
i might just um
get everything and then go back home to
the home
and look at my wheelchair okay
oh
so dark
now it feels like a real horror game
wow
horror game
what's lurking
what's lurking between
in the darkness
spicy
i think this is it
can we put anything else inside
hmm
nothing i guess
rope is for cloth maybe
okay let's go back home
um actually no let's wait
let's wait until morning
here we're like well hydrated anyways
scary
okay i'm gonna wait until morning
so yeah
um i woke up a little bit late again
because um
as you guys know like i'm still
recovering like i haven't been feeling
well um and then
i was like okay if i want to stream then
i need to eat lunch okay
then i need to eat lunch and then i
ordered food basically because like you
know when you're sick you don't really
have like much appetite right
so i ordered um some uh tofu
and then i ordered some chicken
and then i ordered some okay there's
just like soup dumplings like the
shaolin pao and then
um
you know you're you're really not
supposed to like eat them with hands i
guess but you know like for me like if
i'm eating at home like whatever i'm
just gonna like bite it with my hands
and like eat it right and then
[Laughter]
what sound is that
oh the water treatment plant is um empty
no one's taking it for real
like um so yeah basically uh i was
i was trying to eat it with my hands
right and then
i uh oh sunrise look at that so
beautiful
i wanted to take a screenshot but why is
it not working
and then you know i was trying to eat it
but then i don't know i don't know why
i'm eating it like that but like i
i
decided my brain somehow decided like
okay maybe like
as long as i don't bite it like the soup
won't like spill right so i was just
like
okay i'm eating it but then i kind of
flip the dumplings and then
it's everything spilled on my lap
and i'm like
[Music]
okay
yeah
i mean it's just one piece it's whatever
i mean literally not everything's built
but like it still felt like it's
literally the first time that i
experienced something like that
yeah kind of sad because the soup is
like the one you uh
the soup is the one you
you want to eat the most right
but just like that
that's funny but sad did you did it did
you get the burn
uh that's the thing it was like i
ordered like
like
uber sheep so
i ordered uber sheep so no sadly
it's not hot anymore
okay i don't know why i would need to
store wolves wolf skulls maybe to make
fancy hats
but yeah
how much scraps do we get
oh enough for okay guys what do we
research
we have several stuff that needed okay
aka maybe ak
cause we have multiple ak's
let's research the ak
right yeah i see
research a king on guys
let's decide later
i wanna also make sleeping bags
we need clothes
let's make two sleeping bags actually
research the one you already got the
bullet recipe i got both bullets i got
the most important bullets the rifle
bullet and the pistol bullet
so i literally can craft anything i want
uh the reason why i chose a okay
ak or
okay no not this
the thing is i only have one thompson
so if i research it first i'm not gonna
get i'm not gonna have a thompson for
like the remainder of the season
need level three bench to make it yeah
yeah it's for next season guys it's for
next season
not for this season
hmm
yes yes yes yes it's it's uh like
i'm i'm playing this game uh as the
preparation for next season basically so
that's why i'm not like oh upgrading to
stuff like no i only have like barely
like a week
for this
so i want to like craft as much as
possible
yeah
okay
i have one sleeping bag
only one sleeping bag oh two
actually nice
so i'm gonna just put one here
[Music]
bullets
minor hat maybe here
maybe
where else
the season lasts a month or less do we
know a season three should be starting
soonish
hmm
i think we should like have a separate
place to store hazmats
just because
here maybe
the clothing
clothing place um
september 1 reset mikko says yeah there
you go
oh it's morning
i gotta cook but i'm like very lazy
but if i don't cook
i guess i'll be fine
hmm
tarp
[Music]
yeah okay i'll just like i'll just put
this here first because um
i don't know
let's have fiber for
oh it needs to be planted on the ground
well do i wanna
do i wanna like plant stuff here maybe i
will
plant
i need two tarps
oh small
i can make the small one i mean the
larger one looks better
but
i i don't think i have two tarps i know
like i had one tarp but maybe i got then
lost
so i no longer have it
that's what i remember
misen losting so i'm just gonna like
make one small
small planter
hmm
what do you need for workbench level two
it's a good question
yeah
basically this
nice
[Music]
the horse feeder outside looks so sad i
know right it's okay it's waiting for
its owner
i'm gonna put like
i can't feed i can't feed the bullets
so sad
um
okay i guess i'll
put this like here
oh no it's not flat
ground
[Music]
maybe here
where sheesh
[Music]
what the hell why how is that possible
and here's not possible
oh it's a good
what
yeah
oh
like literally here
god this is gonna be so annoying but
this is so ugly
like
okay open
ah
you need fertilizer are you kidding me
nah
um
yeah
we don't need fertilizer
we don't need it i don't think we need
it it tastes fine
i really want to research ak so badly
but you know what i think we i think we
can
all the other guns all the other guns
are like
oh thompson is actually
little too
oh but i guess aka
oh do you have horse dung yeah
can we use horse dung as fertilizer
no we can't
that's bs
how come
short stream you know short stream
[Music]
bye
there we go we learned it that was easy
[Music]
exploring
when exploring
okay i have no idea why i have this
bullet here because i'm not bringing it
anyways
i know fat can get out
[Applause]
okay
nice
how do i use binoculars
how do i use the binoculars guys
what is
did you research any c4 or satchels
no i did research c4 i forgot
i should have researched c4 huh
is
i want 500.
i need to research the c4
or
my
you just want to get scraps
table what's this
oh nice thank you
let's just explore guys what i have a
table but what for
hold right clicks against the binoculars
like a stealth game truly
so nice
um
this is the power plant
i'll actually put a sleeping bag
somewhere
like uh i have a second sleeping bag
here
and it's really funny because uh because
ania and i have been hanging out
together she has like a little shed
she has a little shed and um that's
where i sleep it's kind of like the maid
room
[Laughter]
it's kind of like the maid room of her
house
so
i should have sniped so annoying
why why why why are they so good
why did i die
why are they so
what
also yeah i'm gonna rest is a little bit
confusing
like what should like i i don't know
like where i should be
where'd the apex kill yesterday go
it doesn't apply in rust
that's the thing
you see this anya made room
but um i'll get
yeah it's really different guys
yeah
um
i'm gonna cook first
yeah it's weird like what uh
i think i got it somehow while i was
like a you know
aiming with uh the rifle when i was
doing the oil rig but
i feel like it's just really really
confusing still
the bullet goes up what the [\h__\h] kind of
logic is that
how am i supposed to get it
how am i supposed to get that
i'll try
oh recoil uh okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah
oh okay so that's how the i mean
i mean of course like i know like how
recoil works but also i didn't know that
it's just like you have to compensate
like that much
yeah ironside perhaps try to have to be
lower maybe
let's see yeah i'll just like aim at the
body
yeah i only practiced a lot with the um
the sniping gun
okay
let's get him
okay where'd i die
oh wait i don't have clothes on
okay map map map
okay
aim the balls you got the body in
perfectly okay i'll try that
do you need clothes where you're going i
guess so
hmm
[Music]
i mean i can try that that sounds like a
solid hint
can you just like follow the road
basically
so there
where is it
oh
oh there we go
that's that's that's a
stupid scientist
where is he
[Music]
what how do i oh you slam us a throw
okay
no
i didn't bring healing items
why
it didn't hit
it's so difficult it's so difficult to
aim in this game
what
oh what's up with choco sensei
[Music]
where is he
i'll try to
aim from here
[Music]
oh he did
stupid
[\h__\h]
[Music]
where's my body there we go
okay um
[Music]
what do we do now
we
we look for more scraps
and tarps
where's the gun
i don't know
oh maybe the gun is somewhere else
yeah the thompson should be at the
ground i forgot about that
weapons are usually on the ground there
we go
thank you
thanks for reminding me holy crap i
wouldn't have realized
this is my anger speaking
[Music]
oh
there's my mush
[Music]
my anger
use stone too late
serves you right
here's my thompson
yeah are we
we're actually kind of near the power
plant
huh is the power plant like a safe zone
like are we not allowed to like bring
guns to the power plant or what
[Music]
yeah it's okay it's okay oh also guys um
i don't know if it's pretty obvious but
it kind of i fixed my mic issue with
russ so the next time i play rust with
somebody else i'll be able to use the
open mic just fine
so it was kind of complicated i guess
um some people are saying oh it's from
your like steam mic setting some people
are saying oh it's just from like i
don't know what
but it turns out it is actually from
your absolute
like your pc settings because it kind of
but it kind of confused me
because it kind of confused me because
first
um
i made
a setting override
i made a setting override for this game
but it turns out that it didn't really
work
yeah
i made a setting override but it didn't
work for some reason so i was like why
and how you know
that'll confuse me for the longest
yeah but i finally found because there's
so many like things to like test and
it's kind of complicated to like test
one by one but finally i found it
and of course it's like always really
embarrassing because um
because normally i never really asked
until like i'm like super stumped
and then
you know i was like super stumped so i
asked amy right like yo hey elmy do you
know why this is happening and stop whoa
whoa whoa whoa
oh god
reload reload reload
oh no i died again
no no no no no no and then um
where is it
near
there
and
10.
i'll just go here
i'll just wait for the polar bear to
leave
was i uh what was i talking about i
forgot
uh yeah i asked ame hey ami um why is it
like this and then
when she replied i already found the
answer of course i'm like yo okay
i found it by the way but you know it's
just like a little um
it's a good time for a small talk i
guess i asked her like if she's gonna
like play
and she's got oh my god it's too cold
i asked her if she's gonna um play
season three or something and stuff like
that you know
the you know little socialization stuff
which is cool right
and
yeah
fun
i mean it's prepping rockets for the
finale yeah it's fun wait hold on
um where am i
oh still far away
still pretty far away we just gotta make
sure that um
the bear isn't there
just gonna make sure the bear isn't
there but that's hard you
know is i am more advanced than kyla and
muna i have no idea i have actually have
no idea how uh people are doing in rust
you know
uh so
i literally cannot answer that
i think army's kind of like focusing on
tech or something
um
yeah
but i don't know i like exploring so
i'm really tempted to you know because i
feel like anya really likes doing like
tve stuff like the rays and stuff so
i might actually hang out with her um a
lot next season
i might
hmm
this is where i was
okay
let's see if the
where my body is
seems like the bear isn't there anymore
the bear doesn't seem to be around
where's my body
where is it
huh
hmm
could you zoom in a little bit oh
of course
there
where is it
i remember i died like somewhere around
here
i don't have instinct
[Music]
near the fallen tree oh my god look
it's me
well
[Music]
hmm
naked person
random naked person
there can be only one rainy
open ocean
human skull what's it for
oh my god
what is a human skull for guys
what's that
i know that
bone fragments are good
a human skull
i guess the animal fat isn't really um
useful anyways i'm going to go home
how to go home p8
p-8
oh pumpkin
where where my body
where's my body
where's my body where is it
where is it
oh my god
anita
okay whatever
i'm gonna go home
i'm going home going home home home home
throw a grenade at the
at the scientist worth it
i left thompson behind goddammit
why
that means the
where
i thought this was oh this wasn't this
wasn't thompson where is it
near the fallen tree right do this
where
where's my gun
where is it
slightly apart from the bag where
i don't see it
oh i found it
um what should we sacrifice
there we go we got it
okay guys we're ready to go home
finally
okay
yeah just follow the road i guess
two binoculars for two eyes
i wanted to
recycle it
basically
my thoughts that have flashlight true
it's scary if i use this
it's scary guys torch is less scary
hey
yeah this this looks like a horror game
oh house house silhouette
i think that's my house
no i don't think that's my house but
still it's like a house in my
neighborhood
yes
it kind of is i mean it's okay it's like
man versus nature and sometimes man
versus man
yes
this is
yeah house from my neighborhood
loyal senpai house maybe
okay
that's army house i can see the lights
and this is my house
there we go
yes good
gonna turn on turn this on
ah
what did we some finally some
familiarity
wait i want to cook the human meat
[Music]
this
and binoculars what for i don't even
know
this is to bring tomorrow morning
fuse i guess i can recycle fuse human
skull is
let's put it here
a table
i guess we can have a table
hey
it's just a nice table i don't know
[Laughter]
okay i have a lot of the silencer here
[Music]
metal here that's all here
it's full actually wow
let me like store them in the furnace
yeah we can do that we can use like the
we can use this as a storage
that's okay
okay one binocular we're gonna recycle
this we're gonna recycle
scraps are gonna store here
perhaps we're just gonna store here
spark plugs
these are the stuff basically we're
gonna recycle once morning hits we're
gonna visit the um
once morning hits we're gonna visit the
the the the
the supermarket and recycle again
okay sounds good
why do i have two torches weird okay
well well
[Music]
and one more outfit
nice hazmat storage
okay
see how much to research c4 actually
hmm
okay then
[Music]
this fuse is actually not mine so i'm
gonna like
bring it with me
bandages
okay
i don't think i need bandages
famous last words
okay are you guys ready to go to the
supermarket and why do i have like three
guns with me
oh okay
okay
[Music]
okay we are ready i think to go outside
this morning right
wait
a human flesh
ah they're all burnt
oh no three of them are burnt i mean i
can just like use these to like taunt
people
whatever
okay
let's go guys
don't push too much the wi-fi will be
soon yeah of course my priority is to
gather scraps
uh and to learn stuff so
so they will be there during c uh in
season three
i'm focusing on that
[Music]
i should like you know whenever like
someone's like i need food you know i'll
just like give them back
[Music]
are we going
the wrong way
[Music]
okay
yeah let's just look for scraps
and not stones
oh look there's another one
there's another one there
so like towards
[Music]
oh man
that's so far though
like probably like here
i'm just gonna go to the abandoned
supermarket first
will you be fighting for the reset whoa
whoa whoa sorry man
what
[Music]
yes yes yes
cara online why don't you give this call
i'll give them i'll give her like human
meat also guys there's a
i feel like there's like a soft rule
like when you can
oh animals
i guess like when you can like um
don't give out like too much info about
other players
that are online
something something something like that
oh what's this
apples good for food
yeah um there are like the set of rules
i feel like some members are like
straight up copy pasting it on their
page i think i should i should do that
too so it's like clear
but it's okay yeah i know that kiara's
gonna be streaming
um because i saw her like um
i saw her reservation room room
reservation was that to the left
there we go
yeah no pigeoning only pea fowling it's
bad habit guys actually
like sometimes like i don't really care
about it but like
you know just so you know it's actually
kind of like bad habit to be pigeons
like that
let's go
go
nice food
[Music]
thank you
and this is
there's a bed
the items today are pretty good
got a table this is like you know house
like house slipper edition
or what
i don't have to sleep in a sleeping bag
anymore why are you serious
huh
crazy
what that's insane
imagine not actually sleeping in a
sleeping bag crazy crazy crazy
all right i'm gonna
okay i'm gonna do this first
[Music]
ooh metal blade
mine is crops anyways
so what i'm gonna do is
this is for like metals
i'm just gonna turn this on
and i'm going to
eat these basically
these beans
you put them here
right
oh girl is online
never met her
i never really met her in this game it's
just like um
i don't know
she has um i saw some you can for a low
price of 300 scripts
what a deal
okay
[Music]
a lot of people are online but i think i
don't think they're like around here
didn't hear that
i did not hear that
[Music]
ten ten ten ten
really nothing else
i'm gonna go up
how many green cards you have now i
don't know
i just like loot whenever i go here
someone's like the maps are huge it's a
shame if you just go to the supermarket
and i'm like did you just come here like
five minutes ago or what
i need craps though my priority
my priority
i need 500 more to at least um
do c4
research c4
um
coco is a line with robofull yeah i know
i know
because they were like uh doing the oil
rig thing together
earlier
okay and sheet metal can i oh no i can't
do that with the green card
um
[Music]
anything else i can do
oh this one
okay
why chat keeps niching i don't know
because they um
they don't care i think
because they don't care
[Music]
snitching snitching what snitching about
how so-and-so is teaming up with who or
like oh stuff like that
i think
i think that's what the word that we're
referring to
i could be wrong
[Music]
i think that's all
i guess i'm gonna go explore a little
bit more find some more scraps
what are your plans for the end of the
season the end of the season is coming
soon so literally my plan for season two
is only to gather as many scraps as i
can and to
so i can basically research everything
so i will get like at least a less rough
start in season three
if you guys are wondering why i keep why
i keep like doing the same things over
and over again
that's why
you know
you guys want me to like you know
rate something which i don't know i
guess i can uh do tomorrow or something
have you tried playing haley no and i'm
not really interested maybe it's season
three
you know
149.
that's enough that should be enough
i'm gonna go home and then i'm gonna
maybe just walk around find uh
try to find scraps
in
general yes yes yes yes yes
preparing for next season is smart yeah
of course
that's what i'm trying to do because
you know a lot of people have already
started playing russ in season one
my horse now [\h__\h]
okay
nice
anyways what was i saying
what was i saying
what's the point of season reset i think
it's so that um
it's a very common feature in rust games
from what i know
it's uh so that not people are not
you know because it's snowballs right
everybody will get overpowered and the
power gap will be so big something like
that
yeah
but the thing that doesn't reset is tech
tree and basically like you know
blueprints and stuff like that
so
the smart thing to do because i don't
have much time a lot of people have
started from season one
and of course even though things reset
they're still ahead in the when it comes
to like the tech trees
and
so i i want to at least be able to catch
up with that like it's no use if i have
like oh my god so many like for example
beds or whatever so many resources
because
placing a sleeping bag here will trigger
the cooldown of a nearby sleeping bag
um
i don't care
place it here
hmm
or do i just like
take the sleeping bag
oh it's far away
[Music]
how do i pick this up
how do i pick this up how do i pick up
this leaving bag
there might be a big party before reset
you plan to participate i guess so
hmm
oops
yeah
i don't know
tc
tc time and it's like oh oh
okay so much of this
so many many many many of these
still need a lot more
what the
where is it
oh it's far away
it's far away but it sounds so loud
it sounds really loud even though it's
so far away
like five times
i hope you're not wearing aggressive
clothing oh i am wearing aggressive
clothing
i will always wear aggressive clothing
[Music]
okay
i guess i'll cook
i'll cook i'll put
wolf meat i'll cook with meat
maybe i'll put
boxes here
i'll put oh i'll craft the wood box a
big box
i need metal fragments which i do have
actually
like two
i have what
blasphemy
blasphemy okay i'm gonna make two of
these crafts
okay
here we go now you can cook again
i think something's going on with kind
of the same pie and choco sensei
[Music]
large box
here we go
i have one and then
okay put it here oh my god i can't put
it there then what the hell is the use
of this box
useless
the most useless thing ever in this
whole world
ah so you say same fights online
scary
okay
nice wolf meat
just put this here
maybe okay
they look like coffins
if there's somebody i'm really scared of
in this game it's the senpai and i'm
sure a lot of people share the same
sentiment
like please don't shoot me i'm so scared
put a skull in each of them oh my god
that's so genius
like this one
nice
okay um let's see okay we can throw that
off
okay um
[Music]
binoculars i think you can put this here
i mean i could like make another tc but
also i don't know
um
[Music]
there's like a bed where should i put
the bed
[Music]
hmm
okay
anti-radiation stuff i don't think i
need it
i just like picking them up
[Music]
okay and then maybe i kind of want to
put this here
[Music]
okay oh my gosh the metal fragments
the middle fragments i need to put them
here
okay uh guys um okay let's let's look
for uh
hi
oh okay
they're not even the human meat nice
actually it's
split we split it
there we go
you're gonna eat it
yeah cool
[Music]
good nobody eats the human meat but
the people i meet
yeah
whenever i see someone i'll just like
greet them with this
can you name the horse okay but you know
what we should name the horse i think so
that um
can we eat can we feed the horse
chocolate or something because i feel
like it's cheaper than like feeding them
oh i need to feed them pickles
me later
as a sign of friendship eat my flesh
okay
maybe we can go to the
treat power treatment plant thingy
huh
oh item
a crate
my nightmare
from last time
[Music]
so
oh
nice
where's the
i mean sounds like it's far away
okay
where is it
oh there
okay i think i need to go here first
it's kind of like approaching
if you know by hiding weapon or suit
like
do you mean like hide in the inventory
but is it still okay if i'm not using it
but it's but it's in in the hot bar
hmm
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
but yes guys um
i just like i want to say i feel like my
i've been not feeling well all right but
then uh i'm actually okay now
but the thing is i know i cancelled the
karaoke it's not because i wasn't
healthy
it's because of i think i told you guys
here before um but it's about like my
jaw issue like i feel like my left jaw
is like a little bit
it hurts if i open it like
a lot like when i'm singing
so
it's like uh i don't know
but
yeah but i'm actually getting it uh
treated like for immediate relief like
just just for i feel like you know it's
it doesn't cure it completely but at
least like it's an immediate relief
so i'm going to uh the doctor tomorrow
and hopefully it'll be fine
whose house is this
so much advertising
oh the box is not there anymore
so somebody was camping it i guess
so i'm not interested in those jaw
exercises no shut up with the jaw
exercises oh my god
how am i not exercising my jaw i stream
all the time i talk all the time i do i
do them actually
i have a checked up for tmj you know
what i'm pretty sure i have tmj
and there's really nothing much you can
do about it so sad
so many ads must be your house man i
wish i wish my house is that good
yeah
and it's like really really tough i'm
gonna get it like dry needle just like
relax the muscles
i mean it doesn't like deal with the
issue it's just like but i mean whoa
but it does the job
what is tmj basically um your jaws are
[\h__\h] up i don't know how to explain it
it's not really like messed up messed up
but
it's not really messed up messed up but
you know
i'm just gonna
i'm gonna follow the road because
i'm not really following the road and
i'm not really seeing seeing me like
metals
um
i wonder what was insane friends are
doing choices and friends
because they seem to be um very
oh
got shot by the helicopter
so sad oh my god the helicopter is close
to the water treatment plan though
it's coming here like
heck off
like heck off what are you
i'm just doing like gather somewhere
tmj is
my jaw
yes
i'm just gonna like go to the road i
guess to gather scraps
like you guys are like
i don't know
i feel like the road is faster and
actually the supermarket is faster
it's like just like do a grind going
back and forth but i get what if you
guys think it's boring
um
why am i going here i don't even know
hmm
there's a box here
or is it just like a is it i don't think
it's a box i can open i think it's like
yeah it's like decoration
dang it it's fine
when was the first time you felt
something wrong with jaw oh um oh it's
like it's something that's always been
there like for a long time
but lately it's been getting um more
awful it's okay no need to play doctor
but yeah
it's not i'll be fine
i can try going to the power plant
don't worry there's no ring and rust
yeah
okay
it's so cold
you can like follow the road i think
okay
[Music]
i'm nearly starving for real i can eat
the wolf meat
ah there we go this is what we're
looking for
got another guitar amazing
huh oh no this is like nothing
ah oh no kanta senpai's in lost so sad
[Music]
can sell the guitar to muna
does buna want some
huh
i'm here with the guitar
please i'm just a meat eater
he's a vitamin we're rolling whoa whoa
i'm just um
i'm just uh
whoa whoa whoa sorry
you guys you
you don't like you don't like that as
well
sheesh
you know i pick axes as well
my god
picaxia i mean realistically you can't
kill me i can't kill you with the pig
has like pickaxe just for like salvaging
stuff like you do do you feel like
you're a metal that should be salvaged
what's wrong with you
what's good
i'm peace loving
[Music]
yeah just like
just
doing
[Music]
okay
i think it's safe
i think i'm safe oh there by the power
plant yeah i'm safe i should be safe
in my h10
i pray for kind of a senpai's success
why
why do you keep coming here
like come on
it's like
heck out of here
it's already dark it's okay
darkness is my friend
oh there's a great in the power plant do
you want to do you want to get it
you guys want to try getting it
i want to try getting it
ah
someone wants me dead i guess so
is the beer gonna kill me i mean
it might
i'm gonna i'm gonna ignore this first
and this is actually the first time i'm
going to the parkland um am i not a lot
of weapons in the power plant or what
am i allowed weapons in the far plan or
no
um late
it's late guys
it's night time god it's so dark
okay
sounds like a horse
this is like a horror game
what sound is that
[Music]
radiation poisoning
i need anti-radiation pills
hmm
where's the box
where is it
huh
oh there
[Music]
climb here
okay
this way here
till morning
and then
[Music]
how many minutes
14 minutes
i can just like go around
it's too cold
you can just like go here
oh and make fire cam do you have wood
no i don't
[Music]
i don't have wood i need to um
i need to um do this
huh where is it
[Music]
huh
where is it
where's the where's the sign
god so stupid
okay
where
where the heck is the sign
oh it's too dark
[Music]
oh just wolves
what am i not getting i'm not gonna ah
dang
i can't get stuff
with that can i get the one that's this
no i can't either
i don't have a rock
i can't make fireplace too bad guys
[Music]
still 12 more minutes
so sad
well how long
oh wait here then
[Music]
oh wait here i'm going to idle meeting
i don't know guys what can we do i
didn't bring any wood
what
[Music]
ten
if everything is like so cluttered
[Music]
where do we make it
too close to the monument
as we wait let's just
do this
okay nice
okay
okay thank you
and then what else
man it's so cold
i just bring sleeping bag
yeah i think this is like a monument so
you can't like build stuff here but i'm
gonna try to um
see if there's
things to like for example if there is
there's like a recycling center here or
something
authorized personnel
can't because this is like a real like
monument so you can like just build
stuff randomly
yeah
maybe there's barrels that can't be used
that can be used as a campfire or
something
mayhaps maybe
yeah it's too cold in my hp is slowly
deteriorated to review
no hp
i only have burnt human meat
oh my god
nah i think scary i don't want to go
[Music]
bye-bye
scared guys
yeah
let's try using our green card
where is it
here this one
maybe
i don't know how to use
oh not powered okay okay never mind
how many minutes seven feet minutes can
we survive
can the torch make us warm
no
what's this oh there's a crate
i hope it brings nice stuff
uh okay sure blueberry
and water
okay we can eat the blueberry
my god so scary i wonder what's
happening
ah
you want to build campfire but
i don't know guys
anything else i can eat from here oh the
tuna
i wonder if there's like a recycling
center around here
as we wait
let's just look for stuff
hmm where is this
12 minutes feel like forever i know
right
what is this
do
[Music]
foreign
wow so many things we can get here
okay
and then nothing else okay we can go
back down
wait which way is down
wait which way guys
wait i don't know where the exit is
[Music]
what
oh i need
[Music]
okay
there's something in the middle
[Music]
poisoning
is it open i don't know
[Music]
oh my god so slow guys
three minutes oh my god
it's gonna go here guys
i'm just gonna go idle meeting
i'm gonna go idle meeting brb guys
yeah i guess with the hazmat suit
radiation there's no problem that's why
we need the radiation pills
today i learned it the hard way but i
guess it's better than not using the
radiation suit
right
three minutes be right back
[Music]
so
hello
two minutes though
let's kill time by killing wolves
because i really don't know what to do
rainy what you up to
killing wolves
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's the ankle
food
what's the end goal killing time
honestly
yeah non-human meat is the end goal
did i answer oh yes i did
listen
i'm going to ask her what to do what
she's doing
i'm about i'm about to go end my stream
[Music]
gambling she's freaking gambling you
serious
oh my god 16 15.
that was two hours of short stream
what i miss you
[Laughter]
oh
oh my god
aiming module what's that
okay
[Applause]
so people think it's already like
so p you know so so people don't come
here they think it's already like taken
right
hmm
what should i sacrifice
it's not much i can do
for scraps
hmm
what do i sacrifice
it's no i don't want to sacrifice the
human meat
you need that bowl
no not really i have one
meat maybe
but the meat i just okay maybe the metal
pipe
but it's four but everything's for like
scrapping anyways
[Music]
high quality horseshoes
okay i want the high quality horseshoes
because i have no idea what they what
they are
okay okay
[Applause]
maybe not killers i don't need them
yeah okay this looks let's look this
looks looks fine i'm gonna go home
i'm gonna go home mum
yes yes yes yes yes yes you could run to
a recycler and come back yeah that's the
thing i've been looking for a recycler
but
i think i'm just gonna go home
yeah okay i'm
in the right way
oh
reload your gun
sure
yeah we never know when we might get
third partied
yeah
are you going to take cara's offer to
gamble is she offering i don't think
she's offering
i don't think she's offering
your coffee variety is challenging to
keep packages very specific what you the
little luck coffee yeah because i
figured out like
you guys don't have that outside
indonesia right
so um yeah
and i think
yeah
have you bought luna stock no why would
i i need money
for my tech tree
oh the broken car
[Music]
oh these parts i already uh wait i need
to screenshot
so the next time i see like a broken car
i know what to bring
hmm
she's gambling alone
i'm about to stop my stream though
cause um
shoot i actually yeah i really really
gotta go
surprise her damn it
hmm
[Music]
the car's been there for a week so sad
yeah i know horse her horse might be
better than a car but i don't know
yeah it's not i in a few actually before
uh before i i have something to do
want to visit her real quick sure
where's the gambling spot
she still doesn't know i stole her water
[Music]
i need to go to the recycler
all right i'll just put everything
here
[Music]
just put except like the stuff that i
want to recycle
[Music]
aiming module sheet metal
hmm
that's it right i think
yep
randy what you're doing now uh
i'm at home
come visit
um
whoa shoot oops what
oopsie
i'm gonna give her this
as a gift
[Music]
yeah it happens when i all tab
she's coming
okay wait um actually let me just um
give me a second
i need a
oh
okay
i really really really really gotta go
but
maybe she wants to go to the thing
together
yeah
can you give her the skull too
oh my god okay
i will
it's it's so weird it's like one of
those like morbid um
gifts
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna put the bear meat here
man i don't have food huh
i'll have apple actually
actually
can eat
is kiara addicted to gambling i sure
hope not
i'm gonna be naked just because
okay
i'm gonna go to the once when she
arrives
i'm gonna go to the supermarket
oh no no i'm gonna be like this
[Music]
okay i'm gonna go to the abandoned
supermarket after this
rescue kimama are you far are she far
away
like
let's go here
[Laughter]
oh look there's a plane
oh nice
where's she
oh you can form a team with kimono let's
see where she is well maybe
[Music]
where is she
down
okay
yeah
i have business with m chan after this
actually so that's why i was like i
think i gotta go but
i guess
um
you know i can't wait a little bit
i hear chicken
fuel storage
oh dang
goodbye
seem like you're dangerous
seem like you're very dangerous huh
we're gonna sing our love song i don't
know
are we
just one note
like why would you need a numpad oh
because i want to like serenade
a bird
yeah time to steal our water
[Laughter]
yummy is stealing stealing water
i can
kiwamo water
he want water
where is she
here we are
ah where's kiara
in my house
what
okay
let
[Music]
she's at my house
yeah nice i fixed mine too nice do you
want to go to the supermarket real quick
oh what
oh wait there's definitely a delay sorry
there's like a
two three second delay
okay
[Music]
because she parked it somewhere and
logged out and she forgot about the
horse so i took her horse i have to feed
it um
but i need to figure out how
i mean you're you're horse now right
for a while i can't until
yeah yeah yeah temporarily i guess we
can go on the horse stage we can go
horsing we're sitting around we can we
can i also i also found one actually
choco sensei gave me one but um i i then
lost and then i found one in the wild
today no
oh maybe it was your horse reborn all
over again yeah reincarnated to a
different horse
i'm like ending my stream
pretty soon uh do you want to go to the
supermarket with me i just yeah yeah i
played from like okay two hours ago it's
okay what you doing
yeah i saw you
i'm just leaving the horse you do you
think it's gonna disappear immediately
no no no no it's it's fine
i can i can i can i can post
um
[Music]
beautiful
i can only play one i can only play one
note because i'm uh i don't have a
numpad
there's like a full keyboard option but
i forgot how to press
[Music]
that's what it notepad would be useful
for huh yeah like why would i be needing
a numpad oh
to play guitar and rust
can i beat the horse directly without
giving
yeah you can just like drop food uh
at him or something
oh
really
um
hey kiara i have a gift for you
here i have a gift for you
thank you
i think i know who that is from
is that i was watching a stream a little
bit is that the npc that you killed
uh oh no i got wait i got killed by a
bear and then i retrieved my uh my dead
body and then yeah
it's your old skull
yes
oh my god that's uh i guess i can make
my own uh uh
with that
that's so creepy but it's okay
um are you hungry do you want some meat
but you gave me the head
my ice cream i
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay you want it
okay you want to go to the supermarket
or wait till morning add it to my daki
makura yes yeah
realism
wait uh
let me put on my clothes properly again
okay okay
okay
let's
[Music]
go tried gambling already
no i'm concentrating on like i'm
gathering scraps for like because i
think like because the server is
resetting but the tech trees they're not
resetting so i'm like trying to
you know research stuff
to be so yeah
maybe if i want a gamble i'll do it in
season three
um
gamble together i want to play
blackjack i was there because i thought
there was three people there but when i
got there nobody was there so that's why
i said i was gambling in tears
wait there's blackjack
in here supposedly there's polka
roulette blackjack i want to play
blackjack let's go let's play
me too
yeah the only card game that i can play
yeah me too i kind of don't understand
the other games like blackjack's the
easiest
oh wait you guys don't hear her so well
okay
i also noticed she got very very good
very fast
i missed though so sad i still need to
figure out like the whole aiming thing
with rust
i saw you struggling yeah
yeah i don't know how to like aim
properly because i guess different games
have different
stuff you know
[Music]
more gambling yup
i should get some food
[Music]
what do we have for dinner tonight your
body
like i mean i wouldn't really recommend
it but
i mean
what
my body gave it to me no my body makes
you know if you look at the description
like even the cooked uh the cooked
version of my body makes you dehydrated
you know
so i don't think it's good
yeah it makes you thirsty exactly
revelation wow who would have
don't you need food too
i'm just gonna take like the beans or
something maybe
i feel like oh my god i'm looking like
everything
oh
pump shotgun oh nice
pump pump pump pump pop popper little
pump
from
she's too far away
actually no i found the tweet oh okay
okay i found a tweet that was like
making fun of
um
[Music]
uh 70
of this place
oh that's all right sorry there is a
here's a box here's a box here's the box
yeah i'm gonna go upstairs first what's
that
oh
electric heater
electrocuter
okay
sorry i um i heard that wrong
sorry
[Music]
i need to um i need to go to the
oh
yes i did sorry
i'll i'll get it real quick
[Music]
okay you can use it
yeah
i was just like looking for stuff like i
like using the torch because like if you
use the flashlight
the flashlight from the gun it's so
scary it feels like a horror game
[Music]
are you using it still
okay
no problem
oh just a little bit
[Music]
okay i'm just
okay
hello
feel free to use the video okay
to the horse
okay then
you can of course
i think i don't know they might just
need food or something
[Music]
there we go
okay i'm done
[Music]
yeah let's go home
and then
you can
uh i think it's yes kind of that way
nice zoom
[Music]
oh sorry
yeah like i don't know how i should aim
in rust
get good exactly i need to figure it out
but you're
already like getting much better
yeah
what the [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h]
so cute that was that was the middle
kid you're cute
no
where where'd they run off to where they
run up to
ignore it okay
it's morning
did you have fun today
yes i ate lunch i pretty much did
nothing and i streamed
i have another stream later at like in
like three hours though or like two
hours like i don't know
yeah
oh
these ones by the last song than before
but like is this just decoration or can
you i think you can like put something
yeah
or something i don't know you have to
put something in it i guess
exactly really is it not broken do i
just have to
how do you fix it
you will is that you feel i think you
want to try
you could
no great fuel that's it yeah i'm gonna
do that when when you when you're gone
and i'll continue walking you home yeah
thank you
yeah i never actually yeah tell me your
experience with the hot air balloon once
you get it running
because i'm really scared because
there's like what if i see the
helicopter
what if i see the helicopter when i'm
like riding the hot air balloon
as long as you don't have a weapon it
should be fine
i guess so oh yeah by the way i stole
your water like three times today
that's okay
i have so much
okay
you also have water though i do that's
the problem
i do i do
i'm like yeah you know your house was
like
very very
close by
so i thought maybe i could
but your house
is also close
yeah true but your house
oh was closer
how's this clue all right then um elena
yes thank you for
uh chilling a bit with me
yes yes yes nice to see you
i got like a bed and a
table randomly today
yes
do you have plans for
the
[Music]
minecraft summer vegetable
oh no when is that
um i think it's on
the 30
29 for the 30th
on the 30th
probably japanese japanese prime time
oh okay i mean i don't have plans 29.
japanese
you want to go
cannot be your plan
sure sure
let's go
yay
[Music]
thank you
again yeah i haven't really checked out
the place and stuff talk about it yeah
yeah we can talk about it later i just
saw i just saw the the trailer on
twitter piccolo uploaded the trailer and
it's happening on the 29th and i didn't
make any plans oh
okay okay okay okay
yeah
oh thank you
okay take care
[Music]
like
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah guys like confession actually i
actually have no idea when that is like
i know it's happening because like a
bunch of the idps are also like building
for it
but
yeah i have no idea
yeah i guess
i could still hear her
so funny she never turned off the uh
um the the open mic
maybe that's on purpose
we never know
i'm gonna put this here
metals here
i'm gonna put i'm gonna put everything
before i don't want to put stuff in my
body because i'm paranoid like that
so um
it's just one single bullet effect
maybe like put the fuse here
yeah like just like put the guns
like put the guns here
put the silencer on the um
here maybe yeah or wherever
um
this should be whatever yeah this should
be whatever
[Music]
there's so much green
card i don't know why i have so much
green card i need to get rid of them
i guess that is it
for today
thank you guys for accompanying me uh
with this
short rust stream
yeah i mean we kind of did a bunch of
stuff though so that's good
where's animal fat is there room for
animal fat we're storing like meat the
same places like we're storing horse
dung but i think it's okay
i don't that goes here
yeah
cloth
okay
what if what if like i freak out and be
like yo where are my stuff the next time
i log in like i'm so empty
empty inventory but you know what let's
sleep on the table
[Laughter]
thank you guys
um yeah i'm gonna stop streaming now uh
donors will be read later because i have
a business actually with m chan
i starts on time yeah on time guys don't
worry
all right perfect spot to sleep
they can see from the window though it's
gonna be like inviting i don't know i
think it's too a little bit too spicy to
what you guys think so i'm gonna sleep
in the middle of the room
okay
bye guys
thank you very much for your attention
bye
[Laughter]
[Music]
you