[Music]
on
kiky
hello
hello hello
k i I'm vertical I think let's
go uh are there any people watching on
their
phones who can tell me that even on the
phone it's like properly working as a
short cuz if I look at it on YouTube
it's yeah no I'm not white I didn't mess
it up
like on YouTube it will like stretch it
out anyway
so looks perfect y I did it first
try well well well K
everybody thank you for coming so far um
today is a little mini K which I've
actually been practicing some new songs
for
today um
let me just uh had to readjust myself a
little bit H and uh besides the mini I
will be revealing something to you
something pretty cool uh that
uh mhm I I'm excited about it uh but
it's not a maybe not as exciting as the
thing well definitely not no well I mean
it's both pretty cool but it's not as
exciting or as big as the thing that
I'll be announcing
later on in the
Stream um could be anytime could be
anytime H so you got to be ready for it
is this on archive no it's not on
archive but you want to be here now a
third hat why is there so many people
who say a
thir oh you're so funny guys you're so
funny I'm even giving you the B dump but
really angrily like this is the hardest
I've ever pushed that button purely out
of anger
um but um the thing that I want to show
you but the thing I want to show you I
will show it to
you very early on very
early but I want you
guys to take
in whatever you're seeing
now just to make it even like hit even
harder isn't the vertical thing ah the
vertical thing that's what that's not a
special reveal or so
no um yeah just look at me I mean I'm
just you know the usual Wawa that you've
seen many times
before uh I
think H maybe because this is a k and I
will just sing one song
uh and then I'll show you after the
first song I'll show you what's up okay
but you got to
really observe me today we will have H
some Hol life member
songs uh ID and Ian and we have some uh
one vocal Light song and some anime
songs and we're going to start we're
going to start with uh wait let me see
how many I think I will sing 1 2 3 4
five six seven songs I'm perfect for a
mini Cog right worst case I can still
sing more but so we can stay here after
seven songs or I mean I kind of have to
time it
but kind of have to time it so H 2.0
well I'm in 3D right now when we talk
about 2.0 and 3.0 we talk about life
2D now I'm in 3D though Life 3d but
whatever I'm going to sing an anime song
that I found uh like when I was like
digging through our Kad
application uh to see what they have at
this point what they have to offer for D
yeah and there was one anime song that I
was like oh I know this song I haven't
heard it in a million years I'm
surprised they have it in here I was
surprised to be reminded by its
existence uh I wonder if you guys know
it
so the first
song is from an old
anime
uh do you guys know magy Nikki
magy really old uh
it's really
old okay where was my oh yeah here I'm
going to use
the uh app for the first
time so where is it
[Music]
uh I mean not I think I think I'm am I
using I think I'm using it for the first
time on stream where did it
[Music]
go ah this one okay okay uh I'll be
adjusting audio as we go garu let's go
ah oh yeah yeah yeah let's go let's
go it takes a while to start it loads
each
time come on
oh oh
oh hello
[Music]
go I know it's loud
okay okay now it should be now it should
be
[Music]
good for
hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi hi
[Music]
I'm so nervous oh my God
I said I would be chilled to myself
there I said that to myself
[Music]
go hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi oh God I made so many mistakes it's
okay because this is this is all just
like you know the
[Music]
beginning okay I actually uh I
accidentally closed the chat and I only
was seeing you in OBS and I kind kind of
made me sad so let me get you guys I
need to open the window
again open then there you go now I can
see you
properly okay so so so so so so so and
what is the W going to reveal I'm sure a
lot of you were you know already
thinking about it I forgot the starting
tweet oh okay let me let me do that and
tell everybody that it's time to come in
I'm sweating my hands are sweating so
crazy but just my hands that's it's nice
I
guess oh
sure it's nothing I'm not I don't know I
don't know it's third
hat uh we have started it's time to
reveal you know people normally when
it's like whenever we talk about reveals
usually you know we like to stall until
like 1 hour into the stream and and
that's like kind of become tradition so
people might expect nothing right now
but I'm going to show you something
thing yeah it's not an hour
in okay so you saw me right you watched
you know you watched
me you perceived me you saw how stiff I
am I may have said you know it's not
life Tod 2.0 and whatever but what I
have for prepared for you today it's
actually so to say wa
self commission and organized uh like
it's not an official thing that you know
it's not even in the official app but
it's wa was very own 3D uh
2.0
Yay see right now for example I can't
even move my
eyebrows but okay in the in the 2.0 the
eyebrows are more realistically behind
the uh bank so you won't be able to see
them much but at least they move and my
my eyeballs are barely moving this is
the limit this is the limit like it they
they barely move okay I can't put down
my tongue for example I can't move my
mouth
like from left to right or soever so
what did I do I got 51 blend shapes
uh actually I thought I would use it for
ofy uh but uh well I didn't I
couldn't so today I'm doing it for you
and the cool thing is okay just one one
more thing that you I want you to pay
attention to I can do like you know a
while ago oh yeah we had like this
feature of this hands but they're really
laggy most of the time
see like 1 FPS and and they're really in
accurate inaccurate and they they uh
like see I I don't I'm not even doing
any of that so they suck right so um
remember froggy waa basically I'm going
to use the same tool that I used for
froggy waa hands not the whole I don't
have to use my whole motion capture suit
I have a different tool for just the
hands which is like more comfortable and
all that so yeah that's all kinds of
things just a little a little
explanation of of what's going to happen
okay are you ready to to see this yeah
yeah it's not gloves no no no it's not
gloves it's like a little a little
little
thing okay I hope I didn't get your
hopes up too
high but I think the the difference is
quite quite strong honestly like my eyes
I can't even move my freaking eyebrows
you know it's so stiff everything is so
stiff h
yeah okay oh and my mouth shapes there's
not many mouth shapes and I can't puff
my cheeks so okay here we go uh goodbye
H Life app I don't need you
anymore goodbye H Life app I have
something
else okay I also prepared some nice
filters so that I look cooler are you
ready for
[Music]
this hi no lgy hands yay I mean they're
not like the the best either
but
POG my eyebrows
move
uh it's hard to move them without moving
my eyes right now but um they move they
move
like SC and I have expressions and stuff
and I have these hands so now with these
Great Expressions I thought we should
sing some more songs so that you will
see how beautifully my mouth and my eyes
and everything move you
[Music]
know yeah and maybe I will use my my
hands a little bit to sing
along yeah that is a lot different right
like if you see like the before after
it's crazy and there's still like some
things to be improved like there's a a
little bug but besides that it's like
amazing I want to say right away thank
you so much to HK for throwing this
together it's amazing I'm so happy I'm
so happy that I can be less stiff
now
oh yeah I don't need life Tod 3.0 I got
my tongue out
[Music]
[Laughter]
already sorry that was a cat hair in my
mouth
okay so let's sing a song Wait we sang
One song already so I guess this is now
after six so don't forget I'm showing
you something cool now but there's still
an announcement coming up so you better
stay all
right now let me try to calm the
down cuz I'm so nervous I'm so nervous
let's start with a let's start let's
continue with a Holo song that I most
nervous about perhaps so that we get it
behind
me
[Music]
uh we're not going anywhere yeah I hope
so I hope so for you oh
sh okay
uh I'm going to sing M from
M okay
[Music]
iee
for ah ah ah ah ah I in know
[Music]
fore
fore foree
[Music]
ah ah ah ah
ah
[Music]
fore
ah ah
[Music]
ah ah ah ah ah ah
[Applause]
[Music]
man I could sing that better I practiced
that so much and I messed up so much
no it's so okay though I showed you my
tears which is another feature but tears
no W crying W is so
sad
no well that song is also difficult
because um there is like only an
instrumental but no no like K version
normally we all have like K versions for
our songs where there's like some backup
vocals oh but she doesn't have that for
this song so I have to like be really
really secure about what I'm
singing yeah it's such a it's such an
emotional song it's so beautiful I
wanted to sing it with a little more
little bit more feeling well maybe we
can sing it again as an UNC when I'm
more calm
down uh H yeah I
can I think I get pretty close to uh
Go's little
face no this is like the most I can open
it
I think it gets pretty
close oh yeah and the puffy cheeks I
didn't show you
yet wait
oh
no ah ah wait I have them like
separately too like I can I can uh
trigger them but I can like I can
trigger them with a button or I can
trigger them myself ah there you go
and they they do get puffy and then and
then
look I I'm trying to wait the pulling
thing
I'm doing it yeah I did it I did the
pulling thing let's
go okay
wait okay I wanted to turn a little bit
more towards the microphone immersion
wow okay that was another song you're
getting an announcement in five songs
already oh wo wo wo
wo thank you work
show my face is so meable now right like
wow what 51 blend shs can do to your
face too bad I have a short tongue so
triggering the tongue is pretty
difficult for
me yeah okay H let's do next song oh
okay let's do let's do
let's do that one let's do that one
another anime song we're going to go
back and forth back and forth I would
say
um where did I put
it
[Music]
oh uh blind as always what am I singing
a there it
is
okay so many windows
open
Play hope this is going to not be too
loud Main
norin Cross
[Music]
he he I I I I
ie
[Music]
for spee
there you go I'm nervous again
[Music]
woohoo
for
[Music]
for I I I I I I I
i i i i i i
[Music]
i
d for
[Music]
I I I I I I I I I I I
I one
[Music]
more oh it's pretty long for any long
ending and a bit more
wrap it up wrap it up hey hey wrap it up
thanks
guys thank
you
D is there any song that I'm not going
to mess up
no that question was by me don't worry
it wasn't in the
chat so okay okay okay okay that was fun
though main I I don't think I ever sang
that in a k before
for so that might be a first uh I have
one two three is it really now it should
be four right
possibly yeah four more
songs oh oh oh oh oh oh okay I better
not Yap I better get straight to the
track
wow wow wow wow I'm going to do another
whole life song what is it going to be
now what will it be
[Music]
well I know what it is do you know what
it
is let me put you over here let me put
OBS over
here okay no more
like
this okay ahh wait the no way
did I was it off for the whole
song no way way no
way no
way I hate
myself no way no way I had that off the
whole time okay we're going to sing
rebellion was it on okay was it no
probably
not oh
well n
get this body started by a fire like the
fire you desire chasing all that we
Inspire spreading out like wild fire
never ever have I ever a dream I take
chance light the
fire come pull me out I'm out of sheep
to count Overkill of Saddle stories
wearing me down snap out of the system
break out give it everything this is our
time we're used to
discover hello brand new world would you
welcome the
light and free us from the
night fire fire light the fire brighter
High you the night Bea dance into the
flame of life
dancing to the End of
[Music]
Time Bri High to the chasing all that we
ins one step to the left two steps to
the right then back to where we started
and then over again step out of the
circle go break out we got everything
this is our time we're yours to
discover take us home to where we
belong and free us from the
night take us
to dancing to dancing to that flame of
life so let so
oning to the End of
Time
[Music]
keep oh
narissa I know that I can still be think
it was too early know that I can still
be the future of the story I know that I
can be free the one and the only they
tell me that I'm crazy I'll never let
them stop me with
this our Advent
[Music]
begins
Hearts jump the end of time
[Music]
to the flame of
Life dancing to endellion
[Music]
to high youire time to get
started it's ironic they end the party
when they sing get this party
started I want to get this party started
though look get my hope
stop free songs left
[Music]
wow yeah thank
you w w wo wo W
Rebellion I love the song and I love
nissa's belts 3D streams from now on
well I I do feel like you know with such
an expressive little face where I can
even do
this or even okay I haven't shown this
one
yet upgraded Gangi
mdy yeah shook I'm Shook and I can also
what was this oh yeah I can also do
[Applause]
[Music]
this reaction
image that's pretty good oh y
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah pretty good yeah for thumbnails
it's more expressive too if I if I need
but actually a Chey chy I think can kind
of make all these faces too for me um
when making like poses so that's not you
know too new I think for the sake of
thumbnails you won't believe what
happened next oh you won't believe what
wa is singing next uh what did I say
that as if it's so exciting uh it's
probably not
um what's on my list
next
no okay never non whole life songs song
Perhaps I have two more whole life songs
and one more U vocal song actually
and one that is very familiar to you
guys but I maybe I sang it alone
before maybe I did let's not forget the
echo cuz I'm going to cry if I forget it
again
well you should know you should have
heard me sing this before but I wasn't
alone before so here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
hey hey
hey
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
staye
[Applause]
[Music]
foree no
that
[Music]
for say
fore
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
fore foree
y finally a song I didn't completely
mess
up
[Music]
Wow Let's go thank
you my hands actually go together I can
even kind of do this this is actually
insane because I think with my uh my
proper so to say map my expensive 12,000
or whatever $112,000 MO cap my hands
don't go
together unless we do some like post
edit but not everything is like super
accurate with this like I can do this
but my hands go together when they're
actually together but funnily enough I
don't think I can well well
yeah something of a
heart not
really can you give us an a
prop wait no yeah that's kind of a
problem because the fum is like not
where the camera would see it wait also
it really overheats that's kind of
worrying to me it crashed before I think
but then I just restart it but
yeah I can give you a thumbs
down
wait uh
kind
of and I can
probably no uh difficult cuz H I might
be able to like improve this at some
point probably with the positioning cuz
there's like different kind of positions
you can put this uh hand tracking device
in um
where was it oh
there
and do you notice
something this is my smug
face smug
face okay with this I'll sing another
song we have 10 moments all perfectly
calculated let's go
middle fing is a little bit difficult to
I can do that when I I can thumbs up and
middle finger I can do better when I'm
in my actual mocab stuff with my $6,000
gloves cuz this one it's like a little
camera so to say um it doesn't look like
a camera but it's actually kind of a
camera it's a leap motion and is like
placed on my table so when I want to
show you my hands uh well yeah there's a
chance that they won't really see which
finger if it's like above the rest of
the hand you know what I
mean yeah yeah yeah oh yeah most
mention please sing for blood I don't
prepare for blood
a but you can listen to my song cover if
you want if you're if you're really
craving
it okay H I have two more songs and
they're H life songs
one that I think you guys always wanted
me to sing and I'm also nervous
about but
G which which ID song have you guys been
asking for a
lot you have two lead motions from the
kickstarter oh you supported it oh
you're one of the reasons why I have it
I guess
Anya no
no Everlasting knif I sang that before
sip some tea I sang that too before
didn't I bro bro I sank sip some tea
several
times bro you you were always asking for
illusion
night
hey and that's what I'm going to sing
[Applause]
[Music]
kiss me keep those lips from wondering
off tell me every sweet and tender F
give me all you have to give more
fantasies where Futures are born Can You
Feel The Beat the rhm the tune your
heart and mind a
countdown if you feel something come
coming to you believe it and scream it
aloud I don't think I'll miss you any
more like I the day you left there's so
many just like you I could
you cuz passion's burning bright we hurt
till in the end the city will swallow
the
pain tomorrow's another
day G calls at on darling show time SP
moment Dancing in the Moonlight till
your gate starts weighing my body keep
your eyes on
me take me somewhere deep into the night
touch me here there anywhere you like
trust me won't you let me look inside
fantasies and Futures coll just two of
us Beneath The stary Sky
[Music]
no need to say goodbye to me I'm already
gone just wipe all your tears
away and know we start over
[Music]
somay hi hi hi
hi how does this part go
[Music]
again you belong to one and I'm being
taken over by the harmony oh
no
the bond between us grw tied we're
closer than we've ever been follow me
mat your R to mine and let it all out
from
within I don't think
I
miss I missed it
[Music]
though burn bright and quick when cand
wind could never last a city that's
living in fast forward the perfect place
for lovers like us to take a chance
there's nothing here to stop us when in
Ro Rance and I won't let you leave me
alone without a dance I don't want to
hear you
goodbye don't break the illusion
tonight curtain calls at dawn darling
Showtime spend forever living till the
sunrise fill that look even with the
lights up dance until
[Music]
we Sorry way I got really nervous
sorry way I messed up so
much okay
yeah H yeah yeah yeah yeah JMA is
writing to me JMA did you wake up just
for
this announcement you know I'm fine it's
been it's been free over I I keep on
saying three and a half years these past
days but it's
like already way past 3 and a half years
at this point we're almost four 4 years
actually 4 years is maybe closer now or
is
said but yeah I'll wait until the
announcement and then I'll sing another
song the last
one oh she didn't
sleep damn go go to
sleep actually wait I didn't save the
picture yet to show it on over here let
me grab
it where is it where is it I I have it
don't worry JMA don't don't worry JMA
don't worry I got it I got it I found it
what yeah what was I saying about the
four years I don't remember what I was
saying a yeah then like after almost
four years don't worry don't worry you
need you don't need to be here for
everything it's
okay so there's going to be a tweet
going out maybe I'll be I'm going to be
a little bit earlier than this I
surprised that not many of you guys were
like uh expecting
this just I don't know why I don't know
why you guys don't not many people or I
sound like almost no one guessing that
this is the
announcement so I'm quite
surprised
uh what will it be what will it be my
down download folder still loads so long
oh no come on download folder you have
two minutes to
load where did I oh yeah
here I guess fre the outfit but not new
3D
model what do you I mean 3D outfit I'm
never getting that because I used up my
1 million wish so that's not it
sadly okay I'm going to announce it now
announce announcement
[Music]
time are you ready I'm so excited so
this is for Sunday
T takana new outfit
review fav night is
real what fite is Real June 9th we're
starting the stream at the same time as
today is Sunday at this time H fite
wa let's
go so we're having actually two reveals
this week
oh you guys are being you guys are being
in for tree you're being spoiled
yeah
yay exciting new outfit
reveal that this is actually my 2020
free
outfit yeah oh Mone didn't throw it but
it's uh well it's obviously you can
already tell I think it's obviously
going to be inspired by fever Knight my
original song that I uh released couple
years ago it's crazy that I can say a
couple years ago it's actually weird to
say
that getting outfits left and right I
guess so are you are you getting outfits
left and right well now you're getting
one frontally from me frontally and
vertically well I actually you're
getting it no okay today is vertical but
the reveal stream will not be vertical
although I was thinking like actually
you could totally do it in a vertical
stream because there's no reason for it
to be horizontal I guess I don't
know would be dope it's it's an idea
it's an idea if I can see someone doing
it then it would be narissa
verti fiva W let's go it's not going to
be vertical though
no
yeah please go and check it out yeah so
it's like two days so I don't really
expect many people to participate in a
silhouette drawing but I guess I'll um I
guess I suppose I I might put the
silhouette up anyway for people who do
want to give it a try but yeah I mean
usually there's always so many
submissions that I can't feature all of
them anyway so we we're going to give it
a
try it's tradition yeah but I do have
something else in mind uh to spend the
time until the reveal with I have I've
had something in my mind for a long time
now now I still didn't 100% figure it
all out how I'm going to do it um but uh
I have an idea h of what what we'll be
doing besides looking at silhouette
guessing yeah pictures a
treadmill h no let's just say I I do
want to use my 3D for uh whatever comes
before the outfit
reveal that is the
plan oh when I drink water my my cheek
sco p
damn let's
go you're going to dance our names how
do you do that how I don't know how that
would work but I have one more
song so please stay at least for one
more
[Music]
song Oh tweet is out by the way I'm
going to retweeted
afterwards I messed up like pretty much
every song now this one for sure I'll
also mess
up wait so this can
go this can go but I can say what for
people who came in later and do you
think they're wondering like what what
what did she reveal what's different
maybe if you didn't see the before after
then you're like H but yeah uh
um 3D 2 let's just call it 3D 2.0 for
now reveal
this this is what what's happening now
okay besides you know I think it's
pretty obvious yeah really I really like
how much more my my eyeballs
move
hi hi
it's
nice
okay come on Wawa come on Wawa don't
crumble under every single pressure
don't just sing like you sang when you
practiced
but I'm going to mess up I'm going to
mess
up last song
is from
go sh
sh
sh ah this one starts right
away I'll have okay I'll at least have
to find my way into it
[Music]
one one more come on that's like where
the hell are we
[Music]
sorry okay I freaked out sorry sorry
sorry one more
I learned this today okay
[Music]
memories
for for
[Music]
la la la la la
la it's
[Music]
raining fore
that wasn't the
worst okay can I
read can I try red doing
[Music]
M I want to
try now that we're through all the songs
now now that we've done all of
them maybe I'll just redo all of the
songs no but I want to redo
this it's just like cuz I learned like
five six seven songs in one day even
though I sang each like so many times
when I when I sing it a few few times in
a go in one roow then it's like super no
problem but when I like mix them all now
and then they're like leaving my brain
cuz I just learned them today and then
it's like how does this go again how
does this go
again panic panic M somebody said M
wasn't so bad you
think thank you but I'll I'll still redo
it where did I have the lyrics
h ah here right in front of me I already
have them open I'm like looking for my
tabs where is oh I already have it open
I'm so
dumb I'm so
dumb okay let's try
again it starts at like 12 seconds 12
[Music]
seconds
e for
[Music]
my on my
fore
[Music]
fore fore
ah
[Music]
ahe fore
no mama e
[Music]
[Applause]
I look so
sad bamboozle I'm not
sad I'm not sad I'm excited for my
outfit
Reve we we we we this Sunday at June 9th
H 1 p.m. PD 4:00 p.m. Ed 1000 p.m. W
time m
6 maybe 6: a.m.
jst on Sunday Sunday Sunday
Sunday so late but it's just like a
usually it's just like a 1 hour stream
so don't worry about it don't worry
about
it what's that in Freedom time this is
freedom time is that not Freedom time to
you 1 p.m. PDT and 400 p.m.
EDT what here I translated I mean you
may not be able to read like military
time okay I'll give you that but I said
it out loud for
you yeah that is freedom
time that it literally is freedom time
how clearer can I make it how much
clearer hey this time I'm I'm not so
unhappy with how I did with M cuz at
least Le I didn't miss all the
say timings and uh a lot of other things
yeah was better was definitely
better no C wait what was C is C my time
no Central you mean Central Central
American time I don't know somewhere in
between there
right I got so much cat hair on my face
y illusion night again I can sing it
better with waya I feel like at this
point if I don't hear way again I'm
going to be so lost again should we sing
it with way
together I
mean it's got to be with
[Music]
way okay doet doet
time let me drink some water
though the cheeks went puffy again
sing with
[Applause]
[Music]
way kiss me keep those lips from
wondering off tell me every sweet and
tender thought give me all you have to
give and more fantasies where few
Bor Can You Feel The Beat the RM to tune
your heart and mind
countown if you feel something coming to
you believe it and scream it
Al I don't think I'll miss you any like
I did you there so many just like you
like instead cuz passion burning R hurts
you in the end the city will SW follow
the
pain another
today calls at darling time spend moment
Dancing in the Moonlight till your game
starts weighing with my body keep your
eyes on
me take me somewhere deep into the night
touch me here there anywhere you like
trust me won't you let me look inside
fantasies and futes Collide it's just
the two of us the
SK it's the only way to keep on living
is keep on living strong then you can
keep the kindness cuz I'm moving no need
to say goodbye to me I'm already gone
just your tears
away and now let start today okay I
ready all you
heart no don't s here wait great
[Music]
time your heart your soul your body you
belong to one and only un
conditionning knowing no one else will
do feel the B between us TI we're Clos
we've ever
been your rib to mine and let it all out
fromin I don't think I miss you any I
did the day you I say I love you know
I'll take it back I'm used to this I'm
not to same
loser ring quick when camels and wind
could never last a city that's living in
fast for the perfect place for like us
to take a turn there's nothing here to
stop us when
in and I won let you leave me alone
without a dance I don't want to hear it
goodbye don't break the illusion
tonight and call that darling show time
spend forever living till the sun rise
[Music]
all right that was
better it's so different when you
actually
hear uh the
Melody and I was just so
nervous forgive me waya
H but she also did two takes right on
Kima she also did two takes on Chima so
maybe you know I was allowed to do two
Tes too my sorry I was feeling a little
bit
stiff very stiff
actually see that's what I mean when I I
love this I can kind of there's a lot of
adjustments I can make with like the
hand position like right now is drinking
water and my hand was like you know
quite far I could like adjust all of
that but then other things look weird
but I'm I'm uh way happier with this
than with
the our own like you know the hand
tracking that kind of works through the
phone that one is like extremely laggy
and
inaccurate not reliable but funny funny
the first first time the few first few
times when we did
it the leaks above thank you for
acknowledging it yeah I can now today
for the Super Chat reading I can throw
you kisses
again again as in I think I did that
maybe as forua or so I definitely did it
before illusion night hope for doet with
rain next school have opportunity yeah
if we do if we made a again for an off
collab and maybe like we do Off K yeah
for
sure I got to learn all of waya
songs yeah right I mostly memmed you
that's
right oh I'm uses Leap Motion in her 3D
soon you can ask her how she does it
with the
regular oh I wouldn't uh automatically
agree that she assume that she uses the
regular app for that either I didn't see
a an option for Leap Motion but maybe
there is but also the thing is so okay
the thing
is this when I'm when I why my face
looks like so much more expressive right
now is called 51 blend shapes okay I
don't know much about this stuff either
okay I was I learned this stuff from
like Amy and and husk and so on um but
it's called 51 blend shapes I guess
because there like yeah my my face is
just 51 times better now
um and um I can't use this in the whole
life app
unless unless I use like a 1 million
wish for
it so I have to use an external app for
it which is allowed and all that
yeah yeah um
which uh also means that like for
example when I do full body
3D I can probably figure out how to use
my full body 3D in external apps as well
um but up until now I was using the
whole live app for that and then I
wouldn't be able to combine the fresh
looking fancy 51 Bland shapes with the
full body tracking that I can't do
because I don't have the 51 blend Jabs
in my in the app in the Holo app 2
million endurance stream if I get 2
million that's not what I'm using it for
you know guys what I would be using it
for
but yeah can you commission models with
new designs
um
um well I've like I've I've commissioned
like like Po low po models
before uh I I I think I'm a allowed to
do like more high quality models too but
it's like really expensive so I don't
know about that oh good night JMA sleep
[Music]
well two million wishes for the third
hat
no by the way I can I can put my hats
on but no oh yeah I wanted to show you
like the super cool let me put on BM I
want to show you some super cool things
I can do in this external app do you
want to see
it let's get rid of um this for a moment
so right now I have some filters on
right
uh uh so okay
uh light settings okay so we
have like okay all kinds of Shadows and
stuff and like ambient lighning ignore
the lighting let's look at the effects
cuz the effects are pretty dope so I
currently have a
bloomon which I can make stronger like
it can be like uh uh like this
wo I can totally become a
goling but let me show you all the all
the features right this is w
wow that's a bloom I had it on a little
bit then ambient occlusion oh I don't
know I think it's just I'm not sure what
that does I didn't have it on Lance
Distortion is funny are you
ready
hi hi what's
up wait wait wait wait you can have your
white waa I think yeah I mean this is
kind of white
waa oh
oh it's almost as if I did something
wrong in my
settings what does this one do oh oh
oh
oh who what is this it's like Center X
axe what
w w what's happening here I'm not sure
where's normal where's normal I don't I
don't know what's I think we were like
somewhere here here right what is this
oh this doesn't do anything oh and then
there's the scale oh oh oh
oh I feel like I mean I've never taken
drugs before but I feel like this might
be how it would
be
what okay reset spaghetti what this why
does this feel ah okay okay okay I
thought I thought because I said I put
reset settings I thought what do you
mean this is my default is this am I
just like going crazy right
now you mean I'm supposed to look like
this I guess so I'm just like too
freaked out by what I just
saw and the normal normal me doesn't
look normal anymore but no this is
normal but now I feel like my head is
kind of long is it
not no I guess not but I'm having that
effect right now like I saw I saw myself
weirdly and now I'm like
it I can never look at myself normal
again my head looks really big my my top
the top of my head looks big to
me okay we have um a yeah oh this is
really cool this is what kind of makes
my head a little bit longer but I can
you see can you tell look at the bottom
and the top especially the bottom I
think is very
noticeable it's chromatic aberration
it's so
cool makes it look I don't know like TV
I don't know you don't like this effect
well I like it deal with
it it's it's so
cool and then there's uh oh yeah I can
do like well colors
right colors colors but this is just I
can just do in OBS anyway and then oh
this is cool uh
if I want to look like low quality or
like TV
is okay you got to look closely if
you're on your phone or so you got to
yeah I'll make him bigger for you but I
can make him small
too I can like grain grain
myself
grain
ah maybe for gossing waa a little bit of
grain would help I don't know
and then this is maybe the coolest thing
and I'm thinking maybe Amma use this for
her playthrough of Oprah din or
something like
that yo this is so sick this is so sick
half tone I'm like a manga I'm no more
anime I'm
[Music]
manga sick filter right I know and then
you know I can make it like you know
however I want I can make it brighter
and I can change the dot grid
size to be like
less oh oh and I guess I oh I forgot I
didn't realize yeah I can change like
the color the white
level I going be like orangish and then
the dot size factor is also a
thing but I would make the dots smaller
like this so you can still see my
features quite well
maybe this looks like when I'm on your
Pip
Boy this is how I looked in the
1500s Game Boy yeah Game Boy Game Boy
vaa Game Boy
baa Game Boy w got to be more green
a like a
dirty dirty screen and then probably
like darker like this oh my the thing is
kind of
interesting and what does a pit boy say
hello uh you you are uh you are
crippled congratulations you're
crippled good
luck don't lose your head don't lose
your head and uh oh make sure to use
your fum which I can't really well maybe
you can use it this way around too
probably not a good idea um but yeah the
mushroom the mushroom cloud
right snake snake I go sneaky NY NY NY
NY NY NY sneaky like I'm
snake thanks peep Joel you're
welcome uh Metal Gear one yeah see I'm
like all all kinds of old school things
and then I go back to normal wow
[Music]
W yeah wait let me let me try to shush
Gosling wait oh wait if you type in
Gosling I guess it's just his name what
about the movie what do I type in to
find that movie
scene goling
meme oh that's it oh that's pretty
purple for some reason I was thinking of
it more like like
orange it's pretty purple a Blade Runner
is what it is purple
okay but
what H but isn't he looking at like
a like a like a uh like a what's it
called he's looking at he's looking at
some
something a hologram yeah I want to see
a picture of
the of the Hologram oh yeah uh wait
that's those are just memes that's
that's not what really was there
before don't put Barbie
there oh well whatever let's let's
freestyle it I feel like I'm already
pretty close
though uh so
more more of this
who what the
I can give myself a tan I
think what what's
this
who oh I see now that's what that is
it's like a shadow yeah I guess so
ambient occlusion is what it's
called well there's some funky looking
Parts there
this is
so well that doesn't work quite well
does it oh but oh with blue it's kind of
cool like if I make it a little bit
lighter I don't know this it can't be
cool if if my if around my like eyelids
it wouldn't look so funky
the inside of my mouth looks
blue okay no we don't need this that's
weird what else was
there the grain right we we want a
little bit of
grain or we can have colored grain
apparently I don't
know and do we want
some I don't know do we want some of uh
does this
help not
[Music]
really I love
this wait I
oh what does this
do
oh
no no back to
normal that was
that that was the bloom let's make the
bloom
stronger
uh yeah I mean and
then
wait I'm too I got to be like
this it's a bit difficult with the arms
right now wait I can probably
change that that's that's that's the
thing here that just appeared that that
that thing over
there oh what is it
here see this is like wa I can make it
smaller and bigger and depending on that
the hands will like be further away or
closer to that you see woo smack that
ass smack that ass smack that ass smack
it smack it smack it smack it
good I don't know anymore what we're
going
for
probably further I don't
know I can do this woo woo
I had the
height this is like I can set a base for
it so
push and push and push and push and
push it's so
go let's keep it
closer feel like I'm messing up
everything shouldn't play around with it
that much oh wait this this
uh
huh okay okay okay
whoa okay
here wait let's remove
the mic and then you got your little you
got your little
screenshot wait that's
[Music]
wrong which one's my
microphone there it is
you cutie PTI I don't even know what she
says in the uh movie I think I've seen
the scene before but what do I say like
well marry me
or what do you I what did I
say what's the is there a phrase you
look lonely
a you look
lonely little chicken
you look lonely and I can change
that come with
[Laughter]
me cut that's a
wrap
[Music]
W all right all right I'm going to read
super chats now in this new
form exciting should I keep all these
effects or should I I don't I think it
just you know it's interesting to see
that I can do this kind of stuff maybe
we'll we'll turn a few off
um we'll turn the grain off and we'll
turn off the chromatic operation
here
okay so did you like it did you like the
the new uh 3D wav 2.0 hm actually I
guess 2.0 there's like depends depends
on how you see it because remember our
scuff 3d full body
3D that also made like separ sepal
several
Transformations
right H but when it comes to the face
only see I messed up the hands so much
they should not be here when it comes to
the hand and the face only then this is
an an
upgrade that kind of it reminds me of um
how my face I don't was that I don't
think it was 51 blend shipes remember
when that that little life that I did at
Amy's
place where my eyes were also pretty
goggly
googly and I was like dancing around
am my my face was more
Express expressive than usual there but
I don't think it was uh 51 blend
shapes let me reset
the the leap motion kind
of where did I have
it got to be in the
middle there we go
that should
be kind of
it thank you for the red I I can fix
you I will try to fix you but it's just
like with frogy waa om Meo Meo are you
here let me mod
[Music]
you and stand up mod I don't know you've
been modded look beautiful f thank you
[Music]
see I got 51 PL CHS let's
go M mint is
here everybody
scatter no there's no reason to scatter
I'm I'm so
[Music]
happy D she hunting us
I'm so scared I'm so
scared yeah yeah yeah wait what was I
what was I going to say before she
showed
up you guys know what I was trying
to
say I don't I don't
remember something about shapes super CH
well no ah I mentioned froggy wobble you
guys
are you guys are supposed to help
me because yeah frogy waa remember frogy
waa I used to like you know use my hands
a lot because it's so fun to like be
able to use them without having to wear
you know like the whole suit the whole
getup so I think you know every once in
a while when I feel like it when I when
I don't mind wearing my default outfit
for specific specific stream then I
think I I'll I'll be using my little
Leap Motion
to have the hands ready
[Music]
my hands are
powerful hey y' hey y'
lucky I'm not I'm not that perfect I'm
not that freaking
perfect I don't hey don't compare me
with he's such a pervert
M
what cat hair in my mouth let's
go okay so we're going to read Super
Chat guys where do I when did I leave
off help me out
please do you
know I want to one more I wonder if we
can do this I don't know husk if you're
listening but I was thinking you know
kissy face kissy lips if we can make my
mouth into like a a number free you know
like the cat
face cuz like that's I guess that's a a
thing that it doesn't it I see it
capturing my my kissy
face in like the phone app that I have
but it doesn't translate to the free
model 3D model maybe that's a
possibility to like
put like like a yeah like that you know
what I
mean
what what do you mean coefficient is
coefficient also in the
chat I didn't see
him why your hands so small
small normal size normal size hands if
anything big anime had
they mean you me what
oh I'm not coefficient if anything
coefficient was waa but I am
waa you know like it's not like I am
coefficient just because you want my
outfit once or twice doesn't mean that
he's the real waa
seems like we need to clear up some
things
here obviously I'm the real
wa please guys don't don't
misunderstand I'm the real one you know
it you're used to you're used to a no
belly hair Wawa
remember belly hair waa is not the real
waa
waa barely has hair the real
one okay so anyway super
chats H sorry did anybody tell me like
what's the Super Chat I should uh which
which
stream I'm perceiving
you Fallout the the most recent one
by the way tomorrow we are also
streaming Fallout
we Fallout fallout
Fallout uh
okay can't tilt the camera
though oh yeah I can why which
way we can do a little bit of this or
this
je I Can Read Super chats like
this where was
my where
was I
here pathetic
pathetic it's not the first time I'm in
3D guys
like you guys are acting like this is
the first time I'm in
Fr R Bell hair yeah that's right that's
that's the real Wawa the no belly hair
Wawa is the Real the true form of
me hurt
us see that actually worked better with
slap your butt slap your butt slap your
butt no let me let me come back to
normal okay so so so so so Tak
seeing you and Fry is somewhat rare
compared to the others yeah I guess so
but this isn't even this isn't even
normal
fry this is my upgraded awesome
fry expressive
frie okay Super Chat reading
time thumbnails
Fallout wait so the second Fallout
stream or the first
one I think the second one
right yeah okay I almost started reading
the first
one I'm going to put it up just just you
know oh but wait I have to put up my
wait let's let's
okay let's put this
here super chat reading
time okay now you don't you don't need
the thumbnail do you there's not much
space
here there's not much
space okay
I've only had more stuff space to put
well no like no no don't don't criticize
this form because like normally I don't
F that much out in the screen there's so
much space left and right and actually
this is better for revealing I thought
it's better to reveal something
like this stuff because I only need this
and this is all I need to show you so
it's actually perfect that's why I
thought oh well I never tried short
stream before actually it could be kind
of makes sense for this purpose it
works okay here we go going to read
super
chats little py dun I was going to read
the Super Chat itself before reading
your
name thank you D check out 47 D oh yeah
pineapple hit 1 million thank you guys
thank you and I saw just randomly I
don't know why but YouTube recommended
me my Korean version of do you and I saw
it was at half a million which I'm not
telling you guys to stream it or so I
didn't even think because it's just a a
a second version of the song that was
released like a year a year after the do
you original release I released the
Korean version I think so I I didn't
think it would get anywhere near that
half a fam milon on a uh like a
different language version it's pretty
sick H Korean Bros
probably listening to it a lot I don't
know you told a cute Korean streamer
that she should check out the Korean
version really thank you when was
that oh my God
hello yeah yeah I don't know I I I I
haven't looked at like how many views it
has for I don't know since the release
so that was uh really surprising I was
like what is it half a million what
people so many people listen to this I
wonder if there was like actual like a
spurt of growth at some
point or if it just grew
steadily but thank
you thank you for listening to the
Korean version of do you and for
pineapple hitting 1 million yeah many
milestones in terms of songs I Love It J
D Omega
gaming g k St
B
action space waterall d cobs than pinky
your podcast mode for me today because
I'm at work but uh get Boon as a
companion he likes to clock up Legion
yeah I did get boon and then I got
another
one I have this feeling you guys are
going to keep on making me replace my
companions over and over again is that
like a is that like I don't know if if
that's normal if that's what you just do
in Fallout then I'm fine with
it but I genuinely don't know if most
people just stay with the
same companion until the
end you can have two I had like a dog
right later on
those two are the best H
okay I'm surprised you find like the
best ones right in the beginning when
the game is so long and so
easily like they're literally on the
way on the main quest
path use so you like your game your
rules
okay you're supposed to switch it oh
really you're supposed to switch it
[Music]
up depends on the person some people
stick with the same companion some
switch out all the
time I see I might stay if I'm happy
with Veronica what's her name then I'll
I'll keep her I
suppose after finishing their companion
Quest I switch them all
I don't think I'll be doing that that
much though I guess that's for
completionists where was
I oh
yeah no
b space waterful wait I already read
those cops that was the pinky that I was
talking to thank you CS D appreciate
it I feel like I wanted to say something
and I forgot about
it oh well L St thank you oh I must say
your frd is so realistic especially that
Chima Dance I'm looking forward to
seeing you seeing everyone react to your
fre at ofai what do you mean your oh cuz
the your is in like exclamation marks
you mean the
coefficient that was was 40 though that
was actually
40 cuz I'm assuming it comes with a a
certain degree of
[Music]
scent yeah he's not that what do you
mean oh no I don't mean
40 four for d
[Music]
St now we didn't get the smell
coefficient I guess you didn't get close
enough you should
have some of you guys maybe did I'm sure
some of you guys took pictures with
him Guru D nathon thanks for the pinky
honestly analysis paralysis is my most
constant problem so life as your cat
wouldn't be wait this is I think I know
what this is about when I was like is
this when I talked about my
cats not being able to
decide what to do or
so ah pade oh she streamed up until
now wow thank you it was Pano's birthday
happy
birthday I can't believe she really has
my merch yo she sent me a picture of her
backpack
the turquoise one and today on her
stream she showed off the little memo
memo
pad can't believe it yo because
like that you you would H have to have
ordered it like
sevenish 7 eight months ago wait was
that my
anniversary Anniversary
merchandise limited I I don't think it
was I'd be surprised if she even got the
limited stuff was it even limited I
don't think that was limited this time
anniversary so
that's 6 7 8 n nine months
ago
W because why I'm saying this is because
like like that means already N9 months
ago she loved me that much it's not just
recently because I noticed her or so
which means she's a real one it's she's
a real one it's a legit
one that's what I'm trying to point
[Music]
out she's Italian
no I asked
her if she likes the
beach she said no and I was really
disappointed by
it and I didn't tell her why I even
asked this
question I was just
already considering my
options if I can
go to
Italy and go to the beach with her
but she said she doesn't like the beach
at all so I was like
e well let's go to the
[Music]
mountains yes you
fumbled like you could have gone the
beach for me how much do you hate the
beach that you would miss out on a
chance like
that no but like maybe maybe sometime we
can um hang out in Italy I don't know
Italy's big and I don't know which area
you're in but maybe maybe I don't
know you know we're close we're close
you and
me distance is not an issue
[Music]
P hates sand well I know sand isn't so
great and and I guess also like a lot of
there's certainly good Italian beaches
but a lot of them are
also not so good so maybe she doesn't
like them because of those experiences
she would probably like them if it was
like the
mes just as an example of a beautiful
Beach where you cannot say you hate the
beach there's no way you can say you
hate
it there's no
way it's CL and rough and it gets
everywhere sand all my homies hate
sand but yeah anyway happy
birthday little pun mon
[Music]
pun right now be like what she
say she's so expressive right I
know this is the new the new wow the new
[Music]
upgraded fre D 2.1 was so
cute thank you
okay continue uh where was I
uh no ah yeah okay Nathan
cotton life as your cat wouldn't be much
different for
me compared to your current Life as a
human I don't know about that I think it
would be different very
different but
maybe maybe I'd prefer to be your cat I
want to be somebody's
cat I want to be a cat Elsie love
and oh K pin badges she found e oh ni is
crazy yours are the only one sold out in
Hol
shop but but that's just because you
bought them right oh you mean you mean
the online
shop you mean on the online shop they
sold out I think I saw that and I'm like
H are
they are those those are like I guess
always in stock not like pre-order
right maybe they just had a lower stock
prepared for me than for the others
because well maybe my sales are lower
compared to others and that's why it's
sold out maybe that's why I'm the only
sold out
one I mean it could I'm not trying to
like like dep pre dep fre it myself or
whatever like it's a legit like could be
suggestion you
know no for real though like that could
be an explanation they they could really
be doing it like that
H they should have made more H is it
still sold out if you guys really want
it if you guys are trying to buy it and
you're like I can't buy it it's
so loud if you serious about it I can
ask
them to restock it I don't know I don't
know if they have like a
ritual where they look every month they
look like okay what's sold out and then
they restock it but that's the kind of
merch that should be always in stock so
I'm kind of confused about
[Music]
it it's always been sold out you want
one you want one you actually want
one
one I knew that what H was you were
buying my stuff before you knew what H
was what are you talking
about
what what you
mean wait are you saying you were a fan
of me without knowing I belong to a
company called whole life oh is that
what you're saying that's funny that's
interesting I'm takas of H life
Ian that could I it could be
[Music]
that could be POS I see how that would
be possible I mean you just completely
ignore the whole life I in my channel
name I mean if you don't know what it is
then it could mean nothing to you you
you don't necessarily have to know what
that
means I would like an
answer but I don't see them replying in
the
chat I'm at good events who never heard
of the rest of her life either yeah well
that's more common yeah it's more common
than you would think is especially for
good
yeah I watched her Clips that's why my
Clips
ah uhuh so you just stumbled over the
clips you didn't know what this was
until recently and now you here and now
you know the more you know it really is
out of stock do you want
it do you do you guys okay show of hands
who's actually like hope like waiting
for a restock cuz it's it's just a pin
badge like a pretty basic one at that so
I thought you guys maybe don't care so
much about
it
really I ordered one already I already
have it okay they'll restock soon you
think
so
H are you guys for real
okay you better be buying it then if I
get a restock
[Music]
waiting for restock has it ever been in
stock on peek Jack ever since it was
first reled I don't know I have really
not been paying attention to
it oh I really will buy another one okay
I want to put them on a jacket oh thank
[Music]
you JMA wake up we need you no don't
wake her up now let her sleep the Steal
D Axel deand D and happy belated
birthday
congratulations the steel Dan Typhon Dan
the steel Dan referee boils Dan lunchbox
Dan golden I Dan de pan San dang the
steel dang sleeping Forest
dangun I think I'm him from the meet and
GRE LOL I remember you seem disappointed
I don't have an O I just love h I had no
questions I just wanted to Express
gratitude I didn't go well but I still
love
you I don't know if you were the one I
don't even to be honest I thought
about what I said in that stream
afterwards and I was
like like is I think it's like maybe two
incidents mixed into one in my memory I
don't I really don't remember it that
well anymore um I don't know if you're
hear in the Stream now but yeah don't
worry about it I I
mean if you are the one I was talking
about then yeah I mean you you were
there in my Fallout stream listening to
me streaming and just coincidently you
were there so that already tells me that
you weren't as random as I thought you
were
yeah I don't worry about
it if you don't have an ooshi at
all that's better than you going maybe
that's better than you going to my meet
and grade without me being your Ori that
might actually be better you're still up
for the taking for
example now you don't seem to be here
now maybe you'll be here for the Fallout
stream I don't
know if I looking for a tangent
tomorrow remind me to try addressing
sleeping Forest
again and say Let Me Be Your aie
please
please my okay my hand shrinking is like
not so good anymore please
permission to be or she granted well you
say that you say that I need to hear it
from sleeping
Forest how old are you
now uh I don't have a particular age I
am a phoenix I stopped counting after
many many hundreds of years of being
reborn over and over again I don't
really know
because I am
Timeless thanks chat for bringing that
one
[Laughter]
[Music]
up everybody's everybody who's laughing
has been here since the debut I would
say or you just caught up on everything
that happened in the past
I am
Timeless oh
man it's a throwback
man
throwback is that the new 2 no no no I'm
in 3D right now okay uh this is 2.0 but
if anything it's the 2.0 of my 3D uh
it's not the live Tod 2 .0 3.0 which we
talked about before please no
misunderstanding or else I'll have to
make my own misunderstanding
corner it's just my own upgrade on my
own 3D which also does not mean that
everybody's getting that everybody could
get it if they wanted
to well maybe not into the H Life app
but uh in a separate program
yes my reverse birthday
today happy reverse birthday to me happy
reverse birthday to me happy reverse
birthday to me happy reverse birthday to
me
hey why because today oh okay at this
point it's already eth but in America
it's still 7th of June and my birthday
is 6th of July so if you look at the
dates you
know basically it means there's less
than a month left to my
birthday it's still fun final
month to my
birthday it's just one more month to my
birthday I'm getting so hyp walk doie
doy what's up
[Music]
everybody W fourth fourth third
fourth four third third birthday third
fourth third third birthday fourth
anniversary right
[Music]
okay I'm glad you like it
Thiago no isn't it my thir
bir first birthday
first first wait
debut first birthday first
anniversary second
birthday second it's oh okay
fourth had to do some thinking there
fourth birthday it
is confused
[Music]
this where was
I H the steel D Simeon D soon it's funny
seeing others play the game because of
the show when I only do it cuz I try to
100% all the
achievements oh well you sound like a
gamer but it was kind of on my
eventually I mention you know wanting to
play it eventually even before watching
the show but the show definitely got me
[Music]
motivated uh
it's you
again thank you for the
re was so cute your aim is amazing I'm
always cheering for you I love
[Music]
you thank you very much for the Super
Chat
King Hulu
R up than the
pinky congrats on your ultra high
definition 3DW yesterday here's my
payday salary to celebrate wait a
freaking
second what a coincidence that I'm
reading the super chat
now was this
about ultra high definition fre DW the
day before the second Fallout
stream what
what did I
do
[Music]
coefficient
coefficient you're ruining my
reputation you're putting me in quite a
predicament
coefficient you cannot replace me
coefficient stop stop you must Coe you
must make a clear statement to all
people of the world and tell them that
you are not Kiana we need to make it
clear because these people think you are
me and who am I if you are me who am I
going to be I'm having extal crises
please Co
Vision help
me please relay this message to
coefficient safely
Amigos yeah that's a clip it and Chip
it send it off
CH on the w train on the W communication
Revelation indication
[Music]
train the waa
Express this whole operation was your
idea no no it wasn't
I guess it
[Laughter]
was I'm having too much fun with this
face but I ran out of water that's going
to be a
problem Oh wait I have a bit
more oh it's almost a full
glass
H that will keep me above water for a
little while
longer is that a
joke being a keeping above water is a
metaphor for surviving right and I have
water so the water that I drink is
keeping me above water that's a joke
right I'm created a joke
right okay let's go and and thank you R
for you little
fancy D logical Paradox D don't
worry about being late thank you for
showing up in the first place y mik
Thomas the med kit and
D oh I thank you yeah I would mostly
agree with that but you're talking I
think you say you say myth designs held
up so well that sometimes I forgot and
you guys haven't got any updates you say
this designs I think that's two
different things I do think the my
designs became like a
iconic thing visual that really did hold
up well but then at the same time the
life to D that's a different story that
also hold up held up well I would
say cuz it was just so good for at the
time the life to you was so good for
what what it
was myth is timeless no no no no no
no I am
[Music]
[Applause]
Timeless thank you thank you chill chill
out man you guys are too
excited uh what was that acceptable
casualty Dan kishun not a good username
dun py Dan another good username danin
again Michael H danin Dax jayen dun
Common Sense bro
DAV fell and naan coton thank you for
the pinky death is a minor inconvenience
to a chant Phoenix like Boon much like
how being lit on Fires like wearing a
warm
jacket no no I will now say when the wa
is on
fire wah wah wah on fire eh fire fire
Wah on
fire uh it's just normal
like I don't really feel a temperature
change
this this why was on fire
this was on
[Music]
fire
fire there I was on
[Music]
fire lava is a bit of a
problem what was I saying what was I
what okay what I wanted to say though
um you wrote Death is a minor
inconvenience to your Chad Phoenix like
Boon you saying Chad in caps log
reminded me of the Chad cast and that
reminded me of the thought that I
[Music]
had up there and I can't reach that high
right
now I have an idea
for a
podcast that's all I'll say
now
W make it the
podcast
but not birdcast no something
else entirely
separate but I will I will keep it to
myself still I'm just telling you that I
have an idea m
Randy acceptable casualty space water
delar D B Jones D looking for the top D
the steel D wa do you have a question
looking for the top let me ask you have
you thought about doing a dance sh for
the Chica Dance Now that you can record
dances at home old Trend but it's very
cute ah ah that one oh yeah oh possible
but I haven't thought about doing that
one in particular
M maybe at some point if I'm like H I
want to do a YouTube short dance but I
don't know
what maybe but there's still like I'm
kind of still kind of confused but I
think it I think seems fine now I just
I'm
I'm not 100% per sure about the rules
now but I think it's fine in terms of um
using existing tracks
Original singing like their their the
singing of the original tracks so just
the original track instead of singing
above it myself because like I don't
know a year ago or
so when I was like Hey I want to do a
little YouTube dance cover
short for this song for example Mas BL
jeans Mas
Mas you know remember that
one I did that one as one of my actually
one of my first YouTube dance
shorts and back then I uh I was told uh
I can't use the original song I can
however sing above it like use an
instrumental that I have permission for
and then sing over
it as long as it's not like K-pop or or
American songs or whatever but now like
at some point somewhere along the line
since like whatever last year till now
some at some point like more and more
members started uploading YouTube shorts
of the original audio and I was like is
this okay now like nobody told me that
this is a possibility now and I kind of
asked like okay what's the what's is
there can we use anything or
like any
song or just like Japanese songs you
know I think for now it's like as long
as it's those kind of songs that we
would be able to sing in archived Kadoka
streams then we can seemingly use the
original
track I guess it's not really so clear I
think but I think it's okay as long as
it seems like it cuz I already did it
with a few songs too at this
point and I really appreciate it because
I don't want to like cover everything
and the thing is also like I used to
even need like the the instrumental like
my own instrumental for it and I'm not
going to commission a new instrumental
just for the sake of a YouTube shirt I
need something existing right so that's
kind of me uh a bit too much
effort and I just think it sounds better
if you use the original music with the
original
singing so yeah but in terms of other
dances as long as it's like Japanese
tracks then I think we can do all kinds
of things maybe even the maybe even the
chick
dance the Ste
I a
[Music]
chck I didn't say the
nend I stopped that
ticket I stopped
there yeah yeah you didn't hear it
either you didn't hear it two people are
speaking for
me T um I'm a
che SL fellow things the
pinky uh great progress no depths and
only free crashes oh yeah we had a few
crashes on that day Yahoo gamert rules
the wasel sorry about not super chatting
as much anymore I'm working on changing
my jobs job and things are not going
smoothly Oh you mean you like quit your
job before having a new job lined up
or comat good
luck I hope it works out for you
eventually I hope you're going to get
back on
track but if you're having some you know
no job time right now maybe enjoy it a
little
bit you don't have any UH
responsibilities to Super Chat to me so
especially in you're if you're in a
situation like that don't feel obligated
or so or don't feel guilty or
bad take the time and maybe
enjoy not having to go to work every
day no don't enjoy having no money just
enjoy not not going to work every day
what I'm trying to
say oh yeah I hope it gets better thank
you for
watching space wonderful Dan delar Dan
Cruise Dan and fried screw Dan and
Unwritten
Dan that was the second Fallout stream
super
[Music]
chats moving on
to wa do lingo I red thank God in that
stream I guess we
have wait we're not that far
behind we're not that far
behind it's just which spring
r
or oh a previous members right not the
Le not not the most recent one
oh where is
it all right it doesn't show on why is
this ah this one only shows because it's
the waa waiting
room
ah ah
CH okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay no I'm not going to catch up
probably but let me find the member
super chats which
one day of ofai is it the second Bak
watch along right I think
so ah finally met you at OFA after the
three years of trying K was awesome
thanks Kaa ah thank you I'm happy to
hear that you guys are getting good good
uh what's it not not feedback but like
good good
evaluation no not the I mean the second
part of B got Daddy watch
[Music]
along well thank you I'm so glad we
could
meet
yeah happy
times I think I found
it I think I found it
oh yeah I think I found it that's a lot
yeah I have to do a lingo
[Music]
basically they're talking about me
coefficient
no no they're not
no no God please no no God please no no
no and Michael
Scott and Michael
[Music]
Scott
no
no um space Water full dun I'm bringing
members
only after ofai now
okay well I don't know if I can do all
of them there's a lot of pinkies and
reds chocolate and snic F with of Pinky
yeah hey Kima by the time you get this
I'm probably on a plane back from home
from offy you made us all proud and we
had we had moments that we can't be will
never forget ooh spicy thank you w I
will hatch the V because I want to see
your reaction to Nao and hanuk AR hell
yeah that's important
priorities thank you so much chocolate
insomnia I I I'm
sad because no meet and greet but I'm
glad you could be there and by the way
when I was going through
the K app today I found chocolate
Insomniac wait that's the name of the
song right that's not just your name
right I'm getting confused now but I'm
I'm pretty sure I was like
ah
ah you
know it was in there and so R ey
circulation and chocolate
insomnia and one more song that I I'm
like what I watched all of the seasons
before and this song sounds so
unfamiliar to
me
um but yeah that's a few but in any case
while I was looking at them I was
thinking I got to I got to you
know take some time to commission some
songs and I should commission every
single one of
them monali openings and perhaps endings
is there orange mint no
no and no over no no no no no no
mathematics no
Magics yeah I can commission them but it
will take a
while been Ling since the debut and
yo thank you don't keep Ling no at least
use your members message each month and
say hi
please thank you for supporting me
Trevor thanks for the red super
chat happy I had the opportunity to have
squawked with you at the med and grade
now picking up where I left
off right cuz as Trav G was leaving the
room after lots of yapping that has been
exchanged as he was off the screen that
I was able to
see uh he was like still yelling out um
that I should watch Godzilla
Godzilla minus one I'll just say it's a
solid movie to have on the watchong list
now that it's available what do you mean
available is it a new one a perfect way
for you to understand and get closer to
eie and
Luna minus one is
Wild on Netflix is it a new movie or is
it just like recently being picked up
on streaming service
it's a new
one I don't know I really don't give a
about
Godzilla uh to me that's like Jurassic
Park Vibes I don't probably no probably
it's
more
like Japanese style I suppose because
Godzilla itself is like I don't know
it's a good movie is it an action movie
is it like kind of like
uh Indiana Jones is in terms of like
[Music]
genre more serious and usual Godzilla
uh-huh It's a
drama one an
Oscar well is there a Godzilla
wait Godzilla why do I think about a
monkey climbing up a
building when I think of Godzilla why do
I always think about a monkey climbing
up a building Godzilla is the one that's
really big and and Stomps on all the
buildings just by walking through it
right yeah that's King Kong I always
think about King Kong what's wrong with
me I guess they had movies together
okay are you thinking of The Hobbit no
I'm
not you're so
dumb monkey on the
brain
monkey well I don't know I man TR I want
to do it for you I want to do it for you
um but I'm really not interested but I
will maybe consider it in the
future but anyway it was really nice
talking to
[Music]
you I'm glad we
could clear
up any of my
concerns so happy to meet you you shy
shy little chicken
owl
try I love talking to
you sorry sorry if I like I don't know
make you feel uh pressured or whatever I
don't know thank you
Trevy p stand thanks for red Super Chat
hello Teno you and the others put on a
hell of an event last night loved each
and every song you put before I'm
feeling all the energy in the room was
insane I can
imagine I did imagine I felt it actually
when watching the VA I legit felt it I
only cried
twice during my segment I didn't even
get that
emotional I only like slightly Tippy
toed around an emotional topic something
I haven't done in Long done during your
segment so thanks for that considering
this as a OnePlus year one plus year
message I don't know how I fell into you
quickly becoming my kosi over a year ago
to being able one year ago
only feels like you've been around
longer to being able to see you live and
spending time with other lovely CP
person I'm so grateful to have met so
many of you I just really appreciate
that you put your front foot and on my
back foot my back foot is dangerous
forward about a lot of things are super
communicative and most importantly have
raw honesty
[Music]
see but also on top of all of that
remember when to just have fun so D also
do you have a favorite scene in the
watch along so far ah wait there's so
many things okay first of all thank you
for becoming my fan yeah and staying my
fan for a year and making me your Kami
Oshi that means a lot to
me
m and I'm happy to see you know
oldtimers who've been here since day one
but we need to grow so I'm always happy
to see some so to say
newcomers thank
you thank you for traveling to ofai to
see
me and having fun with auto kfp I'm glad
you
did also I was not like trying to make
fun or or criticize you for crying at
all like I'm I'm glad you feel so
emotionally connected with the situation
and me to do that that means that I mean
a lot to you and that means a lot to
me and you
saying what you appreciate about me you
know a lot of those things is exact or
actually all of that is exactly what
leads often to me saying things that
people will
then on me
for um so I appreciate everybody who can
appreciate
me being like that um cuz a lot of
people don't
understand what I'm really trying to
convey a lot of the
[Music]
time and misinterpret things or
so I think the people who become a fan
of
me who maybe somebody sometime has
issues with
communication and putting words in the
right way the people who manag to find a
liking in me are the absolute
Chads and it proves to me that you guys
are all very very open-minded and
big-hearted
people and that you're not like you
don't have a stick in your ass and
you're
not
like you know you don't you see the good
and people
people yeah and you're
considerate and you see you try
to understand me you try to understand
me and that's like something that maybe
a lot of people don't even
try and that's what makes you all so
special and that's what I love so much
about you and I'm so thankful to have
people like
you who see
me the
way perhaps I see
me yeah I know things that I say can
sometimes seem controversial or whatever
from a certain point of view but I do
think sometimes honestly most of the
time I'm not even controversial
enough because I can't be h
I can't even
be as open so maybe me speaking in
riddles or so and not as cly as it like
to be leads to misunderstandings but I
do think you guys everybody who's here
watching
me I think you
are the best of the best in terms
of people and personalities
I
think you know people say Europeans
are maybe also depending on the country
within Europe but people generally say
we're like
pretty straightforward and we say what's
on our mind and all
that and depending on other countries
and continents it might be different and
people say that I don't even for my P I
don't I even think like it's that
different to America but the more I deal
with Americans the more I realize I
guess we are quite different it's it's I
don't even know how because like you
guys have carens and all
that like it's not like it's not like
you're like the most polite people on
Earth ever that's like
Japan you know so I don't quite get it
why Europeans are apparently so much
more controversially direct than you
know no from Americans I don't get it
where how but but then you know as I
said The more I work with Americans and
talk to Americans and so on I'm like H
yeah there seems to be
some something
there some
something some kind of Disconnect
there it's hard to pinpoint yeah maybe
you guys have a lot of taboos I don't
know but but I don't
know it's I I think I think we can be
very
similar I don't know what it is
Americans can be blunt I don't think so
yeah just like me but it comes off more
as being rude as opposed to just being
honest H you mean when Americans are
blunt it comes off as
rude but isn't that what how I come up
to you guys not not you guys but like
you know generally that's like the issue
so to
say I don't know whatever I'm just
trying to say like yeah you guys
are you guys are able to understand
me I love that about
you oh God caps lock Daisy
overly sensitive yeah that's that is a
thing mhm like just not Americans but
like people in general
yeah Luen B over here what what is this
like actually a YouTube shorts algorithm
kind of
thing wait where did the Super Chat
go it
disappeared oh no here it is from
freaking Luxembourg let's go Europeans
I'm I'm from
Austria I'm from Austria hello scrolling
people I'm I'm doing this like super
deep talk when there could be so many
randos in here
huh huh I should just shut up let me
continue
reading
uh uh where was I favorite scene of the
watch long in the watch long well now we
had already we're already done with n
mon yeah so favorite
[Music]
scene of the episodes we
watched hey I don't know that's hard to
say we already watched so many
episodes maybe um
[Music]
uh I I can't remember just whatever I
got excited about I don't remember you
also answered this before but what new
outfit would you want without
restrictions any new ideas specific
talks this is also funny that you're
asking that a couple days ago because
this I just announced it
so that's a new outfit that I wanted um
I mean I made this decision long long
time ago I just thought it would be cute
because the fite outfits were just such
a nice
aesthetic yeah so looking forward to
that and then after that honestly I
still haven't decided what my next one
will be because I'm still kind of like
begging that I can do a 3D outfit
instead of a 2d outfit but that's not
going to
happen I'm still kind of keeping my
options open to be be
honest
yeah anyway thank you for now I'll leave
it at that thank you so much for your
support people
[Music]
stand but it's not equal you
know I guess Fredy outfit is like more
effort and more expensive and all that
so it's not equal can't really replace
it like that I
suppose Ro toar thanks for WR Super Chat
kiaha I was at the amazing concert no
way you guys so many of you were there
last night almost in the front row so
many people talked about like even other
performers they talked about how the
like a whole block was completely
orange I think there were like kfps all
over the crowd but a certain very
passionate group of kfp waited really
early to fill up the best slots the best
seats and so that whole section was
fully
[Music]
orange so
funny
yeah you guys made kfp look
strong they said that the organizers
allowed them to reserve oh
wow oh that's so nice of them
[Music]
I'm glad you got good seats
guys it didn't happen to all the panels
I know mints fans didn't get to oh I
heard that
like I heard that the Min fans like got
in early were like moved to the side
even though they wanted to sit in the
middle but like they were moved over
because it was still early and in terms
of panels and the staff was just like
trying to figure out the best way to do
things and we're trying to squeeze in
the people and that's just what happened
but aren't there from what I I guess it
was a different room was the mint panel
in a different room from where I was
in because in the room I was in there
were free screens from what I was able
to observe right same room oh so wasn't
there free
screens a same
room but there's free screens right free
I can't say it only one camera
for the
stage I mean for mint to see
I think I had two
views I was adjustable too I
think feel like I had two views but I
don't
remember oh well I I think you know she
was probably not upset about it but
maybe the fans were a little bit upset
but you know they tried their best you
know the staff I'm sure they did
[Music]
it is what it is anyway you made me a
bit sad for an instant when you said all
the other girls were better than you
well like in terms of singing they were
let's be honest you stayed up whole
night to stream all original songs in a
home pretty setup maybe they are but to
me know oh man I love you thank
[Music]
you well yeah I mean also you got to
consider you know like you singing I
noticed that like the later it got the
more raspy my voice got and like when
you have you guys ever tried singing
after pulling an all
nighter
it's weird what that does to your
voice now of course many of you haven't
tried it cuz that's kind of weird but
yeah I tried my best with like froat
candies and and tea and all that and and
resting my voice before
but um when I was practicing at like 2 3
a.m. I already noticed oh oh this
is
bad I should not use my voice at all
until the time
comes also like the more not just like
pulling an all night but the the longer
unusually longer you are up the more
your voice seems to
fall apart I've
noticed what me he thought she was
bad she had a big crisis of that
girl girl
what I listened to her whole set
[Music]
girl what
what
what it was lovely I loved it like I got
you know I was like oh man I wish I had
a voice like that you
know that's how you no no no no no no I
really have worse like technical skill
and all that than them but also
you
know I debuffed myself in other ways you
know but it's okay like I'm not saying
I'm a bad singer I honestly think like
if I'm not like nervous as if I
just you know like focus and take my
time and I'm not like being watched by
thousands of people then like if I'm
just recording for an album or so or
song then when my voice is at its best
it can be pretty good and and um even
when it's not at its best it just it has
its good moments you know but I'm um not
the best but I I don't think I'm the
worst I think I'm pretty decent um at
singing I'm Not uh what's the word in
English like on when you when you can't
hit a single note that's not
me but damn you got to admit those girls
were
insane those other girls girls were
[Music]
insane there's T death yeah there's
nothing wrong with them being you know a
little bit better maybe it's also
preference I don't know but no
technically they were really
[Laughter]
insane uh I can I can proudly admit that
and that's fine but I'm not saying I was
bad just by saying how good they were
you know
[Music]
yeah but thank you I'm I'm flattered
thank you Road thank you especially for
the r of chat and the sweet words you're
so
[Music]
kind J D for the pinky hey wa can you
say something for me oh
no is this isn't this the one that we
that I tried doing I said it didn't
I I'm not going to say it again
especially cuz you wrote it in full on
Ki I can't read that
not like this write it out in ragi
or hiana
please has been one of my alltime
favorites since season 1 I really think
if you like it you'd enjoy bunny go
Senai
uh it shes a little DNA with but I think
that younger Wawa would have most likely
very much enjoyed that
show I know what you
mean uh the problem
is if I never watched mono katali before
and I would be watching it for the first
time now now I can't guarantee I would
like it as much just generally because
cuz I'm not really into anime anymore
just monali will forever have a special
place in my heart whenever they bring
out a new season I will be jumping on it
um just watching any kind of anime now
first of all is already difficult for me
and then if it's one that's kind of like
fan service or harmish or too
cutesy anything like
that
critical critical
I can see how I would really love it if
I was younger and still into anime more
that anime for sure
100% maybe I'll even give it a
try at some point
nowadays who knows maybe I'll go grow
into another anime face at some
point but I'm I I I've always been
lowkey interested in in that anime I
don't know why I never watched it I've
always wanted to watch it I think when I
was in my anime
years yeah thanks for understanding guys
you guys are guys are vibing with me I
see because you still love all these jpg
games that's
true u i I talked about it
before why I think it is I'm not 100%
sure either I think it's just I don't
want to I don't want to say it again cuz
I don't want to talk down anime it's
been a big part of my life for a long
time I don't really know
either but you know I just uh and you
guys always on me for like having
bad taste or
whatever and and being too picky on like
graphics and games and stuff like
that when I and I was saying before that
I think and now I don't feel confident
about saying this but I think it might
just really have something to do with me
growing out of it and and and
appreciating like like liveaction so to
say shows and movies more because of the
beauty of like real
people seeing skin texture and beautiful
cinematics and all that I'm just I just
uh I don't know I don't
know anime became more and more immature
for me and I can't take it seriously in
a lot of most
cases m
[Music]
I don't know I want to like it because I
would have so much more
choices I don't agree but I understand
that's good that's
good I've become more picky but there's
still good stuff I believe that very
much and I don't want to give up on it
completely but for years now I haven't
really watched anything besides that one
time when I watched Violet
evergarden which was serious you know it
was serious and Visually
beautiful and I did not dislike it but I
was also not like
oh I need to watch more anime now and I
need to watch the movie of violet
evergarden and all that it didn't like
make me feel like I I necessarily need
more of
it Belle oh okay see one thing that I
still enjoy watching is like uh certain
anime movies like whenever there's a new
JBL movie or uh what's that
production company that made like your
name and so on the movies I'm still
always like so up for it Belle as
well somehow why
why I wonder
why
yeah what wait that's so weird why do I
why am I so eager to watch the movies I
don't know maybe because there's a lot
more budget put into them and so there's
more production value that I can see
visually I don't
know let me read super Chats on Tangen
thing too much we discussed this before
anyway but yeah thank
you
[Music]
man oh man
low commit I don't think it's the
commitment I don't think
so oh in terms of One Piece it would be
the
commitment not going to watch a show
with a million episodes
nah and it's also too dorky for
me I think the anime would probably be
too dorky for me the visuals of the next
nflix show really help out balance the
dorkiness anyway it do I
I I'm not riding it off for good you
know I'm not writing anime off for
good I'm hoping there will be a Revival
in interest for me and I do kind of feel
like wanting to
re-watch my old old favorite
animes like
working and Mina mik I really want to
rewatch Mina
[Music]
mik like all my old favorites I kind of
want to rewatch
them ra
gun yeah yeah I want to rewatch it the
most recent season that came out when
like a couple years ago I I
feel like I didn't get into it though
and that's when I also again I was like
oh I guess I don't like anime that much
anymore what
[Music]
why but I want to watch anything that's
nostalgic to me like kanagi I just want
to rewatch animes that I loved that that
I have a big big big love for
established blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah
blah H Ro toar sent another r Super Chat
you built such a great family with kfb
without usering Fire Emblem I probably
never would have gotten into V Road
toar are you here right
now excuse me Ro
toar you're not here are you
you you seem to be a
lurker you've been around since
Fire
Emblem why do you like so much your name
is very new to
me explain yourself we're not
here how can you explain
yourself I probably never would have
gotten into vtubers without my freaking
Fire Emblem
stream are we talking free
houses what let alone Idols to where I'm
I I can't believe people who watch my
fry emblem stream are looking for years
and saying hi to me the for seemingly
the first time ever after 4 years or
so talk to me more
let alone I towear I'm screaming myself
horse
learning learning what at a dang BTU con
handing out bad ribons
everyone it's orange for your pen like
she oh wait this is like a continuation
I hope one day I can say this to you
directly at a meet and greet you're
always going to be my Kam oi and you're
always going to
be thank you for being incredible
[Music]
you little
how can you be so wholesome and
nice and
sweet and say all the right
words and be here since like super
early just be
lurking
stop stop
thank you everybody thank you to the
other lurkers
too but I just don't get it you seem
like you have so much love for me and
yet you you this is now the first time
you kind of properly Express It To Me
Maybe I'm Wrong maybe I just I'm sorry
if I forgot like
another moment when when this happened
sorry if I did but you feels very fresh
to me Road
toar you're such a cool name too anyway
thank you for going to offy and
supporting me there in person and I'm
I'm so happy that you found your place
here and that I dragged you into the
rabbit hole I'm guilty I'm guilty as
charged thank you so much M now show
your face more often or
else girl didn't think the red super
chat I love your concert you fire I have
no voice anymore girl dance
[Music]
there's so many
kfps dad went to off
gu dad I wanted to talk to in me and
green
man why you so
unlucky why are you so unlucky man where
did you use your luck why what you doing
it did you like go to the casino before
signing up for the mid and grade and
spend all your luck
there why would you do
that see I'm shelfing all my luck for
when I can go yeah you
better I survived being born that's when
you used up your luck you should have
more luck available to you in in your
whole life over the course of
it I'm going to be mad you guys you
you're you you you got to you
you're I mean it's not like you could
have done anything differently but it's
your
responsibility to come meet me in minig
grits when you have the opportunity
[Music]
don't use up your
luck please
thank you the
[Music]
monin I hope you will never forget this
gratitude you have towards
me thank you Anthony too
never going to get to you
today anyway GED
in you better come to see me sometime
promise me you little promise
me spanking thank you for the re good
morning T fantastic show last night but
I'll never forgive you for bamboozling
us on the anchor I wish I could have
been there but I was wearing orange eh
is that a
joke wait
H that
explain what does that mean you wish you
could have been there but you were
wearing orange
what Oh you mean it's not like uh the
reason for why you couldn't be there I
thought it was like some jokeer why why
you couldn't be
there so you mean you couldn't be there
but you were still wearing orange at
home is that what you mean or are you in
jail see that could have been the joke I
wish I could have been there but I was
wearing
orange which means I was in jail which
is why I couldn't be
there maybe it was cat jail wait maybe
you mean you were wearing orange as in
there was an orange cat sitting on you
could be could be many options thank you
do the Anor by the way it's kind of last
minute decision they were like oh yeah
so uh can you give us like a sign when
you do the Anor and I'm like
uncor I don't I I don't have one planned
there's no sign there's no
Anor and they were like okay and I was
like
H now you made me think about it I guess
we could do one I can just pretend that
the last song is going to be the
uncore and then I said just leave it to
me I'm just going to like leave the
screen you don't have to do anything and
then they were probably kind of
disappointed because I didn't keep it
going for too long the charades I like
immediately made it very obvious that
I'm doing an uncore thingy that I'm not
leaving the stage for real for real cuz
I just I don't know I didn't I didn't
want to lie to you guys it honestly felt
like a I was lying to to you guys and I
wanted to be honest with you we have a
you know this honest relationship that
we have is very important to me and I
didn't want to misuse your trust I I
really felt like I cannot pretend that
I'm leaving for too long in any any
capacity the moment I walked off I
already acted suspiciously so that you
guys could notice that I'm I'm not
really leaving I didn't want you to
think that it was already over I didn't
want you even for even if it was for a
short amount of time I didn't want you
to be like oh man that was short oh man
she already left oh man too
bad I wanted you to know like oh wait
there's more she's just pretending okay
good all is well she's not gone yet I'm
happy she's not gone
[Laughter]
yet
yeah I'm glad you can notice that the
Freddy is superior thank you
I'm I'm getting tired man from smiling
so much because I'm I see
myself I'm trying to be more expressive
than
usual
tired thank you sping time
Mah time for
n
d yay I'm happy cheese on my beans
Dun
A sorry I flapped
kiaha oh funny GC e d soon don't worry
about it thanks for saying hi though oh
again Ro
toar man thank you now you're so
talkative you should be this talkative
more
often M thank you
a Cruz d forand d oh you were in the
[Music]
choir the choir was hype I liked your
song Choices I mean I didn't know some
of them but
um I was so happy that you put in so
many whole life
songs Roo D again he
yo thank you
space oh thank
you and Brandon thanks for the pinky
kiaha my work schedule keeps me in VA
gang these days but I wanted to say I
love the offy concert and seeing all the
othero kfp we were all so hyped also I
think I'd give i' give it out over a
dozen copies of POV to people including
coefficient what
really you did
you gave a th is 100 right no way you're
just exaggerating
right you didn't have one of course you
didn't oh 12 is it
oh oh Still Still 100 would have been
crazy you gave us 17
wow wow thank you
I mean 100 would be crazy sorry if I
sounded disappointed there's no
way 17 is insane thank
you he what kind of people did you give
it to like seeming people people who are
already fans but maybe just they just
don't have the CD they didn't have a
chance to get it or so or they weren't
as as you know they were like lowkey
fans but not maybe not hard key or did
you give it out to completely random
people
people who were not necessarily Wawa
fans tell
me jst jst I feel like I haven't seen
you in a
while I missed
you kind of random but kfp was preferred
oh good job good
job they whoever got it all of them
better appreciate the hell out of it the
hell out of
it I was very
busy I'm so happy to see you again
though mint got a copy too
oh I tried to give one to Mint hopefully
she got it seems like
it oh yeah listen to D expire work s
[Music]
yeah well cool I mentioned it
nice SEO can't be me if I have if he
just
like although wait wait
wait wait I don't have my own CD though
do I I don't
h
let's not
it
he no I
[Music]
don't could I have received it in
March when I was in
Japan wait
was it already sent out at that
point okay on
the on
the oh
yeah yeah I just checked my DMs of
JMA I
think I was
in
Japan at the
yeah while I was still in Japan around
the end of my trip I I wrote to Gemma I
got no CD of my own album crying
emoji
and
yeah I
think I think what may have happened is
they may have tried to send it to
me um but they didn't have my new
address yet I think and then maybe they
sent it to the wrong address or that's
what I would say if I give them the
benefit of the doubt or they didn't have
it at all but at the time in Japan uh on
on that like in that moment because it
was it was that's like it was pre-order
only so they couldn't just like suddenly
give me CDs I guess so
easily they got to have some spare CD
somewhere it's my own album I need my
own
album but I totally for forgot about
that I did remind them at the end of my
last trip like he
yo so can I now that I'm in Japan can I
receive a copy of my own CD please and
then it just like I think it just became
forgotten let
me
T we just
realized thanks to chat that I still
don't have my POV CD
is there any spare
ones at the office or
so
that I can have
one I need my own
CD no she's not going to wake up through
that don't
worry sorry that is a big shock to me I
just kind of
like put myself into a situation where I
was going to say well I got the CD first
before coefficient so how can he be the
real waa but then I realized while I was
saying that I don't have my own
[Laughter]
cine I just like owned
myself okay I'm
shocked I'm just shocked now
you are D Man Nathan thanks for the
pinky hi attent you just wanted to hop
in and say congrats on the concert last
night thank you I know you might not
like the scuff but we kfp love it cuz it
means you're working so hard for us
which makes us want to work harder for
you love you wa thank you
m I
think cuz I watched the V
and so I saw saw how often the camera
changed to the audience which was the
most interesting thing
anyway so that uh hit a lot of the scuff
and also wasn't too bad I
guess because the hype hearing the hype
from the crowd just made everything less
awkward and much better so it's okay I
honestly I thought that I would
be digging myself a
hole and hide in it afterwards out of
embarrassment but it was the absolute
opposite so it was just a good
experience so all is good I'm happy you
were awesome from watching virtually
thank you you guys know I can do better
I'll show you I'll show you when I get
another free proper 3D opportunity my
own 3D YouTube live the next one and so
on those are the moments where you can
see no SCU wa I really wish your part
was
longer would you guys have preferred
like a normal panel over this I'm
honestly that's what I originally
thought it was going to be until I was
notified that I was going to be in like
the after show not after show ending
closing show whatever
H this way I didn't have to think about
something funny to do for a panel I
could just full on focus on making it a
musical
thing I think that was
cool yeah and everyone went into it
expecting a musical
show everybody was hyped about it which
also kind of heightens the pressure I
would say wait holy it's already
halfast 1 y
I didn't notice I was yapping too much
I've been yapping too much
what how the the
just thank you Nathan for the
[Music]
pinky let me Zoom a little bit through
these just a little bit py d chck d
GTC sky py
cheese
meum
oh no no no F cannot be done streaming
before
me it's time to
[Music]
go thank you FAA this is so wrong this
feels so
wrong okay well I'll take this
opportunity hello saplings I'm going to
end the stream anyway but let me just
show you first of all this right on
Sunday new outfit reveal please check it
out I'd be so excited if everybody would
check it out but then do you notice
something different here wait I I
I how how my hands moving when I closed
this wait so um let me show
you just before I
go what
remember
remember her where is she there she is
remember her cannot move eyebrows cannot
pull out tongue cannot move my mouth
from left to right left to right cannot
move my eyes very much
either cannot puff my cheeks cannot do
all kinds of things who is she
stiff Wawa stiff CH stiff as CH
that's her but I have uh originally for
the sake of ofai I've uh prepared 51 PL
shapes so this is old Wawa in
3D and as you saw already but direct
comparison will make it feel so much
stronger
my mouth moves so much
more
yeah I can do
tears okay now I have a lot of filters
on too to look Fanci but yeah wow wow
wow wow and the hands okay maybe you
guys saw I don't know did FAA use it
before um in the normal whole life app
go go
you here too oh my God
okay okay I'm I'm wait now I'm lagging
that's crazy the first lag
today wait oh I think I need to close
these apps here it's too
many okay there we go we're back again
so this these hands are way better than
the whole life application
hands that we use used before that you
know are really janky and for me they're
really laggy and uh they're not really
accurate at all what I'm using now is
not my accent suit I'm using a leap
motion that I've also used for froggy
waa before basically this whole setup is
the froggy waa
setup yeah it's the hands are yeah big
Improvement to the like iPhone tracking
hands because you guys maybe know okay
this is a little bit wall breaking but
you guys May me know that YouTubers
mostly use
iPhones um to track their faces because
iPhones just have this like
magical face tracking programmed into it
I guess um and then at some point they
added hat tracking and uh then we were
able to use it in our whole life app but
that was cute that was funny you
know uh being able to use that without
putting on a whole motion capture suit
but it was really janky and scuffed and
now with the leap motion which I've been
using since uh froggy
Wawa I can move my hands more accurately
and without lag and all
that
no wait if I okay if I put them in front
of my face then yeah it gets it's also
little it's not perfect but at least I
don't have to put on my whole motion
capture
suit
yay so much motion mention
yeah that's kind of what I wanted to
show you today that's what I've been
showing you since the beginning of the
stream this is basically Wawa's personal
2.0 uh update of my
3D and more important than that we had
of oh not
that where it go that's not
it ah here haha
outfit reveal this Sunday starting at at
the same time as
today
[Music]
yeah show them the widest no no but I
show I can also show you
this new Gangi Mari and yeah the tongue
is something that is very special when
we get
3.0 life 2D upgrade but I can already do
it now in my
freey
yeah okay all right I'll continue
reading super chats next time and I'll
finish this with a
beautiful beautiful
beloved not necessarily white
Cho but something is wrong with her
Cho you want it you get it let me bring
her back then okay distorted
chel well okay let me find the right
one
H where where is she how did I do it in
the
OG that was that just felt so
intense
what can't do it anymore
[Music]
guys
ah
there
so I hope you enjoyed the Stream and my
3D
2.0
upgrade just one more disclaimer it's
not like everybody's getting this this
is kind of a personal thing that anybody
can do if they want to but um yeah Vegas
sphere what I am
orb POV you're
being wait that sounds weird POV I am
POV
[Music]
should I just not say
anything no you are you are in the
screen you are the vtuber now you are in
my
phone oh this is amazing oh
what's
this edible edible maybe can try to
lick and see if salty or
spicy very
salty very
salty um it's very late I should not be
streaming at this
time see you at Fallout
[Music]
tomorrow oh
um no I I got to go I got to go and the
German we say I'll be the Z see you at
Fallout and my outfit reveal on
Sunday thank you for listening today oh
good by the way I sang
Toyo in the Koke part of
today I sang it cute song it's so
cute and and I heard your beautiful
harmonies in the backing
track I was like he
yo are those are those good has
beautiful
harmonies
[Music]
byebye oh God
oh
oh let me see let me
see let me see is this double I'm
hearing
double no maybe not
[Music]
okay ah
oh oh I okay I know what I'm going to
raid you into it's not live yet but I
need you to watch this if you guys are
still
up then make
sure can I rate it oh yeah I
can it seems as if it will be an
exciting stream
[Music]
woohoo
announcements enjoy guys I'll I'll might
might I might still be awake
unfortunately I might still be awake at
the
time bye-bye