[Music]
p
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
p
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
p
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
I
[Music]
good
tomorrow my
subjects is I your
princess call be
you I have had somewhat of a revelation
last night maybe it was my stay
companion whispering to me in my
head
but I have noticed
that the king talks about corruption
spreading through the
kingdom but I see no
corruption around the Kingdom so where
may this corruption
lie Maybe
it is within
us maybe it's is a
person maybe it
is a
catalyst among us so I believe
that
oh what is this
inside the
kingdom inside the
kingdom what is
this has
corruption taken
root within the
kingdom oh
another this
corruption threatened to flow in these
lands
ah what is this blight
that has fallen upon
us yes you see as I was sleeping
sleeping last
night a
power a
power reached into my soul and I have
uncovered the truth of my
being I
am not my Queen's
mother I am not a subject
of t
but they do not know
that I am but a harbinger of what is to
come and I must do my
duty
as but no one should know no one must
know they must think they must believe
that I am a subject of my queen mother
that I am the heir to the to the
throne because corruption is best spread
from the
inside
yes stained Queen what titles do you
call
me no
something is growing with the
[Music]
lands oh
dear what is this
[Music]
Darkness take off the hat no my hat is
my loyal
companion it Whispers to me the secrets
of the stains and their movement I must
use it to better the kingdom
yes it's not saying weird things it's my
friend my
friend
my
Joe yes this stained hat named
Joe has revealed the truth to me
yes Joe
mama I started to
[Music]
remember I remember who I am supposed to
supped to
be here in this cruel cruel
world they they kill my
people they do they're the ones with
their
Revelations they kill
them just
because we follow the path of Darkness
does not mean our path is not righteous
[Music]
they use us they use us to gain a
coin they use our people to gain coin
and
experience to strengthen their weapons
but what about our weapons who protects
them who protects them
[Music]
the potato
salad no the potato salad is evil look
at them in their greed they
[Music]
greed they greed and they're gambling I
almost fell I almost fell into the
darkness I almost fell into
their plot
to their material ways but I my Joe my
Joe mama has has righten my ways no
longer will I
partake in these mortal
Delights
yes I know what my true path is now
yes let them
believe let
them let
them have their full sense of
[Music]
security little do they know
their false Queen is going
down all of
them a
world bursting into
flames yes that is the ideal world that
I shall live in flam is in
death so voices in my head we are going
on a journey
[Music]
ah
yes visit this queen statue
[Music]
yes
yeah it shall spread
[Music]
yes I've seen
that the ribbon has been
cast they did not like my contribution
I see how it is this this world is not
for
me it is not my world it is not my sight
how dare they how dare
[Music]
my beloved I'm sorry
but it cannot be so I
cannot
have I cannot have
bonds Earthly
[Music]
bonds your flower shall take root and
begin the corrupted
lands oh
yeah that's
it may chaos take the world
[Music]
yes make ha take
root hello
hello hello are we ready you join our
party yes the princess would love to
help okay uh she she needs to run around
and do some other stuff but it's like
you're already in another party oh oh
hold on let me let me leave the
party uh where's my
[Music]
book okay I should be able to now
okay we're in a party call so you can
join right now Kiana is over at Ain
she's doing the rest of the quest she's
going to King Li bestel to finish off
okay sounds good
yes feel free to join the party call
when You' like hello there she is Hello
babina uh who is B I am princess toy
bizu um blood FL
panthera
Evergreen oh yeah yeah yeah yeah so
sorry Princess it's is okay you're
forgiven daughter of Queen Mario I'm so
sorry yes I am I am daughter of Queen
Mario nice to meet you what is come I
have never heard of like your
royalty we we have recently discovered
it because you know we have lost our
memories so the memories took a while to
come back M yes I am my mother you are
the daughter yes I am the daughter of
Queen Mario therefore I am King who is
the father the King was conspiring
actually and that's why he took our
memories away so that they would forget
who they were who I am now going to was
conspiring yes yes should I not go to
him then no you may still go to him but
we just need to keep in mind that he's a
dirty filthy
liar okay is he really yes oh is that
the plot twist yeah yes that is that is
the plot
twist okay let's see let's see uh ooh
wait this looks so like Super Mario like
cute
cute very Dem
miror very modest very mindful yes
da oh this place looks uh familiar by
the way
um uh and Nissa are currently not
sharing their and yeah not streaming
right B is right okay princess
beu uh uh yes princess
beu
sure I am
uh uh she's my daughter so she's the
princess so I I request you to be kind
and polite and respect her names
thanks yes you must respect you must
respect the heir to the throne princess
I believe that you are her
daughter I will not share my other
political views for the meantime for my
own safety I know your political views
Shakira Shakira Shakira
I know it already don't worry and you
know what it's my duty as a as a nice
and kind Queen to respect forging thank
you yes you you may view politicals as
whatever you would like yes okay all
then uh the king says our battle grows
ever fiercer be vigilant hero and ready
yourself
for does not matter what
would be they will all see eventually
are you okay Nissa they will all it was
a strong earthquake right yeah it's
really strong really crazy oh never in
my life have I felt the Earth Tremor so
violently where's your PR accent he oh
he's British of
course oh oh I think I used to read him
like I fear is B ill for one is to
come your majesty urgent report most of
stains is gathered near St wait this
feels
[Music]
like this feels like I'm reliving
things reliving
things yeah stain stains at the
gate when the Calamity began spreading
stains would of emerg from the seers so
the entrance was sealed shut but if the
light of Revelation also stirs in those
watery corridors then we cannot but
invest investigate oh investigate let's
[Music]
go
what voices in my head are confusing me
here I'm going to temporarily leave the
group it might end the whole group call
for everyone it not so just as a warning
so everyone might need to rejoin the
party call but I I'm going to Quick talk
to gathan Okay g okay
okay there are splies everywhere
whatever hased
happened noiss a raven cross I had I had
to come to I had come to the kingdom
earlier last night and when I was piing
on my beautiful statue of Queen Tam
Ganer someone had to faced it what what
did they do to it I had not seen they
had placed let me send you a photo by
carrier pigeon I drew a sketch of it yes
one second I will wait what what
happened to the Statue someone deed it
deced it they defaced
it wait I'm waiting I will I one second
I have to dig deep into my mind's Palace
and reach and obtain the sketch for you
one
second so you it they took off her
face no no they did something worse
worse
something so
[Music]
terrible please check your pigeon mail
dear narissa ravencraft I'm looking at
my pigeon
mail may I may I
see yes I will send it to you as well
that is quite that is quite the defacing
that is quite oh my goodness I I don't
even know what to say how yes I can
believe they would do such a thing such
a terrible terrible thing I can barely
even look at this oh how vulgar yes how
vulgar how uning of the
kingdom it makes me want to throw
up that is my reaction as well the only
people who could def face the statue are
are people who are in your own
Guild think and the only two people who
are was the princess and the hot pink
one you dare accuse the
princess my goodness it could have only
been two other people
though you dare accuse the princess of
such I do not want to but the does make
a fair point we need we need your
your my you need my ah ah I see wait you
see by carrier pigeon let me quick share
an image with you that Gigi has sent or
excuse me Jonathan has sent to me
Jonathan I you mean on Discord hi my
carrier Pig pigon hello
Mario car carrier pigeon carrier pigeon
name to Discord look at the Statue
currently that is fixed of Tam
Gander yes queen as in is married to the
king now if you check if you check the
message I have sent you via carrier
pigeon you can see how it was defaced it
is so LW I can barely even bear to look
at it yes I can bear I cannot even
eyes I am taking it down because I was
fixing her but when I logged on when I
arrived in the kingdom and I saw it I
was so full of shock I I wanted to throw
up wait who who which is the queen that
you are supporting I support Queen Tam
ganner the one and only me too yes I
think that someone would do such a
terrible disgusting thing we estimated
that you can only build within your own
your own boundaries meaning that it had
to have been someone on the team
Cerulean cup H obviously didn't the
princess or the hot pink one also known
as Iris the hot pink one well she's not
speaking right now the I just want to
mention that yesterday the hot pink one
uh admit that I I am the first queen and
she time B is the second so just let you
know do we have a think Pro do it yeah
you actually have proved that it happen
you think the hot pink one would do it
it has been recorded in the arive of
should we take this mayhaps we should
put both of them on trial both the
princess and the hot pink one to
determine their in have to princess not
on trial mother I don't think so you you
are not allowed to touch or talk to my
um daughter
don't talk to me my daughter ever again
exactly prove her innocent I do not need
to prove such no she doesn't have to
prove anything yes she needs to prove
her
innocence yes I cannot accept it I
cannot just let it go uh we were going
to go and do and do a
dungeon's dungeon to be exact of
us has not had the opportunity could you
give me
mayhaps 6 minutes to craft a what one
would call a
[Music]
thumbnail needs needs to go herself and
actually finish the rest of the quest so
why don't you do so yes yes I will I
will
back oh yeah backpack and of the rest of
the quest Miss Kara can you keep talking
so I can equalize the voices in my head
um
um um yes how is the equalization going
uh sweet little princess okay she'll be
good now thank you shameful things on to
my Queen oh I would like to show you
something your hat is nice thank this
moai this moai emits
sound quite impressive hold on I will
show you stay stay in front of the moai
with
me oh
I need to
investigate
oh what kind of sounds can it play yes
wait outside while I I show you in front
of the muai it will emit sounds
okay please play the Beautiful
music
delighted oh my God I love this
[Music]
spe
I can hear
[Music]
to keep
on ah ah ah ah ah ah
[Music]
they keep pushing and
pulling oh beautiful katchup
we revelation
[Music]
praning
about celebrating their achievements
when they don't
know they'll never
know let them enjoy this moment
[Music]
foolishness the lot to them they don't
know right under their nose
literally that the world bless the moai
statue which projects music built by you
Inc do you like it that was divine
yay you have a gift it seems to be able
to control this M Mis mysterious
mythical
statue uh Vu would you like to join the
party PA oh
yes oh hello oh this whole time laa was
sorry sorry for making
noise no way I was enjoying it I
was uh K why don't you now go and finish
the rest of the preparations for your
quest okay I'm on my
way oh thank you for doing this for
me oh gathan isn't in this did you def
face the statue princess Pichu huh I did
not no did you def face do you know who
did I I don't
know it I lo I loged up kind of early
last
night yeah well I mean you were you
weren't doing so today were you
oh I only logged on like 30 minutes ago
oh that's true I suppose then I wonder
who else was on today maybe we will be
able to find some sort of archive yes I
wonder Wasn't Me Maybe do you think
gathan might be making it up and have
defaced it him himself that would be a
plot twist what if gathan is not as
righteous of a hero as we
thought I think there may be a potential
there may be a potential that that might
maybe some of the one of the Les leeston
vloggers may have captured it in one of
their Vlogs yes perhaps may maybe the
voices in in takanashi Kyra's heads will
know or tanakak Kyra's head excuse me
will know they're saying it was the hot
pink one oh yes yeah but who knows if my
voices can be trusted the hot yeah
because you know the voices in my head
told me that apparently Moko had put a
bounty over my head but it turns out
that that was not true ah well it seems
like they are there to start trouble
those voices the voices they would lie
to us yes I know they they caused a
whole lot of drama over
nothing maybe we should put the voices
on trial maybe we should mayhaps they're
not to be
trusted okay I'm talking to scol one
guil master here have the
key the storm gate key
okay the rolling cup
master I'm proceeding to where is
[Music]
it it's uh yeah headed generally
Jonathan
G yeah Jonathan with a G still observing
my
blog I I
[Music]
am oh so beautiful when the Sun is
setting this is so
gorgeous wow I am so blessed to be
living in this wonderful Kingdom yes
what a wonderful
lesbi
best what
wonderful wonderful
indeed I go grab a drink I'll be back
Qui okay they all you know I'm surprised
at how flat Tam gander is where is her
assat
yeah I was cling that yesterday when
this was being built Queen Tam Gander
where is your ass come look you me her
butto yes her
butto please be respectful of my Queen's
butto in fact it is not only just flat
but it is
inverted what wait what come look it is
inverted oh look oh my inverted as
correct have you done something with it
also I am very very sensitive when it
comes to inverted buttocks because I
myself has suffered this illness before
please I have never thought to look at
her
backside yes but it looks quite cursed I
think that they need to correct this
this mistake
immediately this is
unacceptable There is almost no cure to
an inverted ass it is difficult to
undo how does one get Afflicted with
inverted
but it is possibly by birth the only
thing that can save you is something
called a
BBB a b no BBL BBL L what's that yes it
stands
for benevolent buttock
[Music]
lamp ification you know I've heard that
word that acronym before but I I don't
think I've ever known what it
meant that's what it means ah I see I've
tried it but um on me it has only
partially worked so I don't know if it's
like really safe to recommend to the
queen Tim tender I would not want her to
suffer the same pain as me so let's just
ignore her inverted butt otherwise she
might feel very sad about it I see be
sensitive you you are so considerate yes
very mindful very very demure modest
very demure Very
cutesy Yes where do you learn such words
my
ladies it's I don't know it's just the
memories in my
head sometimes I hear a a clock ticking
and talking
sometimes tick tock tick tock when I
think of a clock ticking I think of
something else than you
perhaps it's like we come from different
worlds and different perhaps even
different times of
birth I cannot follow you with your new
yes we we we must be from different
timelines yes
um I'm going back to the
king so is the king your father
be I I do not I have just um been aware
of my familiar line I just know of the
king of liest as far as I understand
seems to be the situation that he is
married to Tam Gander however him and
Tam Gander are usurpers to the throne
that is rightfully Queen mari's and uh
princess
kishu I see therefore they are not she
she is not the King's Daughter however
the king is not the rightful Heir or or
leader of the throne he has simply
usurped it from the rightful Queen whom
he stole the memories of wait if the
king is not the
rightful uh uh King then does that mean
that Tim tender would not be the
rightful Queen yes oh
exactly I need to find proof for this I
still believe in my
queen even if her King by her side is
not the rightful one I still believe she
has the destiny and the Fate on her side
to be the rightful Queen all right well
that's on you that's on you and in the
end we are saving the Les leeston and
and I think what they really want is a
queen K
Kori Kori in what queen do you believe
in yeah Kori what queen do you believe
in do you believe in Queen Tam Gander or
queen
Mario is there any other queens I don't
know about yeah no I think those are the
only two bam fishy IDK well she has
spoken death has
spoken maybe the real King was the Dad
we met along the way yeah maybe the real
King was the friends we made along the
way and the king the Dad should
choose ah the gardens are full today
this makes me happy you have been taken
care of the
plots I'm
glad oh I'm ready to investigate the
sewers dungeon but oh we still need
Jonathan a Gucci bag
please uh well that that'll be uh R's
responsibility but you what you're going
to do is you're going to have you done
the quest to unlock the
bag no uh KIU yes do you remember what
quest it is to unlock the
bag
um
Chien I am back whenever you guys ready
oh ah
waa can Mario can you it's one of the
it's one of the blacksmith Apprentice
class I believe could you assist me with
the
uh with the bag the act of getting a bag
oh yeah yeah I already make the Matas
for you come come over yeah oh I'm
coming to you now okay hello greetings
salutations
salvation okay so I give you
now uh uh accept the
trade you
need five ingots I give you
10 oh I have enough oh you have
it do you have stain
hide well
15 I think that's enough okay then we
just got to go to the black black well
she needs to finish a quest first is
that not true oh you need to finish a
quest okay let's see what what kind of
quests I have up
here uh ah looking for five gold ingots
should I continue this one and see uh no
uh uh voices in our head I see it I see
it oh yes yes accept the
quest okay I talk
to I talk to the
guy probably yes okay somehow I
accidentally keep on mounting
my yes we are almost ready for the
dungeon I I found
J I am here I am the part as well I pray
tell join the party call oh I will now
enter the telepathic phone
call not I don't know why I capable of
buying the backpack welcome
gathan I I am on my way hey what do you
mean we will wait for you fair hero yes
I will make haste I have the backpack
thank you oh you got it good job let's
see what corruption we can find on the
outside to grow the corruption on the
[Music]
inside I am finally Gucci
up let me store so I room
yes ah some things seem to be unmovable
from my
hands yeah yeah any any any like uh
critical game items you are not able to
move so like the fire the thing that
makes you live in Fire and so on and so
forth I
understand uh
oh this shall
suffice I am ready whenever to
strike all right yes yes let's go then
we must wait for I see gathan in the
distance I on my
way where is Queen
Mario right behind you my lady wonderful
one second my
dears yes
this looks like the kind of pack I would
but just way
smaller all right I am I am ready I am
also ready all right for this
adventure let's Embark let us go park
onward we ride we ride at
dawn we are all such sophisticated hat
wearer yes yes I would not be caught
without hat M I love yes and now you
have a hat yes I am one of you
now you do not know how I feel about an
Amber coin but if you if you support
Queen Tam Gander I will speak a truth we
are we are compassion and empathy we do
not we do not make
prejudices ah yes I will open My Heart
To
Thee thank you you for your kindness
thank you for I knew I could remaining
ever loyal to Queen Tam
Gander she's uh I I have a complaint to
make however with the Tam Gander statue
what can you please fill out her ass it
is currently inverted I need you to make
it uh real true to life true to
life Fallen I am attempting she is still
a work in progress she needs am I the
only one who hasn't done it yet yes has
has everyone here finished the dungeon
yes yes okay you shall spoil me yes lead
my lady please read uh okay we find
ourselves in a white empty space it's so
vast that the very concept of distance
seems to lose meaning why is this not
about Burgers huh why was mine about
burgers in the midst of that space we
see an atique desk and a lever chair and
on that chair sits a girl sipping te
okay okay okay close enough tick tock
tick tock tick tock tick tock tick tock
tick tock PE what do you say about this
does it sound familiar perhaps it Sparks
something within my mind yes tick tock
tick tock tick tock as more and more
clocks join the chorus the girl closes
her
eyes tick tock tick tock
tick tock tick tock tick
tock I shall close my eyes
too oh there's words sense it
words words okay okay o it's a quiz
cannot believe they are floating all
right s of energy did a certain off
Reaper discover ah Soul energy Soul
energy oh and no uh oh sorry never mind
people's strong emotions people's no
people's Souls no uh
uh
both well we'll vote on whatever one you
want so make it this one strong emotions
strong emotions there's a third one you
do not think it's the eating lots of
sushi oh there's a
first no this one it's it's this one I
am sure this trust me okay
right
huz huz
so
intelligent well I have paid close
attention to what I have learned so far
what is this book oh souls are not a
zero sum game that's what the reaper
realized for if she could stir the
hearts of her audience the power of
their emotions were energy enough yawn
Crimson bows bows a treasure lies in
wait the Gaze of orus will point you
straight I do not understand that
somebody understand this uh it sounds
like a a hint to where her thing was in
the last dungeon no yes doesn't that
sound familiar remember remember when we
when you went to cross the Crimson bows
the Crimson branches yes yes the trees
the trees I remember
well a checkpoint a checkpoint huzzah
huzzah oh it's just a hint if you
haven't gotten the thing yet yes yes we
are making great progress and you are
learning so quick you're so intelligent
oh yes indeed because I don't need these
hints it seems I have already found them
all col why yes
wow I'm slow because I'm
starving you like would you like some
bread mother if you have some bread I
have some bread mother for you
starvation Medieval ages who would have
thought it is quite have would have n
thank you so much that's very generous
thank you all right anything for you
thank you so much which of these guards
the force field around Atlantis shark
statues electric jellyfish a dignified
man of a
beard I have collected some sewer water
delicious I
mean uh please do not tatch me gr I have
collected some water keep that keep that
away from us we do not would you like a
drink no I do not drink from Dirty sewer
water no no Charlie it is a dignified
man with a
beard what you want we'll vote for it
Charlie you must be I'm I'm on my way
I'm coming are you in or
what yes okay there we go dedication I
want to see it wait how do I get
in oh rad C oh oh no was it the wrong
answer go my people destroy them kill
them while they stand murder I honestly
way
they're princess no princess I shall
protect help they hurt me oh oh you
saved me thank you what happened
huz a princess must not find the need to
fight thank you she must be protected
thank you for protecting me by a night
MH mhm all right what is your second
choice after a dignified man salute you
let me try recall my Adventures you did
your best I will get revenge
one day um were you part of my
Adventures yeah they will we be they
will be
reborn in a more yes you cannot ask her
um it is so long ago it is hard to
recall but perhaps um
the shark
statues we can vote for
it yeah yeah
one more oh sorry there you go
princess princess thank you
go I
almost thank goodness thank the Le
leest the Le vest yes in the depths the
kingdom of Atlantis sits safe within its
force field Mighty Stone sharks stand
guard to defend it and yet rumor has it
that one girl slipped through those
defenses the ancient doll of meanders in
its maze reward awaits who out the
boundary St I already have this one in
my
possession you're so smart found all
then onward onward
onward
onwards a che the
checko
goodness I wish I had a glass that I
could throw on the ground while yelling
her own yes if
only feels
wrong oh oh question number three come
on this one is must be more closer in my
memory because I have done it today a
mysterious boy appeared at a certain
Shrine what is he particularly good
at H folding
origami a word that is
unfamiliar unfamiliar to me as well not
that is also unfamiliar what is that
what is soccer I only know football ball
what ball what is that I do not know any
of those things um it is when it's an
illness when your feet are in the
illness no terrifying oh no really hard
to walk terrifying it is so hard to walk
that you must do a thing called
dribbling dribbl in order to move ahead
say it not so
yes uh okay to her she was merely
keeping them company but to the souls it
was what they needed to move on one boy
left his bank from orami before
departing for the other side a Lain
fiend passage passage test the eyes
proceed Beyond the Wall to claim a prize
interesting interesting very
interesting uh really smart tall uh soup
lady taught me how to get that
one or queen Mario mother sorry I was I
was drinking some water it's
okay mother must stay hydrated let's see
go tired you should yes check
check check the
checkpoint huzzah we have forgotten our
huz huzzah we have we are one step
closer to solving this
dungeon wait a minute bgm was missing
okay so what is the grand achievement of
a certain excuse me Oddball Mi Oddball I
I wonder who they are talking about oh
how dare this dungeon qu a cruel
place ball helping a fast food
restaurant repay its depth taking first
place in hamburger eating contest or
saving a kingdom that is on the brink of
claps I say this look good because that
sounds way more like something I would
do
yes we will follow
along I am
sorry I must keep up appearances for the
greater good of the Kingdom I so sorry
our little
life I so sorry oh help oh they
hurt
Revelation okay well you know there's
the my family consists of many phoenixes
and maybe one Phoenix made the fast
restaurants certainly not me because I
saved kingdoms yes but I guess way M oh
we went the wrong way yeah yeah yeah
wait was did it
yeah that was confusing me
ladies my honorable ladies we got the
wrong way wait we got little my goodess
oopsies
we have helping a fast food restaurant
to repay STS mhm onwards Revelation
Revelation
huzzah
reation the strong fast restaurant
finally saw success some say the hardw
workking new part is as fiery as a
phoenix a crumbling crack and fiery
Fortress wall the brave may claim reward
where others fall or
oh ooh see you have to jump to it ah not
a h oh wait no my people I will kill you
first come this way ene at least you a
fall by my hands the
door wait what was I the girl stands on
the roadside looking D she just woke up
don't follow me the
picture ever all right I need to find
this dog help I kill I kill I shall kill
and protect the princess expecting a
call from her soon so thank you mother
this detective has a reputation to a
don't worry little guy I'll find you a
promise hey what do you want Jord for
leading me to the not my name it is
Jonathan no no no here here
here down here water watch out goodbye
he to the Yol
do a
n nice where are the rats rest in peace
my
brother
get thank you yes Crow Raven
lady we had to we had to do it multiple
times cuz we couldn't find
it yeah that's fine yeah right D
especially in reation
Revelation has to be earned except you
earned I don't you've earned
it I have earned it long time ago in
other ways yes
yes I have a right to listen to
it huzzah huzzah
huz for the kingdom once again for the
kingdom or the queendom yes the queen
yeah yes clean
sleigh yeah slay what did a certain
detective invent for The Travelers who
made it this far is it a teleportation
thing a golden axe oh it is a oh wait
but that's like we wouldn't really know
this would
we what do you think she would create
for us oh definitely a w Crystal because
she's a Time TR I don't notice but um I
have a feeling a
maybe you're correct
wow I am just really good with my
intuition what's that over there ah that
looks suspiciously placed suspiciously
you should open it oh it really is it
just there oh there's another book over
here too maybe I read the book
first I leave this for the heroes who
will one day visit this place may it
serve you well each chamber past has
offered you a rhyme revealing Secrets
where you've gone before there's one
last thing to find ear out you climb
what British and therefore I present to
you one more The Haunting grounds of
creatures of the night within its deps
you'll find a hidden light
what I see
yeah Crystal are you girls already in
the possession of yes yeah is in our
pockets amazing now I own it to
onward
Revelation
the Revelation
Revelation back into the sew are they
ever ending we find let's Loop we leave
here now that's our it is quite a large
sewer system mhm
M Another Story scary and stinky okay we
find ourselves in the white empty space
the girl still sipping her tea opens her
locker to reveal a number of pictures
each of them shows a girl who looks
exactly like herself one is searching
for a lost dog another is building some
sort of machine yet another is playing a
video game video game what is that she
gazes at the photos with a warm smile
let's see where should I go
today I do
Wonder
okay
complete are you having
a flashbacks
flashback I'm having a
migraine I feel the
migraine it's
it it's do you
remember yeah wait a second I think the
pictures in my head are coming together
the memories in your mind 60 frames per
second
wait you girls up and probably already
have seen
it but I shall play it for me and the
voices of my head yes free recount your
last memories yes wait bgm is not on
okay 3 to one
go
no huh what
husband
yeah yeah can we collect stuff from down
there no
right oh wait but I got I got a or wait
what look can get this
SM you forgot about
me she hates
[Music]
me world okay
wait
what wait I
was I was downgraded
[Music]
there's one that just doesn't fit in
there's one that's just weird I am
finished watching it but I am confused
can I have the change what is wrong
you're the CEO of kfp you run an amazing
restaurant not as I thought I was my
good you are but you are not known for
your mythical you are known for your
amazing restaurant and amazing food you
should build one to rival that of the
divorc diner by
kiai maybe maybe I should or maybe I
should prove my
mythical no no I do not want to be known
as the burger
lady you are more than that you are
beautiful exactly beautiful and mythical
and demure and mindful Dem and very de
very mindful
indeed well thank you for accompanying
me in this adventure of course F than
you for having us I am finally caught up
with all of you
[Music]
yay pocket you need to talk to the king
don't you oh warp to the king you say
let's see how warp towards him m
am I in no need of my horse anymore you
will need your horse it is a big Kingdom
oh there is so many
choices uh Which choice shall I make Lio
castle that is a great choice me
lady I am it's okay if it doesn't
respond it will respond when the server
get back up like it did last time
confused it's okay too much for me as
let have simply come to help the fair
Maiden uh complete I I am going to sign
off well my
Raven conratulations
you wait before you go there Raven coft
will you mayhaps help me with my trial
tomorrow uh trial I yes you have a trial
I will try I if I am online I will be
your witness you will stay as my witness
yes yes of course thank you I will need
to put trial Princess koseki beu and the
hot pink one oh now no thank you
I about the the oh uh about tomorrow I
may not be uh around oh you will not be
oh then we will hold a trial another
time is fine I will find you did
it I shall leave as well because I have
my queen duties to do accomplish so I'm
sorry I got
to thank you so much for your support of
course it was nice to play with to go to
adventures with you thank you so
wonderful to see
everyone
[Music]
fwell see you soon see you soon
bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]
byebye I yes I might not be around
tomorrow because I
need I need a homework day I don't know
what homework is
but I need a day to
complete
[Music]
my otherworldly
task before before or chaos takes the
world but for
today I will do my
utmost that so
that the seeds of corruption spread upon
this kingdom yes take
it little one it is not safe here it's
not safe to be seen with me for if you
are seen with me I must kill you
let's see what other stuff can I
grab where did where did the Wither
flowers come from does anybody
know there's a purple frog light in at l
they sprout in the wild yeah the one the
one that my wife has has given me I'm
trying to find more of
those in this dungeon
[Applause]
perhaps
[Music]
oo well I am scouting for resources near
ena's dungeon okay
I wanted to do every single day this
week but unfortunately my princess has
have caught up with
me I must I must do my
duties and perhaps miss a day but that
is
okay I'm sure the the other hero
will
farewell in my absence but for now the
seeds of corruption must be must be
[Music]
swn let's see can I take anything
anything good that I can take from
here what is it
[Music]
a breing stat that looks kind of
gnarly can I take
this
ah no you do not know you are not aware
that you have the presence you are in
the presence of
you're not aware are you you do not know
that you are trying to murder your true
princess
traitor I'm
[Music]
sorry ow no not another I do not want to
slay my people
no okay I want to find the flowers that
grow in the
night the nerve
[Music]
around
here I only see normal
[Music]
flowers tree with vines near the portal
to the coast area
up now yeah this is the dungeon I can't
get anything from the
dungeon let's okay I'll go to the coast
area and
check oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I have
one
Geniuses voes in my head you are on my
side correct we are on the path of
Darkness together right I cannot have
have you here if you are going
to be in my
way always yes okay please declare thine
loyalties Tree by portal you said
[Music]
the other side of the
PCH on the plain
[Applause]
side oh
house here the vines could be useful as
well as as Vines
spread and encroach upon
territories as
will the
darkness encroach and cover the light
what are these ooh
yes
poison of death signs of death
that
grow life that
[Music]
emerges perfect
what is that ooh yes yes all of this
yes
perfect such plants such evil that
spread through the
world what's
that oh I have no space
already dang it
dang
[Music]
it ah
no away the bone of my
people I do not wish to see those who I
have required to
slain it's okay it was for the
kingdom for the
kingdom no
away with
you
okay are there flowers ow
hey it is okay you have not but
intelligence you just kill kill but I
understand
you spare them I will spare
them I will spare your life for I am
you're true
ruler I will come back
[Music]
here yeah Ione know specifically where
the where the Wither flowers are
[Music]
oh may I ask what you are doing kbu I
don't know
no answer
H I don't know oh oh sorry I was
muted oh I see I see HK
look I feel I fear the corruption has
spread through the land but are you not
the one building
it just go just go along with it the
corruption the corruption builds from
inside
[Music]
it
seems Gordon ramsy may be
aware so you may be aware that means I
may have
to take her out
oh my mic is still on not
[Music]
muted can I put this here
oh no I think the chains coming out of
the ground is better
[Music]
a
greetings
ow how do you spell Targaryen tar Ki beu
princess Ki
hi may I may I ask that you take your
hat off for a second so I may look at
your
crown
no no well why not I would like to take
a peek at your
crown
nah no no is there a reason because it
is my buddy and I spent like $7 million
trying to get to him and and oh but you
can just hold him in your arms my
inventory is literally full I I cannot
actually take it off right now oh but
later you will show me yes yes later
sure yes yes be well take care yes thank
you
let the roots of evil
[Music]
grow let the seeds of
Doubt no
okay oh
yes no no one was around it's it is fine
[Music]
I don't know what that is but it looks
evil so that's cool o
[Music]
yeah I like that
grow
[Music]
growl
yes my darkness take the
[Music]
world hold on
UHA
[Music]
yes
would it be what it be would it be too
like
uh no it wouldn't okay hold
on I I was thinking would it be tooo
dark if something
but how do you get one of
these where where would one where one
get this you can craft it
[Music]
okay smooth Stone how do you get smooth
Stone
Big C
[Music]
melt smelt Cobble okay
I think the darkness is looking pretty
good what do you think voice
[Music]
is needs more purple yes
okay I have
coal I guess I need to go get
[Music]
stone what's
this mang light
light wao
[Music]
I need more I need more of these
trees it's a s oh can I make it turn
into a tree if I plant
it I want see what happens if I plant
[Music]
it
yes okay Cobblestone you said let's go
get
cobblestone my
voes unfortunately I do not have
permissions to cross thy lands so the
darkness shall start with my own kingdom
take away the benevolent empaths
first
yes
yes make my knight do
it maybe my wife sh Nolla I don't know
it's dangerous to bring in others upon
my
plan per
Perhaps Perhaps sh Nolla
[Music]
could yes maybe she
could they would soon learn of your plot
I welcome
that I hide my identity for too
long once is it once is it is uncovered
there will be
War a war of
one I need an ally yes maybe I shall
talk to sh
Nolla is it is it safe to bring allies
into the darkness
though who knows I'm hungry
[Music]
uh ooh ooh can I get oh ooh
ooh ooh
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
yeah Pebble of
Darkness
[Music]
wait
wait wait
yes
[Music]
ideal
no
uh I have no room oh
I don't need this
[Music]
okay
hello how art thou I'm
good good day good
day good day my eyes were blurry for a
second apologies um yes yes uh so uh you
know what my dear daughter I would like
to treat you to um a special treat a
treat at the tavern at the
tavern
yes a delicious treat what kind of treat
may I
ask it is but a surprise Ive saved it
but for you my dear daughter create it a
ious yummy treat well I must know what
it is for perhaps I may be allergic you
know but you was spoiled the surprise
dear daughter but uh you know allergies
are an important you know thing to be
aware of you have multiple options
okay are you allergic to
chocolate
h i are you allergic to cake cake
oh oh I'm good I already have chocolate
cake in my
MOA you can have more I saved it just
for
you wait a second seems that she really
wants to speak to
you last night you were you were quite
you were quite hesitant of being called
mother and me being called your
daughter I remember I remember you were
quite you were
quite confused and and reluctant what
what I look my dearest daughter I slept
on it and I remembered dear I I remember
yes I remembered as I as I before I
slept I could not even sleep uh cuz I
was thinking about a night's Duty and
part of a night's duty is to make others
happy and I want to make you happy by
calling you my daughter
oh moving all right
mother
yeah you are my mother aren't
you yes and you are princess blood flame
yes I am princess blood
flame all right I will go with you to
the
tavern H that is a good girl good
daughter thank you I'm going to go get
you the cake all
right shall we go go to the tavern oh
wait perhaps we
shall how wonderful you have such a kind
mother you're true kind mother what a
kind
mother
yes
not oh I I see I see a Gest yeah it's is
about a justest a
just yes yes a justest
but a justest ah now come if and sit
here dearest
daughter okay
treat you
know you wouldn't lie to me would you of
course not mother you're my mother blood
flame mhm so did you do it did you do it
did you defame the the the statue of did
you do it did
you hey maybe she did not do it why are
you attacking her all of a sudden I'm
being a strict mother here that you need
to sit on the nauy step and stti up you
need to sit here on the nauy step and
think about what you have done trapped
her here to yell at her mother you're
scaring me here I'm the naughty step
what my goodness my brother right here I
didn't do anything my
good why would she do this to me look
she is crying did you did you defame
that statue
no I would never like you bathan spent
hours on that statue Jonathan
hourss and I watched the glory of the
queen yes I did it wasn't it wasn't me
brother I've been I've been flamed you
promise in the name of blood flame you
promise in the name of blood blood flame
yes it was not me mother I did not you
swear on your mother I on my blood flame
mother yes yes oh
see well well dearest
daughter
I who did it then who do you think did
it who did it who do you think did it
who she's in tears and you would push
her in such a way oh yes oh oh
mother yes I love you
too yes now who do you think did it
um well there was there was there was
somebody in the what was in
the the rest of the ravencraft saying
that God and G might have defaced their
own statue to cause chaos with why would
I do that I don't know but I I heard it
from
the N of the Raven C why would Nas the
Raven C thing but that was that might
have suggest in the group call how
terrible wait a minute gathan would you
take your hat off for did you me did you
do it did you do it did you you come
here stand on the nauy step on the NAU
step okay I will prove to you did you do
it no I would never my queen did you did
you maybe you were cursed by the witches
and you you were cursed to Def yes there
are witches de princess dear daughter
yes there are witches maybe they cursed
you to go and defame the witches The
Witches The Witches one of them is
Nissa nissa's a wi you are not the one
possessed she used she used her charm on
me she has used what else has she done
to
you she has kiss you
made no mother have you have you been
corrupted by narissa Raven cross mother
I would never I I am stronger than any
witch you hear me stronger more power
wait let me let me test it nissing Raven
cross right
[Music]
there she is behind you yes no she is
not as much as she has stalked me the
witch has stalked me she is stalking me
to see my weaknesses you see gathan but
it seems like she is your weakness
mother you do seem to fall to her yes
what are those strange noise you are
making every time I mentioned her name
niss ravencraft no I had too I too much
bread niss ravencraft has hexed her you
are not trustworthy at all huh you are
not trustworthy night at all no no no no
no no no I get me out of here I will not
be to trust thank you thank
yes thank you what did you it's
not ooh Ooh Ah that's a wonderful
beautiful ons wow this is nice has made
such a beautiful
thing I am not hexed by the witch I made
out it's
dangerous myself in potion are you
prisoners she dragged us and trapped Us
in the travern the Tav we were trapped I
save you then yes you saved us thank you
I will prove this welcome I am drama URS
I see oh my Pearl hello hello my dear
husband have you committed crimes no I
have not but I cannot speak of it here I
trust I not trust these
two away away
Jonathan is
your your partner is
crazy in a good way yes wait I I believe
I'm receiving a phone call hello oh hang
up if it's gathan hang
up oh okay I I I no oh
God sorry excuse
me oh don't mind that okay um yes I have
a meeting I must attend
oh oh a meeting with who all of a sudden
I must
Listen
whoa
yes
[Music]
yes is red even Beyond the board
yet we
can we can overtake oh we can overtake
the
borders yes
[Music]
yes we can my plan
H how do I do this
[Music]
maybe maybe if I
there we
go
red dye on the sign affects
T I'm trying to make
this I'm trying to make this what is on
my head
D Tex looks good how do we make D
[Music]
Tex just use die on the sign
okay um
[Music]
hold on let me let me hide my
minions let me hide them amongst the
trees
[Music]
W they
are fools in their
[Music]
drama the kingdom grows yes I can fly
you Qui
[Music]
ha let the Shadows Of Darkness go
spread we shall rise look at them
[Music]
where are they going it is of none of my
concern oh can I
[Music]
not another
oh wow I can't even take it cuz oh
that's so funny I can take this one
though yes across
kingdoms let it
spread the roots of corruption it has
spread to one side we must
the other
side
[Music]
yes the darkness shall claim
all yes we need more
mud I don't know if I if I put
one if I put it here will it will it
grow does it need like a 9 by9 like how
much how much space does it need to
[Music]
grow need to different out of what what
if
[Music]
hopefully it'll grow with the sign next
to
[Music]
it I need
dirt uh
[Music]
this I don't need for now I really wish
we could store the key items Oh what a
beautiful
statue oh stay there I will show you
something oh the princess is that you
yeah wait have you done your own dungeon
yet I mean I mean the dungeon of the
sewers I have yet to attempt the dungeon
but I was thinking of waiting for the
heroes help huh Shar just murdered my
child what I had a child with with Lady
blood flame and takaa shikira used her
Revelation on it oh and it is dead yes
my son has died your son we must my
son I'm so sorry I I'm so
sorry we must we must have trial for for
this Heathen trial who decided to kill
my child my child how could
she where is she wait wait wait wa wa
wait wait wait wait you have a child
with blood
follow me uh just recently follow me
okay I will take you I will take you to
them
follow has killed my child oh no what
the left you alone for 3 minutes how
this
happen what has
happened what what has
happened killed my child no no no you
have presented a chicken in front of me
I am I am the owner of kfp as you have
all seen in my video I must make chicken
into Fried Chicken that is just how it
goes she call the video a
memory a video you made a memory video
it is a strange slang I think strange
slang her lands wow the mighty Phoenix
has different wording yes I I came up
with it it's easier to stay I see I see
we we shall learn from this Mighty
Phoenix we will learn you can call it a
video
learn my
child forget that she murdered my
child it was never your child you were
just pretending to get Elizabeth into a
spond that she is not willing to enter
freely I lay
eggs what oh that's wait what what what
you do you lay eggs huh confirm I'm not
going to lie my lady that is a
turnoff oh my goodness see you have
given her the
egg
I how often do you lay these eggs I only
lay eggs here I don't actually lay eggs
wait how could it be her child would it
not be the t's
childi no it was my child with was the
human where was the human in this bird
that we saw it should have been
grotesque
disgusting when did you guys consumate
your marriage yes I did not know that
you guys I thought I thought you were
just calling her a witch like 10 seconds
ago came and trapped me who while we
were trapped while we were trapped in
the tree we consummated our our love for
each other no we did not I trapped her
in the tree I mean the troll came around
and trapped her in the tree um um excuse
me the usual incub ination time for a
bird is about 21 days so if it happened
yesterday you could have not possibly
already late I I
traveled days ago time Trav I I'm
beginning to think you are a witch I'm
not a witch how can you
travel
wi attempted murder attempted murder why
do you hit me oh I'm sorry I was going
for the witch what mother no mother I
have a crystal in my
arm I'm sorry I'll pull it out there I
pulled it out are you okay it is it is
but a
scratch mother Tri you must put the
trial what else would you be doing with
a
witch we questioned her and we show
fine I'll I'll rub this medicinal Beach
on it there you
go thank you what a good daughter you
are thank you you're welome oh no I
refuse how kind oh thank you she's fine
refuse is dead she's dead killed her no
no she's alive she's also uh um
ladies did you uh did you uh uh uh see
the uh the the the notice board with uh
there is a tournament today today
tournament a grand tournament will be
held in an hour and 10 minutes at the uh
the arena the prize is honor join us and
sharpen your blades and prepare to test
your mind what about money I did not
know that they had there is no money the
kingdom it's honor but money I no money
we will watch the
show no you must join in you must join
in it is partially training you
must it is training as well for the
fight
ahead do not worry Jonathan everybody
gets a wooden sword it is a fair
fight while they are arguing I must
continue on my
[Music]
quest Let Them
Fight for their honor I need no honor
here I have no
honor no money
no no it's muted it it's okay there is
no one around what is this mute you talk
[Music]
about let's just see
if let me see if this
work
glorious let corruption spread through
the
L
yes yes okay uh what oh yeah ink
[Music]
what kind of
ink oh dye right
[Music]
dye red
oh yes
[Music]
wonderful how do I make this look like
it needs I think magenta die I think
magenta die would work
[Music]
yes
yes wonderful well let me shape this
[Music]
face uh
there's like drippy
drippy what is
[Music]
that it is not
safe oh where's my tab I don't know
yes
[Music]
yeah are you
okay
hello are you okay you ran off very fast
oh yes I wanted to get some work on my
moai done before the
tournament ah yes you all going to join
in I am proud of you
yes maybe you are
my why is her front dimensional and her
back she is not finished it it's just
here for you to look at her have we seen
the Queen's back is it quite voluptuous
I am not to where is nothing there it is
covered by a cape you would not look she
has a cape on you don't need to look
there's nothing there yes yes I see I
see yes well then it's quite accurate
no quite Beau very accurate Lea wasn't
built in a day so she shall also not bu
be built in a day she she's not built in
a day she will be built over 2 days
mayhaps okay I shall observe her
tomorrow again her beauty I hope to be
impressed by her beauty yes when you
observe her tomorrow she may have a
backside a backside we look forward to
it huz back side
huz back
side I love my goodness good I
love princess what a beautiful hat you
have oh thank you it is my friend uh his
name is
Joe he has a name
yes he does not control
your no no no no he is just my
companion then if he is your comp
compion are you able to remove him for
about a moment I oh yes yes yes see I
can yeah see I can do it anytime Oh what
a beautiful crown you have thank you yes
it is my indication that I am a
princess I see yes yes
yes uh thank you for showing me your
crown I have verified your princessness
thank
you you are you are a wonderful Pearl I
can see what gathan sees in you yeah
oh so kind yes such a benevolent
princess thank you I look forward to
your rule ah yes one day I cannot wait
to take over this beautiful
kingdom such beauty one day yet yes one
day I'm sure that will come what are you
doing up there huh
oh oh they can fly go whatever I think I
think your wife has has trust issues
ah uh she's she can be a
[Music]
little oh she is very
little she's busy she's busy she's
locked in as they
say I
see what are you staring
at oh the beauty of your statue how much
you look like a little fly as you fly up
in the air a
fly she is the poop and you are the
fly oh do not know what you mean there
uh no thing I this just how loyal you
are oh thank you worked very hard in her
in her honor and she has made night
mhm is that really the only
reason yes Jonathan could make you her
night I am her Knight oh well oh you're
twoo timing stat what Jan statue it'll
be right here if you if you wish it I
will make you a statue my sweet I I
don't want to show her her song yet she
she hasn't done the D I don't think I
can stand next to the queen I am not
queen or
King I don't want I don't want to spoil
her for her own
dungeon the
queen no no no no no that would be too
too
too oh right right now ban I think she
was she was asking for you to hold her
hand you want to hand holding I will
have none of that in this Kingdom that
is lwd
EXC it is L I let go I have let go that
is come this way get this
way m m pulling you away over here over
here Mom what what let them be for a
moment oh oh she is she not the queen if
she is the mother of the princess or is
she but a
concort they're having a moment I see
not
know hand holding is okay on wholesome
occasions now kiss what was that oh now
that's who taught you how to
kiss um noce The Raven C the person in
front of me whisperings in my ear
yes she has went off she's in the
haunted
forest oh that is a haunted forest yes
if you go closer there are signs of this
that the darkness will take you yes the
the the corruption seems to be spreading
I have quite concern of this as the
princess of the
Kingdom corruption yes corruption read
the
signs oh darkness is
approaching careful careful
careful
careful happen is approaching wait a
minute
evil yes the introduce this Darkness to
our kingdom the darkness it's taking
over our lands
stains well it's obviously someone of
the cilian cup who has cursed this uh
part of the
land you know who it
was
no no what dear husband you're not lying
to me are
you she has taken the Hat offer what hat
oh oh yeah cuz I have a Crown Princess
welcome a welcome back princess oh thank
you she's free we have freed we have
freed her of of its
influence so influence would you say
that
you do you feel strange mayhaps do you
have any memory the past few days my
head G is in do you have any memories of
do you remember what we've done a couple
hours ago do you remember Hell wait I I
this is the first time I'm seeing you
today
right it was her what do you remember
who I am oh no oh no you're you're my
mother right ah remember I told you
yesterday I'm not your mother oh yeah
yeah oh yeah remember yeah good it's the
first time I've seen you today right
hello
Jan and pearl yes yes what is the last
memory you have
um going to going to sleep last night
and then waking up right now just now
and entering the round now you just
woken right now yes oh oh so you do not
know of this
waa what is
this what see that the darkness has
taken over the land darkness is
approaching Darkness that influence her
oh no I don't
know fo I so why are we
Whispering nothing I nothing no reason
you stay away from the darkness the
forest I am going to create a perimeter
a perimeter yes I will stay far away
some stuff we will contain it yes
contain it
they believed it they fell for
it did musing you cannot take the hat
off and believe that the influence was
gone fools yes isn't it fun it's coming
out of the mouth it's like a
little ah it's not coming out of the
nose right oh wait look I can do this
too hold on hold on hold on it can do
this one
second uh uh uh uh I don't want to do
hers yet
uh wait where did
my something magical happen yes M
something magical will happen one
[Music]
second it emits
noise that's a giant speaker yes [\h__\h] it
kills really must fun more often people
takes guns kind of in the ruins of Hell
the
audience kill my pocket the SC it's like
[Music]
that it's not done
yet I'm still working on it it a work in
progress V Lang comes out of
the with the till we get him to St all
right
[Music]
straight way
I
really think that you know I would like
to
visit it looks so f
[Music]
bch is
fuing
the can we can we get um you guys were
saying something about glow
glow glow
glow glow something is that
possible glow ink yes glow ink yes glow
ink it cuz I see I see uh
the what is
it I see the the fart has glow ink how
does
one get glow
ink
[Music]
cuz I thought there was glow ink here
somewhere
oh no no no it's just it's just ink ink
never
[Music]
mind I don't think we can have glow
ink yeah it's just tack never
[Music]
mind is it is it is have I um my my
allowance is oh oh yes yes allowance
here I I I have been allowance what kind
of relationship is
this no it's to support the family
business yes this is between the two of
us princess ah okay I will I will leave
you be it
is for now see your husband tomorrow yes
I will definitely not be going to the
Ember
coin she would not
go I need more room
[Music]
ow ooh what you
doing oh yes
[Music]
yes
ah oh the flowers smell
nice yes
[Music]
where is my
bucket where is my bucket
did I lose my bucket oh my bucket
where'd it
[Music]
go I don't think I don't think I can go
lower I I think two down is the lowest
we can go
yeah
yes you may fence the area up
but Darkness will spread
it will spread throughout the
land a m fence without WS
[Music]
Preposterous nothing can word off this
pathetic
[Music]
h
yes let them let them go on their
Adventure let them let them let
them let them leave this
area
yes let them go
I must I must stay here to work
[Music]
this is okay she is she's blinded by her
love for she's blinded by her love for
the queen that she does not know that's
right below
[Music]
her it be
is The Bu in the
backpack no
[Music]
oh flower yes we need more
flowers okay I'm going to clear my
inventory and then we we will still go
looking for flowers yet again
[Music]
oh I perhaps need another it's okay I
can go yink
a I can go yink uh a
[Music]
thing let me go yoink some barrels yoink
yes indeed we must yoink
yoink
yoink okay we have you
in oh
[Music]
there's some lava around the cave ooh
let's just let's just Traverse and
see anything anything that looks like it
is a force of evil and death I may
use is so was that a dog oh a dog it
does indeed look like a
dog cave on the store
line you mean you mean the cave to the
dungeon oh who does who does not recycle
Vine boats excuse me
wa so is there lava down
here how do we how do we make stuff to
put
[Music]
it's on the shoreline how do we put like
you know how in the in the Priestess
dungeon you could put stuff down it
it'll look like blood how do you do that
Redstone
right you just put down the just place
redstone
okay just place the dust ah perfect okay
let me get some more of this
thing
um and I might get stuff for enchanting
because I feel like I'm going to need
silk
touch
later ooh is that lava
can we put down lava in I don't think so
I feel like they wouldn't allow that cuz
it's too
dangerous but lava stone
maybe yeah it might be too dangerous it
might not allow for it
[Music]
ow but I will take more lapis
hungry I want lava stone not lava
[Music]
yeah magma blocks
yeah mag I don't know what it's
[Music]
called oh wow that was a lot okay uh
uh you say there was something on the
coastline
cave is this said cave
[Music]
M die to
it the
buffering is by YouTube being all
we I found
it it's been battle night oh stay
TR
[Music]
YouTube it has been fine on my side I
don't think it's my side cuz I've been
able to converse
with
with others
fine cannot handle it then maybe I don't
know I I
die you two cannot handle the darkness
perhaps yes it is too strong
the corruption has reached YouTube
maybe because I don't I don't think it's
me cuz everything has been
loading fine and I haven't heard any lag
when talking to the to my
companions so I am not sure oh she has
fallen
light stutter
weird it was lagging on other streams
today too
H
interesting has been defeated
[Music]
yes she may be on to me
but
alas ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
what is this this is
cool ow ow ow ow owow
owowowowowow I
mean that hurts
what is that I can't collect it all need
shears all
unfortunate I wonder they'll let me put
this down right I think this is enough
let's find
out if I need more I know where to find
it
[Music]
hell
will they let me put it
down
[Music]
yes
yes does it
work
[Music]
yes h
pathetic he is not aware
[Music]
I just want to build a
statue I just watch to build a
statue I am muted
[Music]
right under their noses
well
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes okay still working still working
still working right under their
noses I
must complete my task with I stay in
Kingdom she sits upon on the King's
[Music]
throne n anyone can challenge
me John Watson what what power has
compelled me
[Music]
wonderful ow ow ow ow ow ow
yes
very very nice how how do you make
this this how how how just want make
[Music]
that do you know do you guys
know
hire coal and wood three logs stick and
charcoal
[Music]
oh oh yes I have I have
barrels
[Music]
perfect die will go you know what I'm
just going to shove
whatever okay I got charcoal
and
[Music]
then you can make a soul campfire fire
will be blue
how X stick
stick stick charcoal stick log log
log
stick stick stick charcoal stick log log
log okay okay okay okay
[Music]
so stick stick
stick
charcoal log log log
aha
wonderful I will make
[Music]
another ow oh yeah that's my thing
yes another another I require another
[Music]
I am running out of mud
she is
distracted I need not
worry I am not worried of the power of
thine
enemy I do not cower in fear
[Music]
B
pathetic of pathetic
sort hello beu hello
Mother uh anyway uh I am here to tell
you that the uh due to some uh Heroes
going into a dungeon uh the
the tournament shall be at half past
instead half past okay half
past it's already half pass half pass
next half pass the next the next half
pass next half pass yes yes yes yes I
see very cute thank you mother thank
you you do you do not fail to make me
smile oh I am I am I'm a LED mother I am
happy I am sorry about riding horses in
the castle the other day oh well
mistakes help us grow yes I have learned
uh the princess is still learning her
etiquette see yes yes and I mean if you
are as you say my dear and you are a
princess then yes princesses do not ride
their horses in the castle yes I will
not TR I will no longer ride my horses I
have grown up yes good
girl thank you mother thank
you
uh foolish
oh so how do you make this
[Music]
again what what's this
one smooth Stone and
stick smoo Stone smooth
stone
is cob
Stone Mo
Stone buy from
fa on none of the none of the fart I
thought employees are
here I thought narissa ravencraft was
around but she's not cook Cobble in
furnace Stone smoo okay
God I can do
[Music]
it I will put all
my I have no sense of organization that
is fine the stay King kingdom
is a land of chaos and
disorganization it is
fine there is no method to my
madness all
right I did have
oh
wait oh yeah
okay
yes
wonderful ow ow ow ow ow
wonderful let this be a warning
[Music]
oh ow
ow I love how it goes past territory
lines
amazing
genius PL more
trees
listen if if the corruption spreads too
fast and too much the other kingdoms
will be on high alert I cannot have that
we must sew the seeds
first so that they might think that
there is a chance of them winning yes we
must give them false
hope in order to make them have a sense
of
security
yes yet
for now just
a a small growth I will hide my
soldiers
here
yes H the evidence the evidence I must
away there we go
I I believe that there may be some who
may be already caught on to my Deeds but
I do not fear
them because the staying Kingdom will
surely
grow M would be a good
recruit maybe when they are done with
their
with their dunon I may call
them I may call
them and but we have to choose our
allies carefully maybe
Ena she is she is my sister but she
seems to have a wholesome nature within
her is her
[Music]
heart fully
ready to accept the darkness she is of
kind heart she
is the owl though the owl targarian
perhaps I'll tararan
maybe maybe one who I could
align myself
with we we will only have a chosen view
for
now I may think my
wife and you said Cobblestone
yes the princess of darkness is walking
on
a very dangerous path right now
everyone is against me in this Kingdom I
must I must be
careful okay hopefully that's
enough I'll get coold too perhaps
yes pop pop
pop have you heard the taals of
Darth beu the wise it is a tail that
most
livs would fear to
[Music]
tell yes the kingdom wa might hide this
tail from
you please tell us your short a what did
I say about shortness huh what did I say
what did I
say okay that should be
[Music]
enough
yes B your last B May the kingdom of
stain take
you I am not the be you you
knew I am not the be you you knew
[Music]
what have I
done all bonds
broken all bonds
[Music]
broken
oh uh obviously oh oh uh
oh like
this and then would it be like
[Music]
this
oh I only need three okay
okay I only need one I only need one of
the the armor thingies
[Music]
okay I need a stone cutter we have one
yes how do I make this this is what I
would like we need a slab
okay the false Queen has one in her
quarters yes I believe so
[Music]
oh oh yes oh yes the coal
yes thank you brainworms I mean Pebbles
[Music]
okay there we
go you call it a
word
oh yes my brethren slay them slay all
yes wonderful
take out every
hero how many do I
need one
okay
um then six sticks okay
sticks I can
[Music]
do
uh all right
[Music]
ha
H
H aha
a where shall it
be right
here yes ow ow ow ow owow
owow okay
now no no no no no no not not there not
there not
there right
right hold
on can I put a hat on
it let me see hold on
buddy I don't think I can no can we can
we not make armor at
[Music]
all no okay that's fine
carb pumpkin
[Music]
ooh
oops oh that's cool
when place in mud it sinks and looks
cooler
oh hold on it has to be under a tree I'm
doing
something it's going to look cool it's
going to look
cool I have
[Music]
chains
uh okay I do need more mud
[Music]
okay I wish I could give him clothes or
at least a body to make it
more
scary can I have t that go across
[Music]
something oh ow
oh
[Music]
like
this oh I can't put it down cuz of this
oh
[Music]
sorry if I put a
can I not put this on top I can't okay I
cannot do
that
yes yes
[Music]
yes okay
oh
wait yes another tree
here let me take
this connect that yes
[Music]
yes it just it just needs a head now I
wish I wish I wish there was a head that
I could put on
[Music]
him pumpkin head let's see
are there are there ways to get shears
in
this two iron to make shears can we
craft
that two iron let's see if we have some
iron
[Music]
oh
Ingot I will B this thank you my
guild
yes wonderful
I'll put the one I don't need
back there you
[Music]
go ah there were pumpkins
here can I harest the
pumpkin how this one har like this yes
yes yes yes yes wonderful
okay maybe we need to carve it
first Oh wrong wrong area
[Music]
oh I must plant yes you are correct I do
not want I am still the
princess I am still the princess I must
I must replant I am not that
evil okay there we go
I have
standards all they we well
oh it's kind of
floating is there a way to make it
[Music]
lower ah
yes
[Music]
yes yes
let this be a warning to
[Music]
all course for glowing head
I think there were torches outside that
I could
get can't wear a glowing one oh man
[Music]
can you can the can the thing not wear a
glowing one okay well this is still good
look look at this this is
amazing hold on hold on hold on I need
some lanterns
chaos rain Supreme let this be a
warning ow
h
Huh
huh huh
dang
it dang
it
oh run
I can't take the Torches from over
there but I can't take
these is there anywhere in the world I
can get torches
[Music]
from a a dungeon have
one Co and sticky they're cheap
oh in front of Ina
[Music]
dungeon ow oh the princess
ow
[Music]
help and we oh should we warp home then
oh yes warp home feel free let's warp
all the way home oh yes we must talk to
the king hello princess hello goodbye
[Music]
oh oh oh I was muted oh oh oh what
shame oh oh my
bad I was muted oh my
bad good day Pearl and
alar girl
[Music]
I am running low on food
yeah yeah let's just make torches I
think I have I have sticks and I have
coal I think that's how you do it it's
cheap let's go
home ah
yes why does my inventory fill up so
quickly ah go away
[Music]
oh it's in my magical to how
wonderful
hello what do we want torches
for oh
yeah I don't think it will work though
ow
no
yes let this be let this be a warning to
all
yes
oop to much
stuff
ow the corruption
is
beautiful not not all the pumpkin people
it's a person it's a person can't you
tell it's a dead guy it's a dead thing
it's not a it's not a pumpkin it's a
dead it's a dead guy
[Music]
I can't I don't know if I can put armor
on it I don't think we can we have
access to
armor hello Jonathan with the G hello
Miss
ninoa how fairy I am building a statue
of our dear Queen wow she's beautiful
yes it looks just like
her it does
how has your day been to the kingdom
it's been great we have uh traversed the
sewers and found found things the
memories you have found things memories
yes um may I ask you did my dear sweet
Pearl say anything about me after she
had regained her
memories
uh um she she did mention
something about detective
work detective work and how she should
offer her
services oh she should that would be
great to find
whoever ruined the statue of the queen
my
[Music]
Pearl what do you hear something
[Applause]
[Music]
where'd she
go she totally just ran out of there
[Music]
name
Waton it is the pleasure to meet you
Amilia
wat here that's right I'm not just a
detective I'm aav
[Music]
hello hello
hello oh hello hello is this you it
sounds like
you yes that is me I recorded that yeah
oh wow
wonderful yes so was before I came to
this Kingdom and
I
beautiful your voice is beautiful
pearl thank you a lot of people have
been calling me Pearl recently I guess I
made quite a name for for myself oh I'm
sorry you're John Watson yes it's
Bea I'm AIA Watson oh oh you're ailia
Watson have you regained your memories I
have regained my memories yeah AIA watch
what a beautiful name it makes me want
to go thank
you for some
reason Mak me Shy
beautiful can you if I remember
correctly you're the princess right yes
yes I am the
princess princess of rocks yes princess
of
rocks totally not princess of anything
else yes oh yes you princess something
else no just rocks just rock Darkness
perhaps no no not darkness no just just
rocks yes okay this I see this is
spreading past
[Music]
doesn't look safe oh look look look
um it seems that the stains have have
have given us a warning of a dead
guy yes how horrible I I think I must
report this to the king yes you should
report this to the king are are you not
worried that your SP will become
corrupted no rock rock dance my daughter
not my daughter uh
um where does one get eggs eggs don't
from a chicken cuz I know it's from a
chicken I have eggs for
you I mean I could I could get some
myself if you tell me where I do not
have to take your eggs I I have plenty
of eggs hold on hold on hold on hold
on only if you are sure yes I am sure I
have no need for
[Music]
them uh
I one second mother I have no
room
I'm I'm a time travel she's a time
traveler oh
[Music]
yeah m
what's that
noise I'm a a cat what what is that
[Music]
noise is it
this oh it's
outside is a strange noise a cat is
dying sister are you
okay oh sorry I I had the spirit of the
SAR take over over me for a second don't
know what's
happening I think you have a cat stuck
in your throat oh oh
maybe I think I'm
fine okay it happens sometimes don't
worry about it you did such a repetitive
meow caught me off guard okay I mean it
was it was more of a s I was going more
more for yeah there you go oh thank you
enjoy your eggs mother
oh thank you so much if I wanted more
eggs where does one acquire them though
uh the the store the local shop has them
oh they do yes they do for for about uh
10 a piece 10 coin yes they're very
they're fairly
cheap you are so lovely thank you so
much you get one too thank you for
looking pretty and dra me out thank you
wait what are your
relationships mom I used to be her
mother uhoh did you Ste my mother past
kids no I have the name blood flame my
exm mother wait what does that mean
you're also my mother yes cuz we are
sisters we are sister you have a second
daughter mother mother
mother mother I'm going
to I'm going to go make potato
salad oh I remember I'll see you at the
arena
[Music]
in I do quite remember when I was when I
was a really
little really little one sister used to
make delicious potato salad sister I
must talk to you yes over here where
where no one may oh okay H
hello hello good hello good
day good you
sister may I trust you I must know yes
yes how open are you
to allowing darkness in your heart
Darkness yes wooden shovel Darkness
sorry I don't know what what just
happened uh um
well uh I guess it depends
yes does does Darkness seem appealing to
you I mean I've always been a hero for
good but if if things need be maybe I
have to borrow the power of Darkness but
for what what why do you
ask I must tell you the truth my sister
but you cannot repeat it do you swear
you won't repeat it I swear
there my memories have returned and I
have discovered that I am the princess
of the stain yes the ones that we fight
yes the ones that we fight I am I am the
and they are
purple and I am purple and I have
discovered that the crown of my head is
not a for the princess of this Kingdom
but in fact for the stain princess yes
um if you see over here
corruption has begun to
spread upon my
kingdom and I must tell you the truth it
was I who has spread the darkness and
Corruption upon this Kingdom no yes
sister it was
me I can't play now I must ask
you would you like to join me on this
path of Darkness I give you an option
because I know your heart is good but if
you ever feel the lure of Darkness I
will be
here yes no
yes you
cannot it is too late for me it's too
late for I no
yes you
cannot it is too late turn to us sister
it's not too late no I must do this for
they have killed my people
I know I I heard that if you eat the
magical Golden Apple you can come back
Golden Apple you
say
yes no I have awakened I'm I know my
purpose now and the purpose is to fight
this
Kingdom no
yes join me
sister Together We Shall We Shall
Darkness em must save the
world if it
be if it be like this and you cannot
return and I N know
Ena of the
bestto will be the one to strike you
down I see I see how it
is yes sister may we meet one day not
day for my job is not done but oh say
but at at the end of ends may we meet at
the end of ends at the end of end we
shall meet yes but I trust that you will
keep my secret for now I shall
because because you are my dear sister I
must be the one to take you down and yes
only you I will see you at the end of
end sister then I shall meet you at the
end of one yes until then until then
sister we shall we shall full work
together I I suppose in front of in
front of everyone else
okay stay stay safe sister wooden
shovel wooden shovel to you
too wood
shovel okay
I knew that her heart was too pure but
too good but she is my sister so
I I wanted to offer her a place at my
side but I knew deep down that sea was
of
light ow ow ow ow ow ow ow but it's okay
for it is a destined battle at the end
of ends my sister and I and I await that
time where one of us may slay the
other I alone
and I accept
it may the
stain yes
this path I am deemed to walk by my
lonesome um okay hold
[Music]
on I need more sign
what was sign
again was it
[Music]
six yes it was six
okay ah the Reaper is
here the tavern owner
[Music]
can I put it on this chest no
yeah let this be a warning to all a
warning indeed
how how do I read it says let this be a
warning to all how are
you yeah it's clearly that's what it
clearly says excuse me it clearly says
let this be a warning to all
yes she's been
impaled ow
huh I need to make more
stains uh I
need
stick and I need more Cherrywood
[Music]
there we
go okay one staying guard here to guard
the
prisoner ow ow ow ow can I not put this
here is it cuz of this is it cuz of
this there we
go and
[Music]
then one stain guard here to
overlook and then
I am not peain what does that
mean ow
ow ow ow ow
ow are you going to find it oh yes the
tournament is it
on you do yes I went behind that tree to
take a look see at the
outfit good day to you
princess yes I feel like every time I do
that I take your nose I follow and then
I put it back I'm behind you oh you're
here I'm here don't worry don't worry
about
it don't we H scam
call scam call scam call oh now you know
that for Mar just keeps calling everyone
yeah oh yes
yes kick butts you
say oh wait I'm going to leave this call
because this is this is
bye we were never my butt is excuse me I
am a princess I hate you I will fight
you I will kill you oh yes I will fight
you and I will kill
you stop I have I have betrayed you what
you going to do about it what you going
to do about
ity no you
won't this is not a tornament to death
is it the the winner shall receive five
potato salads as well as honor oh oh
now yes I add I add to the PO mag
but the first match shall be Jonathan
and Freda and it's best of three oh uh
Jonathan once uh once gathan is here you
guys will have to set it up yourself so
one of you clicks this guy well Pok this
guy and then you you ask him to duel and
then whoever does it first needs to
click Start once the other person's
in okay does it automatically give us
wooden swords yes yes it will it will
even out our inventory so it's just
swords nice yes even ground m is it the
Knight Jonathan or or is it it is you
Jonathan oh me ah you are against
[Laughter]
Freda we can wait until gathan is here
we can wait
a minute or so they said they'll be here
in a moment wait I'm still
lit is us we're fighting yes yeah so
first first match shall be Jonathan and
Frida and then it shall be beu and
Shakira and then it shall be Nina and
and thenie and
myself you do that how you do that it is
a secret no it's not it's not a secret
it is I'm not leaving any secrets are I
will tell you for
coin three
rounds best of three then the winner
goes on to the TR part of the tournament
I
will no you w fight I
will prino do you know how to get up
there I am trying to figure it out right
now back was it the horse oh is the
horse is cheating the horse uh down here
here the one with the horse inside the
put that horse away dang
it but I needed
it you're all cheats of course yes I got
up here fair and square oh oh that's how
you trying to get up there oh I see oh
that's how you got onto the frone no
it's
not hello welcome welcome we waited cuz
your your beloved is going to fight
first against Freda I'm going to kill
your beloved don't die have a
beloved I'm going to kill your ex
beloved I'm going to kill them what do
they mean what do they mean that I
wonder if the night is taken
perhaps play along
oh she does not know me
if play along
uh
sure are you okay you okay bro I am I am
fine are you right let us go huzzah
huzzah
huz huzzah all right so Freda and and
and Jonathan one of you click this guy
first and then the other one also joins
has a development happened in the
relationship huh not you Jonathan
Jonathan first her name is not Jonathan
it is Amelia Watson I believe I go down
as
Jonathan I see I see wait why does it
say dual cancelled 5 minutes have
passed 5 minutes have not
passed
me he is
gatekeeping he G quite literally rules
we cannot use our Revelation correct I
don't think you can you get poofed yes
you get your Revelation is taken away
you not use your Revelation yes I am not
able to it says the arena is currently
in use
try hm that's strange let me try it says
I've joined the red team oh
uh
H it does not let me join the duel for
some
reason are you in a
party I I'm not in a party now I left it
I just banded the party m say we're in a
party
together J J sword J the sword the J
sword J sword
sword J sword user it says I joined uh
it says that I'm sword okay I left I
left the game so somebody here I'll just
I I will go away for a moment and come
back okay sword very J very it seemed it
worked when I when I left my party
though so maybe it is to do with parties
no don't leave where are you
going
no dear J sword
user a c some people are just like some
people have not been educated on how to
use the futuristic keyboard okay do not
bully my jade sword member how dare you
all right again it's she she's wearing a
red hat oh yeah she's wearing a red hat
okay how are you leg
it should say start it didn't work do
cancel cuz the opponent left oh you got
to you got to stay in it and one of you
click Start okay I joined you joined oh
yes it says I've joined the so one of
you say
start yummy red
[Music]
cake yeah I oh it says canell yeah e
it's uh
I press Start okay I'll join one more
time I joined again I
joined all right start the game
yeah fight fight they're fighting fight
huzzah to the death
fight huzzah come closer to
us oh they're fighting
I
want what are they
saying they're poking each
[Music]
other only
one conratulations
congratulations W she disappeared too
disappeared as well
magic there we
go up
okay best of three best of three
mhm here we
go
oh I see how it
is the wi
again again oh they are circling each
other what does the winner win oh they
are backing away she got a
Pok her again Shez not letting her touch
her oh she ran forward and oh fighting
oh oh they got a hit on each other oh
this is intense exchanging blows oh she
hadow anyone's anyone's game
anyone's many
H win she's too powerful she's so
powerful who comes from Amber coin
originally out of this tournament my
head you did you did very well though
head really
hard oh I'm sorry that was not very
Sportsman as I watch the rest of the
[Music]
tournament okay next up is beu and
Shakira oh okay and Shakira Shak let's
go
Shakira Shakira Shakira do this onward
Shakira you
press you click the guy and join the
duel and one of you will have a start I
okay are you
ready uh very ready okay let's
go for Honor for Honor for
Honor but
honor oh princess I am sorry for what I
must do to
you I have this
slain
ouch SEC has beaten me it must totally
be the Ping hello is only natural that
hurts you a princess after all yes I am
I am a princess not a we shall try again
though we shall try round two round two
let's go I shall train you my princess
so you can protect yourself from Evil
oh ways of the fighting excuse me please
well I mean this is a good way to
prepare for get to come as the king
says oh again oh
again oh it
says five minutes have passed since
first particip join try it
again
okay I've joined the blue team begin da
there we go
[Music]
the
pig would have been
embarrassing it is fine can
congratulations
Secura congratulations my
enemy for am
coin do not Li Co not Amber coin this is
all part of my plan I am hiding
let them have their full sense of
security her hips never
lied I do
not okay think who this be your name for
tomorrow so both of you click this one
of you will have a a button behind the
desk to click the they not know my power
level
yes we are starting then you get yummy
oh they are
fighting the fight has
begun I just watch my
sister you are so wonderful yes is my
sister
G KN yes L of bread she seems so
strong KN the Knight has one
I believe in you sister you can do it no
I have been
weak I must eat some meat you have taken
a lot out of
me yes you are a good a good F you're a
good opponent you are also a close game
indeed close game gathan with the de do
we go again yes the best of three onward
onward oh I'll join the again okay oh
yes yes down us here we go where did let
us fight till the end
again there we go
ha
fight go
again
fight let's go The Exchange
[Music]
blows they're tied they are tied now we
tied one more one
more
glorious I do we got to make sure we're
full full HP first though I feel like
that was not a fair fight make
yes delicious anyone's game now it is
anyone's game okay let us go good luck
Knight hold on I'm still not full oh yes
yes
soon surely
okay all right surely surely let us see
who wins let us go let us go to battle
to battle you press the start fight
button
okay you're
forgiven
Focus happening
they are exchanging
blows go go will it be Jonathan or will
it be Nina my sister I lost count
count Orange has one congratulations
Knight thank you well done Gan KN you
are victorious you did your best great
fight to got us in if it was a great
fight you were very close was close
fight I almost I almost fell the future
of Cilan is bright it is bright very
bright right join the
battle mother I believe in you
mother thank you my child I mean I'm not
your
mother good good good luck
mother oh good luck they all she
mothering oh she's mothering
help and the other one is
fing
mother
mother powerful very very
powerful you were
mothering
[Music]
mothering that was a great fight yes
mother we are proud of you mother never
seen any mother daughters I mean you're
both not my daughters
daughters are they they're not my
daughters yes we are siblings oh door
canell yes although we haven't done much
to make her proud
okay it's okay mother will show us how
it's done yes side chick I don't see a
start button do you see a start button
so many side chicks what is a side chick
oh there we go there
are there a chick on your side all
right and thus the second battle begins
yes oh they're keeping their distance
from each other in my head are my
side seems like we have different
understandings no she got a hit
mother oh mother you got to get the hit
in
mother
no mother and father oh is she a father
oh no she is wavering yes
is mothering so hard let's
go oh I don't know who I'm ring
for we're rooting for both mother and
father of course family T how are they
taking so many hits
family a one a Twist a TST
TST oh exciting well done you were
bested this time I was indeed but I
shall happen in the final battle this
time the final the final batt the final
battle notuse this
time I have
joined again I want to see you do it
again oh oh they're drooling once more
ding the sun rises why AR they drooling
they drooling the mothers drool what are
they drooling over
each themselves
mayhaps they're drooling over the
victory that would bring them honor yes
yes the victory who's winning it's so
close but it's so far is this a custody
battle is winning I think
so the pink one the pink one not the
tavern owner is quite strong oh oh oh
wait
[Applause]
she has
won
congratulations power eight eight eight
eight eight she at what does that eight
eight we have been both trained by the
same
Mentor this guy
here well done
call the next ones to fight is Freda and
Shakira
revenge on the traitor the Revenge oh
the traitor of Amber coin this will
prove
everybody fre I'll Target and your
up who it's your turn yes you are up
it's your turn this time I wish to go
back and forth oh yes yes this time you
will and who do I who am I facing now
are you fighting Shakira me your biggest
Shakira
her hips do not lie M her hips does not
lie that's my
honor lie yes I I'm just not going okay
you do it first Shakira do it again
shiraa go in go
in all right I want to spill your blood
does anybody want to play
bets SP do not have any coin with coin I
do not partake in the G
I pr I am beyond that
now I wonder what is wrong with it oh I
oh I
see it should work could you be coinless
I am
it'sing it's
starting Freeda against Shakira
blows win exchanging blows this be
anyone anyone's game
oh see is strong secure her hips indeed
do not lie
restor typical Behavior still two more
rounds what did I hear
the what did I hear typical Amber corn
Behavior it is my honor again again okay
I shall be happy
once
again my hands are bloody I'm ready oh
wait wait wait wait to
eat do you not get like healed back up
before the fight I'm
ready okay all right let's go let's go
one more time and
go are they still so despised mayhaps
they are the Second Battle has commenced
it is hard to get over my
this oh they are exchanging
blows they're exchanging
blows no to the it looks like Shakira's
got a lot of hits
in
wow wow wow Sakira is strong
sheo I say I hit her so many times
[Music]
C you fought valiantly fra you
fought
well I will never ever return to
ambercoin I detest it
so IED I will do everything in my power
to see
amberin give you the corruption does not
even need to go over there they will
destroy themselves from the inside
yes what is the booby PR a what prize a
booby prize a what prize you never heard
that term what Say booby
prize hey what do you mean by that I
went to trade with you the more I see
Miss alar and the more I think that she
may be a
Ally big brain cannot comprehend what
this priz is she too I see booby prize I
may talk to her later yes well I I shall
tiet and have you never heard the term
booby prize booby prize
not it is uh so if you are doing a like
uh a pub quiz whoever is the the last
one gets a booby prize which is
something silly maybe or your lands that
you are from I'm not sure it just comes
to mind whenever I think of a booby
pridee booby Pride aaper Reaper prize
when I am sad I would like to have a
booby prize indeed oh Reaper are you
there well you have to lose to get the
booby prize I would like to give like to
give you a good luck charm mother I am
such a loser May I have a booby prize
please take
it but but I lost I want a booby prize
booby prize as well you want in my heart
you want in my heart no but I I'm such a
loser on my forehead my goodness other
kind of what happened to her I guess I
killed her
surprise you whacked her too much you
whacked her so much leave me
to no no I I
wait give her your booby prize booby
prize what did she receive let me trade
what the queen statue is missing the
booby prize the booby
prize leave her alone she's being worked
on I was just I was just thinking the
queen was missing you are not booby we
the booby prize wear the booby prize put
on the booby prize put on the booby
prize put on the booby prize what is the
boy pre what is the booby prize wait we
see the booby
[Music]
prize
this bur It To The
Ground first I will display the booty
wait can I boot it's booby not booty
hat I cannot display the booty I can the
boot
after she is an Amber coin no I
on I know I know it belongs what a
wondrous booby prize public display of
my my taste my next is gathan against
Calli
oh the tavern owner versus fight look
Jade sword Knight makes Ruan proud I
will do my best but it seems that the
reaper is quite Adept at
fighting I believe in you show her some
empathy show her empathy yes
[Music]
empathy empathy and love fight for the
king Callie fight for the king please
the Jade sword let me fight she wishes
for your wife's hands what
to Jou for your wife's
hand what is
it oh here we go I wonder I have no idea
who to bet
on for
empathy you can do
it oh she's gotten so many got to be
aggressive
oh
oh oh oh hard to tell I I do not know
who is it she's running she's
running you're on or
night them all you got
it goodness goodness is going to for
empathy I believed in you for empathy
one more my heart
up I saw that it was the same Strat you
used against me it was very effective
thank you believe in you just one more
for your wife thank you
[Laughter]
will one
more one you're fo me Princess bio oh Li
you run with the cattle you run with the
Sheep we are the Wolves oh where where
other wolf dang it she sheep now PR I
got poofed back
then oh
not your fault then ow targaryan I may
need to speak with you in later after
this tournament yes okay may I inform
you that is not my name you can call me
whatever you please Hest oh what's is
your name oh Kell's getting some more
blows you can do it Brave J sword Knight
anet Senor okay Miss
anet is G the winner EMP
well done
[Music]
gathan that mouth what mouth why what
were you saying on the battlefield to
tell nothing nothing trash talking she
just showing some empathetic words to
her you know showering her with empathy
you fought
valiantly vant all right the last match
the final match even shall be Shakira
against
gathan Gan I know you're exhausted
but
show True empathy I will do my best
though she is a murderer I will say this
is the Battle of the oranges so if you
shall win I shall my title of tar of the
oranges of the
oranges you will gain a title if I win
you will go to court and face
trial wait that's both just like
bad oh something else well if you win I
will die if you win you will go to
court you not want that I don't know
about this deal that's kind of like you
no so if I die you get my title of the
oranges if you die what do I
get do you have a title I will I will
stab myself oh huh what about something
like she says ARA ARA or some strange
cursed words what is in Aura Aura well
then come up with something may I take
your may I take I I know since you will
be getting the orange title how about
since you have no title to give me I
shall take your last name and make you
my wedded
person you force me to marry you I don't
request you kindly only if I happen to
win this
battle why let it be off onto the
battlefield the Stak on the
battle wait the stakes are
high this shall be a glorious a glorious
battle oh they are all ah they're
off oh they are circling they are doing
a dance they're dancing they are
dancing so aggressive
oh oh
godak is so
strong one so fast Sakira Sakira just
one
round no I'm going to have to be her
wife this
is this is the worst pull yourself back
together P yourself
together I didn't understand what was
happening she's going to make come back
to us G
Don't Panic Don't
Panic listen to your listen to your wife
it's
starting oh my
Goshen to do for you Pearl the pain
ghost it hurts me so the pain ghost and
he threw me in the air threw me to the
ground like that is
crazy they have tied
oh my good there is but one round left
one round
left to heal but take
those I accept this because I will win
the next fight oh the stakes are high
snap it one more fight
left to
battle the other thing to get but then
if Shakira win oh actually no gathan
also gets to bring Shakira to trial at
court but then if Shaquille wins she
gets to marry Gan so yes it has started
oh my goodness the stakes are
high has either traded blows yet I don't
think so why is Shakira not holding a
sword she oh she is not holding a sword
oh there she still she holding a sword
she got it
now oh oh oh oh
oh just not need to marry EMP
EMP there is no
wedding I only want you to to go to
trial trial a trial has happen gathan it
is a trial where will the trial be held
it will be held at the Gallows I suppose
The Gallows how about we have the trial
the day after tomorrow oh can I make a
proposal because I still have many
things to do uh that I want to do before
I go to prison are you getting are you
trying to get out of this are you trying
to get out of this you would not have
such knowledge of me not being available
on the next day so um how about tomorrow
I uh get a few more quests done and then
we have the trial the day after the
morrow how about you finish your quest
and then we have the
trial have a proposal on the day after
theor we shall discuss it on the
bulletin
board anyway you can also get married
and have the tri you can have both
suspicious she will not marry I if
you're going to courts
anyway true but if you're there anyway
way might as well get married no true I
like to
who I'm married to you no cuz you the
court there my belongs to my da departed
wife de departed I
over I knew that your wife left
you her she did but it is the sensitive
spot I am here for you
you in a sensitive spot and remind you
you are now single at this court you can
I will become a nun are you no longer
her PE I will her this bird oh I will
remain all I remember is going to the
Sewer Dungeons and I regain my memories
of a detective being a detective she
forgotten she forgotten she's forgotten
Oh no I got my memories back and I still
remember my
past come here there and I shall give
you your potato salads
bnk on your head will you will you bnk
me then
okay one more do you remember
anything you remember I I'm here I have
rocks here ready ready here here rocks
ready oh but a sliver wait reation I a
diamond
now I I do remember a diamond oh okay
how about you have a revelation
Revelation what is
that it's my pew
pew it is wet I have no Revelation no
it's
not here smell this it might remind
you H butter butter yes there's butter
yes oh oh what about what about what
about
this delicious cheese oh wait this
reminds me oh what about this it seems
so my loved one
loves here egg egg yes we did exchange
eggs at some point I
believe slow and steady the she starting
to remember is she
remembering ah my head is still foggy I
may need to rest and Eve and maybe in
the morning I will remember maybe maybe
I wish for the best I pray for your
return of memories it is very important
but of course ah yes thank you thank you
for your assistance remember
this remember
remember you think she just like
pretended it was coming back and she ran
away honestly yeah that seems to be the
most lik thing that happen wait is she
Amber coin a glorious
symbols the the Pearl oh I think she's
Jade sword ah Jade okay okay good she's
not she's not gross like okay okay okay
all right accept that both thank you so
much for joining in the tournament I
appreciate
it what did you want from me please
follow
me thank you all so much for joining in
the
tournament she thank you mother it was a
glorious glorious
tournament my hat evidence into head
into my
head hello yes freed I have heard of
your hatred towards the
kingdom I have hatred towards many but
yes that is one of the things yes the
kingdom I must tell you the truth of
myself but if I tell you the truth of
myself will you promise not to divulge
it to others yes I
promise I
yes you see after last night a
revelation came to to me that I am
actually not a princess of this Kingdom
I am the princess of the
stain this oh my gosh col purple yes the
purple yes it makes perfect sense I
know hello hello
hey I will see you Heroes on the
tomorrow ohwell on the tomorrow farewell
Pearl I hope your memories May return to
you oh thank you yes maybe if I rest my
head thank
you good day good day good
day was hold on hold on there's still
there's people near
okay
closer as you see corruption has spread
into our lands if you look behind you I
do see yes to this this fake Idol Oh no
no I'm talking about the corruption the
corruption yes oh this this oh yes this
this too yes the corruption I must tell
you this corruption was done by
me I have corrupted the lands because I
am the stained princess and I offer a
hand to you may you join me in this path
of
Darkness I kneel before Thee I take this
solemn oath that I will Aid you in the
destruction of this world or this
Kingdom even
not yes you are now my Dark
Knight let us destroy this
world
together look I've already placed a
victim as a
warning a victim yes oh my
goodness their face has per so much I
have no idea who they are
exactly no one will
know no one will
know well I kind of you tell me I'm
curious hi oh you can go in here I will
break this
gate
blast sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff H
their scent is not familiar to me
me oh watch out watch out the there's
lots of danger in the corruption oh
you're right okay it makes me feel alive
it makes me more eager to inflict pain
onto others yes now do your best to
spread corruption and pain onto others
so that this Kingdom may fall and fire
and Chaos may take the
land okie dokie yay
BL does you know that I am the true hero
and protagonist of this story I will
defeat
her
oh
blast I knew it I could not trust
anyone it is a path I must walk
alone but
last hear she's
Ving I see they are all my
enemies the lots of
them every single D yes wise words
the corruption shall touch the Queen's
foot
yes
yes how how does how does one
[Music]
hide
youi oh yes um hold on
uh okay there we go
perfect let's just put some finishing
touches
here burn the world to the ground yes
everything must burn burn it
all burn it
all
ow dear sister yes how fair is you I
Fair do you
perhaps like uh milkshakes
oh yes but why are you
asking I'm just wondering cuz I I've
been practicing making some milkshakes
and stuff so just just just just
wondering I I do occasionally enjoy the
shake of the milk yes okay well well I
will uh I'll keep that in mind if I make
another batch of nice uh milkshake and
uh and uh hand it over
to you of course ah I would be delighted
sister love you I hope you look forward
to it I will
sister all right fedy well FY well may
we see each other on the battlefield one
day one day one day uh watch out look
behind you H there we
go one day one day wait behind you again
uh okay there we go wooden shovel wooden
shovel L shovel L shovel
[Music]
ow ow ow ow ow yeah h
yes your sister has a grave weakness it
goes by the name of
violet yes maybe I will play that song
during our final
battle to receive an
edge yes
all
right beautiful beautiful
corruption it is all but
lovely
yes let the kingdom spread it dark
entrails
ah
oh I am tired
now I
must you must I must
rest I must rest my we soul but day
has has
been intense lots of Revelations have
happened I
must I must
away
ah good night
sweet
maidens foolish as they
are fairly well
farewell all
right
[Music]
[Laughter]
away now like I
said I will not
be streaming what is this streaming I
must tell you to deliver upon you a
message I will not be streaming tomorrow
but I may log
in and I if if I get my work done I may
log in for a brief to mayhaps appear on
others
perspectives uh but I must get my work
done first
yes may I may I may may have I may log
in but I will not stream tomorrow for I
must
do the duties outside of the kingdom yes
Perhaps Perhaps May yes
mayhaps thank you mindworm
Pebbles darkness in my mind we have
successfully infiltrated the kingdom and
spread a rot a rot across this land yes
I think I may be able to read super chat
again today or contributions to the
kingdom I may be able to read them yes I
shall before I head off to
my
Slumber for Darkness takes its toll in
one's
heart yeah
[Music]
I am not your shortness excuse
me I am sorry about thine connection
issues today I am not aware of what it
was that corrupted
my
stream but hopefully tomorrow or I mean
the next day it was it
will not happen again I was too powerful
it was happening on Fest stream ah at
least at least it was not just
I ah the YouTube I don't know what that
is but the YouTube must must
be they cannot handle the
darkness as I feel like fa is is also an
agent of Darkness seeing how how uh
how how her business is fair
[Music]
yes the blight will conquer all the
rot uh where I need to squint again hold
on
squinting I
squint wait I squinted too hard
[Music]
uh wa
where did
[Music]
I
uh
[Music]
uh okay I think I found it yes okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
no it's the thumbnail the thumbnails are
extremely tiny and the same that is uh
that is a consequence of making
consistent making consistent uh
thumbnails it's quite small and I cannot
see which one is which oh but it's okay
it's okay it's fine I remember have you
considered labeling them there is no
label it's just
the it it is anyway anyway I found it
though I found it I found it I found it
[Music]
your boy Steven thank you for the
contributions to the kingdom randomized
thank you for the contributions to the
kingdom um your highness princess BBU
who is Princess bibu there is no such
thing there is only a princess bizu
please call me by if you are talking to
me please address me by my proper
name if we Pebbles help out with farming
does that mean we are the
Dual
cultivating together the
plants yes but unfortunately not much
farming was done today as my I have a
new purpose now of
spreading M rod
I am no longer a mere farmer I have
discovered my purpose are we a Cults
perhaps
but we must save the
[Music]
stains from from the kingdom the kingdom
is true
evil
[Music]
yes yeah so that's your name now uh
boom thank you for
the red contribution to the
kingdom W that's loud I'm so sorry oh
why was that so loud oh why was that why
okay oh
what what I can't hear you what do we
say anyway
[Music]
um greetings your cuteness I do
apologize for I will be missing the
majority of the broadcast of your
adventures that's okay here please take
this money whatever you do please avoid
anything that deals with the lottery no
I have sworn off gambling Lottery gotcha
all of that all of the mortal mortal
Delight I will have none of that
anymore for I have one purpose now and
it's just to
spread to spread the
corruption yes we you must Liberate the
stain hat oh you have a good point oh
actually that's a good point um
anyway you may get addicted to it be say
safe out there you're cuteness do not
worry I will not be
addicted night spear heads thank you for
the contributions to the kingdom Long
Live Her Majesty the queen of the stains
princess farmer kosak beiju blood flame
Panther Evergreen yes that is I may may
I live
long I will take no more allies no
allies I walk this path
alone me stone think of for the
contributions to the kingdom capino
thank you for the contributions to the
king
Kingdom my wife I yes s Nolla maybe she
would be interested but one last try but
if she denies me would my heart be able
to handle it I do not
know I do not
know was my wife betray
me I don't know maybe it is safer to
walk path by
myself we must trust in the life you
think
so we shall
see um yay thank you for the
contributions to the kingdom Empress
kosek beesu AR rule over the land with
an iron fist that is what I plan to
do Captain anamia thank you for the
contributions to the kingdom cornbread
Thief thank you for the contributions to
the kingdom three cheers for Bibble who
is
bibu I am the stained princess Co
hip hip hi hip hi who is that I do not
know Robert P thank you for
[Music]
the contribution to the
kingdom the the darkness in my head may
have caused a little bit of a throb
within my skull I must I must see to it
that I must get a proper rest tonight it
is fine I will finish the contributions
to the kingdom are indeed of
importance
ah Robert Panda thank you for the
contributions to the
kingdom dearest princess beu on this day
six take thy tribute good luck with this
corruption spreads cuz this pebble is
totally in the god of EP and V later
gang I believe in you princess thank you
may you have good
e a space lion thank you for the
contribution to the kingdom no beu you
are supposed to destroy the stains not
join them it is too late for
I it is too
late what is
happening
uh oh wow
[Music]
huh
weird the Darkness it is it is trying to
overtake me I will
continue ar oh Kami thank you for the
contributions to the
kingdom hell your tuning is COI he
following a line with Adventure so far
makes it as enjoyable no magnetic as
Branch Arc such as Arc GTA 5 and Rush oh
oh oh oh oh oh with each view full of
suspense and surprise looking for to the
anniversary of
grindstone
yes thank you I do as well look forward
to the anniversary of
grindstone was this the Ping perhaps
maybe I have been maybe I have been
hindered by ping this entire time I do
not know
[Music]
cheeseburger thank you for
the contributions to the kingdom Mo
demon thank you for the contributions to
the kingdom my Lord she's only Li with
the princess of darkness and Corruption
kosak bizu I shall be in thine service
forever more good good we need more
loyal soldiers yes for I walk alone in
this path so any loyalty is appreci
ated night spear had thank you
for the contribution to the kingdom I
forever pledge my loyalty to you queen
of stains princess farmer kosek Beil
blood flame Panther Evergreen yes thank
you thank you for your loyalty as well
rock
rock Yi thank you to the contributions
to the kingdom I plad allegiance to the
corruption your highness kosek be you
take this as funds to raise your army ah
what loyal loyal soldiers I have I
greatly appreciate it black Ace thank
you for the contributions to the kingdom
the path of state is an unpredictable
Journey yes if our princess deems it
necessary I shall walk that path our
princess will guide us to our true
calling she will guide us to the truth
our
Salvation I will save
them I will give them salvation in the
form of death
[Music]
yes nice bear Hadad thank you for our
contributions to the kingdom don't trust
anyone your majesty they will all plot
as shown by your own bloodflame mother
yes even even
freed not owl targaryan even my own
sister I cannot trust anyone but myself
and maybe the voice is in my head we
shall see we shall see I don't know
yet bird thank you for the contribution
to the kingdom what have you done to the
Jeep princess I know of no
Jeep for that you shall be cursed to
never grow taller your shortness I know
no Jeep I know no
sheep I have no bonds that tie me down
[Music]
no what is a Jeep I have no
idea
rock tanaz thank you for the
contributions to the kingdom can't let
my mom know that I'm the harbinger of
Decay yes None Shall know until it is
too late well it is already too late for
them as it has already started but let
them have their hope and their
Joys
yes Ray May Kawaii thank you for the
contribution to the kingdom Mas thaning
for the contribution to the kingdom
please take my apologies your highness
what you did yesterday recall me a
cursed chaotic memory and the chaos
consumed me and let me want you to
embrace it for the Peace of the land
please exal me into the
abyss oh you want to be into yeated into
the abyss do not worry all will be
yeated into the
abyss yes for that is my purpose as
stain
princess so sweaty pokari thank you for
the contribution to the kingdom did you
ever hear the tragedy of dark U but the
cringe no I thought not it's not a story
the heroes would tell you it's a stain
Legend dark UI was a tuny lord of the
edge so cringe and so lame yet he was
quite
yikes
yes it is a legend that we must not
forget
for it has important lessons that we may
learn from
it yeah indeed
quite yay thank you for
the contribution to the kingdom thank
you for the corruption coak be you good
luck with these works that you do at
home thank you please please give me uh
please give me strength in these trying
times I will I will do my best so that I
can get back to you as soon as possible
huh I will have strength
yes I may or may not appear tomorrow it
is we shall see please give me
strength um Umar Rea thank you for the
contribution to the kingdom s p thank
you for the contributions to the
kingdom your peeness this is my
contribution for the kingdom this enjoy
your homework tomorrow also since you
have a new purpose now I guess you don't
care about who's not replaying
anymore
replaying replaying
what what what replaying what do you
mean by
replaying oh replanting oh
replanting I will be on the lookout
maybe I will let the culprits
feel safe for now but I will keep an eye
I will keep an
eye an Ever watchful
eye
yes on the
kingdom replanting yes yes I think I
think replanting was meant to be the
word
um also hopefully
tomorrow since I have the day hopefully
I can finish
my emotes that I was working
on as well so we may be able to use more
reactions yes hopefully
[Music]
hopefully um ear warning AKB thank you
for the contributions to the kingdom
hell I just want to say that
I ow oh that's oh
[Music]
thank
you thank you for the contributions to
the
kingdom wait hold is it is way to turn
it down is there a
[Music]
uh ah ah there we go there we go there
we go there we go
hold on check you
check okay that's not as bad that's not
as bad that's not as
bad hold how on now okay there we go
much better much better much better
okay sorry sorry about that sorry okay
uh
anyway thank you for the
the contribution to the kingdom your
dark highness since you had trouble
saying your enemy's name I will help Lee
as in lick candy feet best as in best
cutest aisle and all as all the Pebbles
love liest
ah Li liest lick Li
best yes ah I see I kind of
like though I kind of like saying it
like
that as
saying a name makes it all the more
powerful so I do not acknowledge the
kingdom
of yes because they are my enemies so I
will not say their name correctly but I
will not give them power
yes can no Han thank you for the
contributions to the
kingdom princess I will follow you no
matter if the kingdom Burns I believe in
the princess till the end long live the
princess good luck tomorrow princess
thank
[Music]
you thank you I
will hopefully be able to seow the seeds
of darkness in the in the guys of
Darkness where no one can observe me yes
are you fan Pebble thank you for
the contributions to the kingdom
[Music]
okay I have finished
my daily duties I must
[Applause]
rest okay anyway um sorry about
[Music]
that for the stains the oppressed the
wicked the darkness I bid you
farewell may we meet on another day it
is time for me to enter my
Slumber
AA be you
later go scatter in the wind my Pebble
brain worms let Darkness approach and
let chaos take the world
a
[Music]
oh