[Music]
for
n
[Music]
the
n
[Music]
in
n
[Music]
the
e
[Music]
oh I was talking to myself k k
what's up hello
Yi hey I was muted oh wait sorry I'm
probably sorry I was a a little bit
quiet maybe
hello can you see me through this thing
this magnifying glass I I almost it's
like a mirage I feel like it is making
me bigger for a moment I think so and
then I look closer and I realize no it's
not making me bigger at all it's a
mirage I throw you up into shreds
you sold me on aage I to you up into
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this
mess hopefully the bags will not be too
[Music]
messy I'm using my my my my ex what's
the word my upgraded 3D face I'm using
it again in case you haven't
noticed when I open my mouth wide then
you notice yeah I've been forced to
because of this asset being in these
sleeves I guess that's one way to force
me to use my default outfit
more
but don't don't don't you don't don't
like don't go by that
now
um before we get like started for real
for real
I wanted to ask you guys do you hear the
PGM and I'll make it a little bit louder
actually and I wanted to yeah okay I
wanted to Yap a little bit before we get
real started I wanted to say first of
all thank you thank you thank you thank
you um which thumnail
here thank you for
supporting H Mirage so far the music
video has been doing quite
well
picture this let's just put this here
still have it from last stream in case
you missed it I shared a lot of
interesting inside knowledge and BTS
about my 3D life that transpired a few
days ago and the creation of the song
and the music video but
anyway uh I thought of some wonderful
one wonderful rewards so to say uh as
like kind of a reward for Milestones if
we reach them so far uh I've uploaded a
YouTube short of me dancing the chorus
which I think you know uh you can see
very clearly as if you're looking
through this
lens um stuff like you know the
movements uh are more visible there and
if you want to see more of that well
well well well I got you I'm planning to
for every 50 or
100K of views on the music video
releasing something so keep on giving
the music video some views guys once a
day would already be lovely um if not
twice per day uh for example I will
release for
500k which we're not so far off anymore
and for 500k I'll upload a dance shot
version so from beginning to end of the
full
choreography and actually I can even
already show you a preview of
the uh video just a
[Music]
screenshot and I think it's really worth
it because first of all I love I love
watching these in uh like K-pop for
K-pop songs I love watching these
because it's a really nice look at the
Coro it's it's really interesting
M oh yeah a capella I'll also upload
that I suppose I forgot about that but
yeah I should upload that huh maybe uh
at 600k or so um but let me show you
here's a little little preview of what
you could get a clear Reve of the dance
it's really nice dance video in dance
studio yeah so I'll upload that for 500k
and then I was thinking for 1
million 1 million when we reach that
I'll be doing a
3D special at home stream in the Mirage
outfit
oo maybe if you watch the previous
stream uh that I where I talked about
Mirage and so on uh you would be aware
that there were like some issues with
like 3D model creation because there
were two people working on it but not at
the same time first there was one person
Sian working on it and then uh chainon
kind of took over and started from
scratch again uh but San Sian actually
finished the model he was working on and
it's kind of like made to be used uh at
home for an at home
stream while the chain Ton video that
was used uh model that was used in the
music video is not really made for that
uh there's like you know the H the
shaders and everything of the outfit uh
don't show up the same way in my at home
3D application if you know what I mean
so Sion actually finished his model and
it looks so good and it's like made to
be used you know with those programs
that I'm using so it's so pretty do you
want to see like just a little preview
of what the the fabric looks so pretty
I'm going to
die I and it's like it
changes depending on you know let me
show you
[Music]
oh maybe should I show it I don't know
I'm too like I spoiler everything why
why am I like this but okay I'll show
you this
the
here
safe
spoiler no no it's okay I SP it's my
it's my my
decision here
do you see that like wow is it real or
is it a
mirage AOA
[Music]
stop but do you know what that mean like
it's this like um like a what do you
call this kind of like coloring I I was
trying to describe it before but
pearlescent yeah and then depending on
how I change the lighting in the app it
it changes too it becomes like blue and
so on it's really pretty
yeah so uh basically what I'm saying is
you'll get a lot of cool stuff if you
keep on watching the music video um but
that's not all like the dance video and
a capella and the uh freedy at home
stream is not all I have something
special
planned not just wa solo dance shorts no
collaboration dance shorts with other
members
[Applause]
n yes I've been working on something now
last
night uh I've selected a few
members from all
branches to join me on the dance yeah
I'm cooking I'm cooking at
home yeah was like doing some motion
capture last night at 3:00 a.m. 4:00
a.m. yeah I selected a few you'll see
you'll
see um and those will also go out per
Milestone maybe even for like 50k
Milestones oh I have quite a few cooking
in the in the air fryer right now so you
know what you got to do you know what
you got to do stream Mirage music video
on the
YouTube
yeah the Dona I guess kind of like that
but all you you don't got to donate all
you got to do is watch the music video
it's
free I might make a clear plan like a
graphic and then put it up on Twitter
and then you can work towards
that if you
want m stream Mirage of course also like
Spotify Etc I would appreciate it if you
can it's such a banger I I have it in my
head
too Mir Mir Mir it's in my head is it in
your guys' heads am I in your
head I'm doing my PO well thank
you no 500k is the dance
video 500K a dance video the the full uh
choreography for you to take a look
[Music]
at so uh one more thing I wanted to say
before we get started 7 days to die I
will participate tonight but it's like
3:00 a.m. my time and then goes on until
like probably 7 a.m. my time so um I've
been preparing for that by [\h__\h] up my
sleep schedule well it's been already
[\h__\h] up and I purposefully didn't fix
it uh I was up until 8:00 a.m. last
night um but so basically I was I I I I
might not stream my POV this time this
in the first stream because I don't know
I feel like uh I might not be super
energetic and I don't want to like force
myself to be super energetic we'll see
we'll
see I I don't know and we'll see how
many povs there are and like uh when it
gets closer to the stream if there are
too little then I might put up a POV but
if there are plenty then uh I'll think
about it I'll think about it I still
have time to decide cuz it's in like
7even hours from
now but yeah I might take a nap
honestly yeah but yeah even if I don't
have a POV up I'll be in other povs but
we'll see we'll see we'll
[Music]
see okay okay so today is the comeback
of a special stream project program
whatever that I have been doing for a
while now h H
bags yay yay yay H bags the first Hol
bag stream oh my god when was that like
2 years ago or so I've been doing it
periodically uh whenever I have new bags
a potentially good amount of bags to
show
off um in the past we already featured a
a lot of members from uh all gener all
branches on all
generations now we finally got a good
amount of new M so there has uh been a
lot of new potential
additions no not EAB bags I'm not asking
for bags from fans in the style of H
life no we are looking at bags the
insides most particularly the insides of
bags of Hol life members themselves what
do they like to carry around in their
everyday life whenever they go outside
if they ever go outside that is well
well
well it's a bag but not an e a
bag the secrets will be exposed and
revealed maybe some of them are carrying
something
scandalous no I actually I don't think
so but
um I'm looking for
Expressions scandalous
no probably not um and some might be
like super minimalistic uh there's
always like someone super minimalistic
let me tell you we have some minimalists
once again it's quite
interesting but yeah who should we start
while we're looking at it it will be
blurred and I will then like start to
unblur little things and we will look at
it and discuss who it might belong to
so feel free to discuss
together let's start some of these feel
like a little bit
obvious uh well okay let's start with
this one
maybe okay here we
go well now that is that is a good
amount a decent amount of it
wait let me move
this let me move this window to my main
screen oh now it became
like all eyes on the TV screen
please blur yeah of course it's blurred
that is on
[Music]
purpose this really looks a lot like
yours like mine I mean you don't really
see much yet but I guess so okay let me
I don't want to reveal like look at the
most obvious revealing items just yet so
on the side let me have a let me have a
a picture of it unblurred
open just so that I know what to reveal
first okay H yeah okay okay okay let's
see uh there will be like
uh Japanese members too I think no ID
because from ID I I pretty much you know
they haven't gotten a new gen since the
last time I did this so you know not
really I don't know who maybe there are
still some members who didn't
participate but I
yeah all right all right all right all
right are you ready to take a look
o that doesn't mean it's fauna fauna has
pre viously participated already okay we
got
some lip items this looks like a lip
balm and a
lip gloss
maybe and another like some kind of
makeup next to it maybe
mascara but yeah this is a
moisturizing lip balm 100% natural
origin oh yeah with bwax responsibly s
for be wax I see and then I can't read
the flower
something oh you thinking of RA Nissa M
fa Faun already participated you got to
think who who hasn't participated yet
well it's been a long time since the
last stream if you missed it you guys
should watch The Archives this is really
fun if you guessing along yeah so this
could be anyone this is you know just
some girly stuff
uh you know just um
yeah uh there's some writing there but I
I want to try to avoid the writing still
if I can so because maybe you can guess
by the uh the handwriting hopefully
not one more item let's reveal this
[Music]
part what is
this you guys I don't know it says USA
um so maybe this is a brand and that you
guys know tide yeah like the logo looks
a little bit familiar what the [\h__\h]
isn't tide like um for like dishwashers
or or washing machines or like I feel
like I've seen that logo on something
else I I said a stain remover for like
clothes I so normally that there's
probably washing machine like laundry
detergents with that right yeah yeah oh
handy I need something like this does it
work I need to ask this person if it
works I don't know anybody who ever
brings this but now that I know that
this person carries this
around I'll keep this in mind if I ever
need it oh hi narissa they work guys
literal fact that narissa commented kind
of means that this isn't hers right cuz
she wouldn't she
wouldn't surely she wouldn't comment on
it when it's her
bag we'll see you you never know you
never
know oh interesting that's cute I want
to try it out I I'll purposefully you
know stain myself and then uh try to get
it get rid of it with
that totally not nissa's back
no okay we can maybe reveal this one
next
is wow
wow but I mean this could give
away oopsie this could give away that
this isn't this an iPhone
cable oh yeah no thank god let's go to
this person M mwah you know my hate for
airpods I prefer these kind of cheap
wireless earphones when like when I'm on
the road like I bring nowadays I always
bring my what are they called again
those like noise cancelling head
headphones that I have I like to bring
those recently cuz those are Wireless
but at least they don't fall out of my
ears the worst combination for me is
wireless and
Tiny when they're like they never hold
in my
ears
yeahum not Bose not Bose what am I call
you know them there's so many whole
alive especially on the Ian side so many
members who have
those uh the Sony yeah the Sony ones
somehow the surface is so smooth I
really like
it and I I used a I I bring them along a
lot because like on the airplane the
noise cancelling is really nice but yeah
this person seems to be this kind of
person which I find this very um in
German we say sysh but in English
sympathetic is kind of different what's
the right word I like this person is
what I'm saying like this gives me a
good
vibe relatable yeah yeah yeah yeah
relatable I guess yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah but the thing is I always also like
H I could say as an argument I don't use
those Wireless ones because I always
lose them but I lose these ones as well
even more
so I don't I never I always forget where
where I put
them do you guys have the same
problem but I I like her for using
these so yeah that's just some cables
and wires and I guess I guess the the
the the black cable is like a iPhone
loading cable I assume right oh here I
found another item that doesn't quite
give too much yet here
pens wow I don't I like these I like
these they they look
fine um yeah just some random
pens why not why not responsible yeah
always ready to write something down
maybe this person likes to draw who
knows H I think this
one it's just the gcha ball that doesn't
give away too
much uh anybody could be having some
gacha ball in their bag and like likes
to use
gacha you guys are all
say I see I
see okay now we're getting into a
territory that
is going to be revealing more of their
hobbies and their fandoms that are into
so let's start with this one it's a
little bit less obvious because
everybody loves Pokmon right
let's just show the font don't look at
the font too much you'll think too much
about who writes like
this cute that is a pocket mirror
[Music]
apparently a pocket mirror cute it looks
cute I guess the top is transparent or
is it it's cute and then we have another
Pokemon item right here
it's a card holder
with wait that Dragon thingy isn't that
like beo was giving those out to
everyone
so somebody must have taken that and
attached that to their to their item I
also got one
yeah or is it bi boo m it's either some
bi gave it to everybody so it could be
biu or it could be anybody who received
one from biu which is
everybody but this card holder is cute
why does it say pocket
piece it's a card holder why does it say
that have you guys seen uh Pokemon
released like a Al alarm clock or like
the announcement that they're releasing
an alarm clock I watch the video I'm
like it's so funny gimmick but
okay I have a feeling my manager JMA
will get it cuz she's like she gets
everything that's related to Pokemon and
she's so into Pokemon sleep and
everything man yeah what do you think
about alarmo guys you're going to get
yourself an alarm clock that wakes you
up with Pokemon sounds and other uh
Nintendo related sounds until you wake
up because it can sense your movement
and if you don't get up it'll be really
which is I guess on purpose I wonder if
you can't forcefully then just turn it
off because normally if something gets
really on your nerves and you just want
to sleep you just turn it
off then if you really want this to be
efficient you should make it forcefully
so that it won't turn
[Music]
off well well well
back well the next uh items will
certainly
reveal I don't have any Escape
anymore the last items man all right
let's let's just H let's just get it
over with a cloth that this person will
never
use
and
stop Devil May Cry M yeah yeah
well thanks people thanks for that
[Music]
I had to blur that one so
hard B this is people this is people's
bad yay pouches for stuff I see I see
those are
cute oh from the Capcom Cafe I see it's
nice like in Japan there's so many cool
like collaborations you can get so much
merch of your beloved things so she
probably got it like from a from the
actual Cafe I
guess yeah that's B boo op him literally
a selfie of
her can't believe she she reveals that
like
this got is for shielding oh yeah right
that's right got a gift for shielding
holding until I see her you hear that
shielding
[Music]
W who who what's going on am
sh let's
go that's the first one oh thank you
what oh golly oh go h no okay no I I'll
stop I I won't even attempt
[Music]
it she living inside my Throne oh my God
help me help me no oh don't help me
don't help me I like
it okay all right all right thank you so
much for your submission people actually
is so funny like normally I give people
like this uh request hey can you send me
a picture and then it will take like one
or two weeks and I have to remind them
often bio literally 2 seconds after I
requested her to send me something for
the first time 2 seconds after she sends
me this picture it's like she was born
ready
thank you bi really appreciate
it okay all right let's move on to the
next one uh let's do perhaps
uh this
one
H oh let me pull up a picture for myself
as a reference
[Music]
all right
okay I think
generally this doesn't give
away too much overall these items that's
a these are like items like there's a
lot of cute mascots here too but those
are very popular mascots that a lot of
people like so all right here we go
where do we
start all right let's start
here it's an air tag so this person
likes apple stuff maybe or just air tags
in
[Music]
general I see I see air tags air tags
are useful maybe this person you loses a
lot of things and needs needs this not
crony why because she hates apple or
what or because she lost her passport is
that what you're
saying because she loses
things oh cuz CR ah do these only work
with iPhones I thought they use uh
without I they I thought they work
without iPhones
too she's a pixel
user yeah I'm almost an Android
person yeah but we do we do have iPhones
for work so everybody in Fe everybody in
whole life is an iPhone user but uh
privately it's a different
story they do work with and but they
work best with Ione I see
oh I see I I do think they they seem
pretty useful man but oh well I don't
really lose that much stuff I lose
myself but yeah here we have chicawa
Pand it's cute
cute so I like people who carry around
Band-Aids they're they're so ready
they're so ready to get
[Music]
hurt ah he's a cute right so previously
that wasn't nervous back you maybe you
can tell if she gets completely quiet
that's her back
then who knows who
knows oh oh I like this I I use that one
all the time Rola do you guys know do
you guys have
Rola these crough drops those are like
basically my favorite crough drops in
like outside of Japan or even I like to
use them even in Japan honestly
especially this yellow one the what's it
what is it like herbs and honey or
something like
that I like this one in
particular
yeah there yummy actually and they
really help so big recommend and
then let's look at um here some makeup
ooh I got to do girls talk to now that I
revived H bags I got to revive girls
talk
too we have yeah some lip stuff M lip
lipstick lip gloss lip tint who knows
the right one looks no it's a BAL blam a
glasting glass in
glasting I know lasting but I don't know
glasting is that a word or is that
really what that
[Music]
says glass
GL help me out English-speaking
people herb herb herb herb herb herb
herb herb bbbbb herb glossing gloss but
then it would be double s this doesn't
look like double s maybe they made up
some fancy word you know to appeal to
the
Zoomers oh maybe it's the brand huh all
right all right here we have what is
this cute clip what the hell I know a
couple of whole life members who like to
use Clips like this like any kind of
clip claw in their hair um but this one
is so cute what the hell it's
dorky cute
M I feel like this means that this
person likes dogs maybe more so than
cats might
be uh a dog person don't you
think
yeah interesting oh wait I got some DMS
maybe somebody no I thought somebody
delivered another picture cuz in reality
I'm missing one picture but we'll see
maybe this this person will deliver
during my
stream oh interesting uh there
is I almost missed this coin there's a
10 Yen
[Music]
coin must be just you know randomly in
the bag
or or
[Music]
somewh okay okay okay and we have air
pogs okay
okay I'm thinking I'm thinking
Zumer I I don't know why I reveal I
shouldn't have revealed that because I'm
thinking
[Laughter]
zomer a cute little clip oh another hair
accessory very cute this this one what
is that I don't know that mascot
but
H wait when this is just blurred it
almost looks like Ra's little chatini
but but it is uh what's this one called
again not cinnamon roll or is it
cinnamon roll I'm I'm not too well
versed in these I
forgot
um is it cinnamon roll oh it is cinnamon
roll okay okay okay a lot of girls in
all I like cinnamon roll this is not the
only cinnamon roll that I have in the
bags today I think I'm pretty sure
there's other cinnamon rolls yeah
cinnamon roll is
everywhere crazy
I should choose like a favorite mascot
too and and carry it around but okay but
then here we have a
microfiber uh thing and a mirror that
mirror is chawa so this person seems to
be torn between honestly all kinds of
mascots but mostly chikawa and cinnamon
roll I
think cute am miror H this girl is like
surprisingly girl
H we have a chica
pouch cute this this looks like it's
been used for a while
now no but now the last two items I feel
like maybe like what is this looks a
little bit like arcanites to me but it's
probably not it's a charging block
though charging block for your phone or
what that's kind of
huge what is this what is this is this
aret or is this um
gin ah gin gin yeah it kind of looked a
little bit familiar these
[Music]
characters okay okay
okay well not
Roblox thank
[Music]
God that's geky ship that's geky ship is
it known to be her
ship I see oh that's this that's bad
that's bad you guys know you guys I mean
I thought this was the most
revealing because this
is this is maple
story
oops oh my God these buttons are making
things
[Music]
disappear ah
ah yeah um it's
Sky
surprise not pictured car keys and phone
the maple story keychain
cute yeah the charging block and the
maple story stuff I guess it's very
revealing but also stuff like just like
um giving it a yellow outline
giggy giggy why you like the moment I
showed it and it had yellow outlines I
think in the beginning you guys were
already saying yellow outline GGY GGY
GGY GGY GGY GGY
H gy why why do you have to give it the
yellow outline it's cute though it makes
it cute I like it I like the sense of
styl like graphic design might be her
passion you can really tell by her use
of Comic
Sans she has such a sense for
comic comic sense get
it I
don't confirmed driver oh right somehow
car keys to me I auto corrected it to
just like house keys but car
keys oh yeah right I mean I mean she's
been driving taxis
right so wait she actually does Drive
huh wait I feel like I knew this I feel
like I knew this already cuz yeah I
think I already asked her to drive me
around oh Naro thank you gy for
participating very nice very very nice
insides of your bag I feel like I've
learned so much about you
already all right let's go to the next
[Music]
one
wow this doesn't look as
like uh like how to say like
cutesy doesn't look very cute
[Music]
uh you guys think it's so obvious huh
well can you just pretend it's not for
the sake of the stream
please
please let's
begin
well it's interesting how something
so simple like you would think like for
example you know
the ones who had like stuff that reveals
their interests by brand and and
characters and so on is so easy but then
there's someone who is so simple and
supposedly this shouldn't reveal
anything
but apparently that reveals it
all so we have a little a little uh yeah
um Note book with a nice mature looking
pen you can basically already tell even
though I blurred it quite well it's uh
glasses tinted
glasses even the top ones look kind of
tinted don't
they a little bit tinted to me both
round shaped she likes round shaped
glasses M instead of like a square
interesting I feel like maybe we'll see
that in fan art then after the
stream and we have a very simple fan
paper fan simple but oh the wood on that
the wood on that looks high
quality
ooh not not too cheap perhaps I don't
know but it looks the paper looks very
strong too
M please hold your horses chat here we
have what is it it looks like it could
be a switch case but uh cuz it looks too
big for a glasses
case but some kind of some kind of
container 3DS
case ah is it the freed is is the 3DS
this
big whiskey case pen bag I honestly yeah
it doesn't it can be anything uh here
is I think a wallet it looks like a
wallet to
me can't read the text on it it just
says the brand I think but I even I
can't read
it it's hard to read but yeah the left
top left is probably a wallet then we
have a book and I've inquired about this
book I've inquired what this book is
because she told me she lost the cover
so this is the no cover version
[Music]
um she
says so okay let me just say it's a
Japanese uh
participant uh yeah it's
some it's it's some GMA select is the
company name of this book and the title
in case you're C curious here I I'll put
it in the
chat
uh this is apparently the
title and then uh we have a Jill Stewart
um handkerchief do you guys have Jill do
you guys know Jill Stewart outside of
Japan is that the
um I'm forgetting is this a non is it is
this a worldwide popular
brand it's never heard of it it's very
very well known in Japan at
least could be
Anya yeah well okay uh people should
know that didn't Lov pom pin and pom pin
was already standing out with all the
blur the pom pin is the one one thing
that's not like mature and cutesy about
this but let me tell you ladin ladin is
so dorky and like cutesy and energetic
and she kind of you know she has a very
very childlike innocent side to her um
so I find this
incredibly fascinating how
she
just combines these two personalities
these these two characteristics of like
a very mature simplistic
minimalistic uh and then but then she's
like so you know yeah it's ladden it's
ladden very very unique I must say the
Gap is so real
[Music]
oh yeah I'm sure it's fine don't worry
about it I'll risk it for the
biscuit has been fine in the past two to
show
[Music]
these it's LED yeah maybe if we would
have done this um like right around her
debut maybe there would still be
cigarettes in here
which I so far we've never seen
cigarettes in anybody's bag right
boring does really nobody
smoke is it like I legitimately I've
never smoked in my whole life and I
think it's great if people don't smoke
especially in a job where your voice is
so important but does legitimately
nobody
smoke there's a lot of drinkers but no
SM smokers which is good yeah it's good
hello hello
hello so many cute girls in my chat wow
you can always start well no I really
shouldn't
start lad Laden you lost one thing that
could have been so unique to you that
could have made a lot of people feel
like oh she's so relatable cuz she smks
why does she see smoking but thought she
was like the one life member I could
relate
to was the
Vodka you're already smoking W
oh thank you don't don't encourage her
don't smor don't smor sming is not good
for
you okay well that was uh our first
Japan submission for the day it seems
let's look into the next one perhaps
shall
[Music]
we next
bag let me throw another one on
there who does this bag belong to me
let's take a look oh God that's that's
really blurry that's really is are my
eyes okay I can't see
[\h__\h] you guys are guessing louder for
everything okay here we
go um uh uh uh tooth the string for the
tooth uh [\h__\h] I forgot the
word what's the the tooth string called
again uh floss floss floss that's a
dance move
though because you dance as if you were
flossing your teeth but you're flossing
your hips I
guess yes tooth strings let's just call
it too
strings okay
somebody somebody's
carrying some very hygienic things
around because perhaps although I mean I
guess those other things are not
necessarily hygienic but this
one wow do you guys even know like why
somebody would carry oil absorbing
sheets with
them if you have a very oily face then
this might help
you yeah no it's not to remove makeup
it's um you Pat it slightly on your skin
to get the oily effect gone yeah absorb
oil I haven't
haven't really used these in my life but
uh I guess they're really useful Yeah
couple girls that I know use
[Laughter]
[Music]
these okay next one uh moisturizing lip
balm
uh from Vaseline what is is that the
brand wow Rosy lips somebody with Rosy
[Laughter]
lips I hate you guys why can't you make
this this is why we can't have fun this
is why we can't have nice
be stop pointing out the obious guys
please see she wrote something so surely
this is not her
bag oh
and this is even one of the bags that
are less obvious
honestly here compact Cur oh
cute I didn't know they made these I
only know like the typical
curlers which are so like they look so
weird they look like some kind of
torture device honestly like something
that's supposed to pull out your
fingernails or something I don't know
yeah this one's cute you guys understand
what like the way this looks it's
confusing this is not what they normally
look like they're for your
lashes but I don't know how this unfolds
like
literally how does this
unfold the floss game oh really
really interesting I guess she may have
I mean if you watch these girls' streams
a lot if there's any girl who stream you
watch a lot then surely there's
something like she would talk about like
oh yes I I I use this every day like you
know you know like oil absorbing sheets
Sur some girls who use those talk about
it
yeah so okay what's next uh here this
scrunchie ah I know
[Music]
this I I I know what a scrunchie
[Laughter]
is I no I was just saying I know what a
scrunchie is do you guys know what a
scrunchie is do you even know what a
scrunchie is although it's not much of a
is this even a scrunchie because it's so
thin I thought scrunchies were thicker
but I guess it's a scrunchie because it
looks so scrunched
up H yeah this person has hair
mhm oh interesting man I I have no idea
who this belongs
to I don't know who any of these belong
to of course
hair claw clip claw clip claw clip claw
clip claw clip alert remember G's
clip this one is more
demure not saying that giggy's dog clip
wasn't de it was very cute it was so
cute but this one's deure very mindful
clock clip clock clip clock clip that's
Sur not how you normally call it but I'm
going to call it clock clip that sounds
funny
clock lip clock lip the lips of the
[Music]
clock well well well let's look at
another item that doesn't give away
anything I don't think this gives away
anything it's just a nice you know
umbrella uh for when the sun is too
harsh or when it rains a little bit um
doesn't look familiar to me at all does
not look familiar to me but it's cute it
looks Dem
miror a sun
Sombrero mhm a little small one fits
into that back perfectly or gidy gidy
honestly like really barely looks like
it's uh there's not much space in this
bag saman for tabasa I also have wait is
this like a peach collaboration is this
a Mario collaboration I know they do
collaboration sometimes but this um this
Crown gives me Peach Vibes don't
answer just saying but
um cute I have a Samantha tasa bag
[Music]
[Laughter]
too doesn't it look like Peach's Crown
right it does I think I
wonder and then oh is this also wait
wait this one's oh yeah this is isn't
this the sister brand Sam no it's the
same Samantha tabasa tabasa what does it
say
there is that a
p i can't read it but cute but is that
cute little emblem so
demure this is so girly oh my God like
but not like overwhelmingly in your face
girly it's more the
Mir it's more the Mir isn't it and this
person is so the
[Music]
mirror she got style but she got no
sheets cuz that blanket underneath looks
like there's no top sheet on
it she got style but she got no
[Music]
sheets okay last but not least this
gives away what their personal favorite
mascot is I guess I don't know if that
is well known for this girl is it well
known uh this is
kud I think a bunch of people like kudi
there's not just one person for sure no
but now we have revealed all the items
so reveal
yourself reveal yourself the mirr lady
it is H oh cron crony
no ma'am that's my quilted Comfort
comforter and yes that bagonal RP ah
really nice cute when did you get
that cute a quilted
comp she will not let that stand no but
I I noticed that depending on the
continent people do their beds
differently and it's it's it's a
cultural difference
[Music]
actually like what kind of sheets they
use some I've seen like
one thing one thing that I don't like is
like when uh some places you do this but
um in Austria our sheets will um enclose
the whole blanket and have either a
zipper or buttons but in some countries
I've seen that it's literally just
like
um like okay imagine the
blanket is maybe a relatively thick
blanket or so and underneath it's just
one
sheet so that the blanket doesn't
directly touch you but the sheet doesn't
go around the whole blanket and it's
just the sheet is like a 1 mm thin sheet
but everything moves it's not set in
place so I'm just thinking the whole
time I end up touching the blanket quite
often because it's there's no zipper or
no button there's just this like yeah
top sheet or so I guess and so I find
that relatively unhygienic in
hotels yeah like what's if you don't set
it in
place I'm going to end up while I sleep
and toss and turn I'm going to move this
around and end up touching and being
touched by the by the unwashed maybe
washed once in a in half a year or a
year blanket the raw blanket you know
what I
[Music]
mean it's hard to
explain I'm talking about hotels
specifically how they do it in
hotels it's
[Music]
raw [\h__\h] idiot
sandwich should have brought more
Coca-Cola damn it I ran out it's in the
[Music]
fridge I definitely was them well I
wouldn't I how often though they don't
wash the the main like raw inside like
the the main
blanket every day they don't they don't
they wash the sheets every day but not
the blanket so if I'm touching the
blanket that a stranger touch before you
know it's gross you don't
understand yeah and then in other places
I've noticed um there's no blanket
there's just a sh cheat to cover
yourself with and that's so thin and I I
just don't feel like I'm covered
properly and it's like mostly in in hot
countries I've noticed I think I think I
had that when I stayed
in Brazil was it in Brazil I wonder I
don't remember so well anymore but it
was just a
sheet and I mean I get it cuz it's hot
but also the room is air conditioned
so it's just not comfy if it's just one
sheet like even even an austr like my
mom for example and other people I guess
also who feel hot in the night in the
summer they just use a sheet and in like
really bad situations I would do that
too just because it's unbearing
unbearingly
hot and no summer blanket can ever be
cooling enough it seems so I just use a
sheet in like emergencies but
yeah I don't like that generally
come to Brazil I've been there I just
talked about it I've been there twice
but I know what you mean it's just the
mean Come Again Come Again Come Again
Come to
Brazil come back to Brazil yeah that's
how you got to say it come back to
Brazil I really liked Brazil I mean I've
just been to sou Paulo but I really
liked it come to Mexico honestly I
really want to go to
Mexico I been like more and more looking
into certain cities I want to go
Mexico
Vos
[Music]
Amigos okay let's look at the next bag M
which one shall it be let's let's pick a
funny
one let me just double check if I
blurred it I think I did yeah okay
[Music]
sometimes you saw how dad's bag was
pretty
simplistic
[Music]
well some girls don't give me much to
work with but honestly that's fine um
because that's also funny that's also
unique
Nissa so this is obviously not nissa's
bag
um apparently this person carries two
things with them and it doesn't even
seem to be a wallet this one will be
short we have a I think lip
balm it looks familiar I think it's a
lip balm right I don't even use lip balm
my I feel like my my lips get more
[\h__\h] up if you use a lip if I use a
lip balm but okay lip balm user
everybody's a lip balm user and
then a power
bank these power that's a that's a
powerful power bank anchor power banks
are very powerful yeah this person puts
a lot of value on a powerful power
[Music]
bank and that's really everything there
is the other thing is just the bag I
guess which is a Fela bag kind of sporty
very sporty
well
so
um there's no wallet there's no okay see
probably she would be carrying keys and
the phone around but I understand why
you might not want to show that that's
okay although I would have liked to see
the keychains are there any keychains H
it's a fanny pack but no I'm sure she
doesn't wear it like on her like crotch
right probably she carries the like how
people carry it nowadays over the
chest like cross body
[Music]
yeah okay uh I got some interesting
suggestions let me tell you it is
quason yeah quason one of one you know
somebody not a new member but somebody
who didn't participate uh before and I
um I
I pursuaded her to
participate I love crony but this is so
funny it just reminds me of like Amed
submission back in the
day or like who else was funny like kind
of similar I think cobal horse though
was also
similar is this really all you carry
around Quon I need to pay attention next
time I meet her if that's really
everything I I do feel like she didn't
carry around much last time I met her
but was it really this
[Music]
little all her stuff is on her phone
yeah maybe even her money like I also
don't care I I try to just um because my
bags are also so small I try to not
carry around my purse in my wallet
anymore these days and just pay with my
cart and stick the cart somewhere into
the bag to save
space yeah but but I don't know I still
have purses wallets I mean I don't
know she has a wallet phone case ah I
see I see I see well I don't see because
it's not on the
picture it's fine that's funny she would
car more but she lost her passport Yeah
well
yeah honestly yeah passport I feel like
nowadays it's realistic for me to if I
were to participate again I don't think
I had it in my first submission but
would probably include my passport
because I do carry around my passport a
lot especially when I'm in Japan cuz you
have to in FY you have to but I'm always
scared of losing it bro but yeah usually
I carry it with
[Music]
me but
yeah yeah you're supposed to yeah you
kind of should and passport also is the
only thing I have for um identification
so even in Austria when I need to go
somewhere where they might need an ID I
bring my passport to my passport is cool
though it's got all kinds of cool stuff
in it so many stamps
yeah she doesn't need yeah like makeup
eh I'm surprised honestly like Quon does
wear makeup but I guess honestly just
like me I don't bring the makeup with me
now I need to check if she really
doesn't bring makeup with her when she
goes somewhere I'll be I'll be
confirming next time I meet her if this
is accurate I'll confirm all right yeah
cuz she's perfect perfect yeah that's
true I she doesn't need to carry makeup
with her no need to put too much stuff
into this
[Music]
bag yeah to take one look at her and you
know looks like a gym bag I don't think
it's a gym bag it's too tiny look at the
look at the proportions of the lip balm
versus the bag if this if the dimensions
were differently uh different then
surely this could be a gym
bag h
where where is she going to put her
workout clothes
eh maybe she just goes there in workout
clothes I would I would
honestly all right next bag next
bag which one should we do next ah let's
let's do
uh let's do this
one a
cute aesthetically
[Music]
[Laughter]
pleasing
cute all right here we
[Music]
go let's go let's start with which item
should I show
first here okay
it's a
n hand cream how do you guys say that in
English I'm pretty sure the real
pronunciation is
n she has skin wait then can't be a
vtuber
right nvea hand cream
it's like everything's blue right so
does this person choose NAA because they
like NAA or did they just choose it
because they like blue and thought Oh
this will match with my overall
[Music]
aesthetic mayia chose
them like some people I guess when
they're very into Aesthetics they will
go for whatever like I love when people
make their whole like work PC setup at
home just one or two particular colors
it's so aesthetic I'm kind of I I want
to do that but it's very difficult you
need a lot of specific things for
that or maybe it was on sale yeah but
then I guess it was a coincidence that
it fits so well
huh oh wait this picture is the
one let me
actually
quickly place this cuz it has some
something censored that I don't think we
need censored and I have a non-censored
version
[Music]
too hey I love this circus music I feel
like I'm in the
circus
okay uh yeah wait we're back to being
blurred God this is so blurred where am
I here I've revealed
[Music]
this uh the hand cream okay now let's
look at um let's look at this
one it is it looks like a ah it's a
makeup
pouch in the shape of a round dog it's a
dog it's a dog it says like in the other
picture that has the writing in it it
says dog
cute cute it's very small doesn't fit
too much makeup I would say but you
don't need too much when you're running
around let's
see what next where is this where are we
here
okay a blue hair clip so much
blue one single blue hair clip okay very
useful when maybe your bangs are in the
way or so here we have a
blue notebook to write down somebody who
needs to write down things to remember
them or so somebody who's very diligent
maybe oh did the Stream
die are we
[Music]
back I'm
back okay that was weird I was saying
okay this must be somebody who needs to
write down things to not forget them or
somebody who's very diligent or so
welcome back welcome back and then we
have oh a little fan oh yeah it it it do
be hot uh actually not so much anymore
but oh andon c cute what are
these what are H oh they're handmade
apparently by the way little figurines I
don't know what what they would be
besides figurines maybe they have some
use but a cute little fan too and then
we have another fluffy thing there's so
many fluffy things
here
cute uh it says that this one is
handmade I'm not sure what what it is
maybe it's just a plushy maybe it
doesn't have any particular
use fluffy and
blue and we have some
Japanese uh fruit candies
M I know some people who strain their
throat a lot but honestly I think a lot
of Us carry froat candies
around but well
I see where you're going with this guys
and I'm glad you're going
there but
argument this is the
argument this and now everybody will
change
probably CU I am not aware or I maybe
May should doday I what
oh glasses are very versatile sure sure
sure sure sure I am honestly so glad you
guys are very confused
now I love it I love to see this chaos
more please now I will show you the
version that has the the little the
little decorations and notes to it t ik
note reglass oo oo means matching it was
Al it's so cute what the hell this is so
like
aesthetic why are you guys making it so
obvious with your colors
though but yeah I'm I'm thinking you
know there might be some sketching going
on in that note as well but yeah um dog
I I love that the blue with the dog and
the fluffy was pointing you towards
fuaa I was so relieved to see you guys
wrong wrong wrong
[Music]
wrong my colors are obvious Al so cute
your colors no no not your colors but I
mean like um giggy with the yellow
outlines and there's some others that
are that's
feel you
know uh yeah no no there's no obvious
color
no don't think too much about what I
said but this this is kind of obvious
handmade yeah handmade like I need to
look at this closer I want a 3D view an
all all directions view of this little
plushy what is it is cute it's so
fluffy yeah this cute you could really
think this might be Fu but fua wears
glasses I don't know I don't know about
that maybe she does and I just don't
know maybe she has bad
eyesight but no it's Alon from
rosu
yay now let's move on to
the next
bag uh let's go this next submission is
um drawn I gave the uh girls the option
to either draw them or put like a weird
filter on it that makes it look drawn or
to just send me a normal picture but
some of them drew it or so or decorated
it and so on so next one is
drawn cute I already can tell it's
cute all right all right let me pull
this one up on my side so I can see what
is
where here we go
where do we start let's start with some
hair
ties just some simple these look like
the tiny hair ties to me like not the
typical big one but tiny ones to make
tiny tiny braids for example in your
hair or sever roll ponytails or so like
twin Tails or
so cute this could be quite cute then we
have oh another lip balm user I see lip
balm is very popular these days
H So Many Items yeah this is a lot this
this girl carries around a lot of things
it seems might get kind of chaotic
inside of the bag um what should we do
next here oh my Arch Enemy my Nemesis
earbuds wow I see okay ear buts they're
pink or like Ros
pretty
cute and then we have a hand sanitizer
mhm I like to carry one around now too
because am it I may actually I told you
that she was like gifting a lot of
people things uh but one thing I didn't
mention last time we met she gifted a
couple of people this like really cute
hand sanitizer that seems to be
weirdly weirdly popular because it looks
like the design is
interesting uh I don't know how to
describe
it but it's popular and she gifted me
one it's pink and it's a hand sanitizer
but it smells really nice and it also
hydrates your hands and the design is
interesting I should give you guys a a
picture so you know what I mean
Callie mentioned it did she yeah I'm
give me a bunch of St she she gave me a
frog candle that I have standing around
now and I'm too scared to burn it
because I have a feeling if I burn the
Frog candle that means that froggy
Wabble will be revived and kill me um so
I better be
careful all right next we have a uh a
brush uh mirror that can be folded away
I know these these are really handy cuz
they they're really small and the brush
kind of
like inflates and deflates more or
less guys just pretend you don't
know here we have some tissues
[Music]
mhm see let
see here some chewing gum this person
likes chewing gum I see I don't like
chewing gum because I don't know like
first when there's still flavor that's
okay but once their flavor is gone I
immediately want to get rid of it also I
can't make bubbles I never really
understood how to make bubbles with
chewing gum
so what's the point what's the point if
you can't make bubbles can you make
bubbles person behind this
picture here we have
pens okay pens h ready at all times I
see to write something down but on what
on what are you going to write it down I
don't see any
paper but here's a phone cable okay
little phone cable floating around like
a danger noodle cute a phone is that the
color of your
phone or is it the
case is it is it pink purple is magenta
by default h
I don't know autographs autographs not
with that kind of
pen ah okay here we have some money wow
these look like super chats to
me these look like super chats is this
color um
representing like the color of the money
that is actually used where
this person lives I
wonder to me it just looks like super
chats or Monopoly money imagine someone
just carrying around Monopoly money a
little bit delusional thinking I'll pay
with this I'll be fine I just I don't
have any more normal money but I still
have my Monopoly money when I'm broke I
guess I'll just try with the Monopoly
money it'll be fine for
sure everything will be fine I'm not
broke I have Monopoly
money sounds
sad the cope the absolute cope here we
have a little mini perfume cute I wonder
what the scent is if only I could smell
through the
screen sniffer
sniffer I smell nothing I'm sorry guys
maybe one day I can report to you what
this perfume smells like then we have
some little mini bags a bag in a bag can
we get a hollow bag review of the mini
bag what's in the mini bag but no I
asked about this because I figured maybe
it's for like dog poop when you're on a
walk well well well the person said it's
for many things it is very versatile
is very versatile but that might be one
of the things
yes um yeah it can be a dog poop bag it
can be but it can also be other
things no but they're really mini
they're not shopping bags don't I mean
the size doesn't look like a shopping
bag bag oh yeah we liptick yeah o o girl
girl M what kind of brand tell me tell
me more about it and a random cookie or
shall we call
it
biscuit is this
um is this is this way of speaking a
[Music]
giveaway you know having the writing on
these is really cute but I need to tell
the girls in the future to not write
anything
down cuz first of all the handw WR and
also the usage of words can be revealing
well then let's continue to pretend we
don't know who this belongs to uh a
travel charm interesting I've seen like
Japanese travel charms before but the
this looks like a rose to
me I need to investigate what what part
of that is a travel charm
good luck charm no I guess anything can
be that if you want it to be maybe maybe
if someone gifts it to you it's like
this is for you to be safe in your
travels and then you see it like that I
guess I don't know H and what is
this is this does this bag belong to a
witch who believes in Witchcraft and
crystals a
crystal which which
no that's interesting I thought that's
like uh that is one of the most
interesting things about this bag do we
know about this person that she likes
crystals like crystal energy and stuff
like that I've heard of people who are
into
crystals but I have yet to come across
one of these Crystal
[Music]
girls maybe it's maybe she's a witch
and then the purse so the wallet I
suppose oh cute it's a BB must be a h to
member then guys you were wrong all
along you guys keep on saying herb herb
herb herb herb herb herb but this is
obviously a horony member wh H I don't
know a burp a burp
the oh now the name fits even better and
then the bag itself I have a bag like
this exactly like this but I don't use
it all of these things are fitting into
this tiny black bag are you kidding me
this looks like a pretty small one like
I mean surely this is not in the same
proportion um but this type of bag comes
across to me as a pretty small
one are you fitting all of that in there
I feel like if you're looking for
something you have to take out
everything to reach the one thing you're
looking for
well well yes it is the bag
of my
dearest kohai herb not the BB not BB not
BB herb it's herb
yeah some of you guys seem to already
realize from the hand writing and the
way it's drawn but in the past there's
been similar submissions like this the
fauna one I think was pretty similar to
this but fauna already submitted and you
guys were thinking of new members so I
guess you're just doing your math smart
people that reminds me of the dream I
had last night oh God I was taking a
test as if I was still in
[Music]
school 2hour test and I was failing it
really badly oh God what a that's a
really bad nightmare going back to
school and then waking up and then the
nicest realization is waking up from
such a nightmare and then while you're
still half asleep and wondering if that
was a dream or not then realizing like
oh wait I'm fine don't worry I have no
tests coming up I right I'm not a
student I'm not I'm not going to school
anymore ever in my life probably thank
my god oh I'm fine I have no nothing to
learn I don't have to go to school I
don't have to take a test I'm good oh
God thank God I had that realization
while I was waking up from my dream I
felt so good such a
relief realizing you have to go to court
instead well that sounds terrifying but
you're you're you're at least going
there for work and not for being sued
[Music]
yeah the [\h__\h]
PTSD I don't know why I dreamt that so
weird okay next next bag let's
[Music]
go
um
[Music]
H H I don't have that many bags left
anymore
[Music]
I what
YouTube what shut up
Chad shut up
what no how you can't you can't just
remember remember this one you were
thinking of someone completely different
and then it was somebody completely
different
okay so give it give it some time to
cook
please don't jump to conclusions so fast
please I beg
[Music]
you okay let's
begin oh this is relat this is sympatic
I don't think relatable is the right
word after all relatable is not the
right word relatable cuz just because I
say somebody's sympathic doesn't mean
that they're relatable to me it means
more like I like this person because of
what this represents or
so but yeah here we have earphones with
cable let's go
yippee I appreciate that
but they're they're um a nice color too
cute now let's look
[Music]
at it's difficult this one's difficult I
don't know what would be a giveaway I'm
honestly not so sure but I like this
ribbon this ribbon is really
pretty it's a clip probably for the hair
there's some more hair stuff actually
but this ribbon is cute right
wow so
shiny and there's a clock clip clock
clip let's go clock clip clock clip
clock clip clock clip clock clip so many
clock Clips today I like clock Clips but
I never wear them cuz I don't really
understand how to wear them nicely like
the clock clip ladies do how do they do
it explain to me Nissa teach me the ways
of the clock clip there's another
there's another isn't this also a clock
lip I think that's also a clock lip and
that's also a clock
lip she has threee clock this girl likes
clock lips
clps
wow some
earrings
cute I don't have ear
holes I need to get them again and then
I see some candy and one single bobby
pin she has
ears shocking shocking Revelation first
we have skin and now we have ears no
don't ruin my
immersion um let's
see well this is pretty
scrunchy scrunchy cute scrunchy with
like moons on it I like it it's very
fluffy very
fluffy and the little oh cute a good
luck
charm oh it looks like it might be from
somewhere in Asia maybe Japan I don't
know looks like the pattern looks like
that and a little bit of the writing
that I can barely
tell shut up chat shut up
shut up
pretend pretend or this is going to
[Music]
end now we have a lip
balm and some kind of face
mist uh by brands that I don't recognize
but thank God that it's not written in
um some revealing language see it can't
be it can't be CeCe because otherwise
this would be like some German written
on
it think chat
[Music]
think see this also has English on it
the
sunscreen honic acid watery sunel
what what her luronic acid watery sunel
I've never heard of such a thing
H is the way this is designed like
scribbled on and written on so obvious
are you kidding
[Music]
me all right no problem uh we have some
makeup stuff here uh first a perfume
from
Gucci can't believe this I can't believe
this um I say English again English it's
a a aroma therapy roll on wow I know
these kind of things those are
nice some
mascara so this person has lashes do you
think an automaton has lashes
maybe but why would she use
mascara wouldn't her lashes that are
built in just be perfect without
mascara yeah this could be laa because
she smells rich and this is a Gucci
perfume that means it's the
[Music]
OD a one pen well this
pen this pen looks
like like a pen I could get here maybe I
don't
know the my notebook wow that looks
ancient I like the
design but do you see any Germany I I
don't see any German this must be that
bag guys I don't know why but chewing
gum I don't see German here guys I don't
know do
I it's hard to read dris drages how do
you say drages
drages d r a g e e s oh yeah okay maybe
ah [\h__\h] I knew that this might have
German on it oh I guess we say dragy
do we say that in German I don't say
that in German when you say there's so
and so many chewing gums in the chewing
gum box what what you say pieces or
daggies or or drag
D what do you say will the packaging say
[Music]
pieces well this could be my bag for all
you
know this could be my bag okay maybe I'm
anticipating again to bamboozle you but
yeah here's a wallet bag that goes into
backpack and holds phone and wallet
[Music]
stuff it just so happens to be in this
greenish
color and
her backpack just so happens to be in
this color too I don't know if it's
really like
that if it is really like that then wow
she is
also adjusting her
colors to
her uh outer
[Music]
appearance now can you stop knowing it
already from the beginning just pretend
to be like I wonder what this belongs
[Music]
to ah
it wasn't always so obvious when we
still had so many more options but even
now I feel like we had a good amount of
options who we could be
today but now that we're more towards
the end of the bags now we're really
running out of
[Music]
options so now now I guess it's
really obvious it gets really obvious I
have
uh one two three I have I think three
more bags
maybe W whoa my my
eyes are being weird maybe I who I see
like blue in the chat as if as if a
member commented whoa my
eyes it's a
mirage
miru miru
SP on and on and on
[Music]
this stream please
guys okay let's go
[Music]
next all right at least this one doesn't
seem too obvious at least to me
you guys are saying that for every
submission have you
noticed is this just your two
goal I got a
message
um oh
[Music]
sorry I got a little bit
distracted okay let's go let's go let's
go let's begin uh but what does this
what what part of this seems likea to
you it's blurred still what is what is
screaming to you what tell me what is
it the the Pokemon we've had Pokemon
things before today remember bio's
bag Pokemon is everywhere
guys the CH that's the name of this
Pokemon does she like
Chikorita I I didn't even know the
English name of this
Pokemon Chikorita that sounds like a
Spanish
word very few people like cholita wow
okay you didn't have to say it like
that yeah
indivia and
Divia well anyway Let's uh look at this
let's start with oh I don't
know what even is this it's a little
towel and what is
that what what is a is this a hair thing
when you put your hair up and it's like
one of those hair
[Music]
sticks I think it's something like yeah
it's a hairstick I've never seen them
shaped like
this
interesting
interesting cute that's the first time I
don't think it's a bookmark I don't
think it's a
bookmark a pizza
color no I don't think it's a bookmark I
think it's a yeah one of those
[Music]
hairsticks oh
God Pizza
C no it's metallic what bookmark looks
like this I've never seen the bookmark
that wouldn't even be a good book
bookmark that wouldn't be efficient as a
bookmark okay um here we have a is this
Chanel some lipstick but it looks it
looks High and rich rich Vibe
no oh Rich it's
l yeah maybe is this CH wait we have
right next to it uh oh I thought it was
dor but no D I don't know DLP DP I'm not
sure what that
says de smells rich
rich I don't even know I can't I can't
accurately
uh say what these brands are so uh I
don't think it looks like Chanel to me
but then again it doesn't so I can't
tell are these air ear air
[Music]
earpods just
kidding oh Mama Mia airports once again
airports Rich airports very rich pog
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay so somebody who likes to listen to
things so well since you already can
tell what this is Let's uh show it
cute why why is this Pokemon so
unpopular why I didn't know it was
unpopular and a little
Coach wallet
R now coach is all right it's not that
expensive is it I don't know but cute I
feel like people who have Coach things
they are very
elegant and
Rich it has bad stats bad stats oh oh
wow
always don't aren't stats like they
differ I thought they differ a little
bit and here we have the key attached to
the Pokemon
which of course
we oh no there's an
R oh oh no oh no oh oh I I should have
waited with that r with that ever
so
uh condemning r that will
reveal who it is for
it uh well this person must really like
Pokmon because here's some more this
could be from my manager
honestly Pokemon cards being carried
around a whole deck though a whole deck
this person is ready to battle
whenever
wow she's ready to play she's serious
H who likes Pokmon this much but it's
also quite an elegant demure lady and
Rich and Carries little little piece of
toothpaste around but no
brush do you just like brush it with
your
fingers I mean for an emergency sure why
not I
guess or she just or it's like a snack
she just just eats
[Music]
it and now this year I use that a lot
too um I every time I go to Japan I get
like a stock of these um this is like
this the the secret from almost all of
whole life members even the overseas
members when they don't notice yet and
when they get to
Japan they're being given this by the
company often like as a little like here
take care of yourself kind of thing
um yeah it's really good for the
throat I I some people I know they take
this like small packages and they just
like eat it like that but I still use
the small packages to put it into hot
water so generally this is supposed to
be um melted into hot water and it
becomes kind of like a
tea yeah oh I remember I was drinking
shitloads of this when I was sick in
Japan uh at the time where do you
remember when I got sick where I had the
the collab of crony for that song cover
but I slept through the
collab I was really sick back then
too man I get sick a lot but this thing
this thing is really good so they also
sell it like overseas in like Asian
markets but in different shapes often
it's like in a in like a glass bottle
but just look out for this
n n it has many names I feel like it's
known under many
names Paca or
n n n loquat syrup yes yes yes yes yes
if you ever have throat
H like even for even if it's a cold or
if it's like just by after like
screaming your heart out at a concert or
so this should really help you
[Music]
and then last but Le we have a switch
with also a Pokemon cover I like this
design that's cute
[Music]
M so what do you think thank God this
one wasn't too obvious it
seems honestly yeah this does give me um
the switch especially gives me Raina
Vibes and
some of these items could could give me
waya Vibes yeah and R of course yeah so
it's R so it's either
waya or laa wait did waya participate
before I'm not sure did
she I don't
remember she did okay okay okay yeah I
think Way's bag was uh also pretty like
sporty or like not too girly I
think yeah okay I find it so funny that
the r was there but it didn't even [\h__\h]
me over because you guys were still
mostly wrong it is Lia but now by the
end more of you guys were going towards
Lua it is l l let's go but the R I was
like for a moment I was like oh [\h__\h] but
wait no you guys are either thinking LA
or Lia well then perfect the r is fine
yipp yeah you guys were thinking more L
got at the end maybe because of I don't
even know why you what this um throat
thing would make you think Rika more
because Raa has very easy access to that
too living in Japan so I mean I mean
nothing here speaks against laa I just
didn't I wouldn't have assumed that she
like surely she likes uh she likes uh
Pokmon but not this much right I didn't
know that Rica likes Pokmon this much
though to carry around I need to tell
that to jenma because jenma would surely
love to
[Music]
battle give give me a give me one moment
M the pizza cutter what do you mean they
were wrong I think it's a hair
clip not not a hair clip a hair
stick um but yeah
[Music]
uh let me look at this let me
look
[Music]
M
oops all right all right all right all
right uh let's go to the next
submission next bag we don't have so
many anymore
but uh let's
do what what do we have left wa I did
this one I did this one I did this one I
this one okay you guys are going
[Music]
to all right here we
go here we go what do you say what do
you
think it's not who you think it
is maybe I don't know what do you think
it
is H
[Music]
sorry uh
huh huh interesting interesting okay
it's still kind of mixed all right all
right all right all right I appreciate
that are you guys doing this just so
that I won't uh cry
or uh do you really are you really torn
are you actually torn between
[Music]
these you truly
guessing Okay Okay well
surely in your heart whatever you say
makes sense and you're not just you're
not just doing this for me okay
um ah interesting H well I think on ly
this is whatever let's just get through
it but I'm going to reveal this first
item because we just talked about it a
moment
ago this is the hand sanitizer that I
also got from Amy mine was um pink now
you know what I'm talking about how
convenient do you know these hand
sanitizers am yeah yeah just Spam Amy in
the chat please please just do
that she gave a couple of these away
she just brought a couple and gave them
to some
[Music]
membersy thank you she wants us to you
know not get sick what a
sweetheart what a sweet lady lady lady
if you curious what was in am's bag she
participated before so check it out
um here's some lip
balms
cute they are very colorful
H lip balms I'm not going to reveal what
is written above it just says lip balm
okay and we have a phone is that an
iPhone that I see with a very simple
pretty and neat Ros
cover
pretty we love those pastel colors don't
we um
this is
sad well I have to get fruit this okay
this is maybe not very revealing
handkerchief a handkerchief handkerchief
handkerchief handkerchief
handker okay so uh ready
to ready to get rid of any sweat or snot
perhaps
mhm
ah he I'm having a d Vu what the
hell what's going
on uh next next
next this is
interesting why does she carry this
around
um does she what does she need to
measure I have
like measuring tapes but I don't carry
them around cuz there's nothing really
that I need to measure when I'm out and
about maybe this makes sense once we
know who this belongs
to here we have some eye
drops I see I see maybe someone who has
bad eyes but I don't see any glasses on
here but still I guess maybe maybe
somebody who doesn't wear glasses but
actually um contacts
and then we have some
napkins ah handkerchief and napkins
she's dual wielding
this dual wielding wow so hygienic a
girl with
eyes
no she only uses an old iPhone is this
an old iPhone I don't
know maybe other people
Iris okay see wonderful you guys are
between Iris and shodin they both
apparently use old phones wow we have a
showdown ladies and gentlemen we have a
showdown throw it
down
meds take your meds
jet and the s a card holder now you may
wonder why am I hiding certain for fonts
I ideally I'd love to hide all the fonts
right now but why am I hiding certain
ones because I feel like the way she
names things is going to give it away so
here we go eye crap lip
crap measuring tape SL assassin
Tool uh this doesn't give it away but
also it's not it can't be Iris right
because there's US dollars in wait is
that wait actually I don't know is
is it Yen or Us
doll I think it's right us right so
[Music]
yeah well I I guess she could also have
USD
but I was thinking like the overall
color theme like the background being so
dark and there being some purples here
and there and the font that you used
font will'll probably give it away to
you guys just like The Vibes are pretty
much uh yeah
[Music]
Shing it's it's on brand
oopsie yeah assassin
tool I'm
scared this doesn't include the big ass
plushy she carries around though
probably because it doesn't fit into the
bag that she carries so it's like a
separate
[Music]
item where's our bag no no they don't
have to show the bag itself I said
showing the bag is optional like if you
have a bag that you feel like you're
comfortable with showing because you
don't use it a lot or so then feel free
to show the bag but if you don't want to
that's fine too because I'm more
interested uh about what's inside the
bag
anyway where is her
scissor maybe the scissor is currently
stuck in someone's throat
just kidding wow that was
intense yeah like not a single person
not even a a small one that's actually
surprising to me right cuz like
shouldn't there be a Dimitri plushy yeah
yeah Dimitri where are you Fire Emblem
Demitri I know
him I fought him on the
battlefield no Demitri this is
fake oh
maybe he doesn't fit into the bag I
don't
know okay but what about the measur I
I'll inquire I'll
inquire okay uh all right right I think
I have two
more so let's
go oh wait I
[Music]
got okay
um yeah let's
go what do you say change bgf is it
making you do you hate the
circus do you
what I like I like that you guys are so
confused is this
better or
how about
this
[Music]
um I must say these bags in this episode
are
very difficult for me to
[Music]
reveal they're they're giving me a hard
time not going to lie well we have have
something I'm not even sure myself it's
I think it's a hand cream or a face
lotion it's I think it says face lotion
face no it says face
Edition is this can't read no Powder I
think it's a
powder it's a
powder
[Music]
okay
um okay we have
some cough drops like cough cro candy
thingy I know these I have these I I got
these recently from
JMA M lemon ginger
M this is this is this is
from this is from
Japan wait a [\h__\h]
[Music]
second I hate I hate I hate this m
tissues from myy
[Music]
Brand there's not much here to reveal
there's an anchor power bank a tiny one
okay okay Please Release Me From My
suffering a no what is this some cute
plushy I don't think it's like any of
the sunre plushies
doesn't look familiar to
me what light sticks why do you need to
carry light sticks around why is that
necessary they're orange though they're
orange who the [\h__\h] is
that why do you Mak it so obvious
[Music]
why are you making so
obvious and I didn't even realize but
like I don't think she did this on
purpose
but I thought this would not be too
obvious maybe it would even mislead you
because they're from Japan these things
but um the
like is a brain warm in your
head yeah it's it's
made it's a surprise bag that I thought
would throw you off but it seems like it
doesn't because it seems to be very
obvious to you that that I would even
invite her to participate so even before
I showed any bags in the first
place hi ah there is she there h where
is this where is the culprit here I'm
sorry I have to bring him
error I should have abducted him so that
he's not in your bag and so that this
isn't too
[Laughter]
obvious thank you for participating no I
can't believe did you do that on purpose
sorry that's just my Photoshop that's
not the PC but it
what did you even realize what you were
doing with this that's not on purpose
right at least you didn't have anything
turqu oise colored in
here but that's why I was hoping you
guys would say mint for the for the CCE
bag cuz it was so turquoise I had hopes
still hi
hopes did she say something did she say
if this was um kind of on purpose I
didn't catch a
comment yeah I know the light sticks I
was like girl like okay I can hide the
Fig figure quite well she didn't realize
okay I can blur the figurine quite well
but like when I blur the light sticks
they're still they still look like light
sticks and who else carries light sticks
around I don't know anybody who carries
light sticks
around they're so bright too even though
they're not even turned
on those are the ones that you crack by
the
way you crack him and then they work
only for is are these all these
are these Ultra orange
actually what if my car actually so
convenient actually what a life savior
yeah you can like you know wave them
over your head and be like come here
emergency uh police whatever whatever
who comes when your car breaks down did
you watch when we introduced your back
people thought it was very obvious
too especially when we hit the the
random Biscuit the the random biscuit
was like the
end I tried to make it not too obvious
but the biscuit ended all of
us it was so
over okay okay I
have uh one last bag explain the oh yeah
I would be interested to hear too are
you like into Crystal or like magic and
stuff no judgment I find that very
interesting you know another very unique
unique thing to find in these bags this
is why I like these bag
reviews is it crystal energy I throw it
at my enemies wow okay does it
work what happens when you throw it at
them are they going to be
cursed are you into like other stuff
like that like I don't know tarot cards
or so cuz I like cards but I I tried to
learn how to read them but I I never
really got deep enough into it it
explodes oh dear oh got to be
careful I use it to see
ghosts what the crystal or ter cards
what she's getting more and more
interesting very mysterious it helps me
detect
ad ah oh yeah maybe the crystal glows
when Advent is is close
by what a nice
Gadget sometimes tells me when it's
going to rain wow very versatille this
crystals maybe I should get into
crystals
okay
um another bag guys this is the last bag
so enjoy guess as hard as you can for
this last bag
overall it seems very orange but I think
that's just bad
lighting let me uh put it up as a on my
side as a guide okay okay
okay all right all right all right let's
start somewhere
here
round
sunglasses okay okay that that doesn't
say anything in
particular looks Italian really what's
that blue thing
oh behold hold your horses slow slow
slow slowly
slowly it is
tissues who would have
thought but honestly
I I I won't I won't say
anything I'll be careful Chi No you
thought it looks like
chatini is that mean maybe a little
bit
um here is the scissor that maybe she
only
lost scissors and a ziplock bag okay
does this really seem like louder to you
guys it doesn't seem like louder to me
but maybe we're getting very surprised
in bamboozles here
evidence oh oh maybe this is just shi's
second
bag I'm not sure what to show next maybe
just this this wallet I think that's a
wallet the wallet doesn't really say
anything here um
some perfume small perfume big
[Music]
perfume uh per per yeah a little random
ribbon I see that that um it's just a
ribbon just a
ribbon some hair ties and like little
accessories little accessories that I've
never seen this person wear
before they're numbered yeah yeah
there's some notes on the left side
about it
[Music]
um
what that is yours face in Austrian
brand what no it's not my it's not my
bag maybe I gifted these tissues to some
whole life
remember maybe I
did uh and
really not really but somewhat old
looking phone so could be Iris
[Laughter]
right what do you mean that's my bag
it's not my bag
what some oh this cute some uh something
to write down yeah little little note
and a pen and that's lip
okay
[Music]
uh I always thought that was so
questionable what is this well well so
the thing in the in the in the in that
little plastic container is
seeds from maybe I don't know trees or
whatever or flowers of
flowers
[Music]
and uh oh yeah then there's a bandid and
then there's
a
yeah that seems to be a tree
branch maybe something from a tree
[Music]
and and then we have a I mean you guys
are starting to say Faun wonderful
because we have a a cow patterned
bag with a little
umbrella cow pattern bag cini oh oh we
can now do the math and understand this
is from
[Laughter]
Cal and then we have some some euros
maybe I don't know and uh well fauna
surely loves me a lot fauna seems to
love me because that's a kiata
keychain that is a kiar keychain and
some
glasses that's my mommy's
bag it's my mom's bag and a lot of a lot
of her belongings
I didn't even remember this but um when
was this last episode like over a year
ago or so it's the last time I did a
hollow bags episode and my mom really
wanted to participate and sent me I
think during the stream back then sent
me a picture of her back but I didn't
see it so I couldn't feature it and now
I forgot it again cuz it's been too long
but she reminded me she was wa she is
watching the stream right now she was
like oh I guess you're not featuring my
bag huh and I'm like I forgot
oh you want your back to be
featured why tree branch well she's the
she collects a lot of things almost like
Amy and she's um you know she has a huge
ass garden and
she you know she just like has a lot of
flowers and trees and stuff um the tree
branch I think she's just trying not to
tease me but uh
yeah yeah uh the asran tissues man who
the hell recognized these as asrian
tissues it can only be an oh did you
guys look it up you guys must have
looked it up huh cuz even as an Austrian
I didn't know that this was an Austrian
brand of
tissues the garden you slept on yeah
yeah yeah no that was the deep deep
Wilderness what the hell what do you
[Music]
mean I mean maybe not just a like maybe
it's an Austrian brand but it's
available in in more than just Austria I
think so yeah um L's bag is missing she
seems to have forgotten to submitted but
that's fine we can keep her for the
future if I ever do another one I'll
have to wait until I have some more
maybe I'll do a Japanese member focused
Hol bags stream there's just I think
there's still a lot of Holo uh Japanese
Holo bags that I haven't featured yet
and maybe one or two Ian members still
uh I think Iris or so probably you guys
are saying Iris didn't
participate yeah fuu said they don't
have anything
interesting so they didn't participate
but you don't I mean I mean look at
crony submission I mean not that that's
not interesting but like you don't have
to have much stuff
you don't have to have much stuff for it
to be worthy of the whole B stream
that's the funny
[Laughter]
thing crowning's back I love it I love
it I love
it yeah it reminds me of one of the
older I still have it I have the like a
folder
[Music]
do you guys
remember oopsie what here ah [\h__\h] well
no what's
happening you guys remember this bag
this
submission not even laid out on a
table I'm a submission was so funny
uh yeah there were a couple of
simplistic simple ones in in the past
too
yeah not too much I honestly like in in
the back that I showed in the first
stream like my own one uh I put a lot of
stuff out there but it's not like I
carry these things all the time around
often I I will like to minimiz it as
much as I can here a little throwback to
to Wawa bag h
M yeah those are bags that I don't even
use I don't know why they're cute I
should use them and the stuff in there
like I I honestly never bring that
little that note I never bring that I
always feel like I wish I had a mirror
with me but I never bring the pocket
mirror I rarely actually do bring makeup
with but when I do it's usually
something for the lips to
refresh uh yeah I never bring just like
like this candy was just randomly in the
bag I will admit sometimes there are
things randomly in there just for no
reason well when I'm in Japan I will
bring a mask yeah some of these things
are accurate some are um no actually not
that bad
honestly just the the note I don't write
things down usually I just use my
phone feet lotion it's not a feet lotion
it's a a Band-Aid for when you have
blisters specifically for blisters
M the shades they're so old they have
like scratches at this
point that was my back from the past
from an older stream that's why I didn't
even let you guess it it used to be it
used to be an old submission from the
first hollowback stream as this is the
first the the third one yeah the third
one fancy phone yeah I still I still use
the same me but now oh my
God my that part the back this is the
back this not in a case this is the
uncased version of my phone I have a
huge crack on the back well I guess I
should be happy I don't have it on the
front but all over that beautiful white
surface uh is a huge crack but it's kind
of like inside like when you go over it
with your finger you don't feel the
crack it's like between the most outer
layer of the glass and the the
white plastic or whatever so yeah huge
crack but nowadays I cover it up with
with a
cover get a hard case yeah the thing is
I used to have a case on and then the
one time I take it off my phone falls
down and then it cracks like that but
yeah it is what it is it is what it is
now that I think about it why did I
choose an orange bag that's kind of a
giveaway too huh but no not necessarily
you know not everybody has a bag in
their image color you can't just assume
that it is one particular person
M well thank you so much for guessing
with me I hope next time when I do this
it won't be too obvious I think if I do
a Japanese member focused round then
it'll it'll be more difficult we
featured I think M Senpai before I
remember and
N uh but ah and fi standby fi standby
yeah I I see those pictures I still have
them so that means there's still so many
that we could feature we should do a
Japan round huh okay I want do it A M I
want to space this project out as you
know U but this is always
fun sorry I'm get to
excited thanks for the thank you we were
we were very very very glad to see the
insides of your bag thank you for
sharing an insight into your private
life people were asking where's Dimitri
shooting what did you do to
him where is the me I was surprised too
about the lack of
plushy or like any kind
of like anime
Vibe right yeah where's the
scissor Demetri is to obious F okay
thank you oh you were considering that
but I was also deliberately hiding um
some of your writing because I thought
the lip crap eye crab kind of gives it
away especially at that
point was I right because that that's
very shielding to me to write it down
like that the font also a little bit you
know it kind of gives me Shield Vibes
very shiy
core they want still they still want
explanation about the measuring tape I
I'm curious too do you ever like end up
using that when you're out and
about what are you
[Music]
measuring which iPhone is
that why do you need to
know don't worry about
it only the
corpses understandable have a nice day
thank you thank you for your your
honesty got to be careful around
[Music]
sh it's to measure coffin sizes oh de
dear oh dear no further questions I
plead the
fifth y yeah yay okay that was it that
was it that was it thank you so much
guys for participating I'll read a few
super chats not too many cuz I'm hungry
um and I want to probably take a nap
before the 7 Days to Die stream which
will happen after this late at night for
me 3:00 a.m. oh thank you thank you this
was fun I should bring girls talk back
soon too I hope you guys are in for that
as well of course you are of course you
are and don't forget if you're leaving
now if you don't want to stay for the
Super Chat read don't forget to stream
Mirage the music video especially
because for milestones for each even
smaller Milestones I'm going to give you
guys nice rewards I I quickly want to
reach 500k so I can show you the dance
video the dance dance only choreography
version skip super today n I'll read a
few at least because you know we
can't we can't
afford not too much I'll read like an
hour
maximum we stopped
yesterday on this one so we still got
like anniversary super chats to read
thank you for your patience
[Music]
everybody yeah well I don't want this
bot to be too long e so it doesn't look
so dating but I'm going to change this
music now because Mama Mia of course
it's making me feel weird things as well
I want something chill please thank
you or
this
no
wow no this one's
fine this one's fine
made you think of Minecraft yeah may
have used it
before yeah thank you to all the members
who participated in the hollow B stream
you know I think it's really interesting
to take a look it's a little bit private
you know but uh I'm so glad that the
members are willing to participate it's
fun show me show me more I didn't I I
also wanted to do a kitchen review Holo
kitchen before like the uh fridge
actually Holo fridge
I should I should do that I forgot about
that I was like H one day what will I do
when H bags when I can't find any more
bags oh we should look inside what it's
what is in everybody's
fridge we did fridge reviews before from
you guys like your submissions but I am
curious I feel like the Japanese members
a lot of them have like nothing in their
fridge besides bottled water and maybe
maybe that's pretty much
it I think overseas members have a bit
more stuff in their fridge
usually my fridge is constantly packed
actually
yeah usually with hell fresh packages
so yeah bot water energy drinks yeah
maybe a little bit of alcohol for some
members
M yeah they usually order food
mhm Okay Okay so yesterday I think I can
figure out can I figure out where I
stopped yesterday
um let's
[Music]
see oh one thank
you awesome then I don't have to think
too hard about this uh just have to find
the right Str here it is
and Senai showed her fridge the inside
of her
fridge oh it was sad to look at oh
no what are you holding on your left
hand what does it look like to
you
obviously it's a bubble
blower oh no bubbles coming out tennis R
show sure sure I'm going to Shad this
glass the moment I impact with the
tennis ball that's dangerous that's very
dangerous don't do it don't do this at
home
uh yeah I think I9 I read that one right
and then I
stopped
okay thank you
Jack Redwing thanks for the pinky my
beautiful tentu My adorable Kami oi this
four years with yuk was and is a
wonderful experience let us hope there
will be many more years with Yuki thank
you
Ki oh how I love to hear those words the
most powerful words the hottest thing
you can
[Laughter]
say thank you than hey
it's it's a it's a turn on just
kidding my one and only D thank you so
much yeah hopefully there will be more
thank you so much for staying around for
so
long Good
Times d d n d d the G driving with the
Reed chat yay we at kfb love you so much
Chu
well I would hope so I would hope that
you love your boss thanks for being such
an amazing Idol your passion natural
talent and diligent hardworking attitude
are truly the embodiment of what is
truly a phoenix four years isn't enough
be or oi forever
forever okay you're just saying I should
be oi forever you're not saying I should
stay in whole life forever until I'm 155
years
old I can take that deal yeah I can be
Ori forever that works
[Music]
[Laughter]
fine well you5 years that's not forever
either but you
know he's not so old uh sure I guess not
for
Phoenix I guess that's
[Music]
nothing not a big
deal
Kaba one one day my sweet little
chickens one
day I will still be alive but you will
probably be dead so it's more about you
guys living forever that is the problem
you know you have to be
careful ideally live a healthy lifestyle
yeah
[Music]
make sure to you know work out and uh
don't don't smor no no sming it's really
bad for
you oh thank you
chesra I appreciate it young
lad Kaba gives you a little kissy with
her Shribble Trumble
little
lips no moisture left in these and no
life left in my lips anymore do you
would you like a little kiss from
giaba another
one do you feel all the lines in my old
lips does it feel
nice texture it's got some texture to it
I like to say yeah yeah now you actually
feel what you're
kissing very wrinkly but it's
nice CR no crust I I wouldn't describe
it as crusting excuse
me ain't no crust on here
[Music]
okay
Grandma okay let's put you in the
wheelchair again
taka d
d uh space wonderful thanks for two
pinkies happy 4th anniversary wa already
four years time sure flies by when
having fun but looking back a lot
happened a lot of good memories were
made with you I cherish every good
moment I had thanks to you I feel so
lucky thank you so much for all the hard
work genuine love huge dedication
precious time and great content you gave
us so
far here's so many more great years of
you hopefully I love you so go them much
W thank you thank you thank you thank
you two pinkies makes one red so you get
a
kiss Thank you for the long long support
always staying loyal and supportive and
passionate about me I really appreciate
it yeah keep the pass
Al this last glass of water will be my
my sand sand time
[Music]
clock when the water runs out I run
out okay yeah hourglass yeah yeah yeah
thanks just another give things to the
vinky four years after four long years
you're still here and doing amazing
things can you believe it it's been a
wonderful Journey yeah it's crazy I
didn't think I'd be for here for so long
as you know but it just happens I keep
on like working and weeks and days go by
and years go by and suddenly I'm here
suddenly we're all here and we look back
and we're like What the how has time
passed so fast how is this possible did
we just go through a time machine or
something like
that this can't be so fast H crazy thank
you for the support though for so long
thanks for not getting sick of me K's
chicken nugget thanks to the pinky as
well congratulations on your fourth
anniversary every year since your debut
has been full of really memorable
streams songs and Stage performances the
effort and love you have put into all of
this is clear and it inspires me proud
to have you as my Aussie thank you so
much yay I appreciate it I'm glad thank
you for proudly
repping orange and supporting me thank
you thank you I try to make things
memorable like today you know another
one of those more unique stream ideas
that I have that I'm quite proud of so
I'm glad you enjoy every stream though
thank you so
much
P J love with one
two three four six six oranges I think
that's a red one right in
total 6 * 20 wait
what
120 thank you I was not able to prepare
a proper message for this time because I
was a bit busy with personal matters but
nevertheless I couldn't just uh it let
it go past without any message here to
happy fourth anniversary tangel thanks
for amazing four years and once again
you have outdone yourself this year was
quite a busy year for me due to
traveling and conventions especially and
I bet it was a super busy year for you
as well amazing how you can go strong
continuously I'm proud to say you're are
my Kam oie oh really oh my God I'm
surprised and always continue to support
you as much as I can sorry if all my
message on so scuffed I'm writing this
doing work oh no not at all not at all
unfortunately I don't think I I'll be
able to see all of the anniversary
streams due to to work but thanks for
fun K look an interesting oi Boba
adjustment for the model hope you enjoy
anniversary video by kfp anyways hope
you have a great F anyways you're
looking forward to another years with K
thank you but I need a fro
[Music]
candy time for some
Rola I have the exact same ones right
here I told you but these are they're so
weird why are they so melted is this one
melted too not really it's weirdly
sticky e it's like as if somebody
already put them in the mouth and then
put them back and then wrap them back
again and you know just pranked me like
that
but that' be
[Music]
insane no no they're fine no it's like
humidity or
something yeah JLo thank you so
much you know I've said it again and
again but I'm so glad you're part of kfp
because you're like one of the
most
like your your love display for w it's
always so big and it feels like you're
just a big like walk advertisement for
me wherever you go it's like your
presence is so big that it reminds
people of my existence just by you
walking around it's like I'm paying for
some kind of truck to drive through the
streets with my advertisement on it but
you you're walking
so thank you for the free
advertisement basically all of you are
like giving me like free advertisement
when you want to merchandise it's like
I don't even have to buy these ad
spaces walking Billboards
everywhere thank
you I'm so hyp for the happy me too me
too me too can't wait to see you all in
your
happies everybody will be wearing
happies happy happy morning
[Music]
okay who knows that that's so Niche if
anybody knows this song that's it could
be made MTO might know it
but you don't know it do
you you know yeah yeah yeah yeah at the
home it's a really old made Cafe song
really old old like 15 years or
[Music]
so
amazing and it didn't even have like a
music video or so I
think I think I think it was just like
performed in the
[Music]
cafes crusty and
Dusty yeah but they probably still
perform it to this day maybe but not as
often anymore please tell me to get
uh Happy Happy morning happy
morning shining shining oh they have a
music video now oh really I need to
watch
[Music]
it I'm going check out the music video
anyway thank you
J chicken okab thank you for the red
super chat I love you my Kam oi Ki waa
this is the year of the Wawa happy four
years I was at breaking dimensions and
world tour let's go I'll be there for
you w anytime no regrets ever I'm
learning M to be able to give you my
energy I'm so glad I am part of kfp
thank you wa thank you so much I think a
like the the chants are really difficult
to put into like um
not put what's the right word I don't
know in in in in not insert but well
well to combine them with my songs is
probably very difficult so Implement
yeah any any kind of o o I'm already
happy about but even that since there's
not really normally you're not supposed
to do the oi oi oi during singing uh
when somebody's singing but I've noticed
like in our I think even in the New York
concert it happened
um just because you guys get so hyped up
and I'm not saying you shouldn't do it
um
but it's not how it's usually done but
you guys just get so hyped and then you
for like the last course or so sometimes
you guys would like go like hi hi hi hi
along the
Rhythm but then you can't hear the
singing so well anymore so usually it's
not done uh during any parts where it's
being where where they're singing It's
usually done between the braks where
there's in in the brakes where there is
no
singing but it's okay I I like that you
know it's kind of different how it's
done overseas like you guys are slowly
picking up some things and making it
your own and it just shows that you guys
were so
hyped and wanted to show your hype and
your
appreciation yeah but for Mirage and my
other songs also like like Chima H like
for Chima at least you can like scream
along
Kim and then pineapple also pineapple
here and there there's a few things so
what what always works is just sing
along just sing along the whole song If
you know it learn the lyrics and sing
along that's more western
style like Taylor Swift kind of
[Music]
vibe yeah I want to hear that I want to
sing the whole venue sing my song I want
to hear
[Music]
it honestly that would be a big honor to
me if like cuz my lyrics are
very very long and intricate if you guys
end up remembering them so much that
means you listen to it a lot and I would
I would be so moved if I hear so many
people sing it and become
one but we'll see we'll see how we vibe
to Mirage I have to
think I have to think about
it you know K-pop style chants are also
quite uh fun and similar to J-pop but
has its own flavor and it works better
for K-pop Style songs that have a lot of
like overlapping vocals and stuff and
andless you know Japanese style music uh
breaks and so on
so I think for Mirage I'll try to create
something like
that it's like often for K-pop style is
often like
randomly
interjecting like screaming the lyrics
at very specific
timings very loudly so the impact is
very
strong and then in yeah during intros
they often go
like like some kind of Rhythm like that
and they chant out like all the members
names but what if there's just one
member yeah talking about fan chance I
think K-pop style fan chance will work
better for Mirage so I look into
it now during K-pop they like chanted in
the beginning during Jpop usually when
there's an idle group of different
members when they get solo line after
one solo line they will scream like the
the member's name in a particular Rhythm
not like unorganized it feels like it's
all following the Rhythm and the flow
because Japanese songs are usually
structured in a way that gives it this
kind of moment where you can squeeze
that in
yeah that's like the one where it's kind
of dragged out first you go like I'm
singing something and you go k and then
I'm singing another line and you go k
again and then I'm singing another line
and that's where you kind of overlap and
you go like
oh K yeah you know what you've been
studying and then sometimes you go like
hi but and then also sometimes I don't
really know when how they decide which
one to go because there's like
this Rhythm sometimes they say the name
of the singer sometimes they just go
like
um hi hi hi and sometimes they go like
oh hi no
no do they clap too I'm not sure anymore
I'm confusing
myself hi hi I
guess well different different styles
I love doing that though it's so
fun and so thanks
CH JS thanks for the pinky happy fourth
anniversary Dan never expected to find
you and be a part of your crazy fun
Community I'm glad you are it's been 4
years but you're still that genuine
hardworking Idol I made my
C let's go long ago keep chasing your
dreams BP love you thank you well I I'm
acting like that but I I know I'm your
Kam ooshi I mean look at your profile
picture thank you JS you're the best
thank you so much for your
love I hope I will stay of come you
forever don't betray me don't betray me
you got
it
else yay
yay these keys I'm messing things
up I hope you are
scared I hope you
are e Mayan D or lb Mayan not sure fluke
morph D thank
[Music]
you D ra I I I'm sorry I'm so sorry
Julian B D bang Shi Kami thanks for the
pinky K time sure flies happy
anniversary to my Kam oh
she let's go it goes to participate in
the happy anniversary video at ofy oh
first time I was able to ah that video
mhm there are people all over the world
that love you and think of you as their
signing
Idol yeah that's a wonderful thing to
think
about those little group videos were
really
cute you guys recorded some of them Rel
in advance ADV I guess good planning so
organized thank you so much for your
support and letting me be your
come I'm
Yours
[Music]
i'ms must
thank you I am honored to be yours I'm
honored to be at your
service thank you so much Fallen penguin
also sent a pinky thank you happy fourth
anniversary how fast time flies how much
you have achieved to many more years my
favorite streamer top Tong Cats
Restaurant recommender o yes I am and my
Kami oi oh my God you guys are
you guys are comboing me with these holy
[Music]
macaroni thebo is hitting
heart
combo so many in a row yeah I mean I
know that some of you guys you don't
even mention it in your super chat but
you still think it I know you I know I I
know I know I'm your Kam oi okay not all
of you maybe I'm just your oi but a lot
of you I know I'm your Kam oi for a lot
of I know I know and some even say t
oi I know I
know it better be so just kidding I'm
just happy to be one of the people you
like to watch but being your Koshi is
even
better m
W what you really mean is CI I know I
know I have cat hairs on my nose and
they are annoying
[Music]
me but I don't know I keep on think
it do be like that sometimes Philip hold
for the Super Chat and
also happy belated
birthday
[Music]
congratulations okay LX thank
you and Mos bear comes on thank you for
the Super Chat
[Music]
difficult to
pronounce comes Anita for the pinky
happy 4th anniversary when I was hard to
do some when I was hard to do something
for my dream I always watched how you
try hard to reach your dream you are my
muse thanks for everything oo that's
sweet I'm your Muse
wow thank you so much I'm glad I can
inspire you I hope you will reach your
dream or maybe you already did that
would be amazing but never give up on
your
dreams keep on reaching for your
dreams fighting fighting fighting
fighting
[Music]
fighting we are fighting dreamers
what was that again is that
Naruto that one's
fun I don't care for Naruto but some of
the openings are
definitely a Bop A
vibe no I do do not really like Naruto I
mean I don't hate it but I just don't
really care for it I never got into it
when I was younger which is when people
usually get into Naruto I think it's
like their for overseas people
especially non Japan people it's usually
their like one of their entrance entry
animes together with like Dragon Ball
and whatever but I just I didn't really
care for it what I watched if I watched
any anime back then on TV like Okay
small choice but it it often uh would be
K Kam Kaz K JN I was always looking out
for that whenever it was on and I didn't
even I didn't even watch um salom moon
but um what's it called again the
DMI do me
and sometimes RMA but I it always just
felt so wrong to me I felt like I was
doing something
illegal not in the sense of watching it
illegal but I felt like I was too young
to watch RMA it just felt so it felt so
wrong to me it felt like I was um like
if my mom knew if my mom knew she would
turn off the TV
immediately yeah there's a remix on I've
been hearing a lot about like RMA at the
moment yeah something's going on
Something's
[Music]
Cooking hasn't aged too well oh yeah
will
probably you know Yasha is also one of
those that I didn't watch and I didn't
care about because I don't know they
were just like it just it was
too I don't know I liked more of the
girly
things and then those those were the
ones that were running on TV and once I
got like deeper into it one of the first
ones I watched was
like like like out side of the whatever
was running on TV like vampire
night
typical typical teenage girl and
um uh did I watch that or did I just
read the Manga butam Sama that was the
first manga I
[Music]
read and
ah vampire night and Ka made Sama were
some of the first animes I watched and
iron
Al
um [\h__\h] what was
it oopsie sorry ah ah ironically another
one uh what was it maybe I shouldn't
even remember uh it was like that that
it'll get
anime but don't worry sorry I'm moving
it around don't worry I don't think I
even watched it full I don't
[Laughter]
know I think I just kind of got into it
because the the people like the other
like online anime friends or whatever
that I had were were talking about it or
so it's kind of horror yeah yeah
mhm the anime the anime
wasn't erotic was it I think it was just
the game and the anime was fine just
depressing
right yeah okay yeah it wasn't yeah
that's why I was
like I felt cool because you know I was
still young and I was like yeah one of
my favorite animes is Kim and people
would then like be like oh oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] because they knew that the game was
like a HTI game
and so I'm like cool like you
know but who I really liked in that
anime was that waitress
girl yeah I talked about this a long
time ago I think with you guys Street
Credit yeah hardcore yeah mature
yeah and then and then yeah once I got
more more into it like one of my
favorite animates from back in the day
was
kanagi kanagi
M
[Music]
yeah best kanaki is so B kanaki is so
good that's a
flashbang understandable yeah Min
[\h__\h] loved Mam and then I went into
working and I went into um monat of
course
and like T
again all that kind of
stuff yeah I was watching a lot
then yeah and even a lot of Niche stuff
too like do you guys know I monog which
may I think I got into it when I was
looking into what seasons I haven't
watched yet from bakon and then I found
II monogatari I'm like this is not a
monogatari show but then I thought it
looked kind of cute so I still I ended
up watching it like look it up look it
up it's a it it's
[Music]
[Applause]
cute it's so cute the it's so cute the
redhaired girl is so
[Music]
cute it it it's I don't I
yeah oh and of course like Kon was also
one of the early ones but that that's
just like something everybody watches I
guess Kon and
um yeah I tried to watch like all of the
animes from that studio pretty
much and weak sauce
I kind of miss the times where I was
like really into it ah Lucky Star I love
Lucky
Star I was way more a fan of Lucky Star
than I was of Hadi but Hadi is fine too
and yeah to became one of my all-time
favorites a certain scientific rail
gun clanet I didn't B clanet yeah I I
know I know oh
ni I loved all those like ni Jo daily
life uh comedy
shows yeah so
good so
good Slice of Life yeah that's the weird
did you watch K like I think I
[Music]
didn't don't don't think I
did h a few ones of those classic uh
haven't reached me uh yeah a few ones
didn't reach
me I mean I knew of them but I never got
to watching them t love M yeah of course
I love that
one why are we talking about so many
animes right
now I'm trying to remember um there was
one I think also from the
Kon Animation studio uh sorry it's not
coming to my mind right now but
what am I thinking of there there were
these girls that were in like some kind
of war uniforms or so what am I thinking
of I really like the the opening and
ending songs they had for that one
too
yes sorry that was that's so nostalgic I
really like
Sano the anime did you guys know
it English English title is it girl last
trip is it I don't know I I know it
understood on the I was A1 Pages oh it
is it different it looks like Kon to
me yeah sounds of the sky sound sound of
the sky I need to listen to the to the
opening I need to listen to also I
really liked
uh what that the one with Taka
just mentioned
recently yeah I think you can get a an
insight into what kind of animes I was
watching when I mention all of
these oh and the one with the Virgin
witch
Maria oh yeah two play
mhm master and and the one no friends
the friends one the I don't have friends
or something like that
yeah V I didn't recognize it when you
were just riding it down
as
yeah ah now I'm getting nostalgic yeah
don't get Maria yeah and then when I
think of Maria I was also thinking of
Maria holic
[Music]
[\h__\h] love Maria holic so that online
I watched like two seasons of
it but yeah I was more of a rezero kind
of
girl yeah one of my favorites also from
back in the
day H I want to write like a whole list
man compilation of all the animes I
watched and liked
myu Penguin Jump so good I love that
one was one of the
best
[Music]
yeah no I didn't watch Soul either
sadly did you watch flying witch flying
Witch is there Japanese
[Music]
title I no watch that I don't think
so it's different
now does
it
why little wi Academia yeah I watch that
one too no get no life yes
yes yes yes
yes yes
yes is it is it just me growing out of
anime mother yes or have animes just
changed I'm sure there's still a lot of
good animes it's just me growing out of
it pretty sure it's just me angel Beats
M so many tears have been shed over
Angel
Beats Mama
Mia that was traumatizing but such good
music h
Angel so
sad Violet Arden I finally watched like
recently right I watched the the first
season and I still going to watch the
anime uh the movie cuz yeah people kept
on telling me especially one person to
watch Violet ever Garden like I want to
I want to I know it's a good one and I I
would like the visuals very much too
it look quite
[Music]
nice no I did didn't watch that one but
it looks
familiar okay okay enough enough enough
enough we need to CH guys this time is
reserved for Super Chat reading we went
into an anime tangent oh no
[Music]
thank you for yapping with me uh seems
like you guys don't want me to read
super
either
um go okay where was i
t for the red chat congratulations for
fourth anniversary thank you for your
persistence and hard work
[Music]
your kiss has arrived knock
knock knock knock
[Music]
who's
there
[Music]
byebye it was Kiss deliver
surprise surprise
Keys
what the gnome's silliest Propet Prophet
oops than star Platinum dun KP Shadow
dun for the red super chat happy 4th
anniversary tento thank you for being
part of her lives and making us smile of
your streams and music here to more
years to my kamhi whoa
another
one you guys know what to
say Wow Wow Wow for my little CI chicken
come here come
[Music]
here thank you so much for for
supporting me for letting me be your
number
one I hope I will be your number one
forever m
don't you dare move me down I want to
stay here it's cozy if I fit I
[Music]
sit Le knle thanks for the pinky I'm
proud to be a member of kfp watching you
grow into the best version of yourself
it's enough to make me cry we'll never
give up on you we'll always be here we
love you you're
by number one come on come Kam
Yoshi to the end
oh let's
go thank
you
wow damn guys now probably the people
who forgot to WR write Koshi even though
I am their Koshi are probably like damn
it [\h__\h] damn
it thank
[Music]
you thank you such a Charming Charming
gentleman thank you m Oh Canada Oh
Canada I haven't sung the Canadian
anthem in a long time sorry I want to
show my
respect Oh Canada Oh Canada I like to
eat maple
Sy Oh Canada Oh
Canada sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
mate yes famously known as daram
accurate
I heard something about Kad
recently in this game Kelly was very
disrespectful towards
them shadow Cross Zero thanks pinky
happy fourth anniversary T here's to
number four and Beyond let's
go beyond and much much further right
further and further Beyond
[Music]
we'll figure it out what's beyond
together hand in hand Shadow CER thank
you so much for the pinky and your
support sky thank you also for the pinky
happy four years anniversary you're a
wonderful girl thanks for everything you
did for us let's go four more years okay
I guess my contract is
signed thank you Skye I appreciate it
thank you for your
support you didn't say I was your Kami
but I know I am right right I'm pretty
sure random collusion thanks for the red
super
chat thanks for brightening our days on
this journey together thank you thank
you for brightening my days my days are
already feeling so depressive expressive
I don't know why it's
conflicting I should be happy I am happy
I'm but then I'm then I'm sad and then
I'm happy and then I'm sad
[Music]
but I'm pretty happy about
Mirage
yeah yeah and like things finally
calming down
and pretty depressed
about not like upset about like uh some
plants falling into the
water for the next month
but it's okay Loki I appreciate it this
is one rare
opportunity where I'm not seeing the
glass half empty but half full
instead yeah cuz I was I was going to go
to Japan again in
November and do some work and it was
going to be busy again but now it has
fallen flat into the water and I'm
lowkey relieved because cuz I was not
ready to already
go and travel again and leave my cats
and
stuff
yeah so it's actually I welcome it a
little
bit but it's also stressful because like
I the things that were planned for that
trip
ah it's very
unfortunate very
unfortunate
yeah but it is what it is and I'll see
the bright side of it cuz I can chill
some more and maybe I'll maybe I'll take
a spa trip within
Austria for like two or 3
days yeah it's time to take a spot trip
hell
yeah hell yeah that's right
attitude more chill more caos more
fluffing C oh
[Music]
oh let me go to a spa and get massages
to fix my neck please
crack
crack fake you random
collusion C great thank you for the red
super chat ooh a little bit of a lurker
no thank you thank you for being such a
positive and Shining spot in my life
these last few years woo you and kfp
Community has helped me keep looking
forward all these days I can't wait to
see what you do this upcoming year W
being cute this feels like we're like
celebrating New Year's for you guys mean
the fifth year yeah fifth year special
year I'm such a veteran now
damn you guys
too you're a veteran like some of not
all of you but a lot of you
vtuber
veteran oh yeah half a decade I would
say Century but I guess it's a
decade I'll never know I will literally
never know
[Music]
huh yeah thank you so much for the
support CA gray thank you long long time
together hopefully much longer we'll
write history together M reine thank you
also for the red super chat for years of
potential myth and kfp thank you for all
thank you all for bringing smiles and
inspiration to to the world every day
and here's for more years to come yippee
H thank you thank
you yeah four years are to be celebrated
together thank you so much for being
part of these great couple of
years and yeah being part of the
community thank you
soon and TP thank you for the
pinky I'm bad with words I'll keep this
short and just say thank you for four
amazing years while on to many more love
you love you
too you got something to say you should
call me Yami ooshi if you're if
you're at a loss of words you should
just call meami say it how just say it
just say it thank you I know you're
thinking it I know you are look at that
kfp beanie that you're that you have on
your
head you see it
can't fool me I know what you're
thinking thank you thank you thank
[Music]
you say a lion chicken you say
it right into my
ear whisper it scream it with
[Music]
confidence
zero always love to say D to D thanks
for the red super chat don't cry don't
cry thank you for the support d d stay
more Sunshine D thank
you come for the red super chat happy
4th anniversary tantel although it's 8
months membership I've been a fan since
2020 mhm actually it was a hard time for
me and I was going to give up everything
I ever seeing Ki shining brightly I had
the hope of life and my dream again
really thank you thank you you're you're
so welcome I thank you thank you for
still being around in many ways thank
you for not giving
up we got to live our life it's one
lifetime one lifetime for you many
lifetimes for
me smug
smug but yeah you got to treasure it
guys I mean
once you're a a hybrid chicken okay then
maybe it's too but that's not much of an
extension
so treasure it thank you
w for spending your life with me for
four years now thank
you Manu Schneider D for the pinky K
LOVE Manuel love thank you than feel Le
d
[Music]
thank you video production what kind of
video production interesting just
no Mr Shadow and duction thank
you I always like saying your
name it's so fun thank you for the red
super
chat oh are you guys ready
K thank you once again for being
my Kam
oie you brought me joy and happiness for
four
years you've helped me get through hard
times I'm proud to have been in kfp this
entire time I love you so much boys I
hope we can spend someone more time to
know he's hitting those spot
[Laughter]
thank you
st stomping now stop it
now Jimmy salivan thank you for the
red thank you for being a shining star
bringing light into life for the last
four years one
cannot wish for a better
come oh you guys are comboing
[Music]
again thank you
Jimmy thank you wow
Jimmy now I feel even worse for all the
jimmies we have
sacrificed you will
be S you will be safe you will not be
sacrificed you are safe here Jimmy don't
worry I'll take care of
you come blind fi D out run the wind D
thank you oh I hope you'll be
back I hope that month is over
now the month of not watching Wawa very
much are you back out run the wind
[Music]
I'm having um the feeling of
not having
enough outrun the wind what do you call
this again
uh things
Shin Chad are you
[Music]
alive oh oh
oh oh yes okay
okay did you die momentarily or where
you just
[Music]
quiet I was trying to say what is the
word and a shin in
[Music]
English oh yeah I'm having withdrawal
simp out run the wind come
back Oz 176 thank you for the red super
chat oohoo congratulations on your
fourth anniversary Tel thank you for all
the fun streams exciting projects and
fantastic SS M Fantastic Baby for four
more years
with with my and my
come what no
way thank
you another one another one for the
books thank you o 176 you're not even
oie what the hell why you call yourself
o when you're donating in
Europe what's the meaning behind
this where are you from
from H talk episode with oie 176 tell me
tell me more tell me more like where are
you from tell me more tell me more from
Rich chicken
[Music]
farm more like your credit card number
tell me more tell me more
or I'll send you to
[Laughter]
Slumber did I
[Music]
himiss I see the end I thanks for the
red super chat love you w happy 4th
anniversary thank you I feel like
something's missing in your message
aluda would you like to add something
would you like to say something to add
on to your super chat it's kind of small
you had so many more letters to spend
yeah there you go
kie I mean I I I felt like when I didn't
want to assume you need to reaffirm it
you know oh there's a sappy super chat
later oh okay all right like in a
different stream huh you just need to
reaffirm me I don't want to assume can't
make
assumptions thank
you all right I'm looking forward to the
STA you one too L dun Brandon dun Fafa
dun for the red super
chat oh no Fafa what have you
done I don't see the word here but I
know I know I know what you're thinking
FAA I know what you really want to
say happy 4th anniversary
[Music]
Wawa time flies love never changes thank
you for everything keeping going we're
growing together I love you my oi K you
forever he hates me Papa or she I don't
know they hate me they hate me Papa it's
why do you hate me so much it says love
and says oh but you hate me I obviously
hate me probably a typo but then you
missed four letters how is that
possible no I know I know like look at
your profile
picture it's a Wawa and there's even a
pineapple or something like that so I
know you just forgot thank you
m Greg thanks for the pinky our dear laa
has a beautiful heart and deserves all
the best
hope you can find even more success in
the future happy fourth anniversary
thank you I hope so
too are you in the chat let me
[Music]
see are you there you are yeah am am I
am I
come I'm just making sure I'm just
making sure thank you
that would be uncomfortable if I wasn't
but um I was trying to make you say it
but I really wasn't
but these people are I guess I can be
pretty feeling pretty secure with these
people I didn't drink any Vanilla Coke
only one glass of normal Coke
dero but uh I'm just like happy to hear
these Koshi words today come out of your
little chicken
beaks
everybody feels good feels
good
[Music]
I so good so good so good
okay zly thanks for the re love you
w you're C oy right simply right simply
say it thank you though I know it I mean
it must be right I mean otherwise I
mean what what what have we been doing
all this time
are you
[Music]
here I'm pretty
sure I I'm pretty
sure but you're not here but I'm pretty
sure I'm pretty sure I mean I
mean I
mean we we'll just assume we'll we'll
take the right to assume
thank you
dippy M A for the red super chat I Know
I Know M you're not you don't usually
say it but I feel like I know
it we'll see congrats on four years
Tanto it's been a fun four years and at
this point all I can really say is
you're my Kam oh no that's not what this
says uh I hope you can feel better and
get to relax for a while before any more
big projects come up yeah yeah
now it seems like I can it will probably
be a while until you read this are you
enjoying
Zelda I'm not playing it right now but I
am still in the process of finishing the
game uh how did you know this is a month
okay not no yeah about a month
ago well I played a little bit yesterday
I try to not do too much off
stream I ran around everywhere were
looking for the blue crystals and side
quests and there were still a few side
quests in the uh Rock
people the
[Music]
gonan uh area there were like maybe two
side quest that I didn't do and then I
found ah well I well you'll see but um I
I did
one uh little tiny baby optional dungeon
I guess you would call it a dungeon it
wasn't a real Dungeon it was just a
little bit of a something uh the one
with the ghosts in the graveyard and
then I found a different one but I
didn't do that one cuz I thought that
one might be kind of nice to do on
[Music]
stream but I I took some screenshots
I'll show you I'll show
you what I did when we get to the next
Dela stream smaller smaller
dungeon H did you do the quest of the
old man in the village below the volcano
old man ah no no no kakaro no no no I I
I know what it's about but I'm I will do
it on stream
too at this point I've been like spoiled
plenty but uh
yeah there's um there's this church I
did a few like optional Rifts closed
them up and one of them basically opened
up this church and which is next to the
graveyard and the guy in the church
gives you some like General hints some
are really obvious some you already know
at this point in the game like tells you
about smoothies and stuff but he also
tells you that there's
clothes uh that you can get in kakaro
cloves that will let you talk to a cat
or two cats so that guy also kind of
spoilers you so to say but I already
knew
beforehand because I got spoilered but
it's okay
okay normally I don't think I don't even
know why
I tried to even read anything of what he
says like the first few things are very
obvious and then you got to dig a little
bit deeper to find anything of substance
but normally I wouldn't even consider
listening to that guy he's just spitting
facts but it's like facts that I already
know but yeah and we'll get those Glo
soon will become a cat yeah thank you
m m did you say what you had to say like
you you think your your whole Super Chat
was
sufficient
[Music]
H Trum roll
what
m m no M what don't break the don't
break the
I know you love
me I know you
do come
on don't break the cycle we're on a roll
we're on a real roll here
[Music]
are you doing that to tease me or CU
you're shy or because I'm not your Kam
Oshi now I'm confused
[Music]
but I'll I'll I'll move on
then emotional
damage emotional H well yeah know okay
yeah that's fine honestly what yellow
heart does that mean I mean wa I mean
that's fine I Kami that doesn't mean tan
oi so you can have two Kami ooshi
honestly is that what you're saying
don't be shy it's okay like I I like to
share my seat with
uh am if that's the
case love to share it with her
I love to share with
her yeah okay okay see it's don't be
don't be so you know there's nothing to
hide good choice good choice of
ooshies H yeah I know no there are cases
where you can have two cameos she if you
love them the
same yeah like you two if you just can't
decide and yeah so it works it works it
do be like that sometimes where I can
have no now would we can't have this be
a twoo common
occurrence dear
kfp this knowledge you have
gained you shall not keep it V be
[Music]
uh uhhuh remember nothing do
you
wonderful mission accomplished okay guys
we we're so close to finish these super
chats let's go certainly Don I am a te
beep D offer thanks for the pinky thank
you all for such a happy and fulfilling
four years always proud of everything
you do and will anticipate everything
that you've got on the horizon I
probably say it every year but I have no
clue where I'd be without you and myth
well I don't see the magic word but
that's okay I love
you I love you I am like the Jesus of
chickens and I love you I am
[Music]
okay happy tears thank you for adding
that in the
chat I'm on a roll it's it's it's kind
of awkward when this roll doesn't
continue until the end of these super
chats thank you thank you you saved my
ass thank you so much and no the 1 hour
it's it's been 1 hour and like 9 minutes
since I said 1 hour so we're not that
far from like my deadline that I put and
there's still like 3 hours and 20
minutes until the 7 days to die so don't
don't you worry don't you
worry thank you
offer let's go thank you so much for the
support Tom J J swag book D for the red
super chat than so much for being you
Kiana I know you have two ois by the way
don't
worry happy anniversary love
forever yay yipp I wish we still had
that had that love for
forever
um emote that was so cute I like our
current emotes too ah had to find the
Kami button on my keyboard it's under
the Tab Key anybody could miss it there
it
is you have a whole key for it I see
it's like the Sparks stream Sparks key
something like that thank you thank you
Kami oi let's go my Kami
chicken love
Forever toy thanks for the
pinky I have been watching myth since
the start oo let's go base wait how come
like this currency is so rare how come
you guys manag to have two uh Norway
super chats in a row Toby and the gamer
Creed same person or
what what is going
on
mysterious I've been watching my since
the start you guys have been a great
inspiration to me especially you just I
didn't expect this
one you are my Kam oi I'm a lurker but I
will yes see because they're a lurker I
wasn't I would not have assumed so oh
thank you oh my God you wanted okay good
good good oh L from Norway but I will
always be watching thank you so much for
four years and many years ago that was a
nice a nice
surprise a good surprise prise thank you
the street lives
on it's
on
H so I have a minimum of two fans in
Norway what was there for let me
Norway
Norway no no
way maybe free
[Music]
H oh my God oh my God no way you're from
nor that is
so
tacky it's always nice to hear from the
lurkers thank you for existing it's
always a nice surprise to be like oh oh
oh another kfp that loves me that I
didn't know like I wasn't so aware of
you I'm sure sure you've like maybe
super chatted before but you know in
those many years and many Super Chat
Super Chat readings some things become a
little bit of a blur so thank you for
reminding me thank you for being part of
kfb
yippee it's a pleasure to have you oh
another Norway right you are Norway too
damn Norway kind of Bas not going to lie
you guys are dope lit super based h
speaking of Norway thank you the gamer
cred for another pinky happy anniversary
it's been one hell of a journey so far
and I'm so happy to have had the chance
to witness you grow and become such a
strong and wonderful content creator no
matter what the fifth year has to offer
will will always be there for
you I mean you didn't write it but I
know it so but say it say it say it
say
it say it a there we
go
yeah oh what's
happening what's happening I'm getting
exhausted I'm pretty exhausted
man I feel like throwing up
thank God this is ending soon thank you
so much let's go the gamer Creed the
Kami
[Music]
Creed Ari d f pandas D Fred screw D I
love how you Ed that by the way F thanks
for the red super chat thank you k for
staying with us for the last four years
and sharing with us so many emotions
from sadness to happiness and success
and always yapping away through so we
didn't fall asleep on the job some of us
literally we love a wa so much happy
anniversary uh uh uh are you
here
fried you're
here I I don't I mean your profile
picture says it all does it not
come on come
[Music]
on oh you were sending a Super Chat the
[\h__\h] you're putting me for this
awkward silence man but thank
you let
go oh Mama Mia Mama Mia thank you for
the r Super
Chat sorry all the F Keys have been
messing up
things thank
you I I am I am almost done guys
Unwritten D should thank you and I have
a feeling you would say the same
I know it but it's okay you don't have
to say it because we're moving on to
space waterfall with a red Super Chat as
well so space wonder I mean there is no
question of space wonderfold wait oh
wait we have an interesting one wait
you're actually going to break the
[\h__\h]
cycle thank you so much for the
incredible K and your sweetheart filled
speech I love you so much I cherish
every second I get to spend with you I
will always be there for when you can I
promise my
my
my t o we'll take it it's like a
joker it's like a
joker it's
like you know it's it means Kami
oi because I'm your only Oshi so it it
it doesn't you know it doesn't there's
there's a tan oi equals kamhi but Kam oi
doesn't equal tanoshi I
guess yeah to many more Amazing years
Yi we did it the fouryear anniversary
super chats are
obliterated you love to see it you love
to see it thank you so
much
thank thank you thank you thank you soon
for the support
and your patience I feel like haven't I
how do I oopsy I have 12 is it no l 11
okay
um after that didn't I read a few of
these smaller ones or did I
not didn't I didn't I sometimes like I
was like I'm going to read this like
this one but not the big what oh what's
with my
face I'm not going to read anything else
now but I'm just
[Music]
checking
really are you
sure oh no
no no no oh well we'll get there we'll
get there now it won't be so difficult
anymore this was like the biggest hurdle
I think we we'll get there when we get
[Music]
there we'll get him next
time it's okay get some sleep yeah I
don't know if I can I'll try I'll chill
in bed the cats will make me tired
probably a yeah I'll
try I mean it's not like I didn't sleep
enough I slept like 7 hours but
but one stream already drains a good
amount of
energy you guys know that right like
screaming and yapping and talking like
this and trying to make things
interesting in it's the you know the the
entertainer voice and
everything it's tiring on its
own and like using your
voice like this like talking louder than
you would in a normal conversation and
Yap more and everything and and try to
make words more powerful by and and
and uh and
emphasizing things here and there and
enunciating stuff like
that you know that is very tiring
without even knowing you notice like
after after you've done a stream it's
like no more
talking can't be animated like that even
if I force
it I feel like you could
but I mean you don't have to be normally
normally you don't have to be like
this but I feel like it even helps you
in like everyday life when you're trying
to tell your friend a story or so and
you notice that they're zoning out when
I notice that someone's zoning out while
I'm talking I try to emphasize more
words like
and so then you know what happened then
I can't believe she did that are you
listening waa I was like so
angry when she said said this and
that
whoa Becky did that oh my God oh my God
all right right I go eat some food
now you know what I did yesterday okay
quick quick CH chat so a couple days ago
maybe like three days ago or so I
wrote that I
um wanted to eat Al alio right but I
didn't eat that on that day yesterday I
was watching a couple of like Alo oio
videos uh on YouTube and you know it's
so simple I was like okay you know what
today is the day I'm going to [\h__\h]
cook Al
alio I got myself some chili flakes but
it wasn't even spicy I didn't put that M
many in but it was good enough yeah so I
uh made Al oo yesterday it turned out
pretty
decent M that was my dinner yesterday
didn't cook anything from my hello fresh
thing I still have like two two
packages that I should will be
cooking and for this coming week I
cancelled so maybe I'll try again
Perfection my
Aloo cook at the pasta did you take a
photo yeah I did but I mean it didn't
look that F let me let me show you this
will be a oh God 5% batteries this will
be a stream
[Music]
exclusive and I'll show you my mushrooms
too
[Music]
oh God I'm my phone is
dying
okay you're at shrooms no but I I picked
up some mushrooms like cuz they keep on
growing with all that rain and stuff and
I don't like mushrooms but I was just I
was thinking of doing a tweet writing oh
man with so many mushrooms growing my
garden this could be free food too bad I
hate mushrooms cuz I I I'm pretty sure
they're actually
edible but I hate
mushrooms okay where did that
save oh
oh
M does it look good I I got to be honest
I used some pretty old garlic but uh I'm
sure it was still fine but I wonder if
it would have tasted better with even
fresher
garlic um but yeah so I roast it first I
put a lot of olive oil a lot a good
amount of olive oil into the frying pan
while I was cooking the cook at the
pasta and you will be so delighted to
[Music]
hear
wait to
here that I did not break a the pasta
I did not break it the pasta but also
this is really low quality um pasta I
noticed because in that one video I
learned some things I didn't know um how
to differentiate I mean I knew it was
cheap pasta because I bought the cheap
pasta on purpose but the video that I
watched taught me uh about how how to
differentiate visually if it's good
pasta or not first of all this pasta if
you look at it closely it'll have like
no texture yeah but the good pasta has
like some texture on it like a rough
texture and uh when you like I don't
know like you take a handful of pasta
right and then you stomp stomp on the
kitchen counter then you see that
there's like
flower like puffing puffing puffing
puffing the the dust is dusting
off this one didn't do that no I already
knew it was cheap faster anyway but yeah
guess maybe I'll get better pasta next
time yeah the pasta starch exactly and
the pasta starch is apparently
important in some cases but yeah so uh
basically yeah I cook at the pasta and
then I meanwhile I put oil it's so easy
I don't even know why I'm explaining
this but I like it it's such an easy
food and so good so olive oil get it hot
put in some garlic good amount good
amount can chop it the whatever way you
want it but keep it in bigger pieces get
it roasted until uh it's like starting
to Brown I think I let it go too much
because I realized at the time when my
garlic was already kind of brown enough
my pasta still wasn't finished and once
the garlic you you're supposed to timey
it better you're supposed to put the
noodles in already into the oil stuff
in the pan in the frying pan when the
garlic is just starting to get brown I
think but I had I timed it really badly
so I still had to like stall for four or
five
minutes yeah and then once the noodles
are in you add you you stir it a little
bit emulsify and then you add the
chopped parsely and that's it can add a
little bit of sea salt maybe or
something like that or I I didn't do it
this time and I think it's fine this way
but next time I make it I'll add um
[Music]
parmesan I think both ways is nice Al
oio with Parmesan and without without
has its like focus on the oiliness and
on the parsley and the
the garlic
but next time I'll make it with Parmesan
yeah
M yeah it makes creamy but I learned a
good trick don't put the parmesan in too
early and like when you put you have you
got to add like a huge mountain of
Parmesan when your dish is already
finished and
then if you don't like Let It uh like
blend blend like don't mix it don't
blend it just let it stay fluffy on
top and enjoy the fresh still unmelted
snow
sowy uh parmesan with each
bite I don't know how to describe it but
in that video it made a lot of
sense n if you don't like spicy things
but I ass show that you like yeah yeah
pepper yeah yeah if it's not too spicy
and there is I don't know if you can see
but there is chili flakes in here just a
a small amount but it added a a flavor
it did add some flavor here there's one
single piece of red over there like it's
hard to tell if it's garlic or not but
that one on the on the next to the
middle on the right side that that's
that's one tiny piece
of uh uh you know what is called chili
chili fix it's in there it's in there
one sing no no no no no no I I I I I
grinded like three times yeah well four
times I grinded the grinder I twisted it
like three four times I think four times
h four time I grinded it four times
no it was just pretty small they were
pretty small the flakes cuz they were in
the grinder I didn't you
know they're blending
in all right guys there we say in thank
you for watching had a good time I love
you guys so much love in the air don't
you feel it you're my CI chicken guys uh
after in 3 hours uh 7 Days to Die um I
think I won't
stream but I'll stream other times uh
probably most of the
time yeah uh find me on like Callie's
Channel or whatever or or crony if she
streams I don't
know yeah it's basically like
rust but with zombie
rushes it'll be
fun we played a little bit off stream to
like get to know the game only like we
didn't even play until zombie rush just
like the first like five
steps yeah a in see you see you see you
see
you stream
Rush do it just do it
n
[Music]
oh I forgot a
kiss
oh illegal
space
waterfall sorry I was going to be
arrested see what x excuse me I don't
use this platform that is called X I'm
not on I'm not on porn
platforms I only use Twitter
[Music]
The Internet Is for Porn The Internet Is
for
Porn click for
[Music]