second to the nation hello
hi okay
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not streaming but guess what
also my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which
means I'll be streaming in 480p which to
be honest why even why even [\h__\h]
bother why even bother okay
swag As a sheriff let's party
Amelia
[Music]
selected people you can get the outfits
yes
[Music]
Among Us Lord now we're written
you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore
[Music]
right here right next
cool please
[Music]
thank you
it's a crazy
wow
[Music]
I don't know it seems like an imposter
it's suspicious
[Music]
people's outfit you can get in the game
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
you're wearing your own hair
yes
I'm wearing a scientist outfit right now
I feel like I'm I'm doing a touring love
in the Among Us
[Music]
yeah yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
looks like physics
ice cream we're working on it right
mommy yeah
what outfit do you want
[Music]
whichever is the closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right and then
we have mayonnaise
today I'm cosplaying as sexy naked money
in your area
was so good what the heck that was
really cool wow
okay and then we have
hello hello I am I will be the second
today
[Music]
oh my God yeah
it sounds fun please the organizer of
today's event responses today's event
wow
I told them I tried to warn them
um
perfect timing
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
look at that was so cool oh my gosh
good I can also do like Amelia
I can do this
[Music]
now change the world settings we will
have everything included we'll have
scientists
[Music]
but you can see if someone's dead before
finding the body and then we have the
engineer engineer can is a crewmate who
can jump into the vents so you can maybe
with that I got that a lot in practice
yeah or you can maybe find some other
imposters because of that might be
healthy eating in the vents oh yeah yeah
very spicy and now we have the guardian
angel which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from
with responsibility
and I only have last but not least the
shape shifter this one is oof that that
calls for a lot of
um
[Music]
can be only an imposter but that
imposter can change the looks of
themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
wow
[Applause]
wow wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
um
I can't there's no mini game
because you need to have a task I have
it's because I'm an imposter
and because good and I were playing
earlier
and
I was there with her
and I remember my last time
oh yeah
wait don't don't that's embarrassing oh
no just kidding look it looks like Lego
floor too far away oh yeah oh they look
like little
how do you do that
you guys
are the lights
[Music]
already
that was so fast that was quick Kiara's
gone real quick that was fast um wait
where was it the um where where was the
body Armory yeah
I saw someone purple in the room with
Kiara I think or was it Ollie
doing tasks
[Music]
I was in the showers I have no idea I
checked the cameras and Kiara was doing
something electrical and I think Ollie
was in the room with her oh
I was on my way back
[Music]
yikes I mean Phoenix tastes good right
wait wait that's your defense
[Applause]
[Music]
she was pretty busy the whole time yeah
no she was pretty busy the whole time I
would say I was putting away hello
the the corpse is in the Armory right
yeah because like uh like in the
beginning of the game I saw Muna in the
armory but like oh but that was the
beginning I was in the Gap room when it
was found out well she got killed fast
you know anybody want to step up and be
like yo I'm something
yeah
uh if if you are you were telling me
that um I was in a Armory you can ask a
gura because I saw Guru also in uh
nearby there in the kitchen
um
[Music]
I have no idea
says
oh girl you right next to me or
something
I want to make me dance
are you always picking the kitchen
together
who it is
I have that one too are you
we could be Alibi I don't know what I am
wait what the heck
how do you tell
you event I'm engineered oh wait so
there are some people who don't have
anything because I don't have anything
hello Ollie says oh God
what the
oh did I reload it
uh
hello goodbye
foreign
[Music]
ER
wait I can do this
what the heck
where'd you go
sharks are scary
how do you do this
copy
electricity is off
the sheriff's of course
um
it was myself a kitchen
a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maury Senpai we were nearby
electrical trying to get your Alibi set
huh
and Kelly said bye I mean I went to the
Armory and put guns away I passed by I
passed by
it was Watts
Ura and Records yeah I can I say that
last time I saw zado they were in the
main hall with Kobo Cobo
[Music]
start pointing fingers
because uh she she telling me on the
previous one it was me well I definitely
like far away from the kitchen and now
good
morning
I don't have enough information
do you have anything that you want to
defend Cobo yeah
so any last words
like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh me herself like like just
what she said and then after that I go
up
that was beginning though that was the
very beginning
I know I I after that I go up
I go after killing her you mean
so we have like we have liters
I have enough information yeah I have no
idea
you haven't heard movie in a while we
may voted for herself
the main size
wait so she wasn't an imposter
at the very beginning
why would she vote
for herself huh what's this
dude
[Music]
they really wanted to throw her out and
I don't like that oh hey Watson
I'm gonna kill you well please stop
should we have [\h__\h] to do
it's fine I believe you please don't
prove me wrong
[Music]
mmm
work
exactly and then you pull this that's
completed hi
hello
now Cali will know that it was mume
[Music]
okay that's insane Watson is dead oh I
found the body
I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
while I was figuring out how to do the
mini game I was like how do you do this
then mume ran in and was like
and doing things and then I walk out and
Watson's dead body is there
[Music]
because you would have passed Watson if
you were entering the front of the ship
you would have passed Watson how did you
not see her
[Music]
half awake
sorry couple
thank you I'm not gonna point fingers at
you immediately I just want to know what
your Alibi is no no no I'm not I just
want to know what your Alibi is because
I Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about I don't know why you
remember so much Kelly I'm I'm just
reading it and moving working together
listen here's the deal so the amount of
we're working together just in between
me entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
it was like no time at all you would
have passed her I just I just want to
remind you that we have 10 seconds left
so I think
to vote for a movie I just don't believe
it
the imposters are gonna win they voted
yes wait who did not vote
it I mean I think I think oh I hope I
wasn't wrong
I don't know I legit don't know wait oh
yeah
nice noise
okay
good job everyone
did it oh
my God
wow the sheriff was actually helpful
I can't believe
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately in Among Us
this shooting Turf thanks I think I
think Kelly you should go for it Amelia
Watson detective outfit
[Music]
you can have the hair you can have my
hair
[Music]
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yes
let's go
[Music]
basketball
[Laughter]
look at that
hey
[Music]
oh
everything looks good
squeaky clean
yep
foreign
[Music]
it's my style
oh
what is that weird noise
I hear something weird
hello
I don't know what is that
yeah
[Music]
I found Ollie dead
um that was crazy so I don't know the
map super well but I left the shower so
I put away all of the washcloths from
the shower and then I walked up and I
turned right and I went down that long
hallway and found Ollie's body right in
the middle of there but I didn't see
anyone coming down
so like above the shower house above the
shower to the right yeah
on the shower I was in electrical
well let's see um Renee was busy doing
things around the shower
um also Raina could have killed me is
that pretty close I think girl was in
the shower as well but she like went
down to the left
because if if it's really if it's
raining if she already killed only
probably she cannot kill you right but
Rene could have killed me several times
and she didn't so I I feel like you're
freaking vouch for me she was trying to
tell me a joke and then I ran away from
her oh yeah Kiara also could have killed
me if it didn't
and I was like at the left side
yeah it was mostly Down Below in the
front of the ships
I don't know just like saying uh so
probably saying that you are nearby the
the place I just like thinking oh true
I'm true you're also there by the way
but I I don't remember I saw Muna Senpai
in the middle-ish or on the left side I
don't know oh wait we're gonna vote for
her yeah
[Music]
beep
there is Spider-Man actors Roto sloped
in the Mario Kart what what oh hello
hello
why are you following me why are you
following me
people people
following
yeah huh
hello hi there's so many people it's
good that means we're safe
we can become one
spicy
oh I have a task here me too
okay
you forget that
then if we all stay together I'm too
scared to go alone
[Music]
safe you fixed it we're all here
you get a task to do though up here
what part of the map is this oh
this is like the oh the showers
thingy doesn't work
uh
I know
[Music]
did something in the toilet
uh
beep beep beep beep beep
[Music]
what
I ate too many so
hello
hi
[Music]
hello I'm gonna and we're trapped no I
don't know don't we have to turn on the
wait what the heck did she shape shift
oh my God
our Sheriff
where was she
very bottom of the armory
Armory oh
did you see anybody else
Kiara and we confirmed each other as
Alibi yeah
below the main
Hallelujah
I was on the way actually I was on the
way to the kitchen so any any sooner I
would have found the body but I'm from
the engine room
I saw you I saw you at the right side of
the map going up
because I was doing tests at the cargo
bay you know there's the test oh okay
cool we
is that before
um
so you from the cargo bay you will go
you went and then
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then bomb that body oh so you
were pretty close by yeah
[Music]
yeah but what if you guys are working
together good and Kiara
always I was like I went like what what
well
Santa's voice who are we gonna vote for
something so
um
okay skip we didn't vote who am I voting
for Gouda
[Music]
we gotta get them out of here
hello
[Music]
here
missed my
opportunity
hello
my tummy hurts oh this thing is working
I didn't do anything hello
hello
[Music]
we live in here right
yeah
we were met in here and you're going
that way I'm going down what happened
what happened
what's happening what's happening
okay that's real Muna though
confirmed that somewhere around here
hello I have a task
not really but I have the thing here
we could have got the double
foreign
I was ready
hovering
hello
oh
[Music]
foreign
I'll do this oh
wait send it back
what where who's that oh Anya
oh yeah
wait where
where I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical test with Anya and I ran into
it raining and mummy hello
that's uh technically that's true I I
was always you got all these spots
sounds about rainy ones yeah really
you're always there when there's a dead
body
huh it wasn't me it wasn't even me
reporting I don't know where the body is
this time
um
don't forget shapeshifters guys
yeah where where was it
I want to ask uh Arena where are you at
I'm at Medical I came from cargo bay
Uma was like going from bottom to up oh
yeah I saw her in the car go back and
where was the body I literally
how about Watson I was with Muna Senpai
for a little bit but then I was down by
electrical like down the ladder that's
where I was coming up when it was
reported me
I don't know why it sounds like a
detective serious why see all I want to
ask why is mume so always so afraid of
me or is she just afraid of everybody
muma's been pretty quiet yeah I was
thinking the same
oh my body for me last time why did you
vote for good uh wait so do we have an
answer where the body was I missed it
yeah where was it where's the body was I
was gonna see
the body both the body is
I don't know what should I choose uh
says
[Music]
okay we finally ejected someone so now
we just need to eject one more we can
win
one more one more
hello
hello you
[Music]
you're lucky I'm on cooldown Gouda
dude
[Music]
hello
hello hi Muna did you see me before uh
up there
I saw you
cleaning up towels in the shower
in the meeting room
hello
foreign
[Music]
shoot I can't take the elevator thingy
weird echoes in here
okay well it's definitely definitely
wasn't rated then I thought it was her
maybe but
that's around I I heard it's rainy so
doppelganger of me
so yeah
wait what I was like before that I was
in a cupcake with with Google with gura
and then and then really come and say
she got she's so double Ginger of me
so somebody was pretending to be you I
did see you again running from Luna but
maybe it wasn't Muna Muna oh wait who
yeah I saw I saw you too I mean what if
Kiara was with Reina for a while so
it's time but I love her often
often I can't remember yeah was that
last game
it might have been last game when I was
a lot with rain was it I ran into combo
Cobo was something very scared though so
and always we have to vote for someone
hobo is killing someone scary is that it
but
she's
fine who says here
I think we already voted one out so
there should only be one imposter left
I have a feeling that maybe but they're
not but then it might be um
I don't know I don't know I just wrote
up because last time sweet arena in the
weapons like oh wait so where was
Reyna's body weapons was that close to
Kitchen I haven't I haven't got I
haven't go to the armory
one vouch for Ahmed and say like she's I
was with Gouda and I didn't kill her
I mean that was nothing about Kobo
though because
I don't know
okay
well hopefully we don't die
no one was ejected
hi who wants to come sit with me while I
clean the bench kitchen we have to vote
someone out
we're not getting anything done like
this
should be down somehow yeah what the
heck
foreign
how do we win what the heck
oh
wow hey guys
I wonder why people kept aggressively
trying to frame me yeah that was pretty
hard to watch
it was really hard it was so easy to do
oh my gosh I'm getting face expressions
[Music]
you're too quiet you're too quiet it was
too easy to frame you
hold on wait okay okay
no evidence
[Music]
I have a question on there because I
heard you in the in the selection screen
where you choose where to go next I
heard you say something that sounded
like something
like you might have been acting oh was
that what you were doing uh so yeah I
was the Imposter
I'm proud person yeah something that
only a crewmate would say yeah
[Music]
right now I know I'm bad okay
too easy
let's go
Holly congratulations Ollie's gonna
shape-shift
he's shape-shifting
I want the kitchen task yes
you see it's like a Webkinz bun onion
wait what the [\h__\h] bun tomato onion
onion fun
tomato onion yeah I know I like the
taste actually I'll order it with onion
but then I'll take it off
where's my stomach what the heck
oh
that it was just tomato and onion
Kiara
doing some sort of task pretending to do
a task Maybe
Watson
okay
oh
I gotta call emergency meetings
Among Us have big hit a dead body data
where
uh I don't know the location of the map
oh you know the location
[Music]
uh Armory and a kitchen when when I want
to go to the engine room so I didn't
know I thought Yoshi from cockpit or
main hall oh yeah
[Music]
and I'm from the communications Armory
kitchen I saw viewing deck oh Ali and
gura oh no it was short yeah it was good
we kind of passed by each other always
meanwhile exactly what you guys have
against me yeah so she was we were in
the group yeah
and Cali was in the shower I I saw her I
saw her in the shower I saw a Cali
running
side I think
she went to the left side so she wasn't
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi Maybe
I was going out to get service I did
pass you Watson I was worried you were
gonna follow me outside but you didn't
uh you probably weren't that worried
since you're a little says uh but yeah I
found Zetta actually right by the body
because uh I was the one who reported it
I was coming up the ladder yeah in Maine
Hall
really dark really
[Music]
you went up I went up
no I didn't see you go up
um
[Music]
oh well I was the one who found the body
with Zeta near it so I'm gonna vote for
Zeta because that says
no they weren't
but they're there
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't yeah I didn't see her and I
was the one who's going without anyone
dying yet first
ah
hi
why I did not say
[Music]
ing
let's see
[Music]
did you stay away from me what are you
targeting me because I called you out
you now you know what people would be I
know you have a cool down just follow me
until her cooldown's over
have
everybody
she's gonna get me Hub hello
then why aren't you going to do your
test why are you following me
she got locked out
you tried to I think she tried to trap
me in here Anya be careful zeta's here
and she's an imposter
wait I need to stay away from me
what the heck
hello
please don't do anything I'm just I'm
just a little guy if I killed humano
Senpai would be right here and she would
know
right
or is it so that
I gotta keep an eye on Zeta
I have tasks to do I'm gonna go do my
tasks
hello
oh no don't watch you pervert I'm doing
my tasks
what are you doing anyway
foreign
does not want to fix the lights it's
trap
she's lying
ah dead body
wait what
I would know that right holy [\h__\h] Anya
is dead
what the frick
I just found Anya's body in the bathroom
and I'm pretty sure Zeta and somebody
else serves us here
okay
[Music]
where's that where's the body uh anybody
in the bathroom is in bath or showers or
no that wait what the [\h__\h] Lounge Lounge
showers
yeah it's it's where the bathroom stalls
are
um so let's we're out a day where
um the last time well the last time I
went near the shower and main hall is I
saw only
amen and I think I think did anybody see
Anya with anyone
we're outside then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zetta
what what the [\h__\h] no no no no no no
wait wait wait wait wait ask me so many
times
your favoritism it's favoritism no no no
no no yeah what's your Alibi where were
you
how do you know listen to me
not a crewmate
nuts us so keep that in mind now you're
saucing me which means I'm a crewmate
uh-huh it's not gonna work
you always over explain what about your
alibi well then I
swear because why aren't you providing
an alibi instead of Defending yourself
huh
why
why if only this included room where
like she was either Zetta Kiara
yeah because you're the Imposter why
would you vote
Ollie voted for me
Ben is it Ollie and Kiara instead
[Music]
Ollie and Kiara says Ollie and Kiara
Luna
I trust you
too
where's the light oh this is the light
okay
nice
I'm gonna try to close the door which
means that they know we're here
stay away from me
but at least I'm contributing and watch
some shop don't kill me
I'm not I'm uh doing a thingy
the thingy killing me uh nope I was just
putting in the code
I want to use this
right now I'm gonna stay with you
no I don't want to say they just hears
ay's here
I'm not gonna kill you I would have
killed you already just kidding my
cooldown's about to be up
come here
[Music]
ah dead body there's a dead body here
then it was just here raining
right okay it's Zetta for sure I'm
voting for Zetta
are you the one you you said you you
found you found a buddy three times in a
row now yeah because I just happened to
be a detective who's really good at
spotting bodies you
can bring it thanks but I don't know man
Rayna could I have killed you or would I
have uh killed that body if I was with
you and in that room for like over 30
seconds
[Music]
oh you want me oh maybe honest uh what
you said was oh just kidding I was just
waiting for my cool day yeah but I was
already in the room doing the task
before you got there
instrument
s
so that's extra time
uh-huh it's like three times
can anyone anyone uh give an alibi to
Jetta
no
no but I mean I saw Zetta running away
from the body because Rayna and I were
both up in the room like in the meeting
room and then as I went down I was with
Rayna the whole time and then we saw
Zeta pass us and in that hallway
why
yeah I saw Kobo take the little elevator
across yeah I'm gonna vote for Zeta
when I take the elevator what's in like
near the fan yeah if I die events not me
okay wait what 30 seconds 30 seconds
oh so then it was probably maybe it's
Kiara and Kobo working together trying
to vote out Zeta
everybody
I have no reason to suspect you
I voted for Zeta but maybe it's wrong
ah did the two what the heck combo
Zeta
that was Cobo then is the last one Kobo
task task doing my tasks
wait not up here this is a dead end
shoot
no I landed in the middle wait
[Music]
I could kill you but I won't
you know why you don't open the door
because I suck
hi
hi combo what do you want huh you want
to kill us
and watch me clean
I'm doing this task here
right now Let's Stay Together
are you doing a task in here or
something
no
then what are you doing are you just
waiting to kill one of us
all right
all right have fun
good luck
did you guys eat breakfast dinner uh not
yet
[Music]
I don't know how to get up there
up from here couple's not doing anything
she's just trying to kill us
yeah uh I'll let it be known that Kobo
and Zeta both voted for me
[Music]
oh no no no I don't want to be I don't
want to say
bye-bye good luck I'll come back and
check for a body hi
I need to get on that
send it back
I'm stuck
uh
gotta go do my task
hi
oh no come back I'm safe we should stay
together
[Music]
foreign
back
Mickey Mickey
it's Kiara
[Music]
why are you calling a vote I was just
doing my electrical thing
I wasn't even near you
you just didn't have an opportunity to
kill anybody did you
what what you didn't have an opportunity
to kill so you you decide to call him
[Music]
I'm telling you
it's probably like Kobo to be honest
because she was with Raina and I were
together and Kobo was not doing any
tasks and she was just following us
trying to wait until one of us was like
separated
what were you doing recently
I was just following them why
are you done with your task or no my
last stars is in electrical
um
then why did you go up to where we were
Ollie Ollie I'm just scared you're
usually so good with numbers but why did
you mess up why did you keep messing up
that number thing I had to do the keypad
thing for you oh true that was such it
took so long after Cobra went over to
that side but I'm gonna look on that
side too right no I was on the other
side
I'm sorry wait so why do we call this
emergency meeting in the first place
just because all right uh because we
want to develop you off yes you're gonna
vote for me believe it's not me it's
either Kiara Kobo
I'm gonna vote for Ollie because I kind
of feel bad for her because nobody ever
cusses her
okay bye-bye
good luck
it was Cobra wasn't it
[Music]
hi who is it we're we're [\h__\h] we're
boned
who was it just kidding
down there where's Kobo
what's this
[Music]
episode
it's electrical this is electrical okay
yeah is it Kobo
wait was it is it Cobo
I thought it was but I don't know
back to my photos
come on
good
I already used it so it has to be
someone else
okay oh now they realize it was Kobo
a
[Music]
who has
finished we could
I'm already accept diverted power do I
have to do something
my tasks
is this a task
this is a task
like this is accomplished
gaming I'm gaming
oh I can't do this one
download medical data
this way
I'm almost done with my tasks
where is it oh
my ghost on a computer
oh
[Music]
okay last one
this way
upload data where's that
down here
oh
I should look at all the
how do I do this
oh
I should look at a I should go watch the
action what's happening
oh we won
how do we win
even the multiplier
where's the multiplier
a multiplier
now for no reason Kiara what the heck
I'm a teammate for real for real then
you vote me out for nothing
[Music]
the gaslighting was so intense
but to be honest I mean it was so
spot-on
this was kind of funny not gonna lie
I'm so scared
that was right
that's just not that she's the Imposter
that's just her personality
[Music]
why didn't you believe me Kiara I
thought you would believe me
I believe you uh-huh uh-huh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you finally
I can do my tasks
I forgot to say
I'll just pretend I said it with
everybody else
hi Mommy
well then I have a task in here
this is a long one what the heck
1702.
sweet
attack
just where is this oh
hi
mommy mommy
okay hello
I'm very busy
what about me
running around
me still here is it because she got
imposter
she doesn't want to leave on her
imposter game huh
he wants to try to win and get some
kills
[Music]
whoa
where were they
die you watched her die
wait
what who said that
where
oh my God she really wants to die oh
okay
is probably imposter that's why she
didn't leave she wants to stay and pass
well she said please oh man you want to
be cute all right movie we'll give you
some more time to get some kills
kill all our Chiara here I just uh go to
mumeso if she was the first one or maybe
we can just start a game
uh mermaid if you if you get voted out
you'll still get killed I mean you'll
suffocate
really
okay
all right we'll give you until the next
meeting and then
um
yeah where was the party where did you
find the body Cobble I found the body in
front of
Communications between Communications
and communication and I was I was uh
um
so that's why she's staying the last
time I saw Cali was somewhere all right
we'll give you until the next meeting
or to kill as many people as you can
[Music]
all right
laughs
[Music]
here right now
hello
I have a task up here
yes I do
foreign
[Music]
wait this thing still works if there's
no power Oh no I got turned back on
already
I have a task over here in the bathroom
I do this
foreign
who clogged the toilet
all right to the armory
all right I might as well do it while
I'm here
listen bye
hello where the lights were off so I
couldn't tell
electrical
an electrical that's pretty close to
where the body was pretty quick to get
an alibi there huh
which body though there's three parts I
found zeta's body in cargo bay and it
wasn't there a moment ago I think but
the lights were off so it's hard to tell
I didn't
um
at the very top
an alibi for for Oli and gura because I
saw them and we were we were near the
kitchen first and then go to security
and electrical we haven't go to medical
and cargo bay yet so
what is what's uh what is
I was in cargo bay why I went to us and
also why Kiara is not screaming at all
yeah
he went when she was the crew I voted
to cut me off I did scream are you sure
about that yeah what the [\h__\h]
I don't know I've been I've been I've
been uh watching all of you guys
um you know
Sound by on the previous uh previous
games
Kiera Kiara really loves to scream when
I ever met anyone that's when she was
scared that's because we weren't too
surprised that this body was dead huh
and I know that you are scared
I didn't anymore
were you with Ollie the whole time
you saw them last minute okay
yeah early predictions Kiara and Ollie
or it could have been Muna and Ollie
married for my life I don't know
sure you are Ali
it would have been good to know where
gouda she said she saw them last minute
but hello ah why are you going that way
instead of this way
safe for now
hi oh you already did it hi I just saw
Ollie and she was going the opposite way
of the electrical light so
so see
my tasks
foreign
what's this little arrow it's gone
oh it's right there
[Music]
how to get up there
yeah I'll just do this for now where's
it
[Music]
how do I get up there
okay [\h__\h] this I don't even need to go
up there
thing that's over here
yeah I'm gonna go do this stuff over
here
probably not that important right
[\h__\h]
I'm gonna hi I'm stuck
okay let's go let's go thank you wait I
have to go in here uh me too I had to
upload the data
okay
ah
all right
I hate it I'll just wait for you
close
need the electrical thingy
[Music]
why did this just go out again
Ollie
very says
she ran away
is it because there's a body close by
she doesn't want to get caught
I just hear her she's out there
so it says Ollie's over there be careful
no I'm I'm just looking at guns
I thought for a second while doing the
gun test that you could uh
that you could pick it up and like use
it
hold on let me do this
ask really quick
what's this
oh
uh-oh what happened hello
it was Ollie
yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai going
towards where Ollie was and that was the
last time I saw her
oh really did you see on your way there
or over there
we actually put ways no I didn't see the
body I pressed the emergency button
oh okay you didn't see the body yeah
you didn't see the body
I really wanted to check up anyone's
bed or you're the last one left and you
want to try to vote people out
[Laughter]
[Music]
Shape Shifter because you didn't say
anything but I guess oh
yeah why'd you call a meeting what the
egg
just stop the tasks is that it
okay fine well you know what I'm done
with my task anyways so like maybe I can
just go chat with the girls you guys can
vote me up if that's what you guys want
I might just [\h__\h] with the Ghost Dance
I bet you can already hear them
yeah they're like no Ollie no don't true
all I wanted to be is us all the time
maybe it's gonna so maybe it's cold
what do you mean I'm allowed now
whoever what is this
I have no idea I've been stuck in
electrical so on the stupid voted
we might this might be the end of us
we either win or we lose here right
laughs
[Music]
oh
oh shoot
okay no go go no combo now have
gooder than she sounds too happy
could have sounded too happy
foreign
I would have already been dead right the
game would be over
if it was both
what the [\h__\h]
why are they trapping me in here
hey
let me out
[\h__\h]
okay I was close at least I got Kiara
right oh that's funny
that's funny
I'll take hello what is that weird who
is breathing it's really strange
combo
damn it I just think she's just happy
from winning
she's just happy from winning guys
morning
every time that Kobo is the Imposter
it's incredibly difficult that should
tell you whenever people are dying
really fast it's definitely Kobo
don't cry yeah she's so quiet
[Music]
I was right with you Kiara salty huh
so you gotta take it out too early
foreign
[Music]
I feel comfortable now
congratulations Cobo you sounded really
excited
let's go let's go
nice chat
[Music]
finally let's go
where is Kitchen I want the Webkinz mini
game
time to do my tasks I like being an uh
what is it oh crewmate I like being
crewmate
I like doing the tasks
six five eight five four
okay
not good
no you won't be able to help yourselves
I love the sound of the propeller
what
hey what once again
no no I thought it was your body I
thought it was uh no rain is dead so
here's what I found I was picking up all
of the towels and [\h__\h] in the shower and
I said I hope gura doesn't kill me a
girl is fine I don't think that she did
it but I went to the left and uh we were
in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta okay well let me tell you where
I found the body first before you start
pointing fingers okay I don't think she
was playing she was just saying let me
tell you where I found the body you just
immediately jumped it
from the left from the left of the
shower walked up and in that photo room
we're all like it's like a dark room I
guess that's where I found the body I
didn't see that there was a dead body in
there because the lights were out until
it said report Netflix report and I
guess Renee was killed in the dark room
so that's all I have to say about that I
literally was just cleaning up the
shower was anybody down there
electrical
S I was at electrical showers okay I was
at electrical and I saw no one yeah I
saw Zeta but I was there
where where I was at electrical I have
my time I was at the bottom right of
electricity
no I didn't finish picking them up I
thought I did but it wouldn't let me put
them inside of the hamper thing so I
still have to grab a couple towels I I
whatever I am shuffling with only
because that was in the electrical I saw
I was in the electrical I was in the
middle I was in the middle bottom and
see that he was in the bottom but I
didn't see it Cali says
[Music]
foreign
sounds a little too happy there
[Music]
enjoying her Alibi a little too much
hello
for this scary cruel world stay away
from me Callie
get down there
I need to go down that way
I wanted to do my best
[Music]
hey
seems fine hello
it will be weird hello hi oh this one I
don't remember this one ah
foreign
[Music]
when I'm a crewmate oh so uh that means
you're the Imposter
um
I I I pass uh on always I pass on
Ollie's uh in the in the electrical I
was doing because I wanted to do it and
then after that she's going up and then
I saw I saw
I ran into Ollie after
she was saying and I quote
[Music]
oh yeah
the first time the first time only said
that she was an electrical but I didn't
see it and then the second time you know
we we had to teleport first right and
then after that she said you know I'm an
electrical I find you and after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie pass by going up uh and
then I was on my my aunt task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
all right
actually I wish your partner good luck
Ollie whoever was with you
hopefully can do this alone
been pretty quiet
gotta be careful the next one might be
insane Bond
is it actually Ollie
is
[Music]
everybody voted
for herself
maybe it wasn't her
okay maybe it's Karen she wanted to vote
Ali off
I don't know anymore
hold on
I'm going
[Music]
oh
break I don't see any notifications oh
they're just hello
where's this so oh it stopped
[Laughter]
mm-hmm
oh yeah
where
like a second ago oh from the alarm like
as she finished the alarm and then she
walked to the right side towards the
records Lounge Etc
who found the body
is it that Best Buy
check like around the showers and then I
go up a bit and there's Anya's body
there yeah Cara was pretty close
yeah
yeah but I was asking me again
I was coming from the left side
uh-huh
come on come on we need we need
I wanna I wanna
Shape Shifter accessed here
we don't know for sure but it could we
don't know for sure I don't know I don't
know but uh me neither but she's like
she's like uh you know when police tried
to do her out there has been quiet it
says
[Music]
because I because I know what if it's
not me what if there's
wait maybe it was Kiara Kiara voted
really fast why are you so convinced
oh it's not ourselves I'm is voting for
me again isn't she Kara why'd you vote
so fast we don't really have that much
evidence and you were really quick to
get Ollie out huh
[Music]
taking him for a while
sorry
bye
[Music]
I didn't even have like 10 seconds of
gameplay
[Laughter]
[Music]
you guys figured it out heck yeah
good job everyone
[Music]
that was a great job
that was my alarm sorry
I got imposed for a single time me me
it's always Cali and gouda yeah
burgers
no I do a terrible job as imposter
anyway
I like you in my past to help sussing
people out you know this game is like
never end I feel like I want to play it
until I got a me too sorry
yeah it's addictive
I don't mind playing more but I'm just
worried about the ID members because
it's like you know it's crazy
it's fine because I usually
at the morning
oh I can keep going
on
okay let's go okay
[Music]
yeah all right one more
oh
[Music]
thank you
I feel like it might actually be always
she's like the type Maybe
that'll say oh no me again but she's
like being for real you know what I mean
as like a reverse psychology
it's a possibility
is what I'm saying
okay I'll get uh this one in the cockpit
excuse me
downloading give me
give me give me give me
did I get it
everybody else is gonna get the power
stuff
I don't need to worry about that oh
hello let me in wait who is it
okay thank you
what are you doing
oh
my self-report self-report
ation
oh come on give me
first come on
one more time I don't want to talk
anymore
[Music]
it was it was in the hallways it was in
the main hall actually yeah
okay
yeah so uh I was I was I actually uh saw
her through the showers I went to
electrical a little bit and I went back
to the main hall and yes this I actually
met another Ollie so if you guys said
anything like oh my God no there was
actually a doppelganger and I actually
like this story
listen she was teasing me down and you
know what even if you get
me a gun and we're not gonna kill you
okay
[Music]
because I don't know um
ourselves always just like very very
nice
if you guys want to [\h__\h] me up and vote
me off because I'll do the task easier
that way anyways I can just fly now
[Music]
what happened
no hi do you want to see a magic trick
no thank you
then I'm about done with this task wait
oh I'm missing a town oh yeah and
they're more like down below
on here uh
leave me alone go away go away yeah
somebody's here Kiara just saw me
she knows you're gonna kill me if you
kill me
no I'm not gonna kill you yeah it's
probably because you just killed
somebody else over here who'd you kill
who did she kill
me
hello
hi
how do I get up there
oh I have to like go all the way around
hello
um
wait there's a body here who is that
rare right here
okay it wasn't gonna
yeah oh Dolly gets a pretty name plate I
want it me I mean I have I have an alibi
you do you know so I was I was on the
first I wasn't security we train it if
if by the way closer I've been I've been
with rainy uh for like a couple of
seconds I'm not killing her at all so if
and then I got to the Middle Town
Kiara quick to point a finger huh
I passed I thought at least Gorham at
least at least Gora like girls were like
was heading towards the showers I think
or the main hall I don't really remember
to the right and then I think Ollie was
asking like have you seen girl okay it's
definitely ugly
or something
instead of trying to show me a magic
trick
I feel like I wanted to show a magic
tricky I'm just telling what I saw okay
I mean um
okay I don't know yeah Luna and Ollie
maybe yeah I feel like it's the only is
fine I was alone I can't say that I was
around Muna a lot but she never killed
me but okay
nothing to say for yourself
is it because you're also an imposter
and you want to save her yeah but the
thing is I don't know Anya Anya was also
there but Anya is also dead but girls
also dead
I haven't heard Ollie say anything I
can because
oh sorry don't vote for Ali vote for
Kiara I want to go to the right cards to
do another thought and then I saw what's
up it's a tie yeah I reported the body
uh
Kiara says
did I stay away from me
she's gonna show me a magic trick
I don't want to see it
the magic trick will be ending my life
no thingy
nothing
hi
hi there hi
and that actually makes sense you're
right
yeah like if somebody ever says that
my friend it does
I know who did it
like oops
oh
hey hi
I couldn't hear what you said what
is trying to kill me
I'm gonna kill you
why are you following me
I'm gonna try to kill you hello
[Music]
wanna help me
hello help me why
I don't know yeah right
she's below left if you want to see a
magic trick
well then wait why can't I do this wait
don't don't uh don't show me the magic
okay I'm not looking okay now you can
[\h__\h] wait hold on
wait wait hold on wait I'm not looking
I'm not looking
she killed me and trampled Over My Dead
Body
shoot
task in the
right
let's go
yeah go this way
please don't kill me wait wait wait wait
oh wait
back
oh yeah now she can't reach me
I wonder if she's gone yet
don't fix that or is that I mean you're
still alive I'm so happy
that was this my imagination didn't
really
uh oh yeah hello what happened what
whenever
I want to say
it's cool
because
like previously when I was the Imposter
with Google
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know one died
but that's because she's a very hesitant
killer she did that before too I was
watching her and she passed gouda alone
a million times and she just would not
kill gura for whatever reason she's very
hesitant and she goes always always to
the electrical to
practice if she's doing that task but it
takes one second
sit there believe me bro we don't have
any proof of her I will I will vow
because the only thing the only thing
that's like for me suspicious is that uh
she's she's being like awfully quiet
yeah she hasn't really said anything up
until about a discussion at all do you
have a defense for yourself yeah do you
have a defense for yourself like why are
you so quiet or you know I'm always
quiet from the beginning
[Music]
a lullaby
what if I really
do my task in electrical I mean why
mommy I'm gonna be so that aggressive
to you too and I know it takes one
second I'm just gonna say rosetta Ollie
and Watson are always together
yes
[Music]
I'll skip
I don't know
I don't have any evidence
I don't have any evidence but you're
really like pointing to people what do
you mean an important to anybody I don't
know hello
wait am I done with all my thingies
I'm done too I'm done with my tasks
done with my
what should I do oh Muna please don't
kill me I know you're the Imposter
what
I have to get a word before she comes
killing me
why are you chasing me
it's minutes
I don't know she's she says Luna says
I finished all my tasks so if you guys
okay
wait do we need power no
we don't need power
actually I don't think we can all go
because there's like a little elevator
thingy
yeah yeah
I don't think we can get on at the same
time yeah
where are we hello okay so we're all
here
nice yeah
um
too late
wanna see a magic week where are you
going she has a task to do over there
but we can't go over there with her
right now okay
you guys found the tasks too me too yeah
I'm done I think rain is the last one
[Music]
I got locked out
Zeta
hold on don't leave me alone
I opened it
[Music]
why did you steal my outfit
hello
yeah go to the other side please thank
you now we can finally be alone so I can
show you
[Music]
trick
uh yeah look
are you looking
yeah
pretty cool right you sound like the
machine
[Applause]
what are you trying to show me
do you see it
I don't know what are you looking at
what are you what am I looking at you
didn't see my magic trick
oh
it must have been too good
I don't want to go over there because
then we can only go alone
yeah I guess so
now did you just come back from killing
someone
okay we're gonna check it down here
oh
my God
where was that
okay
in the cargo bay and she was about to
vent because she thinks she's cool
um and then I saw a red body
okay I just saw Moonah it must be Muna
It's Mona definitely don't you see that
um I was from the Gap room and I passed
by when you are electricity and I go to
the shower and then I go to the cards
again okay I was
I was I I saw I saw I saw I think it was
Kiara and then Zeta Kiara from the
shower too yeah oh okay
which way was Muna going was where is
where is the location of the body
cargo bay I don't know what do you think
in the cargo bay between the door of
medicine Reina and Zeta which way were
you guys going through the showers like
to the left or towards the right no I
was
oh oh sorry sorry Kiara did it
wasn't for me we came from the top to
the bottom and we saw Moonah going the
other way or you saw her going with you
in that direction
[Music]
I think there goes some of them going to
the up to go into the record and then
after so after that I saw
okay
[Music]
I don't know would you say your brain
cannot handle that kind of skill
we will see we'll see if the game ends
now
no it's not me
Watson can vouch for me I think bye
[Music]
nice nice job guys good win
that was fun
I'm born
[Music]
[Applause]
you guys you guys like playing girls
like you guys going to two two groups so
yeah which one should I evolve yeah
make it difficult for you yeah yeah but
you know your speech during the meeting
was actually really scary yeah
I wear the crewmates
[Music]
is
Space Cowboy yeah so hurry up December
20th you got to get all of it
[Music]
I need to detect his hat
yeah nice let's go
please
I think I want to hear a goodbye from
everyone if that's okay yeah bye no no
no no no
yes
[Music]
how was it today oh yeah it was pretty
fun I won an imposter round and then won
all the crewmate rounds or pretty much
all of them so it's you know pretty good
day pretty good game thank you for
inviting me Kiara thank you for setting
it up uh yeah thank you guys for playing
thank you for always sussing me even
though it's me almost never
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I test you
okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impossible but it's fine
[Music]
as long as you have fun right yeah
together thank you
you think knew it was fun yeah yeah
and next we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
yeah so I think I was born to be
crewmate I don't like playing imposter
anyway so I had a good round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your boy that's fine just let it be
and then everyone killed you
thanks yeah you always die first
whenever you like explain something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like yeah it sounded so convincing and
you were not lying yeah bullshitting us
I just gotta work on my longevity in the
game
but I got to do tasks and I love doing
tasks so it was fun thanks for the
invite here I'm just doing tasks I do
right I didn't but I made sure to be the
damn this best teammate that I possibly
could good job
honestly I'm a bit relieved I I was
scared to see what happens if gouda gets
like especially like shape-shift there
you're probably all of you
oh my God that's terrifying thank God I
really want to be a shift there I
haven't got that
come on Coco killer killer statement
today we
wait
could you share those with the rest of
us it's like something so big and these
collabs there's always like one person
yeah I only got it quite a bit too right
like twice yeah I want to say sorry for
uh
um we imposter together with me because
I cannot
um I don't know why but a playhouse room
like a there's
maybe are you sure yeah yeah yeah
like yeah so I'm not that like I felt
that you you seem very proud
if I if I silent for a long time because
uh first I I don't really uh can make a
good execution I will buy maybe in
Bahasa Indonesia uh um it's so easy but
um I don't know you can always use that
as the excuse yeah I used that with the
JP no members please
yeah
you did a good job being imposter Kobo
you're yeah good yeah you gotta get a
lot of kills
yeah
and then we have
to get so many times
[Laughter]
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
like I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually asked us and say oh I'm
actually says
Ali's just messing around but nah yeah
all right
yeah and uh I actually want to thank
Garrison fight especially because uh
organizing these source of collabs is
like a big castle and
well all the most utmost respect thank
you for accommodating all of us in this
collab yay Kiara thank you
[Music]
thank you
is not here anymore
[Music]
oh hello yeah I started the stream naked
in the end naked even though I unlocked
the houses
[Laughter]
was really fun playing with you guys was
fun also to all the crewmates and also
the Imposter you guys were great
and Cali
and then it's gonna be a time for us to
be the imposters
[Music]
that's so much fun I
like
[Music]
two or three I don't remember yeah
it was fun thank you for those who
teamed up with me and thank you Kiana
can fight for hosting it and I want to
apologize because my stream died six
times
how did you survive okay
you're pretty good
I think Zeta killed me more than any
other member
can you talk oh
[Music]
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
are you able to talk
no please
want to leave something in the chat
yeah
you can try something oh there she is
oh oh Discord
oh yeah let's go to Discord everybody
Discord hey
um
oh yeah
[Music]
you did
yay congrats thank you exclamation mark
Oh I wanna buy you have fun Mona I have
fun uh actually uh the first time I'm
doing uh the to become an imposter with
I mean it's really fun
yeah because I miss the one that I'm I'm
usually Alfredo whenever I become an
imposter and because of everyone
if I make it a list it's probably a me
Kiara and then Kali is the one who can
like talk a lot that make me you know
so that's usually the personality
yeah I'm the sheriff hey what was that
surprise there oh well anyway we can
just talk in here yeah yeah we can talk
in here yeah but now we're done anyway I
think I got to hear from everybody I'm
glad that we all came together for
another big Enid collab I think the last
one was Mario Kart right yeah
a year ago that's a long time ago but
maybe since there's a lot of people this
weekend we can try it again sometime
soon
[Music]
um
something I'm having so much fun yeah
and I really don't have any
besides good job everybody hope you had
fun and yeah see you again soon sometime
[Music]
thank you for watching everybody
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah I'm feeling pretty sleepy and
sweaty and a little sick so I'll
probably uh save Super Sunday until
Tuesday I think Tuesday maybe yeah I'll
just switch around the off days and
it'll go Tuesday Super Chat reading
um
Wednesday what's a Wednesday and do the
rest of the week
talking about the schedule for this
coming week
um
let me tell you guys so that you know
let's see
yeah on Wednesday we'll have Watson
Wednesday and then I actually don't have
anything planned oh the last worms
tournament I believe will be on Sunday
night
so not for another week so no collabs
and then uh
yeah no collabs um
this week
okay sorry just scheduling something
okay yep we'll just play games uh finish
Elden ring maybe definitely finish neon
white
start a new game I have a Sherlock game
that I want to play
and then maybe start a new game too
another new game
and uh
yeah okay I'll see you guys soon then
bye-bye thank you for watching I'm gonna
go shower and
pass out
see you guys again hey
[Music]
thank you
foreign