[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] [Applause
]
[Music]
[Applause]
How are you all doing? This day has arrived again this year.  Are you
sitting down? I'm
a bit quiet and won't sit down.
Okay. That's why I was planning to go to Gamers this time,
but it's a little porridge. I'm not
feeling well this time, so I'm taking a break.
[Applause]
Let's get everyone excited.
Self  Let's do some introductions.
[Music]
[Applause]
Before we get into the planning, let's
take a look at the timetable for Negoru Hohorotaku. Click here.
This quiz year-end party is going to
be special.  However, at around 7:30 pm, there
is a winter scene for the Revealing Battle 2020.
That's right. It seems like it
's a project that uses the secrets of the members.
But
whose secret will be revealed? It
's new. And
from 83 onwards, it's the Toretaka Grand Prize 2022, which is held every year.  This
is an annual event, but everyone who is watching this year's broadcast
has voted, so
please look forward to it.
Afterwards, from 9:30 p.m., there
will be a variety show called Hinadan Talk, which will be held in Horo no Yomoyama.  I do
n't know. It seems like the only thing that comes out is Oyayomoya.
What does that mean? It
seems like they're saying they don't care about anything else.
Also, from 11 p.m., there
will be an on-live production countdown live performance,
but here it is.  The distribution slot will be in a separate slot,
so
please make sure to move carefully.
This year's New Year's Eve, we will be
delivering a variety of live shows.
Let's all have the best New Year's holiday together.
Well,
that's it.The more we go about our first project, the more
famous it becomes.This
year's representative is the belly quiz.Decky
[Music]
[Applause]
Teacher,
we're sorry.What's
special about us?Yes, yes
, this is what we saw earlier.The
time table.  First of all, I got a hint of this in the flow and the
opening video.This
time, I'm a special
guest.Let
's go, shall we?
Let's have him appear right away.Thank you
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause] - [
Music]
[Applause] It's my
first time.
Well, I
'm nervous, but I'd
like you to practice Takanashi's character from Phoenix.
[Music]
Please.
[Applause]
Here's to everyone. My butt
has been fixed.
[Applause] It's
gotten a little louder.
[Applause] - It's
nothing.
Well, these two are a bit uneasy today. They
're broken.
[Laughs]
So
let's move on.
[Applause]
Well, here are the rules for the quiz.
But it's going to be a team competition. This time, we're going to
leave it to
Cheese &
Team.
[Applause]
[Music] The
team with the most points at the end of the game will be the winner, so
please do your best.
[Music]
Let's hear about the team's enthusiasm. Hey,
how do you feel about the team's enthusiasm? Well,
today is the first time we've been invited like this.
But the eyes are like this, red and orange.Yes, that's right, the
coloring is really nice.So
, I think I can beat the smartphone chicken.It's probably
hot.Yes,
thank you very much.So next,
what's the deal with the dark burning flame?
[Applause]
How are you feeling? I guess we won't
be able to win on this ship, but we'll do our best. I
think we're a good team. Well, let's
get started right away. The first
quiz is:
Partner, Ishin
Full Body Quiz
[Applause]
N Telegraph Saturday Bow?
I thought of it  Kira-chan knows that you are there.
Just a little bit I
know. Being in touch means having a connection.
That
means being connected with our hearts. Ok, OK. I'll ask you to
try. There
are dummy answers so that you don't get fooled by the dummy answers.10  Second The
first Meiji Restoration Denshin Quiz is
in kanji. You
can read it.
Predict what your partner will choose as the kanji to represent the year 2022.
[Applause] We
'll try to predict your partner's answer.
Can I ask you a question?
[Music] No
more. It's interesting
. It sounds
like it might be something
like, okokok. Please guess what it is.
[Laughs]
This is so cute. My
partner's kanji for this year
is the new b.
Journey
C is the key point
D is
Please answer like
[Laughter]
[Music]
That's it, Corone's ABCD It's
okay, snacks The
fonts are so thick that I can't even tell what title they are in. It
's cute, isn't it?
That's right, this year's
kanji
2022 has gone by in the blink of an eye because it was a bit early for a lot of things.
[Laughs]
So, the Shinjuku ball is over.
[Music]
Well then, let's take a look at the answers from both teams.
Well then, here are the answers.
Don
Oni That's it,
both of them.
Turby:
Why did you think it was a trip? Subaru-chan has been doing a lot of things at the same time this year, like watching movies, playing new games, and traveling to many different worlds. [Music] No, look, why did you
think it was love? No, somehow,
Tiara.  It
's a
cute movie, isn't it?
Because I'm a phoenix, I can go anywhere, and I
have the image of traveling, so I've
always been attracted to here and there.
Let's do it. Here's the correct answer. Correct answer. [Applause] [Applause] [Music] This year we're going to Molodive, going to Romantic Italy, going to Japan, going to America, and probably other places as well, but I forget, but
here and there.  This is the image of me going.
Hey, this year I
cleared Tsubo Oji for the first time.
That's what Tsubo was like in
1971. I've
cleared Tsubo before, but I've never played Tsubo before.
Oh well, next year, please. I'll give you
mental support and try
something new.  You said you touched on it a lot.
That's right, but there are some people who don't have anything anymore
. Really, no, it
doesn't feel like one blow.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Yes,
[Applause] The
next problem is
Yes, guess the sound of your partner slurping soba.
By the way, do you like soba? I'm
not bad at it, but I
don't have a lot of opportunities to
eat soba. I
don't have a decision, but on the
other hand, I'm not in Japan and it's amazing.  I
wonder why they don't do this when they're going to set off fireworks at midnight.
[Music]
Now, I'm going to have one person on the team answer the questions, and the other
person
will be the one who slurps the soba noodles. We'll
put them blindfolded.  I was
looking for a partner from the sounds of soba coming in order.Okay,
first, decide who will be serving soba from both teams.That
's right, for the Uchiha team, I
would like to hear the sounds of soba being sipped today.  It's been a long time
since I last saw it, so I forgot the taste,
so I definitely want to try it. They
also sell soba noodles, so I
can eat them.
[Applause]
In addition to the representative,
Shirakami will serve as a dummy for sipping. I
don't think so.  Yes, please.
I'll do it when I eat. Would you like me to
put on glasses for Netomio
? Is that
okay?
Yes, yes, then.
Blindfold set
[Music]
[Applause]
Area expansion I
hear a peeing voice.
And  There's someone who's the most dangerous.
What's wrong with that? What's going on?
What's going on? It's okay, it's
not heavy. It's
moving.
What's so special about this program? There's a
robot that looks strong.
[Applause]
[Music]
[  [Applause]
Hey,
first of all, the first person is you.
[Music]
First of all, the first person
is the second person.
[Music]
OK, so the
tree is not allowed to make any noise either. Yes,
first of all. Let's call this the first person A.
Alright, A, I think I'm going to sip first.
This is going to test your ears.
[Music]
Okay, okay, so you two just listened to it, and I think it
sounds a bit like who you are.
Huh? I don't
know.  But you're
being honest.
Even if you hear the sound of soba being smoked, you'll be able to
answer in one go who the guy is smoking soba.
Expand your horizons. Yeah, I
thought it was Subaru. What do you think?
[Music]
Okay, then continue with B.  I'm going to go to B, please. It looks like
someone who looks like a dwarf.
Nails.
Yes, that's B's sushi. What do you think? Mio-sensei, I
won't know unless I look and listen for a bit,
but I think
this one looks a bit like a character.
What on earth was that? You
said a sparrow. It's the
same as the one on the right.
Who? It looks
like a Chan.
Who? But
maybe if you listen to it for the third time, it might be
a little cute again. It
has a dignified feel to it.  But yes, the
next one is C. Let's go to C1.
Eh,
it's [ __ ].
Wait a minute, it's
okay. It's okay. It's
okay.  Cheers, do
n't make a toast, you're swallowing. No, I was doing it for a while. I'm sure it's coming. It's coming. [Music] This is ABC's profile. [Music] [Applause] Let's take off the blindfold. Hurry up.
[Music]  ]
Character charge Good morning Good morning It
was delicious
So what's the good thing?
Which of the ABCs was it?It
doesn't matter who ate it in what order, you can take this.It's a
good game for your partner that was difficult.  The
order of the three people
If you can answer the order of ABC, it's OK to tell me more. Are
you serious? I want to think about it a little. If you can answer the order as well, I'll give you another point. 123 Any ABC is OK. Yes, that's right.  I've
heard that Kaedo is really a senior with breasts. It's an
app, so I
tried to appeal to him. No matter
how people think about it, it seems like it's a little weird. The
white team can control cats, so
come on.  What will happen?
Please write down the number and order of your partner. I wonder
what it will be like.
[Music]
Okay. It looks like we have all the answers, so I guess we
went guessing. Let's
take a look at the team.
Here's the team's answer:
Seno Suma-chan
B is a blizzard
C is kiyada
[Music]
- It's
a bit too much,
isn't it? To eat soba, I thought that Chiara, who doesn't have much family, might be C. It's a
bit too much of a field.
No,
that's right,
so it seems like this is the
order. Let's
take a look. Is it
possible? 1 Subaru 23 Chiage It
's exactly the same. I was
a little worried about the number 1 Subaru being A.
[Music] I
was worried about everyone except Mr. [ __ ].  Yeah,
that's true after all. I think C is 99% correct here too.
I see.
So, Ryo-chan, the answer is the same. Let's
go with the correct answer.
Well, let's start with person B and person B.  I think I put it in the body etc. The
person who was B
was Suzume and that Oshirogami. He
gives off the feeling that he doesn't like sipping.But
what happens in the surf?
Let's get into it.Let
's start with the picture.  People
[Music]
Okay, I wonder why they're doing that. They
can do it when there's nothing in their mouths.
[Applause] They're
really good at slurping, but it
doesn't do anything strange. I guess it's a
cultural thing. When you
make noise, your mana drains.  That's too bad. I've
never learned how to serve it.
Thank you. It
was silent, but it
wasn't empty.
3rd
was the piano.
But I'm happy to eat soba for the first time in a while. Hey,
Japanese food.
[Applause]
Delicious.
[Music]
Okay, so we'll
get 2 points for the team.
So, can we just say a little bit
about what's going on right now?
How about the management?
Sorry, okay. Let's take a look at the points at this stage.
[Applause]
[Music]  ]
What's up
? I guess they can understand something because they've been together for so long.Actually,
that's because they
have too many wig points.That's
a bit painful.I was
looking forward to it, but I'd like to see a comparison between the two of them.
Here we are,
let's try it out.
[Music] It
smelled really nice from earlier. They're
really, really into it.
[Music]
Everyone's making out. They're
trying to do something unusual.
[Applause]
[Music]
[
[Applause] That's cute! It's time for a break. Since you're here, there's a quiz corner that I'd like to try. Yes, this time I'm going to try it out. Listening in English, a standard variety show. [Music] I'm going to ask you to
play a message game in English.  Let's put
your English skills to the test. I Can't Speak
Sorry
[Music] I
can do it,
but I'll
pass it on to the next person over and over again, and at the end,
if you listen to it, tell Chiara-chan the
English text of your message.  Please,
eh, are you okay? I can't remember. Please
remember, thank you.
[Music] Thank
you. We
go around and
finally succeed.
How confident are you with your English? The
other two are a little confused. Why doesn't the universe listen to you?
Nesora-chan and others.  You seem to be pretty good at English,
but I can't give a hearing.There's a
famous English phrase created by Ok Ok.What do you remember?  I felt like a Mim.
This time, let's make sure we get the message
right and make sure we don't end up in Senkyu Forever.
So here it is. This is a game that has nothing to do with anything specific,
so both teams would like to play it in the future.
Tiara-chan  For those who are going first, I
haven't called everyone yet [Music]
Hey, let's take a look, let's do this. The crow
will answer properly from the container.
Alright, first of all, I'm going to share the topic with Chiara, and I
'll show it to everyone who's watching.  The three
of you, please look down a little. Yes, behind you. Look down, please. I
understand. Can you remember? Are you
okay? Well,
first of all,
let's send a message to Mio. Let's
cover our ears for a moment, okay?
That's right
[Music]
Good luck,
good luck. I
went there as soon as I could remember.
Ice cake.
What? I
got it. Ok, it was
amazing, but it was in English. I
really
want you to answer. Please answer.
Oh yeah, what do you think mochi means in Japanese?
[Laughs]
Combine with mochi, combine, let's combine.
[Music]
[Applause] I
'd like to ask everyone a question. I'm
sure it
was a prize. Part-time job chocking on
rice cake
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sure it's
because there are no points.
I'm just talking
about the honest world of facts, which is a bit of a
show off
.
Please don't look down on me.
[Applause]
Well then, for Mr. Kihara and everyone,
here it is. It's
longer than the previous one. It's
true.  That's a bit fast.
Learn it.
[Music] Now
that you've memorized it, let's go right away.
Let's go first.
[Applause] Please give me
the answer one more time. Give me a star in front of Zaken-chan.
[Music]
United
Reading
Ennandakke the end  Oh, it's
the
last one, isn't it? Everyone at the meeting. United Meeting. I can't remember the last one.
Bomb Bourbon
[Applause]
Style
[Music]
That's United Meeting Club.
[Laughter]
[Applause] Yes, that's
correct. Is that correct? I'm not 100% sure.
ButOk
[Music]
[Applause] There's
really nothing left to do...
[Music] Oh,
wait a minute, wait a minute, the
words I told Cody and Konni
said different words, so yeah, I did
n't understand, but what does it mean?  Do you
think that's what we heard?
Ted,
we've already
eaten the sad crab. It's dark.
[Music]
But, but,
there's something about that final phrase.  I feel
like we're all connected.In other words, when we eat a crab,
we're all
connected.
[Music]
So, we
played a message game in English, and everyone was connected.Now, it
's a team game again.
[Music] [
Music]
Here  I'm going to ask representatives from both teams
to express various questions using gestures.
Those who know the answer, please answer as many as possible.
[Music]
I'll give each team 1 point, so
please do your best.
[Music]
First, let's ask the representatives of both teams.  Decide who will do the team gesture.
Which one will do it?
I want to do it.
[Music]
Maybe we'll have one person at a time. Then,
concretely,
with the two of us in pajamas, please decide which one to go with. Eh,
which one will do it first?  Kako-senpai,
if you want to do it, please do so. Well, I'll do it first.
This is for construction work, so you can answer with all three of you
.
[Music]
Okay,
okay. The three people behind me, please don't look at me for a second.
everyone is here.
[Music] I see.
Just express yourself with gestures.
So please deliver it to me. Now, all three of you,
please look at my face.
Okay, let's go.
[Music]
This is it.
This is it
[Music]
Minecraft Minecraft You can go ahead and move on.
Yes, yes, please go ahead and trouble Mr. Hakuta.
Let's go. Here's the next question. Please
do it without voice. The
movements are  Of course I've seen it before,
but it's
okay if you understand this movement, so yeah,
maybe something like this. If you
can do it, please
lower it. The
three in the back did it. Please give it to me.
[Music]
Rabbit
Rabbit  Apparently it's a club
activity.
[Applause]
Please give your answer.
[Music]
[Applause] [
Applause]
[Music]
Next question. Here's the question.
[Music] The
three people behind me, please look up.
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's a lie.
Bird
Photosynthesis
Individual got the correct answer.
[Music] The
ping pong doesn't play.
But Tiara got it right.
[Music]
[Applause]
Phoenix When you
try to express something like that, this is what happens.
That's not right. Sorry.
[Applause]
Okay, let's see. Are you
coming to make a heart? I'm in suspense. I
can't believe it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
Yellow team,
tell them to see you next year. They do
n't really get involved with us. They're
feeling quite hurt right now.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] It's been
like this for a long time.  I wanted to participate,
so I'm
really happy.Everyone,
except for Subaru-senpai, I don't like
him that much.I'm
so happy to be friends with him.I'm about to
cry, thank you.
[Music]
Nine, I'm so happy to be able to appear again this year.  I
hope
everyone has a good year-end and will do well in electronics.
[Applause] - I'll
do my best next year.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Well, that's
okay. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you very much.
This is the year.  That's all for
now. There's still more to go. Have fun.
[Music]
Everyone, it's finally
time.
[Applause] -
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
[Music]
[Music]  ]
This year is already over.
[Music]
Somebody reply and this year is already over.
-
That's right. I
guess it's
bullying. I want to go home. Get motivated.
Hey,
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yawn What's up with Yawn? Yes,
there's things I've left behind, things I've left unfinished.
Yeah, I want to go out and play a lot. [Music] No, but anyway, come on.  Is
n't it boring?
Well, it's New Year's Eve,
so it's okay. Well, it looks like we've done it all this year. All we have to do is wait for it to
become very popular and then
start everything. Hey
everyone, it's the end
of the year. It's New Year's Eve, so it's a wonderful time for
everyone to watch.  It's being streamed at the same time.
[Music] We're
taking a moment, so let's all stop
lazing around and
play something. It's just a perfect place to be. Hey,
let's play a board game or something.
Let's play the video.  It's
okay to have fun filming.
You don't have to follow the script. Let's
stop. Let's
go home.
[Music]
Thank you, thank you
.
Hey, it's finally going to get weird. It's
getting weird. I'm
always forced to play roles like this.
Hey, you guys are trapped
in a world of secret games where you compete for treasure. What's
that?
You don't seem to be
having any fun. From now on, you'll be divided into the Nicolette duo and the Shishibata duo, and you'll have to fight for position and compete for treasure.
Let me explain to you if you fight even if you fall down.
You can earn points by collecting the treasures placed on the squares while expanding. Yay. In
order to get the treasures, you need to complete the
overall process.  It
would be naive to try to get the treasure for free, so
to get the gold coins, an
embarrassing story about one of the duo, and
to get the jewels,
reveal the secrets of the Hololive members,
and
In order to get the treasure chest with the most points, I
'll have you guys reveal your secrets.
[Music]
Can't you steal the enemy's territory and treasure
?  There
is also a
special rule like this.The
enemy's base and treasure next to the personnel
can be set and stolen.
Of course I'll put it in. The
contents of the mini-game and other rules will be
explained during the game, so let's
get started right away.
[Music]
Let's show you the power of business.
Thank you.
[Music]  ] Let's
go, let's do it already. Is this an
embroidery pose?
That's right, it's a pose.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
2022 Winter Camp
Weekly
So yes, first of all,
let's have you decide on your high school.
Well, if I say it's decided, it might be rock-paper-scissors. If I say rock-paper-
scissors, I
won't lose.
[Laughs]
[Music]
What you get will change depending on the defeat. I
wonder if it's better to stop.
This is aone-
shot chance to turn things around.  But
when you can't get to the treasure chest, if you get a good result, you
have a chance to find a treasure chest.I see.Let
's start.
First of all, it's a question of
which one to reveal, but I guess I
'd like to go with the one with more points.
[Music] I'm
sorry, but now,
Mr. Hoshimatsu, whose secret are you going to reveal? Then,
eh?  I
look at the night sky, but I
'd like to ask you a secret about how I look at the night sky.Yes, this is
Mel Yozora's house.I talked about the time I went to her house, and I
visited her.She's a
mother, so
she has
furniture,
[music],
game consoles,
everything,
everything.  It
's all white.
[Laughs]
People like me are working hard to make it exciting
.
[Applause]
[Laughs]
[Music] I'm
sorry.
[Music] It's
2 points for ore and 1 point for gold coins, but I'll
go for the gold coins.  And the dice
will probably get the next one. Ah, I see.
[Music] It's
going to be one of the embarrassing stories.
Which embarrassing story will you go to? Which one will you
do first? [
Music] [Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Please  I
wonder what Botan-chan's embarrassing story was the other day. Eh, when we started a bonfire, I tried to toast some marshmallows. The cat in Majima ended up burning all the marshmallows. It's embarrassing. I can't even toast the marshmallows. You saw it, right? It's a comment. I
'll give you 1 point.  Let's
move [Music] I'm moving
Admission and Combi It
's
fine, it's
random, I've decided on a random one Well, this is
gold coins Yes, it's a combination It's an embarrassing story for one of them,
so which one is it?
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I'm
going to tell you something embarrassing. Yes, please.
Yes, this is it. We
all took an embarrassing bath. The bath
was a hot spring.
Then,
when we soaked in the hot spring.  There
was a scene where Mikochi went crazy and
there was a scene where she washed her head.
[Laughs] She looked
really embarrassed.
[Music] It was
really embarrassing, so I'll give her 1 point for this one.  I'd
like to go
for a walk. This
is a great chance to play the dice.
Okay, no dice.
Level: It
's okay
. Basically, it's better if the cat grows a big bud.
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
With the jewels.
[Laughs]
[Music] I'm
excited in the summer
depressed
[Music] That's a
good thing, too. It's
just right, because you can enjoy two different types.
Now, 2 Comments Where did the team go?
What should we do?
There's a treasure chest.
[Music]
Here we go
Hey, are you okay? You might be a bit dangerous. No, no
.
[Music]
[Music] The
secret things that Hollow Live members do. There's no way to do it.
Cat
[Music] I
sold Mel-chan earlier. I wonder
if it's an episode.  Okay,
whose secret is this?
Mio-chan's umm, there
was a sports day, wasn't there? Well, we
went to the studio this time, right?
That city and Japan, you know, that day. Good morning,
big
baggage.  I
thought I'd shut it up when I brought something like that, but when I looked at it, I found it was a
big,
transparent box filled with stuff like the ones sold at candy stores.I
ended up bringing a lot of things that looked like they were for business use.
[Laughter]
[Music]
To Mio-chan
Now, where do we go? No matter where we
go, it's already there. So we can go, we can go
. How does it feel?
But if I take it, I
want it back. It's
still the next turn.
But
then, this is the
secret bomb of the duo.
Now look at me
[music] I
think you probably don't know
what I've said. I've said it before. I do
n't know.
I haven't said it yet. Maybe I'll
go.  I'll tell you if you've never
done it before. Yes, please. Then I'll sell it to you. [Laughs] It's a girl's secret, but yes, after I take a bath, I go to bed without using the hair dryer. [Laughs] Or no, but if I dry it, it'll be
straight forward.
[Music]
But you know, when you
wake up in the morning and say, "Good morning," you're doing it. You're not wearing it,
but it's kind of normal.
But you're not saying that you don't use the hair dryer. No, you're not
saying
this.
Hey 4
[Music]
[Laughter]
Rotation
[Music]
[Applause]
Well then again, this is really a treasure chest. We have no
choice but to go, let's go. Hey, hey,
here we are. The
duo's secret skull has 4 points.
Now, what's your secret even though we've never stopped? That's why
we don't have any episodes like that. No, it's a combination secret box.
I'm sorry, I have
n't had much fun in my private life.It's a
business, so I thought it
was just the two of us, wondering if it was revealing secrets,
or we went out a
lot together, or went out, or went
out to a house or
something like that.I recorded it only once.
On the way home from school, I had dinner
because it was already late and I wasn't eating anywhere else, so my
sister made dinner for us,
so it's like our night, and that's what everyone calls Sui-chan.I've
even had a captain.
Yes,
but what is this?
Destroying the dreams of people who hold such high hopes and
precious secrets. I
would like to give you four points.
[Applause]
[Music] I
feel like this is the case.
[Music]
Please choose who will be the representative.
[Music] I wonder if they're
always eating well.
I'll do my best. Having
two people compete is a
one-legged showdown. See
if you can handle it, then get ready. Are you sure you want to
experience it? Yes.  So, let's
stand on one leg and have a showdown. Start. Please
raise your legs just a little bit.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] This pose is
a little
weird. We
could spend hours like this. Please lift your
legs a little. [Music] [Applause] [Applause]
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] Let's
go
[Music]
[
Applause] [Laughter] [
Laughter]
[Music] [Laughter] [Laughter] [Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter  ]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [Music]
[Music] [Applause] [Music]
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music] [Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Treasure Chest  So it's a secret box with a 4-point combo.Next
up is Ajaa-
chan. What's coming? I've never said this
before.
[Music]
Please,
Button-chan, yes. I
can't get on a plane. [Applause
]
[Music] If it's a
plane, it's 2.  Why take the Shinkansen when you can go there in an
hour? How many hours did it
take? In the end, it took 6 and a half hours. The
return trip was of course
amazing.  I
'm going to get off. Well, it was the cat earlier. I can't leave it to you. Don't be silly. Is it your friend? Yes, it's poisonous. [Music] Yes, it's 1. [Applause] It's going to be an embarrassing story about either the cat or the duo.
Which one's embarrassing story?  Which one of those
two things did you have to talk about earlier?
[Music] I
went to my new house. Yes, I
went to the second floor here at Watermelon's house.  It's amazing,
isn't it? It's even more amazing, right? [Music] [Laughs] It's a stream, but when you have that equipment, it's so cool, it's so cool
, and you're kind of smug about being able to use it.  I do
n't know. I ca
n't use it. How
do I use it? When I moved, I bought a lot of new equipment. I thought I was using this machine, so I bought a lot of things at that time, and I also bought a lot of things that I probably wouldn't use.  I was able to
buy a pen tablet, I
changed my monitor, I changed my keyboard,
etc. At that time, I
thought this was the one that the staff often used in the studio, so I
wanted to try it out. Have you
tried using this?  Are
n't you using it?
[Applause]
Okay, that was pretty embarrassing. So, can I
give you points?
[Music]
Personally, I'd like to hear Watanabe's backstory about Holomen.
Fubu-chan
calls it a big doujin.  Well,
when I went to event 2, I
got so excited that I
got a nosebleed.
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I'd love for you to tell me that stupid story, and at the same time, please
go and see the white-haired person who gets a nosebleed at the event. I'll
get that bird back.
Next  I have no choice but to aim for that one
.
[Laughs]
Well, no,
I'm just going to
sell it.
Wow.
[Music]
So that's the
point. Now, Mr. Stars, whose
secret is it?
What is it about Tokoyami and Asan?
Sorry, this is this stream.  This was before the show started.I
suddenly
asked the staff to prepare a story that revealed the Holo side.
[Applause]
Hoshimachi was waiting for departure, wondering what to do.
[Music] I
made a phone call.I called
Tokoyami's father, and that person was that serious.  Even though I
called without any kind of
chat, asking if I could make that call without making an appointment, they
answered and said, ``Hello.''
Isn't this TMT?
So, I...  That's what I said. I
had a revelation. When I
told him directly, the
door
said, ``It's okay, someone is threatening me.'' This
door is just an angel. He
answered the phone right away, and after I hung up.
Moo really
thought that someone was threatening her, and
this angel seemed to be worried, but she was kind enough to say something.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] I'll
give you honey points for sabotaging business.  I think it
's better
if we talk about the duo's embarrassing stories.Okay, let's go
with the gold coins.Is
there any more embarrassing stories about either of the duo?Both of
us have already told them, but are there
any more?
[Music]
When I went to Kyushu for filming, the
train I wanted to take was scheduled to leave in just a few minutes, but it turned out that I might
not be able to get on it.Everyone,
including the staff, was in a panic because of the ticket issue.  We were in such a
hurry that we were all in a hurry to
explain the situation to the conductor, and as we
were saying things like, ``Wow,'' the conductor
kindly told us that we were in 5th place and
asked for another person to get on the train.  So we all went through some
formalities and
decided to post it. Thank
you very much.
Everyone was in a hurry because we only had about a minute to board the train.  When I got to the place where I was going
to board the train,
there was another female flight attendant there,
but her
bag was sitting there in front of the door.  It's like the female flight attendant
thinks it's my baggage and the seaweed is
going to go there.
[Applause] The
female flight attendant panics and says it's not me.
There's no honorific language.  Oh, I
forgot.
No, it's a bit of a wheel stop. It's really close. It's
not that bad.
Thank you for playing such an exquisite thief.
Now, let's move on. Comments.
What are you going to do?
[Music]
OK,
[Music] Here we come -
First of all
[Music]  ]
Please choose a representative.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes, we'll have them look at each other and
tell each other that they seriously love each other, but it's better if they get shy first. Shall we
try it anyway? Yes, it's
about when we couldn't decide.  That's the year I'll think about it later,
but instead of that, it seems like I
love you.Which order should I start with?
Since I'm playing my part, I'll go ahead.I
love you, I
love you.My
hard work, my
efforts, my singing.  By the way, I'm also
working hard on dancing. I'm always
broadcasting for a long time, and I
'm doing my best. I'm
praising you for that. I
love you. That's
bad. That's
bad. Our love is deepening. What should we do? My
love for Sui-chan
makes me think. Cards like this are so advanced.  Grandpa
's
interest and the fact that he
sometimes sings cute songs makes me happy again.
[Music] I
love you. It's a
smile. It's
like a smile. Is it
just as safe?
[Music] Are you
smiling? I'm so
happy that I feel like
tears are about to fall.  Right now,
what I'm looking for from the summary
is the truth of the beautiful summary.The
golden paper that makes
me so adorable and charming.[Music]I want you to accept my love like this.  I
want to call it a grand anniversary that I don't have, but I don't know
if I can call it something.I guess it's
okay to stop at what I asked for.It's
over.
[Laughs]
[Laughs] It
wasn't a final resolution, but even for both of us.  It
was amazing, but it was a good time. I
love you both in a pretty good way,
so it's over.
[Applause] Let
's go. Okay, here
's the 12th point.
Well, miracles make you
angry.
Our story, the
team's, begins.  I'll announce the points
[Music]
Okay, 14 points
[Applause]
Chijishi
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay, calm down. Okay,
calm down. How was it? Something like this. Let's
hear your thoughts on the Bakuro Battle.  Now, it's
better to swallow the loss of a team that was expected to lose. You've heard this before.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Please cancel the squats. How was it? There
was a tea party in the middle of the match, right? That's
14 points.  I hit a lot of different forms,
and I got a lot of points, so
in order to win, I have to do something embarrassing.I
think I'll continue to do dirty things.I'll do
my best, I'll do my best.
No,
I'm sorry, but the captain is a naked woman, so it's
okay. I'm
sorry.
Please keep this in mind.
[Music] It's
kind of like that. Yes, the
captain was actually in the waiting room earlier,
and he
already threw it away on the internet.
Go ahead.  No,
that's why I won't
take any foolish positions. It's the winter camp of 2022.
Goodbye
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
Music] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause
]
[Music]
[  applause]
[music]
[clap]
[clap] [
music] [clap] [music]
[clap]
[music]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
[Music]
[Music] The
more you go, the more you get to the second half.
From now on, I'm going to
do this annual project.Hololive
Shoot High Gymnastics
[Applause]
[Music]
So this year,
I, the brain behind Forox, and
White Coat Retail will be the MC.  Itadakimasu
And today, we have the largest number of participants in the history of the Toretaka Grand Prize.
Please introduce yourselves from left to right.
Mail Senpai: Hello, I'm Mel Yosoda, a member of the
1st generation of Vampire Afro Live, a genius in the sensory demon world.
Please.  Yes, please. I'm
Alice-senpai.
[Music] I
'm Iris. Thank you for your time today.
And
from the box, Senpai: Chaos. My name
is Hackspace, and I'm in charge.
Please. Please. And
Ollie-senpai. You're shaking.
[Music]
End.  Thank you very much for your support,
and Luxury, the
coolest genius spy festival in the world.
[Music] Well, there
are some people who are floating towards the top, but yes.  I
thought I was going to support you as a god, but I
think you're just being noisy.Thank you in advance.I
just want to see you.Thank
you in advance.This member's
en
ID is already mixed with various JPE IDs.Actually,
this is my first time swimming competitively.  It's surprising that there's no one like me, that's
amazing.
[Music] Are you
getting involved with each other this year?
[Music] It feels
like we all know each other, and we can
overcome the language barrier. I'm happy to be able to connect like this. That
means yes.  So, I'd like to
share this with you today on this 6-person plus paper.
Well then,
if I start talking like this from the beginning, we'll run out of time,
so let's move on. This is the
first time I've seen the Toretaka Grand Prize.  There may be some people out there,
so I
'll give you a brief explanation: It's a live broadcast that will be
broadcast by Hololive Talent or officially in 2022. It
's a corner that will announce the recommended points and yields based on the published video.
Cute,
interesting,
miracle.  I kind of like it.
[Music]
None. And finally, I
would like to decide on the Grand Prix winner from among the ones introduced today.
Hey, first of all, I'm really curious about what kind of works are out there.
So, I'd like to start with this category right away.  I
think this is
Live
Toretaka Exercise 2022
Talent Staff Recommended Category
[Music] It's
really scary
[Applause]
[Music]
This is Hololive Talent
Let's take a look at the streams nominated by the staff questionnaire First of all, the
first one.  Let's take a look.
After everyone's 3D unveiling was finished,
everyone gathered together for the broadcast at the hideout.
Here we go
[Music] I
got lost on that day
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music]
[Laughter]  ] When we
all sing together, it looks really nice,
right? I guess you mean height-wise.
Well, let's try lining up. Even ourselves, the
height difference is quite good. It's a good balance.
[Laughs] It's
true.  I'm
looking forward to seeing you all in 3D someday.So, let's move on to the second video.This is the second video and the two people's
broadcast.A
new feature called the virtual space collaboration feature has been
implemented, and it will be released
soon.  It
's a must-see for the two of them who are having fun even though they are having a hard
time with the controls that they are not used to yet.Here you go.
That's how I felt.
[Laughs] It
was interesting
[Laughs]
Okay, so let's
move on to the third one.
Will the treasure be found? It's a
scene that makes you think it's a sunken RTA ship.
Now then,
[music]
[applause]
Wait a minute, is
n't that bad
? You're good at riding just by talking.
[laughter]
So the third one is probably
from the end.  It was a scene from Lamy-senpai, my senior.
[Music] I'm
sure you all played the last one quite a bit,
but that tiny little boat has
rolled over.
[Music] I wonder if it was
suspicious. I wonder if I'll buy it tomorrow
I sometimes come across some sharks, some not so pretty,
but I
think it's pretty rare to be able to get in there for a while.I'm
lucky.I was
sad that I never got to see the amazing Espoir.So, here's the fourth and final one.  Let's take a look at
Hosho Marine's 3rd Anniversary Distribution.The
famous Showa Song Festival from Marin Senpai's Showa Song Festival, where the
video size of the other party is 4 to 3, the
Showa quality of the
opponent, and the other party's Showa production, is now available.
This is a general scene.
[Music] This
is Gakuen Tengoku.
[Music]
[Applause]
So it
was Gakuen Tengoku from the Showa Song Festival and Kamashi Musume.
Are you familiar with the Showa era song festival?My
mother really liked Showa songs, so
I know quite a bit.Today I
heard it for the first time
[Music]
Even after all these years.  It's a great song that will never fade
. I hope you'll watch all of our music festivals, too. It's
amazing, and I hope you'll
enjoy the atmosphere as well. So, that's all
for the 4 works from the Talent Staff Recommendation category.
Let's move on to the next category. The
next category is
here
[Music]
Listener Clip Category
This is a new category created this year.
Easy kills using YouTube's clip function.  Anyone can create a clipped video,
but we
asked our listeners to submit their quotas.Here, we would like to introduce a stream
selected from the quotas submitted by listeners.Hashtags
on Twitter  If you
search for yield target 2022, you
can see a lot of submitted yields,
so if
you'd like, please check it out when you have time for New Year's holidays.It turns out that
over 1,000 bids have
been submitted.
[Applause] When I
look at the cat, I see that everyone is also making clips
while writing recommendations and comments,
so
even if you just look at the hash tag, it's really fun to see what catches your eye,
so please check it out.
Please, let's take a look at the first one.
Thank you Aqua's Aquarium. A
love adventure game starring Aqua Senpai. The
game Aquarium is
a strong Minato
Aqua player. Minato Aqua.
This is all from the scene where she appears. Now then,
please.
[Music]
As a girl, it's
fast
.  [Laughter]
[Music]
That's where the girl was looking at me. Well,
go over there.
[Music]
[Laughter] There
was a battle, wasn't it?
Aqua-senpai was writhing in agony in the aquarium.
[Music]
[Applause]
What if I made it? Can you do it
? I want to stream it myself I want to hang out with myself
[Applause]
Embarrassing
[Music]
Embarrassing Embarrassing? That's right.
When it's released, everyone, please
play it yourself.  I'd like you to do that, yes.
So let's move on to the second video. It's for
Fish and Black.
Chloe plays a horror game called Hell Battle. What will happen if
Chloe, who is famous for hating baths, plays this game?
Well then,
the statue
[Music]
[Laughter]
So the second nominated work is ``
Game characters also take a bath.''
Is Sakamoto A giving advice?
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] It
's a normal scene, but
Sakamoto's bathing scene was
pretty trendy.
[Music] Are
there any of you who actually hate bathing?
[Music]  ]
It doesn't smell bad. It's
true that in Japan you take a bath in a bathtub,
but
in other countries it's more like a shower.
[Music]
When you come to Japan, it's
a public bath or a hot spring. I'd
definitely
like you to take a bath in a hot spring.  [
Music]
[Laughs]
So let's move on to the third episode. Here we go again,
Sakura and
Miko's last stream. Last: A
gambling place where you can put in the scraps you brought in. The
scraps you stole from the seniors at the festival who fell down in gambling are
mercilessly stolen.  The more I get caught up in the running shrine maiden, the more I
bet on 20x, which has the highest odds but is also the least likely to win.What will
happen to the gambling family's fate?
[Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Laughter]  ]
[Music]
[Laughter]
So the third nominated work
is ``A Shrine Maiden who wins big when gambling with other people's money.  You're
working hard to gamble.
[Music]
Actually, I once won 20x with my little finger,
but
when I didn't have any money and only had 100 yen or so, I
didn't make any more money.
[Music] It
was sad.  If you say yes, then let's move on to the
fourth song.
Tokoyami and Ha's 2nd anniversary distribution song was also decided with a bang, and when I got
to my impressions, I noticed that the
three guests were
confused by their unrehearsed movements.
Let's pay attention to the video
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
So the fourth nominated work is
at his 2nd anniversary live performance where he was
pranked by a guest and was
embarrassed.  Then, I was in trouble. I could
n't have predicted that the main character would be pulled a prank. The cast must have been in a good mood.
[Music] It was
a bit of a prank on the seniors and porridge-senpai. They
didn't do it with their hearts in mind.
But you know, pranks like this are being pranked
even after this.  I haven't seen it yet, so I'm sure there will be another one
at some point. It
was really cute, Mr. Door TMT.
Check it out. Now, let's take a look at the last piece.
This one is a collection of short and impactful ones
from among the high-paying candidates that were submitted.
So,
let's summarize.
[Music]
An old man making mochi
[Laughs]
[Music]
Because of the hiragana, there's a cute atmosphere.
[Music] - I
did this.
[Music]  ]
Yeah
[Music]
[Laughter] That's nice
[Laughter]
[Applause] The
last nominated work was a short summary video -
nice
[Music]
Umami-chan,
Zeta-chan had that pet at the end.  I heard that
Kokoro and Senpai had an accident and pulled that thing on a horse, and
behind the scenes, they were imagining a story where Kokoyori and Polka-senpai
would fight together.So,
let's meet up.  As we were talking, I
suddenly got a call
from a person who had been in a terrible accident,
and I couldn't help it anymore.
Please
cheer me up. It's
okay. So that's it for the listeners.
Thank you very much to the recruiting department.  Thank you very much. There's
more to come, so here's the next
category:
[Music]
2022 Performers will choose this Japanese
AR.
Since they're performing, they should let us choose as well.
Everyone at SN.  We asked each player to choose the highest pitch for each one. Are
you confident?
Great. Now, let's
take a closer look at this one, which has such high expectations. First, this
is the one selected by top batter Mel-senpai. Okay, here we go again.
It's a scene from the end of the century game where anything goes, Last 2, where Mel-senpai is acting with Polka-senpai and is concerned about the helicopter circling above. Well then, please go ahead. It's going to
be broadcast in the morning. The
morning broadcast will be around here at
24:40.
24320 It's
scary. I've been
attacked by helicopters a few times. I've
been shot a lot, but I guess that
's what happened.
[Music]
[Laughter] -
Mel-senpai accepts his senior's pranks and gets hit by a helicopter.
[ __ ]
[Music] I
didn't realize that my senpai was streaming. I
didn't notice and thought it was off.
What was it? When I got shot, I hadn't died before. I
hadn't died before.  I was
told that I would be shot if I wore those clothes,
so I still couldn't dance, but that
was an insight.
[Music] That
was sad.
[Laughs] Um, I
had to swallow again from the point where I died and when I respawned, so I feel like I've already
failed.  It was tough
because I'm a beginner,
but I wonder if I can get rid of those sad memories now.It
's the one I chose.I
chose it myself, or rather, Level-senpai.Thank
you, thank you.Now
then, Iris-senpai.  That's it,
Iris-
senpai. What do you
mean by buying new clothes and cosmetics and showing them off?
[Music]
Who is this person?
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Stop it!
So I'm Iris-senpai North, who has been reborn with new costumes.
Congratulations. Thank
you.
Really, um, finally, I can
buy new clothes.
More at the department store.  You can buy it at a super low price. It's cheap.
Thanks to the block [music], I can now shake in many places
.
[Laughs]
Thank you, Senpai. Thank you
. Let's move on to the next one.
From Hololive ID  Luxury A
new student who has started Royale. The
heroine saves the hero who is surrounded by enemies. I
can't help but date her.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Look at that! It
's crazy. The way you laugh is not too funny.
[Music]
[Music] It's been a long time, has
n't it? [Music] [Laughter] [Music] Is it Bestia Zeta-chan, who has become limited by the new heroine and has lost her vocabulary? Well, she's still a little mesmerized, but what about her? Student-chan Wow, I don't know much about files.
That's the first one, the first goddess, so...
[Music]
I'm
definitely a bit like a prince.
[Music] I said
it was cute, so it
was Jet-chan.
Next up
is Hakotaro-senpai.  This is a casual chat stream.
Hakotaro-senpai is serious when answering questions from listeners. It does
n't seem like a big deal, but why is this so
high? Let's
take a look right away.
[Music]
[Music] I see.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] I'm
trying to see if my elbows can touch. It's
Hakotaro-senpai. No, Kotaro-senpai.
It's impossible.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yeah, we're all really stiff, aren't we?
[Laughter]  ]
There's someone who's been bitten by that one person,
Wally-sensei,
what's wrong? Is there something wrong? It
's okay.
Yes, it's okay. I don't think bullying is good.
But the clippings are also
getting a lot of playback.This
year's ``Fire Money'' and a little chat were
broadcast in Japanese, and this year's kanji was ``elbow'', which was
kind of spread out, and it
was interesting that it was my favorite bird high school.  Isn't that
cute?
Thank you for saying yes.Thank
you very much.Next,
let's introduce you to a unique yield.It was
recommended by Olly Senpai from Hololive ID, but surprisingly, it wasn't his
own stream, but one from
ID Junior.  This
is Hobo-chan's broadcast.I
got all excited during the countdown broadcast the day before my birthday,
so let's take a look.
]
[Music]
Where did you get the lighting from
?
So, it
was a bit un-Hololive-like, but what does that mean?
Senpai, what do you think? That
's the preliminary reason why someone crazier wanted to show it. It
looked like fun, though.
[Music]
There are listeners during the broadcast, but
after the broadcast is over,
why not enjoy it on your own?
How can I explain it?
[Music]
Thank you for your wonderful side. It was
interesting. Now that's the last part.
MC.  It meant I could choose as well, so I
chose it over
Eko.Hololive High School, led by the employment director,
Spring Koshien Semifinals The
score remained tied, and the game went
into 11 extra innings, and the
enemy gave away a lot of benefits, so everyone thought it was no good.  The
final attack, with two outs, the bases loaded. Will there
be any chance drama?
Please take a look at the manager's decision.
[Music] It
was 3-3 until the 10th inning.
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [  [
Applause]
This
[Music]
[Music] I'm
thankful to the streaming gods for all of this. It was
such a good
match that I'm uploading a clipped video of it myself. I
think it's even hotter if you watch the whole thing, so I hope
you enjoy it.  I hope you can see everyone's success.
[Laughs]
So, thank you very much.
This is the end of the cast category. The next one
will be the last nominated work. Click
here for the final introduction.
Oh 2022
Yago receives the special award.
This
is also an annual tradition.
Everyone has chosen one for Yaai, who loves it.
I'd like you to check it out. You'll have no
choice but to watch this without any explanation.
Please go ahead.
[Music]
[Music] [  [
Music]
[Music]
This year's Yago Special Award was for disseminating the 3D of Mu na Star Field -
here it is. I
received a comment from the shop name. I
will swim with it. I
was happy. That's why it was selected for the Night Travel Award.
That's what I received.
Not
even at the third festival.
[Music] I was
moved. My
senior appeared.
Hmm. It's
beautiful. I love this senior.
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay, so now
all the best-shot works will be shortlisted.  All entries have been submitted.
Finally, we
would like to decide on the work for the Hololive Training High School Gymnastics 2022 Grand Prix.
Well then, this time, we would like to collect one vote from each person.
Please send it to the person who said which one you liked best.  Thank you in advance. I
'm worried.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Amoa That's amazing.
But there's only one thing left.
Now, I'd like to announce the
winner of the prestigious Grand Prix of the Hololive Toretaka Grand Prix 2022
.  Music]
Congratulations to the Met duo who are expected to enjoy the virtual space collaboration feature.
[Music] It's
really interesting.
Moreover, it's a new feature, right
? I have high expectations for this.
[Music]
Hey,
[Music] That's
it.  Well then, I'd like to congratulate the two of you.It's not
going to be that simple, but I'd like to hear your impressions if you don't mind.So,
Mel-senpai, well,
even just introducing this just now
has a lot of volume.  But it's
interesting because it's over the line, so I
thought I'd like to see some of the other things that I'm a little curious about.That's because
everyone at Hololive has been streaming a lot and
making it exciting over the past year, so I'll see you
next year as well.  I
want to make fun memories with everyone.
Thank you very much for today. Thank you very much.
That's Alice-
senpai. It's all very interesting, as expected. I
think it's Hololive.
All of the talents are
interesting.  I'm sure this year has been an incredibly eventful year, as we've been broadcasting only moments every day.If next
year is just like this, it'll
be great.Thank
you very much for this time.It
was a lot of fun.
Thank you to everyone who watched. Thank you very much.
Now then, Hakotaro-senpai,
Wow, it
was really quick.
But when I look at the free skates like this, I
think it's amazing that there were so many of them.
Hey, I want to make some fun memories with everyone at Hololive.
Thank you very much. Please
join us.
Yes, I'm sorry, but is
English okay? I have difficulty speaking Japanese, so
WeIthing
tomanythmantomy
everyone.
Thank you for your continued support.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. And
Data-
chan, please speak English too.
[Music]
[Music] I
want to continue to make many memories with you all.
Thank you, Um.
[Music] It's
really the first time.  As I said earlier, when I
watched the Hashtag Photography High School Award 2022,
everything was really interesting.
Thank you for your hard work. I hope
you all use that hashtag and
watch a lot of other members' scenes as well.  I'm really happy about that,
and I want to
continue to do that holo live show in 2023 without stopping.I
think the 2023 Toreko Grand
Prize will be even more amazing.Thank
you very much.
I want to introduce them all to you. There are so many
great talents
gathered on Hololive, and I want you to watch JP, CN, and
ID, so
I'll continue to work hard on my English.  We
will continue to do our best to connect each fan and talent, so please love everyone.
Thank you for your support.
[Music]
From now on too.
Hololive is full of laughter.  Yes, I
hope you enjoy it.
Unfortunately for everyone, the
end time is approaching soon. I would like to conclude the
Hololive Shooting High Award 2022 by watching this. I
hope everyone will continue to
enjoy it.  We hope to continue to build a reputation for
Hololive in 2023, so please continue to support Hololive in 2023.Next, we
will have a Hinadan talk at 9:30 pm, followed by Yomoyama Variety Holo.It's
almost 9:30 pm, though.Thank you in advance.
Please,
thank you very much. Let's
close with a greeting. Goodbye
everyone.
Thank
you. Bye-bye
[Music]
[Applause]
From now on,
our...  Corner
[Applause]
More
[Music]
[Applause] Are you
ready
[Music]?
[Applause]
Yes, there are some people who aren't ready.
Since there are so many people here, let's all say the title call. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
[Music]
In this corner, you can talk about various themes as you like. In layman's terms,
we can talk about wool stories.  It's become a matter of posting a chat and defeating it. I
see. So, this time the moderators are
Full Live 4th generation students Kanatan and Amane.
Canada and Kore Life 5th generation students. Their faces are dry snow skin. Lamy
's
gorilla liver
[  [Music] I'm
going to serve you
Gorilla's Gorilla's Liver Gorilla's Liver
That's why it's Mori Liver, but please remember it today.That's what I'm talking about.Today, I'm going to have
fun and talk about having fun.  It's a
fun
group of friends.
Who are you talking about?
[Music]
[Applause] Who's
going around? It's
starting. Okay, so I'd
like to ask you to introduce yourself a little bit. Since it's
New Year's Eve, I'd like to ask you a question.  I would like to
ask you to tell me about your 2022 episodes, so first of all, let me
tell you about the joyous stories of both men and women, and please introduce yourselves.Everyone, I
'm Shirogane, the Iron Stomach Daimajin, a member of the 3rd generation of Comas Through Hololive.
[Music]
There are many things that made me happy.  But, of
course, in the dungeon, there's something more to it than that, right? Everyone might be giving it
to me,
but I've seen an
increase in the number of times I've been asked to imitate movements from this aspect of the radio.
[Music]
[Music]  Are you trying to
move like this when you're trying to move?
This is the first time I've said this, but I've been
doing these strange movements since I was in high school, and
when I was in high school, people were
saying a lot, but when I
joined Yamazaka Hololive, everyone
imitated me so much.  I didn't expect you to give it to me,
but thank you very much. I
hope you don't stop, though. It
keeps going on and on, and I'm sure you'll be curious to see if it comes out when you come as a
guest at a live show or something.  That
's normal.Next, I
'd like Lunar to tell us about this year's misdeeds.
[Music]
[Applause]
Cute corona bouyon regulations. Various things until I die.
[Music] Well,
what's this? This year's misdeed was when I
entered Hololam and
drank alcohol for the first time, making me vomit.  Did you mean that
Gap Gap Gap was
being streamed or something like that?
Just after the stream finished,
I couldn't hold back anymore and went to the toilet.
This started the trend of getting drunk on Sharp in the middle of the night.
[Music]
By the way,  When it comes to alcohol, of course there's
Lamy, who
has some really interesting ones.
Hey, do you
have any bad stories? When I
found out, I was
sleeping with my own Rainbow at the ticket gate of that virtual Shibuya in Shibuya, so
please be careful.
Let's be careful next year. Let's
talk about this year.
So let's talk about Tide's bad performance earlier,
Rapture. It's amazing. It's a little like Baru. When
introducing yourself, please tell me what made you happy this year.
[Music] Are you
going to say that again this year?
Yamada Well, this year ends today, right?
Well, I was happy.
What made me happy this week is no, this is bad. The
script
is Yankee 4K, isn't it? One
of your favorite movies, Mr. Evil.
[Music] I
told you I was happy, but I'm
starting to see more of you.
Please, Yasuke,
who is as good at live training as Alola,
is highly praised by Kiropeko and Akira.
[Laughs]
Maybe he's been drinking?
This year, I've
been playing a game called Splatoon in my head, and I almost
forgot to introduce myself.
Everyone knows this.
[Music]
[Music] I
thought I could make it if I surpassed it twice, but
no matter how many times I tried, I couldn't.
[Applause] That's
amazing. I've already paid off all my debts, so I'm going to go for now.
[Music]  [Applause] It's
starting to look like that sport,
right? Let's
all do it, too. Splatoon. So far, let's see what we can do. Well, for the last part, let
's talk about something that made you laugh this year. I've
never had fun or laughed.  The
thing that made me laugh this year was that
Jaures
[music] I
took it for granted, so go ahead, I
want to hear more about it.It's a little bit
different, so I can tell you, but first of all, I
suddenly felt like my forehead was
being held down and I fell down for some reason.  I
was told that there was a ghost there, and when I was acting normal, I
didn't fall down at all, but I was pushed as hard as I could, and I was told that I was falling
down.But
at that point, I thought, ``That's not the case,'' and
after that, something like the Edo period happened.
[Music] I was
half-smiling as I listened, thinking, ``Oh, it's all a lie,''
but then they
finally said that it was all over, and just when I
thought, ``Oh, finally, this farce is over,
come out, you're hiding.''
[Music] The final
boss
turned out to be a tengu monster after all.
[Applause]
[Music] That
makes
sense. I don't know, but I'm a little curious as to whether it cost that much or
something. It was like
230,000 yen.  That's not true. Yay
Sakamoto. I
thought that if it was a Pachimon like that, I would get hundreds of thousands of dollars, so I was
prepared for it. This is the worst. It's
like watching a musical.
This one is really unique.  Yes, we are rich.
Please wait with a total of 8 people.
Please make it 7 years.
[Music]
[Applause] I
made a mistake in counting. We
would like to deliver a unit chat with 7 people.
[Applause] [
Music]
Or
[Music]  ]
Well, today I'd like to ask you about a
topic you'd like to talk about or
something you'd like to hear from the members here. I
think everyone answered a little survey, but we'll
mainly be talking.  I'd like to come. There's no script
for the content of the talk.
[Music] I want to make sure it
doesn't cross the border. So,
first of all, this is the
theme that Sakamoto would like to talk about. There's
something more he wants to talk about than slavery.  But seriously, I
just
don't want to see him being shy.
Well, I want to see it.
Everyone talks about the most embarrassing thing they've ever felt recently.
[Music]
Apparently they were embarrassed. It
came out loud and
embarrassing.  Hey
everyone, please raise your hand and say yes, it's
easier if you do it. No,
leader, back in November,
when we collaborated with a certain yakiniku restaurant, we
used coupons.
When I went there, I was alone, and I
knew that I was wearing a paper apron.When I
got home with my hair up, it was a bit
[laughter] I know. People
definitely laughed at me, right?
When did you finally realize that?  That's what happened
when I went home and washed my hands and gargled.It was the
day I walked home thinking I wanted to feel the night breeze, but it didn't
flap around.I
wonder if this is an embarrassing thing that happened recently.  If you ask me to tell you a story, it won't come out.Ah, I
want to hear it, so please try to tell me a little.Since
you will be asked something like this,
don't you prepare something of your own?Isn't
there one?
Story: I've
already talked about something, but
when I went to the New Year's market, I
thought I'd bring some souvenirs with me, but that day I felt really
bad.
If it didn't open, I took a taxi,
but
in the taxi, I
was wearing jeans as my assistant, and I
took off my zipper, so I
got off from here [music] and carried the souvenirs, so I
thought I had some time.  I was thinking about going to karaoke,
but when I saw the order code on the sidewalk and the
permission code, the lady was really on my side, and I was
wondering what the hell, but
the moment I went to karaoke, I realized that.
Everything is in full
view, in full view, seriously, and
suddenly suddenly it's
hidden.In
full view, wow, it's completely visible.No
one really
said anything, not even the store clerk, but
even the store clerk clearly looked like something,
but that's not how I thought it was fashion.  It seems like
this kind of thing is popular. It's the
same with the story about the dungeon earlier.
Surprisingly, the store clerk and
other people will do it for you. It's
tough, isn't it? It's
embarrassing because you'll be made fun of later. I
want you to say that. Yes,
yes.  Yes, yes, that's an
embarrassing story. I
wonder if there's anyone else out there. I wonder if there really isn't. It's really embarrassing, but the
listeners say that it's me who
has this tendency to misunderstand things, and it's embarrassing.
Oh,
for example, what is it?
This kid likes me a lot.
[Music]
Oh, there's the misunderstood gorilla. I
heard some really bad things, but I'm
being called the misunderstood gorilla. I can't climb it. It's
really amazing. I woke up because of some kind of hand-wringing.  I
feel like something's going to happen to me, but it's okay. I like you a little. But hey, he's just the prince of Hinadan. Everyone, Hinadan-san. That's why I don't like men. Hey, I understand, but if it can't be helped, uh, I
was sleeping the other day.  Yes, I'm
tired. Are you going to release this already
? I'm going to release this. You know, this is really the year 2022. I
want to be in the top 3.
[Music]
In the middle of the night.
One side.  My butt has gotten a little
tighter.If it
looks like it, I
thought it would hurt, so I squeezed my butt.The moment I squeezed it into my butt, I sucked it into my butt.The
muscles in my butt are connected to my thighs, so let's
start
from here.  It's really
painful, but I'm really alone on my futon, crying, and it's already
hurting. This isn't a painful story. But it's probably an embarrassing story. Everyone's so kind, they're already moving. I heard this story in the dressing room earlier, and I was laughing so hard I was dying.  Yes, I
laughed, but it was a bit of a big bomb
. It was unexpected, but I was a little
embarrassed about the board. I could hear it.
Now, let's talk about the next person's theme. Now, the
next theme is one of my seniors.
This is the theme.
Idol theory
. Is it
okay for us to talk about it? It has already
been decided that we should talk about it. Idols.
After all, everyone is being lined up on the stage.
We are idols. We have
n't forgotten. We are idols.
2022 is the year, after all.
As an idol, I think we should talk about a lot of things. Yes, it's a bit
embarrassing. It's embarrassing. It's
serious. We're far away,
so let's
hear from the two of you who weren't able to talk to us earlier.  I do
n't think it's a good idea. So,
first of all, Luna has an idol run.
[Laughs]
She's an idol, so she
has time. I wonder if she's sleepy or not. It's like she's broadcasting from
far away.
But
idols, like idols, sing.  Let's dance and bring happiness to everyone.
[Laughs] I'm
starting to worry. I'm
already getting closer to that ideal idol image.
Even though I'm already an idol.
[Music]
That's right, that's right. I
forgot. I
think it's beautiful.  That's right, I
always thought it was normal to be asked if I
was an idol, so I guess I'm an idol.Then, Laplace Dark seemed to be the furthest away from the idol man who was
sitting in a weird way next to me.What do you think?
No, I don't like that,
but I
think we're probably the only idols in Hololive who think we're idols.That's why.The
management definitely
doesn't treat us like idols.That's because they really
won't let something like this happen.
Well, to put it the other way around, I
feel like I'm still not used to being an idol.
I'm an idol, so what's a side job
? I do it in my spare time, so
why do I just stay lazy even in Tokyo?
Isn't that enough?  It's okay for
everyone to do whatever they want, but I mean, I have a lot of feelings,
right?
After all, it's a little bit like that. It's
like I'm falling in love with you, and I'm so excited. Now that I've
become an idol, I
wonder what I'll think about next year.  I said I was happy when he made some strange movements earlier,
but I don't think the
leader is wondering if this is okay.It's okay, it's okay.  It's an
idol-like move. I'm
even thinking about doing it next year.
Wait, wait, I'm doing that idol-like move right now. I
want to see them one by one. One
by one, it's like an
audition.
Hey,
last month,
when Noel-san first got me up from my chair, this is
how I was born as an idol.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Please, you're so
cute.
Why don't you try Raku-chan?
I'll go.
[Music]  ] -
[Laughter]
Think of it as a stage.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Let's
find a balance there.
Please don't make any noise. Please
open that door. Thank you, Senpai.
[Laughs]
Idols, after all, start from the idol step.
[Applause]
[Music]
Sexy
[Applause] It
's amazing. It's like that. [Music]
Idol-like movements are nice.
Please wait a moment. I'll go.
Yeah, that's
it. Let's take a look at it again. I
'm saying something I didn't see.
[Music] I've
been able to do double jumps since I was 6 years old.
[Laughs]
Robin, come along too.  I do
n't even have refugees, umm, they've been taken away.That's how
Ramy is, after all, he
always does this when he performs live,
sorry for the camera.
But it's
a bit
weak
[laughter]
Since it was a tempura bowl, I'm not going to say another one
[music]
That's how we
do it, so we'll do some things together,
so it's
not a good fit
[laughter]
Well then, let's move on to the next person's talk topic. The
next
question will be from Aki-senpai.
[Music]
Crepes are cute,
delicious and perfect for idols.  I
think so.So I think it's more of a crepe shop.That's
great.That's why I'd
like to do a stream where I make crepes someday.
[Applause]
Next year, I hope to be able to do something like that.Do you
like everyone's side dishes?
Sweets.  Well, I
guess I'll just ask you if that's the case.The market research is
in G major.I wonder
if I can just say it one by one.Well
, I want you to cut it.The
Kuroi-san next door is very
excited.First of all, I've never had a crepe as a side dish.
[Applause]
[Music]
Well, when I
think of crepes, I think of desserts,
and the Scouters and sweet and sour pork with pineapple aren't
good either, but they're
like the ones with the sweet and sour pork and the pizza with pineapple, okay?
[Music]
Eh, whipped cream,
strawberries, and
caramel.
That's cute. That's what I like best. I think I'll
ask
Dungeon next time. I'll have a perfect side dish for lunch. [Applause] No, I don't mind something like chocolate and banana. But Dungeon is definitely going to
order crepes with tuna and
mayo. Yeah, I've
had that before.  It has a bit of a pizza flavor to it, and it's
super delicious. Why, Aki-
senpai, please give me some of your side dishes.
[Music]
First of all,
Mr. Aki's side dish
is the side dish that you eat with that white rice, and
that's the
difference.  Maybe you've never seen it before,
or maybe you don't know about it.I do
n't know about crepes.It's like a side dish, but it's
salty, and it's
more like a sandwich with something like ham or lettuce in it.  The side dish is the one with the inside lying down. It
's not a crepe.
Just
put whatever you like. I want to put bananas in the crepe. I
ate chocolate and fresh cream.
[Laughs]
My heart became beautiful.  By the way, let's go.
[Laughs] I do
n't like sweets, so I'm a
bit of a side dish person. I definitely don't have
tuna and mayo, so
since they're all the same, I'd like to have a number in the middle as well. They're
clearly separated, but I'll answer them already.
At the same time, after all, it's Gorileba, so it
must have been a sweet or a side dish
. After all, it was chocolate banana
[Music] I
love cream-like things
[Music]
Oh, I've only eaten that crepe twice,
but it was a bit of a crush.  Well, that's not the
case. I wanted to try it, even though it
looked a bit fancy from the bottom
and I couldn't eat it,
but I thought it was a bit
cheap, so it
only had that cream and that syrup in it.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
think I'd like to go out and make some crepes
with everyone next time.I want my seniors to make some as well.Yeah, that's
right.Which side are you on
?I don't
want to give up.As a crepe shop, I
'm stepping into forbidden territory.  Is that
okay? It doesn't have a tarantula in it, does it? It
has the same meaning, but no, the
staff at the tape store can eat one crepe per part-time job a day.
So
put them all in. [
Applause]
[Music] It's
so big, isn't it?  I've eaten something like a bouquet.Does it
have both?It has both a side dish and sweets.
[Applause]
Isn't that the pineapple in sweet and sour pork
?It's
true.Only the
pineapple is a little no-nonsense,
but
it feels like you're putting everything in it.Raw  You mean it's creamy,
right? There's no string or anything.Well, I
ate it just once, and the next time I ate it, I asked for something that was sorted properly.I
see, it's about the taste.Yes, yes, it's pretty
good.  I'm getting excited,
but I guess I'll
just have to ask you about one more thing.If you
make all the dishes I mentioned earlier,
there will be people who can eat it, and people who have already eaten it
[laughter].  [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Flour and sweets go well together.The other day when I
put candy in takoyaki, I joked about it right in front of me.  I've
received some questions from a lot of people, so
let's have a talk
based on those questions.I received a message from the person himself, so please
watch it right away.The
VTR
starts.Good
evening.This
year
[Music]
went really fast.  Well,
thank you very much for your help. My question is about New Year's resolutions, and I'd like to hear about your successful and unsuccessful New Year's resolutions. I'm really looking forward to hearing your answers.  This
year is almost over, so I
wish you a happy new year. I look forward to your continued support of hypnosis.
Thank
you. Your
question is about your resolutions for this year in 2022, and your
successes and failures.
Hey guys, do you
remember what your resolutions were in the first place? Seriously, you
don't.
[Music] I
do remember, though.
[Applause]
[Music] I
remember yoga.
There's one goal that doesn't change every year.  So
yeah, I
guess we'll conquer the world. We've failed every year. Next year, for
sure. Next year, next year. [Music] Next year, I want to conquer the world with you and the cat.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
feel like we're going to fail a bit,
but oh well.  I don't think
anyone remembers that, so
for example, what I thought I was going to do this year, or what I
had set as a goal.
But I think it's okay for
men and women to focus on successes and positive things.Last
year, Hololive finally
debuted, and they
released their first original song in September of last year.Since
then, I want to release a lot of original songs.  I was
able to release three songs this year because I had a
feeling that it would be better. [Applause] So, I feel like I want to continue to do my best next year. Yeah, I'll do my best.
[Music] It's a
similar thing again here,
Sakamoto.  I
made it because I wanted to set the button in my life that went viral on TikTok, so I was
happy. [Applause] [Music] I was happy that I was successful, even though I had never been successful. Wow, it was
just like my personality.
I thought it might be bad.  I
think it's really wonderful, so I'll continue to do my best.
[Music]
By the way, there are people who have
failed. I was thinking of doing something like this this year, but
if I fail, well, I'll conquer the world.  It's a failure, but I
'm failing, but I'm doing this, but the
others don't say anything, there's probably something
I did, so I
'm hiding it.  I'm not good
at relying on my followers for things, so I haven't been able to do much,
but this year, when I
tried to call out to everyone, there were some people who looked like they were going to cry,
but their
individuality came out, and
it made me excited.  I
wonder if it was a success for us to be able to collaborate and perform together.I do
n't like it, but I feel like everyone is being fooled a little bit.That's why
when I was staying with that person at Lou's house, I got that
bath salt.  I
forgot,
hey
, I feel like I'm being deceived. This atmosphere makes me
want to be deceived
[laughter],
so I hope I can get it somewhere again. I'm
still
receiving questions from overseas members, so please
continue reading.  Let's go Start I
have a problem and would like to ask everyone for help. I
'm a fan of all generations.
[Music] I'm
not good at coming here, so I'd
like to ask you guys,
um, how are thumbnails determined?  So,
how do you make thumbnails these days?
By the way, you
said that you're not good at making thumbnails, but what do you all think?
Seriously, how do you make thumbnails?
No, I'm not good at it. Seriously, Laplace is super good. He's good. I'll take this [music]. Let's do business. Besides, he's good at it, and he likes it. I don't really dislike him.
He's a creator,
after all.  What I'm most careful about is that
on YouTube, the
thumbnails are displayed smaller than I expected,
so I like to make the people bigger than I expected.Also,
when making thumbnails, I make them smaller.
That's right. I'll
make it in the back. It's
amazing. It's helpful to have a serious and serious answer. I
made a mistake.
But, you're really good at it, so it
'll be helpful.
Everyone says they're not good at it,
too.
What do you dislike about it? Well, if you want to
do something and then stream
it, you don't know what's going to happen, so it's something like a thumbnail title scam.  The title is a bit strange,
and the image is the type that doesn't have much firepower. Why are you so prepared? I
wonder if the
members who are adding things
can do something like that. Are there any
words in it already? Like this, this, this, this, this, this, this,
amazing.  This is how I
do things like tuning, and I'm juggling the thumbnails.I
mean, I'm going to broadcast something like this today,
but I
don't really know until the company starts.Actually, I
do a lot of this.  Actually, when I
tried it, it surprisingly didn't do anything.It's amazing how
amazing it is to be able to create thumbnails.I often
look at other people's pictures, so it works.I
looked at everyone's thumbnails and used them as a reference.  I'm
sure there are
thumbnails of people who are good at rummy.It's
amazing.By the way, I'd
like to ask you personally how much time does it take to create a thumbnail?
[Music]
Sometimes it takes about an hour if it's long. [Music] It takes a long time. It
really depends on whether Lapi-chan is good at it or not,
but if I do something easy, it will
take about 30 minutes, but
even if it's quick, I'll
just ask.  I don't know, I'll
make money if you ask me. Money mark. There are some cases where it
takes 2 hours or half
a day, or something like that.
-
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] It
can be quite difficult, though.
Okay, well then.  Well, I hope you've answered what Ollie wanted to know. So,
please take a look at what I just said and
make your own thumbnails.Next
up are some comments from members from overseas.  Last question:
What are you getting here?Introduction
VTR
Start My
question is, what do you think of my Yoffie?
That's all?
[Music]
How was the sunset this year?A
simple question about UFOs is my impression.  So,
what do you think?That's what everyone is saying.First
of all, I
'm not involved in it, so I
'd like to get involved next year.Thank
you in advance.It would
be great if the fans could come up with cute hair as an icon.I'd like to use the bald person here.  I want to borrow this stick
and say, ``Let's
borrow this opportunity and make the leader bald too.'' I
want you to create that hairstyle.
[Applause] I
want a new style. You
have to get permission. I
suddenly sent you
a picture of someone made bald.  They sent it to me and I'm
doing it on stream. I'm starting
to see the pictures of the state it's in and the state it's in after. It
didn't come that way though...
[Music]
But we did a collaboration together.  I
guess it's okay because we're good friends, or maybe that's the case.There's a big
difference.Okay,
everyone here, please do it without permission.Well,
this year's Yuffie, after all,
is Tsuru.  I'm
not talking about Luffy-senpai because he has a strong image of being a [ __ ], but I would like to
say thank you, so let's come and play together next year.Alright
, everyone, it's the second half of the game,
so let's talk about the members here again.  Well,
let's talk about what I want to talk about. Okay, the
first shot of the second half is already here. I'm sorry.
What's the theme you brought here? Here it
is. Hello.
[Music] If you
hadn't joined Hol Live, what would you be doing by now
?  [Music] I'd
like to ask you a little bit about this. I
wonder if he aspired to be an idol,
or if he aspired to be a comedian. I thought I'd
like to ask everyone this earlier,
but I
guess I'll just have to hear it from Sakamoto.
Was he a
member of Phlox?
No, but he was probably an intern, so he could
leave at any time, so he
just
left,
maybe he went through the hall or something.
Try to express it with your hands.
[Music]
Hey,
but that's it. It's serious.  It's
not like it's been since I debuted,
but since we've only talked about that app,
[Music] I'm
starting to worry, as a senior, and I'm
like, are you okay? Yes, I can take a bath.  Tana
Thank you so much.
Thank you Hololive.
Next time, I'll set up with Akira. It's
a bit of a different world
after all. As a dancer, I guess I was aiming for the top a little.
Please give me the dance costume.
[Laughter]
[Music]
There's also a future like that.
Well, she probably doesn't have that kind of power. She
might have been a programmer, aside from the princess.
Realistic rules. I see. She's a
capable woman.
Yes, then, let's ask the leader and the man. Yes, it was originally
before the full live performance. It was an
emergency.  Since it was my job, I guess I've been doing it by inertia all along.
Could you please
stop for a moment?
No, but to be
honest, I'm not suited to be the leader. I guess it
was a job. But if I hadn't
been to this show, I'd have been doing it by
inertia all the time.
[Music]
Lobby  Does it work for Lamy, who becomes a lobby?
But if I hadn't joined Hololive, I'd probably be in the mansion right now. It's probably a lot
darker. It's a little too dark. It's
not like I'm going to spend the year-end and New Year holidays here. I'm
glad I joined Hololive and met everyone.  After all, I do
n't
have any friends. I bought it, so I don't have any friends.
[Music]
By the way, I wonder if Lapi-chan is a
normal designer.
[Music] That
means she likes what she does.
Legs. Don't do it.
Conquering the world. Well, I'm putting aside the idea of ​​conquering the world for now.
World players. Don't be silly.
Uniform.  I
'm off to
go. [Music] I don't go home. I don't know what I was doing when I didn't go home. Maybe it wasn't much
different from my current private life, like looking for the lowest price for natto at the supermarket.  [
Music] It
's sparkling, thank you
very much. Let's
end
on a note. [Laughs] But next, let's move on to the next topic.
Let's move on. Who's next? Let's see.
Next.  Here's what I want to do, Rap-chan.
[Music]
Please tell me what type of person you are. I
love Koibana.
[Music] I'm a
Kane idol, but I
love girls' manga, and even before this recording, I've
been reading girls' manga today.
[Applause]
After all, that's
Hololive.  When I was watching the stream, I
realized that there weren't that many people who had their favorite type or love stories,
so I
thought I'd take this as a chance and
ask.It'll
take about an hour, but
please
.  [Music]
No, I
like glasses. I guess I do
n't really like glasses. I
don't
mind just wearing glasses, but glasses...  It's the
first time I've completed it
What do you think? Is it your
favorite shellfish or your favorite glasses?
[Music]
[Music] He's
running away, right? Wait a minute, wait a minute,
this is
n't the one protecting him, it's Sugar,
right? It's sign language, isn't it?
That's why when I'm next to him, it's Raigane. By the way, I'm talking about the group leader and the like. Sometimes he says things like Subaru-senpai style, and sometimes he burns things. Hmm, I love that kind of thing. Stop calling it a
relationship.
There's nothing special about it.  I don't think
so. Do you like it?
[Music] I'm talking
about counseling
[Music]
There are people who are crying deep inside, so
what kind of people do you like who cry? But you know,
deafness is just a pushover for idols.  I'm a fan, but I'm the
type of person who can smile and listen to things like Subaruna.Why do I like this leader?My favorite type is
someone who is kind.Eh,
anime
[laughing]
[music] I do
n't really care about the characters.
Even if I don't like the way he looks, he's
just a normal person after all. He's a single-minded person after all. Please be kind to yourself.
Yes, please be kind to
me. It's just my appearance, like my glasses, so I don't care about
my face or anything.  Let
's listen to it. It's
like a two-dimensional genre that I'm into.
[Music]
A little bit of naughty manga and a little
bit of it.
[Music]
Seriously,
it's a little like this. It's a kind of
wild thing that has different opinions.  No, I
won't go as far as filing, but he has a lot of life experience, is
very tolerant, and protects me in times of need.He
looks like John Wig, and seems to be on the halfbeak side.I
wonder how old he is.
About the second half of 30
[Music] I
see.
Then there's Sakamoto,
[Music] He's
blonde, he's
short, his
signature color is purple, and
he's a shitty kid who looks like he can use magic.
[Applause]
[Music] He's
silver-haired.  I was pretty excited about her when she was short,
but the
camera definitely didn't take away the effect even once.
Even the camera took away from me, but it
makes no sense.
[Music]
But it's so cute!  Are
n't you cute
with your bare hands? The
moment I entered Holo, I
thought, ``Is this a lie?'' It's a nerd.
But he's sleeping at Shioai's house.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]  ]
[Applause]
[Music]
Please do it with art It's
scary.
Next theme.
There's something I'd like to ask everyone.
[Music] If you
were to marry one of the current members or the earth would be destroyed, who would you choose
?
What is the situation? After thinking about all these things,
who would you choose?  If you had to marry someone,
who would you
choose? There would definitely be someone who would say, ``I can't,''
but if
the earth was at stake, and the life of the person you care about was
at stake, too.  I'm going to choose,
right? Well, it's a bit like this, but what if I get selected? I'm
really looking forward to it.
Well, let's cut it short.
Who should I ask? Well, I have
n't decided yet.
[Music]  ] It's
okay to despair because you're trying to wear a uniform,
but you can
only do so if you have friends.Of course, who would be good in real life?I know, absolutely, she can cook, she'll take care of you, she'll do everything for you, she's kind, and she'll marry you.
You're getting married, so it
's just a pee thing. Well, that's
it. That's
right, seniors.  I'm really a hunter, and I
want to taste it, so
let me have a little taste of it next year.It might be a good pairing.Of
course, you
can ask me as much as you want.I'm done with
Laplace.I've
finally given up.  He
gave it to me and kidnapped me after it was destroyed. It's so
cute.
Yes, it's a serious story.
Seriously, in this,
everyone.  If she's not there, she'll look like Lamy, so that's right.
[Laughs]
But the good thing about her is that the
good thing about her is that it's being streamed, so I
feel like she has a girlish side, a little weak side, and I want to protect her.  If you
don't talk, you'll be really messed up.I'm the
type of person who wants to protect you.Well, you know, it's
not cool.I can
do that.On
the other hand, I'm
holding up my untied hand, and I do
n't think it's there.Captain,
uh...
Captain?But, Captain, this is my only choice.  What is it?
Well, it's roux butter. Even if I was
asked about it the first time, I thought I'd say
it. I'm a knight who's hard of hearing, so what if I
slept with the princess?
[Laughs] That's
difficult.
[Applause]
Anachronism.
This is amazing.  It looks like we've made a good couple now.
[Music]
Wait,
this is
fine.
[Music]
God's Yuta
This is Luna, who says she feels sorry for him because no one else chose him.
So please
sit down and say, Okay,
no, no, no, wait a minute, if I
were to actually choose Sakamoto, what
would be
attractive about her?  That's all I need to
get married, that's not
true. [Laughs] Good. [Laughs] That's what I'm talking about.
After all, in
2022, I've
told my juniors that I want to get along with them, and now that they've chosen Fish and Rummy, I'm sure the
villagers will be even more excited.  I'm
starting to like things.
[Music]
But it's supposed to be destroyed. It's probably not limited to baths
or anything,
so I guess it's a little high. Let's just
say,
Sakamoto is not particularly
impressed.
Hey,
you know, this is marriage, but it's
called lover, so it's
a little different for me, and this time it's marriage, but
there's also a potential lover.Rose-senpai,
tired of marriage sumo, together
with the overflowing adult milk.  I
think it's very adult-like, like
putting a straw on a flower or drinking juice here.Yes, I
want to marry her.My
lover, my lover.Yeah, for
me, I'm going to choose a moment now.  I
thought you'd give it to me,
but when Lunar said something like that earlier, I was
wondering if he'd come. Well, it's
not like today, right? There's
no misunderstanding. I feel
sorry for this person.  That's what I was thinking, but I
love him. It's funny.
By the way, this
was just a coincidence, but it
seems like there's only one player who wasn't selected. He's the
player here, so why not do it? It's
impossible, it's impossible, it's
impossible, it's impossible.  I don't know about getting married or anything exciting.
[Music]
Well, I'll see you next year. Just make sure you're ready for someone
to choose you.
[Laughs] I
hope you do.  Well, that's
about it
. It's almost time for this corner to
end.
Since it's an illustrated book, I'm
going to keep talking about whether I really like it or not. I wonder who you are,
but it's fun to be able to do whatever you want.
[Music] It
felt like an unusual group of members had gathered together.
But instead of telling a lot of serious stories, we decided to do some strange and mysterious stories.
[Music] I
wanted to hear something like this.  Isn't that the case? Now, it's
next
year.
[Music] I
'm going to play overtime and I want to get along especially well with that member and this member next year, so I'm going to go.
So,
um, I'm going to ask that kind of fish.
Do you want to get along?
Me
[Music] I don't
have to be a member here.
Then,
during that live,
personally, we
collaborated once last time, and I really
wanted to talk about it.  It
was Prea-senpai
[Music] We
were talking behind the scenes, but
Sakamoto wasn't sure if it was okay to take up too much of his time, so I
was really scared to reply.  I
was thinking too much about things like, ``Are you okay? Are you pushing yourself
too hard this time?'' or ``I'm not tired,'' but I'm thinking that next year I'd like to talk to you more. I'll go
and see you next year and
ask you questions.
Well then, today, we
did it together once.I wonder if it's Gorileba's money-chan.
Yay.  I want to
choose from among the members, so I
want to drink more alcohol.
[Laughs]
But there are times when we do live shows together,
but it's more
like I've just split my stomach open like this.  When it
comes to alcohol, Heart of Heart
[Music]
Please release me, that's a picture ball.
[Music] I
want to get along with everyone, but that's right. Well, if you're
talking about this as a whole live show, it's a bit. Last year, I
said I wanted to do a little collaboration.  In the end, the plan
came first, a polka.
Ah, let's
do it. Let's get along. That's how you
look now. Well, it's like polka.
Behind the scenes, it seems like you want to do that kind of collaboration. The
distance between you and me seems to be shrinking, but I
still don't want to do a collaboration.  I think
Nee's Lunaca,
where did this Luna bond go? It's
here. It
's there. It's there. I want it to be there.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] If we
were in this together,
everyone would be involved in some way.  I'm a person,
but Lamy is the only person here who doesn't have any bonds at all.
For some reason, I thought he was with someone, but
he
didn't, so he's
just saying he's putting it down. No, actually, he's been saying no to me behind the scenes.
So that's a good thing.
Talk
[Laughs]
Yes.  So, now that I've
talked to a lot of you, I think I'm feeling a lot
better, and I think I'll be able to go into the New Year feeling a lot better.
But how about that?
[Laughter]
Did you all have fun?
[Applause]
That's it.  Well, there's
only a few days left in 2022, so after this, it's finally
New Year's Eve, so the
production countdown live will
begin,
with a combination of songs that have become a hot topic this year, and a combination that you don't usually see.  There
will be a special video and the unveiling of Sora-senpai's kimono costume after the new year, so don't miss it.
Tomorrow, January 1st, from 7pm, All Humanity Rabbit will be available
on the official Hololive channel.
It's a plan. There's also a
stream. It looks like Senpai will be going wild, so please take a look. So
that's it for this year's full story. Hey everyone,
be sure to check out the Hololive Production Countdown Live after this.  I hope you enjoy it. So, let's say
goodbye for now.
Everyone, let's go. Everyone can say yes. Let's go.
Everyone, finally.
Ah
[Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]