[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah
I'm glad to have the Discord support
today and hopefully also the viewers
support today because uh today will be a
very very passionate and dangerous and
fun and exciting events
like burning rubber yes exactly the
drivers bad drivers no we're not here
everybody's pro drivers here
I may be a bad driver but I'll drive you
guys nuts
of each member uh now let's start with
whole life Indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
Anya melviso from hollow life is an
generation thank you everyone I can't
wait what's your uh
what's my ikigomi um to not be um the
last last place at least
[Applause]
okay what about
um bye oh oh hello oh officers
generation one so my motivation tonight
is
um to show you my practice I guess
oh show me what you got
[Music]
hi attention please I'm popular Rainey
from whole life ID generation 2. my goal
today is to be number one in your heart
and also not that last in the race
yeah I thought you were good you and
Iris have heard good good news about you
yeah we had a good practice yesterday
right
for joining
[Applause]
bye
hello my name is
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
what's it what's the motivation for
today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay but in the middle it's okay
[Music]
not last oh okay
in your heart
the last in someone's heart is that such
a good thing does it sound like a good
thing yeah okay
hello hello everyone I'm ayanda from
Whole Life Indonesia and thank you so
much for inviting me to this collab I'm
so happy though I'm so excited thank you
thank you
[Music]
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right it will be fine
[Applause]
and Ollie
yay
zombies
Indonesia second generation hi guys
motivation I plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms that is my
motivation for today
she wants to be on top I see I don't
know what else is expected from your
motivation only
I'll turn you guys into bottoms
okay when you're ready here
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
wait did I get
I have just one ID I think I did
yeah
let's introduce the E inside let's start
with Iris okay hiris it's Iris holy live
English project hope V singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
thank you
[Music]
yeah thank you so much for having me
here so I heard that you waited for yeah
for me to come on we were literally the
last question that I needed because
before I knew it was we were elf elf
that's what that was German we were 11
people
I did not understand German yeah
12 12 12 is the perfect yeah yeah
yeah thank you next up how about
um
today I'm gonna win probably okay okay
this is the I own I heard you only
played Mario Kart so far in a members
only stream but that's about it
yeah I won in that one too oh oh okay
oh then you might be the hidden winning
choice that the one in the Dark Horse
Dark Horse a wild card player welcome
amazing
thank you thank you next time
English
um
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not last
and to be first so our ultimate best
you know I was also taking this very
seriously in her practice round so I'm a
bit scared of you know I don't know
I'm still falling off Maps it's fun oh
yeah it happens oh Kelly joined yes nice
thanks
let's start and let's continue with the
introduction from
Maury
hello everyone my name is callipi my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning Maury
nice to meet you
because it's a bit early uh so excuse me
for that guys but I'm very excited just
to be here I really didn't think this
was gonna work but it's working I love
it says
thank you Kelly for joining even though
it's such an early time and to kind of
uh Troublesome with some setups and all
that I'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good uh thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
just twists
and I'm kind of sick today and if you're
watching on my side I just need to say
this now I've had some technical
difficulties very suddenly so I am made
of cardboard I'm sorry please well it
was not my fault it's out of my control
right now so anyways I'm PNG tuber Doma
somebody does a PNG tuber Let's Race
today baby I'm the wild card today
my dust well you know on the screen
there's there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so I think it's fun I'm curious I of
course they want to look at me right
guys
[Music]
all right that leaves uh me I think yeah
yeah yes
welcome everyone I wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today
[Music]
but before that let me say thank you is
the hats and the cards are sponsored by
ninoma inanis yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
you look lovely so cute all right let's
everyone switch to the rules image
please thank you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically uh all characters
all courses are allowed however if you
choose uh please do not choose random
courses please choose a certain course
that you want to actually erase but if
not course has been used before like if
it has actually been chosen before
please do not choose the same course
again already
understand oh yeah
number two items are allowed number
three uh we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistance I think you
can check by pressing y
a all right
now okay yeah if uh wait a second it's
if you press Y and select your character
at the point where you select the card
you can press on a plus the
three options on the right side if you
press l
uh if if there is a if there's a sign
that says no
then it's uh Auto steering off that's
how it's supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly you can ignore okay okay okay
okay okay
what do you mean oh
[Laughter]
I'm gonna be on like Auto mute this
whole time so unless I have something to
say I'm gonna be muted don't worry if
I'm a little quiet I'm still here with
you guys in spirit yeah okay okay
and next rule uh oh yeah there's no more
rules it's basically it's just a system
we're doing the first cup all versus all
big mixer for races then we get we will
mute each other by the way during the
race and just to focus everyone on what
we're driving and then we get back
together and Discord talk a little bit
then we go to the second cup which is en
versus ID six versus sixth yes yes we
will separate each other in uh The Voice
channels by team this one in this one we
will actually talk with one another if
you wanna and then we uh give some
comments together again when we get all
back together in the same channel and we
do the third cup with random randomly
thrown together teams ID but like all
mixed together naturally beautiful
random random random we will just like
I'll count down and and then everyone
joins Eva voice chat room zero or voice
chat room one no who's this one
well done we're gonna have to do it
again and again and again
okay okay
perfect
and perfect just so you know the the
those like team cups would basically be
um like the same system as all versus
all the difference is just basically
like if you throw items like red shells
or whatever and there is a teammate in
front of you it will not go to the
teammate obviously it will go directly
to the closest opponent driver uh that's
around you so yeah that's how that team
system works I think yes
is everyone ready
[Applause]
oh
yeah okay
okay
that's random Beauty slowly all right
okay then everyone who is ready mute
yourself on Discord if someone's not
ready then I will ask you why you're not
ready
all right
I'm gonna win this
bye-bye okay wait guys how do you wait
guys uh how do you go forward in the
game
you push the a button you can't go right
now you can't look at the world right
now okay that's what you mean oh gotcha
all right understood thank you okay
thanks guys love you okay love you too
it's so quiet
you guys hear me
can you guys hear me it's so quiet
there was like a lot of noise but
anyways I'm gonna do my best
I'm gonna do my best and um yeah I have
I don't have much to say but I practice
a little bit and I'm just gonna do my
best okay yeah it's starting
yeah somebody's telling me I gotta get
glasses because
for me to see better it's okay I'll
prove to you guys that I can do no
glasses okay I shouldn't choose random
right I'm just gonna choose the most
basic um like Mario Kart style Stadium
the the left most the left most
oh somebody also chose Mario Kart
Stadium oh nice multiple people you
chose Mario Kart Stadium what are the
chances
what are the chances
don't look at chat okay fine
I wanna look at chat like you want you
want me to concentrate you want me to
concentrate fine I can do that no I
won't be able to stop talking but you
know I wonder what everybody else is
talking about there's so many people I
wonder oh
Anthony
okay uh what what what's gonna get
chosen
oh
it's basically what I chose to so that's
great
[Music]
um
okay focus rainy Focus wow you guys
really want me to okay okay okay I'm
gonna go serious I don't know I don't
know how to be serious but you know I'll
try my best yeah
yeah yeah
so we did a practice see I ain't see
homie Amy's using the heavy class
character I'm so scared it scares me
heavy class characters scare me you know
[Music]
I'm so scared yeah
okay it's so scary because if you get if
you get first place really early you're
gonna get screwed like in the second lap
or like what I don't know
but yeah I don't know
I did some practice and I hope it bears
fruit because
I did my best
um like earlier before this match too I
played with I played with the ID girls
just a little bit you know because uh
the tournament rules everything
everything around and we were like okay
we gotta we gotta make the name of the
ID peeps Harum you know you know what
that means that's like uh make our names
very very
Anthony
we're gonna show what the ID girls are
capable of doing that's it I think
because like not many of us play Mario
Kart
and if anything though like none of us
really play Mario Kart
yeah so
during this tournament we're just like
I don't know
um
oh no more squids
[Laughter]
I think I'm doing okay
I don't want to jinx it though I don't I
don't want to say things like that
because
oh yeah there's a blue shell yep I'm
gonna get hit and then somebody's
gonna you know
[Music]
I don't know what I should do with this
I don't know what I should do with the
green shell
oh somebody just stole my items
why
yeah oh somebody's gonna somebody's
gonna somebody's gonna so he's gonna oh
no am I gonna get sniped oh oh that was
so close that was so close who is that
[Music]
who was that that was Eda Senpai it was
so close though
whoa
[Laughter]
that was really close I think like
during the practice too
I chose this okay what am I gonna choose
next I think I'm just gonna choose like
the red I'm just gonna choose it by
order I don't really have a preference
I don't really have a preference but you
know
so it's like I think the rules is like
four every every like one whole cup and
then we can unmute yep
[Music]
okay Animal Crossing Mario Kart Stadium
wait no you're not supposed to pick
Mario Kart Stadium again oh no
[Music]
I hope it won't I hope it doesn't get
picked
I hope it doesn't get picked um
okay okay okay yeah I'm not familiar
with this course so I might do kind of
not good but I'll try my best still
yep
and cheap cheap beach
all right
[Music]
okay I have no idea how this goes well
eat a sandwich
I love cheese steak
I think uh from what I heard es Empires
also has also been practicing
I think
so I'm kind of you know she's one of
good yeah oh my gosh
eighth it's okay if I'm last I'm gonna
get all the good items
so it's good it's all good it's all good
it is all good
wait can I actually do this
this yes I can
I can do that
I don't actually know oh my God okay
oh
bananas bananas for you bananas for
everybody nice
bananas for everybody
oh no there's a moon
avoided that one I don't know how I
avoided that one but yeah
hmm I have no idea if there is like a
good shortcut in this this area I'm
really
oh
no oh
it's okay it's okay owlette
I'll let everybody I'll let everybody go
in front I'll let anybody go in front
because then I'll get the good items
can we can we can we afford to come back
can we afford to come back because I
don't know if you could but we're gonna
try our best
we're gonna try our best
we're still fifth so it's fine I guess
so many blue shells why why are you guys
like this
oh
wow
so many like
you know your eighth and then your third
and then your
okay
oh it's Iris is Iris and Kiara's Empire
that's in front
oh no
yeah I think
I think I think there's no I think um
I'm not drifting
ah fifth I mean not bad
you had some hiccups I feel like what's
yeah what matters in Mario Kart is that
you're familiar okay and please everyone
do not use cheap cheap beach or a Mario
Kart Stadium anymore for your race
collection thank you okay I'm gonna try
and remember that but I don't know yeah
yeah nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life place right but isn't there
multiple Beach
uh yeah but the cheap cheap beach the
one that we just did from the DS version
not anything yeah oh okay okay okay are
we doing team wait what are we doing
teams
uh we still have two races to go before
all this result okay
nice hat in uh she's muted okay are we
oh sorry okay
wow the train tracks are popular
the train tracks are popular so what is
the next one
oh the train tracks
oh no this one too there's a shortcut
but it's it's a pretty hard one oh iris
is 22 E9 is 24. oh
total point
it's okay
hopefully I won't do so bad here
let's try
let's do our best
I think everybody hey what's wrong with
you I'm just kidding
oh
[Music]
okay okay
yeah that's what happens it's okay so
lap one I still have one I still have
one it's fine it's fine guys it's fine
it's still fine unless it's left three
and it is not fine then it is not fine
it would slap for me
yeah
what even is you know what
what even was that
yeah that wasn't even fair that was not
fair there's not fair at all
right and also where is the thing
ow I got the thing rip
the trains I'm not good enough to graze
between the uh between the cars
[Music]
foreign
who was that who was that
um
this is kind of trippy
but hey I'm still a third
[Music]
oh she has she has a shell right in
front of her
oh no then I have to oh
that was a mess on my part
there was a Miss on my oh no I mean
fifth what am I gonna do
what am I gonna do
I still have a chance to redeem this
oh my gosh
oh no there's like a star there
[Music]
oh this is not looking very good I feel
like once you like fall once it just
gets really difficult to catch up
um
somebody somebody can just
oh yeah somebody just did that to me I
want to drive honest but it's difficult
you know oh no yeah I missed okay I
messed that one up
[Music]
I messed that one up
I hope we get I hope we get a map that
I'm better at
whatever I'm gonna keep choosing water
park because I don't know what I'm gonna
choose
foreign
Bowser City
so what's gonna get picked 85 nope oh
this one this course
this course
I gotta score better so I can get a
better overall score you know
this is the final race
um
and because I finished last I don't get
the advantage of
um
um let's see what I can do with this
I don't really know the roads here too
like I mean I don't know I say things
like that but what do I know I don't
play in a Mario Kart to be able to
actually know stuff by heart and then I
fell yeah that's a bad one it's okay
we're still on the on the first lap
oh no that was wasted
it was wasted and that um that exploding
thing I have no idea
I have no idea about the hitbox of that
oh no I should have used it here I
forgot
I think I know like Kiara Senpai was
practicing off stream in the waiting
room
I think that I think that is a good idea
like me me and the girlfriend some of
the ID Girls we practiced
but uh that's all what is this
no idea what this is what am I doing
oh there's more of each
one of each
oh
like what a big truck they gotta use
them wisely huh
oh no oh
a community
guys I got disconnected
wait what
a connection error
I don't even okay I think like nobody is
out I guess it's only me that got kicked
because
I think there's a I think it's only Mina
got kicked because you know I have no
idea what happened well let me see if I
can like rejoin them
can I join
wait what
yeah well I'm kind of high key salty
because like
I don't know I don't know why only I I
don't know why I was the only one who
got kicked okay about the disconnection
I'm yeah I'm not sure like normally it
seems like in in the whole of Japan
tournaments they automatically give the
one like well the like this
qualification like last spot if you uh
oh if you are oh wow congratulations oh
everyone kind of mute themselves now oh
yeah yeah okay oh yeah hi hi
guys
I was very impressed
I got disconnected but she still was a
fourth or what so yeah
I think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it is yeah
so uh let me let me just uh enough was
number one right Inna number one
congratulations
[Applause]
[Music]
I thought you kept on selecting Rainbow
Road
no
one you know
what I'm saying
yeah yeah she practiced on that one a
lot I think that's what she was going
through
it
you'll get it oh okay someone has to uh
yeah wait uh wait who was numbers
no problem no problem who was number two
though
okay
[Music]
I was how did you how did you manage to
get number two today I I did bad on the
first race so that really pulled me back
but yeah Ina Senpai was very quick uh
but I did my best I did my best
status
oh wait me and Elena were third are we
tired
good job good job oh wait wait are we
complete in the lobby right now I want
to I am in the lobby yeah
okay okay
well then shall we uh continue uh but
Muna Senpai is currently unavailable
um
but I don't know my my battery is 100
but it's a low battery so I didn't know
which one is low battery oh
um
do you think you were fine to go or you
need some time I I think I think it
should be fine okay so we're making
coffee right now
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
I want the caffeine shakes already so
I'm banned from coffee I was actually
really surprised about ama's driving too
like I thought you know because she
didn't like we didn't see her practicing
we didn't see her play the game to begin
with a lot so I was like yeah so most of
the races until the end when I got
[\h__\h] over yeah
I saw you go off the edge though Watson
it was pretty good
as planned right it's all party yeah
whatever yeah no it wasn't the waste if
you would have shoutcasted how you uh
suggested America's you were such a good
driver I will need you we need you
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay Ollie is going to another teams are
we picking teams dodgeball no
no that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that
oh my God
my Nintendo again please because that
means someone picked last and I don't
want that I'm gonna go at my full power
now because now I'm fighting for the en
ladies
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah
our teams I'll just warm up now let's
now
and Iris two of the strongest ones are
in Ian wait me too
[Laughter]
oh my God
I'm okay at not getting last place so
that's good news yes Olivia Morrison is
a good asset to have I want her on our
team hell yeah
guys
Dana will have to carry uh Indonesia's
uh back yes
after all this I'll be good all right
I'll do what I can
as long as you don't get disconnected
again oh my gosh yeah
oh I hope you don't get this are we on a
break right now God may have forgiven
the disconnection but I didn't
everyone uh please split into teams by I
think let's just um Ian go to Voice
Channel 01 thank you okay
um I think oh and I guess so we're going
to
hello
am I alone here I don't know or are we
staying at zero what what
wait wait how much more are we gonna go
to this is Kelly wants to be now
okay I think Kelly basically wants to be
gangs games
did you know
yes uh there's a problem with my
Nintendo's actually what should we do
does it arriving
should we go
hold on yeah
hey I got DC room right now
sorry girls I did a little mistake
because like I thought uh yeah you know
okay you can join us again okay
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again I think it closed once you
can join again
sorry
all right
are you gonna be okay
uh
[Music]
um
yeah
so be careful with that
I think that we actually need to buy
separate uh what is it controller
another Another One controller yeah
controller yeah
I was using the uh the normal controller
for the longest time and it had never
had problems
and the worst thing is that my
controller actually died so she might
want to be careful
um
okay now I think they say either
Indonesia
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
outer ring
foreign
[Music]
oh
goodbye everyone
that's not bad
is fine
um
[Music]
I think you have to be at least good at
Mario Kart because this kind of
tournament is gonna like happen in the
future
oh my God I bought the wheels for that
but it's not arrived sadly
[Music]
oh this is
hard yeah
I mean wow metal music
to go I should have worn glasses
it's lava but I'm not born
[Music]
of History
[Applause]
thank you
yes
foreign
Hi how are you doing I'm doing good okay
somebody just like stole my items that's
not cool
[Music]
it was not me
oh my gosh somebody somebody
laugh guys
[Music]
problem in this map
yeah we have problems too I don't like
this one
yeah where is this
um
is
okay
[Music]
that's fine
oh my God
[Laughter]
no idea what you guys are talking about
so where where are we going what did we
choose again
it doesn't matter honestly
cheese land
do you plan again
let's go to salon oh all right that's a
sick strategy
oh my God why did they pick that place
oh my God
rainbow rainbow because it's all the
sunshine and rainbows please please
please
at this time when I saw it I please just
land
oh
yeah
I'm gonna get that cheddar delicious
[Laughter]
oh my God
I don't even know what are you guys
talking about but yes I love
it we just like randomly screaming at
each other at this point right
yes oh it was late
I don't even know I cheese land
ooh lettuce cheese
[Applause]
controller okay
it's okay it's okay it's it's I think
it's okay I I did hope it's okay though
and I fall okay
asideful
oh yeah oh Jesus
okay let's go I don't even know how it
is Empire that was for you
I just want I just want mushrooms why do
I keep getting like weird slash bad
items and everyone else gets such good
items oh no
I didn't
you guys get items
like seriously I'm asking you guys got
an item
nice I kept trying to cheating by flying
you know but I failed how do you feel
how how do I Believe I Can Fly okay I
can fly
I believe I can touch this guy
basically
hell yeah I can bananas delicious
bananas for everybody
ouch
for everybody no oh no there's a Blue
Shield I'm so scared
blue shell is the scariest thing and you
know
it is yes
yes oh no I gotta drive honestly
I'm not liking this I gotta drive honest
here
again
oh yeah
that's dirty that's scary that's so
dirty
yeah I'm so sorry if I failed you
I failed you guys I'm so sorry
oh God I had potential
oh no oh no oh my God oh my God
oh my god let's try popping top five of
all of us
please
[Laughter]
okay we got cheese land so uh oh I'm
hacked
what do I
um let's do the airplane stage
and go to the airport
okay where is that they really want to
do rainbow roads wait
um
Sunshine okay gotcha
sunshine
alrighty sunshine
wind Rainbow Road and shine sunshine
oh it's gonna be a rainbow road isn't it
I'm not so good
guys yeah especially this one this one
is especially hard really I have no idea
that one's easy but this one is
this one is the simplest looking one I
like
I Believe I Can Fly
so I wouldn't drive
there's like shortcuts here in the house
I don't know
[Applause]
um
[Music]
what is even going on everybody
oh my God
[Music]
please oh no I fell oh
yeah it's really not good using this I
don't know what is it called
and I get Falling Again
[Music]
I believe
you know how to stop the car like kind
of like that um
um
yeah yeah
ah
how big are there
I I oh I'm so bad okay I'm just I'm just
smashing
like baby the button right at your
tongue
yeah
I'm Gonna Take It
yes I hate the music now
I hate the music
[Music]
it's allowed because of our ID
what the hell does that mean no we were
not supposed to crash in Indonesia but
if the cars in English I thought I think
it's okay like if it's Indonesia yes
let's go what do you mean let's go which
one is not okay English Indonesian
no English is English is not good
because YouTube YouTube AI is bad bad
right awesome
Indonesia is okay
just this moderation okay in moderation
next time
[Music]
what was the reasoning behind choosing
uh the cheese one and the baby Road I
like cheese that's all because
yeah
someone who told them cheese road
because I like cheese
yes cheese tasty so yeah was somewhat in
control there because like It's gotta be
a road where Elena knows the shortcuts
and stuff yeah I am yeah
you
um
[Applause]
do we have uh some uh comments from the
winner Ina it was number one I think ah
yes uh I would like to thank my chair
mates
um
[Laughter]
for this opportunity because of you I
was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay okay
[Laughter]
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate that oh can you
listen yeah
what did we choose
oh I mean well even if you accidentally
choose one that has been uh chosen
before don't worry it will probably not
be you selective so let's just let's
just try to not choose the ones that we
have uh raced before then we'll do the
random teams now actually there is uh we
don't have to do the voice chat thing
because there is actually a way to do it
here
and then teams are selected oh there it
is okay so uh invoice chat zero zero
zero one we want uh gura
and your feet all right okay all right
let's go
baby
hello hello
[Music]
okay we can do this
and amen they are the two Dangerous Ones
it's not dangerous just push her off
you want
sure
[Music]
you don't have to yeah
oh they're going for the airport
let's fly to the Bahamas
okay okay let's see
all right let's go
um
yes let's go do our best
team
[Music]
I don't know if the shortcuts here are
worth it this isn't worth it I don't
know I don't know it is kind of risky
yeah it's very risky right it's very
high
[Music]
um
let's go hey the hell what happened God
I got uh yeah you eat it oh my God
because he didn't eat
yeah this shortcut is very risky I don't
know if I yes yeah
helping me
oh no
we're doing fine or no we're doing fine
for now
[Music]
don't saw that
I'll get it I missed them I missed I
misdicted
okay oh he's in front of me
I hate these curves
thank you
hella good man
we're on the same team wait what did
that hit you
oh my God you're in Hong Kong that's
fine that's fine
[Music]
okay sorry
who was that
who was that not me
as always the question who the hell hit
me this time who missed
who must hit me oh
[Music]
me and my life again all the speed
yeah it's so fast
too fast
that was a decent safe
who was responsible for that toys
sorry I got Blue Shield right in front
of the Finish Line
we're still pretty much at the top so
yeah
next time
she's on my tail
this is the most adrenaline I've had in
a very long time hey my heart is like
all right
I'm like surprised like I didn't think
it would be this much fun to like have a
full tournament with everyone we're
having a blast man
but now it's like every every half year
we should do something like this I know
yeah
what are we picking oh
[Music]
no problem we didn't have that one yet
no that's the one this is
different right oh again yeah baby oh
this is the right choice
blessed by the RNG
[Applause]
guys I'm not me aren't I you're nice
I hear you I hear you oh okay okay
wondering why I'm my name sorry nope oh
sorry
wow
hey who was that I don't even know what
everyone say you keep saying I'm in the
Mueller
okay okay
[Music]
oh
okay this part I usually choke but okay
I can do this we can do it
[Music]
right
y'all be careful
mushroom
oh my gosh
I didn't know that oh God oh God I
worked that way
my Friendly Fire is all I didn't get a
night then no it shouldn't like
sometimes it hits like people by
accident I think generally it goes oh
God this is bad I don't know why is
oh I didn't know that's not part of the
card I don't even know
during this race
[Music]
iris is scary
she's right behind please run behind me
he's right behind still dominating dope
yeah
good job everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
what do we do
support because they really want these
they absolutely I was looking for
airports
yeah I already picked my bed and before
we get the time the clock
get picked
is this the final is this
I see the airport is okay since day one
airport so much let's direct them in
their favorite course yeah yeah yeah
or do we have one more ah we have two
more I think we have two more third one
okay three out of four Let's go Team
Let's go Team let's go
can you believe that airplanes in the
night skies and the Shooting Stars
win right now iris iris is so scary
oh
my God
[Music]
you will never know what is that oh my
God
thank you
hope you guys enjoyed that in the chat
just got screwed over like you would not
believe
what happened
I'm gonna come back me too me too
because I'm behind you
I got you
yeah okay let's go oh God oh God oh God
oh God
The Blue Team just completed
the team is behind me I
dump it okay let's go let's go let's go
that's Ollie curse is Ollie
oh yeah oh it was good okay all right
and Iris okay that's the Slime
I keep not getting items this is not
looking good yeah okay uh believe in the
orangey yeah
that's Mario Kart Mario Kart
I gotcha
it's not here right now but I'm so proud
of Callie
I don't know how to use the how do you
use the paraglider
uh if you press down
all right I can't hear
oh she blocked it okay
[Music]
oh my gosh
I keep getting screwed over in like the
worst time is Possible Oh my God
everyone in front of me is is Bluetooth
not not the [\h__\h]
again
I love something a miracle happens I
don't know yeah I'm not feeling this one
yeah this is bad this is really bad this
is okay I have never gotten the mushroom
before I couldn't use any of the
shortcuts I can't come back from this me
neither this is unfortunate unless we
get up okay it's okay
yeah couldn't come back
oh
next one next one's gonna be serious
mode wait how many rights
concentration time
this is the last one yeah this is the
last one okay
foreign
I gotta come back how are we gonna come
back what are we picking
I don't know drop down
wait okay
and don't know if she can join in time
wait some someone please don't join
don't choose a race yet if you can
because
I'm joining again okay
oh it's starting oh no it's starting oh
no yeah I think this is uh
one okay
oh no
attention
[Music]
I'm just gonna start playing Mario Kart
because yeah
for the next tournament
already hey hello
right because I I don't at all not
really no really okay okay just for
streams yeah
oh
he's really good at this map
[Music]
it's risky
yeah oh is it the one with the Bouncy
Stuff
yeah yeah
I I don't know how to use it I don't
want to rinse the skin because oh I fell
oh sorry
I'm coming in with the same here comes
it's gonna kill me
oh sorry if I hit someone
yeah okay I can't I guess today I
learned that you know even though it's
tea Early fire is somehow on yeah
though unfortunately fine
girl get me on the ground Captain let's
go
one more race okay
let's go let's go let's go
blue shelling coming
that's garbage
oh no
oh my gosh sorry I should have held that
I was very trigger happy be careful
there's a shall I threw that don't get
hit
and then I'm suddenly said okay I'll
Trust my drifting skills RNG I do see
the Red Shell going around you deserve
that a lot of people though like it
doesn't immediately go to the closest
one it goes it tries
is this it
is it oh because it only finished oh you
finished
only finished the course that's like a
blue shell came to me
it's okay as long as we got the pop
spots
okay
that said sarcasm
oh
[Music]
my God
okay
[Music]
I got disconnected like right before the
last lap oh that was me earlier friends
after the Wi-Fi cables
but that probably means that you know
the last round if if Lisa you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round final
result is not really accurate
um but that's okay but let's just say
the last round was an extra Encore for
fun and yeah and I would like to give
out some golden yugos
right so okay they're not showing up on
your stream they're only on my stream
but I'd like I would like to give one a
golden juggle to Ina for winning almost
everything
by Speedy videos
[Music]
and I would like to give uh another uh
golden Yago as uh to Iris for also being
absolutely amazing
[Music]
another golden juggle goes to Dana for
being I guess the strongest in the ID
team holy moly
another golden yango goes to gura for
being absolutely the speediest shark
I've ever seen yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
speed squirrel
[Applause]
[Music]
another golden yellow
anticipated
and another golden Yago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprised me you surprised me Cali I was
I was looking at you driving there and I
was like damn well what the hell man she
didn't even do practice Arc since she's
so good
my mom was playing
oh
kelly didn't I didn't get last place
even once guys that was my goal yeah
thank you for me everyone thank you we
love you don't mind me uh chat I'm not
gonna be able to fix that now I think
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven
wait who did I not give up
ah you weren't you were surprising me
too sometimes I have I had an eye on you
thank you
goes to me
yeah thank you very much everyone
um I hope you all had fun
um can we get like a last last comment
from everyone let's start with Anya
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more if there's gonna be next
time I don't know maybe
maybe there's gonna I will definitely be
a next time yeah
there's always room for improvement
um
Kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organized the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast Bingo I'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you
[Music]
it was fun to organize
good uh closing comment please
oh thank you I want to say thank you
also to Ina and Kiara for all the hard
work you guys put into this tournament
thank you and I'm very I'm proud of
myself for not doing nearly as bad as I
thought I would and I would like to uh
say that it was probably because I fixed
my switch legs so I didn't have any lag
let's go Gamers let's go
no excuse him so I watched and I won
though I can use that excuse
in a long time I think yeah no practice
baby
let's go
let's go raw challenge
[Music]
ah yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this I know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh Beyond but
yes thank you for this golden yellow I
will cherish it and talk to you tonight
thank you so much
thank you
thank you thank you okay I've completely
disappeared I'm sorry guys
okay Iris closing comments please thank
you so much for inviting me to this
wonderful tournament Kiara and thank you
so much Ina for the very very cute
assets and yes I will practice more so
that we can I can get go against
inaudia yeah yeah my goal is Nina yeah
I'm really excited to do this again
hopefully one day yeah
[Music]
thank you I hope yeah one day I want to
win against Ina too that's a big big
goal that would be a big accomplishment
it's not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
I'm so glad I'm so glad you joined hello
Ian because that's what made this uh
tournament possible yeah I'm really glad
to be able to join this wonderful
Tournament being part of the cool kids
yeah
all right
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go through
logos and stuff and even the thumbnails
those must have been hard and also for
innocent fight for making all of those
acids so quickly like you guys really um
how do I say it I really appreciate it a
lot and I'm sure all of us do so thank
you so much for your hard work it was
really fun playing with everyone and um
I may have not popped everyone but one
way or another you guys will all be my
bottoms
I forgot about that goal yeah
oh my God you'll get them someday only
you'll get them
one day thank you thank you all right
um first of all um thank you for you
Kiara for organized this thing and thank
you you guys stop thanking me
I mean I I don't think without without
you organizing we will don't be like
this
it's it's rare to gather all the whole
life Indonesian whole event to get your
life so I'm so thankful for that and
also
um big thanks to Ina 2 for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and I hope uh in the future we can
be like this again yeah
yes yes yes I hope so too definitely I
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around Christmas or New Year's Eve
[Music]
closing comments please yeah I'd like to
say a big thank you to uh Kiara for
organizing it of course I know like
organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and like schedules
is really really difficult but you
really put a lot of effort into
organizing it commissioning like the
logo and everything really thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
hats and cards like in your Mario Kart
streams in the future too
and uh yeah thank you everyone for
joining us today like it was so much fun
like playing with everyone and I hope
you can do it again
thank you
cooperation this was a great
collaboration between uh kfb and Taco
Taco Bell taco eats definitely
let's work
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speeding
closing comments please okay I know you
said stuff but thank you Kiara
also in a senpai ah thank you so much
and I had a lot of fun uh there was a
little mishap there there was a little
disconnection issue but overall I had a
lot of fun and I would love to have this
kind of tournament again in the future
let's do it you are so good yeah
so I'll get better and I'll erect
everybody next time
[Laughter]
[Music]
comments please
okay so it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you
so to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like those are amazing and
also okay uh I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here yeah yes like well
uh I'd appreciate more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to I'd be I would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much I
love you guys thank you okay
[Music]
closing comments ah well first uh I'd
like to apologize
if I was salty if I curse that you guys
oh no yeah
and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and Inna
you guys worked really hard thank you
guys and thank you everybody for
participating it's really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules so thank you and I
had a lot of fun thank you thank you
thank you
now that we have whole Council we can
like we don't have to rely on these
exact 12 members anymore so next time if
you want you can do shout casting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities to Fan communities of
hello Ian and hello ID together and just
feeling United definitely and I am
always glad to um do stuff like this
again so I I would gladly invite you
guys again whenever you have time for it
and want to join and I'm sorry that you
know because since it's such an
international collaboration
um it's not going to be an ideal time
for everyone so I'm so sorry for the
girls who had to wake up at like six
seven a.m or something like that I'm so
sorry I know it's tough I I have no
problem it was fun
watch the news
I hope your mom enjoyed the
tournaments
then with that I would like to
officially close to Holo Ian Holo ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone take care
of your golden yagos polish him every
day he wants to be shiny and sparkly and
yeah I'll see you guys
[Music]
[Applause]
bye everyone
[Music]
thank you