[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello
[Music]
foreign
okay
ah
in your show
okay
do a
hello hello
I've got a gun unfortunately you know I
still can't really I don't know
can't use the
the thing the attachment thing
I don't know why
[Music]
it will be probably like this
for a while either they fix it or I
completely change my whole setup
hmm
but it's okay we like scuffed
attachments that don't move because it's
nostalgic it's like you know the scuff
it's nice it's nice the amateur look you
know
I like it
[Laughter]
yeah we did it for two years mm-hmm
you know
[Laughter]
[Music]
how you doing guys
I have I have a nectarine for snacking
healthy snacking
when I need it
you know nectarines
I like nectarines they're they they kind
of um I feel like they're one of those
type of fruits that don't like mold and
go bad immediately
um
yeah
and they have lots of lots of uh how to
say fruit flesh
around it so it's not like you know I
feel like certain certain fruit you
don't get much
from it because it's just like most of
it is the seed
yeah
yeah yeah
I think I've seen them before I feel
like they're really popular here because
they're so so durable they don't die as
fast as other fruits
from what I've
um
what I've experienced eh they mold
really badly true yeah yeah like I at
the supermarket they had a separate
individual
okay
fruit slush is how we say it in German
directly translated but yeah they had
like they had them individual and all
the individual ones were beautiful and
then they had them packed and like
packed stuff what five six seven and
those were all moldy yeah but that's
just generally when buying fruit in
packaged packs I feel like they they all
they must know Almost Do It purposefully
to like just get those fruit out too
they just put the the already bad
looking ones at the bottom
hoping that no one will see it
and then you buy it but I always this is
because it happened too many times I
always when I pick up like a package of
whatever fruit I already I I always look
at the bottom of it
and look very closely because I got
[\h__\h] over too many times by buying ex
like expensive fruit
yeah
it sucks it's so annoying man and I I
completely stopped buying strawberries
this year because I literally could not
find any good strawberries
I tried like maybe two and they were
disgusting two packages
or all bad and then I I I I I for some
time I was like oh wait
I get quite lucky when I buy
um what's it called uh not blue
blueberry
I guess
heidelbam
Nick Promenade
blueberries I'm not sure I don't mean
the the dark blue black raspberries I
mean the
are they blueberries okay what do you
call the dark blue raspberries those are
blackberries okay okay so confusing
so blue blueberries
I have some lucky lucky purchases with
blueberries so I thought oh maybe maybe
they're more durable than I thought they
were and then then I bought a package
that was like so tasteless I got
disappointed again man
why why it's so difficult to get like
good yeah blueberry
berries and in my opinion raspberries
are pretty decent when Frozen
uh and strawberries are [\h__\h]
have you guys ever had good strawberries
that are Frozen from the frozen section
I think they're always [\h__\h]
right
oh well oh well for sure
[Music]
thank you
I added five songs
the thing is with the with the remixes
we never get past the first song because
the remixes are like I think free songs
in one data
I don't know if we ever get to the end
of it
[Music]
we're back again
we we failed twice yesterday
at our task but I gotta say it's just a
bit ridiculous what
what's little Jacob's problem huh
oh
what's the little Jacob's problem what
did I do
what did I do to make him mad
huh
take him out [\h__\h] him why do they all I
it's like they're my girlfriends why do
they all want so much attention why do
they get so mad when I don't have time
to get out for them because I need to
get money
huh
[\h__\h] issue
I saw the playlist but I didn't have
time to go through it maybe next time
but thank you for compiling from the
organ thank you for compiling it
it's so quiet in my ear mush
okay better now
let me try something
um
oh
uh uh I don't know where the buzzing
sound comes from
uh uh uh uh is it better
I completely lowered the
uh low frequencies uh
it's a bit better maybe
uh
um
I mean it's still kind of there
ah
but you won't know this once
once we have some sound in the game
anyway
ah so my frequencies are
very alone now when I speak low
but doesn't matter because you normally
don't speak low
I'll have the the boom boom voice
got that boom boom pound
what are we doing are we hopefully still
uh in the middle of what I stopped last
time was it P.M
was it
is PM is PM right yeah
right before okay let's see let's just
go there and see where oh hey hey hey
[Music]
I need that I mean I personally think it
looks ridiculous
but I guess it was like cool back in the
day
it's like a machine gun on your on the
top of your car oh that's the uh-huh
that's the thing I I was
without the comedy club in the game
sometime I heard there's a comedy club I
wanna I wanted
um
okay
let's see if we can find new songs
[Music]
for escaping
[Laughter]
easy easy lyrics
[Music]
wait I'll need it to be louder
thank you
[Music]
sorry
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm giving up the car what Roman cousin
I
you bought it or I did go I'm a
why can't you jump when you're on the
phone
Penthouse mother lunch on okay it's
where he got us the car okay so long ago
that you're dead traffic is [\h__\h]
because of me
I heard this before
okay it was like he got the same car but
the the machine gun is not out
oh
now we have to unfortunately wait
change the radio station
there it is
[Music]
y'all guys if it happens like if you if
anyone here has a car and drives a lot
I recommend putting this on your on like
a mixtape and listening to it in your
car
[Music]
foreign
that was it it was that short I guess it
was running while I was out of the car
I have nothing to say to you I nearly
ran into your house
also before
I wish you had been there we could have
had some fun nothing much fun as I would
have had with Romans believe me
okay
let me listen to my purple ball in peace
I don't want to be disturbed when I pull
football
yeah yeah oh I swear we pick him up
right but first we have to do the chit
chat I guess
[Laughter]
uh
okay
So the plan was you want to listen to
this again let's listen to it again I
guess
oh hey Nico in case also for the people
who didn't watch the ending last night's
off my [\h__\h] sister boy we're talking
not having casual sex Patrick I pray
after the amount of practice you've had
you'd know the difference sure I know
the difference one leaves you feelings
emptying alone and the other's casual
sex and I'm quite sure you and Mr Nico
here I'm sure Dad also leaves him alone
for sure
okay oh we're gonna play real nice
clean is a [\h__\h] whistle one previous
owner yeah yeah shitty guns ready for
action like the I can hear it from the
sound of it the Clickety clackity we got
an opportunity my boy yep fortune favors
the brave gotta make hay while the sun
shines
all right let's go I'm in where's you
out I'm Up Down For What down for Robin
a thief Robin Hood exactly Robin did you
think you're Robin Hood who are you
going through so wrong
wrong with that
unless you will end up sharing the money
that you get we all died
of the public and the money is good
indeed
you in big guy
Kill Ya
well
since you put it that way
I mean mm-hmm they'll only share it
among themselves but that's not you
can't call that Robin Hood
just because you're sharing
can you get
it yeah
car for four people there's one right
here uh
yeah let's hope let's hope nobody saw
that I didn't look closely
yeah I think we're okay
police just drove away
okay
guys get in
here you go
[Music]
it always starts with the same song so
we always have to listen to those in the
beginning okay here's a new one a mafia
controlled Waste Management plan you
[\h__\h] guessed it
talk again about a big payoff they just
got a bad cash payoff enchiladas I can't
tell all those watt families
pecorinos it's the [\h__\h] maybe I'll
change
what type of cheese pegarinos is a bunch
of Guido games
where they don't talk together
um
[Music]
specifically only to her I didn't say it
we were in charge it's [\h__\h] true they
were just communicating
yeah because apparently they have to
rest their fruits
I feel like always
break I mean okay sometimes but really
rarely
[\h__\h] you Gordon I'll [\h__\h] come back I
can't believe this in a minute a quiet
stream was being watched by like over 90
000 people my brother he may have a
badge nine zero zero zero Zeroes
but that was the last thing it was like
94k you know Frankie I got a story oh my
God you do another [\h__\h] story shut up
Gordon
the Lord Jerry knows the truth the truth
he only put on that castle we did it
before remember in December do you
remember when I had a meal stream in
December it was quite funny because I
like the others do the talking model
Community leader in my ass you're just
worries you'll start clamping down on
you ain't your package I'd like to see
him try it and Marina has experience
with it anyway I still remember the
the stream where
my Senpai was sick and they were doing
uh was it was it garlic phone
and people were trying to
for her like in Canada for example
was impersonating mining senpai
I mean for real
[Music]
you know yesterday I was cooking both
individual literal and in the
metaphorical sense I was cooking uh some
another collab
silence I was talking
like acid
and I showed her as an example my
unbelievably believable stream
because the we had like cute assets
there
and then I was like you know what you
know what because I was looking into the
archive listening in a little bit and
and I felt like wait you know I should I
should it's about time I do another
unbelievably believable stream but not
with Memphis time and you will see I'm
like
mixing it up [\h__\h] truth
okay
I should get armor
my armor right now can I like when I I
still have a little bit left apparently
but I can buy new one right
[Music]
the online on this game no I asked I
actually haven't tried online either on
GTA 5 nor on
this one
I should
why is the left side so empty
where's that police car so [\h__\h] oh wait
is that is that normal oh no
[Music]
yeah
I know it's the wrong way but why is the
side so empty
[Music]
all right
what a weird pack that I'm driving I was
in the Middle Island
and I wanted to go that way
but somehow it brought me back to the
other Island I guess to go onto the
highway
[\h__\h] I missed it can I still fix it
let's look it up
[Music]
maybe not
I don't want to go online I have to go
to the green line because I'm
I'm going to the uh armor shop actually
at this point I could go to this one
just four Killers happily listening to
Idol songs from Subaru Senpai in their
car together on the way to their highs
with their machine guns who had their
grand names and their bulletproof vest
nothing to see here all normal they just
you know they have
we have a a cultured music case
they just want to have fun you know
music taste doesn't doesn't necessarily
say anything about the type of person
can you guys stay here and stay in the
car
no
stay in the car
my god listen to the radio AC is on
radio is playing what else do you want
uh
enter okay you guys maybe want to get
some too no okay you're gonna regret it
stay alive
okay same car and now we're gonna go
properly to our destination I don't
think I can buy armor for them
okay now we Follow the yellow
[Music]
I like that part I like when in music
they they put these accents
they start a chorus again but they
started with like kind of like these
quiet breaks and then they go bam bam
bam I love that it's so good it feels so
hype
like yeah let's go another round
so satisfying
do you want to stand by
um
yeah also that yeah when the last chorus
suddenly has a higher key than the rest
hell yeah
and why purple again huh why is this
Pokemon keep on showing up
there we go
[Music]
unfortunately I can't really listen too
much of it but listen to it again in a
moment later afterwards if I finally
finish this Mission and it should be a
boat docked out back for the getaway oh
a bug I completely missed that
information
for the first time
guys why are you huh
wait I'm I'm trying to ah no this is
fine I think this is why I wanted to
start I think on the left side
already
also I've been I've been getting a lot
of feedback uh
oh my God everybody's like apparently
confused or like I don't know fascinated
that I keep on using this gun
and that I tried to do try to hit verify
goals with it all the time
I understand what's the problem it's
just comfortable for me
I like it I wasn't this kind of was it a
different one I think it was that one I
just I just shut the [\h__\h] away who are
you
it's a normal person wait okay yeah it's
that one it's that one this one which
one was that one just uh
I hate this
I want a better position here in this
one
nice
but thanks for all the beautiful
compilations of my
really high level
shots
we gotta warm up right now so they're
not the best right now there's someone
here
can I film with this one
oh yeah I can
see I didn't even know that
foreign
[Music]
yeah that might be true I don't know for
some reason I really enjoyed the handgun
in GTA 5. not so much in GTA 4 though
whoa
okay who's left
oh yeah he did
someone here
on your side
those are my friends right
all right
he just ducked the moment I shot
come on you gotta get him right in front
of him never mind I did it
I did it I'm gonna be MVP man the whole
game I'm the MVP
tell me when I should switch out certain
weapons because they're better because
apparently you guys can tell just by
looking at it should I switch out this
one that looks like [\h__\h] this is in this
this in German I think we call a short
uh
anyway it's trash
[Music]
why does it why does it sometimes when
I'm scrolling in games sometimes shot
flinder right
uh short oh
that's also a spot Flint
he Scrolls my chat sometimes
oh wait I'm on
wrong weapon this one
okay nice job
it's funny because short flinder which
is apparently the actual uh way to say
it
and I would call it a trash gun though
because it I don't like it it's it's
really trash
it's another another word play I'm
really good with wordplays today
are we going in guys
I guess so
foreign
times
[Music]
unsatisfying is he dead I think so no uh
okay
was friendly fire a thing in this game
yes okay
just making sure oh my God my munition
my ammunition I don't have much
ammunition left but when I walk around
those like red glowing guns I'm not sure
is it giving me ammunition but only for
the specific gun that it's showing
I need to use the SMG gladly gladly
yeah if it matches okay okay
what do we got
no one there
so once I go up and I come back down I
feel like they get a lot of
um green green
not reimbursement
re-re-re repopulation
here's here's a bit more
reinforcements yes okay
did you see that that was another
another very very
they're all aiming for something up
there well okay let me go for it guys
it's coming up
okay all dead so so far so good
and then people gave me advice that I
should maybe try to
um you know get some stuff done some
more while I'm here
wow
let go
okay
you're not gonna get anywhere if you
guys keep on shooting without looking
use the AR I don't need it
do I look like I need it
I'm just hoping those are people that I
don't like
okay but we're going in we're going out
a different way from where we
uh where we came in right this time
[Music]
ends with bombing out of nowhere I swear
those are endless reinforcements I I'm
pretty sure
[Music]
right okay maybe I'll just run it
but try my best to clear it but okay
yeah okay
maybe always should have done it this
way where's this boat huh well you hold
these boys back okay
they're holding him back where's the
book
Escape From The Depot with [\h__\h] okay
okay
come on Packy
oh lame when they fall down and it takes
them ages to get back up and I just have
to wait for him
where's the boat
just out there I'll race you
swim out and get in the boat oh that one
okay wait are we sure we're ready
okay
Kyle
it's already turned on I think even
left ship to swim faster that's what I'm
doing and then
then okay ah
space not F okay
I've never tried it before but
cute I want to try to try driving a boat
like this on the Wattpad it looks like
fun oh but I hate it I hate when
you fly up like this [\h__\h] beautiful
we did ourselves
don't figure out it was us they ripped
him off but don't [\h__\h] worry about it
so this figure was another one of the
five families also mccreerys are under
the [\h__\h] radar nowadays it ain't a
problem I hope
for my sake shut up and think about the
money guys that don't work think about
my sister if I'm you you're only getting
your hands on one of those things
I just run out I didn't know that's what
they wanted from me I thought really
they wanted me to clear everything
[Music]
really thought so
[\h__\h] world because that's what I
normally have to do
because when I ran out I attempted to
run out a few times but there were just
so many people and I got so much damage
I got so much HP loss I thought I
thought that's just you know
I thought I should clear first before
running out oh well
oh well
yeah first time I also ran the wrong way
that's not what I wanted to do oh dude
controls
okay I I was on esdf instead of wasd
my fault maybe just maybe how do I get
up oh nice you can actually do that
tutorial skipped what
yeah can't kill me if they're dead Nico
man look also I don't want to leave any
any Witnesses
likes you just as friends
I'm gonna send you a number I'll give
her a call man but uh I don't think
she'll wanna see me trust me she will
call her man
I don't really like to go on these kind
of forced dates that are recommended to
me by
my friends my so-called friends
what are you guys doing anyway where am
I oh
uh should we go to Packy
again let's meet up
I guess so
it doesn't happen at all
officers uh aiming the gun at anyone
besides me
oh
what's happening is he gonna go into the
car
yeah
he's really going in
[\h__\h] idiots
oh my God incompetent police
I told my brother's about to I got a big
job plan put on a suit a tie and some
good shoes and get over here cause a
[\h__\h] shitload but the only place to
go for that shirt yeah I already got all
of that huh where who wrote that to me
where does he want me to go
I want a car but I don't want it to be
around the police
so I want
I want one of those like interesting
boxy cars that are driving around now
well at Nami
I thought I was doing that
Little Italy
sit down
Little Italy New York Has a Little Italy
I thought this one wouldn't have an
alarm
[Music]
together
you and me hit the river is powerful bro
uh gold boating
[Music]
I haven't been voting before
sound like a mini game
I'm actually accepting it I can't
believe it I was about to turn it down
but when he said boating
[Music]
very interesting
I dropped the board I'll gladly drop the
boat this is our boats are always
stealing it
[Music]
all right
way more fun than bowling
I keep on missing my turns
also I need to
Shuffle
[Music]
you're a winner let's treat these ladies
with ladies
bro I thought it was just us
thanks to the memberships
wow nice boat well that's actually a
[\h__\h] nice boat
it looks like um one of those cat
feeders that recognize the chip of the
cat
if you know what I mean you know what I
mean
[Music]
yo how much does a boat like this cost
no Rosie and we can continue to listen
to the music
we met up in a club and it was intense
wasn't it babe yeah I was standing at
the bar ordering a magnum sculpting the
floor you know flexing my pecs
easy solutions these girls were
suppressed
that's amazing
ah and the readies I was dropping all
right get rid of the attitude bro
[Music]
it's probably closer to 200k
all the threats are insane
why does a boat cost so much I guess
because it gives you endless Freedom
over the seas and you can finally become
a pirate oh why
like from a technical point of view I I
don't see how it's much different from
from a car
[Music]
son swim you know just gotta add a
little bits of you know spice to it and
then it will swim too
just like some
some swimming AIDS
take them away from gouda and put them
on a car and there you go you got a boat
[Music]
you can get nice books with 20K you put
Power boots and more like a push oh this
is a power boat okay
but the one I was riding before at the
Escape probably cheaper right
like this one
[Music]
this one's way less fancy
I listen to it already
why I always sing songs yes
shuffles I have like 17 songs in here
I think it's broken
it's broken
it
[Music]
the scan huh
what's what's the radio mode
press n to skip songs not b
okay
um radio has ads number between that's
actually kind of fun too
I want to hear the ads but okay let's
just Shuffle and then
[Music]
okay we heard this one before
yesterday I want to hear what comes
after it because it's like remixes of a
whole life song
always switching to
[Music]
that boat
oh where oh no specific very specific
spot there we go
oh it's really on a star-shaped thing I
didn't know that
you ladies are much hotter than that
[\h__\h]
okay we can go home
that was it we just needed to confirm
that our [\h__\h] are hotter than that
[\h__\h] nice
question was the the freedom happiness
lady an actual person that that was
modeled after
or is it just a random you know
just to sign to show you you know the
freedom or all that yeah actual size
shut up
it's a gift from France
so was was there okay but but they just
like took a random woman or was the
woman actually significant
[Music]
Hillary Clinton hasn't been alive long
enough as much as the the statue right
the statue's been around longer than
Hillary Clinton
it just looks like her problem in the
game maybe
or what you guys are just messing with
me
[Music]
next
in game with modeled after Hillary
trying to use this
whole opportunity to get some education
in and you guys are just messing with me
I'm not learning anything nobody knows
about the IRL ones
okay
so it may have just been a random woman
if it was like a significant woman that
gave that meaning to the Statue I
suppose we would know
she wanted GTA band so they put her in
the game
really
why did she want it banned was it
because she bought it's an evil game
[Music]
I'd let you Captain these ladies but
they want the proceed that's fine I'll
take the lady the big lady
Freedom lady
[Music]
I think last time we had a thumbs down
from Brucie so it's good oh and hey I
was the same song is still playing in
our car
so maybe we can listen to the song that
comes after that if we're lucky
um
X or PM or FM
what do you want guys
your choice
change from time to Green
um I can see that how that would happen
yeah
[Music]
oh
I sang this before in the previous Whole
Life karaoke
if you guys want to hear it look up
sorry
for life
[Music]
oh
cute but we already reached our
destination
[Music]
what's next
what was this song this is a remix but
what was it
because I'm a first
good idea and that was um
the the red track song
okay good
can I get a discount for me not having
used up the previous one
it's already bangkai
maybe our ammo for the fancy gun that
you guys like so much
foreign
[Music]
did you guys see the ID first and second
gen horogram that came out today it's
John
was speaking very good sounding
Indonesian all the time
like legit I mean I don't know
Indonesian but it sounds really good
like she must have practiced really hard
is she practicing
Indonesian now
Indonesia
[Music]
they could have let her like voice it in
Japanese but they made her do it in
Indonesia feel free to browse buddy
okay I buy this again I didn't even ah
because my HP that's not full okay and
how to buy ammo for the gun I'm thinking
for this gun is this the same no
how do I buy ammo
is this huh
I say yes and then I call back to say no
right yeah definitely I will be there in
the next hour
because I will not do that by the gun
again this is it right I think it looks
the same
check back soon this is my model only
no
[Music]
who was that
Little Jacob right
[\h__\h] I can't get the ammunition sorry
I've got to back out of the drinking
what do they call me about
I think I'm fine on ammo on the on the
weapons
can I get in oh
I'll be fine
[Music]
P.M
now it'll be fun I don't need anything
else
[Music]
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
this part is pretty badass
[Music]
what do you call this again
um
I knew it I forgot
at that step yeah that's what I wanted
to say dubstep
[Music]
it's the end of the remix of one of them
foreign
[Music]
huh I want to sing with her
Let's Dance
[Music]
foreign
Hallelujah
bounce
[Music]
foreign
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
for tonight
[Music]
melodies
bam
boom boom boom boom boom
[Music]
la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la
thank you for letting me do that wait
uh
[Music]
in the start
sometimes you just gotta take time to
Vibe you know eh money
even here guys
ah come on
Nani
God damn it
Sam that's in four hours in the game
comedy club which one is it is it this
one
is it the the magic
this one Cabaret Club
Middle Island
where could it be I haven't seen it yet
apparently
is it like middle
or butter or tap
um
save the game to reload time oh that's a
thing
uh uh look at the map ah is it there
[Music]
saving okay but I can't save I have to
go to my home right uh
is my home close
there's one here and one there
that's so lame
a lot of place
[Music]
I wish you could just save anywhere man
why do I have to go home for it
bowling
club together
strip club sounds good I pick you up in
next hour because it's just wonderful
news see you soon
do you really
go there now with you
[Music]
sorry cousin I cannot join you with the
titty bar the tennis ball go by yourself
I have hot [\h__\h] and they're begging
me for my company
okay now we got Thanksgiving
[Music]
sorry I read that someone got dizzy from
my stream doing this
yesterday so I I'll I'll stop
I just want you to feel the beats
[Music]
okay
let me go first this guy is threatening
me
it's a random 360 moments this thing I
mean that was so weird but
I loved the edit for you know with them
I had round round
I like that one it was perfect literally
asking for it to be made
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so much effort to just save my game
uh
f
but what time will it be
that looks so uncomfortable
plus six hours okay so then we can pick
up packing
or Ohio
so now it's 9 46
a wonderful day to start a heist
wonderful time to start a heist there is
no better time than this
oh there's blue Clapper remix I think
running
clap your hands but we heard that one
before
but I think after that comes the uh next
remix so let's
continue
[Music]
diving
swimming
[Music]
your hands
I don't know
[Applause]
just one star
I wanted to pray
[Music]
I'll be moved
you guys like listening to whole life
box with me
it's like a listen along not on what's
wrong
in between having some fun with shooting
spree
[Music]
it's over unfortunately
makes the car rides a lot nicer really I
mean I personally also really liked just
the silent ones but oh well
it's a kind of History
[Applause]
[Music]
Nico these are my two brothers well two
of my brothers the two that count Derek
the two dead count hi Derek has just
returned to the family fold after a good
few years in the Old Country involved in
the struggle sort of like you I'd
imagine and Jerry Jerry's the man Joey
with G that can't mean anything good
it's uh nice to meet you Nico's a trip
man I met him through that Puerto Rican
coke dealer so you won't involve him in
family business what do you know about
him what I know is he likes a fight and
he ain't the [\h__\h] law oh no offense
Mister that ain't good enough well it's
good enough for me he's a good lad Jerry
you don't know [\h__\h] about me I'm good
enough for anything I make a point on
you guys to the unfortunate victims of
brother systems speak about my parents
like that oh you like [\h__\h] Cleopatra
15 generations of brothers sisters
[\h__\h] and you're so thick you take
orders off my Idiot Brother [\h__\h] who's
so stupid
if there is a problem
I'll go no trouble I have other ways of
making money there's no problem Jerry
knows best information
on Wikipedia
ah no problem
possibly boys do it supposedly don't
screw up what's the word that you say if
you don't want to get in trouble with a
lawyer no way
um what was that and you
nothing personal but don't allegedly
help Cleopatra doesn't sue me
no I know about you know them people
anywhere at the time wanting to keep
their bloodline pure yeah
well I had one oh is that mine no it
looks like mando
hey
no no
this one
police
let's do this
all right here's how the [\h__\h] is going
down we're gonna go inside and each take
down a security guard me and say Michael
here are gonna handle the civilians
while Nico and Derek manage the
employees anyone tries anything you put
them down hard once the situation has
been controlled Derek's going to rig the
vault door with explosions I got enough
pe4 here to get through anything they
throw at us I never heard of that it's
so limey name for C4 that Derek here
picked up over there I ain't having this
argument with you
what we're using is controllable enough
to go through any vault door without
incinerating whatever's inside not going
to leave much residue on the notes
either so they should be watching oh
they're going to be washable all right
can't wait to see what sort of kick C4
residue is going to give me when I snort
up a line of Chopped with one of them
notes first what the [\h__\h]
second it's pe4 that's C4
I'm very familiar with C4 you know
nothing about nothing Patrick I'm honest
about me demons I know a thing or two
about C4 expression is hit the nail on
the head backy really Michael you don't
think I know that Jay was right about
you Mike your parents must have been
twins to produce a kid as dumb as you
I'm surprised you ain't got three eyes
no balls and a club foot don't bring my
parents into this packing all right all
right we all know what we're doing
because it was in the airplane that I
was in down into the ball to get the
money while me and my brother handle the
crowd control all makes sense to me
you guys can stop arguing for a few
minutes then
I'll be okay that's what they wrote in
red on the toilet
um inside yeah C4 and then we had to fly
back good story good story
allegedly no for real
but it wouldn't go off apparently I
don't know
[Music]
they need to know
holy [\h__\h] this remix
oh
wow
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
I love it I love it
Hong Kong
[Music]
we're in the perfect perfect area right
now for the song
[Music]
I have to go I'm so sorry maybe we can
listen to it later again maybe it'll
still be playing
wait until you're inside wait to get
dollied up we're grabbing a bag
oh [\h__\h]
this one ain't easy okay and focused
baby
none of you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] move oh [\h__\h]
none of us is gonna get another for
playing hero all he's gonna get is a
bullet to the heart don't none of you
worry about nothing we're here for the
bank's money it's going to a greater
call shut up
what is the greatest cause more
Coca-Cola open the door
hold on
thanks
get on the floor now but sir you twerk
for me okay
very nice very nice hey yo
remember what does that mean I'm gonna
take these
Luis but this ain't such a good idea
yeah
judging that pass in my high school
championship football game was a bad
idea
deep broke my leg in 13 places oh [\h__\h]
I just built out of bed
I guess so
yeah
oh oh
the pe4 has been molded he's so set to
explode in 60 seconds the way he moves
is so funny we're your friends me and my
brother here why are you telling them
with Brothers you idiot that's gonna
make it hard for him to find us isn't it
I'm trying to be honest with these
people we put them through a lot today
[\h__\h] these people [\h__\h] your cars that
shit's over this hasn't been that much
yeah so much trouble that's gonna narrow
the search ain't it [\h__\h] you take the
needle out your arm then tell me what to
do I'll let you tell me what to do
another word from your relatives for
stuff like this
[Music]
yeah
sure what did you think would happen
when there's four people and you just
won
[\h__\h]
what I do
go down to the fold and get the money uh
uh uh let me or orientate is this yeah
oh my God
you better have a helicopter ready for
me
okay crew where
oh
is that police or is that ours okay it's
police
that's the only thing I asked for it's a
helicopter am I
am too much
in GTA if I would have prepared all of
this [\h__\h]
so much better preparation in GTA 5 man
[Music]
so what do we do so stupid it's a bacon
Factory
[\h__\h] stick to me boys
stupid
[Music]
[\h__\h] idiots unbelievable I can't
believe it
you have too many cops play the path I'm
trying uh oh God oh God
oh
that's not gonna happen to the car that
I'm at Ryan oh God
where are my friends
why are they over there
sorry I'm just I'm just
money
I grew up again
[Music]
so far so good right not so bad
I knew he was gonna come out I I was
waiting for it I felt it
don't make things worse
[Music]
got him
he somehow on the right side he doesn't
want to shoot really I think it was my
positioning
you're welcome
okay there's a lot of people involved
here I see it
say okay okay
good job
yo they dropped the best I didn't even
need it that much but
um
look at me relying on my beautiful
little mini gun again and getting
headshots left and right that was
incredible
good job me
are we done on that side
no oh
beautiful I saw fireworks definitely I
can I can put Bingo on that one
where is everybody out there
you go
nice
[Music]
this is what I like to do this is fun
this is big and big mission this is what
I want to do in GTA man look at all
these small fishes I don't want to fry
no small fishes we need the big fishes
[Music]
poor people not gonna feel
fat if they only eat smokers we need to
fry the biscuits
I haven't seen combat like this
where are they oh is someone up there
oh
sneaky little [\h__\h]
but it's hard to shoot through the
stairs
I don't see anyone either
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
all right all right
[Music]
I would like to see some stats after
this who killed the most people I would
say it was me nice headshot
okay
who's who's like always shooting me
[Music]
oh they're in the
armor shop is right there actually
in here
why why why why why no Chicago they're
up what where did they go
here ah sorry guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah maybe they were buying ammo
Chopper
[Music]
needs
where are we four people
by the way
guys stuff like this never ends well
can I take this down
[Music]
why it's not clear that Round Guys
the [\h__\h] you went in first
I want another best place by the way
see that guys Chihuahua cracked
[Music]
now crap
am I cracked or what
just gotta sometimes be a little bit
aggressive you know can we go through
I mean someone's there
okay yay let me pick up some stuff maybe
there's a vest somewhere
no
no no no no fast what that one was too
lucky
for one time I got a vest
oh we're going into
you okay
okay yeah learning a new word what did I
say
being cracked
oh I am am I not okay
but wait
run run run run
nice cover yeah a non-existent cover
s
[Music]
okay here we go I bought us some time
guys faster faster
I'm actually surprised we don't have six
stars yet at this point
it was his job the both of you shut the
[\h__\h] up
at the street level really
mad catch
kid are they where are they are they
already no they're they're still there
okay
I wonder if they'll be waiting for me
five is maximum okay I thought six might
be it
free
are they losing track of me
ah I love packing behind oh my God I
swear if I lose the if
you lose the mission here
I see them all what do you mean I left
packing behind why is he not moving
towards me
huh
oh there he is who are you
he's just working here what is he doing
okay I think he's following me now
I swear Packy if we lose this Mission
because of you
that that is not gonna amuse me
see it was clear before oh is it like
scripted that when only when [\h__\h] comes
along that's when
[Music]
okay
that was that was a pedestrian I'm sorry
but why was The Pedestrian there in the
first place make sure to close it up
here we go
did I get a headshot because I don't
think my health was that low
whoa
[\h__\h] Packy's fault
[Music]
wow
okay but up until that point it was easy
so we can just do it quickly again
that's all right we're heading to this
um
Nico you're the designated driver
um the guy around the corner already
gave me a big shot huh
yeah that's a surprise
because first time I ran around there
was no one there Jesus
yeah this will be the car
no Vesta don't worry I'll go grab on
again
oh this music
let's do this
excuse you man
okay
this music will cheer me up Gerald is
very clear about the way things are
going down boys me and Michael are on
the civilians Derek and Nico yeah Derek
Did you sort out the charge for the
vault door unfortunately
I felt like it at least
and then we get a headshot he was such a
sweet little boy when I left this city
he was gone a long time yeah
I remember you've changed
doesn't oh on the way to there's uh two
armor shops
all right
I feel the brotherly love and
love and the job though sure so there
you got the charge rigged up to your
phone had a bit of trouble with that
couldn't find a pager to rig the Blasted
Capital had to put the thing on the
timer all right all right we can roll
with the timer that's cool
you and Michael to go down into the
Vault to get them grab as much as you
can carry okay don't need to tell me
twice
yeah I think enough ammo is dropping
from the cops so
like they dropped so much
so it doesn't really matter we just need
armor for the beginning
[Music]
and then we good and there was hope one
armor drop too so if we're lucky it's
gonna drop again
[Music]
yeah
my SMG ammo what the [\h__\h] thanks Michael
knew I could count on the dumbest member
of the group to throw himself into
proceedings the most willingly I was
just saying how I do what you said Pat
me no need to get abusive there's no
need for a brother and sister to get
married but your parents did that and
now you're here I can think of one
reason they needed to get married they
were so ugly that no one else would have
them I had nothing like a sibling's love
AJ nothing like it nothing could make me
look Francis though [\h__\h] Frankie he'd
be pissed if he could see us now
did you see Heidi the birthstone is
getting new outfits finally in next week
or next next week
a relay on the 15th
[Music]
and kobo's silhouette again looks so
extra she's going the ollie path I think
where she gotta have every outfit be
extra extra
but the other ones look really cute
judging from the
um silhouette like Kyla her hair looks
so curly and cute really girly
the like weird shape on her shoulders
makes me think it's also gonna be
something girly
[Music]
it's about time because they only had
the kimonos right
which everybody gets once so
[Music]
good
although I really like their kimonosu oh
wait so think about it
the Advent will also get kimonos
eventually but I don't know if if they
can make it for this year I wonder if
they're gonna aim together this year
because they in theory they still have
time wait until you're inside it's
enough time it might be their first
outfits they have half a year from from
my point of view I can tell you that is
enough time especially since they
already knew it they may have already
been planning for it
who's gonna get a medical playing hero
all you're gonna get is a bullet to the
heart don't none of your words
open the door
open the [\h__\h] door okay okay wait a
minute I can imagine
I can imagine all came almost really
well
except for shielding
I'm not sure what she would go for for
the other time I have an image in my
head
oh yes let's skip it
oh okay here we go
Focus mode is on
eyes on the floor
people let's get the money and get out
of here
boys
[Music]
okay
um
the door
everybody
okay I shot his head off
nice
[Music]
and it would be so proud of me man
peaky notes time
[Music]
you want some help
laughs
blow up the cars guys like you did
before
hi guys why are you there why are you
watching this
It's Curious you stupid [\h__\h]
who are we fighting right now I don't
we're on ah they're already in the
corner oops sorry I'm blind
as always you know what we didn't blow
up anything just don't understand so
boring oh
I got plans for this month
here
okay
I had these [\h__\h] again
I'm gonna go to the trash can
can I get a helmet too
I want a helmet too
I feel like it would help me a lot
and they will die in the mission fail if
you are not fast really oh no okay when
let me move
the front
line
hey okay you happy you happy
I'm doing all the work again
so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
so sorry
[Music]
it just looks at me like they were
shooting
um
each other look that looks like they're
shooting each other come on so far one
of them must be the enemies
[Music]
peaceful life
hey yeah
we're heading along here okay
why don't you fall down come on
okay getting all the ammo endless ammo I
don't even know for what weapon is this
oh the there's again armor but I don't
really need it right now
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
I need the armor drop a little bit later
to be honest
[Music]
just the right moment and now
you got no chance against us
I'm too far
[Music]
thank you
for this cash serious Wawa
you guys like serious Wawa
[Music]
looking good
and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they don't stop
coming and they don't stop coming
okay
[Applause]
please
[Music]
like being back into troubles
show best show wow it comes in many
flavors
[Music]
I shot his hand first because that's all
I saw but that made him want to go away
oh yeah
[Music]
I felt shots
from
doko
there's someone
I can't I can't see
where is that one ah
okay
why are you so great
make it not gray
[Music]
wait there's someone there
they got him okay in the alley in the
alley
no okay
[Music]
I love grenade pollution uh epic [\h__\h]
man any more drops Maybe
foreign
[Music]
okay
perfect for on the window did it go to
the window I feel like it bonked off the
window
okay okay nice nice
I cracked the window
yeah as long as I don't kill myself with
it
I could try to throw a grenade against
the chopper but I'm guessing it's
scripted and you can't take it down
I won't let you guys [\h__\h] me over this
time
okay I'll be more careful in this
section I feel like I was a bit Reckless
goodbye
oh nice you got him unbelievable
yeah I feel like I feel like even even
the CPUs are a bit smarter right now
[Music]
he was just standing there menacingly
I still have full help guys thanks to my
armor
let me
there's a medkit I don't need it at home
unfortunate we always get it when you
don't need it
much faster this time yeah it feels like
it because I know what's coming up so
I'm not scared but I wasn't scared last
time either
okay
honey
really
okay I'm coming
maybe we'll throw again a little nice
grenade
oh yeah okay
[Music]
let's go let's go first train coming
from the right side
I'm too far go faster guys
oh I wonder if the train gets the cops
that are left on the track or if they
dodge it
see if the thing was scripted with if
Packy is not there yet
the cops not showing up
I'll be slow for you guys
I still don't need the medkit mother is
even still half of my armor
okay do you guys want to go first Maybe
scared
and they're not coming right away on it
did we actually
shotgun's better which one is the
shotgun this one but I barely have
munition no that's sniper
this is a shotgun
yo they're really like I I remember on
the mini map they even showed like all
the helicopters and everything
but there's nothing now is it the wrong
section oh it might be
what wait it's so dark I can't see
wait wait wait where do I go
me and I I think it's darker on my
screen
ah
does it go up oh yeah okay
I'm freestyles nice
okay and now see nobody came down here
was it a Time issue
Oh what now
we got more cops on us people
find a four-door car
[Music]
s
[Applause]
[Music]
did they forget who we are now I gotta
explain to us
[Music]
when your kid is living a life you gotta
expect someone to come through don't
drive on Bridges I'm on the bridge what
do I do I'm out of the circle though I
on the road Nico wait we don't want you
to have to break no bad news today
neither do I
oh
what are you guys going on about about
wrong direction and dead end and so on I
did the exact right thing
second try was basically a speed run
[Music]
[Applause]
just a quiet drive home now yeah holy
[\h__\h] I can't believe we got away with
all that
[Music]
yo
that second run was so much smoother
they did not come down the the like
Subway at the end so I'm thinking
pack is staying behind really [\h__\h] me
up there
because they already like the mini map
showed that or like they they know were
down there [\h__\h] I missed it again
and I went in
yeah it was literally just Packy's fault
I was so so close to the Escape
[Music]
I didn't realize packing was just gone
and also what the [\h__\h]
it was like just standing there it's not
like he was stuck anywhere
anyways
let me just drive here
laughs
what the [\h__\h] this car is pissing me off
[Laughter]
[Music]
so I took out my machine gun and I went
[Laughter]
oh
oh [\h__\h]
why are they all driving in my way
wasn't me it wasn't me it wasn't me it
wasn't me
[Laughter]
oh you just mean don't bump into them I
know I know I know
[Laughter]
how did she get the idea to make a song
like this what what inspired her
what was the point where she was like uh
so what do we do about lyrics for this
song I don't know how about just
and literally nothing else
I need to ask her
I still have still having a full talk so
that will be a good halotalk question
[Music]
oh by the way today I'm gonna put out
the schedule after the GTA stream
not tomorrow for once I know wow what's
going early early schedule somehow
[Music]
that's it
next week is a little bit irregular
because of weird streaming times because
of the practice of fauna is at a weird
time the actual Minecraft and oh the
Minecraft and and the tournament for
Pokemon they're all at weird times
I wasn't just driving everything's at
weird times guys
remember that we won't forget anything
not bad for any though Europe
sorry about that
oh
I got an accomplishment because I
unlocked all the islands
[Music]
whoa I'm rich [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
that seemed like a very end game
question if you get so much money
suddenly out of nowhere what the [\h__\h]
somebody did uh tell me like that I'm
like you know
moving on very differently than them not
tell me directly but I think I saw it in
the hashtag or so
um
so maybe like which Quest plan am I very
behind on
that was the highlight of the second
island
um yeah I I can sense it I robbed the
Bank of America
what's my completion percent where can I
see that
I hear it
only 31 percent
addiction level that's some good [\h__\h]
people killed 379.
I never got busted before I only died
shake up respect Jacob oh this is how
much they like me and so ah Mission oh
Dwayne Mission progress hundred percent
Elizabeth 100 many hundred
wait go down again uh
[\h__\h] hundred so am I done with packing
completely
and then there's Francis at 50.
Bruce Lee had hundred what why are they
all hundred
huh
what really
Vlad hundred I guess I'm meeting new
people
soon
so Francis okay let's do Francis I
forgot who the [\h__\h] Francis is but uh
or Arby what's RB
we're at a new guy oh yeah see we're
meeting new guys
hmm the Crooked cup ah okay okay
maybe I'll take a taxi to that one
even though that redshift remix of
hinotoli is [\h__\h] amazing
absolutely
God like
uh Taxi
right
it's so good no taxis
can I call Roman
good luck getting a cab here it really
did not no caps around ah
yeah
what were you saying
[Music]
what were you saying where can I take
you holy [\h__\h] heavy metal
so can you take me to Castle tunnel I
know a fun way to go
the fascists
a lot for bringing me here
nickel my boy Packy's brother Gerald
McCreary Jerry how's it going good
at my mom's house
Saucy but uh new contact but I will go
as I said to FM
I want hot dog
yesterday I made chicken with potato
and a oven oven baked potatoes and
tomatoes cherry tomatoes with um what is
the sauce called
[\h__\h]
I forgot but it's like a cream sauce a
white cream sauce is like lemon and
supposed to it had it was supposed to
have baby spinach in it but I didn't put
it in because I hate spinach well
Alfredo
Eric came along on the bank job sure
he's in a bad way last I heard he was
spending his hours in some Park and
asked an actor go down and check on him
me and Gerald will cover any expenses in
court all right man I'll go find him
honestly what was it
so unimportant but now it doesn't
doesn't leave me
Nico give me a call when you ain't
killing people or working on your adults
or whatever there'll be new races on new
races
I thought when we're done with Brucey
which one
I'll be taking care of his older brother
yeah
I will do my best
uh
uh here let me tell you it was
Florentine or I don't know it says
chicken Florentina art Florentina art
Florin Florentine the Florentine way
what is that
never heard of it I heard of it before
in German but I don't know what it is in
English
Italian way Italian sauce what I send
you to destroy an organization and you
only make the boss disciples salmon oh
yeah I feel like it would suit someone
too and he wants to speak to the FED
whoa hold on inorganization
I paid you to do a man's job you amateur
you [\h__\h] boy no no no no you sent me
to kill one guy one guy who would put
you in prison but I did it did not
what's your problem I'll tell you what
did I do wrong Tell It To The Judge tell
him I only sent you to kill one guy so
it ain't your fault I wonder what he'll
say maybe he'll let you walk not a
county I did what he said right I
totally [\h__\h] mentally [\h__\h] maybe
he will either way you're screwed hello
look
you gotta do this for me for us come on
you idiot
one more that guy's a [\h__\h] low life
he means nothing if there is a God and
he loves us if there is he'd want this
country
guy sells heroin to kids okay well
that's not good world is full of bad
people
but we've got a lot to lose I don't have
anything to lose Mr McCreery
ah
how much this is my price five
you're cool small job only five
okay nothing compared to what we just
went on Denver between V and W you
should say no because she's pretty tight
he doesn't need it I left or right right
now in the trunk of a car at the corner
there
we just got 250k
why would we do a little tiny baby job
like this
get ammo for your sniper rifle are you
assuming I don't have enough ammo for my
sniper rifle
where's my sniper rifle
oh okay how did I know that I don't have
enough
how do they know
47 good amount oh you think so oh oh car
nice car
oh I said it in the past mission but I I
guess it's close and you know might as
well
[Music]
I know a fun way to go I mean not with
you Georgie
just quickly and maybe I can also get
ammo for if I need wait wait
let me see what I actually need
this one needs no ammo
this one I don't really use it so
this one still seems fine too this one
also got plenty of ammo now
yeah we picked up so much so it's really
just a sniper rifle
and maybe some grenades if we can buy
them
maybe new armor hello the one in the
drama okay hello
please sell everything to me I I want oh
yeah oh
I'll probably afford it even for a
thousand but it's crazy but I wanted one
two three four five
yeah you guys told me I don't really
need my money anywhere in this game at
least not this much right so what the
hell
this looks like sniper rifle right
so dark
combat sniper whoa is it better than
what I have
kind of expensive
rather Snapchat okay I want to buy it
but I also want the ammo
do I leave behind my my bad sniper rifle
ah how much everyone 500 you can't carry
anymore
okay I have full ammo
uh
[Music]
uh replaces it okay
oh what about the rest guys did I
replace anything else
SMG rounds
[Music]
bad
I think I'm good but this one can't buy
this one either need more progress in
the game
okay
don't use the pistol
I'm good I'm good
uh next
what's this
is this for the quest
vehicle huh
I guess so
[Music]
okay where can I take you so we need to
go to Union Drive East good as gold
this is it I'm excited to try out my new
snarp over our form
where is this car
yeah is it up
above man I wish I was link right now
I could just
zip
myself up there
Young
Which tax driver leaves you on the
freaking Highway like this
[Music]
gotta play cookie yummy oh I want the
new new girls to play cookie yummy
uh everybody has to play cookie on me
so good this is my car oh decent car
with subwoofer in the middle woof woof
no more subwoofer it's now option it's
now a sub Subway
what do we get
as no
[Music]
I'm looking for something
foreign
[Music]
hockey
I want to learn this song too
[Music]
I watched the clip that she uploaded on
her own channel
with uh
and supposedly
allegedly Aqua Senpai okay it's so funny
I think somebody uploaded a subtitled
English version
so go look for that what if he is
call me when it's done
[Music]
uh I go to the Rooftop
okay
excuse me
I want to use my sniper rifle rifle
rifle waffle my schnapper Waffle
my combat sniper rifle
not rifle waifu wife I'm saying rifle
don't you hear the differences rifle I'm
your sniper wife or wife
okay let's go waffle no waffle
[Laughter]
rifle waifu
ATO
upper the all-new Tower of a meal
so how do we get him learn dealer into
the open how would you do that I'm so
far away
here
just shoot inside because that's the
only thing I can literally think of
or call him
what
big freaking brain
uh but wait
you you guys got the number
wait what was it five five
that's what you have to sniper rifle for
maybe
but it wasn't that the Burger Shop
number I don't understand
I wait here ah five four five five five
five one zero one two two five two three
how do I push numbers again
now I forgot it I think it was no irons
no
I'm trying to call someone you got him
yet no I can't take a screenshot he's
sitting down or something look around
the place
I got it already I know what to do
but how do I
stay there stay there oh girl was trying
to kill me
kill me I'm so sorry did that stop your
heart ironically
leave the rooftop okay
[Music]
it was me
destroying the evidence of me having any
guns in my hand I just live here
did you hear that shot guys did you hear
the noise weird stuff
I wonder what was that maybe maybe it
wasn't a gun maybe it was just some kind
of random explosion you know who knows
it could be anything sometimes things
sound like that's it
I dealt with him that's so easy I don't
even get chased for it
was the wind yeah I'm interested in your
sermon Mr McCreary let's not pretend
that this was anything other than
business there's nothing wrong with
it'd be a hundred percent thanks for
making me feel better about it I don't
know
that was so easy easy 5K bucks okay
let's go to x because we're close
why is this taxi empty
very much
can I take it
thanks man I don't know if you'll ever
get out of this traffic jam though maybe
if we just skip it then we will
[Music]
thank you
I'm taking shortcuts everywhere now
because I don't I want to make progress
you know
I want to make good progress today
what's up money it's been a while dude
man
business is tough I ain't a cool person
I mean I am cold
[\h__\h] what are you talking about
you want a drink
man have a seat man all right
I'm not judging
no listen
I paid my dues
now I learned in a hard school man and I
changed stuff you know me I do this
stuff so I got a chance to do some good
in this town so you'll say so I say
so I do
when I get the money man
I will build Parks I will sponsor kids I
will save lives
but I gotta have the money man it's all
this
oh this it means nothing if you ain't
got the heart Amen brother I mean look
here next week oh [\h__\h]
um thing is you know Jesus he did some
crazy [\h__\h] too I didn't consider that I
mean
if you killed that John the Baptist
remind me of that please
what he had I'm eating the nectarine now
correct about that man the point is man
history is a long time and you only got
one chance
and Dwayne
man Dwayne it's like he thinks it's 1992
and the best that you could hope for is
a gold chain and a page
you know he looks at me like he wants me
dead
that's a cab business I gave him money
but because I won't bow down to him and
treat him like he the almighty
[\h__\h] wants to pop me Dwayne is
illegal troubled
he was in prison a long time maybe you
guys I like Dwayne no I tried
I tried giving him half of the business
I tried everything a man could
reasonably try and still call himself a
man
so what you gonna do
kill him hey I didn't say that
and you cold I was joking
what else is there
I mean cat's been talking
now I hear things said you and me was to
tight now
said you disrespected me cold and mad
am crazy I mean he's gone prison does
that maybe my dad can't kill him
nope
but you can
but I don't want to neither do I man but
are those insane
dead anyway
I don't like this conversation do you
think that I do but it's kill or B
killed out there
now I will give you a lot of money
You Could See Me Now I ain't scared of
no one but a [\h__\h]
250 okay
oh
man I'm not sure
I got to think about it well I hope you
see some sense
I will be in touch
[Music]
do you mind if I finish this
nectarine
do I get a choice in this
I wouldn't mind
um protecting
uh Dwayne
no
yes but no okay I will come to collect
you in the next Tower nice one Nico see
you soon
it's
good choice right
I agree
wait who was that
and Packy right
man sorry but pool is off something came
up fine Nico I got a [\h__\h] plan on
banging anyways
really
I kind of don't believe it
hmm
that is it's so juicy oh my God
because if he had that ready to go then
he wouldn't ask me out for a pool for
billiard
okay
by the way
the word that we mentioned yes or I
mentioned yesterday
I know why I felt like saying it I may
have forgotten the the meaning but
subconsciously I guess I still knew it
because
does seem to mean
to go at a really high speed in a car
which at the time I feel like I was
doing anyway
I'm talking about
uh K I think k-a-r-a-c-h-o
um
I think it's a different word than the
one you guys are thinking of
yeah wait wait let me look it up again
me wait I can't
oh the game won't let me tap out
game one let me tap out okay well well
wow wow
meaning
uh
yeah high speed strong rapid Force it's
on on dictionary but it seems to be
maybe mostly used in German I don't know
oh yeah yeah
it is used in German
yeah yeah yeah in German we say
when you go with a car really high speed
so it's like I'm going home
but yeah even I I may have said it
yesterday but I forgot that kind of and
I feel like
nobody really says that anymore
[Music]
where's this Comedy Club tell me tell me
tell me tell me tell me
tummy tummy
I want to know
where is this Comedy Club
south of here
the Magic Hat icon I thought it was in
the Middle Island
near Times Square
which one is Times Square like here
Magic Hat icon oh okay
I should probably take a taxi for that
hmm
yeah
straight along this road
wait okay
it's not the Hat they'll get one guy
okay okay
let me find it oh wait what's this music
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
tell me when to stop
it's pulling you out like gravity
[Music]
left side okay
who's this lady it's got a baby
[Music]
thank you
it seems like the chat is really split
on this one
it's not just one guy
[Music]
what about this one two four seven that
looks special
the supermarket okay
[Music]
these are all the same shops what is
this
guy who kept them saying it's the Magic
Hat icon that's something else
hey and now Mr Ricky gervix wait I know
that person hi it's a British guy thank
you very much
as you know
I do a lot of charity work
but in all honesty I think that some
causes are more worthy than others
obviously cancer is a very worthy cause
AIDS is a very worthy cause but I got
asked to do a benefit gig recently for
sufferers of obesity
I said you mean fat people she went no
because her Beast well she actually went
no because she was eating
obesity is disease
oh and there is no is it
no he's not you just like eating don't
you I was not a disease
oh I'm so [\h__\h] ill oh I am well ill I
went what's the disease
she went
everything tastes good everything not
salads
it's not a disease
leprosy is a disease
can you imagine Jesus in the temple
people coming up to him in band she's
going Jesus my flesh is falling off and
he goes I can't stop now there's a fat
woman over there
I love salads documentary
about a woman who was 350 pounds
because she ate 10 pie and chips a day
wow that'll do it
10 pine chips a day 10 separate meals 10
separate trips to the chip shop in a cab
didn't even walk that wasted calories
so in this documentary they wired her
jaw together
so she liquidized 10 pine chips a day
what the [\h__\h] that doesn't even smell I
don't know I feel like that would ruin
it like that experience of eating it
so uh they took her to hospital
to give her that operation where they
staple your stomach together and she was
sitting there in hospital looking all
depressed
we can't eat for an hour before an
operation
and she went
it's
it's a dangerous operation but it's the
only option left
huh
it's gonna say stop eating jogging oh
you don't even walk um
salads
you don't like salads okay
nine pine chips a day that's the start
isn't it
they make excuses don't they fat people
they say things like it's glandular it's
not glandular it's greed
it's big bones yeah big bones covered in
meat and gravy
unbelievable the way they're laughing
oh
airplane seats um
[Laughter]
they're not big enough for someone like
me no they're not because if they were
we'd get 12 [\h__\h] people on the plane
it's not fair it is fair you wet too
much
and if we're talking about fairness and
airplanes why is it that I get the same
luggage allowance as a guy who's 400
pounds
we're both allowed 32 kilograms on the
plane I want to go no ah yeah okay
thanks very much good night well I mean
not you interesting
this is so different from what I
expected I thought they would like bring
out a random NPC and he does like boobie
booby jokes and PP jokes and I don't
know Coca-Cola jokes and I don't [\h__\h]
know
but they actually got a real dude
to do a real routine
[Music]
listen
if I go wrong now I have the icon in
there yay
I will go here
to the new guy
could you tell me please
[Music]
sure just so that I can turn you down
immediately
guys
[Music]
can I walk into the bank just like
I walked like I walked into
any other place
no oh man
I wanted to give it a try just for fun
and I thought that's how you keep the
relationship
by accepting first and then canceling
instead of turning it down right away
that's what I was told
um
Ray why did you say so you know what I
mean
he's in the back thanks
hey Nikki
how you doing are you doing hey that
Macbeth in front of you says you're okay
good but you're reliable yep hey he's
got Styles I trust you
I like him already why do all this work
because I need the money
not because I can't do anything else and
because I'm good at it sure and because
I'm trying to find someone
okay maybe we can help see how we do
yeah anyways it's kind of nice so far be
my friend no more because he ain't
getting made a video okay seems this guy
does not respect the weight Nico looks
like he's too too small for this tablet
s
do what you gotta do okay kill him
so be it
fine and you'll pay hey you cannot pay
double cool double of what you mess up
bad things are gonna happen
leave it to me
it's another snake to be honest really
Senpai on the radio
man whole life has gotten so big they
just played on the radio in New York
what the [\h__\h]
this might be a views look out for this
guy Alonso he's one of Benavides schools
I'll tell you what you need to know if
you're perspective oh okay
foreign
[Music]
Times Square was that a like fan main
project or was that from cover
[Music]
nice mikopee was it like overseas we
could be doing that
[Music]
damn it
don't shout you're gonna freak me out
I'm gonna get scared
[Music]
I was like what is this woman doing the
standing on this big object
just getting a good view
see it
[Music]
that's the experience I had yesterday
but today it doesn't really switch much
so
I'm quite happy with that wait a second
my chat stopped working it doesn't
a task manager because I Tab out and I
can't click on anything
here we go
[Music]
now you're fixed I fixed you
I love you so I fix you
but no big deal don't don't make a big
deal like this
whoa
[Music]
that's a good driver
I I still haven't gotten to
this one certain song
that's what I wanted
to be afterwards I want to listen to
Nene cheese
uh healthy fun okay
I see him already
[Music]
hi
lands with me you know what apartment
Teddy Benavides I love that one too I'll
say I don't know no teddies you sure
about that you want the last thing to
come out of your mouth to be a lie
intimidate okay easy
okay thanks walk the last few floors
don't go up there they're fixing it up
they kind of scare me
well they scare me well they're not
going up to me okay uh I already forgot
but thank God there's Quest markers
was it 151 or something like that
top floor right
elevator amazing I can't believe it they
got elevator
first time
oh can I be scared
of that gun in my hand someone's coming
up don't know how but he knows where
your apartment is don't know how
um
I don't know how either
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] man
what that [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
up
I almost want to give up but man
because that greeting was
not fair and I had no gun in my hand I
first had to find the right gun
so which one is it
oh thank God
but you guys owe me
you guys owe me an armor
okay well it's still up even higher huh
look from here right
bastard go [\h__\h] yourself go [\h__\h] YouTube
you're mine [\h__\h]
[Music]
there's so many first aid kits in here
do they
how stupid do they think I am
the in the beginning I needed it because
that was out of nowhere but
now
third medkit
first kill of the day
well for me it's the 200th kill of the
day
you bastards
let me show you some real characters
I don't want to get copyright issues
intervene
too slow mama
no I gotta run
take him out what for dinner what are we
doing
Mickey Mouse a walk
huh
where's the exit
here is it no that's Apartments [\h__\h]
take him out for a haircut
nah what do you mean by accident or what
oh wait
what do you mean you mean you mean that
you mean the the preview right no [\h__\h]
gets the better of me
okay
that is announcing not releasing
whatever shoot the airplane with my
sniper does that work
I guess not
[Music]
[Laughter]
this was an accident
look he fell that was or maybe suicide I
don't know who knows
maybe the the gun wound could tell some
stories but
he was gonna fall down anyway
[Music]
yeah all right all right
it was the gravity yes Stone of gravity
not me dead is dead
sorry to hear about your loss I'll be in
thought sticky
I'm so bloody
bloody hellmate
nice
tuned in
at the perfect time
[Music]
this is what I'm talking about
what's next guys should we go to GM
because I don't see anything else ah no
way there's something here and a
question mark
okay I'm going there
[Music]
my nose got like really oh
yeah
I felt that coming
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so why the
[\h__\h]
it's ever made sense
that's what you want seriously nah [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h]
I need you to get them for me I can't do
it myself
boy back in
today
Lithuania no problem that's what I was
planning on Playboy was your best friend
and he's always been straight with me
more or less I'll have to think about it
no no need to think about it I've
already made my decision
okay easy Escape uh and since we're
close I'm checking out the weapon place
first for more armor again
[Laughter]
ah what the [\h__\h] should I should I put
out a song like that
you're going oh my God
Insanity
I found Burgers what they call it here
oh dear
for surprise guess the body part no
thank you this place I don't like it
it smells foul
excuse me
I don't like the
I don't like the the
what's the word
the things they are suggesting
the naming sense it's just not very
appetizing you know
foul Burger I get it you know like a pea
foul yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
put your hands up hey put your hands up
put your put your [\h__\h] heads up
oh my God so fitting
gangster coroner
[Music]
Magic
alrighty wait can I buy this like
bazooka already no still not okay
fine see you brother
and now we go here
I love this part look some somehow it
kind of gets like I don't know tropical
Vibe you know what I mean not really but
I don't know how to describe it but the
chorus is so fun
[Music]
oh
yeah
you know what I mean right
[Music]
I want to make something like that
all right
yeah I I'm trying to choose songs that
could work somehow and just some songs I
just want to listen to for own my own
pleasure
you took care of that thing yes I
appreciate that hey no I look after my
friends I got a lot of friends important
friends Jimmy pegarinos
more or less
hey sweetheart hey
God you look like [\h__\h] oh yes you do I
haven't been to bed yet holy [\h__\h] and
smoking crystal holy [\h__\h] that's what
you look like what yeah you're a [\h__\h]
idiot
white dress [\h__\h] what is wrong
with you give me a break okay I feel
like death oh do you ever ask yourself
why you feel like that [\h__\h] idiot
yeah I know that
now
speaking of the ice yeah they got it
they they left it where you said that's
why I came over here can I get a goddamn
coffee here you look like a really use
some goddamn caffeine I'm [\h__\h] coming
down [\h__\h] I feel like death fine
whatever
need you to go collect some garbage for
me garbage yeah you wanted a career in
waste disposal now you got one since
when have I been a cat what kind of
garden garbage with a lot of ice today
since when's 11 again Columbus in Denver
truck waiting in three guys Good Guys
friends of mine main guy's name is Luca
chill out okay so not from the beginning
right
oh this will be over soon
you gotta stop me smoking this stuff Ray
[\h__\h] killing myself
I want I want Kotori on my head today
what the [\h__\h]
God damn it
it's better
I mean anything is nice
I look good no matter what
tell them
[Music]
we couldn't listen to the Skippy Boop
you couldn't listen to it yeah Unico
this is tuna fish and Johnny specs hey
so we're all friends now we got a crew
again a very smart looking NPCs let's go
Nico here's your gear you're driving
that call
of course
easy
my show
get in the truck Nico there's pickups in
Chinatown let's head it
[Music]
is radio on
so someone's been throwing out the load
of diamonds you could say that right got
that tweaking chicken is the bike abroad
you matter yeah she's pretty struck out
Ray got hurt they got her friends to
steal the ice off of some club owner guy
her friends are the Lost bike again I
think I worked with a member of that
gang up on Bohan it was called Johnny or
uh something
the street said walk away on the bottom
right and I thought it was the wrong way
thank you
foreign
[Music]
try to harm me
move out Nikki you know come on dude
been waiting for you
it's just so good-hearted jazz is just
can't do any harm to anybody
bikers get so [\h__\h] on meth that they
threw the ice way nah it seems his club
Owners got more connections than a
subway line he's in with the ancelottis
the Dominicans up in Northwoods
everybody Ray came up with this plan to
keep a bit of distance between us and
the robbery the bikers has taken the
heat for this [\h__\h] this ain't the
easiest way to pick this [\h__\h] up even if
we don't want to attract any attention
yeah me and Tony was saying that before
you just got here we were saying that
there's a lot of opportunities for this
to go wrong the bank could split the
diamonds could go missing really easy
that's why we're going to be extra
careful right we wouldn't want that to
happen would we of course not you know
how this Ray would get if he found out
some diamonds were missing he is a
pimple are you [\h__\h] kidding me the
manager of one of his waist Depots was
holding out on profits a couple years
back Ray fed him to a dump truck there
was this point where the sounds of his
screams stop and all you could hear was
his bones crushing then the pop of his
skaldo I nearly lost my lunch nice
this is really cool with the
construction going on here
anyway don't worry the other one toner
I'm putting all the diamonds in
into my truck all of them no nothing
will be missing
uh yeah yeah
a crane fell in New York City last week
what the [\h__\h] what how does a crane fall
that sounds [\h__\h] dangerous
it was on fire
what
did it hurt people it looks like we got
company
crap someone's got wise let's get the
hell out of here
no one died okay thank God
that could go really badly
man
thank you I am I am in this ice I'm not
having to rate cut my balls off because
you don't think this truck's fast enough
I didn't say it was impossible it's just
going to be difficult you ain't making
this easy on it but looking on my
beautiful curves
look I mean in game
get us out of here Nikki
close these spots
holy [\h__\h] ain't doing too good back here
wait here through and then
did I lose them
more or less
insane honest no more
you have to do is bring the ice home
safe
ah
all right
maybe it's scripted
this is it you got us here Nikki
[Music]
really chill I like driving trucks I
should really play Euro Truck Simulator
diamonds is serious anyone who heard of
him would want them I ain't surprised we
get a bit of attention you want me to
take the ice to raid them nah me and
Tony will look after them sort them out
from the trash I sure hope we ain't lost
any on the route
shake it up pretty good back then the
way you say it Luca here's hoping we can
find them I love everybody the way they
say it sounds like they
they just they know that something's
missing because they took it
those [\h__\h]
nine fast holy [\h__\h] like everything's
paying so well now
noise
okay
[Music]
on hey we already apparently
uh are welcome to go to the other Island
but
I still got some [\h__\h] to do I'm gonna go
to Gary Jerry
oh
look at this crew we've got the stuff
Ray it's all in the back of the truck
I don't know Ray you don't trust them
then weigh the eyes yeah catch you
around they keep on making these like
hints incense you know
thanks taxi I like how they actually
react to me even when I'm behind them
far away
[Music]
thanks for the membership gift yeah
I appreciate these kind of things yeah
what this looks like Thief simulator
what am I doing here
actions speak louder than words no one's
here just you and me
come in come in here no thank you oh I
agree you got muffins
Becky swears by you absolutely swears by
you 14 months
congratulations and thank you for being
here so well in a bank job it was fun
fun too much fun that's always been this
family's problem fun good causes a good
laugh some stupid dreamers some stupid
distraction but never any [\h__\h] focus
never hmm Focus
before we've ever been is [\h__\h]
working for guineas working for [\h__\h]
any [\h__\h] with a buck a whole lot
spent in a proper man oh yeah wine and
women as quick as possible and remain a
slave forever very poetical yeah I know
National tragedy
yeah he's a [\h__\h]
and friend maybe what is he well first
up we got to create a little problem
between the ancelotties and their
Albanian muscle for Jimmy P
you're gonna plant a bomb in Tony
Black's car be rigged to a phone go off
when you dial a number I want it to blow
when they get back from their meeting
please treat it well exactly bombs in an
alley off of engine Avenue get it give
me a call classical you know back it was
right for once I'm glad you're on board
pick up the bump on inchon Avenue
okay
oh she's so dark so hard to see
what the [\h__\h]
uh doko
eh
what
does not tell me until I'm in a car okay
we've been relaxing so much
with taxes let's get an actual car after
all the police cars are gone
Blue Dot
oh wait there's no what do you mean blue
there's a green one that's what you mean
I didn't see that
so close too
oh
okay I need a car
this one looking good
I think
we can go
be quick be fast be smart
[Music]
[Applause]
huh there it is
okay
[Music]
it's just a short ride anyway whatever
doesn't matter what we listen to
[Music]
what I know
Melissa
[Music]
there's someone sleeping there
foreign
[Music]
make sure
no one walks away
geez right so easily I don't see why you
ain't doing this yourself
call me when it's done it's only because
only because I'm straight edge is why is
the reason why I'm doing this
how far
pretty far okay let me tell you a
tangent while we're driving
about
the
kind of okay that we went to in Japan on
the last night before I flew home
but wait I will talk I just want to open
it up there we go
[Music]
yeah but let me turn it off because it's
too loud for me
so this was like in that one week where
I was in Japan for even less than a week
it was like what five days or so and I
have a fully packed schedule I was
really busy but Cali said she wanted to
do a karaoke with uh girls who enjoyed
singing
like ID Girls
so
um she organized kind of through Ollie
to get some ID girls but unfortunately I
thought
I thought I could meet
um for example but I missed her I missed
pretty soon so we only had only and they
know but that's fine they're a lot of
fun to be around with
and Cali and me and then uh later on
bells and mume also decided to join us I
mean we all wear there at the same time
but uh
yeah they heard about it so they came
along
and
Cali and Ollie were already there and it
was like a really fancy Kadoka room like
damn special place
and they already had I think like
champagne bottles or just one maybe
sitting there in the ice
ice container but of course I wasn't
gonna drink anything but it's fancy
yeah Kelly just went ahead to reserve
the most
Fancy karaoke place she could possibly
find
only the best for the girls right only
the best
when Kelly reserves something it's
always gotta be like extra
can't be anything normal no I think she
just wants to treat the girls that she's
like around with
um
so this was however at the end of a long
day especially for Elena me and me
because we were doing stuff together on
that day
so Dana was kind of like half asleep
because she didn't sleep in the night
before and now it was evening and
throughout the day we did stuff and that
was evening and Elena was really really
tired so like for out half of the
karaoke
she was like half asleep like her eyes
were like this
and she was like looking like a zombie
like Ollie
I thought I was looking at Ollie but no
I was actually looking at Elena you know
that's how much it was really confusing
she had quite a quite a zombie Vibe so
she was so tired
yeah so surprisingly
was kind of inactive during the karaoke
most of the time until like the second
half where she kind of opened her eyes
and because because it's because I
started like putting in some duet songs
for us
and yeah got her to sing them with me we
sang so many songs together
um
and that kind of woke her up I suppose
wait let me switch cars I guess
we sure
no wait we're not taking the car we're
rigging it
like a life today
okay get a vehicle move away from the
record yup
[Music]
excuse me guys thanks
for not moving your fault honestly
it's unbelievable unbelievable
now
I was just backing out of the alley
[Music]
okay people people people people people
We Done Yet okay
I have moved away from the brake car but
I'm gonna go back
so yeah uh and then Bales and Cali were
getting along so well the whole time
they were like sitting next to each
other and they were singing a lot of
songs together
and Bales was putting in Marin Senpai
songs
like she put at least two songs if not
three of money Senpai in and when she
was singing it I legit I was asking her
several times through the noisy room
fails
holy [\h__\h]
you sound like mining did you turn on
the this is is this background Focus or
is this yo and she's like it's me I'm
like what she's like it's me I'm like eh
it sounds like
sounds like for sure
and then she stopped singing for a
moment to proof it's not backup vocals
she really sounded like Marine
fascinating I don't know if she was
trying
to sound like her but she definitely did
especially when singing marine songs
yeah
does she ever sing Mario songs
then you would understand
oh don't let them know your phone oh
okay oh
I think I'm far enough right
now we have a car between us
[Music]
happy to do
yeah Bales was in a really good mood
really hyped and Cali too
I was singing some stuff too and I for
one song I got up and danced
and I tried to sing too
but it was difficult while dancing and
dancing in a really small space because
I was like dancing in between the table
and a chair
and then Cali holy [\h__\h] she put on some
some of her best karaoke songs and
wrapped so hardcore like I was shook at
you know I know I know Cal is a good
rapper but
once in a while I hear her when she goes
like really hard and I'm like holy [\h__\h]
damn yeah this this lady who reminds me
again
of how good she is with rapping holy
moly it was so cool everybody in the
room was like looking at her when she
was rapping I think some Eminem song or
so
I think monster or whatever it was
it's like one famous song ah get closer
get closer okay
wait where is he Oh I thought that was
him [\h__\h]
where it's one
[\h__\h] I was looking at a different car
ah there we go
ah
yeah Kelly's golden holy [\h__\h]
she just she just didn't breathe
she went like babe
or maybe Godzilla I don't know I
recorded it though
I recorded it and some other stuff I was
thinking of maybe uploading on it on
Twitter and then deleting it so that I
don't get in trouble for uploading uh
like stuff that's
you know copyrighted
but some of the songs are also like
Vocaloid stuff
that could maybe be okay to upload on
Twitter
I still have those I forgot about them
so I didn't upload anything
how long are we gonna try them
drive and drive after them
yeah besides me singing you know I
noticed like in the beginning you know
there's always like this is the thing
with karaoke so far my experience with
going to karaoke with these Hollow en
and ID Girls
we order lots of food yeah I mean not me
they order lots of food and then they
don't eat it
or when I order something I'm like hey
do you want to eat this do you guys want
to eat this with me and they're like
yeah yeah and then they don't eat it and
I'm the only one
I feel like I'm almost the only one and
I have to motivate everybody to eat it
we have like honey toasts several
honey toast but we had so many honey
toast coming in and and I was like why
am I eating this
everybody's just like Elena is half
asleep Bells is busy singing she doesn't
like sweet things mume is I don't know
on her phone and and Ollie is only might
want to eat but I don't know she's she
was also busy singing everybody was just
singing and the ice cream on the on the
Honeycombs was melting everything was
melting and the Honeycombs you gotta eat
it fresh you know
so I was like girls please eat this with
me eventually I finally got Kelly to eat
the honey toast with me so I wasn't the
only one but damn
we had some like uh french fries and
chicken nuggets and karaoke and all
kinds of stuff
and lots of yummy food
lots of sweet and savory food but
uh yeah
stop ordering so much sauce
wow
my sing at all no
no I don't think she did
she didn't sing anything take out the
remaining antelope's that sounds like
some kind of uh Italian dessert
huh
this and now
[Music]
tails off surprise
Stars why why why how do you know it was
me
car
excuse me I would like a car
how would they know it was me
they're not supposed to know where am I
going what is this can I hide here do
you think they would find me like in GTA
I tried something like this
and they eventually found me so
uh car not in this game they'll find me
anyway okay
right
oh yeah
there's the cars there's cars
foreign
thank God for the armor
okay
see you later suckers
bye bye
bye
on this car oh this car is [\h__\h]
just stay here come on let's let's hope
for the best
okay easy
nine thousand holy [\h__\h] this is like a
cash machine
this game too easy give me more
difficult tasks please
everyone got
they think the Albanian muscle is
no mercy
okay
um
I want I want to take this car
it's nice I like it I mean it's kind of
nice
the the tall front is kind of cool I
like it
Bentley Chrysler
anyway so uh I sang uh free the words of
Dana one with Ollie
the only to let was
um magnets do you know the one from Luca
and megurina Luca and uh Hatsune Miku
[Music]
yeah cause I always wanted to sing that
as a song cover
uh on YouTube but can't for reasons
but
I was able to sing it in karaoke with
only
yeah and she did so well Ollie's really
good at cuddle again
and she's really hyped like she kept on
dancing and sharing I was also on the
cheering side a lot
yeah
shut up already
our problem Playboy it's yours that's it
I know what I'm going to do all right
oh
look
yeah and so that was very sensual and
beautiful singing that with Owen
and and what else I don't know Bales and
oh oh [\h__\h] oh it's time
uh I'm killing him so I'm going to him
right
Mamma Mia what was I saying oh yeah
Bells put and Cali too put a lot of
songs in that I didn't know only put the
one up by song in like oh
God everybody really hyped everybody was
just joining in kelly didn't know the
song I think but she still got really
like hyped up by it and joined in
everybody was chanting
[Laughter]
unbelievable
um
I I don't know they put songs in that I
didn't know and I I also put some songs
in them they didn't know
hoping that they would like them
okay so how's this gonna go down
I just go in and shoot them
down
um
[Music]
should have done that you got rid of
Dwayne already it's gonna be an open
fire immediately
I did I be killed Dwayne
Wayne step two is [\h__\h] well I
was thinking that maybe Dwayne is not
yeah what's with those clothes maybe
it's you
mother
then you can touch this [\h__\h] you think I
got here but letting little [\h__\h] like
you [\h__\h] with me I own you nobody owns
me
we'll see about that
taking cover at least Nas
the garbage job Gonna Change
loading okay
easy
easy is he alive no
okay
oh
I'll think the game expected me to be
able to shoot him from there
down
here
come here little Mr Playboy it's time to
play you like playing don't you
come here let's play playtime let's go
in your little playpen Playboy
huh is this the excellent already [\h__\h]
do I just oh kill him in the broad
daylight
[Music]
oh hi
can I take the car
wait he's still alive
what I'm done oh he's not dead yet oh
now he is or is he
there we go
I would say he was pretty dead before
then
am I not getting in trouble with this
before this really I even have a like
dead body in my passenger seat
wow nobody gives a [\h__\h] nobody calls the
cops
is it always like this or if you're like
unlucky then maybe there will be a
police
driving by or so
gum you're right I can't give you
hope for me
song
Hey man nice for your living oh
well of course
I'll be your friend well sometime soon
later on good aim ended it quickly
sometimes but not a big deal it's too
easy it shouldn't be this easy what the
[\h__\h]
hmm yeah
sure so now now we have a new new house
wow okay but we gotta we gotta go back
to Jerry I don't know why it keeps on
leading me to this like different Island
the old Island I don't want the old
Island also it's way too far
or just stupid
I got better too thank you hey guys it's
so Charming giving me these compliments
oh you know what I'll I'll let this text
you run for a while let me see
um foreign
so at the end at the end we didn't sing
a single song all together until that
point so I said let's uh oh wait but
this was this was when um mume and Bales
already left they had to leave a little
bit early so it was Ollie Wayne me and
Kelly left and we were like how about we
sing one last song all together
you know what it was you know what I put
in thinking that
thinking that it should
like everybody should know this song and
be able to sing it
I did sing Jet Plane too yeah for Cali
yeah but that's not it that's not what
we sang at the end
no no I didn't want to put in a whole
live songs I avoid putting in whole life
songs in karaoke with other whole life
members
what the [\h__\h] it what
what
the [\h__\h]
huh drunkeno
what is going on
[Music]
what is he doing
nah he'll never get out of this I have
to help him by skipping it
I told you he will get wild when you
press space
69 nice
uh oh yeah okay so I chose
and I would say like
um because I don't want everybody to
sing all at the same time at all times
we would sing the chorus together but I
was like pointing at the girls to
indicate so next up is you so in the
beginning for example Ollie would sing
one verse and then next I point to
Callie and then she would sing one verse
and so on you know
so it was very well organized and lots
of fun it was like a relay
in the song
more interesting than just
holy [\h__\h] singing together the whole
time
oh [\h__\h] that hurt
that was full on
yeah but yeah together was fun and then
at the end me and Wayne went to Idol
meeting
in this Idol meeting room was so fancy
too shiny and had all kinds of items
for ladies like perfumes it had like 10
different perfumes lined up
don't kiss me
[Music]
yeah free perfume
I mean you're not supposed to take the
whole bottle
my boys are out of control
find a man and my husband is in hell I'm
thinking God moves in mysterious ways
they also had I think like hair iron
hair curler and they gave us when we
left they gave us little little like
fancy snack uh
as a goodbye as a present each other in
a nice paper bag
yeah everybody got like one souvenir
yeah it's so fancy some [\h__\h] work for
the pegarinos I owed them oh please
I do it myself but I think I'm being
watched pretty please
I think I'm about to get pinched again
[\h__\h] really yeah right it is really
fancy
all it means is someone's been speaking
we just have to find out who and make
them stop
in the meantime it was comfy too like
the furniture was way better than I need
you other karaoke places furniture
come on that's how you know Cali chose a
place yep exactly
was of his main motivation
available with the five old families
it's a lot he's being weakest he's
decided to stir [\h__\h] up for him
hmm
now the anceladis have an uneasy
alliance with some albanians they use
them as Hitman
I know the time much like Jimmy De Guido
uses us so to what you're gonna do is
disguise yourself as an Albanian and
then go whack Frankie garone an
ancelotti longtime couple sure
which Albanian
this one
no
oh no
doesn't know what to do with the body I
guess okay
oh sure okay
[Music]
foreign
I think everybody went home with a
taxi except me I just I don't know I
always want to save money I just went
public transport and everybody's like
are you okay are you gonna be fine I'm
like yeah sure why not
I'm fine no I took I took the public
transport I'm fine oh wait wrong way
return
[Music]
whoa
yeah no worries easy
yeah and I I was really stressed out
because my flight was early in the
morning on the following day and we
ended the cut I will get pretty late
because we had a lot of fun
um yeah we didn't want to end it but we
had to at a reasonable time
and I think I got back like maybe around
midnight or so and then I still had to
shower pack my suitcase and prepare [\h__\h]
yeah I still had to do a couple of
things
so it was I was quite stressed out and I
barely got any sleep but it is what it
is I was I was looking forward to just
sleeping in my flight yeah
all was okay in the end we had a good
time a fun karaoke with the
Ian and ID Girls
only the hype woman
you said she was really sleepy but she
eventually as I said
was
awake enough to sing a couple duets with
me one we sang was the one that she sang
in her
um 3D debut
[Music]
I wanted to sing that with her because I
really love it the other ones I don't
remember I think
what what
what oh my God guys
what is this
[Music]
you guys know how to drive a car
know how to behave in traffic I don't
think so it doesn't look like it
yeah this Gothic this
this I love this Gothic
[Music]
oh at the airport I actually I ended up
buying shoes so I got my shoes fixed but
I also ended up buying shoes this I
bought the same
type of shoe in two colors I've never
done this before
but oh I really liked them in in both
colors
now after wearing them I can say that
it's they're kind of uncomfortable
to wear
I rarely have this feeling
when wearing uh heels normally I don't
have this problem
these shoes are really rough my little
pinky toe always gets like roughed up by
these shoes uh oh but they look cute so
all okay
yeah blisters too
on the sides because there's like a lot
of like straps
rubbing
on on my feetsies
so these shoes give me a lot of blisters
but I'm hoping that my feet will get
used to it and eventually
eventually won't
get so damaged anymore
have you ever gotten comfy shoes of
course
of course
my other shoes I normally don't get
blisters from them unless they're like
really new but
hmm
also the high heels that I choose I know
like which high heels I can walk in and
which are comfortable for me and which
aren't so I Choose Wisely
yeah maybe they stretch out a little bit
that would be nice
it would be nice indeed
I have shoe problems often yeah
no that's just the imagination just
because the shoe broke for example that
just happens
after a while
oh
Chase time
take out Frankie garone okay let's type
in take him out quickly shall we [\h__\h]
[Music]
how did that not take him out
is that normal
yeah got him
okay
no stars did it reset
did it reset the Stars The Wanted level
[Music]
is going to describe the Albanian you
got on ice
yay
[Applause]
good luck with that Jerry
what's going on here mama mia
yeah that was really easy to holy [\h__\h]
all the missions are so easy
what's kind of [\h__\h] lame why is
everything so easy
this is a baby game
I'm just too good
more say it more
[Music]
bubble game bubble bubble game easier
than Super Mario 64.
well definitely definitely is
and ironically I'm having of course as
you can see a way easier time playing
this than Super Mario 64.
oh another raid hello what's up what's
up how you doing this looks nice this
place bien de morte
wait that
that sounds like
it because all the names of the shops
are obviously like kind of like stupid
names right this sounds like something
like like something
they make you think it's it sounds like
something good but it's not
probably means something like yay yay
eat this and you'll die
he said I like a [\h__\h] Pizza Tower I I
cannot
handle games like that they don't make
me happy they don't spark joy in me
they really don't yeah I like piswasa
exactly
you think I do better at Mario 64 now I
don't know about that me and Mario 64.
we'll just it'll never work
Phil
we're not meant to be
me take it easy oh Phil take it easy
yeah listen tell Jimmy I said hello
okay
I'm sorry
goodbye Jimmy
is in this game we got a problem Oh you
and me yeah
I got two options option one you rip me
off option two Luca and his buddies
ripped his boat hey hey what's up man
the diamonds
rocked it
maybe you're in on it maybe I am but if
you thought that I wouldn't be standing
here right now no smart man you ain't as
dumb as you look
luga hangs out in Castle Gardens go see
him go get my stuff back so everyone can
get paid now right
he left him being joined the mafia what
the [\h__\h] Jimmy
uh
what of course they took some diamonds
for themselves
what did you expect
it's really close Okay oopsie I want to
actually see uh again
yeah 35 so wasn't it like 31 last time I
checked
how how is my percent still so low it's
just like like tears of the Kingdom
where there's like a million kodaks
and shrines that pull your percentage
down
but I feel like I'm doing everything the
game is throwing at me
you guys think if I do one more GTA
stream
I can finish it or do I need to what do
you think
I feel like now that the game is so easy
for me I'm like
zooming through it
two free okay
I need that ice back that's okay I don't
know what you're talking about Nikki I
gave every one of those diamonds to Ray
now we all know that that's not true
[\h__\h] you you cabbage eating prick who
says it weren't you that made off okay
no problem
no problem boys
give me those Diamonds oh my car now
they want me to take that car huh
I want to get the tires
foreign
[Music]
that wasn't me
I had no no hand in this whatsoever
yo
wait what was I supposed to do
oh
oh wait this is a
Oh I thought I did it right
this is a diamond
[Music]
s live
I wanted to stop them so I stopped them
but I stopped them in a way too cool
hardcore way huh
but that was really cool
who's the best way that I ever stopped
someone in a Chase ever
it was so cool
I'm I'm happy with it I'm proud of my
I'm proud of my choices
and my actions
oh wait left
my aim too good
I can easily blow up cars now
yakuni
Luca I need that ice pack
hmm
you need to look at life and get the
diamonds back but which one is Luca
and is he the driver
Maybe
a star Machida
you ducked
just follow them okay well they
eventually stop
that turn was [\h__\h] what is this car
we're heading
that car right
what if I try to stop it without blowing
it up
wouldn't that be ideal
[\h__\h] and we're all getting in trouble
here
but that's a very sweet sweet balance to
hit
I think we at least got one tire yeah or
no well maybe not
ah
um
[Music]
that's boring
it's boring
[Music]
he's so shaky this is literally a
straight Road
wow
oh
ah
you guys okay huh
regret your decisions now yet
[Music]
take him down
okay
wait should I have stayed on the car
because they're they're spreading out
um
okay
thank you
Lucas hiding in the toilets flush your
mouth
[Music]
yeah yeah did I murder civilians I don't
think so
where's this toilet hi Pizza
what 139 flying rats left
eh funny wait where's that it's down
below sorry sorry what
the white blew up it's so funny
199.
it's funny it's like a side quest huh
why don't you do it I don't know it was
calling for me it was a fake pigeon it's
not real
it was like a balloon you know
Luca
where are you where are you little tippy
toes wait that's normal person don't
worry I got you I got you
making things real hard which one is him
hmm
wait we're supposed to live and leave
him alive no you gotta make
up which one is it now
we're killing him now
I don't know about that
what I shot at the side on purpose
you saw that right
you guys are my witness
I just wanted to intimidate him a bit
more
oh [\h__\h] we gotta lose our Stars
unless this end of the call will clear
us again and I got your diamonds
and I got the stuff you want to get
yourself I'm fair I can only walk so
slow but the police are coming here
they're all moving what the [\h__\h]
let me go let me go let me go
I need oh yeah no don't kill the cops it
will make my my star rating higher right
let's just
resolve this peacefully
let me find a car and am I out
not gonna kill anyone
I'm not gonna kill anyone
okay I see cars
which one maybe this one
ah
okay
a verb of peace
yeah he was watering the grass why not
why not he's taking good care of it
can I follow the route
escape the police at the same time we
will see
it's at least leading me out of the
circle
[Music]
well if I reach the goal it will reset
my stars I think
[Music]
oh yeah
thanks for being positioned so nicely
very convenient
[Music]
it's such a piece of cake everything is
such a piece of cake everything's too
easy
9500 holy moly I'm Gonna Be A
Millionaire soon
foreign
[Music]
I've got too much power you know
going down to RB in Little Italy
you guys want music again I don't know
I'd like it quiet right now
you were a millionaire by this time in
GTA 5
oh not my fault
they're all paying so badly we only had
one big job so far
no music is fine okay good
I enjoy all these hunks honks
and just a boom boom sound
it's relaxing
don't miss the return of funeral fact or
American [\h__\h] and a whole new shitty
singer
a competition
sounds like exciting times are ahead of
us
only in this country do they let blind
people drive oh there's like a person
there what does this mean blue person
is this a side quest
s okay but I'm not doing side quests
ain't nobody got time for that
um
[Music]
you know how in Japan taxis
um they open the doors themselves
automatically and they like when you
enter and when you leave and they really
don't want you to try to open it
yourself
and I know that and normally I don't
like I my body knows it so I I would
never attempt it
but last time in Japan
you know that time when mean and the
managers were writing the taxi
I did it and I felt so embarrassed I
haven't done that in a million years
felt so embarrassed I'm like I was like
I was outside the car but I was
apologizing so much because I felt so
stupid
because he surely was thinking that
stupid Gaijin just tried to close my
door I'm supposed to do that somebody
stop her she's on a rampage
probably also was a little bit mad if he
would have seen how much sweat I left on
the
Moon
no I mean I don't think so I think I
left an embarrassing amount of sweat on
the seats
but when I was getting out
the car I
mean I tried to like
swoosh swoosh my butt over it the part
that was closed
make it unnoticeable
I keep doing these favors for you and
you pay [\h__\h] it's a thing a pair of
fries on like lever what just happens I
know
deduct yourself it was a really long
Taxi
fine you got it you want my word you got
my word good
who is he
Florian kravish Florian Cottage
yeah Florian [\h__\h] gravity you guys
act disgusted but there's plenty of
people who know how it is
in the meantime oh yeah lava jackets can
have the same effect yeah
what's he doing there he's waiting to
get paid
good keep things on a level
s behave better with company sure much
better getting shot by two guys than one
is this the merchandise funny
huh I can't see it am I supposed to see
something
ah now I saw something I only saw the
pizza
it's because it's zoomed in
okay meet Johnny at the side entrance to
the libertonian
all right is this the car I was driving
but I want this car
cute oh
cute you cannot deny how cute this car
is right oh my God
this is adorable
Halloween
the the coloring of it
first time I saw this coloring in GTA
cute
yeah look it's the eyes are so cute and
the ears Shrek ears what what do you
mean ears not ears what do you mean
thank you no I want to take care of this
car I don't want anyone to take it take
it away from me where am I can I like
put it
I want to bring it home
is far
actually it doesn't show me home right
now
actually I was not show it to me because
I'm in the mission I guess
it's so cute
this is a real muscle car a sport car
huh
yeah right it's not a muscle car it's a
sports car I know that I know that I
know that
Corvette
it says Coquette
like a potato called kitten croquettes
is that a sports car I don't even have
to question that because sports cars are
just like obvious
when you see a sports car you know that
you see a sports car
but this this felt like
this felt like we're a match made in
heaven you know
we're meant for each other this car and
me it's cute I mean it would be other
colors that I would probably choose over
over this one but oh
we're okay
but this one I like it
orange not necessarily orange but
um
I don't know
the stripe it was really cute though I
like the stripe
oh nice cars over here too oh
what am I doing with this guy kill him
hi
hey all right
all right how's it going how's it going
again yeah likewise uh let's hope this
goes a little better than before yeah
come on let's get inside yo rat tattoo
on you um
no problem let's do this okay let's see
the stuff gentlemen Mori come over here
Cali is here since we're having a little
show and tell let's see some money of
course no problem I hope she's involved
it's gonna be even more fun
show on the stuff
get in there Mori
Isaac look at them
Isaac these are great oh wait we were
talking
real diamonds I thought that it was like
another word for Coca-Cola
just get the [\h__\h] man come on
isn't that what you call it sometimes at
all
you mean you mean I mean the you know
the one that you snort
right
escape the Liberto oh sh ow what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
all right
and today on
beautiful shots with takanasikiara
you see her showing off her amazingly
stunning skills in a beautiful Museum
because why the [\h__\h] not
dangerous Wawa let's go this one instead
although I see someone really far
where are you
huh
[Music]
that guy might still be alive
I'm gonna shoot here because I know
[Music]
I was gonna say that I know that there's
a quarter kid in
in the eye
but
I wish that would have caused collateral
damage
okay
pretty good pretty good I saw some
people down there oh and
[Music]
um
okay
I should steal some nice things while
I'm here oh you're alive be afraid the
[\h__\h]
was this grenade free grenade yo
[Music]
yeah I gotta be a little bit more
careful I'm losing oh
I'm losing my
my carefulness
where
are we done now
down here
oh I still see people
no
okay
okay okay
smooth oh they blend into the scenery so
much with their gray suits and gray
clothes everything's so gray oh
the head isn't sure if it's actually
down there I can tell you it's there
[Music]
[Applause]
and thanks you
ah
all the dinosaurs are in the way man
come down come up come up
okay yeah the head is really like you
don't see it but it's there
can I just leave here
it says Exit
but I feel like it wants me to leave
through over there
[Music]
I knew it I knew someone was right there
thank God he didn't like at any given
time I could get really unlucky and
receive a headshot from them
thank God they're not good shooters
oh there's still people up there
[Music]
ah yes I think I got him I think I got
him
I want this one
yes no invisible heads to hide hide
behind anymore
foreign
[Music]
I've done my gun research
next game c is Geo CS go
[Music]
um
I don't know I know you guys say I'm
good and everything but yeah I mean as
long as long as it's not stuff like Apex
or valorant where I'm playing against
other real people that's really
stressful
then I could still consider it but I
don't know I don't know
I'll stay with my GTA games for now
because they have some funny story and I
appreciate that
stop that William
payday payday maybe I don't know
fauna plated right the fun and played it
a final play that then must be good
okay
so
oh medkit hmm
I appreciate that
what
okay
lose Isaac's crew
come on
do I take I can take my my cute car
again
well something just blew up
right I'm out of here bye-bye
why are you good on grass ah
it turns so much yeah
hahaha
still got the insurance
uh
please no
okay the car didn't like that
um is there any normal exit
when I'm not even wanted anyway
what the hell
I just need to lose them
oh now I'm wanted great
yeah
I can't do this can I
no
I thought I died I'm alive where's my HP
sorry I was blind
I survived it
this time
I survived it I've died with an accident
like this before
you make me something
[Music]
why don't you give it a try
y'all left my cute car behind whatever
it's not real life Just A Game Zone
I shouldn't
get so attached to stupid cars yeah
it's sad but I gotta say goodbye
uh oh
please ah damn it I thought I thought I
had it
would have been just like one more
second or so I'm sure hmm
a rear wheel drive which is good for
performance but it's not good for
traction on slippery surface or grass
it's not good you know I felt that
[\h__\h]
yay impossible Trinity you completed the
mission museum piece yeah 9500 yay
okay and have a mission clear what'd you
say about that right
the deal didn't go so good right
finally's got the cash I don't know who
has the diamonds
I don't like being like
you know sent around this so much like
commented like um
I'm your freaking Butler
have some respect
I want to be respected
guess I gotta kill more people to be
more respected
go to question mark
nice question mark oh
all right
why
better not be a trap that you placed in
my game personally
right
you didn't did you
if you knew you were the attack he would
show some respect
yeah
I would hope so
write down the name of the person who
wrote who told me to go there
write it down just in case
it's a trap and I get kidnapped
and you guys will never see me again
just because I listen to Chad
yeah
I gotta turn around
I'm Laura I'd try at draft Street
we personally placed replays 200 pigeons
hey what's this about the pigeons now I
want to look for them I'll keep an eye
open
wait ah no this is not what I'm looking
for
not quite
GTA koroks yeah
cute
I don't know how
I don't know
I guess that didn't count
thank God
I don't know how to do stuff
what's that sound
oh wait I went to the uh
didn't I go to the question mark
it's here
it's right here
I can't found it
wrong is right
about people's feelings bud
yeah oh [\h__\h]
hey hey
listen you must be thinking but don't
bother I'm sorry but I don't see how you
know what I must be thinking you've
killed people
should be dead yourself
or inside you're just lucky it was me
and not someone else who got their hooks
into you
I'm sorry that I lied to you
and and weirdly in some ways you're a
nice guy normally
oh in some ways Goods no doubt let's go
it gives me a battle Chopper really
the god of pigeons is a battle Chopper
that's amazing
what the hell are we do doing here we're
going to meet someone sounds fun you
know you and your cousin you should get
out what you're looking for you won't
find feds are all over it crime is done
you've watched too many movies crimes
crime is never done whatever your name
means it's Karen
my name is Karen she's a [\h__\h] Karen
and you [\h__\h] for the government
I kind of like the honesty in death I
have a clear conscience how very lucky
for you in here office 396. hi there
here he is I can see that thanks Karen
hey cheer up you did good you get a
Sammy if you care about that sort of
thing this does feel like a trap
I shouldn't be here
who are you if I be yeah am I gonna work
for them do I
I'm not a good guy but I'm fighting with
them and guess what so are you hooray
that's the spirit nothing like a bit of
sarcasm when someone's got you by the
balls now I need you to find something
out for me find out everything you can
about a man called olegminkov he lives
on Iroquois back in Hove Beach
and if I say no I had your file over to
those cretans in the FIB and organized
crime has dealt another serious blow
go to his house any problems call this
number
what's your name not relevant call me
very soon
go
and hey
welcome to America
oh
oh my
God
oh man we got a new round of quests
um noise
can't ever have enough and can you draw
me
no okay
mean
so we're going here okay
neat car don't go car
[Music]
um
which one should we take this one
what is this
what is this sound what
what the [\h__\h]
is this a sound bug
oh it's supposed to be a car horn but
nah
no it's coming like from the building or
so
it wasn't the car I mean I'm having I'm
having a Deja Vu right now what the [\h__\h]
huh
I'm having an inner related to desirable
and I feel like I told like a year ago
I told you guys about this Deja Vu
before
I'm having a Deja boy
something with Ina
I don't know what I'm talking about
[Music]
papa papa
in a bus no smoking music
wait I remember something about that too
did I have a Deja Vu with that
I don't I don't think that's what I
meant I don't know I don't know I don't
want to remember
I don't want to remember
it's too painful
okay taxi guys thinking like me wants to
go through the middle
say it back
[Music]
cute car
I should
oh yeah
I want somebody else
[Music]
all this time
how much do you think this fares will
cost
60 bucks
40 50.
hmm
[Music]
I have arrived
yeah I love new Teen songs
what's up
I like this door but it's a little bit
too visible for the outside what's going
on inside
Anita
curtain
anybody here
oh
an open laptop sus
not much he keeps a clean house he's got
a computer
well
I'm eating in the country it's so
[\h__\h] good
um
the old seeing eyes watching you
lies down my son at home
what the [\h__\h]
what should I look for emails I suppose
but he's got zero
come on you don't even watched by the
government spies your phone isn't tapped
you don't need to drink that bottle of
water or eat from those tins because no
one wants to poison you
please get that into your head okay this
person was very paranoid apparently
wait is that where we could find them
[Music]
tracing the money I reach that ends in
either Caymans or Switzerland sorry I
cannot help you further
[Music]
um
um what should I look for did I find
what I'm looking for I think so
yeah
[Music]
jewelry store
I'll keep the door open I'm sure they
don't mind
open house baby
oh
I didn't skip the call on purpose
did I
oops
yeah Lord I'm sorry
the fall
the fall scripted
Mamma Mia
well we'll catch up
they'll tell us what's up
everything's ruined
oh yeah
take him down so can I blow the car up
for real this time
I feel like yes
mom
what God he's fast [\h__\h] and I'm just
turning I was turning the other way this
whole time
this car is [\h__\h]
it's kind of
[\h__\h]
I'm trying I can't go any faster than
this
um
oh is that could that be him I think I'm
catching up
ah oh
nice maneuver
shitty bus
all right
okay okay and left oh
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
I can't make it blow up he's so fast
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
dude
wait for me which one is it on the right
side okay
Tim
done any damage to this car so far
feels like he's untouchable
Untouchable under the table Untouchable
Untouchable
what what
did he not take this path
[\h__\h] no I'm gonna lose him no no
he painted me yeah
who created
what about cupcake
I need a better car I'll show about a
car
[Music]
perhaps
um
sports car
if I could find one
oh is that
[Music]
um
what's that supposed to be muscle car
it's not a low rider
it says Turbo
it says turbo so
I think it can go turbo mode all right
it's a muscle car it looks fast to me
I think we'll have better chances
Maybe
just that car should do it okay nice
you know what I'm turning the
bgm back on here for this Chase
[Music]
hi hi
hi
hello
[Music]
everybody
demo
[Music]
foreign
awesome
oh
skip scoop skip skip skip skip
don't listen to more than anything she's
so cute I haven't talked to her in a
while
Mr minkov I want to talk to here
I can't skip this for some reason
not much he keeps a clean house he's got
the computer he only turned around the
corner he barely looked at the apartment
and already says not much
who knows maybe in the bathroom he would
have had something
okay do I have to look for this again
I'm guessing yeah
oh oh interesting
interesting wow so go away
this time I'm not falling
so I guess we're getting the missing
piece of lore
killing is very different from gathering
information
[Music]
oh
with me she's so cute
can I why can I not skip these scenes
are they
that's it
ah there we go there was some
problems
I'm Gonna Take You Down
[Music]
you don't want an angry chihuahua on
your ass
gonna miss it
[Music]
too much too much momentum
okay
[Music]
oh yeah
okay is that the
no that's not it
okay
all over the bridge
wait what the [\h__\h] how did he hit how
did he how did he get up there
how did he get up there
was he underneath
he must be underneath yeah
where is he going next that way probably
right
I would think
[Music]
what the hell
he went through there maybe actually
oh oh I saw
it okay
I feel like uh that was like
we were cutting him off there nice
mistake
[Music]
oh
no
I'm not following him on that one not
this time
[Music]
yo I think I got tires
I think
uh okay
okay
[Music]
my ammo how do I switch it I'm switching
uh I keep on Switching the radio I want
to switch a weapon or like ammo
weapon
Q
what the [\h__\h] why are you I can't do
that I'm driving my my fingers must be
on wasd
oh
another grenade not this that's okay
okay
very inconvenient when driving
okay I'm gonna use all my pistol ammo
or a while of ram him
[Music]
I was hoping oh sorry for more than that
he dodged it in the last moment
a police car drive by us until now
oh
blood or something like that
[Music]
yeah all right
yeah yeah
[Music]
is it gonna blow up nicely
oh I'm waiting for it oh
why why now
what
they didn't care
I'll be in touch goodbye just because I
was on the crime scene that's actually
pretty smart if that's the reason
[Music]
stay in the middle stand no oh
and it's right in the middle
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it was exactly the one that was coming
over to me even
[Music]
okay stay here
okay now we're clear
I think I should change car
also where are we going next
there's a u let's go to do you or to the
RB yeah let's go to you
know
yo I'll take a taxi
is there someone that oh
you can kick him out
asserting dominance in the taxi
buy ammo first oh
[Music]
it's true maybe I I should get some ammo
actually just this once
God damn it
sorry I'm getting in again
[Music]
is the wobble winning I think today this
whole episode I was only winning
Adam and I love that part
[Music]
so I need this
I need a ammo for this what does what
looks like this
this is not it this is not it this is
not it
find it
which one is the equivalent
I can't see it I'll buy this for example
[Music]
right corner ah
so
is this like an upgraded version
ah okay now it's a SMG rounds okay so I
think I already have the best version
okay
that's good what about the other things
this one no I think like for the sniper
I don't generally need so many right
and uh
where's my
am I not missing a weapon the the one
that was like close up but not a sniper
rifle
I lost it
this one right oh wait no not this one
which one
what was that
my assault rifle oh I can't believe it I
lost it it's a silver rifle
it says like salmon
what
[Music]
ah assault rifle
nice a piece of weapon for sure
[Music]
okay and some memo um
okay what not this one
sniper
what's this
looks like [\h__\h]
[Music]
sniper rifle
oops Yeah
uh cancel
you got a new stronger pistol too
oh wait is it is is this the uh upgraded
thing
[Music]
is this it
carbine rifle
oh
but then I can't use the same ammo right
I have to buy new animals
what no it uses the same maybe oh yes
it's the same okay nice
I'm guessing these are upgrades too I
don't think I have this kind of thing
should I get this a micro SMG ah we
shopping
and we shopping
no this one's weaker doesn't download
what
what about this one
as this SMG runs people said I should
get even more
I got too much money I need to get rid
of it
the pistols just all look boring to me
more inaccurate oh
buy that pistol this one
[Music]
no this one right
okay
uh
[Music]
don't tell me it's different ammo
I'm buying the right stuff right
okay that's just should be enough
[Music]
too bad you can't make weapons pink in
here
ready for what good pistol oh we gotta
try it out
what's wrong
it rarely rains in this game
and now
RB or U what do you want guys
[Music]
our beanie oh okay
it's so close we could walk
but it doesn't show me
how to walk there
hmm
I'm gonna guess
[Music]
nice to get some workout right
every once in a while having a little
walk I used you know the rain reminds me
of it but when I was uh spending the day
with Nina it was raining and I have
raincoats that I never use fancy
raincoats that I bought
uh ages ago for Korea for going to South
Korea
because of the flood and then I didn't
even really use it
but I used my raincoat and it was so
convenient because like Nina so often I
gave her you know one of my like small
umbrellas that you can make like really
small right
and so often she would like have
troubles closing it she was she was like
walking into a cafe or a building she
would attempt to close it she would
think she had it closed she would let go
and then in the middle of the entrance
of the building the cafe he would like
bam open up again and then it happened
several times she kept on messing with
the
umbrella while for me it was just taking
off the hood of putting it back up
yeah it's because my pockets umbrella
was a little bit too high-tech it has
like a button and everything
oh yeah high tech some odd friends but
you know what are you gonna do you're
right I've been keeping Bad Company Oh
you mean this guy he's okay well he pays
up and uh he ain't got State [\h__\h] very
funny haha listen we got a lot of
missing money and we got a problem with
these [\h__\h] bikers and I've got the
problem finding someone yeah I nearly
got something on that hamburger totally
sent some of our boys after the money
interesting maybe you can continue
causing trouble on the corner of vauxite
and exit sure otherwise you and Raymond
here got a serious problem okay
I showed you with my new combat pistol
It's Gonna Leave
well guys when I'm talking raincoat I'm
not talking like lame raincoat like I
saw so many tourists
wearing these like throwaway raincoats
that were really thin and
not nice looking my raincoats are
something else
they are beautiful they're gorgeous yes
and I never get to use them
yeah the cheap plastic ones but mine's
out of plastic too but like high quality
plastic huh
gorgeous stuff
[Music]
and please thank you
designer plastic that's right
fashionable stuff
thank you for bringing me
[Music]
honestly yeah I do think those are like
designer raincoats like not like okay
Louis Vuitton designer but
they were like special brands
oh [\h__\h] should I have prepared a proper
vehicle no there's a bike there can I
take that one please and then prepare a
proper vehicle it came with with a taxi
for [\h__\h] sake okay thank God thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
uh yeah
wait for me
it's trolling me
okay here we go well now we're talking
and this is my new combat pistol should
I go am I killing them
I think yeah
[Music]
I need your support
it it wait oh okay okay they wait for me
I think they're waiting for me
[Music]
please I need to get in the right
position
[Applause]
I can't believe they're waiting for me
on that one
[Music]
oh my God
don't know
thank God for automatic lines
[Music]
okay one down one more to go put to put
your hands up
now please keep your hands on the
vehicle
uh
is it is it the reach what's going on
wonderful bright round Egghead this
whole time
[Music]
wait
there we go no actually blocked I see
blogs
wait wait wait wait
oh
I need to catch up okay I see blood
again I see blood I see blood here we go
I feel like this is where I would have
ended anyway because he would have
crashed
it's not normal either is it I got rid
of those Bikers For You Johnny wasn't
there though
I should scripted those trains
well well well
we went really far here huh
we gotta go back to our beach
[Music]
what did I miss
wake up
[Music]
[Applause]
put your hands up yeah I got Nina's
stories by the way I just was waiting to
First tell all the stories that came
chronologically before
gotta be fair you know
[Music]
not doing any social connections well
I don't have time for that
bro
Glory
should point in the right direction
wait it's showing me the route force
that was overground right how do I get
out of here
gotta find a station Maybe
[Music]
how dare they download me all the time
I'm coming to collect you from the
apartment why are they panicking
am I are we having a date or are we
doing a story with Roman
I wish I could take the bike with me
story
cool
[Music]
it's a mission is the mission bowling
honestly I would understand I wouldn't
even be mad hello
scary is there really just like police
men with sniper rifles or AKs or
whatever
in the in the subway stations like that
in New York City
yes
what the [\h__\h]
what
that is
that is terrifying
what in the in the in the subway yeah
oh my God
laughs
oh Bank
I take bike
I just don't want to be
that's it that's all I wanted to do and
there okay
I'm gonna give you uh blue balls on my
The Glory Days in life you know I mean
if you think you think wait am I
supposed to take him up in a car but he
can go down the back on the motorcycle
we're ready wait are you guys not
telling me that we're actually secretly
going bowling
[Music]
no okay okay
you know what I mean it felt like we
were about to go bowling
so you play Blackjack Roman
O Let's [\h__\h] up
what do you mean I mean you [\h__\h] up and
I take this [\h__\h] you killed the wrong
guy and these friends will [\h__\h] with me
yeah I never killed the wrong guy
bar to have so many cuts on me you are a
rich chopping board I worry for you
wouldn't be sometimes you just gotta let
the hate go you're really going to kill
the car Florian is dead soon we will
find out the blue one was cute
[Music]
no I really I don't kill so many
pedestrians I don't know what you guys
are on about
he's always at the games being held
around Algonquin hey I asked him to make
a picture of me and he didn't do it
I don't know what you're talking about
you sound very nervous
beat him a little eh all right already
likes to be called Floyd cravic at um
certain moments certain moments
okay for car door what
I I don't I don't I don't know what you
mean I didn't say anything I didn't say
anything
Prius what's your problem got a problem
to freeze
I'm signing a family with this car
nice music but I gotta switch
unfortunately
when I find you okay seems like most
people didn't know this my blunder
don't turn here okay
foreign
[Music]
you are a terrible navigation system sir
try to say it a little bit earlier
please
okay then take this right that's right
oh yeah
what do you mean turn left
I hear okay
oh
what is that what he wants
but this is what it's a wrong
I'm guessing he meant afterwards but
that's suddenly so early normally he's
always so like late with his
announcements here
nah [\h__\h] what
is he butt
I don't want
to know
unless he really means it
above ground it went [\h__\h]
yeah well I don't know I apparently I'm
on the raw it doesn't work in a tunnel
yeah he told me to go into the tunnel
Chicago
it's so misleading
so misleading
turn left he says
unbelievable
things
oh what's that car
[Music]
cute let me think about this yeah think
think really hard don't lead me into a
tunnel again
he's messing with me so what do I do
Talbot
what
okay so like here
[Music]
ridiculous
hangover rides okay
[Music]
am I going straight here
okay can only go straight
what about now take a left
[Music]
uh yeah
I hate him I
am
not right this is terrible
[Music]
tell me yes I will tell me
the most your friend can look forward to
get out of here now you've done your job
yeah
yo red chips remix so good
um
how [\h__\h] strong do you have to be
Gloria
I've come for you nice apartment
yo that TV is very close to bed I mean
mine is in front of the bed too but
that's like
I don't know
Nico
the hell are you doing here
what happened to you
oh I started working out you know toned
up the uh
you used to work in the abattoir oh
don't remind me
he's very European you put on a few
vanity pounds
you guys doing here why don't you kick
my door down
his manners
it wasn't you was it what was it me who
set us up it was your Darko I thought it
must be him
oh my God
you think it was me that's why you are
here you've come to kill me yes
it wasn't me it wasn't I wouldn't do
that
can we stop with the fat jokes Florian
let's not bring Roman to The Comedy Club
he would not be amused
lifestyle coach and I teach in aerobics
of course it's aerobics
[Music]
he's married that picture is so doomed
and he's in politics
he's the deputy mayor
Bryce Dawkins but he's so into Family
Values oh that's just politics where is
that I hope
ah I'm not sure
I I heard he was still in Europe or
Switzerland or somewhere but then I
heard that you had joined the circus so
information can be used
we have to find it
we have to find him I think he's a bit
freaked out I guess he thought seeing
you would answer some questions so I see
it's great to see you guys
almost
because we're keeping him alive
yes he's moved on from what happened to
you
you should have moved on too
what are you going to do he may not be
here in Liberty City but he's still out
there I will find out where Darko
brevich is and I will make him answer
for his actions we know now that it was
him
I need to be alone now Roman only course
sentimental see you later there cute
call me okay
no
no I will not
hey
Roman thumbs up yay
oh hello Ray
it wasn't the one I was looking for
[\h__\h]
I Sim Isis like seems to be a world for
everything
should I take my Prius again
it's practically my car now so
what do we do
uh you guys
last time said RB
should I go to RB again
or you
you
Watch Me Go
[Music]
boy
I love football stand by singing
so cute
she is an impeccable incredible senpai
so professional so skilled
so fun
[Music]
so Charming
I love it
[Music]
put it
I don't mind being friend zoned by her
it's honestly an honor
oh yeah can you guys remind me at the
end of the stream to schedule Hollow
cure for next week because I'm going to
forget it
thanks
foreign
[Music]
that's where I'm going right now
I think no wait never mind
[Music]
I'm sure you do but you said you'd help
me I've already helped you
again
all right
[Music]
when is next qao cooking well I haven't
uploaded my last two
but I was cooking
I've been cooking
so
you fought in the War you know been
yummy but I I noticed
I actually over season things recently
too much but most of us don't want to
kill
a kill because
they don't taste like anything most
wives are killed by their husbands yes
and my wife I better stop sleeping with
that tennis coach or oh tennis coach
again it's always the tennis coaches
it's always the tennis coaches oh I'm
joking
sure she does funny I'm divorced my wife
can sleep with whoever she wants
interesting I'm not divorced I was never
married no details I need you to go find
someone for me I'll be getting a picture
through shortly this is important okay
why use me we always use people like you
Karen Michelle she was the same
someone with something to lose but not
much to live for
what's in it for me two things one
what's this camera 100 murders pinned on
you
maybe I will help you and maybe I won't
now get access to a police computer and
wait for my message go
get access to a police computer
oh in the police car again right
it's been a while
mama
he sees Doom bug yeah something was
weird
uh read the message when it arrives okay
waiting for it and I'm guessing I'll
need a police car
yeah I am please wait
[Music]
just you're trying to find him and take
him out hey hey
[Music]
next please
I should have followed that one maybe
maybe we'll have stopped again soon
um
call 9-1-1
I guess
help me oh someone's trying to short me
please hello
this is the LCPD where would you like us
to send an officer here in front of the
the funny crabs
The Fanny crabs
yep thank you thank you so much for for
being here for me is this the one that's
here for me
is it
[Music]
I'm just going wee wall ow
problem is that I need your car I'm so
sorry please let me in please let me in
please
oh they would have definitely shot by
now
lose your winning level on it on it on
it
Simple and Clean
that was Simple and Clean don't you
think
it's the way that you make me feel
tonight
regardless of warnings
access how how was it how's it work
again
why is it not telling me how
is it like e no enter no
how do I do it
G
it's not g One Stop press e
I'm pressing e oh no there we go
oh
I don't know maybe no okay uh
[Music]
no okay
oh this person okay
where's my photo
oh high tech score
turtleneck man with slick hair
ding ding ding ding that's him he's even
wearing the same elves
it
uh wanted for financing terrorist
activity hangout kamayash import export
okay Adam
uh enter to Mark De Mayo's hang on okay
perfect perfect
[Music]
how far is it oh it's quiet for her is
my radio off or does this car not have
radio
oh it must not have radio
was there a button for the radio
no radio
employee
so sad to real policemen also not listen
to music
[\h__\h] I missed the I always miss it here
always
[Music]
no fun allowed for police
foreign
no music for them it's so sad
I'm the police I'm allowed to do that
and I will take no consequences
with me
both
move out of the way I'm on a mission
what I don't understand the GPS
I'm sorry let me go this way
it's more logical to me this is the
police music
wow it's so beautiful it rings
so many bells in my heart
[Music]
I just ugh I can connect with it and I I
can just
just feel
the world and connect with it on another
level you know
um
speak so sing it
[Music]
oh
all swoosh to the side very cute
except for the police car
what the [\h__\h]
you didn't get the memo
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
okay I'll turn it off it's actually
obnoxious
oh
suddenly felt the need to call someone
[Music]
is there a smart way to do it
I want to like throw a grenade from the
top of one of those buildings
but I'm guessing that's not something
that I can do because I can't enter the
buildings
know those
are not available
[Music]
oh wow yeah this feels really high-tech
if only I could walk while carrying it
oh [\h__\h] but
I wanna can I can I treat myself a
helicopter fly up there and throw down
the grenade
probably not
oh wait can I go up here no
what if I go up here will he notice me
what do you think
well yes
but that one might
and I'll have a silence or anything on
my
gun do I
hmm well whatever
even if he notices
[\h__\h]
okay
we're going the usual way
here we go
fire has opened welcome to the party
baby come on come
on come on who was he shooting he was
showing the wall
aim doko
he wanted to get some style points I see
chicken I'm afraid
you will regret what you two said to me
show you what happens when you call me a
chicken
it will be worse than a usual room
what do you want ah what do you want
from me
all the rats Must Die
all of them
every single one
will be eliminated you two I'm done here
my job is done oh
[Music]
what's this looks cool no no no okay no
no wanted level really really
I have just a huge shooting in the
middle of the city
no I'm I'm dissatisfied I'm unsatisfied
what was that nobody chasing me I like
to be chased like chunky monkey
foreign
well okay
I feel like
[Music]
ah
maybe I should take you know what
um
sorry Wayne I out
I'm gonna take a taxi because it's so
far
let's enter the taxi without a weapon in
our hands shall we
hello taxi mush
oh I see some
online enjoy his car oh wait a minute
what can I do for you
come soon
I'm very oh it's not a hot dog you
actually get burgers here oh
there you are thank you oh man
oh looks actually pretty decentral for
that price especially
oh sure
hey
five bucks yo what oh wait I guess okay
maybe that's expensive actually never
mind
but I feel like for in-game for you know
with looking at my money looking at what
things cost in the game
oh man
Saving Room for Hot Pot later
excuse me I didn't give you a free pass
to act again yes what you're breaking a
lot of heat hang out with bands
I'm an idiot I I move true but the last
thing also is you getting caught you may
get a cheaper burger at like McDonald's
but if you go to a proper restaurants
that has burgers
it can be more expensive right
it's like 10 bucks
in the last days call me up my number
never existed no I'm not too worried
about that I mean you think you'll end
up on a flight deck but that's your
business because you're good because I
need you to keep being good and you're
getting distracted
maybe a little bit Yeah but food someone
neutralized guy is moving a lot of money
for
the guy's got to go but I need to know
his movements first huh I've got
something that's going to help you head
over to Albany Avenue in Lansing give me
a call
how do I get paid for this can I get the
medal can you get a medal in your last
war
what did you give Michelle
for me Michelle Karen
we gave her a life back oh we didn't
play too rough
we gave her some money she still works
for us
what about me we'll discuss that later
um
7-Eleven no it's an American 7-Eleven
and I don't care much
if it's a
car
what's wrong with him
I just saw him driving now he's like
against the wall
soda
[Music]
if it's Japanese 7-Eleven then I might
you know
give you some orders
um and he's having a bad day poor guy
I'm gonna go here uh
uh okay so they don't stop for you but
I need a car lady get out
[Music]
okay
do I get the chopper
home
for the first time in this game I think
I think so let's see how the controls
are because in GTA 5 anything that flies
was a little bit rough
no air pressing f is not allowed f is a
band button
nobody will convince me to press f
[Laughter]
I see it it's got the cute colors for my
Corvette
of the stripes white and red
what do you mean follow
um
the focus on caps lock
okay well that doesn't really help me
[Music]
Japanese
I don't wanna I don't wanna
imagine her recording this
[Laughter]
huh
where is it
okay we're still kind of on the same
route
yeah yeah good good good I should stay
on the highway that's good
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
I'm sorry for taking this path
go here already okay
this music is so good yeah baby why
would you turn like that
ah wait where is he now okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
no I'm not losing it no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no no please don't make me lose it no I
see it I see it
see I can catch up
[Music]
right through the two police cars yeah I
can hear it clearly
foreign
[Music]
going good
oh it's Landing it's Landing
[Music]
let it land and move in to take it uh
will they attack me when I do so
[Music]
I will overtake this helicopter thank
you everybody
just kidding I don't know how to fly it
though how the [\h__\h] do I fly it
decrease okay and now
well what now how do I a noun pad eight
and two
Bank the helicopter in the direction
okay so two what the [\h__\h] Roman
now it's really not the time worst time
possible
[Music]
[Applause]
oh God
okay I lost the police wonderful
[Music]
I got perfect control over it
okay
[Music]
now on to our goal
wait
[Music]
you're bad
I'll take it back I don't have perfect
control over it
because I'm so close
[Applause]
[Music]
it's fun though flying this thing
wow
let's go straight
go straight
I'm so lucky that I haven't crashed yet
no I'm not locking the door
and said Tiny apples and I I'm not gonna
push F no I have I have like
burned it into my brain
don't worry
best
[Music]
hi hi hi
oh
pretty smooth don't you think guys
I have yet to crash
no complaints
[Music]
I'm ready for Vice City relief what
makes you say that these impeccable
controls wait I'm like where am I oh
uh-huh
[Music]
what
what am I landing at
me
[Music]
am I allowed to land it here
are we sure about this
to line up four and six uh wait it's a
bit difficult Landing
yo look at me rocking it
[Applause]
smoothest flyer in Vice City uh whatever
the city was again New York
Liberty City
and we're going back up
it was just oh no they're going without
me
bye bye well while I'm here just kidding
I don't know I don't I don't
[Music]
have the balls for it honestly
wait I was calling someone did I cancel
it by accident what the [\h__\h]
hi how you doing I want to talk
I'm not gonna question me being here
with a knife in front of you no
can I get in here no
no plans wait you're not allowed to you
can't like literally impossible to take
a plane
in GTA 4.
cancel cancel because I bombed
Katie that's a different color
oh
different maybe I am different pick me
up I'm free now
there
sure I'll be there in the next hour I'll
see you then Kate see you Nico
[Music]
no
wait is this the right person
listen Kate forgive me yes something's
come up thanks I love rejection
you're welcome
oh you're so welcome
uh-huh
I feel bad now but it didn't hurt our
relationship right our non-existent
relationship
all right Los Santos
wait I know Los Santos
visit Los Santos 300 bucks
isn't Los Santos where GTA 5 plus
hey Miko what's up Mallory so mine
hasn't spoken to you about anything
happening
I haven't heard anything but I'm sure it
would be a really good thing for both of
you thanks oh sweet excited to be on
YouTube chat then
I guess when he found out about me and
Vlad he couldn't help himself his love
for me took over and he just had to kill
him that's exactly right he's an old
school romantic freaking maniacs
uh what apparently I've been sent a
picture ah
no that's not it uh
why don't I ever say Unico you spending
too much time chasing titties and
avoiding your cousin let's hang out Rome
[Music]
Hey cuz thanks for saving my ass back
there I thought that bled my last hand
when the biker guy kidnapped me for the
Russians you're a [\h__\h] hero man
he loves me so much
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] are you I can't tell you
ain't rolling with bling on [\h__\h] and
the [\h__\h] paper because that's where
I'm at
um
[Music]
hey Roman you want to hit the bowling
alley I love to watch the girls
welcome back
did he say he picks me up or I pick him
up
what the [\h__\h] was that sound that was
scary
wait one second one second
I think I think
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
foreign
that's not a meow that's my door
[\h__\h]
ah
okay
oh
uh
[Music]
um no no no not movie it's just uh
uh
[Music]
just yeah
some things flying around outside
and I had to bring in a chair
where was I
but the chair is now apparently broken
[Music]
no the bubble bubble crying that was
just the door
sound of the door
ah flying chair
um actually
a while ago uh a while ago quite a while
ago when there was like this time where
it was crazy stormy for one or two days
I think
and
I know this sounds crazy but the table
the table of my like
balcony set
flew away
I didn't see the moment when it flew
away but it just eventually was gone and
I never found it again
um yeah so I gave up on balcony balcony
furniture for now
but I like kind of locked the
the current the leftover Furniture in
the like in a position so that it should
be pretty safe from the wind but uh yeah
I know it's [\h__\h] dangerous but that
never that's like that's honestly that
was crazy
like even when I went outside
uh like as a person it felt like I was
gonna be knocked over from the wind
it was actually insane really really
rare strong storm
um it was really bad it was so bad that
I could hear like weird sounds in my
apartment and I couldn't record and I
needed to urgently record things yeah
it was like really weird sounds like not
just wind sounds but like concerning
sounds
that just wouldn't stop it was really
obnoxious I hear them right now too
so it's it's yeah
strong
um
yeah
so I haven't had a balcony balcony table
in a while
yeah
does Austria get tornadoes I don't
remember ever ever
hearing anything about a tornado but
apparently recently in Austria there was
like a lot of rain that um like recently
as in like yesterday and so on
was a lot of rain that it got really bad
and some people died apparently
um
yeah
like really
bad flooding
no I heard of it
um
foreign
yeah I think I heard yeah Slovenia also
very very flooded
I it happens sometimes yeah
yeah yeah what was I doing
um
[Music]
Eva go to Ray or ah Bernie
oh actually no wait we're going bowling
I forgot is he picking me up or am I
picking him up I'm not sure
what did he say he was no
I'm picking him up okay let's pick him
up with uh
limousine
well I gotta commit to the [\h__\h]
[Music]
are you gonna get out at any time
no
[Music]
he'll get out when I pick up Roman
foreign
[Music]
I love this song right now
okay okay okay
[Music]
can I stay here
shut up close the door man rude
[Music]
ah the police car thought that was the
limousine he was looking for but it was
this one
[Music]
Roman can I make it in one hour like
wait where is where is Rome here
so far
[Music]
thank you
don't bump into the police
[Music]
going bowling now
really
I feel like if I would have accepted
that now maybe it would have overwritten
my current promise with um Roma and
that's why I didn't do it
I don't know if it works like that but
better be careful oh it's a cute car
[Music]
[\h__\h] the limousine isn't looking so
pretty anymore and I prepared it just
for Roman
cute
[Music]
oh my God
I just had an idea I had an epiphany
can I ride it really quickly to Gemma
um
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can't say anything about it no
you'll find out
maybe sometimes
just let me cook
I wish I knew the lyrics
to the song or Indonesian at all
I just wanna sing the song of my
daughter
oh I don't know Indonesian
[Music]
changing
baby
[Music]
wait was there an English version
and make an English version
okay closest bowling one is here
I guess that's the closest one
I want some
pretty strong
but you're so happy about life is cheap
he's happy because I finally am bringing
him to bowling even though it was on its
best way to become a meme
know where it is yeah but most people
don't know where it is so there's no
English right
we should make it yeah
that's big shortcuts they stay on the
highway like every other chump I'm an
innovator Nico I drive off Roman is
telling us some deep stuff
deep life knowledge
I might take you there with me
why weren't you such an optimist back
home country the only thing you could
count on was a bomb Landing why do they
always say the old country why don't
they name it do they avoid naming it
because they don't want to be clear
about where the protagonists are from
start drinking
okay
or it's a saying
[Music]
they did stay in early on okay then it's
just a way of saying it
yeah I thought I thought they said it
but
oh my God okay
[Music]
oh
bowling here
[\h__\h]
what
I'm having issues here
[Music]
yo okay
what happened with the taxi I need to I
need a rewind of that
it's falling time [\h__\h] which is our
lane this one again maybe I don't know
how do we choose it how do I start do I
need shoes do I need to talk to you
uh full game
full or nothing
okay we're taking the that corner
outside one because that one's cool
okay I'm not gonna let Broman ruin my
reputation again
[Music]
it doesn't work and one motion pulled
him out backward
it doesn't work
it won't let me do it
ah
that that was like just random movement
of my hand
oh without clicking I guess because I
was clicking maybe without clicking
that's why it just happened
[Music]
yeah okay without clicking please yeah
yeah restart restart
[Music]
X's is EXO
did he get all of them in one try
strike what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
please come on give me at least
oh
okay nine and nothing then is what that
means I think
oh that looks good
[Music]
oh it was a spare ah [\h__\h] but okay I got
a strike I got one strike he got not a
spare okay if that before was a spare
and this must mean that but this is more
points now
what does that mean oh well
um
spare again don't think about it okay
you're right coach it's just gonna make
me nervous this will be a strike too
baby I got it now I got it
I just needed to figure out some things
oh [\h__\h]
I hear things flying again I think
yummy
don't worry I'm I'm probably ending at
least the gaming section after this
bowling game
that is my being not so good
um [\h__\h]
I'll just go for this one then
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay okay but we're still leading
right we're still leaving
until now maybe because he just got a
strike
oh
come on please this is serious
it should have been a strike
okay now it's really on the very edge
am I too far
he's too good at bowling
dude is too good but I still got a
chance
[Music]
yeah looks good it's the middle but
we're still missing one ah not again on
the very edge
Maybe
maybe here
thank God
who's bear
and he gets also spare
[Music]
I need another strike baby
that just ain't it
oh please yeah looks good okay
okay okay
what the [\h__\h]
I need a strike
no what why did it go so far to the
Divine they always went straight before
whoa
[Music]
oh I didn't expect me actually being
able to get the left one too
okay
[Music]
what
The Fad
hmm
Roman if you don't let me win I'm never
going bowling with you again
that's it
bastard that bastard it was close though
if I would have like you know in the
beginning
had some practice because I just had to
get back into it then I would have won
hmm
just just one more quickie okay
okay really fast no one will have to
suffer
strike
see I told you
why does it say zero from me anyway I
don't understand this kind of counting
system
ah
is it because it's waiting for me to
get more strikes and then calculated or
what no it's so why is it still zero
a 10 gets added to my next roll
I don't know about this one
okay at least one
okay I'm leading
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
strikes double your points
from the next frame oh okay
is that too far on the left
no
oh thank God
this music's straight up dmca uh I can't
change it can I no I can't
I could can I turn it off I don't know
what happens when I press Escape in this
situation I don't want to skip uh like
anything
okay
well it's probably too late now anyway
the pressure I need a spank too
oh that looks good yes
all right all right we're back in the
game
back in again
we got a spare
[Music]
two steps to the left and
that should have been a strike
foreign
[Music]
scratched it
okay okay we're leading we're leading
this no what the [\h__\h] okay
as if it was like windy in here too
[Music]
um why'd you have the middle one left
over why
we're still leading
we're still waiting
oh
considering it might do the same thing
yep okay I went extra far left because I
thought I might do the
the thing again by going to the right
side I calculated it
but even though I hit the middle
we left one over
oh
beautiful
[Music]
now he's leading that bastard what
because it didn't it still didn't count
my last one though right
bowling points confuse me
this one's nice
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
uh
no
I don't know losing confidence but okay
gotta believe in yourself
[Music]
please don't go right yeah
how you how do you even professional
bowlers out there how how do you even
solve a situation like this
isn't it like kind of impossible
you cry
you don't what do you mean you don't you
can't right right it's impossible
I mean unless you get in some way that
like one of the pins that you knock over
just
swings over to the left side and luckily
knocks over the the one on the corner
but
How likely is that to happen
you know with momentum but yeah that's
not happening
anyway we're leading we're gonna win
this we're gonna we have to
last one
yay yeah
hey hey hey hey
well one more oh I'm getting a second
strike chance
[Music]
[Applause]
looked like it was gonna go a bit too
far off enough wait didn't someone say
something about I'm out if I get three
strikes
how could it possibly be negative
can I get a turkey at the end
apparently it's called turkey free
strikes no way
no way no way I could be so cool
no
cool
if you cool
[Music]
you
oh
love you
I won right it says number of games is
tied but I what what does that mean I
win
yeah no turkey but almost turkey
ah okay very satisfying
I guess okay come come on
get into the shitty limousine that's
almost about to blow up
I'll bring you home
the moisturized the better I'm bowling
of course obviously maximum score it's
free handles for 12 strikes wow
oh [\h__\h] wrong way huh
I can't turn with a huge car like this
I'm not gonna ditch it no it's my
limousine I'm gonna stay with it until
The Bitter End
speaking of staying until The Bitter End
I think I won't be reading super chats
after this because like I had some
really short days yesterday and today
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] this can't be the end of our
bowling date get out of there Roman get
out of there get away from it
that's not what I meant with Bitter End
oh no
oh even the taxi driver collateral
damage is it gonna blow up let's watch
it together Roman it's romantic trust me
look at it three two a one
damn fireworks you can't tell me that's
not a fireworks Bingo on the Bingo sheet
nicer car nice nice I need that I need
that I need a car
yeah okay whatever this one's fine
[Laughter]
could we take a taxi together is that
possible
let me turn around
yeah oh maybe I should have done that
anyway yeah I wanna I want at least the
evening to be a little bit longer
I feel like I haven't
had any time
yesterday and today to relax
so I will do that
I have to make the schedule anyway so I
need a bit more time I'll upload the
schedule
after the Stream
for the next week
and I just gotta make the whole talk
thumbnail because I want it to be on the
schedule if possible
and yeah tomorrow I think I'm streaming
tomorrow but I think it's it's possibly
after midnight
I think that's what I was gonna do
tomorrow
gaming with fania
I think I might be wrong it's either
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow
I don't know
yeah you guys keep on telling me that
maybe maybe tell me
right when I really end the stream
maybe also tell me on Twitter
I gotta check though cause like
I think we're getting all of us in whole
life I think we're all getting
um Early Access
a little bit I don't know how early
yeah yeah I know you guys are saying
it's in two weeks but I'm I'm I I know
we're getting a little bit early access
I don't know if it's early enough to
play it in the coming week
I just gotta check that
um I gotta check probably
if it's in two weeks from now then
maybe the early accesses in one week
[\h__\h]
wait did I take the wrong it looked
right to me
recalculate route please
[Music]
thanks
yeah there will be oh they haven't told
me that
they told me they will tell me
um
thanks for reminding me because I want
to put it in my schedule
but they have yet to
announce a date I think
uh await it's
um
it
put the practice day on my schedule
okay oh
where
what was that
tabs back into game window randomly
shatters
we good I don't know
they said id said uh a couple days ago
when I asked oh we're inviting me all of
you soon to uh IDE Minecraft uh
practice
server oh
oh I don't know if they mean a Discord
Channel separate because Discord server
because often we make the separate
servers for
big projects or if they mean the
Minecraft server
anyway I'll figure all of this out off
screen
worst case I'll keep some days as
question mark or so I don't know or or
I'll just
fully
forcefully
squeeze it in somewhere afterwards after
putting out the schedule you know I love
to beat civilians
go safe oh is it in here oh yeah
like that we end up here
we got bowling nobody can complain
anymore
I've done everything you guys have asked
of me
nobody can possibly complain
[Music]
and we'll continue
soon hopefully
probably at least two more GTA four
streams
so I'm looking forward to it hope you
guys are looking forward to it too
and yeah I should be streaming tomorrow
if I am not wrong
um
did you fix Minecraft no I didn't I
don't know how but I will have to
I'll figure it out I'll figure it out
yeah yeah yeah so I enjoy when we say
I've been using guys thank you for
watching have a nice evening DLC on the
table sure I'm sure if I feel like it
yeah
yeah if I'm not fed up with the game if
it's not too long if the DLC is not too
long then yeah
bye bye good night thank you for
watching
um
[Music]
love you guys
thank you
foreign
[Music]