[Music]
ah
cake
oh [\h__\h] press something wrong
oh my god
[Music]
it's my birthday
hello oh my god this is so
weird i'm so not prepared for this
mentally oh my i don't know what's going
on
but my mind is uh uh
overwhelmed
thank everyone thank you there's so much
going on i
am overwhelmed really really overwhelmed
oh my god
i'm playing this orchestra version of
our
uh fall guys song just getting crispy
fry fried party
wow did you hear that
do you hear it wow
it's so pretty i don't
know oh my god this is too much okay uh
we are on a really tight schedule
so to explain a little bit um
first hour of this stream we'll be uh
doing some call-ins from whole live
japan members
and maybe he'll live indonesia
a whole lot of english coins later
because uh
no not much time they will if they call
in that they will call in in the second
hour
but in the second hour we'll be also
doing karaoke but in the first hour
we'll also be doing
uh some announcements so wait that that
was kind of like mixed mix around why am
i so
laggy why am i losing fps is it because
of the image image slide shows
oh my god is it
and we tried to hide it
[Music]
did it oh wait it did change didn't it
oh no it didn't i don't know so so
so we first uh i want to look at two
things that oh my god okay no this is
this music is making me
oh this music is making me a bit nervous
right now
um yeah okay
okay okay um we we have to look at some
things
because i i've been told by my manager
um
and i mean all one of them have already
it's been sent to me on twitter so i
kind of already knew that that was
coming but
there's a like uh mr sun said the
four four videos uh that i need to watch
on stream
uh and i said uh
two of them now and two of them later uh
one of one of those videos i already
know uh is coming
the other one was like what the [\h__\h]
she she sent them to me i didn't watch
them yet but i
i know uh who is in those videos
um
okay do we want to watch it together i
have to throw it into obs
uh i don't know how big and how loud
it's going to be
okay let's start off with faye oh my god
oh my god the collins i don't have oh my
god i don't have time okay let's start
out let's see
um let's go happy birthday to you
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait sorry i didn't hear that i
need to turn on the auto audio
ah this is okay for the people who don't
know who this is this is voice actress
uh of many many things one of the things
that she voice acted was
fire emblem we have some funny connect
funny connection
so okay uh let's watch this i think i
should be able to hear it now
he used to commission this and wait no i
don't hear it oopsie wrong setting
oh yeah that was the wrong thing sorry
this one there we go okay let's watch
happy birthday to kiara
your kfp employees commissioned this
and they told me that it is your
birthday
again and again that's just amazing i
can't imagine how many
years old you are because you are you're
a phoenix you just live forever
so whenever you spawn you just keep
having more and more
lives and stuff that's it's just really
impressive
i wish i was ageless anyway i'm supposed
to mention something about
a chicken pot pie i guess
i don't know why i like chicken pot pie
chicken pot pies you do you do and
you're pretty great
but anyway um i i just uh i want to wish
you
a really really happy birthday even if
you have many many lives i hope this
particular life
is is one that you really really enjoy
and you have many different experiences
that you get to
get to grow and learn from over and over
and over again and never get bored
because
you know any one thing in life can be
monotonous or
i don't know um stressful or
or i don't know like i just i just
imagine that
you can experience so many things in all
of your lives so
so i hope you just continue to make the
most of it
and never take anything for granted
because oh because you deserve to
experience the best happy birthday okay
bye
thank you oh yeah this was oh i screwed
it up i was supposed to say
hi i'm faye mana the voice actor of aqua
from coda suburban and petra from fire
emblem houses and
other stuff i usually open that way but
anyway
congratulations another year
thank you on fire okay bye
that was fair thank you
so cute the honestly would say it's like
we we have a really interesting history
now
we also participated in a shadow based
tournament together and she was
so so so sweet to me and
it just feels weird to for once have
someone be very very
flirty and nice with me so that was that
was
really nice i love faye thank you that's
so sweet
okay can we squeeze in one more before
we do the collins oh my god the time
pass is so fast okay let's
um uh squeeze in one more however i have
received uh
the info that after 40 seconds i should
mute the video damn it how i'm gonna do
that
while listening to it because there is a
copyright warning
how am i going to do that
you have it uh wait i should be able let
me test it right here if i do
if i switch it from from monitor
uh monitor
off to
wait let me test this out here
did you hear that because i heard it i
think you shouldn't be able to hear that
just now
did you hear that
no okay so after 40 seconds i will
switch it to that so that i will be able
to hear what you guys want okay good
good good good good good good
okay next up is kind of crazy
i just saw that the thumbnail and the
the name of the video
i'm already speechless oh my god okay
uh wait so wait oh
my god uh wait let me let this real hot
this is chantal
this is jumped out why is she on the
keyboard
okay after 40 seconds i will i will have
to mute it for you guys
let's see
hi kiara i am chantal kraviasik and i
hear
you have a birthday we've got a lot of
fans
over at kfp and so
um and they know you they know you love
my version of um
so i'm gonna sing you a bit of it now
and wish you a very very happy birthday
a quick happy wait can i i can play that
[Music]
happy birthday
oh there it is stop stop stop stop stop
stop stop now let me change the setting
monitor only let's go
you don't hear this you didn't hear that
right
you didn't hear that one second right
okay just gonna make sure
she's yeah she's doing a really smooth
transition to
uh living on the chat plane i think okay
let's go
[Music]
yes she's feeling it
outside your door i hate
to wake you up to say goodbye
but the dawn is breaking
i know i know there is no sound you're
not supposed to hear it copyright
oh
me and smile for me
tell me that you wait for me
so so beautiful
it's so beautiful
on a jet plane
nice nice one
i hate to go to
leave
[Music]
that high note oh
oh
oh my god
that was beautiful that was beautiful
that was that was uh that was beautiful
okay i have to do call-ins now
um but okay
[Music]
i i have some confirmations that certain
people are coming
so i'm i'm i'm i'm ready i'm ready
yeah leaving on a jet plane
yo
ah
[Music]
okay
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
uh yeah we have a collab on the weekend
check it out that was nineteen sorry
that was all japanese although all the
other
will probably also be japanese for a
while sorry
um
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
japanese japanese comedy
japanese comedy
[Music]
i heard you're coming together with
everyone that's going to be noisy oh
dear oh dear oh oh oh oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i guess we can talk in english actually
oh yeah i didn't realize that exactly
i've been i've been watching since
before and i'm like ah
yes you guys you can talk yeah yeah yeah
i think
english is okay yeah the viewers will be
happy
i thank you for for coming to my
birthday college
and that's so sweet of you all
happy birthday thank you
oh my god what is that what is that
actually i'll make something for you
oh i will give you to the
discord oh oh dear why what is it
what do you want is it your pants from
yesterday no
no no no no no no no
yes i don't actually can't i see here
she was streaming with her pants
on on you know let's let's get to the
business shall we oh my
god oh my god
if you really want my past i will give
it to you
wait wait wait wait wait you drew this
yeah i drove that
i didn't know you can draw so well oh
thank you wow that's great
why did i not know until now
oh actually i can draw pretty well i
didn't know what the hell
it's amazing thank you it's so pretty
thank you wait i think i just sent the
wrong one you sent the wrong one
that was the unrenderer version oh
there's another version okay
wait wait let me update oh that's very
pretty
that's that's really pretty
it's so big
for your next thumbnail or something oh
yeah that's a good idea thank you
by the way um i was asking the japanese
members
um do you do you have uh
any memory or or first impression
of takanashikiyana uh maybe start with
uh maybe urisu oh yes
uh for me though i really like your
kitty kitty is this my favorite part
since uh since your first debut and also
yeah i'm really happy when you asked me
to collab playing
uh yeah yeah
that was like so fun let's play together
again
actually i i don't know if you girls
heard
but i am organizing a big big mario kart
tournament between her life english and
whole life indonesia
i didn't tell you yet but you are
invited didn't really tell
anyone directly yet i only said in my
stream that i will do it but
um of course i want you girls to
participate please
are you good in minecraft not migrate
mario kart uh
[Laughter]
oh that that's good that's good that's
good
if you're bad then we i don't have to um
lose maybe let's loose together
until you you've me and muna do you also
have
some first impression or or so i don't
know
well at first at first when you're debut
i really like how
you introduce um chicken because i love
fried chicken so much i love eating
that's really make me happy just like oh
my god there's there's really a
chicken vinegar i was like actually i
was thinking that you are literally
chicken feet
because before before you would i i said
i said something like um i'm gonna i'm
gonna do something like this if there
there is already a chicken feet over
here
yeah i want to keep thinking that you
are a chicken
okay i guess i have no choice right
right music doesn't seem so bad yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah maybe i'm good know
yeah because that kfp will we we we sell
phoenix yep that's yes
it's a little bit of a complicated
situation that we have but let's just
say
it is it is what it is it looks like
it's fine
oh i i wanna i wanna collab with you
mom
[Music]
one of my first impression of you was um
i can finally find someone that uh can't
speak german
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah i wanted to do
something with german with you all this
time
yeah me too because uh uh i'm still
learning so i need uh
i want i just want to know a lot a lot
about it so maybe we can do
you know a little bit of german classes
together
but you are no because you know the
problem is that my my first
language is german and teaching someone
they their first language is
not hard yeah it's kind of hard and and
i can do like simple
like introduction classes but you're
already uh
like advanced so i don't know what i
would teach you
but we can just have a talking
language
okay okay i have a good one that i use
all the time because
i am actually not from germany i am from
the neighboring country
and uh we have some kind of german
accent dialect
there and and one word that we use
all the time is oida
yeah o o i d a
um we say it like in any kind of
situation but it actually directly
translated it means like
like dude or like oh yeah
it's like dude and so so we're always
like
this is so amazing or that this [\h__\h]
sucks all the time
[Music]
yeah we're gonna use it of course i'll
throw this we're gonna use it oh thank
you
and we can have a german talking stream
sometime soon okay
okay thank you oh thank you all three of
you
i'm sorry i have to kick you out now
because i have a tight
tight time schedule
[Music]
bye
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you thank you i'm so happy
bye bye oh my god no no no no no no
they don't stop coming and they don't
stop coming at it
not your dogs
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
my
is
foreign
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
like crispy chicken it's it's crispy you
know you see that texture
no no no i thought the head is just my
sun hats that i wear
but it's crispy
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
i love you too so much love you
thank you bye bye bye
bye
oh my god please wait for the translated
clip of that
puppy
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
oh my god i need to you know i need to
do merch and stuff
uh but is someone coming
right
hello oh my god this is crazy because i
know this is like our first first time
talking to yeah
it is it's crazy well thank you for
having the courage to come hello
hello happy birthday oh thank you
birthday
i hope today will be a good day for you
oh yeah
it's a crazy day right now but yeah
okay sorry we have to do this quick but
what was your first impression of me
oh my first impression of you actually
was
um kind of different from like you were
like more timid especially in your debut
stream
oh yeah um how should i say this um
more say so then now
yeah yeah i mean that's probably true
yeah
oh yeah all right it's really
different oh thank you you're a really
really cool senpai
oh thank you
i hope i didn't scare you no it's okay
you always like you always have
something refreshing and
i'm actually ashamed over how we don't
get the change to like talk that much
but hey we can change that
yeah let's change it soon
let's change it you know it's
[Music]
no problem
okay
[Applause]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
bye
okay i wish i had more time but
yeah bye okay guys we have to clean up
here i have to quickly show you
uh everything uh oh my god oh my god
okay
uh uh wait um
okay uh birthday merchandise let's go
[Music]
um
where do we start okay here uh
done
[Laughter]
this is already looking amazing
right okay we have some merchandise
coming
up but that's not the only thing there's
a bigger announcement even after the
merchandise so
please stay until the end and we're
doing karaoke for one hour afterwards as
well and probably receiving collins from
halloween
so okay uh speed run
i have double jam oh them okay
i have prepared uh this for a long time
and and i hope you will like it
first of all this is
what's inside yeah
let's take a closer look a beethoven's
happy street drawn by hook
and it looks so
dark and cool and strong
do you see that
oh my god it's like my fire my
my my sword is on fire and it's like the
the way that only one eye is peeking out
there really dope
yeah okay and then we have
from scotty a rubber mat is really
really big uh you can use it under your
keyboard and under your mouse
it's pretty big and i'm really excited
about this because i
i uh scotty is one of my favorite
artists
is
looking amazing yeah
i i prefer that over like a boob mouse
pad or so like a small one
i preferred uh this one because you can
really um show
a great illustration on it so i thought
yeah i wanna i wanna showcase scotty's
illustration
with this and then again kfba brandon
slippery
[Applause]
yo i told you i want you guys to have
something
that's like usable you know
something that you can use in your
everyday life or
somehow i don't know uh apron for
cooking slippery's for home
you can wear them while cooking if you
want to and they're really fluffy and
really soft
and and i designed them and uh there's a
in the apron there's a bag in the middle
and the design is like
uh you know it has a it's very inspired
on my
of of my of my original design
okay
yes if you buy the full set uh you get
an ic
card sticker what is that um so in japan
i
i when i lived in japan i used some kind
of sticker on top of my ic card my my my
travel card you know that you go pee
uh and you yeah you go into the the
trade and all that
so this should fit at pretty much
any kind of like card you could put it
on a credit card you can put it on
a on a whatever i i don't know any kind
of card you know
and i thought it was really useful you
can uh put your kfb employee number the
art and the design is by me hashtag
this however you only get uh if you buy
the full set you get this as an extra
for free
yeah full
birthday boys uh i i think you will like
this one it's very very special um
because it's a date at the zoo
yeah it ended up being really really
cute i think it's a situation voice
where i'm at the zoo
thank you guys for giving me the idea i
thought that was the perfect idea
yeah yeah so this is this is the full
thing and
uh wait
we got jago to show it to us i will
upload those on twitter as well
but okay see um i think this picture has
a bit too much contrast uh i don't think
it's that contrasty in real life the
tapestry
but uh here you can see the size and how
[\h__\h] dope it looks with the
with the you know lit up sword and all
that
going on
okay and then did you notice he's
wearing something
i you can kind of see but wait
first put your eyes on the on the
squatty
uh game game pad no
not gamepad the singing you know okay we
don't have time
[Music]
this is how he looks he looks really
handsome he really looks like an
employee oh my god it fits him so well
[Music]
thank you for taking time to work for me
and model for me
so i hope you will uh use this guys uh
it will be up in two minutes for a
purchase
but
that is not all
this is not all
um midnight
wait where is
[Laughter]
where is it
a new song called sparks
me and music video release in
3 hours from now
music video kokai and this time
the song is
created by none other than
kira do you know kira
kina is a vocaloid producer who has been
making some really dope vocaloid music
in
english and i felt like you know
doing a little collaboration because i
thought it was [\h__\h] perfect and
actually we've been working on this for
a while now and
um i don't know if you can see it from
this
thank you thank you you write my mind
beneath your sound that is what i
actually wanted
thank you i didn't know where i had it
the art is by naomi
this is where you make
ah okay my my thingy is gone
sorry this is so chaotic we're doing
karaoke after this we will be able to
calm down
but this is the cover i found video
let's go
and music video bye
so perfect combination of people i would
say
um i'm super excited this is very
different from the usual
music that i put out up until now
because it first of all it will be
english yahoo english song
first takana english song so this
is in every country where it's midnight
it will be
already released on spotify and
amazon music apple music etc
spotify
music video is coming out in three hours
so if you're in one of those countries
where midnight is still a long time to
go
then don't worry in three hours the
music video is gonna be out uh
my manager is probably updating the
description right now if she didn't
already do it
and and then you should be able to jump
to both the merchandise links and
uh oh wait i didn't put up this stream
at the
the music video reservation yet but uh
uh the
the the you know the the thing where all
the
links are usually you know oh my god i
am so
so stressed out uh yeah um this was a
really
uh special thing to me uh everything was
very goody guinea but
i think you guys will enjoy the song
this is the first ever english song and
and and i'm so excited to work with kira
because we have some things in common it
just always felt like a destiny that we
would work together
yeah because uh kena is uh from germany
so german speaking
and um i obviously speak german too my
first language is german
and he has this chicken as his avatar
like
that's his like persona a chicken
a chick a baby chick and that just feels
perfect
and our names are so similar so you know
i i feel like i had to
and i love kira's music um
hi elizabeth
and please please look forward to that
oh my god okay that was uh that was
really tight schedule
uh oh my god let me drink some water
okay i got that out beforehand before
the um
uh scheduled tweets i think so
should all be fine
please support my new song please please
please
thank you thank you everyone
um the stream is not ending we are now
doing karaoke and whole live english
members collins if they want to come
so okay
let's start first with um
vanessa please send me though the
mysterious
two videos oh and all the members of it
are in the show
is welcome to call in uh i'll put i'll
put this uh
put this yeah just leave it here okay
it's all good oh
okay wait
done i i have to receive
someone before the video
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
it was a good choice
there's no time so i didn't really want
to join because i didn't want to
push you back you needed to do your help
and i really wanted to see your
merchandise
i understand i was very very very uh
tight on schedule so
no problem thank you for coming
afterwards
and thank you very much for still having
me i got you a person just like everyone
else's nothing such but i hope you like
it
oh those look cool thank you
hey let me save
[Music]
nice oh yeah oh
i like the sparkly stuff on the edges
oh the problem is just i move so much
[Music]
right because we have yeah it can't be
peppa really yeah
he uh he likes making us bouncy and move
along
exactly
so uh would you do you want to tell me
i don't know your first impression of me
or something
oh when when you know i actually watch
it like before debut right so the first
thing that came up the man was
man this girl is so talented she can
speak so many languages
and she's probably a crackhead
i'm sorry please don't kill me
you did it again you called them you
said it again
uh that's very dangerous you're living a
really dangerous life here
for the people who don't know uh ollie
was introducing
our ax panel on the second day and she
called uh
all of us crackheads and i was just
thinking you are the crackhead only
but i mean no no one's no one's no one's
disagreeing with me right chad agrees
with me right
well if they have to choose between you
or me who's the bigger crackhead
let's ask them we can even do a poll
apparently oh wait oh yeah
we have not used the poll much okay who
who is a bigger crackhead
we're really doing now now don't try to
be funny kfb you know what the real
answer is so
okay let's see let's feel
everyone vote now don't break it
okay oh it's a close call it's a close
call
oh for now give it some time molly
you're in the lead right now
[Music]
i mean you're going to have the karaoke
and you're going to have another call
maybe they'll change their mind
yeah i'll keep it there for a little
while
thank you i leave phone calling in and
for the glasses i love them they're
really cool
i'm glad you loved them and thank you
for having me for letting me call you
they fit perfectly on my chicken
i'll be taking my leave then have a
wonderful birthday oh thank you
good luck with uh chess by the way
you knew thank you good luck with that
bye bye bye
okay okay okay okay so wow that was uh
though the last one here um
now um we're very busy
my name is
i'm gonna stay in that server in case
someone still wants to join from the
japan members but i think they probably
uh are thinking that it's already over
because i was announcing the merchandise
and so on
so probably yeah managers please send me
the videos
that you were talking about the two the
two videos
and i shall look at them on stream
manager son told me that besides the two
videos that we showed in the beginning
there's that there's more ah
ah i saw some premium
okay oh okay let's download this one
first it should be quick
there we go that was fast is there a yes
is there a copyright warning probably
not you would have told me
oh wait wait wait
mama
let me yo
is this the one that i already saw on on
twitter
wait
[Music]
i already listened to this
oh
[Music]
i will live
i'm just gonna do a small tv session oh
i've practiced the most and i don't want
to mess up your wonderful song here
you're so talented
thank you so much fun and you've come so
far
and it's been so fun to watch your
journey and be a tiny tiny part of it
i love you thank you
thank you mama if you guys don't know
um she will tell you she
coached me in the shadowverse tournament
um
and uh it turns out she was actually not
just my coach but
um oh wait oh there's my there's my
fingers
but she also uh was a whole life fan
from the beginning like a whole live
english fan she's she's been watching
she's been watching her live english
ever since we debuted
so yeah thank you for your support dying
kitchen
that was really cute i i told her that
we'll collab
sometime because she helped me with
shadows and we got along so well so i
want to collab
okay by the way i think we can close the
poll i think
a lot of you guys thought you were funny
and that's why you voted for kiana but
we all know it's ollie and
and and i guess the final result uh
shows that so thank you everyone for
voting
i'm closing that
so there's one more video
there's one more video
oh oh
is
let me oh my god oh my god
please please talk to me oh my god
there kiara it is shawn aston here actor
lord of rings
um takanashi
kiara at takanashi kiara
this is your you are a world class
v tuber and youtube
a sensation of compliment sensation
almost sounds like
it's an accident or that it's
inadvertent somehow
a sense say maybe not maybe sensation is
just like wow sensational
anyhow a force you kiara are a force
oh in the v tube youtube
space uh at least that's what the kfp
folks tell me
uh you're super fans and uh and they
also told me that it is your birthday
and i want to wish you a very happy
birthday oh
i have a birthday wish a greeting that i
do for people
um and it's it goes like this it's it's
my uh it's not quite shakespeare but
it's on my heart um kiara i wish for you
to live a long healthy happy life full
of joy
and wonder and magic and poetry
and excitement and adventure and wisdom
and fulfillment and i wish that all of
the good things there are to have in
this world be yours
because you deserve them so saith kfp
and who am i
to argue uh so
i don't think i should sing happy
birthday that wouldn't go well happy
birthday you know what i mean that
doesn't we're just gonna take it right
here from my heart
to you and remember what samus gamgee
says at the end of the two towers which
i've said a million times
uh but it never gets old because it's
just so powerful and that is there is
some good
left in this world and it's worth
fighting for
it's worth fighting for let's mess that
up how could i mess that up
there is some good left in this world mr
frodo
kiara uh and it's worth fighting for
you're the good in the world well we're
all the good in the world that's the big
secret
that's worth fighting for but because
it's your birthday let's focus on you
for a minute
happy birthday kiara much love always
anything else goofy to say uh
oh my god
oh my god oh my god
i'm sweating so much this is
insane what that what
what oh my god oh my god
remember remember caffeine when we
started watching
and the members only though but we
started watching lord of the rings and
then we watched the hobbit it was a long
journey and i just
i told you guys that my favorite is some
i love somebody's country i love him
i love him he's my favorite character
and and oh
that's so cool that's so cool
and i think oh my god i think this oh my
oh my god
oh sorry i felt super dizzy right now
my head just turned itself upside down
okay uh i need to drink some water oh my
god
oh my god oh my god
oh my god
okay um uh
i wish i could do this all a little bit
slower um
uh this is such a rush um but
let's do a whole live english collins
[Laughter]
oh man oh man
oh my god girls i am
i'm ready oh
oh my god i am in there if you want to
come
my i wow yeah
uh let's take a little break up i guess
hello how do you feel uh
dizzy and uh hot and stressed out
but i guess i'm feeling good you have it
i i saw you i saw you there the the
merchandise clock ticket
never stops ticking yeah
that one is really stressful but also
the because i had to do the song
announcement as well you have it
can we talk about how excited i am for
your song
yeah can i say i may have already gotten
a sneak peek so i might have already
known
my buddies i'm excited i'm seriously so
excited for this
i mean i was the one who sent you the
sneak peek yeah i know i know i
don't know if i should say yeah it's a
final
english song people have been waiting
for that what did you think of it yeah
ah instantly it was instant it's gonna
be an instant loop song
so yeah i'm excited to play it it's a
it's a summer banger for sure
it is yeah it's definitely a summer
break that's what i uh that's the vibes
i
had from it too someone said yeah yeah
yeah
yeah yeah so how are you how's your
birthday so far
have you had a good day yes um
it is going great i'm just super
overwhelmed with everything right now
but maybe in the in this second part of
the stream that will uh
calm down but oh my god yes uh
it's it's crazy i've waited uh so long
for
this day and and now it's here and uh
i don't know the past days have been
really stressful too because of
uh all kinds of things and uh i just
want to calm down
and enjoy this moment uh uh a bit in
in in slow motion um yeah uh
yeah well all the all the preparation
birthday preparations are so stressful
it's like all this
all the prep all the gathering of
everything all the making sure all the
timings work and then
you know it's all it's all you're good
now it's time for
chatting and karaoke and games yeah fun
right
yeah yeah
i asked the japanese members this but
what was your first impression of me
my first impression of you i really
liked your extroverted energy
and how you always always and you still
do this you always have conversation
going and
i find i'm really it's really it's the
word admirable
i don't know i really admire that aspect
about you is that you can you always
have
well you can always have a conversation
with with anybody and i really
appreciate that and you're always just
this beam of sunshine
it's like always always just
i was i yeah thank you
you are the collab queen as well
yeah i've been told so but i've been
slowing down a little bit i feel like
with collaborations but that was
definitely
uh a title that you could call me a
little
a little while ago i gotta step up my
game again and do more collabs again
we're doing one this week yeah is it
is tomorrow i think no no no no no no
it's a friday friday night
oh friday okay
we're doing our minecraft collaboration
to build a little monument of ikotoba
yeah i loved doing that with you it's
such a such a sweet song and
i feel like it doing that together with
you
it it became like something a really
special memory that i think we can
always look back
upon in the future yeah i love it
definitely
even more so when we when we uh put up a
statue of it in the minecraft server
yeah
we're to put it though i thought i was
thinking like close to
phoenix done because you were building
something there too
oh yeah we can put it there nice yeah
you you made like an
empty area there uh are you probably
using that for something else but we can
make
more empty areas let's shave all those
mountains
as if they're shaved ice cream that
sounds good
shaved ice me okay
well i will i will let the other members
happen and then
[Music]
collaboration with all the whole live
english members on my channel let's go
let's go all right i'll see you soon
nice good student um uh
that let's go i kind of got that from
gouda
because glass sometimes like when she
when she
says like says a word and and ends it
like
so longly i can't speak
and she's like oh no
you know what i mean i kind of got that
from her and i i can't stop using it
yeah um it's true isn't it
all right if someone
yeah did you sleep
no oh my god oh my god we're oh my god
i don't even understand you
i mean you're scheduled happy
[Music]
it's my birthday it's it's crazy
what the hell what a crazy day
it was it was so crazy for you too does
it feel so crazy
that's what yeah i'm so excited
for all your emotions wait sorry my
merge link is not working supposedly
blink is not working uh so i
it's time i told ourselves you probably
fixed it okay
where was that
[Laughter]
i'm i'm looking forward to cooking
chicken with your kfc apron
i liked the the last part of the
sentence but the first part was like
isn't it today also like like nothing in
there
exactly exactly everyone should
everyone should cook fried chicken in
honor of kiara's uh
birthday i i guess so yeah
yeah that is the reason why i chose this
date to begin with you know because if
i i as a phoenix i have lived so long
back in the day there were no birthdays
people didn't celebrate birthdays so
i didn't really have one and i forgot my
birthday but but but then i was like oh
my god i need a i need a birthday in
order to celebrate a birthday
in her life and then i was like okay
which date should i choose and then i
saw there's the national fried chicken
day let's go with that and there we go
here we have it
and we've come to this day
as expected oh kiara you
are you okay giant ball of happiness
i thought you were gonna say you're just
a giant giant chicken well good thank
god you didn't say that
i mean that too but um i was i was gonna
leave it out but i guess i guess you
uh you did this to yourself anyways
happy happy birthday i am so
so honored and happy that i could be
living in the same time as you are being
your geminate
i don't know i lost track of how old i
was but
um i'm glad that you know i got to meet
you
in this lifetime i guess and um
sorry my friend's really not working i'm
crying i'm crying
[Laughter]
it's okay don't worry about it it's okay
you'll probably be more awake during the
collaboration so we can
we can redo this whole thing if you want
i'll already do it when i when i finish
my gift for you
i'm looking forward to it thank you i
love you
nine thousand oh my god the way you said
i love you it felt like
i gave me a doki doki
all right yeah i
[Music]
be able to finish their sentences
oh my god she has to
sleep i think she sounded very very very
sleepy like she was in the middle of
going to bed or like falling asleep i
guess probably she was waiting for this
oh dear
hello kiara happy birthday
thank you thank you
so exciting you're i love the the apron
it looks so good on yago like
you look like a like a professional
model like it really like hug
hugged his curves yeah yeah he gives him
a nice
shape yeah he looks like an employee of
mine
he does i love that really cool yeah
nice work on it it looks it looks
awesome like the band with the shield on
it such a cool little detail
yeah because of my belt yeah i thought
like i kind of
you know i i i didn't
part of my merchandise unfortunately
there was no no
no t-shirts or or whatever but i was
like i gotta kind of
implement some something that it's
really you know
my design yeah yeah super cool
it's almost like a cosplay i didn't uh
yeah it was like a cosplay i could
totally see somebody doing like a kfb
employee cosplay like at a convention
yeah or like a chicken head yeah
i saw what you just sent me there yes um
yes i don't i'm not too good at drawing
but i made this for you you know how i
usually download stuff for you
this has the the stars as well
yeah okay maybe it's maybe it looks like
it
might be a cute like a mini hat or
something oh you wanted it to be a mini
hat
maybe oh no i like it i think i like it
big better
it's nice it fits well is this supposed
to be a reference to tiana
oh uh no but that that that works i mean
yeah that looks really cool i could
probably see that
because i was gonna make tiana wear
similar hats to that
there you go yeah something similar i'm
glad it works
[Laughter]
thank you oh man thank you so much what
was your first impression no takanashita
um i thought you were really over the
top but in a really good way
yeah over the top
back then you were more over the top
than i was i think
back then i was a bit more i've been
told i was a bit more timid and shy back
then
uh i guess so yeah i guess so
i have i have a pretty bad memory
but i guess when i say over top like i
think you're really outspoken and like
yeah like could have said especially
during recent stuff
i don't know i really admire that you're
able to uh tell people when they might
be wrong
oh oh thank thank you you too though
oh thank you thank you yeah i i
i like your your personality and your
how to say that in english yellow
flavor no but okay
your flavor okay the flavor of love
um flavor of my soul
nah i was actually gonna say something
like i can't find the word for it right
now but you
you you you i
can't find it it's something like you
were so hard working
and and so inspiring and old but
it's like i can't find the word right
now
okay you can tell me later you're
revolutionary you're
innovative something like that probably
ah there you go
cute i think you're really really hard
working too you do so much like holotalk
so many songs that you do and you stream
for so long even while you're in pain
[Laughter]
i'm actually yes uh always in pain yes
that's probably probably why i am the
phoenix yep
yeah that makes sense got a high pain
tolerance yeah yeah
that is true very true well
i'm it i'm looking forward to playing
jackpots of you tonight
yeah all right thank
[Music]
go kelly
hello kelly thank you for coming sorry
it turned out to be so late
duh oh no don't even worry about it my
dog
i was i was waiting to join you on this
glorious livestream celebrating your
birthday
are you are you are you doing fine kelly
oh i'm great i'm just a little insane
right now because i've slept for five
hours in the past three days but don't
even worry
i'm happy to be here to celebrate your
birthday with you
um and i want to say i'm like uh
i'm really really excited about the song
that you made um
because i listened to it and i instantly
was like oh
oh this is a banger people are gonna
love
love the [\h__\h] out of this thing
it's amazing thank you i'm really
excited to hear everyone's opinions on
it i think some people can already
listen to
it because it's already midnight in at
least in japan
so really curious yeah it's very
different from the usual
uh style because i was saying japanese
songs before that but
it's like different from your usual
style but but i think it's it's like in
a in a very good way that like
i don't know it just that kind of song
really fits your voice so i think um
i think uh it's everyone's gonna really
love it because i think it's
fantastic thank you oh
yeah what was your first impression of
me kelly i'm asking everyone
i mean from the beginning of time dude i
don't know i thought you were pretty
annoying
but over time you know you kind of grew
on me a little bit and once we joined
uh once we joined hololive english
together um
i don't know i guess i gotta say we
became a lot closer
um and i'm really glad that we did
because
you're a great friend i i'm really happy
that we became friends because when i
first met you i wasn't sure if like
if we could really be friends for
whatever reason because i'm very closed
off and shy and you know i'm kind of
like
the angel of darkness incarnate and
whatnot
um but but then once we met i was
surprised that we
we got along so well and i'm just really
glad we're friends and i hope you have
an amazing birthday
me too i'm i'm glad i wasn't in in the
same country as you in the beginning
of her whole life it was nice to have a
friend to be able to like
talk to about some of the bs that we had
to go through
but also enjoy the positive times too
you know
yeah we can hang out again oh don't
don't cry kusatori it's cool we'll hang
out again soon i promise
i wrote uh i i wrote a birthday rap for
you i'm going to cheer you up now and
make you not cry i wrote a rap for you
i made you a rap okay you want you want
to hear my rap
yeah all right first tell me if you can
hear this backing track okay
please don't please don't cry i'm gonna
cheer you with my rap okay can you hear
this backing track
hold on
no you hear it wow hi
discord i hate discord so much all right
well you know what everyone just uh
pretend that you hear
uh a beat in the background all right
here we go
this is called happy birthday acousatory
goes like yeah
okay here we go boom clap boom boom clap
boom clap boom boom clap ah kusatori
kusakusatori you and me go way way back
it's a long story
chicken chicken legs that run real fast
a pain in the ass from me but you're my
friend and i might always be your mori
kill you once kill you twice from the
ashes you will rise
no surprise and no lies there's a skull
inside your eyes life is dull
without you by my side you lied at my
world and it's not because i like you
you're a very special girl that's all
soaring high on your own [\h__\h] you own it
you don't need a throne in your zone
[\h__\h] you golden
kfp representing love in the chat
reddest presence
ain't it pleasant [\h__\h] these akkas are
fat chickens meant to be admired and
desired not consumed so before you send
this reaper to the usual room i want to
let you know the deeper i know you the
more you prove there ain't nothing in
the scene
this phoenix cannot do happy birthday
oh my god that was so long longer than i
expected oh my god that was wow
wow
anything for you my dude you're you're
my friend
i wish i had that lyric writing talent
that you have
i mean my birthday song to you obviously
had the best lyrics ever i
uh that was the greatest thing i've
maybe ever heard in my life
yeah no that i can't try my best i could
never
oh my god i could never write something
like that that is so
good how how long does that take you to
write
um i wrote it in the past 10 minutes
ah that's so fast damn oh my god
yeah how do you yeah are you just like
like a waterfall of words
i mean sometimes it just comes to me man
it did apparently it did
i remember you know when we were in the
hotel room and you really had to write
lyrics and
you were like constantly trying to write
letters but it seemed like it took you
days
back then because you were just maybe
not so inspiring
it depends on the subject if my if my
subject is very inspiring i write pretty
quickly
no then i say i am very i'm not your
wait what do you call someone inspiring
to someone who's
yeah well i always wanted to say medusa
but i guess that was nothing
are you my medusa
you are my muse it was very easy to
write about you
basically that's just because we had
such a
special special friendship up until now
with lots of lack of collaborations lots
of history
um so many things happen it is true
there is there is a lot to talk about
when it comes to you so
i hope you have a really wonderful
birthday you deserve it
and i can't wait to watch your karaoke
thank you actually
i i i i should have started like uh 40
minutes ago but i
i kind of wanted to take it easy with
you girls and just talk
slowly so i guess the stream is gonna be
a bit longer
a little bit a little bit i guess well
i'm still really looking forward
no but you should actually sleep because
we have a collaboration later
oh you're right actually yeah jk lol i'm
gonna catch
the archived karaoke a bit later
yeah i need to catch some z's please
sleep uh
see you in i don't know what six hours
or five
five something like that yeah something
like six hours or so yeah
i'll see you then good night five and a
half
good night happy birthday
[Music]
oh my god that was that was that rap was
on fire
damn that was really dope
wow inspiring i can't i really can't
write lyrics i need to
practice that i guess thank you everyone
for calling
in we are now finally at the part where
i will
sing for you okay
i will sing a few songs for you and then
that will be basically it but uh i just
wanna maybe
before we we kind of uh zoomed so fast
through it do we wanna look at the merge
again because i don't know i feel bad
for zooming for it so fast
so oh my god first of all i want to say
the hookah papa illustration to me was
so unexpected
because when he first sent me uh
the sketch kind of uh sketch version
it it seemed very happy and and bright
but and i think that was what he was
originally going for
but then in the end i got the final
version and i was so surprised i was so
shocked because
it it just blew me away it showed such a
different side of me again
somehow somewhere mentioned before that
i would love him to draw me
like in a cool black rock shooter ish
vibe
sometime and i don't know he must have
read my mind or something because
i mean look at it that's i feel like
it's it's uh
it gives me those vibes definitely let
me turn music back on
and then yeah the disappointment yeah
sorry it's been it's been a whole mess
all this time
[Music]
thank you so much he's so badass yeah so
badass and
the the b2 tapestry is something that
you must get i think
it looks so cool oh my god i can't wait
to put that on my wall
damn it's so dark what
what kind of history is hidden behind
this image
what it's beautiful and then for scotty
i don't know if you guys have noticed
but i'm a huge fan of scotty's art i
know
[Music]
i felt like i had to i had to
um ask scotty to draw something for me
for my birthday
and and i was like i i
i i didn't even decide yet what exactly
the item would be
um i just wanted him to draw something
really cool and then i was like whatever
you draw i'll put it on somewhere
on something and and it will be amazing
and then
i went for um this because uh
um i'll always see it in front of me
yeah it looks so cool and i asked for
like a
like after battle after battle situation
kind of
art and that's what you see here like in
the background it's like a
battleground where i just fought with
someone and you see some
feathers flying down too really cool and
my sword my sword looks so cool
actually there was a version that uh in
between version where
my legs were a little bit more spread
apart and you could obviously see my
panties and i was like scotty sang
please uh i don't think we can do that
please put my leg in front of my panties
[Music]
yep can i get the original for science
no
where do i buy that version now so for
this one
um i designed this one myself actually
for the slippers um i made some designs
but the the staff actually helped me a
little bit with the slippers
and that's why they look so good and
yeah i i wanted you guys to have
something that
is usable and you know because kfp
is all about kind of all about food and
cooking and all that
i felt like this would be a fun thing
and i wanted to make it a set
because uh i don't know if you're
wearing an apron why not
why not wear slippers as well
yeah aren't they cute they look so
fluffy
and uh as far as i know i think that
on on the sole on on like beneath on
under um where you know where on under
where you don't see it right now is uh
some some anti slippery
slippy thing uh those those those those
anti-slippy things
yeah you know what i mean so
they should be really easy to walk in
even if you have a slippery
uh
[Music]
thank you so much it has been scheduled
i am uh i have been so busy
and yeah and yeah and i hope you guys
like this one too i thought it would be
a really cute idea i wanted to give you
guys some kind of free
extra and when i was thinking of what
would be a
good free extra that doesn't you know
take up too much cost
and i was like this this should be a
good idea because
um um like here where i live now
um i don't have such a ic card but in
japan i always used to have an ic card
and even if you don't have an sd card or
something like that you can put it on
any kind of
card i think it should fit most most
kind of cards like bank cards or yeah
bus passes whatever
anything you can put it on there
and then and then and then and then you
can put on your employee number
yeah and i drew that little chibi a
while ago
yeah i wanted something on there
so i quickly uh tried to put something
cute
yeah and i tried my best i'm not good
with i mean totally
graphic design is my passion of course
but
um i was worried that it wouldn't look
good it
is probably not not the most
professional looking sticker but i hope
you will use it because my love
is is in there and i tried my best
um passion fashion
wait let me drink something oh man
oh my god okay i think the reason why
dad
that other track was um making me feel
so weird is because i had double audio
wait a second um
do you girl guys uh wanna go into canada
okay because i want to oh yeah
oh yeah the birthday voice i'll just
mention it again it's really cute it's
really really cute
it's really really cute please listen to
it it's really cute okay let's go
karaoke
because i've been spending too much time
uh for all this anyway already
and here i am
um i've been practicing some new songs
for you but we'll start it off with
uh my own songs uh hinotori and high
challenger and then we'll go into a few
covers that i
practiced for you guys that are really
exciting so
let's start this party
tell me if the audio is okay please
[Music]
was that maybe a bit too noisy
you good okay
[Music]
me
i will live to keep on
[Music]
hey
is
[Music]
of day i've been trying to find my
destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray if i go
wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please where i need to
[Applause]
go
[Music]
and in the next level i promise i will
find you
[Music]
gotta leave this somewhere here let's go
woohoo a little bit a little more louder
okay okay
for the next song it'll be a bit more a
tiny bit more louder
yeah that was hindering my first ever
original song
yeah you know he's still freaking on
fire every time
every time i listen to it it's just on
fire constantly
let's go to the next song immediately
next song
[Music]
second single
oh no yeah
stream high challenges
[Music]
wow
a
[Music]
foreign
m
[Music]
uh
is
[Music]
me
i need to tell you that i love you
through and through
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you
i love you kfc
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
wow
my second original single that means a
lot to me
and also to kfp i think
stream high challengers dreamer
challenger the never ending story of
streaming high challenger
thank you everyone and now from here on
we will be singing
covers that i um
i think almost all of them are seeing
for the first time maybe one or two i
think
for the second time
[Music]
during the guitar break normally i go
like i know that but i was actually
writing my manager a message because
i was multitasking asking her to do
something yeah
multitasking
okay okay let me prepare everything
for everything and sorry guys by the way
then that everything has been so
i don't know um so stressed
like i have been stressed out i feel
like i wanted this to be a little bit
more or less
stress stress stressful situation but it
is what it is
um but i
[Music]
did okay anyone in the chat who already
was able to listen to the music i think
like
uh in japan they could already do it i
know
[Music]
already listen to it and they like it
i don't have an order that i want to
sing this in but i guess how about this
one
and okay
i love this song and i love honey works
it's a surprise to me that i have never
sang it for you guys before
but here we go first time takanawa sings
fans with
a
[Music]
it
is
[Music]
maybe now
m
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
foreign
sorry for the retakes well
i really really love honey work songs
and i i don't know why i never sang this
before but finally we did it
i think that was uh that was good
yeah it's such a cute song actually when
i was practicing it i
i teared up a few times uh around the
end
when it says
it says um basically
even even though even those rude people
even the words that they say
also those are also kind of necessary
let's just get stronger
and it made me cry when i was singing
that oh my god
let's let's sing forever together let's
walk together forever
[Music]
all right all right all right all right
uh next song
is a candy tom yup song which
doesn't really um it's not even about my
age but it's about birthdays
and and she's thinking about becoming a
20 i mean i'm not becoming 20 but
i thought it was fitting because it was
kind of a birthday song
so i'll be singing that
if i find where was it
uh there you go okay
raise the music more was it too quiet
now
next song if it's like too loud or
too quiet let me know in dms thank you
oh that was too quiet
damn it sound check first
that's so quiet
[Music]
okay let's go
me
[Music]
it
is
[Music]
[Applause]
m
[Music]
you
a
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
foreign
i haven't heard a song from her in a
while but
she's really really cute i really like
her songs they're so much fun
i also like the koi
[Music]
i don't want to okay
next door
thank you everyone for staying by the
way for this karaoke part
i have a few more songs for you so
please stay until the end
actually you know what next song let's
do the funny one
i have a funny song for you you might
like it because i'm gonna sing in a low
[Music]
voice
like should i have the lyrics up
separately i think so
it's a pretty old song but it was
extremely popular right then
i don't know if any of you guys know it
i would be excited if you
if you knew it then you would probably
enjoy it
the the funniness of it
[Music]
yo
oh
[Music]
yo
oh
[Music]
hey
you
[Music]
i'm sweating i'm like i
ah did you guys know this song
i knew you guys would react like that
oh my god it's actually hard to sing for
me like that because
there's this part where it was like coin
oh
tattoo it's so screwy it's so so low i'm
sweating so much help me
[Music]
no you're making me nervous you stop
shut up dude
you're making me feel weird
thank you i'm glad you liked it everyone
yeah this is a really fun song though
you gotta
watch the music video of it it's really
really dope
okay i wanna sing
um okay next song
is also it is a song i've sang before
[Laughter]
you guys really liked it that much huh
okay
well next song is uh i got i gotta
put in some hello project here so bono
i've said this before but it's such a
fun song to sing
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
my
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
i
is
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
okay a little bit of my looks can i put
on cat ears and
you know what yes i can
make it
[Music]
m okay okay
next song next song
[Music]
yum
oh wait for that wait let me hide one
more time
a good idea
okay let's see if i can do that well
a little challenge
[Music]
wait oh we gotta start from the
beginning okay
[Music]
is
ah
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
m
is
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
what happened there i don't know either
either the
the lyrics so were um aligned
differently
or the gem was aligned differently
i am confused but it's okay
all right all right all right oh the
shower after this will be so much fun
let me put down my gun fingers
one second it's kono table
kakushima
okay that was the song that i sang
before i think but now the next
two songs which are also i think the
last
two songs are new
okay i practiced this oh bubba i hope
they will be good this one is
from k on you and i
really cute song
[Music]
is
my
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
i chose this song because it's about you
know
being thankful being grateful wanting to
be
together forever and all that and
cannot live without you i miss you if
you're not there and all that kind of
stuff
talking about jail cafe talking about
you down there you you
you yeah um
i have uh are you guys enjoying
yourselves
you guys excited um my original song if
you haven't heard it yet if you're one
of the unlucky ones who are not in that
time zone i mean i i'm also not in that
time zone
midnight is far away from me but don't
worry if my time is far away from you
in
one and a half hours the mv is being
released on my channel
the reservation is already up what
i'm so no reason excited about
what you guys are gonna think of it yeah
i heard it was amazing
wait wait where the hell did you hear it
huh illegal
i don't know
just wait for the envy and then once
it's released in your country on spotify
amazon music apple music itunes etc then
you can
get it there as well i would be very
grateful for everyone's support on this
song especially
for now and
ow happy exciting song
from edo manga sensei adrenaline
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
is
yay
that was fun
okay guys i want you to
not forget hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
okay i wanted you guys to not forget
about
the merchandise
it's uh the links should be working in
the description um
yeah there you go doesn't look beautiful
i'm i'm i i ha i've worked on this for a
long time
uh prepared it for a long time finally i
can show it to you i'm so excited that
finally finally finally there's kiana
birthday merchandise you know he's a bit
a bit rough to wait until the very end
because i was the last member of whole
of english to
have birthday which means i was the last
member to have my own merchandise out
there
but yata finally finally finally so
exciting
i hope you guys like it
um
i can't wait to receive those uh the one
from hokey pop
the one from scotty son i want those i
want them now
yeah um i'm sorry that it was kind of
scuffed here and there like me being
absolutely a mess a huge mess
um but later today there will be a
collaboration on my channel the
reservation is
already up there and we will we will be
playing uh
jackpots games uh i think i think i
chose number four
because i wanted to play that monster
dating game
sounds like fun so and this is the
thumbnail
uh i'll see you guys there and no
actually before that i'll see you at the
music video premiere oh yeah
yeah oh my god how exciting y'all be
i had to keep so quiet about the new
song
and it was pretty difficult to keep
quiet i mean i mean you i think you
could have expected i think it was
pretty obvious that i was going to bring
out a new song on my birthday how could
i miss that chance right
i mean i feel like that was to be
expected but i did keep very quiet about
it
i felt like it was um it was kind of
obvious that i would release the song
i mean i've released one for
thanksgiving and one for valentine's day
i could not
not release one on my birthday
and then
[Music]
all the five girls will come together on
my channel for some fun birthday party
because i felt like
i just wanna i just wanna have a little
party with them i just wanna be together
with my
gen mates and enjoy this time that we
have together
as five girls um because i love them
and they're very special to me and i
think this is the best way to celebrate
a birthday
not celebrating it alone here i think
birthday should be a party
yeah ever seen a scrapbook no what
scrapbook
what scrapbook is there something i
should see merely and react to on my
stream right now
how do i find it
read it
read it later read it
so read it read it son i'm coming to you
it don't wait that's not uh hold on i've
read it please not normal already who
cares about that
i only care about who i've read it
please thank you
what's going on do i need to make a post
oh yeah oh yeah read it
ah
wearing my merchandise is up there i'm
scrolling
terry duncan what's happening yo
where where where is the thing that you
guys are talking about
can't find it i'm scrolling
i'm seeing a lot of things
i read it i'm watching you don't think
i'm not watching you
you know i'm watching you always
watching you
could send it yeah send it to me
hello mama mama sent it to me thank you
mama for helping what is this
happy friendship book happy birthday
kiara have you ever returned to 200 plus
what kfc members have filled out pages
of a friendship book based out of your
description of your friendship books
from when you were small phoenix oh
and we've put them all up so you can see
them it's all posted on this website
oh my god i'm going to show you guys the
link what the hell that's so cute
what 200
200 friendship pages oh
oh
oh my god i like making what
oh my god that's so cute what is this
this this almost you know this is
you might want it you might you may be
saying this is like a friendship but to
me it looks like a
dating application
oh god
hello my dizzy things only thing i want
to say is always be happy positive and
awesome as you are now and remember that
all of us love you
happy birthday keep being yourself your
genuineness
is what makes yukiya and i love that
about you
oh german one i just got it
this is translated
you're a huge inspiration wait i circled
the earth
i am the sun huh what wait never mind um
no no no no shut up don't even so i hope
this
book shows you it it's broken
it's broken
the page is broken well i'm still on it
you can't get me off of it
saying it will come your hardships have
encouraged me to conquer my own and i
will always appreciate your support and
energy from behind the screen
when work family or life in general
against raffia streams are one of the
best ways to cheer me up i'm happy to
hear that
you always try your best to entertain
yourself your collab partners
and your audience and it really shows in
how much we at kfp support you we've
made a family
out of a wild bunch of people wild
chickens
i i domesticated my wild chickens that i
hope stick around as long as they can i
can't wait to see what you have planned
for us in the future
yeah those means so many messages
200 oh my god
wow thank you everyone
that is adorable wait
are these not loading i know that
they're slowly loading
wow yeah that's adorable i will i will
go for that and i will also go through
the
the happy birthday 2021 kiana birthday
2021 um uh up up here
though the slideshow is just a small
collection of it uh because
i only have that much time to save
pictures
really barely any time at all ever um
but yeah eh
sorry i've been so stressed out the past
days have been crazy like yesterday the
taste of a rice stream that
the chance of the livestream that that
in itself was
a birthday present for me and being able
to do a stream like that but it took me
hours and hours of preparation
um and then yeah before that what did i
do before that i was really
busy before that as well what did i even
do
and now i'm preparing for whole talk
next oh my god it just doesn't stop
aya ax yeah ax took up both both
full days as well um
more way more than expected so it's been
a busy couple of days that's why
i've been feeling so stressed out but i
want to thank everyone for being here
to support me especially on my birthday
um
you all mean so much to me and
if i wasn't so stressed out i would have
written you a letter
but but yeah um i i just hope that we
can
um go through many many many many many
more days together
and then and have fun times together
yeah
i wish to be there for you when you guys
need me
when you guys are down i want to be
there for you
and entertain you guys and just give you
content
and make the best memories ever i love
you all thank you for
choosing me uh and for supporting me
i'm so honored like i i know i'm not
perfect i have my flaws but you guys
still chose me
to support
[Music]
i will do my best i love my best and now
i'll take a [\h__\h] shower
and in one hour oh my god yeah yeah yeah
the song that was
also i've been preparing so much
the song is up next guys one hour of
music video release
is so hype i i i think the combination
of
me kira neon beat and urigoroma
is just edgy edgy teenager style
and i love it i love it you see you see
those those oppai
that neon beat draw drew the way naomi
draws my
[Applause]
i'm i'm glad i got to choose people uh
that i really really like and
i was i was um you know
the reason why i chose kita i told you
guys before
today in this stream because it just
kind of fits
it fits so well and because you guys
have been asking for
english song for a while to me honestly
the only the only choice
for me was kira because kira's style i
really like it i really dig it
and uh maybe maybe we can work more
often together from now on depending on
what you guys think of the song
if you like it then who knows there
might be more kira x kiara
collaborations yeah kira is amazing
yeah and it's such a talent because
kira is what 19 or something like that i
think
and has been making music for the past
years and holy [\h__\h] so
talented what crazy
really really talented respect
thank you for making a great song for me
okay okay i think that was uh long
enough uh
i was supposed to only do two hours
i'll be taking two days off after the
collaboration
uh i don't know when i will ever read
the super chats but they will be read at
some point and don't worry we have them
saved we have them back up
no one will be skipped no one will be
skipping the doodles
skateboarder
yeah okay i want to talk more of you
guys but we'll probably have
a 12-hour super chat reading stream
where we can talk about
everything slowly and very slowly i love
this my baloney art oh my god
you see that up there your face is
covered up by the stupid ceiling
decoration but look at it on twitter
i'll retweet it
okay and in german we say alfredo sin
thank you everyone for it for all the
love you give me
and the birthday presents the surprises
and everything and just being here
listening to me thank you so much
and all the art as well yummy thank you
thank you i'll do my best
from now on
what's going on
bye bye bye bye see you later
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you