[Music]
so
ah
[Music]
hello everybody
how's it going um
i
i'm currently alone
i don't know if um
um is
joining me
she said she would try to be there but
um she's currently not here maybe she'll
join later i don't know
um
yeah i know there's some other people
streaming right now
but first of all i have absolutely no
idea how to do anything before i started
i logged into the game once and i
ran around a little bit by the ocean
uh
destroying some stones
um
but now i log back in and i'm starting
the same way do you
get a new character every time
uh you log in
eh
is that what it is
was inventory again what is the key for
inventory there we go
wait
no that's there you go aha okay
okay
eh i died in my sleep
oh no i don't think i died wait do i
have my stuff
like what did i have before i had like
i had a lot of uh
yeah okay i still have this stuff see
this is what i was
this is what i was doing oh god it's
laggy
i should turn off v-sync
uh
i don't wanna
i'm scared to show anything that i
shouldn't be showing
it does in in rust
where is there anywhere where you could
accidentally show like the
uh
the ip the server ip
where would that be
if if you die when you're offline your
character will change uh-huh
i just showed it
no
no no no what do you mean you i just
showed no [\h__\h] way yeah i turned uh i
found the setting for sense censoring
i turned that off
uh let me let me turn some more things
off because i think
um
where's that b-sync
setting
it's probably good to turn that
paper on or off whatever it is currently
we're going to turn that around
avi sync is off
should i turn it on
ah
okay
off is better okay but it lacked so much
what the [\h__\h]
my my pc is a good pc okay but i guess
we're gonna um turn down the settings a
little bit
i don't know
uh i'm turning down some
quality things
motion blur off
okay motion player
motion player where's motion blur i see
it in graphics am i blind motion blur
[Music]
it's not in graphics
i'm a muted
i'm not here right now yeah i do have a
beef pc
also once again
five minutes after i was done airing my
room and it was nice and cool of course
it gets hot again
amazing so i'm turning on my um
[Music]
my fan once again see i'm still lagging
why am i still lagging
am i only at least the stream is not
lagging right
i should close this
let me close that
i think i think i've been scammed when i
bought this pc in japan
i was told this is a beef pc i think
it's a lie
it's all lies stream is okay good good
good good good
[Music]
wait what am i doing
ah
there you go
[Music]
no i mean now i'm fine i don't know at
what time do i lag
oh
i think it's
every time like even in the settings
and now i'm lagging again is it
oh i don't know
it shows that you're playing with 4k
with graphics card that's two
generations old ha what do you mean two
generations old
i bought the pc like
not even two years ago one one
one and a half years ago i don't know
you're breaking my heart here man
okay graphics what else can i lower than
water water
water hmm draw distance
let me let me show you
[Music]
resolution
it's normal
wow
that's junkers excuse
her game is like a decade old what day
you [\h__\h] go yes
it's older than my my pc
fps limit to 60.
sexy
apply
oh wait did these things apply
well ah they don't need to apply or do
they
let's say we lower this
i don't see it
grass quality all of this down down down
down down here down oh is this good
am i still lagging i don't know am i am
i meow where are we
i think now
oh
okay
okay no wait i'm scared again i don't
want to judge you from anything wrong
ah wait
ah [\h__\h] it's nighttime what the [\h__\h] i'm
scared
okay guys uh first of all since i'm
alone here after all you guys will have
to help me
and i will tell you i am
um man
[Music]
you can help me are you gonna help me
you're gonna help me play rest you know
i play rest
which i didn't even know you could play
the pc with a pc
oh wait go away
uh what was i saying oh yeah oh
wow beautiful sunrise
yeah i wanted to say that i
i know less
about the game
than i did about minecraft when i first
played minecraft
do you understand if you play if you saw
my first ever minecraft stream
you know i didn't know what i was doing
but this is even worse yeah first of all
i need food and i've been running around
this coast side and i couldn't find a
way to go up
so i don't know how to eat food but i
think i do know how to sprint there you
go
well maybe here maybe i can go up here
how how's the climbing skills huh
i need food can i get like an apple or
my mouth
oh i know i know about the map i'm like
somewhere [\h__\h] nowhere there's like
is there a supermarket here
oh
what is this
i can get stuff there wait mushrooms i
can eat mushrooms right is it e what was
it yeah it was eat okay so i eat this
you know
raw mushrooms even worse than none right
yeah what
what
what is it
i start streaming and you start meowing
like crazy she was sleeping before
okay how do i eat
how do i eat
the left and the right mouse button
doesn't work
ah wait i have to i have to select it
first
right
okay free
e
okay that helped um a little bit
good good i see some more mushrooms
what
she's trying to replace emma she's like
oh mommy might not be here but i'm here
for you mommy
my grandma what did you do
she went like wow
uh okay
i think i saw more mushrooms
it's cat and some more let's go
[Music]
always has been okay well me finding
food already solves a lot of problems
[Music]
she's meowing at the wall right now yeah
what's what did the wall do to you oh my
god so many mushrooms hi
excuse my kid
what is it
no baby
you're quiet now when i talk to you okay
oh so many mushrooms
eat
they sound so crunchy a raw mushroom is
really that crunchy
okay ghosts and maybe there's ghosts
oh oh oh what is that
we are uh we're looking at this stuff
now
is that something someone built now or
is it
yep
[Music]
[Laughter]
please answer my question is that
something someone built or um
is that like automatically
ah generated stopped when i it's does
she stop when i stop talking does she
just not want me to talk
[Laughter]
no no she keeps on meowing i don't think
that mike is picking it up though she
meowed a little bit
oh
pink is it gonna attack me is it a wild
boar
please don't kill me
how fast is it is there like a back view
i don't know how many footsteps i'm
hearing
just run round run no i hear it very
loud okay um please don't kill me please
don't look like wait what is that laser
oh it's it's gone the wild boar is gone
but what is that laser i don't think i
want to step into that i see that do you
guys see that probably not it's very
tiny
is it gonna kill me
please don't kill me
it's it it sensed me being there
this is a safe zone
what no
no
this is like minecraft first episode all
over again i just keep on running
uh
maybe i just wanted to sniff my scent
you know
okay okay
okay
save zone but uh pigs still can't attack
me or what
just like minecraft yeah
this doesn't look so safe but okay we're
going in here oh it's like
like a world after an apocalypse
there's someone there no that's just a
painting maybe
that's just a graffiti huh
oh wait there's people there what the
[\h__\h]
wait there's someone there too is this
npcs
oh i thought there was no one here
except whole life members
oh what do they do they won't kill me
right there's a shop there
what do i do anyway first of all like
what am i supposed to do
i know there's something called a
ct crafting table
or something like that there's a fire
here
survive make a home
gather materials okay
[Music]
um
although like even with the stones
i could
like pick up this specific stone after
throwing it but i couldn't
pick up any other stones that i was
looking at
how do i know what i can pick up
shop
hit three
ah hit a tree with the stone or what
got down some trees and hit some stone
okay i already did hit some a lot of
stone
look
i have a warm where did i get the worm
from
rain worm
cute but disgusting okay so we'll i'll
run out sorry hello hello
i'm i'm a newbie please be nice to me
please send no more
wild boars after me thank you
okay so any tree i can cut down this
tree
oh
plus 10 wood
nobody will be mad at me for cutting
down this tree
[Music]
hit the x what's the x oh ah oh yeah
okay also just like in the like with the
stone i saw like a sparkling
uh
sparkle dammit
what was that
hi
[Music]
i'm new here
run from one from what am i running
someone shot me okay i thought it was in
the same zone it says safe zone
was it mad because i i hit a tree in the
safe zone
was it a whole life member
they've done no damage it's another
hollow oh
maybe it is um
teasing me
see anyone
[Music]
if it was the npcs i did not lose any hp
oh okay
and that's [\h__\h] scary
whoever's bullying me you might want to
say hello
um
[Music]
who wants that
it's making me hell paranoid
i am at least in the en voice
channel
uh hoping that ami will join me
eventually
i wrote her you can join anytime
oh wait no pick it up oh that's big
stuff how can i whoa how can i carry all
that big stuff huh
my mic is off
uh
i did not
this doesn't show anything right
options oh see when i go in there it
lags
in game like audio
audio
where is um
voices for
speaker mode
i don't know how to turn that on there's
just
voices volume
i'll turn it up a little bit
controls aha
thank you
[Music]
is there no like auto i see on the on
the top left of my screen i see like my
my discord thingy lighting up though
auto transmit on
wait what voice transmit
yeah but now i
uh
push
it's supposed to talk is it always
supposed to talk i don't see auto
transmit am i blind it just says
communication voice transmit and then
enter like a key
[Music]
just use game yeah sure but um
mama mia
yeah i only see uh
here voice transmit
v
huh top of the controls ah up there
all the transmit aha okay okay
duck
okay
um am i transmitting yeah okay i'm
transmitting voice now bye
um
how big is the safe zone
i want to stay in the safe zone
toggle shuba
i'm gonna get some more wood
no don't
okay i thought left mouse does it not
work on any tree after all
i thought left mouse click was hit
what
yeah know i i see it says everything
i can't i think
did i unbind it
oh
i probably did when i accident
um primer i say it's nothing though okay
hi there you go thank you
okay is somebody gonna shoot me again
when i do this hopefully not
you can't just mindlessly
gather materials huh if you always have
to hit
the certain markings
thank you for the rest of the chat thank
you
you may not want to gather or attack
things near safety if you don't all go
after oh no yes the wrong key what can i
possibly do right now though
besides hitting a
a tree with a stone
i'm fine
[Music]
i think as long as i don't have a weapon
with better weapons you don't need to
hit x ah
i see oh
i found the train
wow okay is that enough wood to do
something
what are we gonna do though
i have no plan where do you know do you
guys know where like
the young girls live
can i like go there and um
um you know
make my base there
e10
they're scattered ammo is at
07.
oh 7 e10
wha who is that 810
i was
oh 07 oh seven
all the way up there it is so far away
eat ten not eaten
eaten is a trap
uh-huh
funny
i see
what's in shop highlight on the map i i
rc what does i i see mean again
i'll follow this road country world
take
me to my home that i don't have
what was that
the music changed to danger
oh who was that npc i'm sorry i'm sorry
according to the game
so is really somebody trolling me i know
that like muna is
playing right now
maybe it's moona
hey
wait that's so [\h__\h] scary please
don't
you give me oh it's happy music again
it's giving me a [\h__\h] heart attack
i'm just carrying this beautiful stone
to its
home i want to return it to its owner
oh this path is nice where's this lead
where am i there
oh at least over here
there's a shop there too
yeah maybe i should go more towards the
middle though apparently
more people are i guess up there
[Music]
i need to eat and i'm fine
probably
but i don't i'm scared if i'm not in the
safe zone
[Music]
i have no purpose right now either
so
besides
a random ass animals
uh
and
players who just want to [\h__\h] with you
is there any other danger like uh
you know enemies
like in
my craft
there are hostile npcs too oh okay
are there a lot of them
what
okay thank you son of binky
um bandits attack helicopters avoid all
helicopters
[Laughter]
yeah
helicopters helicopters
helicopters
elite cultures
let's go in here
oh there's animals
but this one won't attack me right
that's that's a friendly animal hi
you're running in slow motion how do you
do that that's pretty sick
impressive there's snow over there
hostile npc's helicopters wildlife pick
whatever
dangerous interest wow you summed it up
so nicely i i think
even though i don't know the game well
or at all i believe what you're saying
you get some
i don't know what else to do
i need ammo
green plants can be picked
oh
there's a lot of green plants what do
you mean oh you mean those trees over
there those tiny baby trees
that look like uh soon to be christmas
trees
where's the eggs
funny playing games with me
huh
hit the barrels no that looks like it's
gonna blow up in my face if i do that
i'm seven percent wet no i'm eight
percent wet excuse me
what
it has loot oh okay barrels are the same
okay taro barrel
reminds me of
uh when we played atelier
they have a thing for barrels in that
game
every time you look at a barrel the
character goes arizer goes like taro
[Music]
sturdy is this [\h__\h] tree
oh oh there we go okay
okay so i hit this thing
i put look at the sun
you
sure
oh
binoculars cool
scrap i've heard about those you need
those to keep your
your home
intact
so i the few things that i know about
rust
is that
ooh hemp fibers is that if you leave the
game your home will disappear if you
don't put a lot of materials into it
uh-huh and one more thing i know from
recent tweets at uh
whole live members
or gambling no scraps are for gambling
okay then i guess i if you have a if you
have a a tree house
then you need three to keep it intact i
guess that's that's how it is
okay and the other thing i know is that
if you have a horse if you keep it
indoors it's gonna die
oh metal blade cool stuff
can you find like rare super special
items like this
i want to find something special
the scrap is for upgrade now for
gambling oh people are trying to teach
me
wrong things huh
what do we have here can i pick this up
no
how do i go up oh
maybe there's something cool here
can i have the rope
what no
okay i give up
can i can i open this
no
you cannot gather anything here thanks
a lot
for telling me that
horse needs food that's all
mushrooms let's go
i need food again soon so that's uh
really helpful thank you soon
maybe this game will make me accept the
existence of mushrooms
and start eating them i'm not in the
same zone anymore
but nobody's gonna at least no whole
life member would be so cruel to
suddenly kill me when i just looked
really started the game right i'm very
cold we're heavier clothing or light a
campfire
ah
no i'm just gonna go where it's warm i
guess if that's possible
um
so maybe do i have enough materials you
think for building
oh wait when
for building a
like something
starting a
blueberries
not even close oh
okay so can i i can make a bed and a
shed can i
okay
wait oh oh wait how do you use that
huh
right click
oh
maybe now i can see when somebody
attacks me
from afar
tries to tease me okay
yummy
no huh
and i thought three was to eat
i can't eat with number three anymore
oh it's big oh okay it's
this would be free this would be for aha
okay i thought it was just
set to that
ame
has
appeared it seems she just logged into
the game
i think she's coming to
help me now hey
she's logging in
let me see can i uh
show
you
[Music]
okay if she shows up i think i in the
voice chat i think i would see oh
although i guess she probably won't be
using discord huh
maybe not
okay so far at least i'm i'm keeping
myself alive
hello
how will i'm and know where i am i'm a
i'm if you're watching the stream right
now i am in
uh g13 yeah i'm in g13
i can't wait to um i don't know where
she is
also if anything she's probably really
far away maybe she has a horse and can
come faster to me then i can come to her
good water what is this
materials
is it when i when you sprint does your
hunger and all that go down faster
michelle
yoshu
you sure
you wish
your
oh scraps
take
metal blades nice
yes
that's it
no horse for amino ammo has no horse
what
unbelievable
i'm a bit disappointed tana
oh what is this huge wooden sign cool
you can like write stuff on the right
and scraps
nice do these things like respawn also
what is this okay no i'm gonna ask that
when i'm is here
i'm gonna keep my
all my random ass questions for when i
miss you
[Music]
a sign
a respawn okay cool
what is that
sign
with
oh a road sign wow
mystical mythical
no that's actually korean it's uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i can break
korean now you can't fool me
whoa was that
i was gonna try to hit it but then i
[\h__\h] remembered is that
is that
what
wait i'm on the whole server right that
looks like a randall
what is that
is that for me
but who are you
you're a man
you have streamer mode oh yeah someone
said turn on the stream so is that ahmed
check them out well i'm turning well
i'll turn turn i'll turn stream mode
often wait wait wait i'mma wait
does she even hear me uh
stream
okay i'll turn it off then ah
theresa
wait ah
she was screaming again there you go
theresa
ah where'd she go
what
mommy
was that all the help you're giving me
[Laughter]
mommy
mom
she's [\h__\h] gone
what
i'm so confused
um who could that be that was a game
myrrh name no
berries
theresa
npcs have more like npc-ish names right
honey
theresa isn't real
a manifestation of my
dreams my hopes and dreams
that was no npc yeah it didn't really
look like an npc
is that what amma's avatar looks like
kind of sad that there's no avatar um
[Music]
uh customization
i'm sad about that
okay i don't think she's gone what the
[\h__\h] maybe that was not amen maybe that
was just a another whole member who felt
like oh she's struggling i'm gonna help
her a little bit not too much just a
little bit just a little bit
zeta is also online
maybe i should have just used the chat
and asked who are you but i read the
rules for the holo server
that they set up
and it said something about i don't know
if i misunderstood but it said something
about don't use the chat
use the voice chat
eh and i'm like yeah
don't use the chat why
not spam or so
yeah i saw other members using the chat
so i'm confused oh god why is boris
coming back is it coming at me
no no not yet it didn't see me yet they
didn't see me yet
uh
i'm
i'm gonna um
i'm gonna try to go towards ahmed if oh
wait there's a helicopter
oh [\h__\h] you guys said to stay away from
that right
uh
is coming right at me it's coming to my
to where i am
it's okay if i just hide somewhere right
it won't see me if i'm like here for
example
what is this
wow
[Music]
i feel like if i go down there there's
gonna be some dead bodies down there
danger don't go in there oh
okay now now that you say that i feel
like that's scary
helicopter
uh
wait how do i use it again
[Music]
it's as if it knows i'm here
are they searching for me
they're circling
the safe zone but it's a safe zone right
hey
mommy
are you gonna land
what the [\h__\h]
when are they gonna go
safe
stay hidden okay
it won't attack me okay
um
certain places as its perhaps you are
safe okay okay
uh
try crafting okay
um
uh i can make an arrow
two different kinds of arrows
i can make shop front
wooden window bars
burlap gloves gloves bone helmet wooden
wood armor helmet bone auburn what can i
really make that
no i can't
it's just the recipes i know but
wait uh
how did can it like show me what i
actually wait this one i can make
it says i have 20 and it needs 20.
i can make pants
spare for protection a weapon would be
good
wooden spare okay let's craft this
i have more than enough
crafting
oh it takes 30 seconds
what am i doing in the meantime also is
it gone it's leaving yay
make a sleeping bag okay
sleeping bag
i'm missing ten club was was what was
club i don't remember even picking up
glove
cloth
it's so dark
no weapon if you hold
even if i just hold the weapon
what the [\h__\h]
the hemp glance okay then we gotta go
look for more
uh
uh i forgot uh
someone's coming oh man
no that's a one more
you can't see me you can't see me
you can't see me
everything's terrifying right now in the
beginning
of a game
okay
i ate my food
ah hold torch okay
how do i light it
okay let's go does this not count as a
weapon
i feel like it should
well okay i'll take it
is this hemp
no it's blueberry okay
um
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry i'm not trying to hit
anyone
[Music]
wet and too cold
i'm not this is okay right it's okay
scrap
okay
you can see my store in the okay i think
she wants me to come to her
because she doesn't have a horse g
what's 07 oh
it's so far
can i mark it
uh oh seven
can i mark like
okay will it now show me ah there we go
okay
well let's see if i'll survive this
this is hard mode right now when is that
it's scary in the dark
uh
like suddenly something's gonna surprise
me and kill me
let's run
now i still wonder who the hell that
person was
that mysterious person it didn't have a
name that makes any sense like
for me
will i die because i'm too cold
i hope not
it was probably good huh
are you sure
i will
i die with my help okay okay no no then
we're fine for now
oh we're fine we're fine
uh going this way going this way how far
have i gotten okay
yes
i can make it it'll take a little little
bit
good lips close by oh
oh
car
amp hemp
hemp hemp would be good
while i'm on the run
i don't see any i don't have the eye for
it yet
it will come to me probably is this hemp
no
[Laughter]
um
i don't know what it looks like oh
there's a lot of animals there hi
you're gonna run away from me right now
run at me and kill me yeah okay good
this is him
i think
no it's white berries what a white
berries this is hemp this help yeah
okay
any other hemp
singing
enough for bed oh okay okay okay okay
for you in a sleeping sleeping bag right
uh here just this one
craft
wow
and i have everything i need to sleep
over at ama's home forever
what is this oh
can i hit this thing too
no
doesn't seem so
i want to name my stone
sleeping bag is respawn point
i want to name my stone what are we
gonna name the stone
theresa how about theresa i'm gonna name
it theresa because you know
that person was like a fata morgana it's
like
ah
and you must imagine this this character
i'm playing she's running around in the
wild naked
you can assume she's going crazy already
at this point or she was born crazy
so she will name
her pet rock
after
that one
mysterious
person that she saw at some point
i would say that makes a lot of sense i
can see that storyline in my head so
clearly
like wilson
wilson
where's wilson
theresa is wilson what
what are you guys talking about
wilson
from castaway
oh well why is there a teresa in that
movie
oh
the one with tom i don't think i watch
that
can i oh i can open this
uh
huh
what was that
a shelf
when i get a shelf but now how do i open
are they
he's not it
or is this
oh no this is the loot is this what's
inside
ah
what
put this
here
i needed to get a shelf no idea
[Laughter]
no idea
cool i got some loot yay
maybe uh
maybe we can
give this to ahmed to ask her to let me
stay at her place
like you know a little offering a peace
offering
am i still going the right way yeah
roughly
i figured saw me holy [\h__\h] good eyes
oh
it's in the only path that leads that
way
is it coming no
am i good oh it is coming very slowly
but it's uh i see it
okay i'll go this way
run yes okay
i quit my i'm not gonna try to fight now
oh it it's pretty fast even though it
looks like it's just you know chilling
um please [\h__\h]
i don't want to die
i don't wanna
run die
run
run run run is it never gonna give up
i don't see it anymore
maybe we're safe
wow
wow pretty it's like minecraft with
shaders
with some really realistic shaders
don't
no
you don't want to be my stone it's okay
i have teresa
he's never gonna turn around no i'm not
gonna turn around
never gonna give me up
they're gonna
tear me apart
never gonna rip up my limbs and eat them
yeah
wood oh i can take that whole chunk cool
100.
i have a lot of stuff now
uh
oh we're getting we're getting closer
we're halfway there
oh
there is a [\h__\h] bear
please don't kill me now i just started
the [\h__\h] game i hear a helicopter
[Music]
so far away and i still hear it as if
it's so close by okay
we call we we chill
let me cool
there was a sleeping bag what do you
mean
it only attacks if i have a weapon
really
it looked like it was charging at me
does it mean something when the there's
a horse
um
does it mean something when the music
gets uh dangerous sounding
oh it's coming at me
right let's see if i'm like hidden in
the trees
oh my god oh my god
how does it go
[Music]
yeah it will
oh no we're good we're good i'm like
it's going the other way okay okay
it's going the other way
okay that's your boy
thank you
it's a long way to ahmed man
what is this
this is someone's base that looks like
self-made
it's a nice place to sleep for
an animal maybe shop oh no it's a shop
it's someone's home
hello who is this
a dead body
that i can loot it's a not a whole life
member
don't look okay yeah she's listening
[Laughter]
i heard a voice
yes are you here to save me did you kill
the person that was trying to kill me or
was that you
so [\h__\h] terrifying this game
i'm in
maybe my microphone doesn't work i mean
i know it lights up but i don't know
um
it hurt her
oh man
let's just
i'll just go towards somebody's home
yay
oh nice
i think i saw this place in
um protocol stream just like a moment
ago
we're gonna go
uh
six
five okay
gambling place
oh oh
bear
you guys said it won't attack me
it's bathing oh they're so cute
that is pretty cute
um i'm like stalking someone taking a
bath but it's a it's a bear it's okay
why am i lagging so much holy [\h__\h]
am i lying like this the whole time
i'm peeping
dangerous there
oh my fps yes
not the whole time
where'd you go
emma
where did you go
i heard you
what
oh there we go
and my house
safe
safe zone
oh hello what is this this is ammon
ah i guess it's an npc
okay well it looks like an npc oh my god
this is scary
um
sorry sorry guys
just uh passing through you have a cool
base i'll give you that looks pretty
cool nice nice area you chose
don't take that weapon don't worry i
don't have a weapon although you could
consider literally everything a weapon
okay i'm almost there
oh seven
almost there
is that it oh
but there's a japanese written on it
oh my god did you shoot me
did you try to shoot me just do you hear
me no i was just i'm just trying to see
if you were you know paying attention
you lose [\h__\h] no don't do that sorry
sorry gives me a heart attack
hi
you do you know who theresa is
uh no i think there's quite a delay in
the voice chat
wait
no no
say i say a you say b a
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's like a five second delay
i i did see i have an insane ping like
play yeah
yeah
[Music]
is that normal
can we just talk in discord for you oh
thank you
oh
chocolate thank you
this this is the rust experience oh
really
shitty pingo my ping was like over two
hundred
wake up come on okay awkward silence
um
well do you do you share your home with
someone yeah i think oh
this is mikko senpai's house the thing
yeah there's a lot of japanese working
on it
okay i'll follow
could be a wall for kills i'm starving
oh
ah ah i can eat the chocolate
well it gives a lot of health back
was you're so fast was she so fast
why you're hacking fast mate
i'm here
oh
you're inducted yeah you gotta press
shift
i'm pressing shift
okay this is uh this is my house here
are you missing a horse
says please return like five of them oh
and son over there's mummy's house and
then past that there's some other
people's houses
across over there on the cliff is
rookie senpai's house
is that a fookie somebody's house
that's that's i'm i'm a number one
wow
oh
okay i need to build a base right yeah i
guess so i want to know how
i have some materials
i have um
you know that blueprint thing you're
holding in your hand
i'm holding a blueprint in my hand
[Music]
i'm holding
i'm holding binoculars in my hand
[Music]
can we talk on discord
okay let me let me give you a tour oh
okay
oh wow nice bear rug mom
nice
my stove my new telephone i heard i
heard about telephones make a call
nice stairs
yeah fancy right oh
[Music]
oh blueprint stuff see i don't have that
is that what you need to build stuff
i saw you holding a blueprint in your
hand yeah
i don't know anything about that
you say my mic do you hear me properly
because they say my microphone is not um
activating properly
yeah uh i think it's using like some
other type of microphone interesting
there's a helicopter
is there a setting like that i didn't
see a setting for the microphone in the
game settings
it's probably like the default steam mic
or
like your default windows microphone oh
oh
i'm gonna go plant something
what's right
oh cool she got some crops
ooh blueberries corn corn i love corn
corn is the best mmm i wanna have some
corn too is that a grill
you're gonna build a house right yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i guess
where where do you want to build
um next door
next next doors
oh how close
um
five centimeters apart i gotta hide the
helicopter is coming okay
yeah bye
well then let's hide
yes
hi
[Music]
want it done
yeah why not
i'll i'll take i'll take anything i can
get helicopter passes
how about a grenade
um
sure i don't even know how to handle a
sword right now but
yeah
oh do you have one a sword
uh no i have um i have a i have a spare
oh
where's my spare
inventory
spare
you you were not the one who gave me a
pickaxe an axe right like uh like 20
minutes ago
oops don't lose it hey oh sorry this was
my accident
uh no it wasn't me oh okay
i just saw the blueprint in your hand
don't you
is that just when i go into the
inventory
and it automatically
shows i'm holding a blueprint
i guess
i can i can build uh
some wooden signs in the storage box and
a hitch and fruit and a campfire
oh wait i can build wooden double door
wooden door
yeah i can build dock and build some
stuff what brett
yes
huh
oh blueprint okay
this communication
is uh
awkward blueprint uh-huh i uh it's
locked no wait i don't have that
but
oh just ex
delete the blue
oh she's watching
and it was there in construction it's in
the tab
oh this thing building plan
crafting that's the blueprint
i'm crafting
[Laughter]
what is your goal in rus kiara do you
want to get some kills you want a cool
base uh
my goal is
having played the game once and getting
my money's worth
wait
i think you're like building a base i
mean do you know why i'm lagging so much
when my avatar is like i mean i mean my
my left is lagging so much
no it sounds like an internet issue hey
internet
what you did
okay let me check my mic settings
actually in one second
[Music]
where is uh
maybe steam settings
[Music]
uh
where are
the microphone settings in steam chat
do you know
now it's better i tapped out of
something maybe it's like something like
that
yeah i tapped out of the game
uh
windows settings windows settings
friends list window
lets you go into options friends list
friends
friends list
i'm in the friends list and then options
voice
uh chat mic there we go
okay
[Music]
input volume
uh
[Music]
okay should be fine
i mean do you hear me wait i it doesn't
look bad it doesn't [\h__\h] activate in
game
i said the right thing though in steam
oh
you have to restart or so
[Music]
yo but that takes like so long yeah just
use discord i'm saying that's what i'm
saying can we just use discord for today
just
i'm not gonna shoot you it's okay
she's gonna look at you
what was that was that a no
[Music]
this sounds awkward though
okay okay
all right fine
yeah
[Music]
and i'll turn this [\h__\h] off
uh
where is this
controls
there we go
hallelujah
[Music]
i know people don't use this code and
rust but whatever
it's
better in this case
believe me
is she coming
[Music]
oh amazing i'm in
i'm it oh there she oh she's oh wait i
can't hear you
what it
did
let me see
um
say something
yes yes okay now i can hear you hi
hello yeah discord is using your other
microphone too for a little bit
really what other microphones
i've got nothing connected interesting
what could that be
well
uh okay let's um build something yeah uh
i have this blueprint now
not in my house not by my house well you
could do it kind of close yeah yeah
oh wait wait where did you go i don't
know i'm downstairs
oh
i want to
go outside thank you
okay i i won't be too close to that i'll
go um
i don't know where uh
can i have a ocean view
i think all the properties
oh if you go further down along the
cliff you could probably put a house
oh are these all self-made houses or did
they reuse something that was already
there
uh no they're all self-made there was
nothing here before they put it down aha
okay cool
uh i mean can you explain this whole
thing about seasons to me
oh so i guess in rust
uh actually i don't really know myself
but i think yeah it just runs for a
little bit and then they reset the
server so everything that you build gets
reset but before the reset happens
then everybody goes like a you know
all-out battle and stuff oh this is a
nice area right here
hey i want to be here this is like i
feel like i want to sing the sound of
music when i'm here
i'm going to build right next to that
house we're alive to the sound of music
wait whose house is that
oh it's super senpai's house really
okay
yeah
no wait i think that's noida's emperor's
house
oh there's a lot of people
i mean judging by
the sign i could be wrong
yeah yeah that should be noisy well uh
uh i'm sure she doesn't mind do you
think she minds
uh well oh there's luna senpai's house
oh
nice sea
okay well horse is here maybe she's
online
oh
yeah i'll build what about this little
pocket down here my house will probably
disappear anyway because i uh probably
won't play
you can you can put enough materials so
that it doesn't disappear for like five
days but oh okay i thought you had to do
it like every day
no you don't do it every day
ah okay well uh uh why why this i think
the one up up up there is better
okay it has a better
better ground to build on i would say
okay
uh
so
i made a blueprint now
what what does do i do you can use this
for crafting right click when i cook for
more options
huh uh-huh so put it in your hot bar and
then when you're holding it you right
click where's my heart on there
okay
all right click oh
oh
whoa
so you wanna yeah you put the foundation
for the house first and then you can put
walls and doorways and doors and then
furniture and a roof
so what you're putting down is gonna be
like the floor pretty much
uh-huh oh
i see
i feel like you like this part building
i liked it
we'll stay i mean what i don't really
like is pvp to be honest
so
well there is pvp but you don't have to
like um
i think if you're if you're not uh
holding a weapon and
you get shot like you're not supposed to
shoot people that aren't uh armed oh
okay
okay now can i build oh oh
how do i build the wall
oh
i placed that and why is it red i
thought i have enough materials building
blocked
is it me here it works
one wall
you're only gonna make it like a one by
two
for now
like what what can i even
put inside for now nothing i'll just
make it bigger eventually if i hope i
need more space where are you gonna put
the door you're gonna put it here
because it's a different type of wall
okay
okay i'll put the i'll put that there uh
doorway um but i can't for some reason i
can't build there oh somebody's here oh
[Music]
oh i can't she won't hear me because i'm
it
no i don't think she hears me now
sorry my mic is not
working right now i think
sorry my mind is not working right now
oh it's a steam problem i have no spray
i'm using this one take your steam
hey yo
where's your house
is it far away far away oh my
my house is around
uh
oh wait i thought i turned it off
[Music]
i'm sorry
works like this by the junkyard yeah but
she won't hear me properly anyway oh
yeah you can hear it in game is it yeah
yeah but my microphone cuts off all the
time so
yeah it just yeah it's using a different
microphone and game
your microphone looks so so so
fire somehow it oh it
sounds you have your vr connected it
might be using your vr oh
no oh i know what it is it's a ps5
controller
[Music]
[Applause]
it was the ps5 controller
nice yara's building her house yeah yeah
but it won't place on this side
this side it doesn't place it here
you have to it can help if you're
further away sorry keep talking and rest
what
oh that one
and well
i have to pick
i i
built from inside okay bye bye
[Music]
this one this side works but this one
and this side doesn't work
these two sides but this one looks
that's saying that this little stone's
in the way
oh you can get rid of it
no i can't i can't
can i move my stuff
my base
you can uh while you're while you're
looking at it hold e oh no i think you
need the hammer for that yeah uh try to
craft a hammer if you see one and you're
oh wait i think i might have an extra
one
what is that someone's shooting
should probably minus empire fighting
something
oh
cuckooy
very cool
okay then i think i guess i'm not in
danger
no okay uh what was it
a
doorway this is this a doorway
oh there we go okay let's just build but
i guess
hammer
what did i get a hammer from the
mysterious teresa no i got a a pickaxe
and an axe i need uh
what the [\h__\h] what are these things
you know what i'll eat
i'll eat one of the things
extra hammer i'll give it to you oh
thank you
oh it's turning nighttime maybe i can
get to use my in my sleeping bag for the
first time
oh yeah so the sleeping bag pretty much
what it is it's like a minecraft bed
except obviously you can't sleep through
the night in this game oh
so
it's just it just acts as like a respawn
point for when you die
oh okay wait wait i don't see it in my
inventory oh there it is
so i have to still wait for the whole
two minutes or what like of the night
time
it's two minutes
now i read in the
um instructions for beginners uh for our
server that our night time lasts two
minutes
oh yeah uh you have to wait even though
it's dark oh
okay uh oh hammer
okay so i put the hammer and click hold
e and there should be
uh something that says demolish maybe
i think or right click hold right click
or something on it
i haven't done it in a while will i use
materials by doing this
oh i'm not sure chat
that will know already
i'm going to get a flashlight
actually i have a torch
upgrade upgrade upgrade upgrade
right click
but it just says upgrade oh
oh
i guess you can't demolish it for some
reason
hold e hold e i'm holding e
nothing happened
timer expired it's already permanent
what the [\h__\h] oh you need a tool
cupboard all right go into your invent
or your crafting and make one okay
tool you want to place it right here in
this corner probably okay
the tool cupboard is where you place all
your resources so that your house
doesn't decay over time
so it has a bunch of inventory slots and
you just fill it with some wood
and your house will stay
alive for like five days if you put
enough
okay
um
i also have some i i've got some
furniture somewhere
i got this oh that's huge
wow yeah the shelf utah is really big
whoa you probably have to you can still
expand your house if you want
obviously the bigger it is the more
resources you need in the tool cupboard
for it to stay up longer
okay i'm gonna put down
uh
put down the two cupboards
well
open
audrey you still need to do something
with it let me see
it doesn't work
uh
what i mean too close to noah's house
too close for comfort of what do you
mean chat
oh yeah so there's like a radius that
people have and stuff
radius like uh just like a like a social
anxiety kind of thing or
or like an actual game function
they're saying you can't build because
it's too close so pretty much like when
somebody has their own territory and
their tool covered down you can't like
build in their area like you're not
authorized to build in their area
but i was able to build some stuff
yeah i don't know
you should be able to put something on
the foundation i don't know why i
wouldn't let you
oh
okay okay okay that makes that makes
sense in theory
but um
what so what what do i do how is the two
cupboard supposed to help now
uh so apparently you needed it to
destroy some stuff with the hammer so if
you bring out the hammer and hold e i
right click i don't remember which one
oh yeah demolish there's demolish option
now
slowly and automatically dismantle this
block
uh
okay then i guess we're getting rid of
everything
wait what
is it
that's how it works okay oh thank you
demolish
uh what
it doesn't work anymore
uh sometimes like there's like a timer
oh and it
yeah then you can't destroy and you have
to destroy it by hand with like a tool
oh oh
oh i'm starving
to have some food i have some berries
one berry
i mean i mean do you have some food
okay i'll bring some back yay thank you
i'm just i'm not that far
away ah
demolishing okay okay
so
maybe
should i demolish
everything come
maybe this area is cursed or bugged
filled in the pit
okay
oh the hammer you can just pick up the
tool cupboard with the
e if you hold e on it
oh
if i hold it ah
[Music]
thank you
hello
sorry
[Laughter]
can't pick up
the tc they say
okay
i might i have to make a new one
probably but then i also can't if i
can't pick that up then i also can't get
rid of the base
because it's standing on the base
all right then it stays there forever
[Music]
expand forward
shoot shoot the floor
uh then
we built
stuff again do i even have any
any wood
[Music]
yeah a little bit a little bit of wood
every house
needs a foundation
here we go there's not that much space
for a big house here but okay
hi
[Music]
and
there we go
and one more maybe
and if this is not gonna work then i'm
gonna be mad
okay
uh wait actually maybe no more
foundation foundation because i don't
have that much materials
now we make a wall
so far it's working
oh i'm is muted i'm is better than
discord now
oh wait wait where does the door go [\h__\h]
can't afford to place what do you mean i
can't no more wood
i'll put the door here i guess
[Music]
okay i think i'm out of wood
oh
hello hello
are you here to offer some wood
kind
kind uh lady thank you yata corn my
favorite food
oh that's good stuff i got wood but i
don't know where it went
oh that's okay i can get some myself too
building decaying
oh no
you gotta put your tool covered uh you
gotta pick it up from this place over
here no apparently
it can't be uh uh picked up
they said they
oh one aspect
[Music]
yes
oh
what is that a leg
thank you
[Music]
wow
okay
i shall
help
by also getting some word although i
don't have too much stuff in my
inventory
inventory too small
oh oh oh i'm spamming the coin you get
oh is this a because you don't have any
wood you could uh build
a little box
[Music]
need wood to build but also need wood to
make
a box to put the wood or put everything
in
it's okay i'll
i'll find a way
oh
oh that works good
well that's way better than chopping
down trees with a stone
genius
who felt of this
oh
what
oh i see now i can't i can't carry it
what are those seats i have in my
oh [\h__\h] in my inventory guys you know
what are those
blueberry seeds alpha planting
corn seed
cooked beer meat
what can i get rid of
drop your rock
but it's my rock
where did it go where's my rock
oh this one
bye-bye rock i'll miss you
but no remember where it is it's it's
here
that's teresa and i have to get her back
theresa theresa teresa
let me look at the map teresa is
i know it no theresa is here
did that work
i'll find you
you're the only rock in this area that i
can pick up right
okay okay don't worry teresa i'll be
back
don't worry
there is a little beast bomb now if i
will get her soon right i'll get her
soon where is my
2b home
is that it no that that thing here
wait how much how much wood was that
anyway i think i should get some more
i'll get some more
what about this
can i chop this down too
oh yes
oh it doesn't even even give me an x
or like
chop here oh
ooh
circles it's not gonna be like circles
oh oh
what is why is this wood falling down
am i
is it do i have like a full stack that i
can't
get more of on your inventory is fall
that's all i saw okay then let me use
that
um
here
wow
beautiful house
okay now i make the door
so people can enter
uh also oh yeah windows huh
wait
i need to click it
a window it was gonna be all windows
here
beautiful
and here
kind of unbalanced but uh
we only want i only requested an ocean
view and that's all i'm getting so no
mountain view whatsoever
mm-hmm [\h__\h] front property let's go
and you're in a good neighborhood you
got a lot of neighbors yeah
who else lives here
oh
mommy
uh right here in this area direct area
uh porca is over there across the water
nice
[Music]
so many wow
okay
uh and mikko senpai isn't that far away
too mm-hmm
so who who are you ella allied with you
have any
enemies and any allies
possibly with mummy
she's your enemy or your ally
we haven't decided yet
[Laughter]
we're friendly friendly
okay
[Music]
um okay i'll make a make that
two
toolbox things
housewarming gift
what
oh
noise
thank you
that looks very fluffy
ah put it down
right
here
that's a good spot oh it looks so soft
i mean it's creeping me out and i would
never put this in my own home but sure
craft
two cupboard number two
what else what else do i need besides a
tool cupboard on it
uh you could put your sleeping bag down
in there oh you need a roof and then uh
once you put your tool cupboard oh you
can craft a door and put a door here
and
if you
i think your windows are too high for
people to jump into but you could put
window bars oh
i see
you could put stairs if you wanted to
make a second floor
eventually maybe
so yeah but this looks kind of skinny to
put stairs i don't know where you would
put them
maybe if you move the shelf actually oh
should i
i don't think you can move it
i had to i think i had to destroy mine
because i couldn't pick it up
i'll make a skyscraper yeah what no way
that's lame
you should be able to
shelf doesn't move
you can
big shelf is permanent
it makes no sense you can break it
you can break it okay well
i'll put them on two bones there we go
now open
okay so here this is like my like a
minecraft chest right
the cupboard
no it's just for resources for your
house but you can build like a chest
like in minecraft okay so if i put wood
in here then this place will not fall
apart
yeah okay if you see like uh on the
bottom right above your health it should
it has like a little time
like oh base deteriorating so when you
put stuff in here i could put some wood
in here oh yeah i put some in there too
eight hundred
[Music]
for twenty-five days
okay well then i'll take some out
okay 72 hours it says no
yeah over it's over 72 it just doesn't
show you
oh i heard helicopters are dangerous
what about airplanes
now the airplanes that means that they
dropped off something so like uh if you
watch them yeah they drop off a care
package and you can go to the map oh
that's that's like in i don't know apex
or something i've seen that before
pubg does that i think
man
it's getting more weird can never have
enough woods right
yeah
sleeping bags still not sad oh should i
where should i
should i set it in my home
as a responsibility just put it just put
it down in your house and then make sure
you name it and touch it okay
putting it down here
rename
kiwawa
change does that belong to me now
server is lagging
oh and then uh press e on it like once i
think
it only lets me name it when i press e
okay
but just remember like when you die
you have to select it like in the map
you'll see what i mean you can't just
spawn there it doesn't spawn you there
automatically okay can i have more than
one
yeah you can
okay
oh
theresa
[Music]
threesome we're all huge
[\h__\h]
there's too many stones
theresa
this is you is this you is this you is
this um
it no no way don't worry this spawn
how fast do things do you spawn
i think five minutes
theresa
no
must be here
must be did you just kill something
yes wow
was it a bear
a
boar
impressive
oh
wow like a professional oh you look dead
though are you disconnected oh
shut down
okay
there's already flies i'm not sure if
they're around you or around the board
um but maybe take a shower i think it's
the boy
sure sure surely
i want went through something she's gone
guys
i didn't want to repeat
his story but it's just like uh it's
okay when you die and spawn again you'll
have another one
but will it be the same it will be the
same
it's not teresa that will be wilson
yeah it's gone it's [\h__\h] gone i can't
believe it
unbelievable okay well i'll continue
working i guess
so good at this
yeah
hello
please let me chop you
i'm not that tall
be small please
oh
okay
well
can i build a roof now i wonder
roof or should i um
kind of [\h__\h] up didn't i
what if i
[Music]
is there any space for stairs
you could uh take down this wall and
make it into a u-shape ah
and then you can put the stairs in the
corner
well try something like that
what about this this wall
all right
oh [\h__\h] well how do i do it again there
huh
hey what's happening did i upgrade
something by accident
no i'm breaking something are you
breaking something are you breaking my
house
i thought you wanted to take down the
wall oh yeah can you do it
yeah i can do it really
[Music]
nice okay
i build a new foundation
right
here
okay so here i'll build stairs
spiral or spiral triangle stairs will go
up in the spiral over half a block
height
you can always demolish it like within a
few minutes if you put it down so
uh
rotate seat and know how to rotate how
about here this is probably good
should be able to reach it oh
wow
i got stairs
i'm gonna make a skype
second floor you can just uh instead of
using foundation you just use floor and
you hang it onto the walls you'll see
when you bring it up
okay
hang it onto the walls
well yeah
yeah yeah yeah
good stuff can you make like lights too
or
flights
yeah but electricity is a whole other
ball game you need solar panels or a
wind
uh generator thingy
yeah i did hear a little bit about like
when i was watching podcast stream today
oh somebody just got electricity yeah
somebody just got a phone yeah
interesting
okay and i'm gonna build it why are you
not build it here because the stairs are
in the way jack
this is not what it is
stairs in the way
you can uh demolish the stairs and then
put the
wall down no i don't want to demolish
again
i'm built around it
uh
foundation
um
can i filter
[Music]
this looks like [\h__\h] this building
that's not perfectly happy with it but
okay
steps oh steps
oh are they always that long i just want
some steps here
oh
fine
why not
why not game
you're not making sense to me
um
i'm here you can build but not here why
not
too high steps need a foundation
below it this doesn't need a foundation
below it
you're lying to me chat
okay whatever but we'll continue with uh
whatever works
so here
oh i'm surprised that works
i will make
a
window wall here
and uh window
yes but only on the seaside
i don't want to see anything else
okay okay there we go now i'm very
unhappy with the placement of the stairs
but
it's kind of awkward but okay
can i even pass
i extended it so much just for these
shitty stairs
okay
um then i need that do i need another
pair of stairs
how would i stack that
but does it already lead to the top oh
no there you go
oh wow
amazing
we can still remove them with the hammer
nah it's all right so then i would film
something here and then
here
or
we don't make the whole building two
levels we just you know
have like a a roof on part of the lower
building lower part
and the roof on the higher parts but
that's too complicated for now
we're not gonna do that it's easy it's
easy yeah yeah
okay so this this is this
i'm not supposed to put a wall here i
guess yep makes sense
and now
well
[Music]
now it's way bigger than i wanted it to
be i just wanted a tiny tiny baby house
but okay
i'll take this
it's more than i asked for
it doesn't cost that much wood you're
able to see like when you look in the
tool cupboard how much it costs a day
oh
with the wood that i put into it it
still gives me 72 hours so
it seems oh so i uh i authorized myself
in your building so i can always put
wood in there if it's
oh starting to decay or something i
won't know
but i can check in everything can you
see if something decays
uh walls will start falling down other
than that no okay okay only i think only
the owner well maybe when i walk in i'll
go check till then
um
i'm happy with this now i'm like a roof
now
triangle
a hat for your house oh hats
um
the difference
roofing
not my strong suit
come on
come on you can you have a weird roof
you can like uh put the wall next to it
and it'll cut off like where your roof
cuts off uh-huh
[Music]
i wish there was like all the roof or
something just use floors as a roof
yeah
uh
no
no no no i'll make this look
decent now see this works here
and that will probably look like [\h__\h] if
you put it outside if you put a wall
it'll it'll just close it off it won't
like like if you if you look at it from
the outside your roofs are probably
overlapping
it's a stylistic choice
[Laughter]
uh where's my finger hood oh
you'll be ubi
this looks like [\h__\h] it's not even
closing what is this i think it looks
cool it makes no sense
the [\h__\h]
is it with these roofs
oh i can't even place this up here why
not well i guess i'll just have an open
house
let's see what it looks like
i can't close it at the top i'm it
oh you can't put uh
a floor yeah no
but oh you could you could remove the
roof if you want and then uh
redo it you could just demolish it i
think it looks pretty good
at least i have a roof did uh luna zeppa
doesn't have a roof
oh uh whoever that was over there
noticing by doesn't have a roof fever my
my i have a roof
it doesn't close but i have a roof
oh
oh um
that is
that is architecture
what you see here everybody this is
called modern architecture okay
it's um a technique to
um have
the air flow through the house better
and also it improves your chakra
[Music]
i so have heard
from myself because i'm the
architect chicken coop no
phoenix coop if anything but okay i have
to do something wait no it works
sure uh shore game
oh okay okay
oh that other space you could put a wall
probably okay
can i though
can i maybe if i put the floor down
first
like here
yeah
oh yeah
i i don't believe that any
storage area oh literally
i don't believe that anybody's first
house looked any better than this
my house is my first house
no actually i think it no i think it is
yeah i think we put a balcony on the top
of you
yeah but you need to research a ladder
you can't you don't just have one
yeah no don't need that
there you go it's all closed off
yeah
and it's closed off i'll close it i'll
close it yeah looking from the outside
doesn't all look close
although i could throw a grenade through
your window right now if i wanted to
excuse me
why would you even think about doing
something like that you guys are also
violent in this game in minecraft
everything was so peaceful
oh here everybody's just violent
looks fine
yeah minecraft this is very pvp too
though you can farm you can fish you can
go diving you can get a boat
oh okay well my house is done so yeah
can you show me some of those things
uh can you show me the world
you don't have a door
you need to put a lock on it oh
what what why would anybody even want to
go inside this house anyway
oh you know just check it out see what
they could loot
there's nothing to loot
you can't even take the coupler it's a
nice bear rug
oh
don't tank
don't
how do i make a door
some crafting uh it's it's like a item
you craft mmm
okay the single door probably is
probably size-wise good enough
and a lock okay ah
oh you need wood for the lock that
doesn't
seem right but
okay i make
i make
oh thank you you gave me more wood thank
you
thank you
so i'm when are you building the watson
railways in this game
i don't think there's any rails in this
game maybe something's in the car
like amico senpai uh she was advertising
her
uh helicopter taxi rides oh wow
she has a helicopter
i i guess so yeah we could uh try
calling her number and on my phone no i
don't wanna i don't wanna i don't wanna
trouble her right now
okay it's fine it's fine we'll prank
call her you won't know who it is
never speak english then
ah although she might understand this
with her elite english
up to you hello your extended car
warranty
i put a lock on it
oh
can i put stairs here or something i
couldn't the game wouldn't let me
oh okay i'll try again
man it's just a skill thing you just
have to jump
yeah
see it won't let me maybe it's a
different kind of what about a ramp
no
why
oh oh these kind of stairs exist too
well yeah it's a skill issue
uh
okay closed door
how do i
make like a
how do i lock it then
if you just close it it locks oh
but what if
can anybody get in
oh you can't get is it only me because i
placed the lock
i think you need a certain type of lock
with a keypad
well then i i might be able to make one
chat how do i do it wow pretty
wow
it's getting dark
hold e hold e unlock okay
oh you can make a copy i oh what if i
lose okay
i won't lose it i'll just keep it in my
house unlock open knock
cute
i'll get a better look yay
yeah beachfront property it's my dream
come true
i really want that sometimes okay
yeah
if you hold e on the lock i think you
can make the copy of it
you mean that lock
i think so it says unlock and knock or
open door
press unlock first
oh
create the key
remove lock okay create a key
i made a key where did it go in my
inventory
yeah you want one
yeah i need one
uh how do i drop something
i'll just drag it out of your inventory
okay
[Music]
like with when you press tab
there you go
there's a key for you i think you need
one too oh i don't know do you do you
need one i don't think so maybe i just
need one
wow i made one just in case
try opening it no
oh i don't need a key okay well i have
an extra key for
somebody
okay house is done
yay
what what now
now uh usually so what people do in this
game is if you press
g
look at the map and then do you see the
water treatment oh [\h__\h]
you have a gun use your gun uh
[Music]
i'm drenched in blood
okay one thing we're gonna do is kill
your first thing yeah okay
scary world man
[\h__\h] scary i was looking at the map
and suddenly i hear a bear
roaring into my ear
just slicing it up for dinner tonight
mmm romantic
okay i will should i maybe put some
stuff into my thingy for safekeeping
okay
you can't put in your cupboard you have
to build another chest uh i think you
can put your boxes here though inside
the shelf wait i can't put it in there
okay wait a second i can put the wood
inside though
a box
i should build a box
this is my house
no it's my house
yeah
so much huh
yeah yeah yeah mine
no
i mean sure you can you can have that
space if you want to i live here now
wait why can't i
not make put all my stuff into the
that thing that i made
yeah so the cupboard is only for
resources to keep your house from
decaying
okay
and what what's the thing i can build as
a chest because when i type in chest or
so it doesn't oh come on uh under const
no it's not under construction hold that
oh
under common
common
there's uh something called the wood
storage box
or there's large wood box wait i don't
think you can make that one yet probably
should uh take back some wood
okay
aha
a note what storage box nice
what else what else
small planter boxing
hitch and through
shop front
window bars
[Music]
okay
a place oh just a box
just a box
okay i'll put my seats in here for
later if i want to
plant something can you see what's
inside the box
yes
also here i got this for you
cloves
let's go
i was wondering how long you want to see
me naked like this
you were enjoying the video
let me go put some stuff away in my
house
okay put this on oh
ah
it doesn't show
what
where did it go
how did i throw it i threw it out what
no okay why it looked like i was placing
it on my body
uh-huh
it looks so stupid
that looks so stupid
what is that
i don't know okay
i'm dressed
i want to build a lantern
lantern
what do i need
ah
metal fragments low grade fuel do you
have that ah man
yes
can i have 25 metal fragments and 15
low-grade fuels
for wonderland
yes
i heard scraps are very popular in this
game
you want
some uh well we could also go to this
like a press g open up the map
store we're going to shop yeah if you if
you see all those little carts
uh if you hover over them you can see
how much you could get
cards
yeah the little green cards yeah ah
carts ah
uh
tuna can lamp is that a lamp
it's a lamp you may not have a tuna can
well the lantern all needs low-grade
fuel so
that one also needs a great feel
actually i have an extra one i could
just give you hold on
oh there's a ceiling light for 30 scraps
i don't have that much
i have 17 scraps
now you need electricity for it anyways
okay oh eh
what
i thought the lantern works just with
fire
oh yeah the lantern does but the
ceiling lamp or um
needs a electricity
makes sense
more
wait tuna can one is good
it's very um
original
i can make a lamp out of a phone light
and a plastic bottle
but i guess they don't have oh wait they
do have phones but not that kind of
phone
in this game
build a campfire oh but if i place it in
here won't my whole house be on fire no
no okay
campfire
oh
three
two
yeah i don't know i'm so [\h__\h] laggy
man it's only when i'm tapped into the
game i don't know how to fix it
how many do you know
oh don't i can't thank you i don't know
you don't know
it's fine it's okay really
okay i'll put tuna candle in is this a
tournament
is this it
whoa oh yeah so you could place it on
the wall
oh
uh but it does require fuel so once it
runs for a certain amount of time you
have to
put more fuel in it
aha okay where do you get fuel
you can find it like by looting stuff
oh like when you're ready we can go to
convenience store okay
[Music]
wait a second i'll put a campfire on my
beautiful second floor it's actually
gorgeous look at those big ceilings guys
the other people don't have that because
they don't have a proper roof so i would
say it was worth it
a campfire inside the house
not a good idea if you ask me but um
sure
can't turn it on right now anyway
okay yeah high ceilings
nice feature
okay i'm ready to
[Music]
go
okay come to my house oh that i'm still
building something okay
what is that
can i eat this
you
don't want to
[Music]
oh was it ammo oh you know you guys know
i don't know what ammo looks like didn't
we
what was that about
what was that i remember something
a long time ago
is this ammo that looks like a firework
oh yeah when i was in the titties and i
was like can i reuse
munitions can i reuse bullets
and everybody was like hey what the [\h__\h]
you were you didn't know anything about
guns
i'm like what's in this game
you can make bullets
i would like to leave a live a peaceful
life at least right now so i think 22
bullets are enough
i'm ready to go i'm gonna come over
okay
leave the key oh
i don't really need the key anyways
i'll just
throw it out like this
close your door it's closed
mean uh
look are you happy now i heard this was
one of the things they wrote in the
manual
for beginners
at the
chat will be
full with close your door close your
door close your door if you don't close
your door reminds me of minecraft but in
minecraft i didn't give a [\h__\h] and you
can't lock your door anyway
but okay i will listen
is the business on this house
i don't remember
i mean you have my key but i don't have
your key do you think this is fair
well
yes
oh that's super this house never mind
is there somebody's house no oh that one
that one with the store oh
hi
i see you
sorry i didn't mean to i just came back
in
i literally jumped up
she likes to keep me on my toes
maybe
what are we doing again
ah we wanted to get me a kill oh
yeah
i killed it now if you use like your
stone or an axe so you can uh get food
and claws
what the blood i can use to make oil
uh the animal fat so if you check your
inventory oh yeah i got something it's
chicken yeah you can craft oil hello
hello love you hi i will not kill you
no no no no
so over here
that will go senpai's house in between
these rocks uh on our right
and when she's online she'll
camp this it's a convenience store over
here
she'll camp it
uh-huh why because you get drops you can
get free food you can get uh
um like i don't know this is robocop
senpai's house over here
oh
and so this is a convenience store and
um oh yeah
you can loot the box with this
oh wait what
can i not break the barrel in here
ah this one i can't break what's in
there
rope
oh i can finally tie amme up let's go
how did you get in there oh
here
that needs a recycle machine so if
there's stuff that you don't like or you
don't want to use you can turn it into
metal fragments oh cool
i'll miss some scrap oh there's a
washing machine
futuristic
got the scrap inside like every room
inside the convenience store there's
like a different pitch thingy
you can open this one
oh
scraps
i can just take all this they're just
everywhere
wow you might find some people like
before i've been in here and there's
like another player and they don't want
me to take their stuff so they were
shooting at me
who was that
i think it was
so aggressive oh my god there's a bunch
of little boxes
you get food in here
chocolate
all right ah that's good i actually
should eat anyway
good timing let's eat something let's
eat some chocolate apple and the apple
um
yummy that's that's what i call a good
healthy dinner
yeah
what else do we have
nothing
this one
what what
i hear your footsteps
not anymore
i'm a doco
[Music]
are you on the second floor i hear ya hi
like yeah so if you come around this way
there's a ladder and there's also a box
up there there's a box here too oh
sick
there's a house over there
and they just like camp the convenience
store because you get free resources oh
that's smart
convenience store close by is definitely
a feature i would like for my real house
too
go go
how do you
how do you climb a ladder
i just press w
okay okay it takes a lot of time damn
e
yeah you can shift while pressing w
and something else oh
cool oh but it kind of changes my
my
feel of it
does it give me like armor points or
something though
wait if you're answering me i can't hear
you right now
cause you're too far
oh i didn't know if you were talking to
me or chat huh wait what was the
question uh
if i wear like anything really does
everything give me like extra oh no
says it like when you're in your
inventory there's like a little
percentage thing oh
[Music]
oh nothing went up
like very different
at this percentage
i don't see anything changing
diving masks perhaps clear vision on the
water oh cool
stick
maybe that only helps for
diving then okay hmm
okay i think we got
all the good stuff from here
[Music]
uh i have to go do something really
quick so i'll go stay in my house so we
can go back towards that way but like if
you want more stuff to do
you can always go for the care packages
on the map or you can explore on the map
just look for more stuff and store it in
your house
uh you can build like a workbench so
that you can craft more things
and you can come here and recycle stuff
that you don't want
okay
okay that's fine
thank you
okay i'll go back to my house and i'll
still be in russ so i'll just i'll be
back in like 30 minutes okay
okay but i'll leave this cord for now
okay
recycle okay don't don't get lost
i will
okay chad what do you want me to recycle
what should i recycle
what do i need i don't know what's like
uh what what is of value
sheet metal this stuff here
sheet metal scraps
recycling
anything metal you don't need
what is this
ladder hatch
probably don't need this right on this
lever
metal orb
high quality metal
yeah no i don't think i should keep that
so i'll just turn this on
[Music]
oh
we get some scraps
some metal fragments uh-huh
and
a ladder
oh
some high-quality metal and gears
oh but i can't
um
i have no space
what is this
thing's been doing a radiation level
wait there's radiation somewhere here
recycle the gears okay
oh
scrap gears to okay
whoa
[Music]
so many
so many scraps noise okay
by the way sorry guys i feel like i'm
not quite in my element today
you guys probably noticed or at least
kfp noticed
this is not the usual kiwama oh can i
grill this raw meat here
raw bear meat
okay it's off to switzerland
okay go
do it
i have to put fuel in it i don't have
any fuel
what was it about fuel fuel i can just
find in places
add wood
ah
into the same
wait i don't have any wood i left it all
somewhere else
okay i'll go home once i'll make another
wooden box a little store all the [\h__\h] i
just got is home this way
maybe
somewhere this way
eh i have wood okay
i keep on pressing q and i keep on going
to this pad is there a shortcut to go to
this
page by the way
there it is
tab
hallelujah
thank you you guys probably were
thinking
the whole time
why does she not just press tab i know i
know i know i know i know i know
okay don't we put this in
so much we'll use all of it i hope not
and uh
oh splitting
what
i'm still learning and set amount ah ah
okay sound like this i'll put this here
see now i know how to split items i
still don't know how to do that in
minecraft
[Music]
wow i'm grilling
yeah
i can take the wood out again
oh it gets
it gives me a shark hole too wow what'd
you say i can take it out again it
stopped
don't leave for too long
will it change into
grilled meat
oh what's happening
how do i know it's done
raw
rock
uh continue
it will
overcook no i guess i don't know if it's
done if it just makes another a new one
here
who's that
oh okay
no bears please don't attack me
somebody's on the ground
oh
cooked pork yum yum yum
what about now why take so much time
okay
take
uh oh
jake
[Music]
man i got so many jump scares already
today
it's like a horror game
maybe maybe you know it really bothers
me that i like so much maybe there's
some
[Music]
graphic things that i can
turn down even more
render scale
graphics quality
it's unbelievable though i i don't
understand why it's
why it has to be like this
turn
down shadows yeah shadows are bad
this is only zero one or two hmm
not lagging i'm not lying am i lagging i
think i'm uh yeah
i'm still kind of lagging
but a little bit better
shadows
oh how about how about that
i'm moving i'm moving nope i think i'm
still kind of lagging
cool
okay
a little bit better at least yeah
hmm
am i the only home life member who likes
so much with this game cause i'm
i don't think that i have the worst pc
in her life
rtx off
yeah i sent you a message that might
help i'll
maybe fix it thank you oh try making
ah it's not
i mean
it's not minimized
oh
[Music]
i'm still lagging um whatever
set to high priority automata i'll set
something to high priority
task manager
um where is that again
details
uh
real time or high
i can't use the aliens because i have
amd there you go
you know the exact name of my graphics
card i am amd yes
hi okay
priority and done okay
well
uh
i hear a helicopter and i'm still
lagging but helicopters fall away
i'm i'm still
am i lagging no wait right now i'm not
like let's open this menu uh chop the
lag chop to lag but i mean
kind of better than before no
i will hide maybe
[Music]
an attack helicopter
let me pour some more water
so if miko has a helicopter now doesn't
mean that she can
kill the helicopters with her helicopter
why does it do it like this why does it
always turn itself off
her helicopter very small oh that's cute
mini helicopter
she has a
helicopter
it keeps filling up that's why oh okay
but it should stack on its own
stack stack the same meat
do it
need a rocket to attack one oh
i need wait can anyone find my campfire
in my
in my home
or do i need like an actual grill
then this house is around you can leave
a letter ah
leave a letter
oh i did see like you can craft notes
yeah
you can do it in the campfire okay
okay
ah
oh wait this time it didn't stop it
doesn't stop cooking this time
[Music]
drink water take one of the meat
i will drink it
why did i not drink it
why did i just hold it
ah like this
go go
can i throw it away now is there a
shortcut for throwing away just like out
of my
hot bar like in minecraft
or do i have to go into the inventory
like amma told me
keep
it
you can refill i'll recycle ah
i'll just put it here for now i thought
we were doing this to get like some
space
pork
okay
oh wait no
that one's still not done one more
i heard footsteps
probably just an animal
you know speaking of minecraft i was
watching this video today that was
absolutely sick
um
it was about like a mod
uh
for minecraft uh it was um
the weather storm mod
which is apparently something that the
winter storm is like a like a boss
monster that
exists in the story mode minecraft but
holy [\h__\h] it looks so cool i got it in
my recommended today and it looks so
sick i want to fight the weather storm
but it looks like probably if you if you
don't know how to do it like if it's the
first time you didn't watch a video like
me then you would like probably struggle
a lot with it hi are you gonna come to
me i can shoot you
um but
it's actually pretty easy you just
uh
what
what wasn't that the first one a boom
headshot
why didn't that look
that was a marvelous shot
oh cause that's the i don't know the
difference of like you know gun types
no idea man
just put it away
okay that's overcooked
okay you can stop now
shot that's a shotgun it's so long
though i thought that uh
the shorter the gun
the shorter
maybe the range i don't know because
sniper guns from what i've seen they're
usually like longer guns
so you know that's my logic
i don't i don't think it's too weird of
a logical what did i say there you go
i can't
think tab
what do i not need [\h__\h] this i don't
need it
and
take
longer is more precise ah really how do
i reload
how do i reload
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
it sucks the maximum that you can put in
there
now can i shoot some people
there's no one to shoot
now i understand why
people kept on shooting me out of
nowhere feels good
well i think i'm lost where's my home
somewhere here right
this way
oh i'll shoot you but i gotta get closer
uh
hi
i thought that that was a good shot what
the [\h__\h]
oh that was good why did you not die
instantly
wow
impressive
nice shooting thank you
on it no meat
wanted to pick it up automatically
this way
make
bone hat
ah bone hat bone hat
that looks sick
yeah that's cool
is there anything else that i can make
with phones
bone armor
that looks way better than what i
currently have
sorry ahmed
[Laughter]
should i make this one
i think i can make this one too
more bones for the bone god
i'll make this too
but no space
don't need this
one helmet
uh
i hear a chicken
wear this oh
wow i look like an animal
[Music]
paying a visit yeah where are you
i want to make a chicken farm or like a
chicken coop like in minecraft oh there
you are can i
can you like bring them can you
can you hatch eggs
can you take its eggs can i open it like
an inventory can i open you
excuse me can i open you sir
no
but maybe it drops an egg
you just kill it no but do i get an egg
if i kill it
why are you leading me are you showing
me a hole
only me there's no eggs in this game
okay i'm quitting
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
i'm gonna go ah why did i pick that up i
don't want it
did i finish my armor
hell yeah
oops ah that was not the intention
the pants i'll keep because apparently
there's no
there's no bone pants
wait that's one piece
oh
um
should i be scared right now
laugh away
i can tame chickens oh really
that sounds cute
um
who's faster helicopter army uh
that's some
dangerous maybe um
um
that's not good um
that's my that's my go-to um solution
what happens to my body um
can it still shoot me when i'm out of
the game
this is not like like minecraft
it doesn't save me
but logging back in takes so much time
until it loads the
world ah
okay i'm trying i'm gonna get go back
into the game
i'll try
i may say
save my body i'm gonna cover my body
please please cover my body
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] window
[Music]
no
i can't i oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
window is not reacting okay there we go
play a game but it takes ages
is it gonna kill me
for real
for real sells
joining server now
good learning lesson but what happens to
all my stuff
i'm already dead no
and what about myself will it like drop
on my dead body can i pick it up
why does it have to load the world like
9 000 assets every [\h__\h] time holy
[\h__\h]
five minutes okay
well loading into the game takes four
minutes
it will still be there okay
search my body yeah bye
yeah uh
yeah i guess that would have been too
easy
i mean even in minecraft it wasn't the
best solution
30 minutes 20 minutes okay that sounds
uh better
helicopter might still be there but i'm
gonna respawn in my house right in my
in my uh sleeping bag
if i understood correctly if i choose it
wait so if i log out
randomly somewhere in the middle of a
field
there's a chance that while i'm logged
out that i will be killed while i'm gone
interesting
okay so always go back to home or build
the base
got it
uh
spawning world
i'm almost done
cleaning up why does it take so long
maybe now that i restarted the game
maybe maybe i won't lag anymore because
i changed so many settings but i had to
restart you know
maybe that's the thing
warming prefabs
it takes so long
ah
i thought
guys
what is
what does this mean
sorry about the window size but um why
am i
not where i should be
chill i'm already dead
or am i maybe
[\h__\h]
huh what what it didn't let me choose
what
what what
okay i don't understand why did i not
respawn and uh
what
guys i'm not lagging i'm not lagging
but for some reason uh
the screen size is wrong why
i know what what's the right screen size
this one
no wait that's way too tiny it's so tiny
i need glasses
this one
wait why is it also so tiny it didn't
really change
[\h__\h]
ah this is what i had before i think it
but it looks way tinier than before oh
well okay i'm playing on a tiny screen
now
is that correct yeah on obs it looks
fine okay
now i need to go get my
my body back and hey i'm not lagging
it it's it's fixed
i'm not lagging guys
check back for body
uh
i don't see it
it's not there
should i be seeing it
who gives a [\h__\h] i feel like i'm the
only person online right now besides i'm
in
zoom out
i have to what
okay
closed door
see it was locked anyway okay now i'll
just have to close it okay
theresa yeah
there is a this is julie
surely this is teresa you know what can
i like place her on on the shelf i want
her to have like an altar where she'll
be safe
oh no
no [\h__\h] no
go away
no
i thought they don't attack you if you
don't have a weapon
oh [\h__\h]
oh man
[Applause]
what if i die a second time is it like
in minecraft where your stuff disappears
if you die a second time please don't
kill me please don't kill me it's okay
oh i think it
left
why did it leave did it get enough
of my
body no it's not okay
i died two times i already died oh but
my stuff will be there right it's not
like in minecraft right
okay i think i'm good but um
not really though
i'm zooming out but i don't see anything
that i should i don't know what i'm
supposed to see
check near p4
[Music]
up there
can i
heal myself back up if i sleep or so
ah it only shows the latest stuff on the
map ah
maggie
bear
need a campfire to heal i have a
campfire up there but can i turn it on
uh oh
[Music]
i don't see myself healing
i'm at 50 comfort though
yes i did but yeah
don't question it because i'm not
questioning it either
need food i didn't leave any food in
the
in here i think
i don't think i left anything
unless i can eat this
um um
well i threw up so
we learned a lesson
um
this is not helping
turn it off
yeah yeah but you said 20 30 minutes
so we're fine i think but i'm gonna go
there now hopefully bear doesn't see me
yo my vision is so blurry
i mean i need food
i'm in
any bears
okay cool
the music is making this feel very
dramatic we are going to let you guys
hit p9 you think i died at p9
really
wasn't i on my way from here to here
he ate for p9
oh yeah so just like it
actually that way did i run that way
closer to the supermarket
oh [\h__\h] i hear it again
i swear i held a bear
i heard footsteps
oh man
i'm not gonna find if it's not if it's
not
near
oh you remember that guys you guys are
genius
i died under a power line or near a
power line
no no
not the bears
i passed it okay okay okay but you see
i'm trying to run away from the um
there
oh wait that's that's not a bear
okay that's not a bear
where is that
is this my body
oh where's the small load ah
let's go
all right first first things first eat
thank you guys for the help i would have
never found that without you
okay
oh is that mine
oh
oh my god
let's get all of this
put this on
gorgeous
fabulous
beautiful kiwa
wait do i have two lights
ah because yeah the game gave me
new light and new stone okay cool
happy happy happy
holding dragon mouse over everything ah
okay i'll try to remember i probably
forget
drop touch and stone but
i will put my stone if i can on the
on this shelf
can i
can but then it will disappear right oh
no well then i'll just i'll just put it
i'll put it in here and it's safe
maybe eventually we'll make a super
special
what what about my front door we're fine
oh man
[Laughter]
as if anybody would come by right now
we're safe guys i'm unpopular anyway
nobody would come by to kiwawa's place
animals will
oh
okay
hey guys have you noticed i completely
stopped lagging
i don't know what it was maybe i really
needed to restart the game after
changing so many settings
or i don't know what exactly it was but
yeah
isn't that nice isn't that lovely isn't
that lovely
yummy yum yum yum yum
someone's blowing a horn is that a
ship
oh that thing over there
whoa cool
don't
[Music]
cargo ship okay so what are we gonna do
um this when i put into uh this box
it will not decay will it
make more books okay
large wood box
crafting
low grade low grade fuel
whoa
crafting
can i make high grade fuel do i even
need that
a hat
i'm getting
lock your chests
nah it's fine
no we're fine good you guys are so
you worry too much you know
nobody cares about this [\h__\h] i have here
huh
aha
and that much shiny whips
but um okay so this this sun in here
i'll put this
um i'll put this level up put some at
some point maybe we'll have a system
right now there's no system animal fat
ew
wow
fuel
i mean maybe i'm what what what can i
craft with the fuel again or i put it
into the lamp right
was that oh wait i have right i have
more tuna can lamps now let me place
them around
[Music]
oh i thought it was five
eh
the lamb's car isn't chainsaw
no you can't break because there's a
lock on my door
and
it's uh it's it's not locked locked
right now
ah the lamp comes with five oh oh
[Music]
oh cute but turn it off then enough turn
it off
it's bright right now
okay
um
now we'll keep that put this
okay materials here
materials
this is where you're living in a
material world
and i am your material girl
scraps
uh wood i'll put into the
wood box
okay what do we do now guys
upgrade your house to stone
oh
with the
[Music]
do i need
metal or sulfur or stones with this do i
need this in my inventory
then uh wait how do i do this
i
this thing right
uh
all right what was it again
i upgraded stone
oh
whoa it needs 210 stones per wall okay
and we need some stuff well i guess
we'll go collect some stones
yeah we'll leave it as wood now it's too
expensive now that would take me ages
okay we'll put that here but i'll keep
it in mind i'll keep in mind that i need
those stones
um
now we can put one of those here was
this
electric fuse
oh
someday maybe if i continue playing this
game which i can't promise but just you
know
maybe
i at least want to get my money's worth
because this cost of what forty dollars
i want to make it worthwhile
should i bring this
put this here too
okay then do we go explore
upgrade to wood it's wood
isn't this wood
huh
it's not wood
that's not wood
it looks like wood to me
different kind of wood
okay we can uh
we can do that we have enough wood i can
probably do why am i upgrading it
why do i need to upgrade it and upgrade
it anyway
uh wait no i don't know how to do it
anymore oh there we go
i can't
eh 140 wood what do you mean i have wood
why did i thought i put it in my
inventory
there we go
now
uh
upgrade the wood oh
it looks prettier
upgrade
uh upgrade
wait so why did you say because they can
rate me
they can rate me if it's not wood
i don't understand
why
upcost upkeep class will rise
does everything have to be wood
[\h__\h]
it's prettier
you can use rocks as well
oh
i don't have many rocks
okay we'll do the first floor then is
that good enough for now
oopsie
um
pick up pick up how
it doesn't work
is it because i'm standing on no
i can't pick it up but i also can't work
underneath it hold it
ah thank you
[Music]
sometimes life just wants to be extra
complicated
upgrade
up great
so if my
house
is out of stone i need stone
to upkeep it if it's out of wood i need
wood to upkeep it and i'm out of wood
all right i will try to find some more
wood then
how's it starting to break already no i
still have eight hours what do you mean
i'll go get some more wood
open door
closed door
wow she did it incredible let's go find
some trees chop chop
here's some trees
oh i forgot to put my ragweed down uh
that's fine i'll put it back when i'm
back
[\h__\h] paranoid
yeah yeah yeah
chop it chop it do it
i'm doing good are you sure well i
i even though
minecraft
back in the day had a little bit of a
rough start i think
you know now i'm one of the best
minecraft players in all of english
although we don't really play anymore
but
i do have potential potential
potential
for these kind of games in theory
well
oh wait this one this button oh you get
so much wood
yes and also yes i use doing the pne
mode because you remember the the rough
times we had one and a half years ago
when i was playing minecraft
where everything was going wrong not
really not even only because of you know
minecraft but just because of the pc and
the internet i don't know what
what
the good old times pickaxe breaking some
scares
we should
i remember when i was
uh playing solo
in the beginning
and uh i had this enderman roommate and
i thought it was so funny
turns out and the men are [\h__\h]
everywhere and it's not even such a
special thing but but you know at that
time i thought it was hilarious
hmm
yeah
i wonder if this is really the new
minecraft now in her life if nobody's
gonna touch minecraft anymore but i'm
gonna i want to play that i'm gonna kill
the the withering the the weather storm
well first of all maybe we should kill
the wither
there's still things i want to do it's
not like we're out of content in
minecraft actually there's still things
to do
um i wonder if that's allowed it's a
it's a mod but uh are we
using
mods
so far
are shaders considered months
see hydro wait you can be dehydrated
oh
i thought it's just hunger and that's it
uh
what if i don't have water
server connection mods
i have to ask about that
although the wither storm is kind of
dangerous because like it's
uh and you would have to like spawn
somewhere where it doesn't eat up
everything
you die
yeah yeah phoenix doesn't help to
everybody i would agree with that um
so what do i do without dehydration
where do i get water
can i like take water from the ocean and
then like cleanse it filter it
somehow
emma has water on her roof
water from mushrooms
go to your neighbor you can get what
yeah really is that not considered
stealing
drink water from the okay okay if you
guys say that's okay
do they have like a watery a water
filter machine or something like that
nice i'm getting really good at chopping
down those trees man
it's okay
rain catch watercolor oh
so oh wait i live
where do i live where am i
is this luna senpai's house
[Music]
oh i think that says
if anyone breaks this
you'll pay
if anyone hurts or breaks this
revenge is coming
you shall not get away
how often does that convenience store
refresh by the way because we can go
there again i guess i didn't leave a
plastic bottle there
right here horoscope oh she had a horse
there didn't she but it was outside yeah
so i don't know what happens to
horses [\h__\h] i need to go get water
uh
how do i know
what what does that thing look like
i'll go to ami's place summer's place no
i'll go to amma's place
well
just gonna get a new horse
sorry
okay where is the water
blue barrel thing
oh
i
i don't see is it on top
can i even
what the [\h__\h] is that
what was that
what is that my dehydration hurting me
oh spikes on the house travel house what
okay um but like a
toy
a trap yeah
with my house uh
okay
oh is it that that thing
oh i need that can i build that too
uh but don't i need a bottle i can't
drink straight from this
can i
oh
[Music]
thank you mommy for the water
hey what is that
is that what is it called
whoa
rain ah there it is
small water catcher large watercolor
what do you need metal fragments and a
tarp
i feel like i have metal fragments but
probably don't have a tarp
speaking of i have to drink water too
a tier one workbench okay
a tarp though can i make that myself or
do i have to pick it up somewhere
what were we doing oh yeah we're
upgrading the house go go go go
[Music]
what's this
video
[Music]
okay so but then i have to be lucky
right for it to be there when i'm there
sorry i didn't see an answer in case you
guys answered but how fast is the korean
store refresh
i'm gonna check the answer now
if you tell me
10 minutes oh
2 15. okay different answers but we'll
check it out then
um
oh yeah
uh
and we do this
no right click upgrade the wood
[Music]
beautiful beautiful
mama you left your door open
nobody's here so i don't think oh wait
what this one's upgraded ah but from the
other side
ah that looks lame yeah
mita mega bimio
okay
gonna do it on purpose now i'm gonna
leave it open on purpose
such a rebel
such a rebel no one can stop me i'm not
part of your arrest system
wow i'm doing it guys
i'm resting
i'm playing rust let's go
i still have a bunch
but i don't think this is enough
actually
for like
if i want to do the roof too
can i leave the roof
why is it important that everything is
completely made out of wood
rustic i'm rustic she's right oh no
she's gonna rest
oh no
stand back
holy [\h__\h]
up to me just the first flight
not really important
okay i started though
uh
speaking of morbing
you know when i flew to korea the in the
movie selection there was that movie i
had the choice and for a moment i was
thinking about it maybe i should watch
it even though people say it's bad but
just in order to understand the joke you
know
but i didn't in the end i didn't watch
anything during that uh
during that plane ride
lame
missed opportunity yeah it was for free
there i should have watched it when i
had the option to watch it for free
right man
beautiful
on my way back i watched two movies
though i watched a quite funny one but
you guys gonna
be like where are your taste is [\h__\h] but
i just wanted to watch a comedy movie
and
i don't know i didn't know any of the
ones in this election so i just went
with something that looks like it's
maybe funny it was called i think
the hustle
it's about two
two women
who are
who scam uh dudes oh there's a hole here
huh
is that a problem
you've seen it
it's actually it was actually funny okay
it was actually funny
my mom likes it really
yeah with and have a half the way yeah
yeah
um people sometimes used to tell me i
look like anne hathaway what do you say
what do you say
look at me i look a little bit like anne
hathaway
which celebrity do i look like the most
look at my face
what do you think
that's it
don't
[Laughter]
[Music]
wow i need my wood to keep this place up
i think i'll go for more wood
baby steps baby steps
yeah yeah okay uh i'll put in what i
have oopsie
and now i'll go for my wood although
it's dark i'm kind of scared to go
outside when it's dark um
[Music]
look like the belgians it doesn't mean i
doubt that
you know if i had if hooker papa made
any other
like
v tuber
then
i could at least say i look like her
but i don't have a youtuber sister like
uh
from my father's side
sad
amen has so many so if amma asks you who
do i look like you could just say
you could say any of her sisters
you know one artist said
i was always thinking this artist needs
to become a youtuber mama
recently
became a veto my mama and i saw it and i
was like
yo
let's go
you guys ever have that feeling
like oh this artist should be a v super
mama
i won't tell you which one i guess but
because that's advertising a different
company but it's a new really really new
one i think they're japanese speaking
you know
ah i i told ina that too though
i don't think she's interested because
it's
a lot of work i guess like also having
to do
outfits and stuff but who knows maybe
one day when she has time
i think it would be awesome like it
would be funny like
the
the um
what's what's the words like the
development first she's the veto and
then she's the mama it would be like so
funny especially if it's for whole life
if it's her whole life then you know
no sad sad sad but if she ever does the
g thing
it would be so nice to like leave
something behind like you you become the
mama i like this idea it's just a
wholesome it feels like something has
been completed the circle
the cycle the circle the cycle circle
has been completed where's the axe i
don't see it it's too dark
ah i have good eyes but i just don't see
it
ah
yeah
oops
[\h__\h]
i have to turn it on every
time this chopping is okay too
is this just more effective going by the
eggs
ah there we go
okay
it's too dark to chop trees
uh oh i see a bear it didn't see me
[\h__\h] is it trying to enter my house
no
wait where's my
i will kill it
if i need to
where's my home
here's my home
my door was open
did it die
[\h__\h]
oh man
well um
flashlight can i have a flashlight on
the whole time if i make one
wait why am i
my lights
now i can actually use my light uh
[\h__\h] that was not it
ah beautiful
oh look how nice
cozy
it's pretty cozy
okay
for
61 hours okay that's good enough for now
helmet flashlight reload the gun
nice
i think it died
right probably
issa is uh
a chair
a chair would be nice wouldn't it chair
i can't build it what does it need
wooden metal fragments plant
uh not the right one
so i need to get used to this
metal
high quality metals stones
metal fragments
neither one uh tier one wait how do why
am i dying
why is everything so red
okay
[Music]
here
one
work
workbench
a level one manual fragments oh wait i
can make this
500 wood 50 scraps
uh
got that wood
scraps
yeah i can bound it
oh i'm healing okay okay
okay sit down i don't have a chair i was
trying to build one but first i need to
make a workbench
so complicated uh
uh
workbench okay or should i just make
this one can i make it
high quality amount 20.
i have enough i can already make level
two or does it need to be like separate
once can i only make
a level one first okay
okay
ah workbench level one required ah i
need to make this one on the workbench
okay
but it needs 500 scraps never mind i
can't make that
don't think i have that many scraps
this house gonna be hungry why
no no no see that's why i shouldn't have
made it so big that's why smaller would
have been better
okay i'll put it in here
but yes stained
like this
need a roommate
who would want to move into someone like
me who's even not already playing rust
who could not crony but i don't think
crowley would want to live with me why
would she live with me she could live a
fauna or a movement or whoever
hmm
uh ina doesn't have a homie and doesn't
play russell i don't know if she's wait
i know i know if never mind did she
mention if she's planning on playing
first did she did she mention something
on stream
oh kelly too
okay
guys remember when um i offered or we
were supposed to live together in
minecraft and then she just the moment i
built a beautiful house for us she moved
out remember remember remember remember
remember remember i'm not gonna have
that happen to me again i'm gonna have
her break my heart again
ina did say she would okay good yeah i
saw it in her schedule i just remembered
actually
didn't want to spoil it though but okay
she's starting i could tell her to live
in my house but
um
you know she's an artist
would she want to live in this highly
artistic modern architectural perfect
house
would she
of course she would ha ha ha
what is this
oh what
can't afford
oh this is all with scraps
[Music]
maybe she'll improve it you know
i think it's
it's decent the the roofing is just kind
of awkward here and there but i think
the high ceiling is
beautiful
she can feed the house yeah i hope she
would
you can put a sign oh yeah
wait what was i trying to make before
that a chair a chair
why can i not make this
ah
what
how
am i doing it wrong i'm doing it wrong
oh wait the chair is here
what
no path what does that mean
i have to research it what you mean i
have to go from the top to the bottom
like this
watched it
well i do have to learn this kind of
stuff all of this anyway huh
wait
scraps
of 17 do you have any i think i have a
few more
a few more [\h__\h] stairs
uh
i think i saw more
huh
wait what
i'm out of scraps i guess we have to go
look yeah
look at some markets
all right i guess that's what we're
gonna do
i will leave the important stuff
let me leave this here
on the bear rack i'm gonna place that
leaving this here leaving this here
the rest
i shall bring
uh
hmm maybe i should place it upstairs
might be more comfortable upstairs
[Music]
oh yeah
why not okay can sit by the fire that's
actually
cozy
yeah
like a fur
uh
carpet
what is this
hello who the [\h__\h] is it
someone knocked right i'm not going
to
you have a key you have a key
hello
yeah i know i left it at home i fixed my
lagging i don't know i was just
restarting the game basically i think
oh okay nice where'd you get this new
armor it looks cool oh i made it out of
bones
the bones of my enemies
look like a like a chief
i am i'm a chief of of kfp yes that's
true my intention look at are you
looking at my place i upgraded
everything to wood and i made a
workbench yeah i died once
uh
yeah the funniest thing happened ame i
um
i was on my way back home and i was on a
run
against the helicopter
and then i couldn't take cover anywhere
so the helicopter started shooting and
then i thought logging out closing the
game would be the best idea so i did
that but uh
i died anyway so i learned my lesson
yeah when you log out your body like
goes to sleep on the ground
it was a panic situation you know
i won't do it again now i know
i'm glad you got your stuff back right
yeah i did i did uh but actually when i
woke up when i locked back in
i woke up somewhere completely different
it didn't give me the choice to go to my
bag
uh and then i was killed
by it's because you were logged out uh i
was killed by something else and then i
respawned in my body bag
in my
in my sleeping bag although body bag is
fitting in that case and then i
and then i got myself yeah and and now
now i'm gonna go look for some scraps
because i need to build more things
okay
what are you doing i'm gonna i'm gonna
make a button so a button
okay have fun aren't you doing a member
stream tonight
whatever
maybe
i saw it in your schedule
i didn't know actually that you could
have this like type of wood house it
looks nice you didn't know
oh i i i'm teaching
already
i'm gonna go look for scratch
wait so how do you how do you like rust
it's decent i like
minecraft more maybe
[Laughter]
but maybe
i don't know build more stuff with
minecraft i think i'll do at least the
second episode because you know need to
do my get my money's worth
oh
but when your mouth opens yeah it's like
a 40 game
yeah yeah what the [\h__\h] okay
oh look he's a cafe chicken
yeah you're watching over me you weren't
when i was dying being attacked by a
helicopter thanks for nothing
i don't think she heard that
it was on sale two weeks ago is that why
everybody like
got it so suddenly
you know when i was screaming for amy
i'm honest she didn't come around what
the [\h__\h]
okay are we going to the same place or
should i go like here
wait is that what story or what what is
that what huh
did she make that one
was that not the convenience store
it's i'm a store i'm a store
wait the convenience store is uh is it
this one a shop
did we go that far oh i thought we came
from here ah
[Music]
okay so
uh we're going we're going here
i think
now the green one uh
oh oh this place
can go there
and seven
and and and
and ah this place that's the ah okay
it goes on
beautiful weather today
[Music]
it's already so late man i've been
playing for three and a half hours wood
what
you guys today i kind of want to
stay up late because
at the shittiest time possible at
4 00 am something
they're releasing house of the dragon
in like german speaking countries
but it's like a terrible time i don't
i don't know if i
can or want
because i'll be tired like actually i've
been falling asleep
um at earlier times these days
and uh
yeah it's gonna be every monday at like
four something
terrible timing so i guess probably what
i should do is go to bed and then
watch it after waking up
is it already out in or is it
simultaneous is it already out in other
countries or is it simultaneous and
that's why it's such a shitty time for
us
wait where am i
where's my sign there
it is simultaneous okay yeah otherwise
it wouldn't make sense
huh
you know for a little bit i was even
considering doing like a weekly watch
along but that would take up a slot
every week and yeah
i mean i could do two two short streams
on that day but i don't know
i was considering it but at the same
time i feel a bit awkward watching like
scenes with you guys
twitter space it i don't know i think
it's i think
i would enjoy it the most just
not needing to do any commentary on it
just enjoy it quietly
i guess
so i guess i'm just gonna watch it alone
so where's my stuff
[Music]
what is
cattle beans chocolate bar
i'm looking for scraps man
are there scraps in these
uh
boxes usually
i don't remember
what is this
pickles
oh i like pickles
outside are the crates ah okay okay
well but
but if i eat the tuna can i make a a
lamp of tuna
with the remains
a lot of food yeah but i don't
need it that much right now
i guess i should save food though for
the future when i need it
okay let's loot some stuff
there's one here
yes
weapon flashlight
that's kind of what i needed man
thanks
oh yeah
perfecto
so i can attach that to a weapon it said
interesting
can i not attach it to my head
what am i hearing
i hear footsteps
freaking me out ah
not you again you little [\h__\h]
no
i think i got everything unless there's
something on the roof maybe
how do i get to the roof again
[Music]
oh wait there's something here
okay okay
break the bows okay
wait i'm gonna kill it because it's
freaking me out
come here
oh yeah a booty shot
gonna take you apart let's go
you're so cute i don't want to kill you
but i have to
sorry
military crate in the office
military great oh this thing ah
see i don't have an eye for that yet
smg body
i got a weapon and i have a full
inventory but i can recycle stuff yeah
yeah yeah yeah
but you guys said
what did you guys say
what do you guys say about
i should do weapon part parts of a new
gun
try dragging it onto the shotgun is this
the shotgun
shotgun is okay
[Music]
what else are we doing in here
where was i supposed to go
garage i got a garage door
oh you guys seem excited about the
garage door
how do i get to the roof
oh wait there's one more
our stop sign
i don't need that
i don't need that ah here
recycle
doo doo doo doo doo
why does it take so long should i press
shift what
scraps
[Music]
wait i eat something i'll eat something
crunchy
[Music]
i actually need to eat more anyway
okay
throw away hampshire no need everything
so now we perfect shortcut now we're
gonna recycle
we recycle this
was it no
i don't know what to recycle this stuff
what else is there something else i
should recycle
um
throw the torch you have a flashlight
now
really
press f for flashlight on the shotgun
okay tech trash and somebody said it's
also used for crafting though but okay
what's this
oh shotgun trap oh
i got a trap guys
road sign
do i have to know you mean the one that
was in the
in the
box
48 let's go
thank you i'm satisfied with that to be
honest um just wondering if i missed
some
i had this this i missed
[Music]
well
i can plan stuff i don't have to do it
on my own building the plastic box
what
wha
what a barrel
you mean the one that dropped that uh
picks up
oh
yo
it's not the one that catches it but it
contains it
that's good too now
okay
am i done
oh yeah that was uh
stop signs okay let me let me
recycle that and then we go
back
back and forth back and forth
all right
input turn on
oh
wow
105 scrubs yay
that's probably nothing for like
like
um
rust players that play more than me
i don't need the gunpowder you'll find
plenty of guns we'll need to craft gun
parts if i was a whole gun
oh the bot is only the body oh
[Music]
okay
yeah i was thinking like if i play again
next week um i'm gonna play it during a
time where all the japanese members are
online because that's a good time for me
generally to stream anyway like i stream
a lot during that time so
maybe we get some
live japan members interactions
maybe not oh
oh
i don't know but can i recycle that
i think ina was planning to play
once next week pretty early on too so i
was thinking maybe
maybe
if i overlap with ina we can like
hang out
i don't know
yeah
she's doing uh if i saw correctly she
was gonna do a stream
at an unusual time
if you ever hear matzo you just run you
think she's that aggressive
she's gonna kill everybody she sees is
that what she does oh crazy crazy no no
no
okay we're gonna go
um i guess
is there any more like that
anymore like those supermarkets
do i just go back to i think somewhere
here
my home
follow the towers home towers
oh those electric thingies
i guess they do lead to my home huh
they're all crazy but you know what i
feel like that's actually
pretty noisy like in in minecraft you
could have done the same but everybody
was like holding back and
too friendly i mean piccolo template did
some did some pranks maybe but still
can i take that tarp please
oh wait that doesn't do anything
um
yeah i don't know in general when i say
i don't like pvp i mean like stuff like
oh free
er like in
like world of warcraft i would never
play in a pvp server because just like
no i don't want to be always scared of
being suddenly attacked especially if
you're a healer because
no was that that wasn't the heal that
was a
in world of warcraft i was playing a
magician mage
okay
oh
[Laughter]
uh
but still like i mean i was super young
so i wasn't like
such a gamer yet
so i feel like if i would ever go into
the pvp server i would always
immediately be killed
by everybody
i i don't
i want to enjoy the game normally
without always being scared about that
kind of stuff so pvp was never my thing
but
i don't know we'll see how it goes in
the rest i guess
if
i'll continue playing
we'll see
if i stream it then in the future it
will probably always be like earlier
times because
because
i think chances are higher to run into
someone if i stream during
japanese prime time
than european primetime because no one
plays during european prime time
we're back home safely
should i put the tank inside
or outside
if i put it outside then somebody can
steal it no
if you stay away from supply drops you
shouldn't worry about uh-huh uh-huh
outside make a balcony
i don't know about milk it sounds
complicated right now
i'll put it oh here's a nice
spot for it
put it here
there's no water inside though
progress contain any inventory i don't
know eventually we can put water in
there
battle royale
at the end everybody's just gonna kill
each other
interesting
uh what was i trying to make with the
scraps a chair right
but first before i make a chair i need
to learn all the other things right
yeah yeah yeah okay so let's put the
stuff that
um
i can use
for building stuff
inside my inventory
oh yeah i need to need to put this
somewhere too
ah
because i have seeds too
wow
i wonder how much i can plant then
a little garden for kiwawa where where
do i put
it doesn't have to be on grass huh can
it be on wood but okay i have some space
here
i'll put it here put it inside
need water to plant oh okay
is it okay to put it inside too
i'll at least put it down i'll put it
down here
okay
okay nice too
now inside they need like oh [\h__\h]
can i take it
i can't take it anymore i think
somebody said put it inside
hammer
uh
how do i
have i used a hammer again
i hold it
for how long nothing is happening
however
ah it just opens
it's it
[Music]
what if i put windows there
is that considered light
[\h__\h] hell why is everything so
permanent
nothing in my life is permanent
friendships everything just goes away
this game is too permanent
lamps lamps work
well for now i'm not using it anyway so
let's not worry about it i don't have
water anyway we'll think about it when i
am able to use it actually okay let's go
upstairs
and try to make some progress with my
building
open tech tree
what should we begin with i think this
can i make it yes oh unlock wow
oh now i can make a small watercatcher
and a fridge oh
bucket helmet
water barrel now you already have that i
know
i will unlock this
what am i trying to unlock the chair
but the path's different
i need the fridge
[Music]
mailbox
to accept notes
i'm unlocked to chill let's go
and the table well let's see we should
also unlock something here maybe
oh
ah yeah
a tank
or should i unlock something else
weapons maybe first
tools
i can't afford this one
a lot of scraps already
sad
yeah okay but i'll make a chair
wow can i
ah i'm making a chair guys whoa
i can make a mailbox oh
i can make a fridge oh my god but i
don't have electricity how's that gonna
work
i'll have electricity
magic
it actually works
that's that's uh
that makes no sense
make a sign too
medium small okay medium is good
means good
is that grilled oh
well
should i make that
significant amounts of food
maybe not make everything right now i
don't know yes yes yes
i have a large sun oh where did i put it
where did i put that
well the more signs the merrier oh
that's it
huge wooden sun
how big is huge
i'll put that back
i put down the fridge
where should we put the fridge up
upstairs
well now i'm sleeping
here at home but i cannot change that
yeah
maybe here i don't know
should i or upstairs
in the corner
there's this awkward corner here let's
put it here
freight
looks disgusting okay so if i put this
in here it's not gonna decay
amazing guess i'll put even though this
doesn't have to be in the fridge
it's food so what the hell
at least it has a place to go
food will not spoil
ah put chair
next to it
oh my god
[Music]
is there no fine-tuning rotation like
really slightly rotating
oh wait there is it's just moving around
on your own
okay
mount
i'm setting
wow that is so comfortable oh it really
heals you
[Music]
eating
if she fits
she sits
successfully
nice okay i'm done uh i'm gonna get off
of this chair
how do i
jump okay
okay now it's getting dark in here again
i want more lamps
and there you go
uh what else we need more scraps again
but i can also put the mailbox outside
oh she kept the door open oh no
oh my god
drama llama
drama alert i don't know how i'm placing
this
here
that works
open aha
the door
okay
do i have anything else other the sign
can i do you draw on it after placing it
[Music]
yeah no one dares to enter anyway
how do you turn on the flashlight on the
gun i feel like somebody told me
i forgot
[Music]
f
oh
[Music]
cool
oh quick craft oh
machete
okay what i
would like to make is a water catcher so
um
i want to go get more scraps i guess
because
was that what i needed
uh
water
and ah but i also need that stupid tarp
wait no i have everything i need just
need tarps
[Music]
a-type
can i buy it somewhere oh can i craft it
good question
[Music]
hi
hi hi hi
um i guess we're doing the signs when
there's lights outside
sometime
okay
i don't know i don't really want to go
when it's dark outside but okay we have
a light
are we going to the same place again
g uh
here should we go there again
well can we buy a tarp
um
i
don't
see one
it's nice that it shows you what they
have though
if a rug
raw fish
along the road
[Music]
check if there are loot boxes see if
tarpon amish up
there's not
more than what it shows on the map
like if it says this is what it's in in
the store there's not
who's running are you a wolf
whoops okay shoot
don't be scared don't be scared
i killed it
where's your friend
sorry
where's my musician oh there it is i
thought it had no more thank god
there you go
uh i thought i thought its friend was
coming but no i think we could
okay
it's gone
who wants to challenge me huh
this phoenix will not back down in fear
i will not run away
nothing can scare me
both hat i can make a wolf hat
really
oh
a wolf skull
wolf it looks so good the image looks so
good i think i'm going to eat lasagna
today
i think i want to eat some lasagna today
oh i hear helicopter
don't see it super far away
i don't see it anywhere
yeah it's almost monday
i'll probably eat it pasta midnight
anyway
so then it's monday
um oh it's down there okay i think
i can make it to the supermarket before
it sees me it won't see me anyway it's
going somewhere else
[Music]
yeah we're good
it's not gonna happen again
airdrop look out the sky but
there's nothing
spring rolls and chicken pakora ah ah
[\h__\h] i fought for a moment you wrote the
typo but i actually i saw that like
isn't that indian food because i saw it
on the menu for from an indian
restaurant and i was like
so funny wait
that's so funny
oh
i want to waste my ammo on you
um
i should be fast now though because now
it's coming my way
whose house is dead
need to move my axe
close combat oh don't go there it hurts
oh it's getting pretty close [\h__\h] i can
let you see it yeah
um
die joe boo
[Music]
i can fill my water thingy with that
who keeps on restocking this
convenience store
okay it's gone it's gone it's gone
not that
uh
wait there's no i don't think credits
didn't refresh yet
uh
don't think it refreshed anything
[Music]
maybe this one
i didn't drop any crates on me
but okay
stone barricade and some scraps
check the back rims
roger
there's only one room though
don't see anything
maybe up here
on the table was there something on the
table
time to go somewhere else yeah i want to
where do we go
where should i go
where do i go
i hear
a [\h__\h] bear
uh
there's a crate on the map oh i can see
it
is that that's it but it's so far and
it's locked
can you open that
l10
why why l10
i can open it
the time block ah
why did you but is that is that a safe
zone
or is it danger zone oh there's another
abandoned supermarket here too though
interesting
elton
funny
it's safe mostly okay
should i go there really i have a bad
feeling
but okay
um
more water so much water should i bring
this back home first i know
i feel like i should
if i lose it i'm gonna cry
yeah
okay
p
nine
nine nine nine p nine
okay
this way we got some wood
so i'm not coming back home to
empty-handed hey
hey
there you go
rust is a game about losing i've heard
so much about everybody like oh i lost
my horse oh i lost this and that oh my
house disappeared uh
no
i lost everything where am i scraps oh
what is this about everybody losing
their scraps
why is everybody losing their scraps
though
mmm green berries
ah gambling oh that's what they mean i
thought they disappeared i mean i guess
i disappeared in a different way huh
not gonna happen to me
unless they have blackjack
well i don't understand this whole
gambling thing how does that work do
they have actually like games like in
the casino
they have blackjack
like jack that's that's the one i can
play right that's the only one i can
play
the one where you go to like 21 or so
it's a wheel huh fun
i mean
you know i understand why they would go
there sounds like fun somehow like a
game in the game
where's my what
here
gambling addiction
return of blackjack
yeah
because i can't read like poker cards
and stuff
i don't know the value and i will
probably never understand
but uh for blackjack i you know it's not
it's not difficult
it kind of tells you at least
at least in digital form it tells you
what to do kind of
should increase ah lower everything
because i was lagging so much like my my
avatar was lagging so much but
i can maybe off-screen experiment a
little bit with how much i can raise it
without it lagging around
but for now this will
do what
here
for now this will have to do
poker pretty easy huh
what is that
a car push mount i can drive is this
like gta or what i wanted to play gta 5
by the way at some point in my stream
you can drive cars round the most cars
let's go
yeah why not i don't know
sounds fun where am i going what the
[\h__\h]
here
i feel like i
kept on walking off path
why it's like gta man
i got lost again
no way i'm right here
what do you mean
no i chose the wrong thing didn't i
where do i actually live
it looks so different right now
oh wait it's there oh i didn't realize
there was a road so close to
home
okay
we've arrived and now it's daytime so we
can do the sign i don't know how it
works but we're gonna do it oh look at
that roof
[Music]
i can put water in here
i'll open
put this in here
using the icon on the right what
the icon on the
what i can do you mean
this is not the right
thing
ah
give
if
ah it's working
[Music]
and this i'll drink now
let's drink it
how fast does that
like refill do i have to feel bad about
taking it
i mean
have some good containers here might as
well want to use them
also put this back
put some wood
into the wood shelter
now you're thinking refresh
it come on it's how much it's refilled
yep
there's a yep
right above my house close the door
bye bye
go away
was it flying that low
what
huh
it's burning
get out
no
what did it like fall on my because it
disappeared
[Music]
what
what happened
did it drop a bomb or did it fall on the
ground
what is this
no
my roof is okay though this is um how
can i can i
can i like does this can i help getting
rid of this
oh my god
[\h__\h] it i don't have a bucket i just
have a lot of um
canister
water
i'll go grab water
can i take water
that is
this is mean and it's way too much what
the [\h__\h]
how do i take the
water how do i take it salt water yeah i
don't care ah
doesn't matter
ah
i'll get back up
i'm not gonna drink it
no no no
is my house gonna burn down
yeah i know i thought it doesn't work
oh can i do it
right click
ah
annie any water will do i just wanna
well 5 000 milliliters how am i carrying
this
oh it's gonna be okay
okay okay okay
oh boy watch the cross [\h__\h]
what the hell
how am i jumping so carelessly with five
thousand milliliters of water
and how the [\h__\h] do i get back up
oh that's my house
my house is on fire
i guess
the future it might come in handy do i
have the materials for it
uh
wait don't i need a blueprint for that
no he's making it he's making it
now i have two of those
just walk around i tried
stairs wait no wait that's not how it
works it's not
put this here
uh
close the button i don't want to make a
mistake there we go
steps
i think by now the one the fire is
probably gone anyway
so didn't even need that water i guess
huh
um
how do i build this [\h__\h] here
wait that's not even my house i thought
that was my house is it my house
no it is my house
oh walk around where
it goes down here
[Music]
see it just goes down again
i have to go so far
i can't go up here can i maybe
oh
come on come on
yes yes
yes you can do it don't let your dreams
be dreams
i've acquired the skill of climbing like
a boss
my fire is gone
yep
so the water how do i empty it
right click yeah
okay
um
what did i do that for you guys should
have told me to just leave it
leave it like those kitchen fires
hammer to fix oh i have to fix it
here
74 686
it doesn't look so broken
100.
yeah i didn't really do
damage
86 it seems normal maybe the 74 one
wait
oh
one was that
this one
how do i
how do you reach it
no
not that
one that one
that's stability not help from the
inside okay that makes sense
[Music]
i have to fix it
this one
done wait that's not yeah wait how do
you fix [\h__\h]
[Music]
i did
okay
yeah the strong house
was good to upgrade it into proper wood
oh okay
uh
let me put seats in here
ah
okay i'll eat this
rabbit i feel like i heard a frog
inspiring
okay i need food anyway
you have to keep like stuff in your
house to not have a decoy but what about
your body like will my hunger go down
while i'm when i'm
locked out
because that's that sounds [\h__\h]
annoying
i can find the frog really
no
you're hibernating
you're fine okay
um
okay let's go get water from mummaine
before she notices
and there was a
really shocking
situation there
it just drops a [\h__\h] bump on me when
it saw me like for the window which i
don't even understand how it saw me
because i didn't see it
and it didn't fly that low i think
makes no sense dad is cheating honestly
that's just [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
is it
how do i um
uh take
oh it filled up completely
it fell so fast
just just a little bit just just a
little bit just
[Laughter]
[Music]
at least i'm not taking everything yeah
she's my horritory kohai yeah i'm her
horritory senpai so can't i don't i
don't hear anybody complaining it should
be fine
yeah she wouldn't mind
it's just water
[Music]
i'm putting this
uh where's my house
i'll put this in here and then
we are butchery prepared for everything
hmm huh
a little bit more
yeah
could i build a wall to stop piccolo
from taking her water
what
[Music]
sad
i'll put that here in case i need more
stuff can i
what is this
ah stone barricade made out of stones
how do i use that
i just have one i guess you would have
like several ones and then place them
like a wall
right now it seems rather
useless
it cannot be removed yeah like pretty
much everything in this [\h__\h] game
i'll just put it in here for now i have
no space i need a new one a new
thingy
okay
ah
so the snare
i don't need to drink water
uh bush open
how do you drink one like this
always important to hydrate guys
[Music]
that's right i forgot sign time
where did i put the sign again this time
sign
this is the large one
huge how huge are we talking
oh yeah that is huge wow
how
how do i place
what
uh
how
closer
ah
but i want it to be higher
what
why is this so stupid
why can't it be easier oh
i wanna i want it to be up there
that's way too long make a ladder
[Music]
fine wait i think i have one
didn't i have one
you guys saw one
oh
yeah i found it somewhere before
i show can i even put the thing on the
roof actually although the ladder is
maybe too short for that
well let's just put it as high as
possible
um
if it if it would let me
and won't let me now i'm too close or
what
i'm gonna shoot this [\h__\h] ladder
though how do i take the ladder back
and now the ladder's in the way
wake up there we go okay at least
something can be picked up
what am i supposed to do
yes [\h__\h] scuffed i paid 40 bucks for
this
yeah
the basic rules are so [\h__\h] stupid
but i'm gonna i'm gonna get used to it
you know i'm not gonna complain about it
no no no no i have an adult oh
i i don't know how high that is because
i can't zoom out
i think there was a field of view thingy
[Music]
where was it
this
higher yeah
but it doesn't
no that's still just in the middle
that's still just in the middle
a little temporary foundation
that's a waste
of my precious wood but okay oh wait
that's not that's not it um
why is it so stupid
stupid game
so unnecessary
uh what am i building oh yeah this [\h__\h]
oh i sure
i mean i guess that could even be used
as a balcony maybe i don't know
if
if it lets me place it here here here
maybe
yeah
oh should it be closer
just in case
would that interfere if i put it here
would that interfere
this is good
i have a good feeling
ha
ha we're so young
how much wood did that use
e press e
no
okay [\h__\h] it
it does trigger me
very hard
is this a joke
there must be no there must be another
way how do you do this
i'm here
what what's your problem now
use a florida foundation
i forgot how they're gone
um
[Music]
my wood
mama mia
it's getting dark now i can't [\h__\h]
ride on my side again
my will still still bright enough
hi
you're not telling me that the floor is
interfering right maybe it's just too
big i don't know
what what what what what what what what
what
is the matter
[Music]
it would be the perfect size man
don't get it what if it's if it's the
small the medium one
they have a medium one
i want this one but okay i'll try with
the small that's so small
that's so small
oh that's tiny no
maybe in the front at least and i'll
figure this out at some point
maybe for now
she see this one it will let me place a
pretty up high without being close to it
what the [\h__\h]
ah
how do i draw on it
that's a good spot yeah
a roof problem
i will not let people insult my roof
anymore my roof is not a problem okay so
rude
yeah
sleepy time
also my house is here can i make a
permanent mark for my house
what is this
i do have to to remember it
people can be so roof
yeah hi donkey monkey
no you're just gonna walk by my office
say nothing not even
look at me
wow
i love you i'm sweet
i love you too
now you're coming in
[Music]
cute
okay okay
what do you mean insanity
mouth
i wish uh we could let nighttime go by
like faster yeah
like in minecraft
how do you see who else is online by the
way
can you see that
i'd put bars on my windows
all right
will that keep the helicopter ups from
shooting me
next time will that help
was it here no i guess it was the uh
with something else
oh
boy there you go
how many
couple
my house is too small for it to matter
too small for wood
check phobics farm during the night it's
right outside your windows
why does it like light up nicely or what
fubuki's
house at night
uh which one was it is it like isn't it
far away
the light size is her form
that's over there
well my my torture goes so far wow
oh
why it's so sparkly is that normal is
that just a graphics bug
what kind of farm is it
disco farm
huh
it's normal
oh it's supposed to sparkle i should
have used my
binoculars is this called balls
disco party party
wow
this gives me vaporwave vibes
do school bars on dlc
wait really i saw some what was it like
a summertime dlc or something like that
where you can build a pool and stuff but
if only one person in the server has a
dlc
do the others
uh
not have to have it in order to see it
can you see it without having the same
dlc because i think in minecraft you
know you have to have all the same mods
and all that but
yeah i have a good view to the disco
ball
only need the dlc to craft it
oh
i see
interesting
okay so now you guys have to tell me how
i ride on that do i need to put my
ladder up there
do i need to get like super up close
my my
my
thingy
yeah
like here ah [\h__\h] because it's right
above the door i can't like
get like right in front of it
let me try does this work
paint sign
wow
oh
but i
[Music]
i don't know
maybe for now just my name okay i can
fix it later or
whoa
bigger brush please
oh
wow
you can get really creative with this
oh [\h__\h] that was too big
but the color is that all the colors
[Music]
okay
and
um
i'm left handed but i use my mouse with
the
right hand so it's not the best
to make a masterpiece
wait i can i could use my tablet right i
can draw something nice because if i
just move the the game window over to my
tablet
my wacom tablet
my cintiq then i could literally like
draw a masterpiece
oh maybe i'll do that like at some point
okay
[Music]
well for now i think now it is clear who
lives here right everybody knows kfp
everybody knows
but
are you telling me that in order to get
the big sign to work here
i need to get rid of the roof first
[Music]
i won't do that today
you could raise the roof
[Music]
change the roof
i'll think about it another time i guess
yeah
but we need to make this place nice so
that we can convince ina to live here
too
but for now oh yeah for now the last
thing i'm gonna do
is um
write a note i guess
you guys told me energy left somewhere
close
where do you guys know the
the thingy
on the roof yeah i wouldn't mind putting
it on the roof either
eat ten
are you really
like are you just saying that for the
funny
or
is she actually does she actually upset
oh oh the bar is the bars yes yes yes
yes
i made bars
[Music]
hi
one two
three
four
okay at least this floor has them now
it's the middle of the ocean oh
oh
oh great
i want to build a ship
okay
where's she where does she live
n808 for nina
oh so close bye okay
[Music]
i'm coming for you
orenzu lavu
i didn't know she was so close close the
door ah i i closed it didn't i
ah it's fine even if it's not closed i'm
just gone a little moment
rust collapse
i don't know it's not my
favorite game but
could play it a few times
have some some fun moments hopefully
and then move on
yeah
i'll give it a few chances to entertain
me
and you guys
yeah is this nina's house
is that nana's house
that looks incredible
oh there's miku say about oh okay no
surprise either holy [\h__\h] wow
isn't that a big sign she just painted
it
silver
oh those doors
how can you make fancy doors like that
ah
well then where's the melody you know
that is when you see it
and i went past it though
maybe
[Music]
look for another house around here
is it that one
that looks orange
ah no that's a [\h__\h] what no that's
something no that's that's not it
it's in the woods
okay
i have to find it
for completion's sake
he's right next to mikko's
right next to it
hoisty can i take this horse wait it's
not a horse
is it
yeah you're not a hawaii sorry
sorry for assuming your
um
uh animal
type
is this it
how would i know
you understand species i yeah how would
i know this is dennis house
this looks like my minecraft house
you guys said i would know but that
i expected something orange or really
cute or something
where is her mailbox and you said she
has a mailbox
ah
well i mean
that's
another house with a c
house
good english energy
wait i don't see a mailbox is it hidden
behind the car
oh [\h__\h]
was i have i been lied to
or can i store it in the car no
then a house yeah
nene house
no it's not here
oh
airplane airplane
drop box behind the car
build a mailbox do i have to stop for it
i'm gifting her a note and a mailbox oh
but i don't have i currently don't have
the stuff for it
the front of the car
am i
blind i don't see a mailbox
am i blind
is it is it that thing
well that doesn't look like a mailbox
what is that
this thing
am i allowed to look at this
push the car
it only has
a submit oh
ah i guess that's it okay how do i write
on my notes
uh
do i write on it after putting it in
[Music]
you guys told me to write a note i don't
have anything in particular to say
though
ah
yo uh
should i write in
like japanese but like i know that
hiragana don't work i guess so
[Music]
um uh
don't they have um
one year anniversary like what
at one year two year
like this month
was it already
i don't think
is it next
week
two weeks ago i feel like there was
something but isn't there also an
anniversary next week whose anniversary
is next week
i saw something on the calendar
someone's the anniversary has castle
it was crazy there's so many
anniversaries it's so confusing okay
well hmm
[Music]
forever
okay i wrote your new song cover was
great i also started playing rust
starting from today so let's play
together my house is next to luna
senpai's house
i love you
orange forever
so maggots
okay
see my house already looks better than
hers though
not bad for day one in rest
what do you say guys oops
sure stopped by uh no wait it wasn't
there wait we're so close to the
abandoned supermarket oh she's also
camping huh but she has a car
yeah
yeah i guess so that that that might be
true that might be true okay
i'll give you that
let's see what do we have
oh
where's that
oh anti-radiation suit
is that really good
so far i've had i felt no effects from
the
radiation nice
good yeah
[Music]
is that what muna was wearing
oh more diving goggles
i don't really need two
i mean i could gift it to someone oh
container does not accept items [\h__\h]
scrapple shorts
shorts but i can't wear them with my
current outfit right
yeah that's lame
i want to layer them but okay
[Music]
oh i can recycle them okay rope
scrap
and
outside i think
outside i think we got everything else
take a look at the roof
under armour you can wear them with oh
[\h__\h] and at the end i just jumped hoping
that i would get up faster but when i
jump it
brings me back to the ground
who was this
floor triangle grill
perfect for placing above a large
furnace
interesting
sky michigan
destroy mask destroy
everything
oh what was that rock i got a frog let's
go
[Music]
oh i can make my place even comfier
okay while we're here
let's bring some food home too maybe i
don't know
what uh
oops
[Music]
such water
amazing
can't stop winning this girl
okay i will
recycle
[Music]
what do we have
i can put
it's not a body but i can put this into
the recycling right and then we put
rock nice
the stop signs
the metal pop
green box in the office
okay
i'll check
metal pipes
that's all i can see
shorts
too wow i can recycle that too cool
a little green
ah
another body
okay cool
huh
did that put it in
i right clicked
i guess it did
zooming but my body is zooming scared me
i thought someone
was coming on a horse try i'm about to
kill me or something okay
we got some good stuff from that yeah
[Music]
now
i think
we're gonna go back for real and
uh
that's it for today it's like midnight
yeah
i
will say
this probably will not be my last time
you know even just for the sake of
collabing with others
is everybody's playing this now
i hope you will bear with me for a few
more rush streams
and besides that
uh oh i have a special stream next week
a hand cam stream
oh thank you for the pinky
i i have a a creative hand
hand cam stream for next week planned
and
by the way besides that we're gonna
continue with
uh tunic finish tunic last episode and
continue cult of the kfp lamp
and
uh
no it does not involve hostile
at least
it shouldn't but i mean we can
forcefully involve it don't have to
though
um
when is it next what's your bathroom oh
i don't wanna like do that so quickly
immediately
um
because i feel like
yeah
it's better to space these kind of
things out a bit more
so maybe
i don't know
in november maybe
did you even buy a new glue gun yeah
i'm not
i don't remember maybe i did
i did i did i remember i remember gluing
my shoes back together before
[Music]
before
my italy trip
i remember
i glued
some shoes together which ended up
breaking again in italy
so
it didn't last very long
i was able to pick that up
which one is the hemp is this the hemp
no
is this a hemp
sam
that's a hemp seed
[Music]
which am i blind
am i picking it up
emphasis oh it just comes out of this
club
okay
nice
yeah sorry that the beginning was
scuffed before the not the beginning
half of the stream was scuffed with the
lagging
and
voice chats and stuff
at least the lagging we figured out a
voice chat i'm sure i'll figure it out
because that no we already figured it
out it was just a ps5 controller i
always forget that that counts as a
microphone but every time i have it
connected
it's uh it automatically changes all my
microphones everywhere
what the [\h__\h] i wonder what it sounded
like
at least it didn't change in lbs but i
think it changed it in discord and in
and in the game um
for the ramp on that not not now
not now
oh wait let's refill the
can you recycle the containers for the
water like these ones
because i don't think i need that many
randomly
in my
inventory
i'll drink this one
[Music]
oh
the activator windows didn't work
but that reminds me of something
something that i keep on deactivating
but it it's always still there
ah
i forgot [\h__\h]
never mind but it's really annoying
anyway would you guys call this a
successful first rush stream i i i guess
so like we did a lot holy [\h__\h]
i i learned fast don't i
yeah
fast learner takanasi kiwawa
very successful yeah yeah yeah sorry i
was probably not as entertaining as
usual but so you know i don't know
i don't know
not feeling so
much like an entertainer today but i
hope it was still
fun
and
yeah we had some interactions with ahmed
at
least and some mysterious person
we will
never find out who that was
protected for four days okay i will not
log in again for four days
[Music]
i'll just leave this hold on let me put
down this oh it's like it's lit like uh
lengthy so it's like perfect for this
narrow path
wow
oh it has the rust logo on it
yeah
and i i think
i got i'll i'm planning to stream
tomorrow so i think i'll make the
schedule
uh
[Music]
now
yeah i guess i'll make it now
and then upload it for you guys
so look out for it on twitter and in a
community board
[Music]
gulp
yeah finally his new schedule finally
because we didn't have one this week
and last week um
okay then everybody uh it's so late so
i'm not gonna read subjects but tomorrow
tomorrow i'm gonna read them so that's
why it's my squad
okay
and in german we say
ah freedom
out downstairs
oh okay uh because of the windows oh
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
let me
let me hide
am i am i good to log out am i good to
go if i log out here
the door is closed right
yes
i'll log out here i hope nobody sees my
body
coconut
yeah
ah
when i wake up i can watch the first
episode of the new game of thrones
house of the dragon
oh i'm excited i wish i wish i could
watch before going to sleep but
yeah
[\h__\h] that
you know we are so blessed house of the
dragon this month starts this month and
then next month they start that spin-off
from from lord of the rings oh my god i
mean
i've heard so many opinions like it's
gonna be [\h__\h] at least for house of the
dragon
you know what my mom said
i
this was so funny to me
follow the following conversation
transpired yesterday with my mommy on
whatsapp
i was like
like she wrote to me
that she really really enjoyed uh my
playthrough of cult of the lamp she said
it's a perfect game for you it's so good
and i'm like yeah thank you um tunic was
great too though yeah
and then and she says
house of dragons is going to be a woke
[\h__\h]
and i'm like
what does that mean wait that's such a
silver word but i don't even know the
exact meaning of that
and then she says wheels of time as well
amazon killed it just like it's doing it
just like how they are going to do it
with the lord of the rings prequel i'm
like mommy you're using zuma words and i
don't even understand just wait for it
and she says
yeah just wait i guess but my my
expectations are at zero
whoa [\h__\h] that sounds positive but she
used it in a negative sense so i guess
it means something bad like it's gonna
be bad
but i find it so funny that she uses a
zuma word that i who am whom i am
younger than her i don't even understand
she must have learned it from you guys
or something
two more words yeah
where did you pick that up man did she
even use it correctly
okay
she just picked that up from some super
somewhat probably from you guys so
i heard it but
i heard it before
yeah it's
she used it in a negative way so she's
not excited for it but i'm excited for
it i feel like you know
people are like too
too critical
of it just because
the last
season of game of thrones was maybe not
that good
but come on
it's better than all the other [\h__\h] i'm
currently watching
probably i just assume they definitely
put a lot of money into it i'm sure
so let's give it a chance man let's talk
about it then
yeah for me like my
my standards are pretty low so
i'll probably be extremely entertained
you have bad taste [\h__\h] you
i thought you would meet
i thought you and me when we were we had
a pain you know but you liked me now
you're insulting like this
why
why must you do this
i like cats so what it doesn't mean i
have generally
shitty taste i say i love lord of the
rings right that's a good taste i just
have as i said
lose like
low like
the default level of what you need to
offer to me to entertain me i i can
enjoy shitty things
for it being shitty you know how people
enjoy scuffed games and like
kusogas saw games shitty games
that's it's the same thing basically and
i i like to see the the good side
of people and of
tv shows and of games
oh you're getting my merch thank you
you like big bang theory no i mean
i watch it because like
it's just
you don't need to use your brain to
watch it and
it has
a few
few funny moments maybe sometimes but in
general i can tell you that
the big bang theory
there's a lot of moments where i'm also
like cringing and face palming because
it's kind of stupid often but i'm not
saying it's the perfect show that has no
issues and it's
yeah
the best show ever no no no no
no no not at all
but if i need to binge watch something
that i can fall asleep to then that's
something i i would maybe watch yeah
that's that's why i like always yeah
scrubs i love scrubs scrubs i i i tell
you scrubs
scrubs is something at least for um
scrubs the last one or two seasons maybe
were [\h__\h] but besides that scrubs is
great and i will proudly say
i'm a fan of scrubs for
my whole life
so there's a difference i make a
difference there in my brain too just
because i watch something
even if i watch it the second time
doesn't mean that i
think it's a great show
yeah
lastly subscribes doesn't count yeah
because that's that's like not even
scrubs
that's not even
the same show to be honest
another show where i will probably say
this is great is the office
or
handmaid's tale
um
[Music]
what else
uk or us ah
i've audit did i watch the uk one i
think i wanted to but i had no access to
it i watched the german one and the u.s
i'm not sure did i watch the uk one
probably not i know it's good but
community i
i don't know i like arrested development
better for example mm-hmm
friends friends i like
there's a german one yeah it's called
stromberg i think on it's on netflix but
i'm not sure if you can watch it in
another country but it's pretty good
like
it's it's a very good german version of
the office really
they have like
the same type of like characters in it
it's like a similar theme and all that
it's it's definitely meant to be like
the office
and
in i feel like the like normally i would
never watch german shows because they're
[\h__\h] but
i gave it a try for that one and i have
to say
it was it was really good it was really
funny
yeah that one's worth trying strong back
s-t-i-o-m-b-e-r-g
[Music]
yeah it's funny it's midnight yeah i
should go
i should go
eat my lasagna
what about it crowd ah yeah i didn't
watch that one i think uh that one's not
really available in all the services i
i have i think
wait the i.t crowd you mean right
oh is it i think maybe i
i tell it crowd
maybe i saw it recently and planned on
watching it
[Music]
i don't know okay i don't know why we
suddenly started talking about tv shows
because of house of the dragon but uh
yeah i'm gonna go now let's talk about
tv shows or like let's talk about house
of the dragon tomorrow
tomorrow by the time i stream
i'll be um
i'll be done watching it hopefully
okay
have a good rest you too guys thank you
for watching today
um
at least you get a little too go tangent
yeah
tomorrow tunic i forgot what was i
planning tomorrow
let me see
i'm hungry i'm so hungry oh my god
ah yeah i'm planning to finish tunic
tomorrow
on tuesday off
that's my plan
cult of the lamp on wednesday
yeah
nice pups
thanks
yeah
oh music
okay it goes all
bye bye everybody
whatever you're gonna do afterwards
this stream
do it well
do it with confidence
tomorrow
reading
oh yes
[Music]
she based
yeah sleep with confidence
yeah you should sleep with confidence
that's that's one thing that humans can
do very well
sleeping
at least normally unless you have like
um insomnia
well if that's the case i'm sorry
sleep harder yeah
bye-bye
[Music]
wow
do
[Music]
donkey wonky
i know the microphone is on
[Music]
iwa does everything on purpose
one more meow for the road i don't know
if she's gonna do it are you gonna meow
hmm
no
we're good
are you done meowing because you me out
so much you lost your voice
[Music]
she's cute
okay
[Music]
oh she did something like a meal
it's more like
[Music]
i hear a helicopter
better get out of the game
[Music]