[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
hello everybody sorry for the delay
oh
something urgent i'm sorry um
please forgive me you have to
you have to please please please
yeah okay so now that i'm forgiven
and we're playing a game called cult of
the lamb today because i know it looked
um maybe interesting also uh
window to the left to the left to the
left
window to the right to the right to the
right
okay
i don't
really know much of
what to expect
but
um and i don't know if it's difficult or
not
but let's hope that we're gonna have a
good time also obs does not want to
capture it for some reason
please
oh i should probably go in window mode
anyway
where's the mouse
what rory is the mouse i hate it when
the mouse just disappears
okay settings
i'm using a controller would you guys
say that that is the prefer oh there it
is that is the preferred method of
uh clap uh playing this borderless
wind.windowed
[Music]
oh wait where am i no i'm not here no no
no
yeah i did say that in the beginning so
i was like okay
oh wait now it's tiny
wait what
why is it so
i stopped going down there all the time
i didn't press okay or anything
i did what is oh
what is the a good solution why does it
keep on getting
so tiny i need glasses or something okay
this is is this 16 to nine
nine sixteen to nine
move my mouse why do you see my mouse
oh my god uh ah
maybe that's that nine nine nine
that this is yeah wait why is it so
small
what it doesn't really get bigger oh
that's good
it's still tiny though
[Music]
this this is actually
a comfortable size
can i can i do that am i allowed to
it says x except but it doesn't work
why
[Music]
no okay back i guess whatever it worked
so
that resolution is huge yeah but that at
least covers my screen somehow there's
still
some space on the edges but it covers it
decently
how big is your monitor i don't know
it's a normal size it's not that big but
i think it's like something about the
resolution
isn't it like uh
i don't know higher resolution monitors
even if they're the same
it inches size next to the other one
monitor with a lower resolution then
you know you know yeah then something
like i don't know same window size will
be smaller on the higher resolution
monitor than the other one right yeah
yeah yeah and the monitor i'm using is
probably 4k probably yeah
the other one not every one of my
monitors like when i move a window over
to
the other side
the size changes
it's kind of annoying
kind of annoying
yeah yeah okay uh i don't know what to
do i hope they're gonna explain the game
kindly to me why is there a discord sign
on the bottom right is it like their own
discord
new save new save you save back delete
save okay okay
i i think like the style of the game
already is pretty cute i like it
uh also we can talk a little bit about
um my last day on earth though my last
day on
uh in korea
um we can chit-chat about it um
i don't know how how much time the game
will give me to chit-chat but you know
i wouldn't like this game you think so
that's scary little fellas yeah that's
cute i like the art style it's cute
and the animation cued
and my sushi
members only content dude
decent amount of time to talk okay good
well let's go oh it's kind of loud is it
loud
no maybe not praise the lamb conduit to
great power promised liberator of the
one who waits below
yet sacrificial beast take heed for a
crown cannot sit upon two brows
did i mean humans with that or
oh
i look so sad
oh i'm such a sad lamb cute
[Music]
am i in [\h__\h] am i in a chat yeah i'm
chained i'm a prisoner
okay well i guess we're going upwards
brother can i talk
sorry
i wanted to talk to you i'll call you
know you maybe give me some information
some story some lore oh they're
following me
oh am i on like death row or something
again by massive monster
whoa
oh oh no no i'm an i'm an offering oh
i guess yeah lamb's lamb is an offering
makes sense oh but then i'll turn it
around or what i'll be like you know you
shouldn't offer me you should follow me
i am the one who will lead you
to enlightenment
well what the [\h__\h] are those aliens
ew
wait those are aliens aren't they
have they taken over all the poor normal
animals are all gonna be eaten by the
[\h__\h]
aliens
sorry i'm so sorry
okay
neil to be sacrificed what if i say no
i don't wanna what if i do something
else i don't wanna be sacrificed
i'm so sad
look at that this
face makes me sad it knows it's gonna be
sacrificed
[Music]
that's it i'm i'm turning into a
vegetarian
okay again
look at those eyes
well it won't happen right
before it stays live
no
it's a holy lamp you can't kill it
we just want to sacrifice the prophecy
will be
to fulfill
good what
the heck
who is found below will be condemned to
eternal captivity
[Music]
am i dead
oh
this is the afterlife
looks like it
oh it's like a watery floor okay what is
that over there
let's take a look
what is this
what the [\h__\h] is this
one wait
[Music]
um
time
[Music]
yeah
yes absolutely there's not even a choice
but yeah hell yeah let's go let's go
let's go
oh feel of the devil that's the devil
doesn't look so bad
[Applause]
become as good
oh lamp is happy
and now it goes [\h__\h] all of you
[\h__\h] you
yay happy lamb okay attack dodge roll
oh
[Music]
okay
nice where did i get that sword from
what the [\h__\h]
okay we got that one
look at the angry face when it runs
so cute look look at that determined
angry cute face
cute but dangerous
oh wow
[Music]
this can i hurt i can get rid of that
too okay nice
black for the blood god
oh
oh we want to go there or what okay
we're going here first i guess
[Music]
what animal are you
what could that be
[Music]
is that on the left supposed to be its
snoot but then both eyes are on the
right side that's kind of weird
is it a rat that's a rat
okay where's the tail
fear not i am watau i was once chosen
vessel like you but those days are lost
in the winds look how bouncy and happy
my lamp is
so happy about staying alive and
creating a
a cult instead
worth it
alive but at what cost at a good cost
very good cost yeah
afterwards mm-hmm
to guide you we are deep in the lands of
the old faith and engraved anger
my instructions are to lead you to
safety
continue through the woods escape lies
ahead i will be close by
you like my voice i think oh there it
goes okay i guess that is a rat because
it goes like
into the ground
it always changes into this angry face
when it runs it's so cute
[Music]
oh i can stand in the fire nothing
happens to me i am invincible now
i killed the fire
water in the fire fire in the water
the sword in the water
oh my ah
so um
this is a rogue life game not that i
really oh dodge good boy
i really know
what what's a roguelike skin
what was that like when you kill a [\h__\h]
ton of enemies was that it
uh this one to open inventory okay nice
randomized layout that's roguelike
what what
that is a hack and slash oh
i restart with oh
perma-death eats run different
what
so like hollow cure
i'm about to hollow cute always has the
same map
yeah i don't
wait you start from the very beginning
every time or is there like some saves
at least
i mean what else are those saves for i
guess oh i guess we're not dying
[Music]
every time you enter a dungeon you start
from level one oh
oh okay well we'll find out
how exactly that works here something in
my eye
we'll figure it
out uh my eye ah mega
okay
oh what what what what did i come to the
menu for did you hold me to come to the
menu but what am i supposed to do here
nothing thanks for telling me i know
inventory inventory huh
wait is this the wrong button that i'm
pressing
ah okay uh the left side is inventory i
never get the i'm using a ps5 controller
but i never really sometimes i'm like it
tells me to press the middle pad
and it's depending on where i push it
it gives me something else but it's kind
of like what
i don't get it
okay so we have one currency the last
for gold is oft all consuming of one's
heart
a currency used for all manner of things
okay
consuming my heart yes
money to be like that oh we have like a
equipment thingy in the lamp tarot cards
no terry cards when collected they will
appear here ted cards are reset after
each crusade speaking of tarot cards you
know in in seoul
me and nabi we were
walking past like
um
like a
uh
what's the word um
like a like
fortune reading no not a fortune reading
like
a a fortune teller yeah fortune teller
uh several times and nabi mama always
wanted me to enter and and she was like
come on come on i i love that kind of
stuff it's fun you should do it you
should do it i'm like yeah i don't
really believe in it much but
navi mama does apparently she she likes
to do
fortune she would like to partake in
fortune telling sometimes like being the
one who's having the fortune told
yeah
now you know even more about dobby mama
yeah i did tell her that i want to learn
tarot cards again but not for the sake
not not because oh there's something oh
the birds are like not because i believe
in it
but just because i find the
oh what is this
on the floor oh okay wow
wow where's my hp anyway if this is a
roguelike where i can die where is my hp
uh what was i saying oh yeah i don't
believe in it but
i don't know i kind of
i like um
listening to it
but i don't believe in it
tutorial still i'll kill you
but i mean tariff cards and stuff like
that i still
i still kind of
it's too loud isn't it i still kind of
like those but what i really i really
can't get into horoscopes like
uh that's just the biggest
[\h__\h] bullshite to me
gosh i'm turning it down a little bit
it's so cute
the happy faces all the faces the
expressions are so cute
speaking of [\h__\h] one of the movies i
watched in
in my airplane ride back
was uh what was it called
some some movie with aubrey
aubry plaza about some
some
uh
some offer and he kept on saying both
sides [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] that was his thing
[Music]
it was a
it was a kind of boring movie but i
watched it to the end anyway because i
didn't like the choices they had besides
that
um
oh shine
oh this place looks cool
wait that sounded like diablo
what was that sound
sounded like the altar sound of um the
apple whenever you get like a dude this
one this sound
[Laughter]
emperor ludkin is my other aussie yes
love her
yeah it does it does right it does oh my
god thank
we have nearly reached safety but look
ahead another poor soul about to be
sacrificed
rescue them then they would have no
choice but to join your couple
oh but it's not a lamp what is that i
said oh it looks like a hedgehog
or hedge dog wait hedgehog headstock
oh it's crying
oh no
is it headstock or a hedgehog
it's hedgehog oh
it should be headed off
thank you
are you okay buddy
oh my bishops of the old fave we ask you
to accept the sacrifice of this wretched
soul
hey who interrupts our ritual and dress
passes on secret
facts allowed in this world [\h__\h] them
back if you want to you can join my
culture
i want to get like some cool attacks
like magic spells and [\h__\h] later on
i wonder
oh so cute oh my god
[Music]
you have been rescued oh bye bye
follow awaits indoctrination
i know if i call that being rescued
join kfp
join kfp do it just do it don't question
anything
hello
for each safety
you have done
well red crown will allow you to use
those markings underground to transport
yourself great distance
it will take you to a temple that has
fallen to ruin
there you will be able to begin your new
calls
i will meet you there bye-bye i like the
way it dives into the ground just
head head bomb
return to club
okay
well this is a good start i guess that
was a tutorial
heretics defeated
cleanse the non-believers
oh
34 deaths
one plus one follow-up
we need more followers we only have one
follower what the [\h__\h]
more
please select the difficulty don't worry
you can change the difficulty at any
time
is it is a difficult game in general
oh no extra hard i'm not going for extra
hard wait let's just go for medium
nobody can
complain if i go for medium
it's very easy
it's an easy game okay we'll go for
medium
oh it's so pretty
[Music]
um which way what is
it i'll kill kick it this way
hello
it's kind of bright here nice
this hallowed ground which once was mine
is now yours this crumbling ruin is to
be the sight of your new cult
we have much to do
we begin by indoctrinating this poor
soul into the warm embrace of your colon
followers can gather resources for you
order this one to collect lumber stone
ah
they work for me
[Music]
feels familiar
oh
cute oh he's actually pretty open to
doing it
convict me to your cult i will follow
your teachings faithfully
look at the face is so happy
[Music]
that's your name
it's simple and you know
oh parents choose from what
oh my god
a little biggie
[Music]
are there chickens
can i oh maybe like maybe they are a
frog
wait there's so many animals but i don't
see a [\h__\h] chicken are you kidding me
not that i could use it now but what
why is there no chicken
frog will be unlocked later yeah i mean
if there's no chicken then maybe we make
everyone frogs
instead i don't know
what the [\h__\h] why is there no chickens
what that's not how is that too much to
ask for a chicken chicken is such a
basic animal sorry guys but
am i expecting too much
there's mice there's whatever the [\h__\h]
those are
unplayable
the discrimination
there's a [\h__\h] elephant in the room
and it's that there's no
no [\h__\h]
chicken there's a there's a bunny
they have everything
what
can we get like a
cult of the holo um
game you know like hold up here can we
can we please make
a holo version of this game
oh
there you say what
no well guardian bird knuckle yeah okay
well for now
i like the piggies to be honest they're
cute
oh just color oh my god
maybe something would look like a
chicken if i give it like the right
color
but for now let's just keep it pink
cute variation oh
oh it can be a hairy piggy oh they're so
cute oh my god
ignores the centers when they preach
where can devotion generation speed
reduced by 10.
uh-huh okay
this will do for now um
t-shirt buy my t-shirts buy my t-shirts
yeah
oh
is it praying now oh clear rubble to
collect stone
shop trees okay do that
oh that's so cool
oh it works for me i love that
by your hand the cold will grow powerful
but you followers cannot live on prayer
alone and they must eat
oh there's
[Music]
there's cute little and bees and
butterflies flying around we must make
them join the cult too
necessary resources and build a cooking
fire it will allow you to prepare meals
for your followers
cooking fire okay chip chop choopy doop
chop chop chap
there you go i got fire
i'm faster than
pinky man
okay stone
some more
wood
uh berries
ah what if i was picking them where's
that there you go x
ah
oh i can just actually i can just keep
it pressed i thought i have to
press press
i will mine you to be mine
wait i still kept doing the same thing
oh i already have enough materials huh a
foreign stone oopsie
never mind can never be enough i'm sure
we'll need more of all this
collect lumber
oh we got a lot of lumber out of that
one all right built
cookie fire
ah
cool cute cute let's do it
oh and then we place it somewhere where
there's space okay
what cooking fire
ah we can't put oh we can't put it here
okay i'll put it here
it's cooking fire
oh are you gonna help me
oh
yes okay can i help too
oh speed
your followers need to eat and it's up
to you to provide meals to them
the hunger of your cold can be seen on
the top left of the screen when this
gets too low followers will begin to
starve aha
ah okay it's like a stomach icon
find more food while crusading thank you
for them thank you for the thank you for
the pinky
pick routes that pass through foraging
locations
ah
ah are there no enemies there i wonder
plant farms to grow your own food seeds
can be purchased or found whilst
crusading if i plant my own farm then i
wonder while i'm gone will they continue
to you know work on the farm and then
make their own food continuously
crusade
yeah oh cool
okay nice
i already have some berries i knew they
would come in handy
uh some more berries then and then we
cook a meal
isn't this fitting you know at kfp you
guys work for me but i also provide for
you you know kfb provides
meals it's just
all
chicken
[Laughter]
okay
recipe basic berry bar but basic berry
bone simple meal made from berries mmm
chances have to follow are pooping
instantly
why would i want that it
what
is that good
this is good or bad isn't it bad because
like then they're emptied too fast
is it cooking what
oh
nice i cook the meals for you
oh fertilizer what oh
they fertilize the grounds
wow it's so
convenient and so efficient
damn
now we must build a shrine but first we
will need more followers and more gold
coins
both of which can be found when
crusading for the lands of the old face
our mutual benefactor the one who waits
has been trapped by the four bishops of
the old fave
each of them guards a chain that binds
him to the real ground beyond
it we have conjured the opening realms
that
track them down and slay them so that
you may be free
now go there you shall find gold coins
and willing recruits and for those who
are not willing convert them by force
yay hell yeah let's go sounds good to me
[Music]
and i suddenly started feeling like and
our
our pronunciation would be good oh
you're chopping something did you eat
dull yeah your stomach seems full okay
i kind of want to help like get rid of
all of this
but
let me
let me make sure you have food because
i'm i'm providing for you yeah i'm a
good mommy
i'll make a new one for you
cooking
great
nice have fun with that
bye bye
oh
wow thank you deposit resources here
while you're away oh
i love this so far
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you good night also uh
to korean bros i just wanted to know to
note that um for
popcorn i've heard you know there were
some issues and i've i've actually uh
asked for them to be resolved so seems
that there have been improvements made
and that it will be it was extended to
the 21st if you want to apply for the
meet and greet if there's any issues
that you wanted to that you don't know
what to do oh my god are they going to
kill me
uh then please dm the twitter account of
popcorn
because apparently they help via dm okay
thank you
reed
here godly blood was spilled
here did death no longer wish to wait
wait there's so many doors
a blue a green a red and a purple door
ah it's the form
this is the four aliens that are
capturing my god
open door
what the [\h__\h] was that oh when i open
the door it gets the help from my
my followers
i can only access one right now wait did
i
surprisingly choose the one that i can
actually open
dark wood
placing brooms oh
free heights oh no
oh no can i get heart containers
crusaders
equip
oh oh oh oh i equip it in the beginning
hi hi fine
read
enter the lands of the bishop bless you
those who do not follow the ways of the
old faith will be destroyed
good luck ginger thank you
extreme heart container
you have to go for them all to get to
the final boss okay
enter in the land of the um okay
well hopefully it won't be too difficult
i'm scared only free can i like is there
like healing on
them grass oh can i bring grass to my
to my grounds and will that help to
build anything
[Music]
heart drops okay there are hot drops
that's good oh
is there like a focus button focused on
like an enemy oh there was a hard drop
okay i didn't need it though i'm too
good
grass grass makes vibes ah
very good uh uh there's too many too
many ways ah wait there's a there's a
map on the top right okay uh they're all
dead ends
um apparently
according to the map
is there no stamina i love that
wait i thought i see the the hunger from
my cult uh also when i'm like outside
but
now i see nothing on the top left so
are they does it not deplete when i'm
gone
i thought it was gonna deplete while i'm
no one can tell you to stop rolling
let's go
that's true
that's for later it does oh it does
alert me over time
[Music]
then when i go back to the previous room
it doesn't reload the enemies i like
that too
not so far
i'm really intrigued by this game
[Music]
yeah
that one was kind of strong what the
hell
oh no it was not dead and there's one
more room but then i checked first you
know that's the rpg
gamer syndrome i have to check first if
the other one was a dead end there we go
okay see
what the hell oh it's fortune telling
parrots terry tarrett terrence praise
the lamp okay yeah
praise the lamb conduit to great power
promised liberator of the one that waits
below
so the cards showed me once many
lifetimes ago or has that yet to be
i've always drawn your card slammed and
yet this is the first
take these cards now we'll draw another
each time we meet when drawn by me they
will grant you
[Music]
what power
well that is both known and unfair from
the boom
the cards they shall decide
oh is it random too
these two
and then i choose from the two random
ones a heart
one life
oh my god
10 chance to deal critical hit
[Music]
should i go for the heart i think
maybe i should go for the heart
i think i want the heart
oh is that temporary
temporary
because it's blue
i'm already playing when he said i'm not
playing anymore i'm playing media mode
temporary is lame that's true
only for this run
oh all the tarot cards are always just
for that run
ah
interesting
sorry
you can't heal back a blue heart not a
horde so it's like um yeah yeah yeah
yeah
like something i've seen before in other
games okay
all as it should be as devil was as it
always will be
oh i like your little camp it's very
cute cool listen i'm i'm hey listen i'm
listening what is this
oh it's the different cards i can get
some of them are not visible to me some
of them are
interesting
well there's quite a lot 15 out of 36
i've got what
already collected so many when did i do
that
you can't argue with the draw yeah don't
worry don't worry i'm not going to
okay
because
we have a 10
at least you the ten percent um
[Music]
uh of critical
will not deplete while i'm fighting in
this map but the heart will deplete if i
get hit so
you know
although oh wait temporary i guess i
mean
can i heal it within this map or
also not new tarot cards
the venom of fear knows no cure deals
poison damage to enemies doing stuff
noise so make sure to cut the grass oh
okay okay okay
okay this one didn't really give
anything
diablo
oh this one is for wood oh
oh my god i love this game
i didn't expect much to be honest
because i didn't look into it much
i was just like you know i came back
from
korea and i i actually didn't really
have anything
uh us oopsie i didn't really have
anything planned out
uh beforehand besides finishing tunic
so
i was like what could i play what could
i play what could i play
i was looking for the list and
saw a new game i was like okay
why not give it a try
i didn't really look into it much just
while it looks cute
now here we are
here we are why can i not destroy that
weed
do i have like a full inventory or what
return with more gold return with more
followers i will do that hopefully boss
time boston
first boss can't be too difficult
here or there
neither hero
oh no not boss
but i may be boss at the end of this are
they poisonous because they're green why
am i poisoning them
when did i get poison damage when did i
do that
what
i did
i missed something
monkey noises
oh they did some damage on me holy [\h__\h]
someone dropped me a heart please
oh what's happening
is the boss coming now oh dear here
[Music]
how can this be oh is that one of the
aliens i don't i don't remember what
voice i did for them
you were put to the blade and bears all
your kind with and yet here you stand
before me unrepentant
the crowd is power could it be
but i'm stronger still turn tail and run
little lap
[\h__\h] you
oh it disappeared it's scared of me we
asserted dominance
it's time to ki kitty kill
left or right not the right left or
right left or right i'm gonna go right
[Music]
oh oh yeah oh
it's already a new map is it so wait do
we still have the
critical stuff or is this considered a
new map
where we don't have the
critical attacker
oh when i picked that up i thought it
was just like a new option for what i
could get when i get a tarot card
reading
but i actually still have like this one
and i got this one actually too aha
that's why i've been poisoning them okay
okay okay
rabbit's foot ugh
feels lucky and fluffy increase the
chance to spawn by the chest
fluffy fluffy
i want to squeeze the palm
get an extra half heart
that is not blue
that is not glue so is this one actually
temporary uh
permanently
is that a hard container
[Music]
but that's a permanent one man
ah no it's for the stage but i can at
least heal this one back is that how it
is okay
okay well let's get a better chance
thank you
[Music]
i'm so sorry but i kill you maybe you
give me something you have a funny face
though no
oh i got it i got it while it was trying
to escape into the ground
nice okay wait what did we get right off
the chest i didn't see
oh well
this is
[Music]
am i
saving you you don't look like you need
saving
uh oh
i was the alien again
you have come find that little lamb but
my followers are willing to do anything
for me can you say the same overview
i give myself to the class
of the great ones destroy the red crown
right friends
oh no
enthusiasts it turned into a monster
holy [\h__\h] oh my god i already got him
okay but it's poisoned
it has goddammit let's go
[Music]
i want that i want that ability because
that feels like it can i can make my own
wait isn't it when i'm when i'm doing a
team space
making my own channel
[Music]
to follow me in my club do you want to
follow me oh i can convert them let's go
[Music]
what are you
oh it's crying oh i forgive you oh
you will you will come to a better cult
this will be a better one don't worry
i i i mean i could be wrong but i'm not
making you fight for me only build [\h__\h]
for me
who knows maybe you will fight for me
one day i'm not sure
[Music]
okay egghead
let's do it
choose 15 berries what
oh
god nuggets
what should i go for i would say gold
nuggets
sounds very valuable at the moment
barry's best
food
would best right now
oh berries in lumber early on okay
[Music]
how much do i currently have 59 27
stone
okay i will go for berries then
i guess
i don't know
i don't know whatever but you've just
begun it's probably not
that of a deep
important
decision
okay
so i did my first map for
let's go
[Music]
mummy would be proud
mummy should play this game it would fit
her i feel like
i do i don't know the vibes and the art
style
let me just play it
heretics defeated
cleanse the non-believers
last one oh 35 enemies defeated
she's addicted to rust uh
well she can play more than one game
right
oh
he set
i'm relieved to see you made it safely
and you have not returned alone you have
convinced more to join your faithful
flock
let us indoctrinate this new convert so
that we may continue
yes let's do it you're so green you like
a broccoli
indoctrinate let's go
oh happy
enthusiasts
shall we make you the same as the others
oh that one is noodle that wasn't there
before i think
i mean i don't mind having like a mix of
everything even it gives them more
personality i guess
oh his name is fine
i know
for now for now
i know i cannot want it yeah unless
different colored piggies and you'll be
green piggy because you wear green
originally
i don't even type oh on the keyboard
um
ah bro coolly cause he's so cool
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
is your name
uh
you will clear the rubble
followers will either work or worship
worshipping followers generate devotion
tears for you to collect but to
collective ocean tears you would cry or
shrine let's build a shrine
what i need
oh
no material just fruity coins
oh i guess we'll place it right in the
middle where else would we do that
oh build it building
yes
come to help me
you're too late for cooling you need to
be
faster crazy oh no don't say that it
gives me flashbacks to the hatman's tail
blessed be the fruit
praise bead yeah yeah
there's a new season coming up i think
this year because there was a there was
a trailer and i couldn't get over
watching the trailer even because it's
so [\h__\h] terrifying the most [\h__\h]
terrifying show that i know of is the
handmaid's tale if you need to watch
something that [\h__\h] you up go watch the
handmaid's tale
i will finally watch the last episode
yeah if the new season comes out i will
watch the last episode of the previous
season
it tells you something that i i i love
the show so much but i didn't want to
watch the last episode previously
because it just [\h__\h] me up too much
and i was scared of being [\h__\h] up even
worse
[Music]
i'm good always hydrate guys
oh your followers cannot worship you
nice
assign them to worship at the shrine
then collect the devotion cheers to your
followers generated shrine to unlock
divine inspiration what you just brought
me a new follower thank you dude
it's cute
[Music]
have an idea
how do i make a pun out of surprise
surprise
because it's some
i guess your prize
i don't know how
how how you are prize or
surprise oh my god
we are giving him the third title he's a
[\h__\h] follower new follower of my cult
for pro fair price is better
yeah
fur prize some surprise that's more
fitting we can't give him a certain
title he just arrived surprise
i like that one too
okay
um
good
uh fur prize
choose form you're just a pig
all of you are just pigs
what color are you kind of like this
color i think
natural sceptic
what
on recruiting follow i mainly lose 10
faves what the [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
go [\h__\h] yourself for a price
you're 50 slow and sick and embed rest
you know i should kick you out already
useless
for personal fur oh i could give him
some fur
true
worship go
once you collect enough you will unlock
divine inspiration okay
more followers worshipping at your
shrine the faster they will fill up if
the shrine is full they will stop
worshiping until it is emptied oh
cute
once you have collected divine
inspiration unlock new buildings for
your cult for the shrine
unlock new building oh cool
not a little neck can i
can i am pray to my own
probably not okay oh
wait let me collect the stuff that's in
here whoa
50 lumber
what are you doing are you doing well
vital be faster
oh there's some food here
is that the one i left here
i'll cook some more food for you guys
oh i can make two
[Music]
hard to fail that one but maybe there's
like more difficult ones later on why am
i even working
why am i doing this
okay
have fun guys i guess i'm going to the
next stage
am i
she's gaming yes i'm gaming
okay there's still so many resources
around good
big trees too
i'm out of here
inspire my fault have i not been
inspiring already
i was the last land on earth i think i'm
i am more than just inspiring i am life
changing oh wait i have to collect my
okay okay okay
collect it receive
four tears
oh
divine inspiration unlocked collect
divine inspiration
oh oh oh
temple
establish a temple to preach sermons and
perform rituals
wow
bits is that grass bed sleeping bag
can i get another one no i have zero
nice
let's build it then
this structure is only built once uh-huh
and i have enough materials establishing
temperature
okay what kind of rituals
will we put that pretty up high here in
the beginning
and let's build that [\h__\h]
building
okay every conference room
i want temple yay
i want a kfb mod for this game
[Music]
the temple is the center of your cult
from there you will preach sermons to
grow stronger and perform rituals to
mold the fragile minds of your followers
you're responsible for maintaining the
faith of your cult if it falls too low
your followers will dissent against you
and eventually
your followers are ready to hear your
words
does that require skill too
oh it's so cool in here
[Music]
temple ontario okay i'm doing a sermon
drawing energy from your followers to
bolster the power of the red crown
[Laughter]
what a game what a [\h__\h] game
ah am i echoing i felt like i was
echoing
spooky
oh
i didn't have to do anything
strength for the flock
through the favor of your followers you
grow stronger
[Music]
now
performing sermons will draw power from
them and allow you to unlock new
abilities weapons and curses
oh
let's go
nice
the followers with a higher loyalty
level will generate more devotion
therefore the more followers you have
and the more loyal they are the quicker
you will gain your abilities
parts of the faithful permanently
yes this is what i'm talking about this
is the real permanent heart
all righty
[Music]
i'm enlightened thank you my followers
for making me stronger can we do another
one only once per day
per day is that as in like every time i
leave and come back today
it was amazing to behold a natural
leader i see why you were chosen
praise
but do they say that in other cults too
like in real cults do they say that
maybe they even say that in normal
religions
it sounds so
surreal to me
oh the only place where i ever heard
that was a in a handmaid's tale so
i don't belong to any real cults
oh are you sure about that what about
kfp huh
praise kiwawa you praise me
praising as in
praise me
say how cute
and lovely i am
[Music]
we are what i mean
i mean
you know it
don't be so surprised
[Music]
the loveliest oh thank you
thank you thank you thank you i'm so
sweet of you
[Music]
if you are to guide your coat you will
need to declare dark dreams doctrines so
that they may might obey you
return to the land of the old faith and
seek out commandments stone fragments
with these you will be able to ah
like laws laws for my cult
least i see
okay
well then yeah do your best guys
i think i'm gonna head out
do some good stuff do some work
we were lucky wawa yeah what's the next
door that i can enter
i see okay this one i can't enter i'm
guessing the blue one then
three out of nine ah
three on the nine
no no it requires not what
wait do i have to enter the same door
again
is that normal
is there like an
oh
i guess
an axe a cleaver
a mighty tool of unstoppable brutality
coolio
i don't get a choice it seems to
oh it's very slow
not a huddle
but very brutal and strong
kitchen
okay
i will test out my weapon
i'm
[Music]
we'll have to get used to this one
oh
coins coins coins
oh that was a dead end okay
was it
yeah
day one oh it says day one in the top
right
oh wait so there's actually
oh
interesting
i keep on forgetting the grass oopsie
ah axe is good for dodge play or home
oh is that so i'm glad i found you i
bring good news
no it's totally not a cult
no
no no it's not no
with a credit card you choose fast
weapons
forgetting to touch grass yeah damn it
i already touched so much grass in korea
yo
the one who waits is pleased with your
progress and wishes to grant you a crown
ability
oh the power is coming from
yeah
i'm fine
hold your ammo
does that
come back
or
how does
uh we have to shoot these targets away
oh
it's a fireball
is that kind of auto aim hallelujah
one more there you go i did it
oh enemies enemies you slay will now
drop further
collectors to replenish your curses
ah the righteous anger earned by
striking down non-believers and works
like ammunition for your curses okay the
more i kill the more they will give me
back from
for my
my
mana or whatever will japanese lay an
enemy collecting it refuels your curses
doesn't that say the same thing
[Laughter]
uh okay
oh oh those dots
i'm already full okay okay okay
okay
nice so there's no
oh nothing here
oh never mind there's definitely
something here
oh wow that was quite the hitbox oh it
came really hard let's go
[Music]
hi
grass jumping
that's the grass touch the grass
no escape buddy
hell yeah
yeah baby
i'm going back i think i think i should
go this way
first
judging judging by what i just saw yep
okay
let yourself to the draw of a card
purchase consume
overall weapon damage increase by 1.2 ah
straight card strike fast structure and
ocu
i would say the first one
i think i'll go for the left one yeah
more damage
i love this game
[Music]
it time for boss fight already
wait i forgot how to use the
the magic what button was that
what where was that
triangle okay
there's so much oh so many routes can i
also like go back then is there a
follow-up there
i can get
here's uh berries and food
and stones and stones
yeah i want the follower but can i get
the followers and go back and get this
the other things two up under
i can't go back so pick wisely oh and
then i i need the follower
i need the follower obviously no save
the donkey
it's a donkey the worm it is hungry
it feeds it protects up our flesh but
that is the price for safety for that
wheel gladly give it all we have
we'll see about that
this is fun
rescue
after seeing that show how could that
donkey ever say no to following me right
i mean that was pretty badass and cool
so
i would follow myself
follow me on twitter guys
oh blogs blessed vessel fortune bestows
for gift until daddy d
receive double the health when healing
coolio thank you
[Music]
wait should i chop some breasts
yes i should
okay
are you an owl
oh isn't it
looks a little bit weird but still cute
and i think it's an owl that thing in
the middle still devotion okay what are
we doing
and they're gone
these lines were rifled with coins and
territories
what the hell does pantheon alice just
the nature of beast for that girl
[Music]
returned
those few who were mainspread roads
who'd spun webs molded this world to me
dumb and theirs who told
[Music]
i don't know what the hell you were
saying but that was [\h__\h] cute
oh commandment stone fragment ah i
thought ah okay it's already like
decided what they are it's not just
i can take whatever and i decide at home
what it will be
okay we're taking the middle one
apparently
oh
okay
apparently that's like for devotion
what is it
why did you tell me to pick the middle
one then
lenny
you found enough fragments to form a
commandment stone
commandment stones are used to declare
new doctrines for your call to follow
previous re what go back oh okay
use the altar in your temple to declare
a new doctrine whenever you form a new
commandment uh-huh okay what did what
was something to steal
seal devotion ah that's what you guys
were talking about
oh
can i destroy it too oh
oh got a stone out of that nice no no
don't build yourself it's building
itself together again
can i destroy it again this is like an
endless stone
right generator no it's not
oh [\h__\h] how does it do that
so powerful
we need to learn the skill of
regeneration too
[Music]
i hear your eyes and you smell your feet
the red crown rises again but when what
if he buried his
wait i guess was that really the voice i
was doing or whatever
oh my god
[Music]
okay
bring it on baby
[Music]
okay it's actually
pretty easy to dodge them
mm-hmm
i'm just trying to be extra careful but
maybe not even necessary i don't know ah
we're good we're good we're good we're
good
we're good
we got three coins out of that declare a
new doctrine from the altar in the
temple okay i'm on my way to doing that
just give me a second
it goes up
[Music]
oh my god
my health
it's in danger
holy [\h__\h] okay i need to i need to be
more careful
being a little bit careful was was a
good idea so let's go back to that
uh left or right
oh that's a lot of enemies
[Music]
ah
ah i thought i was my magic where's my
magic i need more magicka
comes only from the enemies i suppose
a lot of materials here too
maybe i should
start telling you about the
navi mama
last thing would not be mama but
i'm so into this right now
all right so if this was not a dead end
oh oh they're connected like a circle
[Music]
critical hit or attack rate increased by
1.25
attack rate
so
uh attack um speeds or
yeah i think i like that one in that
case
hey did i choose the right one
yeah i did
okay
[Music]
good choice
okay
okay now we go up here
oh
crusaders blade oh i can
change my weapon here
[Music]
do i want to
yeah
should i
a level two sword
sword as well okay
all ready
oh boss fight fast fight
i'm scared axe is better oh well
[\h__\h]
you can steal devotion
and some stones
divine inspirational lock let's go
i like the worms they look cute they're
like leaf worms
oh i see you hiding i see you hiding
behind the grass
cutting all the grass feels actually
pretty good
stay very high let's go thank you i
needed that the the contents of the
chest are random too right
[Music]
three points yes random since what i
didn't steal all the devotion
what
oh
i really okay i need to
pay more attention to that then okay
ah going left
what is it
temperature chance deal critical hit i
think i'll go with a critical hit
oh you guys agree with that one
might be the first game i buy in 2022
ooh you should buy tunic too tunic is
really good too
yeah
oh is it is that is the boss coming no
it's an axe again oh they're not for me
the axe again swing with intent
hey
now they're offering me the axe again i
don't know
[Music]
i prefer
being able to attack faster i think
but it's level free
much stronger okay
it does stay level three
ah
[Music]
kind cute fast oh what the [\h__\h]
what
how can i survive
[Music]
i can't
why is
no the pain
yeah what happens when i die wait i lost
25 only not everything
what else did i lose my the respect from
the people
oh god
wow
oh it's very nice and like motivating
thank you
[Music]
don't
um
i hope yeah i hope they don't disrespect
me no your death has made you false
thank you
no
i thought it was a joke what you said in
the chat no i'm not weak i should i show
you that i'm not [\h__\h] weak speak the
brocaulie
really yeah the cult is growing by the
day this time you gave it a name oh okay
hmm
obviously
or just kfp
we could just name it kfp
hmm
which one is which one do you put let me
do a poll on this one
called
oops
health of the phoenix
or just simply
kfp
interesting
interesting actually cultures k and then
let's see
cult of the
that's actually um
maybe that's what it was always
standing for
cult
of the
ah
never mind then
i kind of like that one
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
depends on how you read it it can still
be kfp
okay op oh oh [\h__\h] i did it wrong
okay i wonder if you can still change
this afterwards
cult of the phoenix
accent
was that correct did i do something
wrong
okay fp okay it's fine
this is fine
[Music]
i like it i like it too
[Laughter]
[Music]
cult of the phoenix that has a nice ring
to it
why are you so [\h__\h] angry man go back
to work
ah wait what uh collect huh ah
okay you know even i'll make you a body
pants
why would we why would we ever need such
a thing sleeping bags or
farms oh let's go farm foot grab a seat
into a
crop backs first oh [\h__\h]
too late
too late guys
receipt
ah
wait maybe i can do another one don't
worry guys
sleeping bags place a place for a
follower to sleep where we on stable
will often collapse oh no
farming and sleeping we can do both now
i'm like lagging a little bit huh
okay
we got some cool new stuff
is this
clean is that poop
should i clean it or isn't it good when
it's like there
what
did he just like get sick by the look of
the poopy poop should i clean it why
don't i have to clean it also the face i
just made when cleaning
unsanitary conditions that you called
will cause your falls to become sick oh
if a follower becomes sick assign them
to bed rest or they could die resting
will allow them to slowly recover yeah
i should just let them die
poor vomit and dead bodies cause illness
to spread quickly for what about what
about those
didn't you guys say fertilizing
cleaning messes and burning bodies will
prevent the spread of illness oh look at
the happy face though
oh my god
okay
stop looking so [\h__\h] angry man
making me angry too
indoctrinated
[Music]
sorry you will have to accept this guys
even if you don't like it
i don't care
[Music]
it gray
i already don't remember
memory too short
probably no it wasn't was it like this
ah whatever
what
why why can't it have this these
markings
donkeys yeah it's a donkey pig
recording is following me like intense
faith 15 harder to level up
cynical what can devotion generation
speech reduce button oh come on
uh you shall worship me for now
i guess
okay oh they're kind of hungry let's
make some fruit
i have to do berries
uh clean this [\h__\h] up literally
and wear berries i hear some berries
with those berries that's a cute face
the faces remind me a little bit of um
a lady alligator
it's [\h__\h] cute
it's too cute man
yeah the expressions
you get what i mean get what i'm saying
we'll perform a sermon
face up so you can oh okay bless them
individually
let's switch sermon
i'll couldn't explain the loser
let's do sermon
[Music]
[Applause]
what do we do cruise of the horse now
i'm i'm part of the alliance
[Music]
what should i do
amen
speaking tongues
such a way
you thank you i know that's why i'm the
leader and you're just the chicken bane
weapons okay is that does that mean i'm
batting weapons or what paying weapons
ow okay now i'm not batting weapons
within my cult i'm doing something else
okay poisoning enemies cool
okay we should also ban weapons though
so they don't overthrow me and kill me
oh what is this upgrade and expensively
ah isn't that uh
oh no wait that's something new
in the observation of our rights we
taste divinity divine divinity for the
study of our doctrine we are blessed by
the sacrament of the land
here's a commandment stone to declare a
new talking vehicle ah
select a cat from a category and make a
choice level i'm looking for you ritual
try to follow
wait what
it gives me
it gives me the [\h__\h] randomly
i can't decide dance around the flame to
increase the cult's faith
as a ritual oh
oh dancing around the fire oh nice very
fitting it's fitting i guess
it's not right the first one isn't
random okay
later i get to choose
okay first one also always bonfire
[Music]
oh our first ritual ah isn't that nice
light the fires and let us dance deep
into the net let's
[Music]
da
so fun of that song actually i was i
think
i think i
i think i sang this one in karaoke and
also i remember like
it playing
somewhere when i was hanging out with
nabi that was fun and i was i was
jumping and running and dancing
like a crazy person when i heard it the
moment i heard it so much fun
dancing
[Music]
sorry i really love this song
okay we have a ritual
happy
oh they're happy
oh now we can do the ritual right here
okay cool you shall we do that no i need
to i need some bones
where do i get the bones to have to kill
you guys
i'll put whatever it takes man
preaching sermons performing rituals and
providing for the needs of your
followers will keep your faith high
bones of your enemies are required to
perform such rituals
destroy your skeletons i haven't
destroyed your skeletons but i never
dropped bones they said that
return to the land of the whole faith
cave of bones from falling enemies
recruit my followers in return to
perform a ritual
[Music]
after slaying a non-believer the secret
desecrate the bodies oh to gather their
bones and use them to perform dark
rituals at your temple doc
why are you assuming they're dark
rituals they're bright happy rituals
that's what it'd be
how do i bless them you guys said i
could bless them is it only only after i
do a ritual
can i build something no i need to make
food though
i can only make two can they share
perfect
nice
oh oh they're coming tonight already oh
they're so hungry
you need to talk to them okay
do i need as many bands as i have uh
people or
did i just you know share
okay i'm scared let's put some beds here
here
yeah
as many beds as phones okay and i have
full currently there you go wait i'll
get rid of the [\h__\h] before you see it
and get sick just by looking at it
there you go
yeah i'm building too
shabby bang that's our aim and by the
way shabby bang
chubby bang i'm way too fast for you
guys to even help me
are you claiming your bed
shippity bag
oh cute a sign
a sign too
a patty
sign two broccoli for
[\h__\h] assigned to surprise
and assigned to don don donkey
yeah you're welcome
tommy's gone already okay don't be
overly dramatic
how do you spell that you should know
you're a follower of kfp for a long time
how the hell do you not know oh it's
night time oh it's a sleepy time
where do i sleep though
[Music]
i need a [\h__\h]
double queen-sized king-sized bed yo
oh look at them cute
kind of cute
no sleep for the wicket time for crusade
okay sounds good
no more berries here though how do i
make them grow
oh man okay we gotta go get bones
let's go get some bones let's kill some
people hurry
on to a crusade we go
oh i should have built a farm oh [\h__\h]
goddammit
what
i know she played the game yesterday did
you get it what was her reaction
did she get this weapon
i hope she got it
it would have been
amazing that's literally innocent
you know
she used it and loved it okay good
i will i will use the bayonets it has a
chance of poisoning it's [\h__\h] cool
look at it
[Music]
[Applause]
what
for three enemies with one tentacle
nice
that's a good aim
i was a good [\h__\h] game if i ever seen
one
[Music]
nice
more grass
performer
what what is that weak [\h__\h]
i need uh a long lawnmower
and that's the pound maybe yeah good
feeling
oh what are these is your new 10 chance
of gaining a heart a blue heart when
killing an enemy or damages everything
on screen when hit
that's
insane
isn't it
one more next you'll see
wait one you want me to take this one
yeah
i guess yeah cause i died last time i
guess i need some
some help from the game but wait
a hard drive with vicious corruption
oh oh it's like something that shows up
and i hit it and then ah okay oh well
let's go for the other one
grass
i don't wanna hit you good bird go away
go away
aggressively doesn't like sushi i guess
that's okay
but i did eat sushi
actually yesterday
i told my members i made a diary entry
[Music]
i don't know because i saw
in the supermarket i was like you know
what i kind of
i was i first gonna go for the gyoza but
then i saw like
this california
maki and i was like
you know this is really out of character
but i kind of
i'm kind of feeling it today being out
of character so why the hell not so i i
bought it and i ate it it was actually
good just pretty decent yeah
as long as it's not raw fish
i'm good
also like uh
i i do believe that like if i were to
eat raw fish sushi then i should eat it
in japan and not in austria where we
don't even have an ocean so
yeah
no it wasn't cooked it was literally
just a
cucumber and avocado
[Music]
sushi
acquired lava flowing what
what for what or when i build my oh when
i built my
my my home
[Music]
is
is not a lie
ah there's a lot of decorations the game
decorated flooring oh cool uh does it
cost money or like materials
i guess probably yeah
oh to the left to the left
the axe yeah it sounds impactful doesn't
it oh we got a tarragon
okay you will be free this time only if
you join my cult next time
wouldn't you always
at least in the beginning wouldn't you
always go for the follower
but there's a question mark here
what could that be
uh puffing is free oh
mystery could be anything ah so it could
also be a follower
yeah but i guess we should probably
of course you can join the cult of
phoenix
already part of it before you know it
you shouldn't get too many followers too
quickly
more mouth to feet yeah that is that's
true
i i guess
could be a special room
you know what i'll go for
i go for the mystery room this time
because yeah
i can sacrifice the best oh
there are some bad ones yeah
let's go for this mystery this time
though
i'm feeling it oh hello
who are you
you guys said that could be anything
right
could it have been like a super normal
room
this looks interesting i can receive a
challenge it seems
it's always a challenge
what is a challenge
without using curses i shall give you a
gift with having i am in the triangle
button
if you failed and allah is not for you
okay no no no triangle
sir your chest is
yeah
he has it on the stick
i don't know why he would do that but
you know his choice his life his choices
he seems to be good
okay weapon on me okay okay okay i think
i can do that
and then he gives me some special gift
oh i don't know
is it a really difficult place uh
still the ocean
like that's the room no no he means the
whole
the whole
he doesn't mean this one room right he
means everything that follows after that
too
oh yeah
[Music]
i'm playing on steam but with ps5
controller
what if i use it by accident man even if
i don't want to
now now i feel like i could just push it
accidentally because i'm nervous
what does he mean this room
the challenge until he shows up okay
okay okay
ah right though
[Music]
so this is just for the map right for
while i'm in the map
in this one
and maybe the critical hit um
i'll challenge the right oh okay okay
okay no no okay then critical hit
okay
oh there it is okay
let's see let's see one more room and
then we're good
this room was too easy what the hell
what the heckity heck
i mean those bones
sorry guys i haven't told you anything
about korea yet
i'm like super focused and like immersed
into the game right now
[Music]
our empty heartless friend is back he
may not have a heart but he does have a
soul okay
oh yeah i could talk during tunic too
yeah yeah that's true
tunic final episode
is i think tomorrow tomorrow
and you know i'm very used to tunics so
i probably can talk a lot during it
animation canceling
oh you mean like while i'm attacking or
what
tomorrow
oh
thank you
i think that meant i i can't actually
read that but that judging by the
by the signs it used i feel like it said
the hair and the dress looks nice in
combination cute
i got the game and i finished it what
tuna core cult of the lamb
you mean tunic
fox phoenix warrior into mommy yes yes
yes
see i knew it i knew it meant that
japanese knowledge coming in handy
and a korean talk honestly i only have
one day that i didn't tell you anything
about yet anyway so it's just one day
but
but it was a very
wholesome and fun and eventful day
actually
guessing level pro max
i've been playing some banner games i
agree i mean they might not be like the
most
popular games but i i'm i'm enjoying the
[\h__\h] out of them but i do
plan to play rust on probably sunday and
amen might even join me to help me a
little bit
so
yeah
[Music]
um
i'll check it out
but i don't know
i feel like this is this this kind of
game or tunic
are making me way more happy right now
we'll see though we'll see i'll give it
a chance
um
why aren't you just jumping you've
completed the challenge
what should you get i think it's a
decent reward for something good what is
that
pick up
a wheelbarrow oh flowers is that just a
decorative decorative item
what is that
what
you're [\h__\h] kidding me mate i could
have gotten a follower but this is what
you give me
it they always just get [\h__\h] like this
huh not worth it
[\h__\h] flower
[Music]
oh let's go
i want all the bones
okay the attack speed is actually really
noticeably noticeably a bit faster this
group
sounded like a lampkeeper
hey
i'm i'm giving birth to hopes and dreams
okay
like every second i'm alive
it's not weaker than what i have now
level two
no oh it's a different thing mine's an
axe that was a cleaver cleaver one a
bane acts one and then simply
okay should i use that
cause i'm using that although that has
no poison i think
yeah oh well
we're strong
it's okay
wait wait no
and there's still devotion
uh
left to steal it first
i get it anyway okay good good okay okay
oh i thought i thought i messed up
[Music]
it's a new axe already we're getting the
poison axe again but level up
okay baby
[Music]
that's what i like to see
beautiful
then we didn't even have to think too
much about
wait recycle
oh i didn't know that
okay i didn't do it until now [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] there's so much grass
[Music]
it's fun
i wonder what other weapons they have
like a like a stabbity spare
for example and i can see them
having something like that or i don't
know
maybe
what is these it's not
from the swirling mist of chaos that you
surround that's around allow me to
regard you a holy
you carry the weight of ageless
centuries upon such diminutive shoulders
yet what is this
but cousin is it ruined doesn't really
look like uh
actually that doesn't look like a hutud
yeah that's not a hutu that's is that a
gator alligator dressing up as a hoot
what's the hootroot again um
i forgot to watch
it's a it's a alligator durian carnival
it seems your stature is deceiving what
the weapon is not without the hand that
wheels to fail enemies to defend honor
to break change
let your crown take the form of one of
these works of iron fortune everlasting
fire may you welcome well promised
liberator
oh my god but it's also just temporary
right
bane sword that's a sword looks like a
stick
oh that's um four right that's four
number four
we've also poisoned that's flaming shot
well can i take all of them
wait but the shot is that like the like
the tentacles i have right now
or is it like a main uh
main weapon main hand weapon it is the
magic okay as a curse
sorry i'm destroying your camp
uh
[Applause]
it's just for this map so it's not such
an important
not such an important uh
thing
poison x
and the one i have right now okay okay
we'll go for that this is new let's go
for this one
ah touch of taro bye bye recycle yeah
i did it right for once
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] i'm so
strong i'm too strong for this world oh
my god
i'm too powerful
i'm gonna be the only cult leader on
this whole earth one day
one day oh
[Music]
i'm not gonna die this time i have way
too much help anyway
what what you gonna do what you gonna do
what you gonna do
okay okay okay
yeah oh [\h__\h] damn it i don't care
[Music]
what are you
nothing compared to my mind that's right
that's like you know the reason why i
chose this outfit and this hairstyle
today is i felt i feel like i look
pretty godly pretty
worthy of worshiping like this don't you
agree i think this is my most
worthy
worship worship worthy outfit i can
possibly have
jesus
outfit
i bless a blessed uh blessed be the
fruit i bless die
to
um
much health and happiness yes
show me your devotion
[Laughter]
jesus jesus
if jews follow a form choose
what
oh you mean like uh you know how i
change them to piggies all the time
well you don't have a chicken so nothing
is
really worth it
to be honest besides the frog maybe
the seeds
okay berry bush seed oh yeah for for the
farm that we're gonna build
a green let's let's do this one
okay lots of
money lots of coins here we go
big success return
i like the system of the game
like both parts like like building your
your base is fun and the fighting and
collecting stuff is fun
oh
hello when i kept you from death
at least this time you didn't [\h__\h]
die weekly
maybe now your followers will start
respecting you
i will be watching your every move
it's very short yeah wasn't it also like
something like 11 hours or so
or two episodes like pretty much similar
to tunic
um
is that
is that correct
hey mary's
that's kind of sad
i want it to be longer
14 hours
okay
so just like tunic kind of like free
hi oh they're so happy to see and this
one's not happy to see me you [\h__\h]
little [\h__\h]
broccoli what's your problem again
[Music]
but this dude also wants something
work make demands of you
oh no
make demands
find a meal and eat sleep i don't know
what do you need
[Music]
he's so angry you also what do you want
to eat patty you might first follow it
later if we want to survive here we're
going to need to okay okay
oh my god we're really like oh my god
wait what do i do first let's uh receive
oh 50 out of 50.
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
mama mia let's do sermon oh well let me
um indoctrinate you first
your name will be
um
no
your name will be
uh elmo oh he doesn't look like ammo
elmo cute
you guys can help me name these peeps
thank you
and choose form you are also going to be
a pig what else
oh look at this bambi so cute
choose color
[Music]
oh you can have this color
what what are you germaphobe oh
minus five five faves when a follower
sacrifice
well you're in the wrong place then
we're gonna start sacrificing at some
point
but i'm not gonna tell him yet
we can fluffy oh right oh [\h__\h] anyway
um
i don't know do whatever
what just happened there are not enough
beds for you ah
okay okay just give me a moment chill
chill uh we're gonna build a bed
it's gonna be in the camp here
i
and we don't need any more right okay
so somebody else can build that and now
we're also gonna build farms right
wear a seat into a crop okay so we do
have
why should we build them
i guess just here's fine one two
three four
five six
seven eight how many how many should we
get
is this a good amount for now
2x2 for farm in the center
what
you don't like the alignment what's the
problem with this how would i know
what's the good way of aligning them
build them closer together
okay like like i can i can put them here
look at the farmer so they can water the
seeds
okay you can edit the placement okay
okay okay
and then
what farmhouse i can't build that yet
right
i'll have to learn that
um
also
oh wait is this a farmhouse farming
bundle
farmer station farming station for allos
allows followers to water nearby crabs
oh let's put seeds here for your
followers so okay
every cult starts somewhere yep
oh we will find a new door called tool
called love at all
upgrade templates trying to collect more
devotion a lot more followers pray
coolio okay but we don't have
devotional left so let's do um
let's do us a
speech speech speech speech speech
speech
german here we go
[Music]
so insightful i know
life changing 10 out of 10 would give
the maximum rating and yelp
amazing are there cults on yelp
great and expensive can we do something
here
can we no i don't think we can
oh
that much dalton oh i can oh this is for
myself
[Music]
well
when she said she ever do i really felt
that
wow
what friendship again thank you thank
you please please keep on reviewing me
rituals coming to the original now
[Music]
this is our ritual song
crossover thresholds i got a uh
achievement
noise
because sparks like the flame turtle
one day i'll take your head
to assert dominance
[Music]
otaku cults are wild
indoctrinating followers is well and
good but there is so much more you can
take from them
are you hitting to something like their
their heads
like i just said
oh complete question perform bless okay
you didn't mean that
oh you will increase it lively to you
wednesday i totally love to you they
will give everything they own yeah like
their life
okay
oh
hello
oh it's dead
increase it follows loyalty to level
them up and they will reward you with
devotion tears and a commandment stone
fragment
[Music]
each time a follower levels up they will
generate additional devotion
when at a sermon or worshiping at the
shrine so be sure to cultivate their
loyalty
[Music]
to increase the loyalty you can give a
follower blessing once a day when you
interact with them okay now we can do
that apparently so you can also give
them gifts complete quests so for them
uh what why would i
they should be giving me gifts
and they should complete quests for me
what the [\h__\h]
what is this
the more lawyer followers you have to
strongly become overcome
i have much to teach you but i'm old and
grow weary and visit me at my home and i
will show you how to harness the true
power of the red crown
oh what
overworld
lonely shack
shake shack
okay
so for now he won't come here to tell me
[\h__\h] anymore i have to come to him
hey everybody is becoming so
disrespectful to me oh
kind of rude
got a building here now i'll help a
little bit why not
why can't i not bless this dude make the
men's interact work
make demands find ah this is a blessing
on this follower of a blessing it will
increase the worthy okay do it
[Music]
oh
okay i'm getting rid of the poop
just be loyal
he's hoes and ain't loyal
i keep on liking him i have to wanted
him planned
ah ah
let's see i'm using the scenes
oh
i now have to build the farm thingy into
the mutton huh
[Music]
so
i see there's a radius so if i put it
here then ah
[Music]
okay well
let's just uh i'll put it here for now
yeah
we can move
can we move them
[Music]
helping i can move the crops you can
move buildings with c what's it on the
controller though
from build yo this is taking a long time
help
yeah
teamwork
don't give up if it's the best culture
that was never the question was it
always knew it
okay from here
oh there we go
okay so this one
move
to here
and this one moved to here and then it's
in in the right
area
okay now is it gonna be watered
automatically or do i have to do that i
guess i'm doing it for now add
fertilizer oh
this is where the fertilizer comes in
handy
now i feel like we're playing some
farming simulator
i need to sign someone okay
they will use the poop that i collected
right
how do i sign oh oh do i go to the
person
who is that oh you have a question
what's your question
oh you did it troy you have the outflow
i'm grateful great leader what did i do
what was the question
they can't fertilize yet
[Music]
wait are you guys hungry
not so much it's okay
[Music]
well let's try uh
since you guys are just hanging out here
not doing anything and you look [\h__\h]
angry patty let me let me let me assign
it to you make demands
but i can't ask them to do that
specifically specifical thing
the quest was to build a plum
talk to them and choose the option
of work
ah okay ah here i can do something
specific ah
[Music]
you built and pretend funds
okay patty you're the farm tender
can i help them
this is a lot of work man
wow
i would break a sweat if i did that so
i'm gonna stop
we're so close to another up uh upgrade
yeah
a lot of stone
okay what else were we supposed to do
maybe uh make some food
uh but do i even have berries let me see
there was a bush down here i think
no
ah here
getting those berries
have strawberries in my fridge i need to
eat them today because i bought them
yesterday and if i don't eat them too
yet today they're gonna go bad
really fast
those supermarkets strawberries hey
where's the bed
[\h__\h] i need a do i need like uh one
of those crowns
what the [\h__\h] it stole my seed
huh
what the actual [\h__\h] batman i was gonna
like welcome you but the hell
how do i protect it
scarecrow later
okay
i guess i'll have to wait
i can only make two i need more berries
no [\h__\h] way i i i got it in the green
i i hid it in the green area now
hey
i'm trying my best here
yeah only one food don't feel
how can i make this grow faster
it's the ping man it's the ping
that was rigged down
a weird shade of green no
it was green i got the edge
yeah cause i'm straight edge man
okay then we
we gotta go and get some more materials
quick oh is there berries up there
i'm seeing berries
oh
let's go
why'd you stop while you're going to
it sleep just enough
r.i.p
hello
wow well hi
hi
did you turn off my stream
are we back oh okay
i was talking to smooverella
it's movie how did you know it was
smoothie
how did you guys know it was smoothies
oh hi
i've been cuddling so much this movie
but this movie also has been
um secret cozy
she's been losing so much hair it's
insane like even when i brush her it's
never ending every time i like touch her
every time she loses like
such a chunk of hair
with every s
of abby cause every time we touch you
lose so much hair and every time we
touch my allergies go crazy
every time we
[Music]
touch chatting season never ends
i should sing that in color okay one day
okay collecting
i guess we should go for this one we
don't have any dead people yet
hallelujah probably soon though so we
should go for this one
yes number two
[Music]
[Laughter]
times are tough we can cook grass meals
oh really followers won't like it but
thank you for teaching me that oh
make them don donkey eat grassy grill
oh of course i will do that you even
want to do it well hell yeah okay
i will uh
oh i can make so many here
and one berry meal
one two three four five one two three
four five six seven you make me feel
like eleven
[Music]
oh really
oh don't stop complaining
stop complaining
at least it's food okay
he ate a grass meat but mine is five
fate but like eh you you asked for it
it's only a loose loose situation no
matter what what the hell oh
no you wanted me greatly that i'm
eternally grateful okay
okay
well then
it's a new day right so i can do a
sermon right
here
worship me
somebody
[Music]
[Applause]
oh they love me
[Music]
as they
do a ritual too it's on cooldown okay
okay i think it's time that we go out
again
soon
i think
yeah i think i can go right
the bushes are growing nicely
yeah i'll go i'll go
the sermons really touch my heart
ah they're all mad oh come on don't be
such a little piece of [\h__\h]
here i'm cleaning it for you even
so don't be one okay yes okay stop
[\h__\h] so much
[Music]
i haven't blessed you that have i come
on don't don donkey you want a blessing
here there you go
yeah
you're welcome
make someone's farm i already signed
someone to test did they just stop
i was just
digging something up
what is this
needy follow over those
i think the farms are being intended no
i mean like anything wait didn't i ask
patty to attend the farm well that does
elmo
i think there's attending their ending
oh good
she looks really [\h__\h] excited to be
doing it too
someone can be leveled up what do you
mean
like a member ah this one
loyalty where you would oh that's why
you were glowing so much oh
yeah
oh what's that speak to patty level two
oh it says level two at the end of their
name
interesting
okay
okay these are literally like my cats
they poop so much and i have to clean it
up i have to feed them i have to clean
[\h__\h] up for them and i have to give them
a space to sleep there they are my kitty
cats
hey what
you have to go to the lonely shack wait
i wanted to go to the no no no
i wanna go fight
yes
go go go go
[\h__\h] bird get out of here
sounds like they're your god
yeah i'm in a cat cult
oh
cool looks like a dagger a fastblade
designed for many cuts low damage but
lightning
divine blast knocks back knocks back
enemies within your range while also
damaging them
cool
we're taking both
it is very fast yeah
all right new weapons
fresh out of the oven
it's time
[Music]
so it is through the red crowns it's
upon the brow of another
[Music]
oh that's [\h__\h] creepy oh my god wait
i wanted to drink some water
[Music]
okay
i like this new weapon
oh okay i should do that when they're
like too close to me
oh [\h__\h] my help
keep on dodging keep on dodging thank
you for the red super chat
you also have a nice day yeah
go enjoy yourself on this beautiful day
okay wow that was a lot of enemies
oh i got a temporary heart
thank you
thank you praised beef the fruit blessed
be the fruit
[Music]
oh yes speaking of flowers yesterday
after the collab
ahmed actually
left pretty early uh to take care of her
new fish
oh
but um fauna and cronie
and me stayed behind and we talked like
for over an hour
endlessly it was really late for me like
past midnight but
i don't know we still talked for for
ages it was really nice to talk for and
talk with other
members for once because like
normally is like after collabs
often everybody just scatters very
quickly
and then there's the thing where i
because of time zones don't get to talk
too much many of them
a lot of the time so
yeah
but it was really nice because we talked
about a lot of really
deep
deep stuff
now got some things off of my chest i
guess
that was like stressful stuff from
real life
problems oh
what the [\h__\h]
oh those things again
i haven't seen those in a while so i got
a little bit careless
okay left or right left
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay what is that what is that
green blob i'm guessing i should not
step into that otherwise i'm gonna be
poisoned
or is that my important no it's his
poison right oh oh wow
okay pretty good
pretty good
oh
ah but only for the time when i'm
stepping on it right
nice
good i feel like i didn't even take
damage
well you had the chance to get things
off the pitches yeah yeah not only me i
think um
yeah we exchanged some
some worries
talked about this and that so that was
that was really nice
yeah
i'm glad they stayed to talk to me i
thought they would also just go
oh wait i need to give a gift to my
followers huh i didn't do that yet
i'll do that when i get back oh quiet
stonewall okay
you know i've been the same decorations
but i might get into that too
might get quite deep into decorating my
cult eventually i missed the room
i did i did i did thank you
i forgot it's too focused
cool
[Music]
i guess i'll go for this one this time
no why not
okay
a close one yeah
oh
[Music]
hey what is this
a new building that i can build a recipe
for a building
maybe
that route is interesting it has like
oh change gold coins to meet or
something like that oh shock
[Music]
oh that was a stream hiccup on y'all
please stay with me
youtube
should i go to the shop check it out
because we didn't check it before
i can get food there
follow is always good
ah go for it up to you no
why not you have cash
okay
yeah let's check it out
oh what
oh my god it's so cute it's like a
restaurant
a snail
fresh
[Music]
i didn't even see the other options i
was trying to talk to you
oh is it a rainbow shrimp but wait what
else was there what else was there we
got salmon though
it doesn't sound too bad
my fish
was that free
berries and seeds oh okay i mean
compared to berries and seeds i would
say the fish is more
um
it gives us more
more
nutrients
you get the snail you get some secret ah
snail
oh my god i'm so sorry
don't you dare touch my lap
i'm so sorry what if i do it again
should i
hit it again
wait there's some stuff behind you
wait i can destroy all of this
there's quite a lot of free food here oh
berries
i thought i have to pay for stuff
salami sami calm down
hit me baby one more time should i
should i
just scare it
what's going on
they're crying
move on
[Laughter]
hey it's this birthday and i have
birthday hats off
[Music]
but somebody in the chat told me to
attack the shell
they told me
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
why did you tell me to do this do i have
to kill him
oh [\h__\h]
he has quite a lot of health
okay i can do this i can do this
[Music]
the phoenix
[Laughter]
keep on gobbling
i'm being like a little bit more careful
now because i'm kind of scared to [\h__\h]
it up
come here
lucas come little shrimp rainbow shrimp
oh sorry sorry that i hit the snail
again i don't wanna i didn't want to do
that don't make it any more extra angry
you know i wanna know the secret that
you're hiding
you think it's me
[Music]
i'm so sorry
just don't hurt us anymore then return i
will continue to do business with you
[Music]
i got something out of it a quiet
massive monster try and pray to the
mighty monster
is that just decoration or is it a rival
cult that i can build inside my home
[Music]
true
just for like completion sake
sorry
you know
i have to clean up nicely so
oh my god i'm so sorry i feel so guilty
[Music]
i'm sorry
are you monster no
not monster
not at all
believe
believe in the purpose guys what the
[\h__\h] man until you want to be sacrificed
huh
wormy boy oh
carrot card
oh thank you
extra heart
looking at my low health right now i do
need it
you know the monster and massive monster
hey
the friar with the non-believers
if you're an actual believer then you
would be happy about the friar anyway
[Music]
no damage run
thanks for the fairies
thanks for the berries
ah
i feel like i missed the parent card
[Music]
it feels so good to like loot everything
is this necklace
the quite moonlike let's dream of me
follower will never sleep what
that's freaky
wait they will not sleep because they
don't want to see dreams of me
what if you get a necklace what makes
you dream of me wouldn't you want to
sleep and dream of me
shouldn't make them sleep more
one month away from the fryer
let's go
the goal
the goal is so near
okay
uh
tons of torah too interesting
rain sword two
flaming shot two
i think
i'll go for the sword oh we didn't have
this one before
recycle that
all right thank you dude
right
oh wait there's some bones
hey hey
i used fire on the last one
what's going on here
oh
[Music]
wow wow wow
cleaning up nicely now i'm not
forgetting about the grass anymore
are you proud guys
so much stuff
scramble grab it
i got it last second
yeah amy would cry
if she heard i killed the squirrel
instead of feeding it with nuts
i'm sorry
it has to be it's for the sake of the
cult an attack 10 chance of negating
damage
no it's not good for me
although i might not even get my let
myself be attacked
um
question mark is that a challenge again
will that give me a [\h__\h] reward again
because i don't know what to think about
that
thanks for the pinky
um
oh it's a random room
all right let's go for that looks like
fun i guess if unless they scammed me
again
oh steak oh
i'm bringing back so much food to my
people they will be so happy and
delighted
many many a materials
listen
slushy
youngest after five twice his eyes he
lost whoa
temperamental heck it with her fruit
cutlet
cowardly calamar's
[Applause]
once the brightest of the five tilder
skull were split
[Music]
it's the monkeys
plus one
the one who hates made it so
that's what that was some lore lore room
thank you and some meat
lure always goes best with some steak
yeah
amazing voice acting i'm glad you like
it
thank you you look so cute thank you bye
i have
one and i have extra hearts so that's
that's pretty good
i feel pretty confident have confidence
yeah
all right here we go let's go here we go
i'm scared i'm scared
oh
faint dagger two
tried to raise it too
oh low damage lightning quick chance of
forcing enemies oh it was poison now i
thought i want to go for this one i
don't know should i keep mine or go for
this one
mamma mia
i'm gonna sleep oh goodnight my thanks
mate
i'd keep the sword sword is better oh
okay
then i guess uh getting something from
here is not oh but wait we can get it
and then recycle the new weapon right
because they they still give us the
option to like take
what we were just wearing right
daggers better versus bosses but sword
is better for clearing worms oh
[Music]
should i recycle that now
okay
flaming chattel
oh man are there gonna be enemies who
can shoot me from a distance
that is terrifying
i don't like the part of that
they will have much power
tarot card
this poison damage to enemy struck yeah
i don't even need a poison wait does
that give me like double the poison
damage then if i already have a
poisonous weapon plus that tarot card
oh god oh no
no this diaper was [\h__\h] me up
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] wait i'm gonna die in this
room
i honestly i can't i can't i can't this
is too much for my brain
oh please stop it
oh they did okay but i lost a lot of
hearts from that [\h__\h] that was too much
for me
too much oh avoiding spoilers okay i
probably won't go much further today
after this this level
we'll see we'll see because i have to
read super chats from the vacation too
ah now they offer this to me
now i'll go with my fire whatever
[Music]
no be confident
oh i poisoned him okay
are you going
okay good good
okay okay no no no it's pretty it's a
pretty easy easy opponent
it just takes some time
i love the music though
yup yup okay that's fine that's a pretty
easy easily dodgeable attack oh
yeah that one doesn't go very far either
be careful
music makes me want to dance tango
oh
[Music]
oh my god that timing of me shooting
that was not gonna be good but
uh i did it in an absolute perfect
moment did you say that
i predicted it i predicted his
his arrival
look at this little baby
oh baby
what's up
let me bring you to a safe place yes
safe place
okay berries woods or stone i would say
i mean we didn't we did get a lot of
food on this trip
um
we're not really lacking
or are we let me see
69 nice we're if anything we're lacking
stones but
should i get stones of berries
food
you have a lot of foreign
[Music]
there's never enough food
okay
vlog is ready for another sermon all
right i'm back has collapsed okay we
gotta go back fast and fix this
return to cook
look eight fish seven fish 21 berries
three steaks and four
other meats
damn
that was
big big big success
yeah final area boss next
you mean like from that door the next
map i would do would be the final one ah
then i might play one more map
one more crusade
oh exciting
do not make the mistake of becoming the
servant of your followers they are for
you to use to your advantage
the faith is a resource spend it as you
would gold for you can always regain
your trust with a well-placed gesture of
kindness
wise words indeed yeah
let it empower you let it give you
unspeakable things spend them to your
will
i grant you the power to read their
fatal little minds
mind reading
holy [\h__\h]
interactive followers to read their
thoughts as well as see how hungry oh
that's really useful
ah then i actually know what i should
tell them to do
what are you guys thinking huh
you guys think i can't read your minds
huh
oh i know very well what you're thinking
i know very very well at all times you
guys are too easy to read after all
you don't even have to tell me
no fart said empty
are you sure about that
i'm not so sure
this action will be available to you
okay cool
yeah
out of the phoenix oh it's written there
i just noticed that's cool
hello mommy's back did you not deposit
anything are you guys [\h__\h] useless or
what
[\h__\h] you
okay oh
divine inspiration
[Music]
why are you so happy the one next to me
and your name shall be
um
perfect
shot because i killed you with the
perfect shot and i'm quite proud of that
[Music]
choose color you are kind of like uh
really pale color
[Music]
natural skeptic
[\h__\h] that
[Music]
my netherlands is written all over my
face
okay what do we have
and you can i don't know clear rebel
collect some stone
what is it speak to patty
[Music]
i wanted to do that anyway it's good
that i accepted the quest before that
okay oh can i repair that oh
i don't have to build a new one i just
repair it this one too
and then we need a new bed when you
follow up
doing it right now as we speak
the camps are
getting bigger and bigger
uh six out of six okay
and
can i learn some new right oh i don't
need to learn them oh it's already there
cool
pungent fish stew is punching the bad
word
tasty fish meal
okay well
stringy meat grill
meagre mixed meal
basic barrel
hearty meat bread oh that sounds good
doesn't it okay we'll make em we'll make
some stuff
this is what we're serving today
it's not a bad word i need strong smell
okay okay
let's not [\h__\h] this one up
[Laughter]
wait i think i'm missing one
meal
i only made five but i have six
followers right
now
make more i make more don't worry about
it
[Music]
i'll make you know what i'll make all of
these
yeah why not
hi
hi there you go now no one can complain
patty has become bravely we'll die if
you guys have those
daddy wait which one is patty
daddy
alamo
wait what's with you you're also sick
bed rest you bed rest
honey
what the [\h__\h] that bird
big berries
wait we have so many berries now just
about it ah where's
connie
hi
which poop made you
this one did this one make you sick
bad poop
bad bad bad poop
where did you come from
did he just join
on his own well
it was my cooking
what i made good i made good food what
the pungent fish
should i never make it ever again does
it always make people sick
who
the [\h__\h]
are
you
keyboards please
who is this
[Laughter]
congratulations on your new name uh you
also have like a
gray color there you go
germaphobe
you notice the sun is when you preach
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] yeah what
welcome
oh wait having so many join oh uh yeah
yeah
[Music]
i won't get to that eventually
accepting
well
at least we completed the quest i guess
what what what
why you all sick wait let me make some
new beds okay i'm i'm now i'm panicking
okay sleeping
sleeping bag
here there you go beautiful placements
uh
holy [\h__\h]
yeah
why why did you arrive and you're
already sick
[Music]
are you hungry
no wait they're hungry i see it now okay
never mind and you're sleepy are you
sleepy
maybe you should sleep
[Music]
sleep go sleep
uh
okay i'll make up food
i guess but you is that you who gave me
the questions yeah
go okay to sleep
and uh i make food oh god oh i thought
we had more than enough food but
[Music]
yubby
basic berry bowl and uh some hearty
rough there you go it's all ready
ah
[\h__\h]
did i [\h__\h] it up
was that burnt
or was it getting eating safe
[Music]
what was that
did you just
i think it was uh yeah barely fairly
decent food let me clean your poop can i
build a toilet
ever
is that a thing that i'll be able to do
yeah food i have berries that i can pick
that's your church
[Music]
will you help me satisfy this dark
desire
i mean i don't want to lose 35 faves so
um
that is
for that i should
i should i should
i should kick you out of the cult to be
honest
that is disgusting
i i will judge you and so you may have
you may have asked me to not judge you
but i will judge you for that that is
disgusting
that is so disgusting
don't kink shame this is not a cake man
it's unhealthy
well okay i'll do it green man
can i do it did i get a new recipe
i hope no one else will eat it ew
50 chance of causing illness and
diarrhea well i hope he doesn't die out
of his wish
[Music]
hey
here it's ready
um
nobody else will eat that right oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] they're coming for the food are
they
uh uh demand uh
[Music]
oh he's already on the way to eating
that right is he yeah okay good good
good good good good it's your wish so
you have to eat it don't make anyone
feel
like disgusting
and like throwing up just because you
wish for these disgusting things
you did it broccoli ate some poop
he became bravely ill and well bad
you deserve that oh and you pooped out
boobs what a big surprise
i should let you die
i should let you die seriously
did you learn a lesson from that at
least will you stop eating poop now
if yes and i'll let you rest a little
bit
okay let me get those berries
sacrifice them
i should i mean i feel like i'm having
too many people here right now anyway
uh we don't need to grow bigger red we
have so much space here
i shouldn't be intimidated already
okay we're gonna
oh
oh i can plant flowers too huh
oopsie okay
water ring
why am i doing all this
[Music]
poop
he deserves a name change yeah
i wish i could capture those tarantulas
and sell them for good money like in
animal crossing
[Music]
good stuff
oh
why am i doing all this
i wanted some extra fertilizer
captain tarantulas get into your heart
don't still eat them
wait what can you actually do that
can you actually do that
you can i can catch the spiders
what
hey but i can't
attack while i'm here though
the button doesn't work
i'm running out of fertilizer you guys
need to poop more
okay but it works without fertilizer too
right
is any poop
lying around
oh yes
day 11.
is there is there a final date that's
like already set in stone
no right
there's no limit is there
there's no file there okay okay time for
serving yeah
listen
[Music]
oh yeah
what is this anyway frankie your
christmas will appear in your ooh
and this one
increase the starting level of weapons
when you're being oh
i kind of want this one first
so true
i know
so inspiring
people should write books about me
i should write a book about myself
like those youtubers that write books
that are absolute [\h__\h]
what can we do here can i do one of
these down
um
yeah
oh
instruct them on the liturgies
surrounding their daily bread preach on
the value of earthly goods
teach them uh the true meaning of
obedience
have them
profit both labor and love reassure them
that death is not the end and which one
do i do
what is this what does that mean
instructing all the literary surrounding
their daily bread
[Music]
i should write a book about cats i don't
know that much about cats
sustenance
food is good
okay
so it might be good afterwards broke
well
so they won't
hope i mean that wasn't quite the
problem but okay
[Music]
perform a ritual and your temple to
declare fast fellows will not eat or be
hungry for oh that's good when i'm like
out of food
unlock the feasting ritual throw a grand
feast for your followers and refill
their hunger and in 25 no i'll do this
one
and then i can save up some food
now we don't need to do the ritual
anymore
that's actually good
[Music]
noise don't faking the chicken
the chicken
with the pigs in this case
oh
new ritual
fast yeah let's go
75 bones for that happy
oh
now let's do this one and we have to
uh
make everything
effective
it has begun
don't look like you're suffering so much
yeah
you're happy right you're happy to be
doing that i know i know you are
with this
oh there you go
i unlocked that one okay
good good to see now
don't even think about chicken nuggets
i know i know it's hard i know i get you
but you have to be strong
why are they all praying
do they have anything else to do
oh i can do one ah
we don't have anyone dead yet so it's
not really urgent
we can do upgraded shelters
offering statue
or prison
if offerings in your honor
holds naughty followers
shelter missionary send your followers
in the holy quest to gather resources
that is if they make it back alive
scarecrow prevents birds from stealing
the seeds oh yeah that's not that urgent
either
follower will generate what
stone
the usual room
and
they haven't been that naughty yet i
think i'll go for this one first maybe
the offerings
[Music]
sakiniko nishiokana
lumber yard
we have enough
we have enough things
for resources
well then i would go for a missionary
maybe but it wouldn't be sad if they
don't come back they end up dead
that would actually be pretty sad for
some of them
not for our poopy boy
ah dosio
resources always research
okay i'll do a stone mine
for now
sorry
you guys tell me lava yet but i feel
like we have less stones so
yeah
we'll get a new one soon why are they
all praying
i have nothing to do
oh i really
don't not really have much oh there's a
tree you can drop that [\h__\h] tree
hi
that's why he just came out of nowhere
without even me finding him you should
go speak with them and see what they
have to say
thank you perfect shot
thank you i i knew it had a bad feeling
with that guy
who the [\h__\h] are you is probably also
one of them where is where is yabi
here you are
what a beautiful day in paradise might i
say you look extra like that sounds like
something a spy would say
if only you had the prison
[Music]
talk to me
see the thoughts
remember for one day age 29 fasting i
would not eat drinking water
[Music]
doesn't say anything about being a spy
weirdly
wait i did talk to him is that the quest
already uh dunzo
i guess it is
wait what
complete quest
obviously they're hiding something you
must believe me i do believe you
he said it was a ruler but i believe him
wait is the is the conclusion now that
it was wrong
i mean obviously he wouldn't have
admitted it right away
i could build a toilet now
i can make a seat silo silo that i
haven't done yet
it doesn't have to be like inside right
can it just be
like next to it
[Music]
i didn't unlock it needs to be inside
put it
just near
can be next it doesn't have okay there
we go
i'll pull it here
go built yeah
[Music]
anything else we didn't build yet
i ran out of coins
on y'all
i only have 11.
are you guys still sick
oh these ones are almost healed again i
think
okay okay okay
[Music]
well if i don't give them a job
they'll just continue to pray right
i should tell
i should tell you
to
chop the trees
and nobody's attending
the farms i think so go do that and now
i think that's all we need for now
i told someone to chop the trees
nobody's going there are you going to a
different train no
[\h__\h]
work
wait no test what do you mean no tasks
available
there's a tree right there
ah oh yeah i should really just give the
[\h__\h] gift
oh wait not to you yavi i don't trust
you
i don't believe
in you
wait i wanna
put the chat perfect chat
oh that's a surprise okay i'll give a
i'll give a gift to you
consider yourself blessed
by your leader
[Music]
oh
i have one gift the necklace
i was wondering what i could give to you
it's a necklace get red
oh
i did it
[Music]
uh
seeds
i'll put them all in there
maybe i should make one more farm
[Music]
why not
or like more more plots at least yeah
one two three four five six oh that's it
oh yeah that costs money too oh [\h__\h]
oh well and then they will attend the
farm i hope
um
work
hand the [\h__\h]
doesn't want to do it
you're so sick
okay i'll leave you alone then
okay okay
bankrupt no
i'm not bankrupt
it's not all about money
it's about the future it's about about
the goals
okay i'm going for the last level now
i'm a little bit scared a little bit
frightened but
but i've received a lot of love from my
cult
so i think i think i'll be fine finally
let us end this i'll be waiting in my
temple come with his true power
oh
it's quite far
okay here we go
oh wait
there's something to choose all right
i'll take the traitor's razor full
the oceans of blood hold to aim a
projectile that spreads black
what was that is that a real thing
bitcoir
i cur icker on landing
hold to aim
i have to aim there's no auto aim for
that one
oh [\h__\h]
is no longer alive or so is dead now i
was kind of scared for a moment man
donkey has grown on me he's a good dude
good follower i'm glad he's no longer
ill though
hallelujah
it's a shiny one
[Music]
this is when the gacha finally makes you
feel like it was worth it
[Music]
beautiful
i feel like
wait [\h__\h] wait wait
i thought for some reason i thought we
were getting both so i was like just
whatever let's get out of here
because sometimes you know what the
you know
[Music]
it's okay that was on purpose i'm
choosing heart mode because the game is
too easy
[Music]
why did i do that
okay still gonna win true at least we
saw the shiny you know at least we saw
that
made me feel special and happy for a
moment
we're going to be lucky and get another
one trust me
also hey
what's up
he was unlike the rest of his skinhold
orders dealt with the flux chaos
feminine pestilence war
things which in their constancy must
transpose he's speaking in riddles to me
and yet he was in the inevitable the
obstinate and irresistible the one who
waits
truly peculiar it would seem this a
petted seeds
noble and did you break ancient bow bow
and primordial bone delay cool
tradition
and appetites augment nonetheless stop
tears pay for sunder
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah that same uh question mark question
mark question mark oh you also haven't
seen the word before yata and i don't
feel so stupid
okay
what
what what was he saying
okay oh
like you funny words
hey at least i'm not the only one who
didn't get what he was saying
oh okay cool that was a good aim oh sh
can i step into it without getting
damaged
okay
oh
that's like the the thingy and hollow
killer that you can spread all over
i miss hollow cure
update went when updated
hello
[Music]
my head is looking very round are you i
am
trying to praise me it's not how you do
it
oh
okay i take it
november ooh
okay
well we don't need food right now but
there's uh two shop options and one with
a follow
one do i want a new follower
and question mark
those are but you know you can always
also look here this one comes with an
extra boss an extra boss
and this one comes with
death and coins
oh i don't have the money for it oh i
guess so
i don't have phone that's true
i want the thing with the money
oh that one is the follower
death in texas it's a free card
what
that thing up there
or that one
oh that one
the hat
oh that's a free card okay well um
and then let's go for a question mark i
guess
hey
yeah let's go for the question mark
because then we get a free card too yeah
what the hell
oh
[Laughter]
oh i got it okay what do we have here
choose the seized heart or choose half a
blue heart what does a diseased heart do
cause this heart is better
[Music]
i believe you
that was faster yeah wait what the [\h__\h]
is that what does that do
i never had that one before
so that was a that was a good
question mark roon
i appreciate it
wait i can go down from there i don't
have to go straight up
i can choose to fight more and explore
more
from there on
my uh
at least it looks like i have the option
ow why did i do that
i saw it coming and i still let it hit
me what's happening what the [\h__\h] is
happening
we're not fighting yet right
your persistence is beginning to ignore
me little lamp
amazing yourself clever you may think
yourself righteous in your service to
him
but you should not be so trusting of the
chained one
oh well it's too late for talk once such
as you deserves no absolution this will
not end well for you
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh please okay okay that works
oh [\h__\h]
oh they have perfect tiles
i wonder how this game is in very hard
mode this is medium i mean
it does feel medium
it's not too tough but it's a little bit
challenging i like it
but as we know the gamer
of
whole live english i've been pretty good
at tunic these days so
recently i feel like my gaming skills
have been
getting much better
don't you agree
also did i just negate the damage twice
in a row of what
was that sound
the gamer
yes
yeah i did right
sounded like it
it's made like a thing a decorated bag
of camellia flowers coolio
you've been doing much better thank you
oh i got a crit instead is that so
it felt like something was blocked
is it made
i know
[Music]
his nose and his mustache are still in
the normal place
and kendall keep your eyes off my fishes
they're right enough for the both of us
the best fishing can be found at
pilgrim's passage
where's that you say let me show you
oh he's teaching me about a secret
fishing spot
oh yeah oh yeah
see now get out of here i feel like just
like with that one shop with the snail
we could choose to kill him and fish
could we
i i like him though so i don't really
want to hurt him
[\h__\h] that bird though [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
peach freeze yeah thank you for your
offerings okay now i will not kill you i
will not attempt to kill you
did that purchased moonwalk his way out
of the map
[Laughter]
okay then bye bye dude oh wait there's
more fish
thank you nice i appreciate the offering
oh there it goes please give me my shiny
bag give me my shiny bag
i got the same one again
i chose the right one
thank you they really want me to have it
oh my god what
something sucks about this place
am i really okay to accept all of this
latin oh nice pretty um
i needed money and the game gives me
money
thank you for cooperating game i thought
one of these was gonna spawn an enemy or
something but no
what
[Music]
beautiful beautiful beautifully
humiliated
um
rng streamer look
you didn't know the room
because yeah that could have been like
any room right because they're putting
it together randomly
i'm so
lucky so lucky lucky lucky
stream of luck is real hell yeah baby
what'd i get here ooh
the axe or the dagger five and five
both poisoning
i think i'll go for the put a dagger
actually
yeah
and then
recycle that one thank you
i like the fast damage you know i'm a
sucker for it so we could uh we could go
down here for food
or
wow we could even like
we could go up here then we could go
down and go down here and then we could
go up here
hey can we really no we can't actually
no no we can't go down never mind
i thought i could
but no only the white uh the white lines
i thought that would be
fun but then you could end up going
literally everywhere
kind of
okay what's up you guys said this is a
card right but this this could be
anything this could be anything
[Music]
the crown are you calling this a crown
could even be a card yeah i could mean
could be a bowl of poo no way
another decoration yeah [\h__\h] dad okay
we're going to this one
it's like actually something cool
oh that's really scary your possessions
will follow you through death
oh okay for like if i die here in this
case i'm not losing anything
cool okay but i'm not gonna die
okay it's like a
nice safe point
basically
no i won't lose nice okay could i have
gotten something else out of that
wow
i will steal your devotion
let me take
everything you have
done
okay here we go
we're getting closer to the bus
gosh i love the sound it makes when i
kill the monsters
i'm enjoying
the games i play recently so much
i know about you guys i hope you enjoy
seeing me enjoy games
a lot of
good games
these days
listen
to temporary hearts containers thank you
[Music]
games are meant to be enjoyed hell yeah
a lot
feels really nice no pain only winning
yeah yeah
oh do you guys want to know what i woke
what nice thing i woke up to today when
i tweeted about i want to know one
another
[Music]
i know
i'll tell you
now that i'm getting used to fighting
i think i can talk while i'm
talk properly about stories while i'm
fighting yay
well well when i woke up today i finally
got the first
draft that was already like pretty much
the whole song
of my new songs music video
yeah
baby finally finally finally finally and
it already looked pretty good left or
right
on this way
i got that made wrong choice probably
carrot card probably on the left side
oh that was fast
[Music]
i think i'll go for this one actually
because i don't like the korean curse
that i have
yeah
is it getting closer to release yeah
well i would have hoped to release it
within
um this month but
even though it might be finished within
this month it has to go for like legal
checks and all that before i release it
and that might be the thing that
stops it from being released within this
month
but then in the first week of the next
month probably i i i think i hope well
it's soon in another case it's soon
i guess i'll go for the rabbit's foot
[Music]
although aren't we like pretty much done
here like oh wow
maybe for the anniversary no no no no
i'm not gonna overlay that but i want to
bring it out as soon as possible
[Music]
i have them actually
i think you guys will be very
delighted by the music video because i
have a very special idea for this one
a lot of special ideas actually
so
i'm really excited to show
i can't tell though
[Music]
i'm really excited
it's very different
an interesting concept
wow this this is you can notice you see
it's a special
room because of the path and all that
looks different from usual kawaii
but my health is looking pretty good and
yeah
my weapons are fine i hope fine then
keep your secrets i will
let's just start attacking anyway i
started blasting
you guys we're tired of your little lamp
time to put an end to this frivolous
masquerade
[Music]
wow okay that's impressive man they just
did that right there they just did it
oh my okay [\h__\h]
is it gonna be my follower afterwards
anyway i started laughing
should i ignore those tiny
[Music]
what is moths doing oh
okay you're coming here wonderful
pretty good so far
easy boss
easy too easy
what is that okay
oh too easy i'm such a gamer
again okay
yeah it's too boring otherwise it's not
a proper party
[Music]
earthquake
all the way to the end okay he has a
face too i like that that's fun
he doesn't continue doing the same
attacks until the very end
okay but he's still using the same old
ones too
recycling
okay uh
earthquake
but i rolled right through that
sometimes you need to
just accept
the way things are
in the bathroom
you need do you need oh no do you need a
pacifier you need milk
you need milk from mommy
oh
you have no mommy
maybe you should join my cousin and i
can be your mommy
[Music]
i can't promise you uh milk though
almost no damage to me
gives me a heart wait let me just get
some bones you know
i have to bring everything home that i
can possibly get
to get the respect from my cult
i will take the heart and i will eat it
like daenerys
i'm
you have taken the beating heart of a
heretic
oh
wait we don't get this one as our
follower oh too bad
the red crown can feast the pot inside
oh we're really gonna eat it
unlock new crown abilities visit the
altar
in your temple so at least the true
power of the red crown
oh that's fun
what a shame yeah i would have liked to
see his small baby form you know like
the other ones that after fighting them
turned back into like
little little
animals that was cute
a simple way to light the dark okay cool
a lantern oh we have two different
lanterns
[Music]
don't really have the money for that
kind of stuff oh a trophy for killing
this cool
that looks nice
it was kind of cute
but it's just decorative huh
kfb we got pretty far with this game
today we did uh
uh one fourth i guess
if i'm assuming correctly dead done
yeah we got
ooh 127 coins
quite a lot of bones some meat that we
don't need at the moment we can we can
store it
but for when the feet the the fasting is
over
oh nice
hello friend
unless she fell before you like a grain
of sand before a tidal wave
impressive little man
looking forward to your future endeavors
oh
my children they're all angry or some of
them are dancing though hey why's not
everybody and dancing what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
attendance list writes down everybody
who was not dancing for me what the [\h__\h]
followers are inspired by your victory
against bishop
are you guys going to sleep oh you're so
tired oh man they have like uh but eye
bags
what
oh no it's broken i'll repair it here
there you go there you go
i didn't assign bets to the new
followers but they will just sleep in it
anyways right
it'll be fine
oh yeah sleepy sleep
good night
oh it's so cute how did they sleep look
at the berry bushes they took care of
them all right
[Music]
and they're always upset
totally i will take care of this before
we
uh collect oopsie [\h__\h]
they will plant the seeds right if when
i'm done with this
i don't want to do the planting that's
annoying
really messed up analog crust thing you
kind of yeah cause you get like
different animals too yeah yeah yeah
although here at least you can change
their appearance and all that in animal
crossing
you just bully them as long as you can't
you get them get rid of them because you
think they're ugly too ugly for your
island wait
did i just
oh wait i just uh pulled out my net for
the spider but i didn't catch it how did
i do that with x i guess no yeah x
[Music]
oh why was that sound so sad there are
not enough but oh what
oh did one break again
well it's not my fault that you're so
fat
you break the bed
man
oh i didn't have enough money okay okay
thank you for giving me the quest
because
i was gonna do that once i have money
yeah okay
no fat shaming the piggies they're pigs
so
what what am i expecting right
that cute piece
my chubby cuties chunky monkeys
okay have fun with that
okay
uh we have to take care of this place
before we leave i i could play this
endlessly right now to be honest but i
need to read super chats
but first i'll take care of it a little
bit so we have a still mine um
guess how
how does this work they just go in
i didn't have to build anything around
right they just go in i'll put it here
and then i would like to learn how to
make the other thing but uh
wait i don't need to make food
[Music]
let's get all this
would it close the stones
oh let's just go inside to get the
stones
okay uh
oh yeah you see now we can get the
lumber yard all right okay
[Music]
very efficient
place that
right next to it can you guys have fun
with it please
do your best impress your leader aka me
[Music]
now if you guys are ready for it
alas shabbat event
[Music]
[Applause]
amazing
wow
this just leaves me speechless and i
think it leaves you guys speechless too
what is this
we could go for
this one or this one vampiric weapons
and bearing weapons have a chance to
heal the wielder using the life force of
a slain foe
it will appear on your crosshairs
or increase the starting level of
weapons when you begin a new crusade
[Music]
oh wait no we already got that one right
yeah yeah
i guess yeah i will steal some life
become ass vampire
oh yeah
i am invigorated beautiful beautiful
they're all so happy
oh yeah the crown the crown
[Music]
we have a heart now so we can do like
one of these right
yeah yeah when caleb and crusade
uh run for the first time sacrifice of
far to be
yeah
i can sacrifice someone else so that i
would be resurrected on the spot
wow
that for a cause um once a day eat a
meal to receive a blue heart
i can eat a meal
focus once on a crusade run to instantly
return to the base
oh so i can get out of it faster if i
need to for some reason
escape
receive a deceased heart at the
beginning of each crusade run
well in the end i'll get all of them
right because there will be four hearts
and i only have four choices anyway
okay i would go for either this one or
the one on the very right
for now
what would you guys do hmm
i think i'll go for it
yeah omnipresence
wait the diseased heart was that the one
uh
that like
gives damage to everybody who hits me
[Music]
yeah okay
yeah i mean no why not
no i'll go for this one first just in
case we die
but it would break my heart or
to sacrifice one day
[Music]
oh well whatever it just in case
i died once i did
yeah
wow what i've unlocked the new crown
ability
death is no longer the end
when killed on a crusade you may
sacrifice a follower to be resurrected
and continue around i don't need to be
sad about it right because they will be
happy to do it to keep their leader
alive
it will be an honor to them
[Music]
what does this again it just inspires
them right
[Music]
wow blessed be the fruit
and here i can't do anything right
right now
yeah yeah okay
what's up so far so good
the heart is gone now build a lamborgh
oh wait they're not done building it
okay let
[Music]
i can't even help
there you go
it's a german version yeah i used to
watch it when i was a baby
yeah
and says german voice and yeah
oh look at him go oh
[Music]
he's being such a good boy
i mean i'm so proud of my cult i'm so
proud there's some poop yeah okay
get the poop
oh i'm right here you have a quest too
wonderful
perfect timing oh patty it's you again
oh oh
what was it what did i do
it's already level free this follower
holy [\h__\h]
oh ow because you asked for the two um
thingies oh yeah i did that i did do
that
and now the game just wants me to visit
the pilgrims for sash but i'm not gonna
do that now no no no no
no no no no
i'm quite satisfied and happy with this
so far
i guess it's a good spot to end it but
it's like oh man
i could go on and on and on and on and
on and on and on and on and on and on
and on
now i'm gonna end it i can unlock i know
i can i could go on and on and on and on
and on
make food
but why they're they're fasting
well are they done
they're not done they're still fasting
right
wait but the hunger is going down i
guess not
oh they're done
okay
well they're not that hungry yet
i'll make some
not too many
it's a luxury okay
they have to learn that
having food
is a blessing from me
are you going to poop
wow
impressive that went out so smoothly
good job good job i'm proud of you
there's a berry bush
i don't want to stop i don't want to
stop playing
[Music]
what are you doing
well we can continue playing uh soon
maybe on monday probably
no
okay
uh do we stay here
saving
[Music]
that was fun
i'm glad i gave this game a chance yeah
i enjoyed that a lot
plate finished this in two days wow yeah
i would too if i would just play it
privately i would probably also
go until the end grind through
thank you guys for watching so far we're
gonna continue streaming and uh read
some super chats
and then i'll cook afterwards hopefully
um
yeah so you're welcome to stay my little
piglets and chickens
you're welcome to stay to listen to
my inspiring words while i continuously
repeat the donkey shootings the
duncashims and the donkey shoes
and the feeling thanks
please no burning food
[Music]
i wish i i could hire a chef
to cook for me instead
um
okay moving to my
office oh it's that music
uh okay wait you hear you hear it right
you heard a double and now you hear it
normal
[Music]
yeah it's a nostalgic track yeah it's
good
normal now okay
[Music]
thank you for playing well thank you for
watching
it was a lot of fun
there's some good games out there that
need to be shown to the world
and it's nice to hear it for the first
time in a long time
[Music]
the original of the superchats is of the
utmost importance to the cult oh wait
another girl
uh yes supposedly
okay i'm gonna close the game now
[Music]
the first
first [\h__\h] post that i did after leaving
maybe um
ah mario kart
let me take a break
[Music]
for a second i was like what do you mean
when did i do a collab with amma alone
recently
because everybody left
midway through
for for a second yesterday i thought i
was gonna do it again
because uh she was having issue with her
capture card early on
during the stream
well no
thankfully thankfully it worked out
i thought there was a curse or something
the anchors
oh okay we start uh there okay it's not
i mean there's not so many streams to
read actually
oh you know what
oh no number one
ah
where is mine
ah they won their super chats on on the
uh when i released the uh just do it
video where are there no super chat's on
i guess they're wearing
i guess i remember that
that's fine
regarding that by the way
so when we were um
doing the
the off collab when we were at cali's
place that she rented
you know i i think i told you guys
already that during that time i i
re-recorded some things
with like the a different suit like like
most of the
um concert was recording in amish studio
but ame also has like different kinds of
a little bit like oh okay
ahmed has like different kinds of um
you know
3d recording options
and one of them is pretty easy to bring
along overseas but it's it's not the
highest quality you know it's the one
that we use for the arm wrestling
yeah yeah so
we brought that along anyway because i
we wanted to try recording the hand
movements separately because it seemed
like it would
help and be easier with that suit even
though like generally it's not as good
as the other stuff that ame has
but at least the hand movements are like
pretty
well tracked so we want we're gonna do
that and um so on one of the days
when i thought i was already done
recording
um i was recording the hand movements to
every single song separately
and then we tried to like stitch it
together afterwards and all that then i
told you that already i think right um
but yeah
one more thing that i did you know i was
wearing the whole suit so i was like
i mean while we're here maybe i can
record some some [\h__\h] posts in 3d
for the time
when i need it at some point
and i was like what should i do what
should i do because i didn't think about
it beforehand i was like ah what could i
do what could i do
and then
it came to me
i should record
just do it
in the suit right now
so
without practicing
we just like um
turned it on
on the phone or so and recorded it at
the spot pretty much i had like two
takes or so
yeah
just recorded right there actually you
know i'm always centered in the video
because for some reason we couldn't turn
that off but i actually i was even
managing mannequin
mimicking the movement where i was going
side to side like the dude
i was doing that too no it's not perfect
because you know the tracking wasn't
perfect but
but i did it
[Music]
but it um we couldn't record the voice
so the voice is actually
recorded afterwards on top of it after i
arrived home in austria
in case you
didn't notice that something was off but
so i i i voice acted myself
yeah
such a voice actor
i self-dubbed mm-hmm
well i think it turned out pretty well
yeah i wrote down in order to self-doubt
myself i wrote down
everything he said
and then tried my best to time it so
that it fits the facial
movement and the body movement
i mean you are chris pratt
it's so oh
good stretch
oh she has
water all over her mouth
because she just drank water
[Music]
anyway i hope you guys enjoyed that [\h__\h]
post
i didn't know at the time when i was
gonna release it i just wanted to record
something
for
certain occasions when i need it
[Music]
i think i recorded something else too
but i don't know what it was and
if it was good
but i'm i'm pretty sure i recorded a
second thing
i need to check with amer because it's
on her pc
but i think i think to just do it was
pretty much the only
funny thing i did
and then uh
i i could have
if i had more ideas i could have
recorded endlessly but i think
yeah that was good enough i hope i hope
i get the wait it's it's like almost end
of
what the [\h__\h] it's almost in the focus
already what the [\h__\h]
i was gonna say
i still haven't received the
suit to do home 3d but
i'm even more shocked by the fact that
it's already the 19th of august what the
[\h__\h]
korea kind of made time go so fast this
month holy [\h__\h]
hey somebody stop the time please
i can't handle this
it's going too fast
your whole talk is not really in my
hands right now i'm just waiting for the
new sets to be
completed it's not in my hands i can't
accelerate it and for
the german channel i'm still waiting for
all the layout stuff to be finished it's
uh
yeah
there's currently there's like a million
things that i keep on having to like
confirm and control and
assign and
check and all that um
because like i have like i plans the
membership uh
membership wallpapers
ahead of time until the end of the year
until december so
all the artists have started drawing
already
and they all are they all have been
sending me their drafts
uh
in the past one week
so i've been getting like a million
things to check
up on
and give like my feedback on
including the german channel
layouts
so sometimes there's a few things that
i'm like uh
i don't know i don't know what to say to
this i don't i don't know
what i would change i have no feedback
brain empty head empty
and one artist gave me two
completely different drafts for one
month's wallpaper and i'm like
they're both so good how the [\h__\h] do i
choose
and then for one for one month i think
the upcoming month
i liked the art so much that i'm
i'm actually
doing something extra special for the
members for that one
you will see
next month i think i think it was the
one for september
so
every morning i wake up man i have so
many discord mentions
it's not only that it's like a lot of
other things too man
but today was nice to wake up to the
draft of the music video
yeah
it's gonna be a serious one though
i'm gonna
you know i could i could include some
you know typical
uh kfb or whole life related references
or whatever but i i have i'm having it
all
be serious and even even the slightest
dakuma chicken
is
not gonna make an appearance with them
even though it breaks my heart i kind of
also want them to be in there
but but
now i want this one to be really serious
i want it to be like
something that an outsider can look at
and understand completely and not have
like question marks above their head
when looking at it
i mean these kind of insider jokes
they're really fun to watch if you're
already part of
the cult
but i want it to be um
really really really really clean and
serious this time
really um easy to
uh
eat up for
outsiders
people who maybe don't even know whole
life
not everything used to be a meme yeah
yeah
yeah even though you know the draft was
with some tacoma chickens and i said
raise my heart but please take them out
that sounds
threatening but
i kind of want these they look so cute
but
but i think i think i
i i want all of it
gone
i'm sorry guys i'm sorry guys you guys
you guys are behind the scenes for this
one okay not not on camera
yeah
average consumers yeah yeah yeah if if
there are any i want it to be accessible
to all of them
um
yeah that's why the the theme of the
song is actually
also pretty generic just saying
ahead of time it's a pretty
the lyrics are pretty generic um
like there's no like
phoenix references or whole live
references or
v2 references or anything like that
but it is a banger of a song
yeah
i'm so excited
we'll see we'll see how soon i can
release it
thank you
thank you thank you
okay
i snoozed
sneezy
okay then i think it's time to reach the
super chat tools
okay the first one is
the mario kart collab i guess
a lot of snacks
okay
making my show
it can be a good bait for the nominees
hell yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i want i
want
maybe you guys can also like show it to
your non-beautiful friends
and and don't worry about you know them
not understanding anything just show it
to them and
hope they will enjoy it
i don't know about that come on
friends oh come on you're friends
i'm i'm sure you've got some
acquaintances at least
no i mean me too were youtubing related
thank you very much
four beautiful
hearts you know those look like
in those colors they look like they
could be um
skittles
i want to eat them
thank you tai chi
[Music]
write the look away the long
thanksgiving maps in a tanki mental
jetty thank you
thank you
thank you for the pinky hi kena can you
please try the scream
in a way similar to how sebastian vettel
said it after he got tire puncture
at the 2019 brazilian grand prix maybe
that when maybe when something's wrong
thanks i feel like i said that already
before because somebody
may have requested it before but i'm
pretty sure i said that that exact
phrase before but i didn't know it was a
reference to
a dude
who's driving speedy cars
what
wait i really think i said this before
when did i say this before
that sounds so familiar you guys don't
even know what i'm talking about right
phrase
i feel like i said did somebody ask this
before
okay okay i'll say it i say it
my god musta signs so i'm bookmast about
okay i don't know how sebastian vettel
said it before but
hope this gets close enough
now
can't be arc archivists please tell me
if i said this before
find
find the the clues find the proof
you said you were michael schumacher
well i mean yeah so what i'm not
sebastian better
why does it sound familiar exactly right
all i heard was oscar
okay well continuing moon dog
oh
there's a love potion at the baskin
robbins oh my god what see i didn't even
i really wanted to go to baskin robbins
while i was in korea and i even saw one
once when i arrived at the airport
but then uh i didn't end up going
because i didn't feel like ice cream at
that moment and then i didn't see a
baskin robbins ever again afterwards
so i don't even know if they would have
had the potion 31 there but is it really
patsy isn't really the one the one and
only love person love potion love
portion 31
baskin robbins australia
oh my god
[Music]
i think that's it i'm opening the baskin
robbins website and holy [\h__\h] there's so
much going on
toasted s'mores are here
holy [\h__\h]
no just take me to the website oh [\h__\h]
there is love potion 21
but i mean
i mean i'm not gonna i'm not gonna fly
to australia just because of the potion
for anyone
[Music]
oh man but good to know good to know
for the future
[Music]
i actually got in i think there's a
slight delay because it's loaded quicker
than on my system than in the stream
and of course yeah there's definitely
always a little bit of a delay it would
be incredible if streams were really
like one on one perfectly in real time i
got eight for the headphone nice i'm
glad you were able to join yeah
hope you had fun you were probably
placed above me so
congratulations i'm so happy for you
thank you
little
[\h__\h] function
yeah
[Music]
why not [\h__\h] you
cheetie thank you
okay
oh that was already it for that stream
done
a couple to go
speaking
of your little [\h__\h] now we have some
super chats there so i'll keep my
chit chat for that
i don't even have anything particularly
i just wanted to ask if you guys enjoyed
it
so many
people have been enjoying the song of my
people
it's nice it's really beautiful
so emotional
okay so
next one
this one
is
yeah
maybe we'll have a lot of korean super
chats for this one i don't know
it's our anthem
yeah
okay i think i can read this one
[Music]
i can read this one
for a lot of those signs i'm still like
a little bit
uncertain so i'm scared to read it out
loud but those with those ones i was
pretty
pretty confident
yo i did it
oh my god
[Music]
i can read your name i feel like a baby
like a toddler but i'm so proud
um how helpful was your korean studies
not really helpful
because even if you couldn't read it i
couldn't understand the meanings of what
i was reading but but at least um navi
mama was
you know impressed a few times when i
was able to
read something she was like us
i know
[Music]
that's like free writing systems you can
read now that's actually insane
that's actually insane if you think
about it three different writing systems
although the english writing system
is used by so many different languages
so it's pretty powerful
while korean and japanese well
are pretty
um
specified on some on the language
yes yes yes
mr kai's biggest action poem
are you having a thank you for the pinky
are you having lots of fun in korea
whether it's bad but it looks like
you're having lots of fun with navi mama
now it is your chance to know everything
about amen i'm sure you already know
lots also i hope that map was somewhat
helpful for you thank you
yes it was and also about ame i think
i think nabi mama doesn't really know
that much about alex
i don't think they communicate much
uh i probably communicated more with
navi mama than ami did so far at this
point way more way more especially after
that trip
um
but yeah the weather actually holy [\h__\h]
i was so lucky i think there's a word in
japanese
i don't know if there's a word for that
in korean
but i think i am hareona at this point
like i'm i'm 100
certain of it now
because
it there was literally
insane amounts of rain and monsoon
monsoon season
rainy season when i was there it was
flooding on the on the day before i went
there
and yet
i arrived
with the weather reports being rainy
every day
on every night before
rain rain rain and i come there and it's
like every morning i wake up the weather
reports suddenly
it's like
sunny day today or like it still says
not really sunny but then i go outside
and i've i've never encountered rain
so i am
a hareon
yeah
a woman who makes it
sunny
outside i bring out the sun
[Music]
tomato
i said in japanese i couldn't meet amit
which is funny it's a pun
i couldn't meet ami but i meant i met
her mom i couldn't meet the rain
japanese pot let's go
laugh with me please it's funny
[Music]
so proud
wow
wow amazing 10 of the 10 pun
she's funnier and japanese
am i no i don't think i am
i'm done with the bunny yes
yes
okay well thank you so much pong thank
you thank you for all the help and you
know
for being so sweet and supportive about
my trip
and now hopefully you can make it into
popcorn meet and greet yeah
have been on point today yeah yeah yeah
that day i for some reason like i found
so many restaurants that i felt like i
could make a joke about so i did it the
whole day i post kept on uploading them
on twitter posting the jokes
wow
for the whole day i was not done with
the funny i kept on being the funny one
so funny
oh but i actually uploaded them like one
day in delay because i didn't want
people to you know
follow me throughout the day
so the photos were from the previous day
but
they came quite in handy
i was on the roll
maybe in the egg roll
yeah
yes
okay
jim tracy duncan spanking time
hope you're having an excellent time in
kr korea i'm just chilling here with my
head scratch [\h__\h]
because i'm excellent
oh my god don't call them that
speaking
well even even when i know that you're
referencing to the eggslut restaurant
which i'm really regretful that i didn't
try it out
i don't like you calling your cat stands
please take it back never call them that
again
it doesn't sound good
it's very confusing
thank you mwah
bottom fragger thank you
i was in your country
ah it was really nice
i'm very nice
thank you for letting me in i have to
say like
um arriving
and leaving as well everything went so
[\h__\h] smoothly
it was
it was weird everything went way too
smoothly i was expecting more
troubles you know i already told you
about the arrival didn't tell you about
how i left but
oh my god i will keep that for tuning
tomorrow
something
incredible happened
yeah when i left
um but yeah arrival was also so smoothly
i didn't have any issues with anything
like i arrived and you know let me not
have to do the pcr test and all that but
everything was so easy
and i got the
i got the pocket wi-fi with no problems
which
that pocket wi-fi i've used pocket wi-fi
you know portable ones small ones that
you have to turn on and off
in in japan before several times from
different providers too
but
the one i had in korea
i would charge it overnight but
i
it
never ever i was you i was i was using
it the whole day every day you know
and uh i never turned it off when i
didn't need it i just had it on
the whole time the whole day until late
in the evening when i came home
and
the batteries were like endless they
were like eternal batteries
fitting for phoenix but holy [\h__\h]
i thought i was gonna have trouble with
the pocket wi-fi like having to charge
it in the middle of the day or like
running out of wi-fi in the middle of
the day and all that but no it was never
a problem you could not use phone
battery yeah
yeah that was something else but
um
that pocket wifi holy [\h__\h] the speed was
good too
and the
the batteries the battery life
wow in japan the pocket wifi that i used
in japan
it had like it felt like maximum 30
minutes of life
for a whole day if i would charge it
fully i could use it
maybe 30 minutes to an hour
throughout the whole day and so i would
have to continuously turn it off and on
again whenever i needed it
i was so impressed i know it's like just
a small thing maybe
that you guys can't really be excited
for but i was really impressed and it
was really helpful because um i think on
on two
two full days i was without knobby mama
and uh without the wi-fi i would have
been
very lost you know
so i'm really glad i got it
and um
you know i was thinking oh i'll be
around navi mama anyway so maybe i don't
need the pocket wi-fi but i'm so glad i
got it because even on the days when i
was with nabi mama her her phone would
die so
at the end of the day often it was very
helpful to have wi-fi on my side
appreciate the small things in life it
was a really big thing for me though i
know it sounds like a small thing but
for me it was really big to have such a
efficient pocket wi-fi portable wi-fi
very very
did she get the power bank no
she didn't i i was like on on the last
day where we saw each other in the
morning
she was in my hotel room because she was
gonna pick me up so i i was like hey
mama i have this power bank for you take
it because i have two like with two
different designs from annapolis
and uh she was like
oh thank you thank you but she didn't
bring it i guess partially because her
back was too small but she just left it
on my bed
and then in the evening she didn't um
you know go to my room anymore so i
couldn't give it to her anymore and then
uh on the next day when i flew
i went to the airport alone because it
was pretty
i mean it was like
i offered the chance of going to the
airport with me
um to navi mama
but she would have to have been at my
hotel at 8 30 or so
and which yeah would have probably meant
that she had to leave quite early and
then she was like ah
8 30
i don't think i can do it kiana sorry
i'm like okay no problem i mean i'm a
bit worried about
uh
going to the airport alone with the taxi
i'll be fine i'll be fine
so i went alone and i couldn't give her
the pocket wi-fi any at the the portable
charger anymore in the end
well she will have to visit you in
australia to get it back how unfortunate
or she just buys her own charger but
she probably won't
probably won
she did eat however
uh the amelia cookie that i got
uh with the menus
she did eat one of the cookies so at
least she consumed
some of the merchandise by eating the
cookie
she said it was really good
and i'm a cookie she was like hey can i
really eat this i'm like yeah and she's
like really really and i'm like yeah
just eat it
that's what they're for
i can't bring it to austria
i i brought a lot of stuff you know as
much as i could but the cookies no
so anyway
yeah i'm done playing for today i'm
wearing super chats right now and chit
chatting endlessly so let me continue
reading the game and create duncan since
comes on the doll for the red super chat
oh i have a feeling i could read it but
even if i can read it i wouldn't
understand so
let me just
i agree but i also don't understand let
me just um translate
ah it says have a great time in korea
[Music]
i was sad about leaving happy too
because you know a lot of stuff to do at
home and i was traveling so much as i as
i said on twitter
it's nice to
like just
have some
like try to
get like some calm home time at home
not really that calm because i have to
do stuff here anyway but i don't really
have time for traveling now so yeah but
um it was it was a really cool trip with
like i made
i made
a new friend you know
and
yeah i made some really nice memories
[Music]
so it was worth it no
i'll talk more about
about it tomorrow
well thanks for the memberships um
that was turned off again for a while
because it was like apparently just
testing phase
uh and then now it's turned on again i
don't think i can turn it off it's
something that doesn't give you a choice
so
we'll have to deal with it whether you
like it or not
but i think it's it's all right
um
give some people the chance who can't
afford it to be a member but really want
to
because i really like watching me
gives them a chance to enjoy the content
as well
i mean there's no need to be too
too
you know
uh
pessimistic about it i understand some
of the concerns but
i mean it's not like we had any problems
with it yet right so
i don't think we need to be too
pessimistic about every single thing
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
i think that is
king
over the table
[Music]
something like that
and shane's beach above watching channel
duncan
miniature pinches thank you for the red
super chat yeah
i hope you can do all the things that
you plan to do before coming to korea
and i hope tanja will have excellent
days
thank you
did i get to do anything i planned i
mean i didn't plan much to begin with it
was mostly not in my mouth
i think
i don't have any
regrets i think uh except i mean there
were some some things that i was like
you know throwing out there as a
possibility like going to like some kind
of
um
live show in the audience
uh couldn't do that but that's okay
that's fine
seems like a really difficult thing
especially to do it so last minute maybe
another time
one thing i regret though is like in
hindsight
in hindsight
ah it
i i could have never stayed free for
full weeks in
korea to be there for the time when my
menu is being sold at the annapolis cafe
and popcorn
but i feel like it would have been nice
to be there during popcorn too but you
know part of me wanted to do it from
home so that i have all my equipment
here in a like a comfortable space don't
have to bring it all to to korea to a
hotel room where it's unreliable and i
don't know if things gonna go well
um
yeah
yeah but
somehow maybe at least like i could have
added one or two days to my trip
i did feel like it ended too a little
bit too fast
but three weeks would have been yeah
definitely too long
and not only because of like
you know not being able to stream
normally but also asking my friends to
take care of my cats for three weeks is
quite something
yeah this and that so
but maybe one or two days extra could
have been nice
oh well but i'll come again
sometime next year
oh it was six days i thought it was
enough
i didn't want to go any longer because i
would have felt guilty for being away
for too long because of cats and because
of work
and this and then
yeah
i'll come again i'll come again
[Music]
yeah and hopefully next time i come
maybe
maybe there's more people than just nabi
mama that i can hang out with
i mean i did have a lot of fun with nami
mama but i did find out about one person
that i know
that lives there too
so
at least one more person as a
possibility
but i want to make more
more friends in korea
would be nice to have like more people
to hang out with
yeah
uh yeah yeah yeah the thing was with
ayami mama it absolutely overlapped with
her trip to japan
for comic market
so we couldn't meet one next time then
[Music]
and make some minsang comes on nida for
the rest of the chat wow wow welcome to
korean attention i hope you have a great
trip how's the weather how's meeting
navi how does it feel seeing the country
well
the weather
as i said was really not as bad as
expected
it was actually pretty
decent i mean
it was [\h__\h] humid and i was sweating
buckets every day
i swear to god holy [\h__\h]
oh on some days i even changed
clothes
um
midway through the day in the middle of
the day because i was
too
drenched in sweat
and like
it was one time where that wasn't even
really my intention but you know i i was
shopping alone in in hongdae
and okay it's kind of embarrassing okay
but
no everybody sweats especially in the
weather like that come on
so
but i think i did sweat a little bit
more than
koreans who are used to it but
i was walking for the shopping street i
was looking for
like a
certain types of clothing
so i was looking like really
um
how to stay i had a goal i had specific
clothes in mind that i wanted to find so
i i was shopping and um
when i found something i found a certain
pair of pants and i was like i need
these pants so i go into the shop and i
i i tried all of the pants which was a
kind of uh awkward situation because
the shop was like a really tiny narrow
one that didn't have a changing room
um i did ask if i could try it on if she
has a changing room and she said
yeah just try it on right here and i'll
stand in front of you
to uh you know protect you it was a lady
at least and i'm like
but i did want to make sure the pants
would fit because that was important to
me
and then i'm like are there cameras here
and then she's like no and then i look
up and i see a camera and i'm like
there's a camera literally up there
and she's like i think she was trying to
tell me that that one doesn't work
i'm not sure about that but so
but then but then she like brings out
like some kind of fabric and stands like
in front of me makes a wall so that
people outside don't see me
so i'm like okay i guess well at least i
was wearing like a long skirt so i was
thinking oh i can just
wear the pants by
putting them on
underneath the skirt you know what i
mean so i felt like okay i i guess i
guess
yeah yeah some are indeed definitely
just props to make people think
it's a
it's a safe place safe as and
don't steal [\h__\h]
so i put on the pants and i'm done
and i take off the the skirt when once i
was
wearing the pants and then i checked
myself in the mirror and i'm like okay
this fits it's nice thank you very much
i'm buying it
and then
um
and then she's like
she points at my
my shirt
and she's like
getting me to lift my arms and she's
like trying to
signal and tell me
i have like
just it wasn't even that bad just like a
little bit of
like a little bit of
um
sweat stains okay it's just a little bit
dope it wasn't it was even like a a blue
a blue tank top
and honestly
i mean i don't unless i lift my arms you
wouldn't have seen so it's not like
any anyone would have given a [\h__\h]
outside anyway but since she was like
trying to convince me to buy a shirt buy
a shirt buy a shirt
as if it was
such a thing i have to be ashamed of to
have like a tiny amount mountain
sorry i swear okay something excuse me
it's [\h__\h] humid here
it was so humid
but i'm like okay i guess
i guess
so she sells me like a simple tank top
um
[Music]
but you know what it was nice
getting a completely new outfit when i
was sweating so much
now i was gonna put on my my skirt again
because the shorts were kind of
embarrassing but she was like no wear it
you look great it looks good wear it
continue wearing it go out like this it
looks perfect
and then i was like oh okay you actually
made me feel kind of confident so i
guess i'm gonna wear this so i continued
shopping
while wearing a
pretty
reviewing
outfit
but it was fitting for the heat but i i
felt um
a little bit embarrassed
like i have some friends who would wear
that totally without
um worrying about it but i'm not used to
reviewing that much
revealing that much
[Music]
especially not like i feel like if i
would wear the same stuff in
la
then
i probably wouldn't have felt that weird
about it
but in korea i saw i saw a lot of the
girls were wearing like
long baggy
um jeans
combined with a
um a really
uh
tight crop top
you know that was a combination i saw a
lot in korea
and i really liked it i i think it
looked really good
like baggy long jeans
and then a tight crop top
yeah i like that
fashion
combination
skater girls
oh i don't know
i'm sure
but
yeah so most of them were wearing
long pants
actually
even in the [\h__\h] heat i don't know
how to do it
so then there was i with my booty shorts
man
and a really
tight crop top
i felt kind of embarrassed man
and ashamed for
having
some sweat in the first place
but then my i don't know it was so bad
oh
it was so hot
god damn it
but i felt at least a little bit
refreshed yeah
changing my clothes in the middle of the
day
um
sweat shaming yeah man i mean
it wasn't even that much i would
understand if you could see like
huge sweat stains on my back or
something but you couldn't it was just
it was just alone
man
people gonna say now i'm disgusting for
having a normal human body function
oh man
she was she was just looking for an
excuse to sell a shirt
yeah i couldn't say no she was so pushy
but also like in a in a good friendly
kind of way and like
convincingly
self-confidence pushing kind of way
oh yeah oh well
where was i
oh yeah yeah thank you max songwinsen i
went on a tangent thank you so much for
your support it was great seeing your
country i want to go again
thank you very much please continue
supporting me
[Music]
um
i forgot that one
something like that what was it
oh yeah yeah yeah what's getting there
what's getting there no that was a no
not enough
the other way around no good gentleman
let's go thanks for the pinky
when the tensor reaches it must be when
you come back from a long trip right
yeah we racoons wish you brought a lot
of great memories
thank you i did make a lot of great
memories
thanks for the memories even though they
were really great pretty
okay it says please come again next time
i will i will not live in this year i
can't spam
visits to the same country too much i
you know i want to make
use of my time on this earth to see as
many places as possible too
so i shouldn't
repeat too much but i don't want to go
again maybe next year
i hope
so yeah thank you max and duncan thank
you
oh you agree with me thank you they
actually didn't play the the k-pop um
introduction to the airline uh on my way
back they only played it on on the way
to korea
i didn't play it on the way back even
though it was the same airline korean
air
oh
mr btm thank you
[Music]
broken man thank you for the pinky
welcome to korea attention all korean
kfp employees are so happy from your
visit i thought so i'm glad i could make
you guys happy
i wish you have a good time in korea and
hope you revisit here later enjoy your
travel
list of days and see you in seo popcorn
we love you so much yeah i mean i will
be doing it from austria but
i will be able to interact with you guys
and maybe it will feel like i'm in korea
at the moment i hope so i'm looking
forward to it
please wait for me and i hope i can see
as many as possible
of you guys there
yeah yeah enjoy
take care till then okay
random collusion dashing for the pinky
[Music]
korea is one of the most credit-based
country in the world if you use visa or
massacres you can use them well at least
in every places home
but like my master debit card didn't
work anywhere except at the airport and
at shinhan bank
but if it was a master
card credit card would have would it
have worked then i wonder
just a debit card huh
that has problems [\h__\h] hell
i really need to get a credit card
but i don't know where to make it
because depending on where you make it
you get different benefits and i don't
know where it's good
because i bought the table really bad
i'm so sorry you didn't deserve that
sorry sorry table
sorry
i'm sorry
sorry table sorry sorry
sorry
kim yang
you see if yeah enjoying that
thank you for the rest of the chat with
no message
why
why why why tell me what you got to say
to me
nothing nothing
but thank you thank you so much i
appreciate it
[Music]
yeah
very sweet of you
and next we have oh
give me him again
oh yeah a second time thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you this one is
that
uh or under the table
cool
[Applause]
i'm so proud i'm so proud the um the ooh
and the oh
no matter how many times i look at them
i still have to i always tell myself
under the table and over the table
it helps though
i read raccoon
your baby
thank you pepsi dancer and shane's beat
you are watching channel thank you it
gives you such a feeling of
accomplishment
when you're able to read a different
writing system
then
golden culture
celebrates big factions
[Music]
thank you everybody
thank you
yeah i learned it on my own i didn't
even use duolingo for that one
i used just a different app application
and i was writing with my phone because
it has a pen
i was writing the signs
but i need to repeat again otherwise
i'll forget again
thank you
thank you for praising me
okay
this might be the last one i'm reading
because it's already getting late
again thank you
said to just do it so i did it i went
through a laser eye surgery that i've
been avoiding for the past five years
full of [\h__\h]
thank you my lady that was a confidence
boost i needed i can watch your streams
in hd quality without glass now wow
that that's something i'm so happy for
that i don't
need glasses so that i have relatively
good eyesight because that sounds so
scary
you know but
actually i think rmt
did that before
and she was fine but i don't know it
sounds really scary
but i'm glad it went well
congratulations i'm proud of you
good job
no you don't need glasses anymore that's
amazing
dark astronomy
i was on a flight to australia for
university so the last stream was the
first time i missed the stream from you
after about
1.5 years of never missing anything holy
[\h__\h]
i already watched the vld as soon as i
got into nadel i hope you're having a
wonderful time here ava
oh man please don't i hope you don't
feel like guilty or anything about it
you know sometimes you just really have
to do something
it's impressive how you
managed to go through with it
for for 1.5 years you know what i'll
give you a free card of of
you know
a pass
so
you don't have to say
uh the first time you missed something
you was just gonna ignore that happened
because you deserve it so
two years later
you can still say you never missed a
stream from me live
yeah okay
you can still say it i allow it i allow
it it's a freebie the streak continues
yeah
wow
how's australia
how's it going get that love potion 31
while you're there
why not
go get it get that love potion have you
had it before if not then go go go go
i want you to eat it because i can't
i can't have it so at least you
please
enjoy the love potion
tell me how it was sent me a picture
thank you mwah unknown thank you
i want that later but it isn't season
for it here yet at least it will be in
season at some point we don't even have
a basket in robins in australia or
austria yeah
uh until 907.000
[Music]
i almost almost
threw uh my glass of water on the ground
santa amara's dunking shoe in jeff star
thank you
oh my god
i haven't seen you in a while you're
typing in korean now oh ho oh oh ho ho
is this
okay this will take too much time
there's a whole sentence here
but i can read dumb down them
that's something
over the table
under the table over the table
oh
[Music]
wait what beef what did i get stolen
london
what happened oh the post-it right
and we're supposed to be
like oh yeah something there was
something i've already forgot i'm not
even mad anymore i already forgot
uh i need a picture of what it looks
like now
[Music]
i i heard people look for it but
couldn't find it i need a picture like
has it been put up again in the frame i
need to see it
if anyone sees it let me know
thank you so much
thank you very much
wow can you actually speak fluent korean
hickey cake you always like write in
different languages
when you when you actually do write
something
i'm i'm really confused i don't know
what your actual language is at this
point
thank you though
hope you're doing well hickey king
a kiss for you
yeah
he's a mystery yeah
mystery person
thank you
[Music]
oh it was way too humid
if i ever visit again i'm not gonna
visit in summer it was stupid of me
to think
that was a good idea but i wanted to
time it with the cafe
i mean originally i think originally i
already started planning on it before
even
before even knowing the exact date
oh but yeah then i timed it
accurately
[Music]
korean cloaks are very special tonight
thanks to dantel oh i hope you enjoy and
make good memories in korea i salute
thank you and the person who picked
andrew's nose made a great achievement
what
what my nose
who took my nose i thought it was just a
post-it
who stole my nose i didn't know this was
my nose
get my nose back get my nose back
of course i have one
where's my oh the sweater
i already forgot everything
it's about to swab ah
ah the person who picked tantrums okay
that makes a lot of sense now
made a great achievement
i wish we could have done a different
test not the nose
i hate it
[Music]
thank god i usually never really have to
do these kind of tests like when flying
to america it wasn't necessary
same for italy
[Music]
hallelujah
i probably will have to do one when i
fly to japan sometime
whenever they open up the gates for us
we probably still have to do the pcr
test so
oh man
oh man don't like it don't like it at
all
at least it wasn't the pro thread swap
but i did that one uh
on my like in austria because i had to
do a pcr test before flying and one
after flying
and i did the the throat
swap it wouldn't even feel like
it was somewhere between fruit and mouth
so
i mean
that was fine i feel like
that's uh it's a it's a tickly feeling
but it's better for me than the nose
swab in my opinion
i
prefer that one
christian left me with an intense
incoming sneeze sensation pretty
uncomfortable yeah yeah yeah i had to
blow my nose afterwards because that was
so so weird look
i hate blah
i hope i don't have to do it again
anytime soon thank you montagne
for reminding me of that terrible memory
thank you so much mwah
eugene ha danke soon
i could probably read this one
yes
[Music]
this month may or may not include a week
that may or may not include a special
day for me oh your birthday that may or
may not require me to get a cake and get
drunk apologies in advance for getting
drunk and i hope you're having fun and
eating good food in korea oh
when was it happy filing a birthday ah
i want some birthday cake right now
oh man
but i have strawberries at least have
strawberries i have to eat strawberries
yes yes yes yes and it's so late now i
don't think i'm gonna cook anymore
i thankfully have some food that's um
like some frozen food that i can warm up
at least something
yeah and then eat the strawberries
i don't feel like cooking though this is
always the problem
don't feel like cooking after such a
long stream
so late in the night
also partially i mean the other reason
is just you know after that one time i
don't i don't want to cook anymore ah
but i have three recipes from
uh
hello fresh
two of them are with meat but i think i
think they're the meat is still okay
[Music]
well if my stream starts at like 6 p.m
or earlier normally
like tunic probably tomorrow is gonna be
longer
start earlier and around the same time
then
eating dinner at four p.m or so
it's not gonna be quite dinner because
i'm gonna be hungry afterwards
so
even if i
i could make it before and then
eat it afterwards but yeah
i look like i don't know a lot of the
things that
i would make with hellofresh just are
the best when you eat them fresh warming
them up is yeah
yeah
i mean i still do it sometimes but
no i don't know i don't think i wanna
if i i i if i do a short stream then
i'll cook but if i do a long stream then
the chances that i'll be cooking are
really low
yeah
this cold hello fresh now the hello
laughter was exactly
[Music]
that's not hello microwave
that is a smart argument that i couldn't
come up with that was so obviously right
there in front of my nose
goddammit anyway happy belated birthday
to jacob's monkey
oh man
i wish you would have shared some cake
with me kind of mean but okay i'll take
it hope you had a lovely birthday
congratulations
thank you for the red super chat
thank you so much for the cute chicken
heart emote
love love
[Music]
wonder if you're watching now
probably not
[Music]
the one before the the
two korean red super chats in a row they
both have cats uh cat's faces as their
um profile picture it makes me really
happy to look at that
cute cats they're so cute oh baby
thank you for the red supergiant gift
kim i'm glad you seem to enjoy korea and
i'm sorry about the post-it i hope you
enjoyed the rest of your trip and
animals cafe chicken is so delicious oh
did you eat it oh
did you also get to eat the curry or not
i'm glad you enjoyed the cafe thank you
so much for trying it out
i really enjoyed it too it was really
special for me a nice
nice memories and i felt so proud and
wow and i showed off everything to
um
the other myth members
and finally finally kelly
acknowledged it too
on twitter yeah yeah
they
they seemed very very impressed
by it
you know i've been following it the
whole time supporting it the whole time
so i'm i'm really happy it's doing so
well
yeah
i wish i wish we could do it in several
locations
but you know this is something that
uh
anaplus and korea wanted to do and and
they
they wanted to have a labor with us so
if
some store in america or canada or
australia or wherever wants to do that
with us i'm sure we can
figure something out if there
someone wants to work with us but
yeah that's why it's in korea that's why
it's there i was surprised too that the
first ever
collab cafe like that is in korea out of
all places
but
yeah they did a great job with it
and they were so so so so
professional i feel like like
organizing my visit
to the cafe and they were so generous
giving me all the merchandise for free
even though i just said i just wanted a
few certain items
yeah i think they did amazing the staff
is really great
[Music]
great to work with them
good comfy place for fans yeah
yeah
now it's even better because now the
wall is signed by me
it's a really special place now
rich hall on twitter was really insane
there's like even even even even more
though they gave me every single item
and you know what they gave me that
little curtain too i think i'm gonna
hang it up on the door that leads to my
office
yeah
i think that would be cute it makes
sense
so thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
now i need a different translator
we are so grateful you're having a good
time in korea
is yummy too but i hope you try korean
dessert too i did hopefully someone's to
finish it in a family in korea
and
also wow you tried
did you
know the rest says
what ah
is that fake korean
[Music]
they
they wrote some german
in korean
little [\h__\h]
oh sneaky sneaky sneaky
the moment i put korean sentences into
papago and it ends up looking and
looking like some gibberish that makes
absolutely no sense that's when i know
something's wrong
i haven't been bamboozled like this in a
while
uh
no
nine nine nine my answer to you is nine
nine
welcome to mike thank you and jpeg 72
thank you
[Music]
i need to drink water i'm so dehydrated
is
[Music]
um
he came up with the idea for whole talk
to interview
english-speaking members and translate
to
uh
japanese but i said i already had that
idea a long time ago
i'm gonna do it at some point when i ran
out of japanese members to interview
probably probably
hey wj thank you soon thank you
[Music]
google maps doesn't work well in korea
neighborhood cacao maps works better it
was weird though because it's not like
it doesn't work at all it's just some
features are kind of
bugging out like you can see the map
of soul for example
uh
and
you
on the map you see yourself moving
around
but
when i choose
route from a to b
it only shows me the option with public
transport and when it's when i try to go
by foot or whatever it doesn't work
it doesn't load so what i can do however
is just go with other routes i'm just
trying
finding my own way through the map
yeah yeah yeah but i i and then in the
end i i just and i just used google maps
the whole time and it was fine
i didn't get lost
hallelujah
[Music]
it works quite well
no why though because they generally
just don't use google i guess they use
nava
all the time
a site called neighbor that has like all
kinds of functions
thank you though thank you i learned i
learned my lesson i learned things
yeah good to know wow
thank you soon combat pioneer thank you
for the pinky i recommend to use naval
map or cacao map because korean
government are not provide the reason
yeah yeah anyways i hope you enjoyed the
recent the rest of your trip kiana thank
you
thank you very much
um
yeah
uh no i i was i was fine i ended up
getting around
seoul pretty well and
i was first i was a bit worried about
using public transport especially alone
um
but after using public transport with
navi mama once or twice
i was able to
use it alone just fine
and uh pretty proud of that
yeah
i was using it alone several
times i never got into the wrong train
and i never got
off of the wrong stuff
and i usually also always found the
right exit
[Music]
yeah
yeah i'm proud
i was thinking you know i might have to
use
taxis a lot but no it wasn't necessary
although
even though they don't have uber or
anything like that they have normal
taxis
the taxis are actually really cheap
there i think they're
quite a bit cheaper than
in austria
um
[Music]
made us use the taxi a couple times
i was like if really it's quite the
distance should we really take a taxi
but it ended up being pretty cheap
the second day i move around the public
transport like a native
yeah then you feel like you have
blended in nicely right
once you're able to do that
in the country that you're not familiar
with
spoof
moroccan blue thank you g c
k e thank you soon
are the indian korean isle group still
dancing in honda i didn't see any
i saw straight performers but no like
dancers or singers
well i saw somebody singing but
not like an idol group
thank you
you know i tried to eat as much as
possible
but there's still some things i didn't
eat but that's good because then next
time i still have some
foods that i can try out for the first
time
still some first-time memories to make
isn't that nice
nice name
thank you soon
v312
[Music]
it says
oh wait you don't i thought i thought
you guys were hearing the
ah you didn't hear that
you didn't hear the truth i thought i
had the desktop audio on you didn't hear
the german the weird funny german before
did you
wait let me play it for you
i thought you were hearing it
that's awkward
wait the weird funny german was this
demonstration please
part of that is german if you speak
german then you then you i think
figured it out and heard it it was
pretty good
yeah
and then
when i just
listened to was
just a normal uh message nothing hidden
i hope you enjoy the rest of your trip
okay there you go
let me turn it off again
thank you very much
yeah
i did enjoy my trip very much it was
very full
fulfilled full of memories
worth it
um
[Music]
ah thank you for making one jim tracy
duncan and the last super chat is from
miniature pincha zhang
thank you for the pinky i'm glad to hear
that the cash problem was solved there
was something disappointing issue today
but please enjoy tomorrow more happy
oh yeah yeah no no no it didn't bother
me
it's all okay
yeah the cash bubble was thankfully
solved
hallelujah because i had to spend a lot
more money after that
thank you very much for taking care of
me so kindly everybody
during my korea trip
and uh now i will go my fruit is tired
i shall take my leave
i think i'll eat first and then i'll put
up
the stream reservation
and then we'll finish tuning tomorrow oh
no i'm kind of sad about it
oh ah fox game
[Music]
thanks guys very much for watching today
hope you enjoyed it
thank you
and in germany
bye bye love you guys thank you
how did you know i'm ending this thing
yeah did you hear that guys
okay time to cuddle
[Music]
bye
do
[Music]
i