[Music]
[Applause]
n
pap
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
kick out again
what oh it's not quite what maybe I go
full
screen
uh
uh oh did this actually change
oh
oh oh
ah oh now it's
small and the size is not quite
right just like yeah
cintique I love my cintique and where's
like window and full ah
here let's do full mode yeah that looks
good H welcome should I change something
here
uh any recommendations from people who
played no audio uh
oh there it
is better not to touch anything dlss on
DLS oh super
resolution output high resolution
Graphics from a lower resolution put to
improve frame
rate sounds
[Music]
good but volion blur and depth of field
off
uh
[Music]
oh really isn't this kind of nice having
this
but oh all of this shows me
they show me how much Graphics memory it
takes not a hold the processing load I
don't think I've seen any other game
show you
this I guess they know it's a heavy
game no no motion yeah I think I've had
bad experience with other games having
motion
blur yeah I feel kind of hot let me
drink my my lemon water I I squeezed
one4 of a lemon into my water with some
ice
[Music]
cubes I
think I think I'm becoming
um a lemon water person oh can I tell
you something really
quick because lemon water reminds me of
it so in
Austria uh okay I I used to grow up in
uh certain city which Now isn't much of
a secret anymore
but um but when I had a lot of friends
from the capital Vienna already when I
lived in the other city um and I noticed
all my friends they order something
called soda
Citron which is just uh soda water
sparkling water with lemon juice in
there and I notic they just all order it
no matter where they go they all order
that and I thought that's quite
interesting because that's quite a
simple drink but everybody likes to
order that um yeah I don't think it's
bad oh I should do a starting yeah one
second and then you think it's fancy
really I feel like it's so so simple H
yeah it's so common everybody but not
like I thought it it's really it really
seems to be not a whole ustra kind of
thing more like a dead area of Austra
kind of thing it is refreshing yeah and
like not sweetened so that's good and
then you know I went to Cologne a while
ago with a friend
who actually isn't originally from
Vienna I think but lives in
Vienna um and we went to a restaurant in
Germany right and I already know they
don't really do that with the soda
Citron um but he tried ordering it and
the the the waiter was like H what and
I'm like dude dude they don't do this in
Germany like they don't have that on the
menu it's uh you
know this that's a ustra thing you know
I had to educate
him there's a few of these kind of
things I've also noticed like uh this is
a while ago but I used to try travel a
lot more to Germany when I was like
going to Anime conventions way more
often and my favorite drink to order in
a restaurant is like peach or lemon iced
tea the sweet type like from nesty or
whatever and uh I tried ordering that
again and again in Germany because in
Austria you it was usually always on the
menu but I noticed in Germany they they
never had it on the menu what the hell
so
sad they never have it on the menu it's
like less common I don't know maybe
times have changed though maybe nowadays
it's different I just love IC
tea what gives yeah what the
[\h__\h] it's a tragedy
here that's a bit
dramatic so many flavored te here too
where where where PE icy got here hell
yeah I love I love Peach and and lemon
IC tea and sometimes these like IC tea
companies after doing a peach and a
lemon IC tea they start branching out
into different kind of ice teas and I'm
like dude that's just
juice what you making now tastes just
like Juice Stop branching out we're
happy with just Peach and lemon ice te
although also like GRE green tea lemon
ice tea
from I think or actually several
companies did it I like that one too
green tea lemon iced tea they have it at
uh McDonald's too no wait that was was
it fused tea not
sure but yeah that one's maybe still
forgivable but other otherwise just stay
with the basic flavors
man yeah and why am I tanging about uh
drinks no one knows let me cherry and
blueberry tees well in hot in hot uh
version I like any kind of fru tea but
if it's cold and sweet then
[Music]
it's oh God what am I
doing then it's uh I I it just changed
back to Window mode for some reason I'll
fix it then then it's got to be peach or
lemon okay let me tweet I forgot to
tweet at least I didn't forget to do the
the starting tweet that's a good
thing Hing
uh starting
now hii
[Music]
Mario I wonder if there's actually like
any people who come to my stream from
the starting tweets I've been doing it
for years now I I hope it has some kind
of like meaning to
[Music]
it no it's not at the stream aren't you
like surprised that I even started on
the game screen
already wait where did chat
go were you ever
[Music]
there where do I put you here for now
maybe or I don't know where where where
where will we have
[Music]
space would be nice if you could be in a
corner okay wait did did it confirm yeah
I think so what the [\h__\h] is ambient
inclusion safe yeah change saved okay
huh did I get the wrong game wait wait a
[\h__\h]
second wait this says Dragon's
Dogma no I can't have gotten the wrong
game because I
uh wait where's the to but I got the Cod
so I put in the
code and the why does it say Dragon's
Dogma not two
it doesn't show
why this makes me think it's the first
one we got earned
two there's no two because
Capcom they never put it on the screen
oh really that that's so
weird okay so I think this is like a RPG
game right
uh just just so you know it I usually
make these kind of games into a series
this one might not become a series we'll
see here we
go wait is this too
loud we'll
see
[Music]
con I can't
read conviction is the human will that
reaches its great
power what does that
mean behind New Game Plus oh
[Music]
no looks good so
far by the way thank you thank you for
giving me free code but not spoil not
sponsored by the way oh he looks cool on
a guess lend me your ears
yes get do I get them back long as our
faon suffered without a true Monarch to
guide her and her
people good thing I'm in a party outfit
right since last his majesty Erland sat
a top the draon throne oh
long have we
endured yet it has not been for we talk
so
wonderfully at last the Bell has to on
the age of the
console at last we may celebrate the
coming of our rightful ruler
won the
return of the
[Music]
Sovereign who are The
Sovereign nice shoes my word such an
inspiring message Bes your majesty shall
have my eternal
[Music]
F this gives me Witter
Vibes d d d who is
[Applause]
it is it me because we're in the first
person POV
[Music]
wobbly
water behold W you sit the rifle
inheritor of the Dron Throne chosen by
the dragon as its enemy ohuh Behold a
Rejoice Fort you has delivered us our
savior At Last At Last for praise be for
only the sovereign's guidance can lead
us
true all hell The Sovereign all
Sovereign as an s
o pledge their allegiance to E I let us
be United in the hope that their alleges
reign will they end Long Live a
sovereign of
one okay I spell it wrong
but thou who would slay the
dragon if thou seekest to behold this
world in its true
aspect abandon thy what trying to make
me evil cast aside thine heart and thy
KN both
no I ask thee to demonstrate thy
will
hello I say ah you say B
ah we
good uh OBS died for um
second but then chat also kind of
died oh chat's kind of late
weird is
this I just stopped right after I
fainted though I don't think it's too
heavy I
mean that should not impact
it I'm sure it's
fine my controller vibrates of every
[\h__\h] step that's a bit too
much well fancy
now which one of you was it no need to
be shy I've just got to take down a
record of your name and face come on
step forward you asking which one
poisoned him you can either select the
prisoner to use as a preset or select
the hooded prisoner to customize your
Char a yeah okay we got to customize a
little bit I thought I recognized
you let's go character creation
choose a race body type and base head to
determine the character's basic
appearance you will then be able to make
further edits by selecting
customize
okay oh my God I can become a cat's
actor
furry no but I don't want to I want to
be normal
person which one looks like
waa m
her maybe I don't
know uh adjust the face to suit your
liking by making selections of fre
stages huh you will then be able to use
the head you have chosen as a base for
further cust why is this so
complicated what free
stages what you mean what does that mean
yeah
maybe ah okay ah so this is like all
these faces are a little bit different
but still very similar from the one I
chose I guess hairstyle I shouldn't pay
much attention to the hairstyle I can
probably change it
right so oh there pretty cute pretty
cute I like these squinty
eyes
but I don't know it doesn't matter but
this one's cute maybe not doesn't look
much like me but
still oh
oh oh oh oh not
a e it's actually like even the ones
that are like more
like wide or you know two slim or so
even those don't look too weird like I
feel like in other character creation
you can look pretty weird pretty
[Music]
quickly but I don't see this issue here
oh
uh what was it I don't
know torso length oh okay that looks
funny oh long long upper
Budd looks funny
too looks somewhere here muscle
Style
ah I can barely
tell I see some ABS here I see some ABS
let's go with the type eight mus ah here
comes the strength of
them I can see a little bit it's hard to
see
though traps
size what is that the upper oh no that's
oh ah that's what you call
traps trapez or
what upper body muscle
mass oh buff not yet w we still kind of
noodle
arms oh yeah but fig fighs fi fighs yes
I have shees bable
hips upper body size W oh the BBA also
Bobba should be separate dude I guess
actually the upper body is barely
growing up until this point and that's
when you
getat oh the booty the
booty wow
sheesh that's
the the booty lift no no no no no we'll
sayage just somewhere fairly in the
middle oh it says my weight oh wait the
weight changes even is that
important whatever next please uh how do
I
go how do I go
next oh ah okay I got to go back
okay it dictates how much stuff I can
carry so what if I make my character
really fat then I
can carry less wow but shouldn't I also
be like stronger
then ooh head
length head
Wiz see it doesn't even look so weird
head
depth
oh does that change my weight too
no face
height it's already at its highest oh
[Music]
sure thickness W buff neck no we we'll
have a delicate neck here somewhere
around here uh see you guys worry that
I'll take so much with character
creation but I don't think so you guys
worried that in other games too but it
it's really not the case I I hurry
especially for the sake of the stream
but in the end it doesn't really matter
that much anyway ah here we go there's
chest size
oh yeah yeah yeah oh the shape
too oh wait is like more a frontal
thing
oh if they're more like looking at each
other or looking
away they're like somewhere in the
middle and the height oh you can lift
them well this is quite the chest
modification can you modify that out as
a male character
too or modify something else wink
wonk course so oh yeah we'll keep it
we'll keep it like nice
nice what's this depth oh I can never
say this word dep death
death this just sounds like I'm saying d
e a
t arm length too long arm
size oh oh oh oh it adjusts everything
else too that's fine lower body
uh
wow that looks kind of funny the the
super wide hip look uh unrealistic with
the
rest what
this oh I don't do rear size now we're
talking oh now okay wait that exact that
looks exactly like my butt though like
kind of a weird eggy
shape that does look unrealistic and
like
mine when I squat all right we shall do
that leg
size okay we good posture oh oh my God
the booty
press four on Chima movement
[Music]
style this is a little bit more
determined I
guess yeah oh a little bit more forward
leaning or so I don't know sure whatever
that's cool that you can you can't just
like choose the
Styles like one by one no you you
actually change it so smoothly that's
interesting
I can barely tell the difference though
it's really slightly I'm really against
something that doesn't matter but it's
cool that you can do it oh that's me in
about 30 years
probably if not
earlier that's that's pretty
cool not at all oh okay we're going to
the head can I go closer please oh yeah
yeah oh oh hello oh oh okay here I can
change that again and now actually maybe
I like something else uh What
uh
oh that one's nice maybe
base skin waa anime character very
[\h__\h]
pale
six oh that's a nice ooh that's a nice
color
sheesh they're all nice colors oh
wow I can look kind of old but it's well
actually no here there's some oldness as
well on the tummy oh wow
okay that's
[Music]
detail that leg looks old like compared
to this or this or every every skin has
a different
texture
what even the naval look at the navels
they're all different
[Music]
shees as if the naval matters it totally
doesn't but damn and then you can still
change the wrinkles and skin Sheen
whatever that is wait wait oh the color
can also still be
changed oh what so it's not about the
color here it's like the type of the
texture more like
that oh damn wait this is impressive
it's oh wait so now I actually I chose
something more
pinkish uh oh wait there's so
many waa Naval matters it's
essential there's too much like oh this
is this looks nice I
think oh oh that's a nice warm tone
[Music]
oh damn so
realistic
wa I don't know it's hard to
[Music]
choose maybe this I know H what's that
what's that
Naval does she have a piercing before
and to take it out took it out or what
what the [\h__\h] is that na I can't I can't
I can't choose this that one's a better
Naval but it's too red why is it so
red
oh yeah I mean this kind of looks a
little bit yellowish but it's okay
whatever choosing base on the naval well
yeah I mean I'm by the way more of a fan
of inside Naval than AIS atis I'm sorry
they freak me out they freak me out
probably because I don't have
one an an aoui not a naval I have a naal
but you know what I
[Music]
mean huh I can't see maybe this is more
for the skin types that already have
wrinkles
I have an inie and I prefer inis as well
yeah maybe that's just like when you're
an inie you like the inis and when
you're an Audi you're coping by saying
you like
Audi's oh shiny
skin so that's after all of d means okay
o I'll take the shiny skin yeah yeah
glow glow girl yes sheesh that skin
section is
crazy which year
are I
that's not what I mean where's that scar
coming from by the way I think it was in
all skin types maybe that's also uh a
setting brow height now we can keep all
of
that
although maybe a bit
higher it's brow
spacing oh [\h__\h] oh damn
she pretty her her like side face looks
very pretty I like
it the scar star related oh
okay we all share that one scar I
hide you can have is this called lazy
eye you going have a lazy eye
constantly what the [\h__\h] is this detail
or like I have one eye closed cuz you're
blind
what
[Music]
what she's not it's not win I
mean I'm I'm sending you signals guys
wink won wink wonk
oh that's
[Music]
funny
Bridge no oh bridge is only that
[Music]
part nostril a nostril nostril what's
the middle part
then feel like it's not covering the
middle part tip depth
long long nose
wow ah she looks like a big fat liar to
me
Pinocchio tip angle yeah a little bit
angle is
cute tip sh oh
sharp sharp wow wow wow wow wow wow
cute she's a cut
P I can't see your ears so well no I
can't see them I can't see them what I
don't [\h__\h] know got to wait let's do
the hair first then although maybe I'll
choose a hairstyle that oh you know
doesn't show oh no oh
[Laughter]
no she looks great bald though damn oh I
like this I like this looks good in a
wavy
ponytail oh also looks good hot kind of
H High forehead but we can fix
it
oh oh it looks like a lion
wow oh I like I like this too kind
of oh oh very very
medieval actually so
pretty oh yes I love it I love it I love
it oh that looks nice too it's a bit
fluffier oh
oh oh nice oh oh the the the curly hair
wait are we trying to get a hairstyle
that looks like me or just a nice one
that I like oh
pretty she girl your hair is so healthy
and beautiful and
shiny
OMG
damn oh oh actually I know that's uh
supposed to be for the more male
characters but looks hot on you
too oh kind of cute kind of cute very
[Music]
cute oh did we cycle
back yeah we did okay
M uh maybe maybe just
[Music]
uh can we choose a are we choosing a
class or something or is there no such
thing I did not inform myself at all
about this game I have no idea what I'm
getting myself
into press a to see them all together
what ah like this I F
all
uh all over one
another oh there are classes that comes
later but it's not permanent
okay you can choose class but you can
change them
[Music]
no feel like I'd want to focus on one
thing though I mean the banks here at
least kind of look like my bangs but I
don't know the hairstyle is so simple
and like not very
medieval
so there's not really much that looks
similar let's just go
for this one or that one
[Music]
or what's the difference longer side
hairs let's go with this I don't care I
don't care let's make it orange though W
okay these colors are
M they look kind of funky like the
texture looks funky on like more
unrealistic colors it's also not
orange can I still change
the oh oh why so
green I can adjust the color blend okay
what does that mean oh
oh wait currently it's blue in this
hairstyle is kind of blue can we find
the
blueish uh blue no they're so
dark
blue okay blue blue not really a
thing can I make it brighter
no ah the skin was so detailed but this
is like a little bit
n then instead of looking for blue I'll
try to just make it look
[Music]
better
more natural I don't
know I don't
know how do this how does this change I
I I I I didn't even know I did that okay
I I did end up choosing the same color
how about something like
this
[Music]
ah oh maybe just a little bit Sheen
position what a weird way to say shine I
don't see a
[Music]
change ah because there is barely any
Sheen I still don't see a
[Music]
change I don't see
it weird yeah not not too happy with the
hair but it's okay
they got to be a bit darker like this
yeah not exactly the same but also not
black this looks good I
think
yeah oh she looks like a red hair with
those green eyes looking really pretty
but I'm going to end up giving her
purple eyes if I
can damn damn those lips M they're very
kissable
yeah strong
eyebrows sexy now we can see her
ears uh ears I mean we can adjust the
ears oh oh elf
ears no no I'm not an elf sly oh these
are so outy
outwards I look like freaking freaking
from Malcolm in the Middle this younger
boy forgot his name now
just normal please just
normal just normal cheeks you yeah
Dey what's what's check cheek neck
thickness uhhuh bul
cute
starving mm neck fat
oh oh
cheek
height cheek
with anything with dth is just
impossible for me to
say I don't care
thanks mouth actually the mouth looks
perfect
jaw jaw whatever it's okay see aren't
you proud of me I'm zooming through
[Music]
it even hard for Native speakers really
you're just saying that okay I uh I both
eyes yeah I style
oh oh okay there's three Tes one two wow
pretty they're all pretty but this one
freaks me out
[Music]
oh pretty they could have done a few
more but okay
um uh what's this eye color presets
both oh oh you okay okay you can change
Four Color colors even the iris main
color oh wow
what wow they're so pretty are you
seeing this properly can we get a purple
pretty
oh oh
purple okay there's like two purples
it's like more like a pink purple
though
[Music]
pretty eye customization is so good
yeah first I was complaining now I like
it
that's so
pretty she smirked a little bit at
me Okay girl okay okay oh you're so
pretty with even with these dark eyes so
pretty okay let's take like this as a
base and change this
to
oh aha
feel like it barely changed but that was
like really small color I
guess is it just uh purposefully giving
me mostly Blues can I get more purples
elsewhere maybe not what about like more
pink don't think that uh
actually uh to
Musashi what about here like the Reds
[Music]
M Ah that's that's a bit difficult and
then we got to go more purple and pink
change the lighting
yeah
oh wow beautiful aren't you a beauty
patootie this is the iris probably
shouldn't CH oh wait it's not the iris
oh okay okay okay oh these are very
bright ones
okay so this is A fitting
purple maybe something pinkish
here
[Music]
y h this
one these ones 28 wait then
oh oh oh oh oh I found a good
Hue now if I mix more of it then it's
more red but if
[Music]
I mix at least one color got to got to
stay kind of in the pur blue
purple oh oh that's kind of cool with
the dark
inside something like
this nice I found a good plan and yeah
now let's blend
[Music]
[Applause]
it here is
your muffin I made muffins today cuz
yesterday I found this recipe oopsie I
found this recipe
for uh low calorie breakfast desserts o
but I mean low calories supposedly it
was like
200 but out of the batter I got like
free muffins and in the video it shows
one muffin so I don't know generally I
guess I wasn't following the the recipe
that well but I think it was still low
carb and I only ate a low calorie and I
only ate one I got threee muffins
doll yeah first the first bite I was
like n oatmeal me makes it weird I'm not
a big oatmeal fan but the more I ate the
more I felt like it was indeed
satisfying this like chocolate craving
even though it was wasn't tasting very
strongly like chocolate and also even
though I put a whole banana in there it
didn't taste much like banana
either so I don't know it was all right
it it it satisfied a few Cravings a
little
bit yeah nice eyes I
think oh
lashes
oh I feel like it's only really changing
the lower
[Music]
lashes I don't know something like this
is nice cute cute oh the color
dark is
fine sounds like it was good enough yeah
I still made myself one boiled egg
because I was craving the boiled eggs
and now I'm now I'm really a big fan of
boiled eggs for
breakfast uh what's what are we changing
eyelash tip color
oh
[Music]
oh just one is fine root ah oh there was
no blend okay
[Music]
mhm
Brandy oh she's so
[Music]
pretty Bings are so good for
real good morning hello we're going to
make you into go into a gym I don't have
to go into a gym I have you know my my
thing I just got to I've been dancing
yesterday okay dancing learning a new
dance for YouTube short I didn't have
time to record it uh before the stream
but I'll end up recording
it probably after the stream if I'm not
too
[Music]
tired and I did feel like it was
exhausting me uh because I was putting a
lot of effort into it although I learned
it really fast
yeah I learned it really
fast what do we
have I feel like too strong makeup is
kind of unrealistic
anyway I don't want it to be
like yeah just just keep it this
way yeah you know you're going to like
it I think I hope it just captures it
well I got to pray that the motion
capture is somewhat accurate yo her
wings on
fleek I do like a a more I used to
always have my eyeliner like
this but then probably influenced by
Japanese makeup more and more I started
doing more like downwards but longer
than this way longer but like the
downward uh Wing is very
very unappreciated I think outside of
the Asian realm but it it looks good on
non-asian eyes too so uh I recommend to
girls all over the world try dry a down
not not cing a down but like just extend
the line of the upper eye shape extended
and it will give you a nice uh wi of
your with of your eye but like it looks
a little bit more natural and cute not
as like cat eye e as this you know can
look a little bit intimidating or so I
don't know who about talking to is there
any girls in here anyway where are my
girls at where are my girls at this one
looks kind of good on her
though girls girls girls I like girls
girls I'm a guy but I was righty
really oh a few girls the ladies what's
up what's
up oh I'll keep it uh dark dark dark
eyeliner coverage
oh oh
[Music]
n opacity yeah let's make it strong I
said I don't really care about the eye
shadow but an eyeliner you know it it
just looks hot we got to do
it oh we just made it glossy oh [\h__\h] she
went from the pen eyeliner to the the
the liquid eyeliner let's go girl yes
sheesh girl
sheesh although
now it's too much a little bit too
much I wish I could adjust the angle of
the
[Music]
eyeliner
nah now you're putting me into a
difficult position man oh
well
uh
[Music]
ooh my wife you look so beautiful in
this light Mama
Mia oh
sensual a pretty
woman well walking down the street
Pretty
[Music]
Woman why is she so
pretty
freckles I love freckles but I don't
have
freckles can I still give myself
some is it allowed is it
accepted okay this light it's hard to
tell what's like the most neutral light
I guess
yeah contrast kind of high need a soft
box oh
ah yeah like the eag girls do it this is
the eag girl cheek all over the
nose got to do it all over the
nose actually or or orangish maybe looks
good yeah see she already looks like a
[\h__\h] eag
[Laughter]
girl what the
[\h__\h] this doesn't look
right oh oh wait now I see what's
happening but the edges are do you see
it maybe not if you're on the phone but
if you're on a bigger screen you can see
the edges are like
um
like noisy like a noise
effect so let's not do
that oh [\h__\h] she's so
wet no I'd like to stay um matte please
thank
you
oh
girl she pretty wait she's looking less
and less medieval
[\h__\h] this yep uh the lips got to stay a
little bit
[Music]
natural yeah let's keep it whatever oh
my God don't do this to me wait you look
like someone now oh am I thinking of oh
God
[Music]
girl I don't [\h__\h] care no ah
what okay I wasn't done I don't want to
look at your teeth I don't care about
them she the buta do is a little bit
[Music]
strong wait now my skin looks so yellow
so
unhealthy where's skin
here I know uh was it this maybe just uh
here
this uh kind of red maybe this this
maybe maybe it's kind of pink though
apparently [\h__\h] it's so
different it's so different so hard to
tell
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah
five
[Music]
maybe okay it just looks yellow
and what I look so unhe heavy [\h__\h] here
[Music]
four what how can I it looks different
in every [\h__\h] lightning they're
interesting but like how can can I ever
make a decision then I don't know what I
look
like uh what what's your problem with my
twig arms they're noodle arms okay
excuse me they're staying because I
don't know where they are anyway uh okay
let's just do this in this light I think
the skin looks uh healthy not really
pale enough but it freaks me out in the
other Lightnings so [\h__\h] it tattoos nah
I don't know if I want to do this just
too much to look at
[Music]
dirt oh my God actually kind of cute
actually kind of cute to have it in the
[Music]
face wow she's girl girl went into a cat
fight in the
mud actually I just want a little bit of
dirt in the face not all over the body
H this is like not too much but actually
you know what I
don't I don't want the dirt after all
okay I'm done although the hair color
really bothers
[Music]
me
because you
know it's just the the texture with
these brighter saturated
colors are h
like the Browns look fine the black uh
would need a little bit more different
colors in there but especially the roots
look kind of funky with the brighter
ones
[Music]
see maybe it's because of my graphic
settings
though
yeah wait um
yeah orange is just uh not really
[Music]
easy what the what do you mean that's
the only thing I can really change is
like the
back lower part of the hair with these
root tip
Blends ah and an NPC does the NPC give
me more
[Music]
Choice I'll just go with this you can
get brighter dyes do they look better
it's much later in game oh yeah who
knows if we'll get
there all right lady uh your
Vito
vocation oh that's the class okay we can
be a fighter fighters battle their
enemies in close quarters an Archer will
the boat striking down FES from a
distance a mage use their St St staffs
cast a variety of
spells mhm addition to any party are we
going to have a party thief
thief F appear and Flash of daggers on
the battlefield too quick for the eye
maybe I want to be fief
CH but I don't know the the armor looks
dump on
her but we're probably not getting this
armor from the beginning
right she looks so bulky like the skirt
looks so bulky
she looks best as an Archer but I feel
like I want to be
to Fe for dodging Fighter for
blocking you know I won't be doing
either we'll
see
uh can I hear it
please ah here x what which one's x h
square is X
[Music]
[Laughter]
whatever
I would have liked them to say a few
words or so that would have been
helpful
okay Monica my my name is not Monica I
am
Kiwa who the [\h__\h] are
you what can I put in my name ah
okay who who is caps lock who is moniker
what the [\h__\h] oh my last name is is my
last
name
a uh what's my last name takanashi do we
have
a
takanashi
takur there's some Japanese sounding
names there
t FMA F
tiger I don't
know
Tyrant K Tyrant
Tyrant there's no Taki what the [\h__\h] can
I not change it on my
[Music]
own
teren Tal
T also not
there turn
tigeri Tachi sounds
funny kind of like
Tachi
T Hello nice to meet you everybody my
name is T from Whole
Life there was a t but I don't I I I
want a longer name I feel like the
longer ones sound have a nicer ring to
it it's a nickname it's a
nickname oh no I don't want to be
nicknamed Tachi what the [\h__\h] are they
going to call me that in the
game not good not good C it why do I not
get to choose or type in my own
nickname kiata becomes K maybe or kiata
becomes
Kelly
Kimberly
Kirk I kind of want to do
Kirk I want to be Kirk I just want to be
Kirk and I'll just never be happy when
anybody calls me Kirk let's go Kirk I
will to be Kirk
I ill like that look in your eyes is
querly brazen for a porn let's go
Kirk okay let's go we're in the game
here we go I ill like that look in your
eyes just cly Brazen for a p most of
your kind Have Eyes blank as a cadavers
mayap is only natural seeing us how you
rise from the dead there's ought
different about you though could it be
that you fear death just as we Mortals
do K Kirk
Kirk Kirk my beloved was there a phoenix
nickname
really it's okay I'm Kirk I am Kirk I've
always been Kirk OD counter are you
going to say that a lot worry not vessel
vessel 3 days here and you'll be longing
for death's sweet
Embrace yeah I I would like a hug from
C seems like she's actually resting
because she didn't reply to me so sad
come along you stards oh I thought you
said
fuckless
okay let's look at me oh I am too
pretty why did you hey hey I I should
have gone before you lady can I run
I don't think I can I'm just going to
follow Chad W game is very dark yeah I
made the settings appropriately it's got
to be dark although it does look much
darker on my other screen
yeah yeah game is Just dark it's what it
is is it too quiet though by the way
this doesn't look so dark guys but I can
still if you guys say so I'll make it
brighter
uh sound is fine okay
oh excavation side the
hole oh nice
architecture too bright dark is
immersive care to play about get a move
on I don't know I don't know what's
what's more accurate cuz my middle
screen is uh brighter than my right
screen that did look pretty dark I don't
know what to go
by it's washed out
now okay maybe the
[Music]
um this one maybe a little bit
less is it different Prett kind I still
kind of washed out maybe can't wait for
the new equipment to come in the darkest
spots are too
gray okay we're been maxing not only the
character creation but also the the
darkness
oopsie
uh how about now
I've have no time for you now leave me
be uh
okay don't know why you would say this
to me when I'm so pretty everybody wants
to talk to
me do your injuries pain you pray do not
overexert yourself oh you're so nice
thanks mate this is no place for one of
your ilk ilk is Harsh beyond measure oh
there a lion in the to the brink me you
ought not anger the overseer let us
proceed to the
site the
overseer I I did start watching Fallout
last night I watched the first episode
it was amazing and there's overseers
there too so that felt relatable oh
she's running let's
go the the main girl oh my God she's so
pretty she has like such nice facial
features and I I love all the music they
play I think in the game they also play
music like
that oh RPG instincts lead me in a
different path oh
no
oh there you go I found something got
the old timey stuff it's really cool I
was kind of confused by the end of the
first episode but I'm sure it's kind of
normal um because they're like
introducing all kinds of different
groups the guy with the hat with no nose
looked really familiar I've seen him
before maybe from people cosplaying him
or so I don't know time for you to get
to work he's famous I
think the ghoul yeah is the is the ghoul
in the games too the buttons to mirror
the a it's okay actually because on the
bottom right they show uh which ones
they are that the right one is be and so
on so it's actually
fine W Walton Goggins there are many
different ghouls ah but they all seem to
wear
hats yeah and so there's a so what from
what I understand there's the the people
who live in
the in the underground safely and then
uh there's the people who are Raiders
but do they also live underground it
seems like they didn't come from
overground but maybe I'm wrong uh how
else how how else did they get into the
Vault because it was so secure did the
Raiders also Come From the
Vault just like from a different Vault
they used to live underground too yeah I
I'm curious to find out why they started
raiding I'm very curious about that uh
explanation I'll find out okay and then
there's the the people the weird people
who are like who are hunting the ghoul
but then they got killed and then
there's the people that are like AR Army
kind of people who are looking for
someone they talked about they're
looking for someone but also the the
hunters the that wanted to hunt the
ghoul were also hunting for the same
person I'm like wait I think they talked
about moldaver or so which is the leader
from the raiding party I think oh maybe
I'm mixing up things yeah the
Brotherhood it's very interesting I'm
excited to watch more
very
excited hey I got it right so they they
were looking for moldava and then we uh
we as in the main character is looking
for her dad H and who got taken by the
moldaver so we'll also be looking for
moldaver so interesting I'm excited yeah
it's so nice man it's kind of sad like
it starts with the like uh 200 years
before
scene uh like I mean it explains of
course how how it became this setting
but like you get like a little bit
attached to that family the the hus the
the the guy who's like raising this kid
right you get a little bit attached to
them and then it says bam 219 years
later oh
no so sad play Fallout Baba I will I
will I
will I'm getting into it I I decided to
like watch the series and play the game
like kind of at the same time
yeah yeah the scene was shocking when
the he tells her like about the fun
thing I didn't know that either I didn't
know that's what that guy in the logo
was doing he was measuring the cloud I
didn't
know and he tells her and then
immediately after Kaboom
sheesh you like this model I was
thinking like the other my my dark Wawa
uh model also fits really well but uh I
forgot about it and I thought this one
looks also good they both fit this game
I think anyway sorry sorry sorry for the
tangent Fallout
tangent I'm excited yeah I can use
both now I want to play uh New Vegas
right not Las
Vegas yeah it's been a while since I
used Empress wava so this is a good
opportunity
anyway
what pick up a
boulder okay these look like I can pick
prep to work then you all Begin by
carrying stones out from the station in
the back and bringing them here mhm
oh okay I kind I want to go on an
adventure but okay light Lantern
lb
lb is that not left Mouse button wait
what okay it's this
okay okay I'm I'm figuring it out even
if the prompts are different the
vicinity is quite bum pray leap oh that
oh
I don't understand you people I'm not
from
here can you like talk to me in Latin or
something and I bring it here here was
it a job well done than now the next
step is
to
yeah oh [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] do we have to use our pump to
measure something perhaps we ought to
investigate no not that kind of
explosion right right okay perhaps we
ought to investigate guys I'm an
investigator lb Dash oh oh
e wait which one's be uh this one's be
oh I hear a monster is it a
dragon what's going on no that is
Medusa what the
[\h__\h] oh no
she's
real no the dam thing's been
awoken
you even at the cost of your lives uh
okay I never fought
before suddenly I'm up against
this get me out of here you got someing
weapons maybe I'll try
is the my doesn't look orange at
[Music]
allone no
okay Swift
strikes weapon watch for an open then
press your phone till they over I'm
carving I'm carving you can stop showing
me that
now I'm twin fanging I'm twin
fanging I am fanging the twins
can I dodge who wa Whata where am I may
not carry Shields but Nimble allow them
to
dodge oh even at the end of her tail I
can do damage that's pretty cool Al I
think it's kind of [\h__\h] loud is
it uh sound
Boulders barrels and theik can make
effective weapons ever what
really I don't see any boulders to use
here oh wait never mind let me try using
this grab op oh where did it go oh
that's fro them with
RB when delivering strikes I would
recommend to your press RT to grab on to
them oh oh wait and now I'm riding
her riding the snake am I though am
I I should be on there wait is it
dead I guess they
died are you unharmed get
chased but a stretch SC scratch while
you can
after all your charge awaits you my
charge you cannot linger in this place
forever ringa linger you have lost your
memories is surely the work of a f curse
but worry not there is there was a curse
after all you need only believe in your
own tesy ARA Tails over eyes oh I'm
lagging let's
go let's go I'm
lagging woo can't son it the cursive
creature escaped that's
okay oh you get back
here
quickly this way or is it as long as the
game looks nice come this way and it's
only the cut
sclee uh okay
here oh my God there's another weird
dude there Flee for Your Life flee flee
you must jump that is the
[Applause]
only
yumy the same weird dude don't follow me
don't follow me I'm going for no can
survive a fall from this height not even
a
porn let's go I want to play World Of
Warr I want to play World Of Warr don't
just stand there put it down next week
while question
mark not quite a bird but yeah kind of a
bird H bird H lion let's go it grains
are amazing I love
[Music]
Gins go now so fluffy so cute Best of
Both Worlds learn all you can of this
world and
bird United to be
fi bana
baby Capcom let's go how do you what's
how do they say Capcom when like Sega is
Sega Dragon's
Dogma two question
mark oh my God this is just like world
the
[Music]
barup Capcom presents wait I can't
really hear it in my brain
No Cap
Club medieval
helicopter D oh wait is this like a
mostly oh guess the fact that it's from
Capcom should have told me but it's like
very western
style to me like the game gives me such
a western impression but these are all
Japanese people
[Music]
Western
Inspire it's like their take on
Boulder's Gate or
[Music]
so
yeah what the [\h__\h]
man hey
oh my God my poor bird
no
[Music]
no what the
[\h__\h] nice that looks like a really cool
scen scenery
though
man we're being raided
I have hyper chat on I can't see
it it's gone thank you do thank
you oh you B sorry one one moment
po okay I wanted to fix
something sure
sure ah
Rea
Rea thank
you okay here we go un
pause pray keep your distance or isn't
what is happening worry not for me the
Grine May swallow me home you fing with
but I will not perish no there's a stone
not far from here known as a rift Stone
pray seek it
out if you're truly the Arisen then our
heart surely so funny
actually he's like he's being drowned by
this weird [\h__\h] curse thingy and he's
like so calmly talking like oh yeah make
sure uh you'll go somewhere I'll be back
go a this but the scratch he's like so
CH this is so weird
again does it not hurt
or that looks like it would hurt are you
all right what's happened here are you
all right are you all
right o
o all right are you all right a griffin
appears one moment and Falls the next
and now now you stand before
me yeah that is what happened thanks for
uh reading out loud the script was it
you then the one who was riding on its
back perhaps I was being
transported um against my will it is a
wonder you survived accompany me to the
stronghold we'll treat your wounds and
hear your story oh really oh really
you're just going to be naturally so
friendly to a stranger
m i don't sense any danger in this at
all Ultra Mar Senai
Waterfall oh
no the
Gino oh my God can somebody close its
mouth oh man follow Justin with double
n Justin all right
Justin I am right behind you Justin
where are you is this is this you
Justin wait what can I open toata Justin
I have to open the
box salubri is dropped cbri is
beat oh we're getting more and
more random mentions of kfb
members never heard of certainly like
that here in ver could it be you were
held in the neighboring country of
batal I wish the subtitles would be at
the bottom of the screen not cuz when
he's running they're like wobble wobble
wobble wobble wobble hard to read for
you guys I think that's unlikely we've
been estranged from Bal since the war it
is difficult to imagine any citizen of
verant being sent there wait can you
wait like what if I find an item oh F
goblins let's take up your weapon sir
you'll be needing
it Str buy the Cur or have a bit green
one like this what
that I don't know when one of the things
comes best guard or
Dodge quick fighting style
though make use of the SL we'll give you
an advantage against their ranks oh
really are you just saying that or is
that really a thing there are oft items
to be scavenged from the bodies of
monsters in their ilk if you're not sque
sorry why did it interrupt him shelf or
Draw your weapon of LT uh there we go
yeah I like it so far the battle is nice
B system where are you going I'll not
force you to receive treatment but I'd
at least like a word I don't know I
found some stuff together man my RPG
eyes I can't help it I'll try to I'll
try to hold
back combat is the best part of the game
ST eff at
stabbing oh what's
this doing a little fishy fish oh yum
debilitations are
NE why am I getting a negative status
with effects that range from inflicting
damage at steady intervals to making the
uh Target vulnerable to a specific type
of attack they're not exclusive to the
original their pawns but can be
inflicted upon their enemies as well
granting a fierce Edge in battle if
applied wisely did the fish eat
me or it's because I'm wet oh
consult each debilitation entry for more
information about
effects okay I'm just wet shut
up where do you think you go you can't
just run off
now what about this boat I'm sure I can
yeah yeah yeah there's just certain
things that look like you can do
something with
it 100 gold k
k the sound of
money and of green weish oh what the
[\h__\h]
no oh he's got like a shield on
him when an enemy is fling you can pick
him up
with uh what the [\h__\h] where's the
where's
Dodge y
[Music]
okay he's dead he's dead I'm dying too
though is that my HP down
there okay he died thank God can I heal
level up
bye level two let's
go Apple oh my God my
HP how to heal
where are you
going there's more Goblin
horn I picked up okay can I eat
oh W this inventory ah I like it I don't
know why I'm so excited but it gives me
hey a little bit of uh Diablo Vibe I
don't know I don't know what I'm
feeling sh fish yummy can I cook too in
this
game wait I'm kind of liking this so far
salubrious draw is a basic
heal oh and then the salubrious beats
must be the ex Superior heal
H where do you think you're go you can't
just run off now
nice nice oh fief tutorial loog book
wait what
H hold it
ah wait which one where
what oh
here press RP to use Swift step of Dodge
okay thanks
[Laughter]
reads free words all right thanks I
happy Mother's Day in case there's any
mothers in the chat besides my own mom
I'll not force you to receive treatment
but I'd at least like a word I kind of
doubt it that there's more than my own
mom in the
chat oh yeah I saw those
berries I saw them berries mommy was um
I gave her a call today she was like
flexing at me
about all the berries she was able to
harvest
man I'm so jelly I want more berries
too happy Mother's
Day I'm your
mommy I'm your mommy
now welcome Arisen you're prettier than
me we porns have long awaited your
arrival
okay you know more than I do porns seems
they bend the knee to you so readily but
then no surely you cannot be the Arisen
oh app I am Stone do you not we can take
you to
it pray come this way how do I
know what do you mean Pawn like you guys
talk about pawns I don't know what that
even is before you stands a rift
Stone
teleportation is a gate by which we of
the porn Legion may cross over into this
world pray summon your porn simply paint
with your mind's eye the loyal attendant
whom you would have serve
[Music]
you oh
okay n I'm choosing a preset try to and
Visage their parents you can even begin
with
preset
what you for real a
[Music]
pawn I got to make a
pwn get pwn I'm I'm going to make it a
kitty
cat feminine Beast
Ren uh I do
something I'll make I'll make either
chunky wonky or
smoothie ah but oh man it's going to
take a while no I just want to choose
like the
color
uh but yeah these bright colors they
don't
work they don't work so well
yeah this they're so
dark they're so
dark it's not going to work oh CH there
we
go oh my
God that
looks not
good maybe orange will be better let's
make a chunky
wonky no
[Music]
no no no what part is
this all kinds of this looks so yellow
though why is it so
yellow ah here's more
green here's very Orange
H again it's very hard to
tell
narissa build a
Nissa uh wait how do I how do I
uh oh no why did you give me this idea
it's actually good oh no
oh
no uh what yeah what what what what
character creator T
tall base
head
yeah
eh there
[Music]
Isa I'm going to speed through it don't
worry I don't know I don't know I don't
know I don't
know no
we'll figure it
out oh
[\h__\h]
ah oh
no yeah okay okay okay okay okay
okay black hair will be easy at least
big
head no small pretty small head um a
little bit a little bit
lengthy
uh maybe she's going to end up looking
better than Mikey
waa long neck we all have surprisingly
long
necks okay uh upper body um
can I make him bigger I want to make him
bigger oh
well just a little
bit how's it looking guys I'm not going
to make Shrek you're watching the wrong
channel that would be korei whole life
Ian Channel
[Music]
see I'm speeding for it it's like I'm an
artist
shes oh I didn't I didn't do the the FES
and the CLS different separately I
think uh rear size she thinks she's got
big big booty I don't know about
that I got to look at it again
closely she's got to show me that booty
again
oh uh wait must
tight she's just going to look really
tall but she's not really that tall
what's her actual size
180 something
right and she's got like endless legs so
the Torso it's got to be a little bit on
the short
side well was all oh a little bit short
after all something like that uh trap oh
yeah that was that thing
[Music]
okay actually it looks exactly like her
although her head is kind of too
big
yeah
um the
posture she does not move like these I
don't know
the Ang the elbow doesn't really look so
different to
me this also doesn't look so different
to
me
straight
okay now the more important stuff
caveman
walk let's try to find the right hair
first it's really just like really long
straight hair but they don't have such
long hair so maybe just something like
this I know I said it doesn't look so
medieval but
[Music]
and
then oh wait root color dip color oh
yeah root color can stay like that and
then the tip color can we find something
bluish this is this blue is this
supposed to be
blue I can't see a
blue they all don't look so
blue although like something like this
actually looks nice
blue I think it should be blue but
like ah I see the sheen now I see the
sheen
now ooh nice shiny
hair I don't see the
blue 168 looks blue oh yeah that's the
one I chose
but I can't see it maybe it's my screen
no here these colors I can
[Music]
see this
brown that's I don't know what that
is
[\h__\h] h
it is what it is it is what it is okay
uh I don't
know let's go
closer thickness what about the
finess
Finesse eh what's nissa's eye color
again oh
what's her eye
color ah red it was
red wait where's the eye
[Music]
color not red magenta
pinkish red well we probably won't be
able to nail it that perfectly
anyway where was here IE callor
here I call a preset okay red actually
wait I think I saw some good red ones no
in the
presets
oh this is kind of like brown
red did I cycle for them all
already I don't
know uh no let's use this as a base most
the red to
purple what am I changing ah the inner
thing then a purple
it might end up kind of looking like
mine although no this pretty this looks
pretty
cool I think that's kind of it
oh what do you
[Music]
think yeah she's got more red inside
mine is more like pink inside I think
that looks
nice e do
maybe this one's like more more detailed
a little bit pupil size make it a little
bit bigger oh I
size size oh big cute okay eyes Shadow I
mean I feel like M
yeah a little bit would look good on her
oh wow
dark I feel she's getting a lot of shade
from that from those bangs
[Music]
already but I do want to give her a
little bit of a darker eye
look without spending too much time on
it
oh there we
go oo the metallic looks weird
okay and then
eyeliner should
be M although actually well she doesn't
wear makeup but I'm just trying to you
know get the nursea look down a little
bit just a
Vibe she looks
cute actually I was rushing through it
all and she still looks
cute what does that tell you about
Nome no freckles
uh actually her skin color I mean skin
color is like my biggest problem
here but something
brighter
yeah more
shininess effortlessly
stunning let's do
something her head really looks so long
to me right
now I know one can change but like this
is probably not going to have many more
episodes so I bet I got to get it right
now LST Dr
[Music]
LST cute nose kind of I uh maybe the
maybe it's a little bit angled too much
upwards but whatever
ah what else I don't think we should
like change
everything
but a nice profile you think
so main story isn't very long so you
could probably beat the game if you
really wanted
to but I don't want to rush through it
either just because you can I know I did
that with Yakuza
but if it's a game like
this I don't know how long how long is
it then like when you don't rush through
it when you chill through
it U maybe a little bit
of lipstick
wandering around is fun is it like as
big as Ballers gate in terms of like the
[Music]
world yeah bigger
really flip-flop do a fault cuz both
games are more about exploring rather
than main story
H I'll have to think about it I also
still am like at the beginning of this
so I don't know if I really like it so
far I like it but it's hard to tell
[Music]
really
so I don't know I don't
know it's too too early to say to make a
decision
she looks so human to
me needs to look more like a demon but
[Music]
smiling Nissa is very happy always I
feel like she's very
Smiley she exudes the happy Vibe at
least when she's around me I don't know
maybe it's just because of me um but you
know probably also around
she I I I'm having uh this feeling you
know I saw her schedule saying shieldy
shieldy shieldy shieldy every day and I
thought it was a joke U but now she did
two shieldy off collab streams in a row
so maybe it wasn't a joke was she
serious is she going to do one today
too maybe I should start taking her
seriously I think we're done I'm happy
with this narissa how do I oh
wait no we're good we're good
uh
yes she should be a Mage and what
inclination
oh she is 100%
[Music]
serious she's staying in her place what
did they not get their
own did they not get their own what do
you mean her own do they have you mean
the same building but different places
or are they actually
living they should have
separate
quarters they haven't said that they are
in Japan oh right didn't they like ah
wait yeah they might not I don't know I
don't
know two women living
together I maybe there not I don't know
where they are she's a shoty house well
she might very much
be she might
be uh well okay kind heart calm simple
straightforward she's not calm she is
very not calm she's also not simple she
is a little bit straightforward but I
think most of all
she's a mix of all of
these except for C uh compassionate
devoted be
beautiful the most obedient sort of
pal but now now I kind of feel bad that
I'm making her my Pawn in this game
because of this
implication rational shrew Str nope
curious Earnest
adventurers perhaps that uh is
surprising that they call that simple a
pond with their heart on their sleeve
and enjoys exploring and Gathering items
and is always up for a challenge candid
flippant impulsive upon Unbound by
precepts if anything that would probably
be
me
so curious Earnest yeah yeah kind harded
and call out the best for Mages oh that
matters in
combination
then I think kindhearted she is devoted
to me and she is compassion
are you playing on PC yeah I wanted to
play on PS5 but they they gave me a code
for PC first and I said sorry can you
give me a code for PS5 and then they did
but then I didn't uh try to activate it
until last night and then I noticed it
was like wrong region so I had to use
the PC one after all but the it's fine
it's working
fine oh the people here are evacuated
and the people here are evacuated the
people here are evacuated and the people
here are the people here are evacuated
and safe there are more who can yet be
saved huh it seems the rain has abated
so the pond is actually allowed to have
like actual talking voice lines huh
former Arisen appear to be plentiful in
this world plentiful danger might lur
anywhere where there are more who can
yet be saved there are more who can yet
be saved fine showing I think four is
kind of there
uh I'm still in caps
loog Monker uh her name her
nickname is there something
similar Nemo n
n oh I feel like out of these narrow n
so becomes oh Raven is there a raven you
guys think of like these animal names
that I don't
even think about that they might have
them but if I'm Kirk shouldn't she be
something
Rex maybe there is a Rissa no wait Ra
was there a raven should be
higher Ringo R
Rex Rebecca
what if I just call her
Rebecca I like that idea
Rebecca hey
Rebecca oh I love it I kind of love it
Rebecca is kind of good she's like I'm
just teasing her like [\h__\h] with
her my name's not Rebecca it's [\h__\h]
narissa oh my God stop calling me
Rebecca but you kind of look like a
Rebecca Rebecca ravencraft it's it
doesn't even feel so unrealistic it
feels like it could have been her
name Rebecca and
Kirk
yay best things forever and eventually I
call her Becky oh hi Rebecca sorry
narissa
right
[Music]
Rebecca porns are known as crossers of
the rift for we are able to connect to
and Traverse Realms Beyond
this looks
good when we return it's our duty to use
our experiences and the knowledge we
have gained to Aid you on your journey
Arisen from this day forth I Shall Serve
you as your loyal porn and ought I learn
beyond the rift will be at your disposal
um where did you come from were you just
born out of that stone or did you have a
life before
that well I'll be me a porn summoning
before my very
eyes is that a is that I borned her I'm
her mommy happy Mother's Day Rebecca you
truly are the Arison then strange I
thought the Arisen was in the
capital surely there's only meant to be
one Arisen F this is all beyond my Ken
the watch head would know what to do K
I'm sure Beyond would have it he's don't
wor you're K enough I suppose we'll save
any further questions till the watch
head Returns what we like her for
then Rebecca focus focus
Rebecca what you've no memories you say
Thanks for the Memories perhap you could
make for Mel then Mel it was set upon by
the dragon not long ago Dragon's Dogma
the Arisen is said to Bear some deep
connection to the dragon should you be
arisen what is it a bear or a
dragon um what does Dogma even
mean is that a word an actual word or
did they make it up
Justin awful just off excuse
me dog Dogma
balls what a principal or set of princip
laid down by an
authority oh really that's a a
word by touching a riftstone the orison
can travel to the bridge at Twix
Twix
worlds which a great many ponds Traverse
as they Journey beyond the rift I want
to eat a
Twix [\h__\h] I love Twix like out of like
the Mars and Twix and Bounty or whatever
my favorite is Twix
man
yeah
[\h__\h]
diet well I can have like
one I need Tic Tacs for you now
no yeah kit Kat's also awesome I like
Milky Way too but just not Bounty
because of the coconut and Mars is like
a little bit too much and then what was
the other one there's um like one that's
very very chewy and nutty
or what's the other one Snickers yeah I
don't like Snickers that much either I
can eat all of them except for Bounty
though yeah these PS will not wait wait
I may skip
something as the journey beyond the rift
this allows the Austrian to summon pawns
it looks like Austrian if you just
whoosh whoosh your eyes over
it accurate this allows the Austrian to
summon pawns who meet their specified
preferences these pawns will not level
up while they are accompanying you
however so you may find that you need to
hire new support pawns
at they don't level up and I got to keep
on making new ones that so that they
keep up with me
and
what I want to keep Rebecca
though oh my person one levels up this
one pray ask all you wish to know ah
okay I shall answer if it is within my
power to do so well why are you so just
act normal I'm a normal person tell me
of the austrians it is the name given to
Fate's chosen those destined to command
the porn Legion and Safeguard the world
from the threat of the Dragon
uh what those say
command save guard the world oh okay is
there only one even with your memories
lost to you I am afraid you cannot
Escape your fate ah [\h__\h] really man
that's so annoying what a pain in the
ass tell me of Pawns Nomads we are off
cool oh born in other worlds we travel
here by means of the rift stones that we
might Aid you Arisen Austrian however I
cannot speak as to our true nature for I
know of it not none of us do we do not
need to we merely do as we are commanded
a booty press
for Rift stones are Gates that connect
this world to a multitude of others
she's not even listening she's looking
at the floor by their power have we
crossed into this world and when our
mission is done by their power should we
return to our own look at them oh am I
listening who knows what's happening in
my head we will never
know very well may Fortune speed you on
your way Arisen
Arisen
Austrian this you not Australian not
Arisen Austrian remember it remember my
name right Rebecca
I am attentive and loyal and prefer to
remain by your side in battle I shall
follow your lead and prioritize support
sounds like something Rebecca would
say can we talk more might small the Sun
's
High okay that's all you have to
say I feel like narissa normally would
have a little bit more to say so maybe
you're not therea maybe you are Rebecca
after
all uh what what do I touch this thing
now or is it touched
already
oh oh oops
sorry B watch RI Stone whoa what the
[\h__\h] oh I can see their
levels oh like I can invite someone to
come with me or
what level
four I can hire two more PS
[Music]
oh okay ter Terren it is a pleasure to
meet you that's cool if it's like that
then okay that's cool wait he's so
expensive we got to get a lower level
one uh 68 68
zero
zero oh when they're maybe maybe when
they're on my level they cost zero cuz
I'm level
two if is discipline your company Lacks
shall we discuss tactics now or later uh
later maybe we'll just fight with no
tactics just have fun pleased to make
your acquaintance you're so tall oh my
God delighted to meet you
especi yeah it makes sense that they're
more expensive if they're
overlevel oops okay I'm done I have my
group I think right leave the rift
there they are we're party four
now I have a a warrior and Archer so we
got all the classes now I did that on
purpose looks like Shaggy ah you're
right you're right and
now what do we
do do I follow that yellow sign on my
map a treasure chest shall we see if we
can't make our way over to it what
where oh going out are you you sure
that's a good idea you seem rather
unwell oh really you ought at least rest
for the evening there should be a spare
only don't go rushing off before you're
ready take it from me you're better okay
that's fine but I want that Treasure
Chest what where is
it I see it on the
map but I am blind
is it just like Freedom now do whatever
you want already I need like some kind
of main
quest all the save data cannot be relied
upon to save your progress in this world
is recommended that you rest at inss at
regular intervals oh so that's how you
save thank you for the py Hoy there you
seem well tired tell you what you can
stay here tonight free a charge let's go
I'll expect coin from Tomorrow mind yeah
my P always used to say there's no to
good night sleep can't fix not much else
I can offer I'm afraid but you'll find
all sorts at a finer
in okay I being armed is better than
being defenseless even if you're
untrained but still it is worth devoting
yourself to a vocation if you can opens
up new doors it does he said something
else in the beginning you should stop by
the Inn in Mel if you get the chance no
hard feelings if you prefer it they've
much more to
offer resting at ins staying at an in
full restores your part's health and
stamina it also recovers the Lost gge
which represents a reduction in your
health and accumulates when uh taking
damage when resting at an inn you can
choose whether to rise the morning or at
night useful if you need to set out at a
particular time for sighted adventurers
will stay at ins regularly to avoid
risks when traveling
[Music]
farfield uh let's go there are worse
things than turning in early on living
he's going his own way he's like you
can't hold me back subtitles I say what
I want for a moment did I doubt you'd
grow stronger someday having said that
is quite a Rel there's no discipline
that deadfast devotion cannot teach why
the [\h__\h] did she level
up gaining exp what did you do what did
you guys do at night what were you doing
while I was
sleeping okay what now
at the quest of going to sleep this is
quite a
quandry I find goods for S find goods
for
sale hey you a
soldier to be a surprise to see you one
what I AMS of monsters have been
plaguing in this area of late you see
we've had to start sending
out play and watch me
Wayne is that so who went
Yonder Lan but I dare say he'll Fair all
right I I expect he will who was sent
out that way
then
Accardo to be honest sir his nickname is
I'm a little worried for him AB what
weren't harpies reported in that area I
can't have those on his own not
listening this is the first time hearing
of it f i want to go to his aid but we
can't just abandon our posts Rebecca's
listening say you seem Stout of heart
would you be willing to go in our stead
it isn't far only a short ways out the
main
gate very
obviously youve my thanks and a cardos
as well I'm
sure I have a
quest she'll fill us in later once she
St us the current state of the Sun
that's all I care for
though you can select a quest to
prioritize from among those you have
accepted if the quest destination is
known it is
known a marker will be placed on your
map to indicated furthermore if you have
a pawn in your party who possesses
knowledge of this particular Quest they
will be able to guide you oh however
Pawns of such knowledge will not offer
guidance unless the quest is set as a
priority oh some quests are affected by
the passage of time and will progress
even without their arisen's
involvement taking on multiple Quest at
once comes with the risk of being unable
to act in time and this can result in
unintended consequences oh [\h__\h] try to
Bear the factor of time in mind when
managing your current Quest and taking
on new ones let us do everything in our
power to render Aid to those in need
okay Siro is in need of our Aid oh me
thinks I know where to find the person
you're looking for me thinks
a guide is most welcome now we sh lose
our way hi let's go but we got to fight
B There are four commands that the Risen
can use to direct their Pawn
companions yeah I see them on the bottom
left I can
tell go instructs pawns to act in the
penalty of the Rison during the combat
it directs pawns to spread out across
the battlefield it can also be used to
request assistance with carrying on an
action to request guidance to a location
or to instruct a pawn to resume guidance
that has been interrupted okay so do I
use that if they want if I want them to
help me in the
fight Tumi instructs pawns to approach
the Austrian during combat it directs
pawns to fight by the Austrian okay
there we
go wait yeah help ins to support healing
and Recovery oh would seem our fight is
not yet down we fight well
fast aware of the woohoo did she heal me
are you healing me what is this what is
this
wait damn we're such a good
party I knew that I could count upon
your strength
Arisen let's see this looks
fun oh
are plentiful hereabouts no harm in
picking a few what if I take this can I
drop it somewhere to do something fun I
can maybe drop it on that
sleeping
[Music]
douchebag stupid
human oh no bad aim why are they why are
they seeing me already
[\h__\h] can she guide me
again uh like maybe I say go oh wait
never mind you wish me to return at once
Master
oh quick death okay now maybe I say
go can
we well where's where's lady who wanted
to guide me wait did she leave [\h__\h]
where is
she where is she
oh
butterflies I'll take that we might find
a use for it nice nice nice she ran
while you were turning around wait wait
wait oh wait is that her is being
drenched how do I make her like lead me
to the quest goal
again
oh what what's he doing
he's so excited let's go okay ah when I
said it towards her she started
running I hope she's running this
generally used as
aial I'm sure we'll find a purpose for
it in
time is this healing
me I think it is
why are you still fighting let's go
let's go let's go it is n nice nice nice
I felt the warm embrace of
Rebecca I missed the warm embrace of
Rebeca what the [\h__\h] heartbe or what
down things yeah get down who are you
get down
they look a little bit stronger than the
other ones I'm like I don't know what's
happening with me wait what who
died fell we fell asleep shall Aid you
directly I suppose there is such a thing
as too much
sleep well destroy it hurts she woke me
up
okay what what the
hell
interesting ripened Apple oh who are you
should we talk to him maybe he's going
to say thanks to us or are you the guy
of them I avocado the avocado guy oh
this was part of the quest there a
[Music]
bunny you have my thanks I do not
believe for a moment I could have slain
those creatures without your help I
don't don't believe it either they would
have made you go sleepy time I've only
just enlisted and when I thought this
could be the end of me I I was
paralyzed you saved me this time but I
won't always be so fortunate I'll have
to train harder till I have the
confidence to face such beasts on my own
oh I'd best be heading back but I'll be
sure to let my superiors know of your
good deed I hope we meet again let be
known let it be known making our report
ought to be our next
priority here you are master I hope you
like it oh I found it myself thank you
in another world they're all learn Rift
Stone lies nearby shall I escort you
there Master uh yes how do I say yes
allow me to lead the way I can take you
to our destination by the optimum route
so she's bringing me to the
riftstone that would be smart if she
follows up on the thing she just said
she could
do now there's a worthy prize if only
tweren't so far
away oh I'm feeling something oh it's my
stamina
oh wait what the [\h__\h] is
this cinnamon
barg yum cinnamon here we go again
you must on fighting Victory whatever
are you
guys or uh enemy before you vanilla
flavor people and victory shall be
ours wo wo
wo
she crazy
both both you can't just say both that's
the easy way out vocation rank up let's
go
both cinnamon cinnamon vanilla I think
there's more cinnamons over here if you
would I will also say
both over here where over where there oh
the way you're waving she's waiting for
me hey yo there's uh something
here modest camping kit oh can I cook
here I can make a camp oh for healing
and saving I
suppose where'd she go oh
there that's the correct
answer
oh I like this game so far like the drop
take care not to fall careful
now I like
it hey don't hurt my Archer
he only wears Lea armor I mean I don't
I'm not wearing much more but all I'm
de I died I died I'm dying I'm dying I'm
dying I'm I died I died I
died this tail has
ended
yo it's over it's so
over uh there are Auto saves right
so where where where may we
proceed okay
this is a
oh we're here well then we good but
proceeding over there seems very
dangerous slowing you down master oh
pray bear in mind that you can only
carry so much by yourself thanks for the
reminder maybe we should not go over
there like she wants to bring me to that
stone but maybe it's too
early maybe I shall go back I shall
return for
safety right give item to
pawn
how oh my God that's so cool I love the
menu what do I
give
nice that's what the pawns are good for
huh
nice I can't use it why
not I can combine in the inventory to
make new
items you want to stay
on hereabouts so light of light very
light is
good oh okay just for me or for
everybody cuz one is average now we see
if there's to be found while we're here
where am I how do I go
back oh wrong
way now then I learned of a forgotten
Rift Stone in this area during my time
beyond the rift which way am I going I
can take you to it if you like where am
I I think I want to go here right
yeah okay then I'm on the right way
right right there's a dude
there hello dude are you friend or fo
have a knack for Gathering items and I'm
ever on the hunt for new finds I'll
gladly try out any useful mechanisms I
Aspire the right way you look so
hugable oh you sell [\h__\h] no I can hire
you uh oh you guys will just like
randomly appear on the path to no I'll
GA these now it'll be a shame forget
their location we need them most calm
down now we don't want to carry too much
stuff oh I see
kadab
Abracadabra
um says narissa when she
turns people into cabers with her
magic thank
you thank
you are you also one of the those pawns
that I can pick
up I'm going to go back in and Report
you never reach our destination if you
continue with hey old friend many thanks
for aiding aard avocado a relief to see
him return and none the worse for
where I that it was the poor s might not
have made it back alive had you not
interv it was a bit too early for him to
be seing actual comat that much was made
well just a baby a baby we'll be
extending his train period
the instructors here are well known for
whipping recruits into shape with their
grueling regimes H speaking of training
regimes I must admit of half a mind to
ask you to join us we could use someone
with your exp or are you talking to
him
huh I reported back I got thousand gold
and lantern oil th gold let's
go orals of a new recruit
complete okay what next a treasure
cheest
shall we see if we can't make our way
over to it okay again you talk about
this Treasure Chest I don't know which
one you
mean not myy I guess there's this one on
the quest but I feel like that's not
even what you mean we're running low on
everything from we've had a hard time
procuring Goods what we've order
monsters looking on the road I sent
Marcus to gather what we need but I've
just taken stock and I Fe the list I
gave him was incomplete oh what say you
could have trouble you to run there and
glad to hear it here take this list of
additional supplies to Markus oh he
ought to be somewhere north of here
North and in the note and he'll take
care of the rest mouth is the next door
stle where where is mou do I have a main
quest for that not
myy uh ah yes I know just where to find
this person you follow me okay well this
simplifies things our task is nearly
done we need only pass our burden into
the hands that await it I like I knew it
to be
so you'll always know if there's a
ladder around because your pawns will
tell you about it 20 times a
minute I like how they like know what to
do like there's always Apparently one
pwn who knows what to
do it's
cute that they like take charge and want
to show me the why do you know the why
right just follow me yeah okay I'm here
I'm
here it's like it actually feels like
they're helping me it was an eventful
Journey oh there we are there everything
assembled a job well done if I do say so
Sor dud apparently you have to gather a
few more things wait did you need
something
it uh here's a
note
deliver this is from Sir Jeffrey is it
right s
then the ultimate back seaters I don't
know I would call it back
seaters they're with me with my team
wants these as well does he I thought I
was finished yeah you're not finished at
all why should I have to do all this on
my own I've got plenty to carry as tee
say as te your arms look free you can
handle that list in my state wow okay
she is just like giving me the whole
list
so that you can go back and be done and
drink your coffee and make haste I would
depart for the encampment even a moment
sooner wow his
attitude go
on ooh combining materials you can find
two materials to create a new item when
combining you can either choose the
materials individually or select the
combination that you have previously
tried you can also prioritize the
inventory you materials to be taken from
first the r order pawns uhuh should
begin by asking ourselves where where is
it and how can we get
it you are so funny art the items on
this list can be crafted by combining
certain materials and I happen to know
where they can be
found I like it I can guide you to the
vicinity of our destination Master yes
please do I will follow you your much
obliged why are they so
sweet I like what they say oh good thing
I'm here really I know just where to go
good thing I'm here really
what
H is it these
things grapes let's go we can make some
wine with this
maybe fresh natural grapes Suppose there
can be no harm in bringing this along we
cannot expect gleaming Treasures around
every
corner wait so what exactly do I have to
make uh
uh can I read how do I
know gather free hor spots and two
salubrious
droughts uh free salubris droughts okay
but it showed I can make that
out of something else how do I go to the
other
inventories oh
here har buts there's some
here
um he's got some too but how do I make
the
cous
DRS how do I know how to make
it X yeah but like how do I know what
how which
item cook green warish green warish
combine ah it gives me the options okay
ah any of these
ahuh
uh yeah let's just make a
maximum
M but I have to give it to him I want to
keep it shall we report back now yeah
H I
suppose might not be too bad to do
that wait where is he if I might be so
bold as to speak near already are
we I would have liked him to speak his
mine why did he cut himself off I wanted
to hear how goes it have you gathered
everything on the list yet I I think
so ah
yeah yeah
yeah okay let's
go partial delivery would also be okay
apparently brilliant oh knew I could
count on you but you're still carrying
it now then yeah cuz I gave it to I'll
be heading back to the encampment now
they'll be expecting me first he
complain about having to carry so much
no he's carrying it after all don't we
have a report to make Master I suppose
so uh then I shall return to the
encampment can I make a set way
point does it show yeah
okay
we oh now that we've delivered the items
on the list I suppose we ought to report
back to Sir Jeffrey no way for me ah yes
I know just way to find this person
follow me I didn't expect her to like
we're in your hands sir much obliged
fall down with her face straight to the
ground like that I thought she would
maybe try to land on her feet but no
no oh [\h__\h] my stamina so realistic
please that's exactly the amount of time
it would take me to be
exhausted is he leading me back to the
quester
Lost Bo it was you many thanks for as I
hear it you even assisted him in
gathering anyway you've been a great
help our efforts have seen the
encampment resupply and Sir Jeffrey with
one less care a good deed all round
woohoo let's go
Splendid okay I did like two side quests
shall we try uh to do a main quest
now oopsie uh if I mark it maybe I can
find my way you have heard word that the
dragon attacked mouth make for the
village and witness the aftermath
yourself or is it too early for me what
do you
think uh okay I
think if I maybe I can go there if I go
through here and then down oh yeah I see
the path a little bit or this path also
works but seems like more around it
you want to share do you want to use my
Rebecca I'll think about
it might want to rest first okay bridge
is down oh like this one here there okay
then I got to go this
way all right all right all
right
oh you want to use
Rebecca how do I show you my Pawn ID
here where's
the she has no PA
ID uh
late
love click that I
did I'm clicking
it you can find in the rift you think
so I don't know how it works I'm
pressing
it I'm pressing I'm pressing all the
buttons and then the cancel button cuz
there's no other buttons that seem to
work I did um maybe it's because at the
beginning of the game before I you guys
saw the screen I pressed something that
said like kind of disabling
stuff uh like online stuff but I don't
know if that also affected that
part press at the end okay
oops I've W to spare if you're looking
for lodgings and if you'd like to change
your vocation it's thousand gold
now I don't want
to I don't no I don't want to no can I
just
go I only have 4,000 I worked hard for
Tak what a rip off
man oh 250 for person
she why this is such a
ripoff always a
pleasure yeah can we not make like a
campsite at that camp for
example yeah okay fancy
aganda I'll be fine uh but just I need
to figure out the path uh right let's
get
out
okay is that the right path
yeah I want to eat snacks I want to
eat chocolate snacks
or chips what manner of treasures will I
find today I'm hungry that's definitely
to find out I've already noticed this
I'm like I'm
hungry yesterday too and I'm not even
100% following the diet uh even so far
today I've eaten that one
muffin and one egg and I feel like I I
should be allowed to
eat now but I'm in the middle of the
stream so that makes it difficult I have
the other muffin but I don't want to eat
a muffin I want to eat my sandwich but
the sandwich I have to make
first
problem you can eat you can have healthy
snacks ow I yeah I should have prepared
some cucumbers or
so goblins Master oh yeah I should drink
more water advantage against this are we
all in the same
boat is it dead all right level five for
Rebecca diet makes you think about
eating more no I don't think I'm
thinking of it's just really I'm not as
full as I usually am after my breakfast
so it's like not very
satisfying and I generally already don't
eat that
much but like one bowl of cereal like
fills me up for a while and
then I'm happy for a
while but yeah now now I've really
minimized it a little bit in another
world I learned that a forgotten Rift
Stone lies nearby oh you with your Rift
shall I escort you there Master is that
where I need to go actually the mou
place
[Music]
we see about it
oh most
impressive EV more victories like that
and we'll have them run in for the hills
a result to be proud of one of us
is I will protect
you heal me Rebecca heal me thank you
nice good
fight yeah they're hiding so well
they're coming out of
nowhere the Mage will heal you oh okay
no it's okay it wasn't that
urgent okay am I going the right way
still yeah and now decisions decisions
yeah fretting will get us nowhere let us
pick aart and see where it takes us
that's what I was thinking because the
map the mini map is upside down uh I got
to go
left here this
way I
think but I really don't know what to do
about food I can eat I have a banana I
have more muffins but I'm kind of
craving something more Savory that's why
I'm thinking of the sandwich but the
sandwich I have to make
M go out to the settings and fix the
north on the minim oh I can do that oh
i' wager our merry band can handle
whatever comes no challenges Beyond
where am
I uh left our combined might is as you
say oh are we going
there are they the ones that shot my
Griffin
no it's too it's too early in the Stream
to make a
sandwich it's only been 2 hours 40
[Music]
minutes says
waah whoa what the [\h__\h] there's a
remarkable treasure
[Music]
I'll take that we might want to
use fish there fish fish fish fish fish
the fish are so close to the shore they
are asking to be eaten by me
tide
swimmer one more no you can't oh wait
that worked sheesh okay
nice how's the inventory
looking light light average light okay
okay you're carrying some hairy stuff
huh um let's help him out a little bit
yeah that uh almost
worked still oh my God I can't help you
much more somebody's got to carry the
camping
kit uh yeah did you guys see my dance
shorts
recently you guys got to watch the the n
one the most recent one but damn oh my
God shorts algorithm kind of crazy so we
say short like I just like look at my
shorts one day and it was at 100K and
the next day is at 200k and the next day
is at 300K what the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what's happening martyr's resting
place
yeah the
algorithm oh I'm I went the kind of the
wrong way I got to go back and then
right I
guess Sun Bloom ooh sunflowers you mean
or
what but I'm hoping that with the next
one I can hit the
algorithm in a good way again I feel
like I might because the song I have
chosen yeah cuz also I feel like with B
DEA I was actually a little bit late
piggy oh what's happening I feel like I
can probably hit it and get meat from it
but I don't want to it seems to
be having a good sleep I don't want
to but yeah was say with BB was a little
bit late I think to the hype but it
still worked out
but with the next one I'll be super
Speedy I can throw it at my pond you can
carry it well and do what with
it are we there is this
[Music]
it now let me get one of my
muffins a [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] behold the
state of the village is a sow sight
indeed Dragon truly Isam Dragon truly is
Calamity
incarnate mayap a walk through the
streets would help jog your
memory when the Arison appears so too
does the dragon it is an immutable truth
of this
world right you are
I found chunky wonky
too she is so chunky and
Walky she was sleeping now I have her in
my
arms yes exactly like the
emote you can't hire me yet what nervous
H oh
baby oh baby my baby she's so soft she's
so fluffy so
fluffy he's like why did you make me up
why did you wake me up and pick me
up need to sleep and an in to upload the
pon oh we so expensive can I not just
the but I already slept once in does it
have to be the second time the first
time doesn't count or
what yeah I probably need to have
the network thingy
on okay
[Music]
can I take a bite of you chunky
wonky she's so warm just stay stay on my
lap please please just
stay MIM MOS hello
did I talk to you
oh
pable what's so pitiable about
Austrian
well the
[\h__\h] this is just what I
needed n forgot thy Destiny th charge
oh yeah I think I forgot it
actually no CA it's very pitiable truth
that is most
unfortunate but it do not release thee
from thy
fate I think it's time to let go chunky
wonky
bye-bye wa this is very balers
gy the Mind
flares Hello Dragon
[Music]
son oh was going to eat my
muffin how the [\h__\h] am I supposed to
fight that your faith in yourself that's
not
happening
down wait how do I
dodge it's not working anymore I'm a
different class now have
courage send help the fees I'm sure they
ticklish tickle tickle tickle tickle
tick I can't see
oh that's
it that was
it are you
smile oh she's
pretty we have to save her
[Music]
what the
[\h__\h] happened to my
face oh
me Quest it's like an ant for
you are you sure you want to eat that
just eat my whole
body that's why I have the scar from
this moment
forth Thou Art risen
Char and
door
cool hard
moner though art
Austrian pretty
lady can you hear me sir sir stay with
me stay with me
[Music]
she is
pretty thank goodness how are you
feeling this is the second time I've
watched this isn't it
m you do not remember m- then have you
forgotten that you protected me from the
dragon's
flames you withstood the fire in my
stead and were well and truly charred
it was
terrible I had thought your life
forfeit I could not hear the beating of
your
heart you hung on and by some
miracle
survived because I wanted to meet you
again I seem to have become Austrian the
isn't I'm afraid I don't understand your
meaning why why do nobody know what
Austrian is
man we may be a small country but we are
a significant one do not downplay
Austria please not while I'm here in
front of you does it have ought to do
with why you were taken to the
castle well maybe I'm Austrian royalty
yes that's why I would be in a castle
they said was so that your wounds could
be treated though I fear you have no
memory of this either m
I am of the Border watch someone with
Arisen like abilities came to this
Village porn in to know you is she my
porn no she come for
you we are to part so soon
then mayh you will visit me again
someday
a till
then take care
I love
her ah excellent you must be the one you
match my solders
description I'm glad I found
you the ruler of vermund currently
convalescing in the capital became
Arisen here in this very Village you
can't just become Austrian can you if
you claim the the same then word must be
borne to the capital I dispatched a
missive before coming here though I
doubt the matter can be settled without
your
presence would you be willing to
accompany me to the capital if you truly
are Arisen you will be received with
open
arms as I should as I should oh but
forgive me I scattered my soldiers in a
bit to few years
yeah I would not depart without them we
shall have to wait till they are
reassembled come to think of it sir
lennet was asking after you as well
mayap now would be a good time to speak
with him last I saw he was having a
drink at the Inn that rooftop looks like
my lawn after I mowed
it from pursuing the
information uh okay wait so the dragon
thing I thought that was us like uh
think this one's really seeing the past
or the
future but now it's kind of confusing
how connected all of that was
and what's happening it's all the same
to
me oh should I get new people maybe not
because they're like
although did you guys say they don't
level right so I guess now they're kind
of on the level Maybe maybe I should let
them go but what happens to the stuff
that they carry guess it goes back to
me not needed
yet you have to level eventually or it
gets harder you should replace them with
stronger
ones I like
[Music]
them goes to your
chest and that's kind of annoying that
every time I get someone new one I have
to put the items back where they should
go
oh so PR me if you must Master but I've
nothing more to
say I love him do I like him so
much after the partner levels them the
part
partner goodbye forever no out to F out
to
fav I hope you know how much I like you
art artsy
fartsy um give gift I can give him a
gift is that uh important that is
something good what does that do
camping
kit usually just give them camping kit
your stor is good because food don't rot
in
there the own of the upon the player oh
wait you're saying that art was created
by someone another Real Player and not
just automatically generated by the
game but I'm offline so I would think
they're automatically
generated oh but
ahuh if I wear online then yes not a
hold so maybe I don't it doesn't have to
be anything
really I only hope your memories of our
journey are as fond as mine AR isn't I
will miss you Arty party bye bye don't
go like that don't go
art I will miss you
no like I don't want to leave the rift
without
you okay we can uh higher level uh fives
now got to get rid
of
uh Fang to I guess I'll carefully
conserve my
strength have
uh what's the shittiest thing that I
have
this should you have further need of a
marksman my bow
is because it's not even like why why
would I give them something nice
H they're not even real people okay
Blues you are the next Chosen One
organized pack is my special if we share
our strengths
we only be acquired by pawns they are
not stly beneficial for they allow the
pond to act independently oh [\h__\h] what's
her
specialization if you would like your
pond to learn a specialization you would
do well to befriend people with various
traits and tendencies in the world
around you sooner or later these
friendships are bound to create
opportunities for your Pawn to acquire
specialization uh
okay a pawn can only acquire one
specialization at a time and learning a
new specialization will replace the old
one consult each specializations and for
more information about effect could you
not have chosen like a shorter
word so did I hire you yeah right and
then we
hire that's a
fif uh we have a Mage and there's
a what do we want yeah maybe you
Nigel my talance line combining
materials and I'll use those in my
possession to craft things for you in my
spare time strong lady to be honor to
serve by your side another strong
lady Pawn quests are task given to your
main Pawn to be completed beyond the
rift you set the task and must stipulate
a reward for the Arisen who hires your
main Pawn to receive upon the T what
what
what pqu provide valuable opportunities
for you to
obtain when sending a reward for no
reason who hires your main Pawn to
receive you is this uh do I have to do
this now what
is she
unique what does that even
mean
h for the other player yeah too much
blah blah blah blah
blah shall we go and speak with sir
Lenard Master oh yes have you some
business with the Apothecary sir no
Dreadful sorry if I was in your way you
are not in my way you're next to the
door oh no I'm not lost or not sir you
needn't worry yourself on my account I'm
in a perect training you see my family
runs a little shop in verw worth so when
I heard t a medicine only to be found in
this Village I thought I'd come and
fetch some for us made the journey all
by myself as well if you can believe
it why you yapping so much to me well as
luck would have it I've have not enough
gold for the medicine it will be a shame
to return empty-handed after coming all
this way but what more can I do what
could you do H besides begging towards
me I don't trust her suppose there's not
else to be done but make for home mayap
I'll browse the shops before I leave she
doesn't sound genuine to me can't find
what else to take back she sounds like
she's manipulating me I don't know what
to do yeah I don't trust
you maybe it was a genuine side quest
but I do not trust you where do I
go
here well met you're the one who saved
Ora's life aren't you m she told me all
about it it was a very Brave thing you
did did I really do
that but or is the pretty girl that I
protected from the
fire but like I thought that happened
longer time
ago I'm confused I'm in your debt or is
as good as my daughter here consider
this a small token of my gratitude now
tell me are you registered with a guild
perhaps you already know this but
registering with a guild Guild will
grant you access to specialized training
which comes in very useful when pursuing
a vacation well now that would do you
need only speak with the inkeeper to
register go on it will only take a
moment T if there is ought you wish to
know of vacations mayap I can advise you
I would like to know about
vacations but no uh I don't really know
very well there is no wrong choice in
any case it is entirely up to you which
vocation you adop I'm happy with my
current vocation but I Shan take up any
more of your time pray be
well the MA's teaching the MA's teaching
is the most powerful skill that can be
acquired by each vocation learning a
Ma's teaching requires the use of a
special tomb which will uh which you
will receive if you impress the vocation
maester with your abilities however the
true potential of the skill can only be
realized by those whose vocation rank is
high enough
I suppose I'm not ready for
that probably uh and then what what did
you told me about like registering for a
guild what am I to do here at the end I
get so few customers you see that I can
manage both rolls myself but enough
about me did you need something it got
even more
expensive I will never rest always a
pleasure and ever any in I this is a no
in resting run
so this is where you've been come with
me to the Village entrance the watch
head's waiting for you okay we may
benefit from pursuing the information
go we shall P pursue pursue the
information why are you going in
circles sir GRE wishes to speak with you
master shall we go to
him but I don't know what I take it
you've some business with this person is
this a side quest or a main quest right
now follow
me a guide is most welcome now we sh
lose our way I'm just going to we have
arrived
oh and
now no first and foremost will you
accompany me to the capital yeah yeah my
thanks are you ready to depart or do you
need some time to prepare
uh I I
I guess I'm ready good then let us be on
our way am I ready yeah B I don't know
if I'm actually ready I didn't do
anything else in the quest so maybe I'm
underleveled I don't
know I am not
ready uh oh oh no cancel aort aort
I knew
[Applause]
you oh oh oh oh flailing
flailing they're good they're
good thank God for the NPCs
woo level
six dare I say it we TRC our a foe well
and true we mustn't allow ourselves to
become complacent take each trial as it
comes oh wow celeb dos all over the
place uh wait
so they're not carrying anything oh all
my stuff at least I have some healing
potions in my
inventory can learn skills in the city
well it's too late
now it's too late there
or can I actually go
back use the golden bug in your
inventory what does it
do a rapula GL like gold increases the
weight
oh oh that's
cool helpful little bug
slow Treasure
Chest there is a level up fruit Robo
rant
what tell you if you will get from the
main okay then I'll try to go
back but you guys have to a find place
to harvest some ingredients teach me how
to where to get those skills
is it that in The
Inn at the M
Star
okay uh the skills by the way we mean
like carve and and twin fangs that I
have
now something that we replaced that time
to get back to work where where
this one last long Hil if you've a
moment to as you can see we're
rebuilding a task that can always
benefit from another pair of
hands oh I have no actual skills oh okay
okay
okay what say you would you be willing
to help I have we'll be in need of
Helping Hands for a while yet yeah yeah
yeah
yeah where where okay armor we maybe can
buy too yeah yeah
am I my you really ought to have
returned by okay where do I get
what what should I
do what's this
place can I get can I wear this wonder
if
there's yeah I know the in but what
about buying
armor about
can I buy something is anybody tending
the store M MOS are you are you I only
work when I fancy but I get okay so
you're not fancying it
[Music]
now I don't see a sword icon to a chest
I shall take a look
inside oh [\h__\h] she looked inside the
chest on her own all right well that's
fine okay is this the in or what is
this ah well
met
aha here we go and I think this is my
kind of weapon the throat
Cutters is quite a bit better
does that sound familiar to
you it's
um sh yeah I'm trying to sound like Shi
because like some Clipper uses like
sh the
end that's I heard it like so often here
for some fruit roborant are we it's very
[Music]
catchy okay and then do I have something
some
particular
material here that I should be yeah wait
there this one's for thief there's a
thief
icon but I'm going to be out of
money I hope skills don't cost money
this one too oh yeah looking kind of
funny but kind of
cute I don't have to get armor for my
pawns
[Music]
right
criteria Miner
shirt only for
Becky for
narissa it doesn't show me
narissa where's narissa where' she going
oh was she just fed up with me calling
her Rebecca I'm
sorry I didn't mean it like that I mean
I I did mean it like that
but she's too far oh where is
she uh this one has Elemental resistance
as
well this one's just a little bit better
in terms of the stats
overall but I can wear both of them
apparently get the cheaper one yeah
okay hopefully now I won't die that
easily okay I don't know if I can afford
stuff for Rebecca pleasure Rebecca come
over here I cannot wait to put this new
equipment to use by what margin will it
improve our performance in battle I
wonder uh
Rebecca I said to
me I don't know what to
do is she where is she is she
dead what's she doing she
stuck at once Master oh now she's coming
when I say go and not when I say too
me what should I
do okay you really to have
returned is she wearing anything at all
right
now is this considered that she's
wearing something what about a staff
just a new staff but then I'll be so out
of
money I shall give it to her
she's never wearing anything clearly
naked
mhm not really worth it you think
so this one is this a funny hat it's a
little bit funny
indeed FY would normally wear that
sideways maybe maybe
not it's not that much of a big increase
though save it for later here for some
fruit roant are we do come
again for now she she shall uh continue
wearing what she has that's where that
chest
was and
now to the in
to return and you can teach me skills or
what sorry I always jump cuz like I
always think that's the button to talk
to people get so few customers you see I
can manage both roles myself but enough
about me did you need
something location gills all manner of
vocational procedures can be carried out
in the Guild Hall of a vacation Guild
changing
vocation no I don't want to change each
vacation trains different skills and you
will be able to learn new skills as you
rank within your vacation Rises learning
skills requires discipline core skills
can be employed from the moment they are
acquired but weapon skills must be
equipped before they can be
used
what what what did you
say oh I have quite a bit of
DCP core skills are passives
not weapon
skills what should I
get Scarlet kisses choo choo choo
unleashes a flurry of forward slashes
that doesn't sound very passive doesn't
look very passive Helm
splitter leaps up dives through the air
while
spinning blades extended more powerful
when performed from high places also
employable in
midair also right now I do have one
skill it's called biting wind but I
don't think I really knew how to
activate it
okay
L1 R1 giving me mixed messages is it
both I think it was
L1 I remember them teaching me in the
tutorial always got core skills
the body into a tight roll when hitting
the ground ah this looks more passive
after being knocked down allowing the
user to swiftly regain their feet reduce
damage and when knock them press
a a as an X or o oh oh I
think no
X I shall get that
maybe get all core
okay tap X repeatedly ah
okay well it's kind of passive as in X
is just like my normal attack I think
and then if I tap it a lot then it turns
into the flurry of forward
slashes a Ms
oh oh I can't afford it anymore
decreases the likelihood of being
targeted by for
oh that's the only one I could get
though these ones I could still afford
one of them brings daggers together to
ignite reaving them in flame for a short
time cool can also be employed while
clinging to or pinning down a
foe
oh na to us it to blend ah very fify
into the surroundings rendering them
more difficult for H TS I feel like
that's cool but like when like at the
moment it seems a little bit useless
because we have a
party and we're like always fighting
actively I don't know
oh do I have to use my DCP for narissa
too oh no she has her own
okay is there one you like for Nissa we
have
11 strikes the enemy from above with
tongues of
lightning padium get Boon and Palladium
okay she uses it on her own right oh
there's several
bons maybe a fire
Boon although she already has a fire
attack oh
well and her her core
skills oh f are condensed magical burst
does it make sense to get core skills
for the
pawn fireable will buff
you ah ah oh they all buff me ah okay
okay
okay that blocks up to free attacks from
targets cool cool cool core skills for
pawns are
good okay I'm
broke maybe I'll get this too
okay are we good
now do come
again are we happy now with
this I'm way better prepared than before
I think very well I shall go on ahead
yeah but like do you know where to
go where do we
go lead me my Entourage return by now I
think it was this way
my soldiers they're just following me
now
soldiers uh how do I just like tell them
to go where they need to
go oh are you going to you going to go
good let us make for the capital
oh okay
okay I was safe but no it's too
expensive there's all to safe
anyway I was rescued by it last
time surely it will be fine you can save
from the menu
okay well then why would I go to
the why would I go to the inn and pay so
much money when I can save for free huh
huh hard save and it is to take whatever
you like from my pack Master I'd gladly
see you I find to good
use my save doesn't heal me okay
well next
time back up and lets your pond return
of with gifts if you've got onine
services not a hot
you can get soft locked he yo Arisen is
the lawful ruler of verland so it has
always been to claim the title is to
claim the throne yet not all claims are
true I see go sees many Pretenders and
they are not dealt with likely let's go
let's fight oh what the [\h__\h] regard no
no is that the Sleep invite my Mist
[\h__\h]
oh wo wo wo that was a skill I
think I grant you roaring
Flames wait am I waking them up wake up
all of you were sleeping really well
done master that sounded
sarcastic well done everybody good job
for sleeping you little
shits good job on paying attention
as if the casting uh of the heart piece
was not very [\h__\h] obvious is there
nothing we can do about this obstacle
what obstacle if a ranged attack is
needed you can count goblins Master You
Can Count goblins
[Applause]
Master okay he that was easy that was
easy
peasy lemon in my water
squeezy
oh and now here there's a exclamation
mark what does it
mean what does it mean oh
ah oh we can actually with my daggers we
can destroy this big ass Rock
okay
okay all right then guys uh should I
carry this for
you the Austrian must carry the stone
really you guys should be carrying this
for
me is my army with me oh
yeah
okay this if was game looking
good n
y definitely not what I
expected I thought it was a one can see
far to the distance from here it would
be a good place to take stock of our
surroundings indeed you are
correct where are we going I'd wager
there's ought to be found here wait we
to take a closer look are we actually
going where he wants to go
oh wait now he's going
back I feel like yeah that was a side
path okay I let them there I was just I
don't know he wasn't going
anywhere go go go
dude stop losing the
way oh wow it's really hard to get up
the hill
Graphics looking nice right now out
here
oh oh hold here a moment I shall bid
them open the
gate
szie who's that you've brought with you
watch head
sir watch head an Arisen by all
appearances I we all watch heads an
Arisen another Pretender you mean uh I
am a real Austrian the sovereign's
Ascension has done little to stop such
charlatans from caring their trade
excuse me Knight it is uncertain this
one commands the Loyalty of the porns
mhm y'all are my porns all of Y what
impossible you know as well as I do that
there can be but one Arisen and he's up
in the
palace I'm well aware of how
preposterous idear is thank you however
as I do not believe it my place to rule
on such a matter I would make my report
to the capital if the claim is false we
will be rewarded handsomely for our
trouble if the claim is true however who
can say
h i don't quite believe it myself either
but my birth certificate says I'm
Austrian let us pass through the gate
and I shall trust what it says
because what else can I trust if not my
birth
certificate
berries we have found a material we have
found a material sure find a purpose for
it in due time I think you are a
robot I should not have hired
you please speak more naturally if you
want to fool me into thinking that you
are a
human be B Be B
yeah the Shaggy Pawn man he was so
natural he was such a delightful
companion chest TR allow me to open your
chest oh oh I got another
Beetle let's go beetle be where did the
beetle
what did you guys steal my beetle
Blues you bastard stole my
Beetle you shall be fired upon the
next
day nice what the [\h__\h] man you can't
just steal that from me
what's
this why do I still have this am I not
done with this
Quest put in stage at
in you can probably just toss that
oh yeah why does it stay in my
inventory how do I craft something
again I thought I can craft with the
horse but maybe I just don't have the
materials comb I don't see the comb oh
does it have to be in my inventory
yes well that's kind of
lame ooh detoxifying the cockin wait so
the other things do they also have to be
in my inventory or is this like taking
from I think this takes from everybody
cuz this is not in my inventory I
think uh
ooh
oh I want to make this whatever that is
Mighty roband AEL of impressive
medicinal properties
[Music]
y containing Cooling and fire coiling
elements poisons and I guess I can make
one cool cool cool cool
cool random crafting
done wait where are we going
where's my Army ah here you
are my head will row with fors goes
arai we're there
yet come
on are ass an ox cart was meant to meet
us yet it is nowhere in sight o may have
befallen it best we press on a card with
an ox
what does the ox
say oink oink oink oink oink oink oink
oink
oink what does the ax say can I open
this
yeah nice money I need it that you
needn't trouble yourself oh don't worry
I'm I want to pick it up because I feel
like you are a little Thief more than I
am more than I am you do not thief from
the
Austrian fous Lord what is it a
book a grim moir that casts a spell upon
being red usable even by those incapable
of magic invokes highle a lightning
spell but I wouldn't want to use it now
right probably not
I wish I could select several things at
once can I
not don't worry about saving them oh
oh I only sell them M maybe I'll do that
too
then oh there's a backpack or something
like that there I think yeah but those
are
heavy
ah o average average average it's okay
if they're average right they'll be
fine nice wful
I want to go to a place like
this there's a chest over there I doubt
you can really go there from here right
the current is probably way too strong I
which is fine okay make
Camp what for for healing right but it's
not the hard save I can do in the Inn or
is it the same if the Austrian has a
camping kit to hand they can pitch their
tent by the remains of a campfire
oh you can it's kind of a secret
entrance
oh not a heart save but will heal you
okay uh found at set spots throughout
the Wilderness much like staying at an
inn in town resting at a campsite rest
blah blah blah blah
blah should
be should be sure to keep a camping kit
in their
[Music]
packs uh affords opportunity to grill
meat granting a boost to certain stats
m before setting up camp it would be
prudent to eliminate any fos looking
nearby
oh I mean I'm not low on health but why
not use it oh looks
nice are we camping right now what if I
just leave now let's bask in the
warmth
O A everybody's chilling
[Music]
nice my Camp is
reusable and
now are we
done make pardon sir I mustn't be
distracted
aha
morning now we've the Vim to tackle the
day ahead for lighter ones we much to be
getting on
with there's lighter ones I trust so
somebody said I can go over there let's
try tread carefully by the water's
edge uh the brain lurk in deep Waters
rivers lakes and the Sea and will
instantly consume anyone or thing that
waits in into their midst uh if this
fate befalls the Austrian they will be
revived momentarily but they are the
exception pwns will become forfeit and
all other living creatures are met with
an immediate watery Dev uh return return
return return return don't don't
go so what how do
I hey come back come back stop catching
a fish [\h__\h] the
fish we don't need the fish oh
interesting oh oh I can rebuild
it wait I guess I rebuilt the other ones
too so far did
I but I think I don't need any new
people for now I think I'm
okay so I hope we're all still alive
let's
go no River baths
man man
he
so they just
said like basically you die unless
you're
Austrian so that guy who was like super
chill about it and said we'll meet again
maybe he shouldn't have been so chill
about it sounds like we're not meeting
again what Main Pawn I can get him
back oh no oh no the deers is everyone
all right
um be careful the deers the deers may
not be all right marks of the dragon's
Fury its Rampage must have don't worry
about it don't worry about us worry
about the
deers CH the M
dude the chest he's still on my
mind maybe I can reach it from here or
was it up there or is it on this
level oh wait I think
who what the
flex that's how you
climb uh or maybe it's difficult from
here I think the path leads us maybe a
bit higher
again it's probably nothing special
anyway although I feel like there's
something special in there why is there
a dead
Goblin I have not been here yet I
think well I would have preferred not to
have to fight so soon but at least I
know I am up to the challenge we must
not down
why is she in the front line my magic
brought to an
elemental thank you NOA H sorry Rebecca
oh the high five is
cute
oh that is so
cute the
interactions TT
oh oh they're coming
back they're coming
back that's
[Music]
interesting and but the one the the elk
is like kind of very focused on
something on the
ground
Apple Goblin horn 200 gold
o must explode more
more the uh way she like climbs up to
stones and stuff it's really
smooth what is this music are we facing
a
[Music]
botle
woo oh does it use my stamina this stuff
vocation rank up yay that was well
thought there's no one standing who
might say otherwise over confidence is
an enemy in and of itself let us instead
strive to better ourselves with every
battle ah have stamina so no MP for
me that's good I
suppose wow
check that place
out I mean maybe we're going there
anyway oh was
that I think we might be going there
anyway I dare say the cart Shan be
traversing this onward it might await us
on the road ahead oh that
way well what about that
way but that's a a lot of goblins we can
handle it
I could have done no better I can do no
to
easy for fake for f fate beats all your
belongings to me stay with me AR wait
right
there are they still alive level
seven and some good money
all right o yummy yummy yummy oh more
more rank
up let's check up
here no they had a nice little
Camp I will give them
that okay back on track sorry about
that I'm doing well well at the game I
really like it
man I like
it I am enjoying it so
far it was a glorious success let us try
for the same result Away really when I
first talked about being interested in
Dragon's Dogma I remember some of you
guys being like surprised about it but I
don't understand what's so surprising
about it now that I'm playing it this is
like totally up my alley just because
it's not anime style I love all kinds of
RPGs you
know well especially the medil ones I an
inkling this place will yield a rarity
or two well spotted shall we see what we
can find thank you for kissing my
ass yeah load of the Ring
[Music]
Style no no no no no you're not making
me
sleep no no no no no no no no no no
somebody shoot it shoot it you must wait
thanks
welcome the Archer is so important in
this
situation hey hey hary on my
way it was a coin flip but lots to like
well what's the Cornet part
be it's talk M everybody while you're
[Music]
fighting yeah
[Laughter]
pretty Beetle you need help there not
coming down H I guess with my ba skill I
could get him down too
maybe your dislike of el what I liked
the vibe of it it was really just a
difficulty
though this is not as difficult at all
so I didn't dislike Elden ring I want I
wanted to succeed in it
more but I felt like I was doing really
badly oh you got it going that way which
way you want to go this way which way
this way
okay no what's that what's going on
there someone else is finding
them who is
you wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
no can I lock on to Talent are useless
while pinned pray make full use of this
opportunity to fell it back got out of
hand ah I don't know if it's only that I
knew that I could count upon your
strength Arisen I feel like you were
capable of beating alen ring
maybe wasn't there something that made
it like easier after I was done
playing something changed and then I
could have maybe
uh I enjoy tackling Fierce foes and
prefer combat's Thrills to Gathering
items that's what you are there some
kind of update right are they nerfed
yeah I [\h__\h] struggled so hard and
then they Nerf him but I was so proud
that I killed him before he
got we
can't we'll have to get up there until
down my herur of magics are at your
disposal St [\h__\h] wait a
minute okay I think we're
done
oh another
one
okay I feel bad but oh there was some oh
there's FPS loss here oh oh w w
okay feels a little bit
laggy what I do with all this meat
should I eat
it consume it to recover a small amount
of Health small that looks like it would
recover a good chunk of
Health not even low on HP
really but damn I have so much stuff
wait combine
no combine
no I have nothing to
combine oh
combine an arrow but I don't use
arrows let it age and then sell be aware
that once you get to the city you might
get some major lag oh
the game is crazy on CPU usage but I
thought they like kind of updated it a
little
bit you you cook meat at campfire for or
combine it when it ages oh so it
actually ages within my
inventory also what's the point of
making these arrows when I don't use
arrows is there a
point or maybe I can use them even even
then
expanded when using drenching shot or
delusion oh this is like
uh Sal them the
arrows do I get more money if I sell it
like
this I shall do
it right SP that looks like the dried
mangoes are are my dried mangoes a
healthy snack that I can eat during my
diet I want to eat it would be such a
waste to not eat
it a fair amount of
stamina yeah
yeah I want to try them can I try them
on stream
now I'm going to go get him
and I only found I only found the nuts I
don't know where I put the
magar can I eat some cashews
[Music]
salted and roasted cashew nuts from
Thailand I do need your permission cuz
you guys are going to judge me and you
guys are going to be like you're on a
diet thought you weren't supposed to eat
that yeah
well
heyo they taste so
[Music]
different interesting dried fruit is
high in sugar yeah I can imagine
oh not
bad not bad not quite what I
expected they have an
interesting taste but I don't know what
it is I think it's just the
roasting you don't even need to
diet yeah I mean you
know just trying it
out the average casew is nine calories
apparently give or take M okay I ate
two
no I ate
two yeah I'm not overweight I'm normal
weight very
normal but well I talked about it in my
members only stream
plentyful wo
wo you're filling up my inventory so
much stop stop when would I get an
opportunity to sell stuff again also
where where are we going where am I uh
where are the dudes
out where are
they where are
they I feel
like they would go this way that's
probably your
goal uh
[Music]
mhimi
hello oh another one but this one is
rotten maybe the rotten one I won't
take are they up
here oh come
on come
on
woo they're gone my Army is gone I do
not Aspire any suitable footh holes what
does that
mean suitable
foothold hello oh
anybody anybody here Army maybe they
already went ahead of
time I know it was the wrong way but I'm
looking for the
dudes Morning
Tide Morning
Tide they're right
there oh H I swear he just showed up
hello here an enchant to freeze
our must kill everybody Mex come
on yeah burn going to burn your dead
Goblin Buddies
stinky stinky
Goblins the fights are so short wouldn't
mind them to be uh
longer feels too easy oh y what's
this I think I got him
,500 oo that is the fanciest Strat I
have I'll go and open the chest no no no
he have patience with me master I've
shared all I know
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] where ought we to go now matters
of importance I must talk to you that
you shall not open the chest right in
front of my face when I was about to
open it remember that Rebecca or
else you shall forget your name due to
the amounts of times I will have called
you this is mine
okay hands off
ring of indifference that's what I'll
give you Rebecca if you keep on opening
those treasure
chests before I get to it Y chest is in
a place not easily accessed I know Y
chest I was wondering about that one
[Music]
yeah yeat her but then she opens it the
Sun 's High how do
I how do I eat
it's up
there the own chest is guarded by a
mighty
bra oh wait I can probably uh no that's
not the one have I incurred your wrath
and some
respect yes indeed you
have oh
[\h__\h] sorry I thought I could get you up
there
uh oh well
there ought to be another chest for me
to
enjoy vulgar is Lord another
[Music]
book what's up there maybe I think I I
can't make much out from here but I have
a feeling to be worth the
climb well you can't climb that can you
I don't
know yeah I know I found a ring but I'm
indifferent about
it grants power to the wearer whose
spirit resonates with its magic reduces
damage taken from Strike
attacks all
right it is on my finger
m
MH I don't know it's kind of hard to
tell how to get
there we shall proceed me ours is a
party of women by and large there's
another one and yet no two of us are the
same there's really a lot of chests are
all over the place 550 gold man it's
really worth picking up stuff from the
dead
dudes they often have a lot of money
with
them she I've just record I found a
treasure chest near here during my
travels beyond the rift you mean may
show you to its location yeah if you
know how how do I tell her to go
again follow me okay I know the way so
there's no chance of our getting
lost
okay sounds like you're reading from a
script
uh you're kind of going in a weird now
you stopped moving so what does it mean
what does it mean
Nissa did you forget where the chest was
H gets lost
immediately do you mean this one perhaps
I don't know how to get
there it's from
here still a bit daed from the bro well
yeah understandably
so I think I
can guys have you gone to that chest or
or what the people who played the near
goblins dead body
oh which one there's many
plentiful dead bodies wait where am
I where am I
where am I where am I where am
I oh hi
dudes where am
I I got
lost I really want that freaking chest
now maybe
it is rather High it might be beyond our
reach don't be so
negative
almost but maybe can I do a double jump
like no no it's like a set height
there sheld on you have to aim while
from I
aimed let's try
again how do you aim wait can you
actually aim like differently just or is
it just a camera wherever you look hold
the frot
ah uh
wait ah
uh she didn't want to be held by me
anymore look up
[Music]
Nissa come
on what if it's like I don't know if
it's too far
but it's like from here
is like from here
here that looks good but I don't know
it's unrealistic to throw that
far s
[Music]
I can't look up higher I can look
down but not
higher if I was taller
really [\h__\h] man
[\h__\h] will she hate me her HP is fine
though new skill later on really oh have
they been this rotten before is this
like with time the dead bodies actually
more and
more become more
wasted that would be amazing oh my God
thanks for the 100
gold size does matter small pwns are
easier to throw shees okay dude go
understood I shall proceed
ahead I follow you
dude I'm done with trying for the chest
I'm sorry I'm sorry for wasting your
time is this the right
way wait I'm
distracted was I not here
before isn't this isn't this where the
the dog was where yeah yeah yeah yeah
the distance is too great but why is the
the exclamation mark still there what
does it mean I can see a path just
Yonder but how to reach it indeed e it
seems so close and it's I think maybe
they want me to take
this
no there's a ladder I can't reach
there's a
cave a ladder at the top
oh okay sometimes I'm like a little bit
l
like what do you want
game why why why would I take the rotten
mid ew
oh maybe I could combine it with
something
but doesn't seem like it right
now don't pick that up it's
stinky okay sorry sorry sorry please
proceed
he must be so annoyed with me by now
what do you
think oh didn't we go in a circle what
might that be no we ought to take a
closer look yeah we ought to take a
closer look but isn't this where I was
before yeah yeah yeah the chest is even
marked
there sir we went in a
circle well can't right Circle without
sir
I'll that you need trouble yourself
right oh grapes somebody
grapes got to grab some grapes gra grab
grape some what what grape some
grapes oh there's a fire
here shall we
heal just a tiny bit just for fun
oh cook uh don't know how should I have
cooked well I'll do it again the Vim
tole the day
ahead
okay oh
yes oh this one's already aged h
I'll go with
it that's
IRL what the [\h__\h] no budget for
animating it or what well we've eaten
our fill won't say we settle our
stomachs with a few hours sleep agreed
we ought to give ourselves a chance to
recover if we continue on our journey oh
4K
meat
[Music]
yum [\h__\h] you I'm on a
diet oh yo yesterday I have to
admit so the food that I cooked the day
before yesterday from Hello beep
the sauce it was very very little sauce
and it kind of just
like was soaked up by the noodles by the
next day and it just didn't look
appetizing anymore so I made something
we're trapped no we're not
tra I made something else because before
I decided to go on a diet I bought
something that I saw in the supermarket
where I was like hey
yo that's one of my favorite comfort
food you know I had I hate spinach but a
cyclops to think we' encounter one here
of old we have something that's
called
uh not
how and that's called SP gu it has
spinach inside but you don't really T it
what the [\h__\h] is happening now to bring
it down and let it taste our Fury could
you lend me a hand my magic can view
your weapon with the fury of the element
thank you thank you thank you and you
eat those cheese it's like little little
I don't know what do you
call oh I jumped up so it didn't hit me
I think
[Music]
oh our
loed but I made that and it's probably
not really a uh you know cheese sauce is
probably not healthy and all that but uh
yeah I made SP noar spinach dump baby
baby dumplings with um with uh cheese
sauce because I had them in my fridge
and I had all the ingredients and the
other thing was not looking appetizing
anymore but I added the asparagus
so the remaining asparagus was very
yummy and it was just overall really
yummy and I just like freestyled it and
it turned out so yummy so I'm like quite
proud of myself let's just say it was my
cheat
day also yeah I didn't even eat that
much because it filled me up pretty fast
so didn't even eat like a full serving I
think and grabbing larg of foes in
battle you can grab a hold of a foe
while standing by making contact with
them while pressing e or probably e
would be on the keyboard once you have
hold uh of an enemy you can push or pull
them to draw their focus or knock them
off bounds okay the strike fast and true
and
our I'm trying I'm trying but I think
it's too
[Music]
late just done it just done gratitude
sir it would seem I misjudged you pretty
much anytime oh
really it I had taken you for another
fce Arison goodness knows we see a lot
of them yet the value you showed in
coming to our Aid has dispelled such
thoughts it was fun here I'm going fight
more Cyclops more a mark of my trust
stronger ones give it to one of the
Sentinels stationed at the gates to the
capital and you'll be granted an
audience with Captain brand your free to
make your own way to the capital now I
see no need to keep you under constant
watch but how will find way a little
easier as well I uh
no of course if you'd rather continue to
accompany us you are still welcome to
join us on the ox card oh it is your
decision well now I want to wait what
happened the road's blocked the car the
powerful current ought to set this rock
to crumbling summon one I shall summon
one one yeah I don't know how but I'll
I'll make it
happen but first let me see for
Gathering items and I'm ever on the hunt
for news I have my own ponds try out any
useful mechanisms I
aspy Arison details Capcom level one
username P
what uh he's free and he's level
eight oh wait you your name's Barbara
wait what I'm confused my part is full
we shall dismiss somebody because you're
level
five he's free with
f do I have to give a I don't see an
option that I could I hope I can count
on you in a scrape
I thought I was counting on you why is a
treasure in the truest sense how
exciting my heart is fit to
bust it's a patching
bag let's go how
fun
yeah should take some of that meat with
us what a waste
how is the stone going to help
me oh this works again like
before really
okay wait is it
done it's done well that was easy oh he
was like he was shoved out of the way
too
nice all
right
proceed oh is that the useful
ingredients to be gathered here all way
an o c now do you intend to join us very
well board the op oh but what what about
me looking around you're staring Arisen
thought Yonder caught your
[Music]
eye I'm
sorry I'm sorry the oh it's fast travel
[Music]
oh so it's like the opposite of what I
want to do but I already said I will go
it looks kind of nice
it was well worth the effort breaking it
I can activate this yeah then I can come
back if I
want where stuff you give to the
apparently it goes to my storage
somewhere so I can maybe get it when I'm
in the
city I was thinking so too like where
the [\h__\h] does it
go narissa exploring the big Ogar
on her
own all right I guess we can
go wo um I'm
readyy oh they don't get to sit in here
you can't sit with us Rebecca or Barbara
none of you can sit with us I can't wait
to find out what's
inside it's a Tok
Tok where am I standing
I thought this was fast travel it's not
very fast at
all Barbara you catching up
Barbara
barara oh I can dose off
a goblin what rotten luck we've need of
your Aid again sir
okay I guess I'll get up
guess I'll get up all right took me a
moment I'm
hereen fight on Victory I feel so strong
can you imagine us doing all of this
without all the upgrades allow me went
right there couldn't be me wouldn't do
such a rookie mistake seems we drove
them off burnworth isn't far from here
will you join us the rest of the
way no I hope to see you in the capital
andon they gave me another chance to
jump
off
not which is the way is this the
way I think it's the other way is
it
hey oh
no I think I'm on the right
way thanks for the membership
gifts oh why do I think I can break it
open like that
cinnamon beautiful scen
Mar wow oh is that the capital over
there oh let's
[Music]
go dare I say it we trous our a phone
well and true we mustn't allow ourselves
to become complacent take each trial as
it comes m m yeah yeah yeah for sure for
real I agree that's so
true Victory hop hoity you are now my
property
oo let my magic Grant you an elemental
room oh thank you I was actually just
activating my fire magic and they're
always dead so fast it's not even worth
using my
skills oh he's
burning roasted
Goble almost missed you little Beetle
John is
Y A fitting reward for a rigorous SE
[Music]
that song so
exhausting so exhausting you guys should
try it oh the goblin the not Goblin the
ogre or something look there's a chest
down there should to go all the way down
for the [\h__\h] chest
there can
I it might hurt hurt a little from
here
H well maybe the path leads me there
does it go in a
curve
oh save first nice okay I'm not going
like that I am not
so crazy Treasure Chest mhm we shall
have to find a way to reach it you mean
well there's so many which one do you
mean which one do you
mean oh the
oh
well I think there's yeah there's one
right
there stop teasing me with all these
unreachable chests please
ow ow come on
open
Jasper what that's
uh yeah yeah bone a jewel prized for its
use as a protective charm can I do
something with this do it to
Barbara it's getting heavy
again oh wait let's combine it to
something removing excess oils on the
[Music]
skin I can make one
used for upgrading certain items despite
not counting as a crafting material
uhuh once you know you there's a bit of
post game challenge before the NG plus
with
special whoa whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
whoa
okay uh was I actually going
backwards no if I go around
here then I think we're good
then I think we're going to reach the
chest too maybe or many other chests oh
there's some
harpies okay I want to
use I want to use my my
skill oh oh that's it that's
it that's it
that was exactly how it should look like
a perfect
example wo get
me that was me
embodying
beyblades in the most beautiful way
Beyblades are in my brain now
thanks to V
Senai you guys like V Senpai hold talk I
was nervous again because it's been a
while
again but I think mostly it went fine
some some mute accidents
but at least the opening wasn't like
[\h__\h] up for
once yeah what I sire out of all of the
holot talks I've done so far I feel like
she
was the most easiest for me to
interview or like to think about what to
ask
her we should be able to move this
Boulder with our combined might there
just like we give it a push and see
happens I every ooh I think every whole
life member in their time over the years
does like interesting
things that one could talk about but
then people like rat Senai they have
like very obvious could do this all day
things very like the the projects are
like just so easy
to bring up because they're like you
know I don't have to dig so deep to find
something yeah it's just very out in the
open and easy to find like interesting
stuff about
her
so that was ooh that was very
comfortable very quick wake Stone Shard
is that also something
craftable gather free to form a wake
Stone which can restore dead to life oh
also myself
[Music]
or stoutness
extract oh little birds nest oh lots of
Bones next to it what is that a harpy
nest
H NPCs and yourself it's for when NPCs
die uhhuh okay okay okay
are
careful yeah now I have one more member
in the fourth
generationa Senai I'm going to try to do
uh her whole talk episode within the
month as
well don't want too much time to pass
[Music]
[Applause]
now I'll try my best also I have some
other I happened upon a treasure chest
rather close by here perhaps I could
show you the way you show me the way
yeah do it
who said that you here really I know
just where to go ah wait I think that
marked the exclamation
mark yeah there's a game that I played a
long time ago lost oh thank
you that now released a
sequel that is
multiplayer and I already saw some
Japanese senis play it
the [\h__\h] is
that and so I asked uh very certain
girls to accompany me playing
it and here are Wars hoping for some
great treasure now I going here why am I
going here we can't expect gleaning
Treasures around every
corner what game
well you must find out yourself
perhaps
W is this really the right path to get
down
here certainly not the path that the
story wants me to
go keep your secrets yeah probably not
next week but the week after next week
heo I know precisely what a Curative is
needed Master you'll never fall in
battle so long as I'm around
hello level 12 you're free you're level
12 uh wait the the blue sign is he a
Healer I already have a
mage he's a mage
right but he's so high level 12 level
threee so I guess these ones that show
up there individually those are always
free no matter what level they are
maybe they're quite the
catch man
[\h__\h] he
a shiren Shir what how do you say that
in
English in German we say sh sh Shir I
think uh replace Archer really
may
I you think it's not weird to have the
same one I mean she's only level five
man that's rep Place why is she running
like that why is she running like
that at least I go knowing I fought to
the best of my ability you ran to the
best of your ability that's for sure
deled to meet you especially if we share
a sweet tooth oh I do what the
[\h__\h] well welcome I thought this was a I
thought I could activate this to
teleport here but no this is a pretty
cool
outcome um pawns are rendered in Mobile
when their health Falls to zero uh okay
I do you see
guys did someone
die what what why do you see here
there's on the map something a skull and
a red
circle Ponda don't tell me a pond
died wait uh if you and are unable to
stir from where they have fallen without
Aid if you leave your Pawn in an IM
immobile state for
okay can attempt to revive by
approaching them touching them okay I'll
try it probably over
there oh oh that's what that is I
thought it was a boss fight or so where
are
you what down there
oh God
wait wait go go
on okay I'm okay I'm okay uh
revive those
idiots more thanks oh revive be without
you
Arisen I have no idea what's this what
did you find
here found something special thanks to
their
deaths their deaths had a a cause there
are 240 of these tokens scattered across
the land hidden in all sorts of out of
the way and unexpected
[Music]
places bring them to a guil hall and you
will revive receive special rewards now
and then as your collection progresses
you must leave no stun unturned nor
corner of the world unexplored if you
would complete this is like for 100% in
the game huh I thought we'd never find
one a splendid discovery
okay so oh no I have to remember to tell
my own Master about
thisor what is this
axxel I grch fire use it well my curates
of magics are at your disposal that's it
wait a moment looked
stronger maed an
art I should remember this place
oh so what are you doing
here I swear the moment I pressed the
attack button I was like wait I remember
what this
was open map Mount Alice
tunnel no wait here
what do I remember this place
for what
purpose oh oh they're fighting with each
other are
you comes up later much later huh
well we might not get there what is this
oh it's a tree I was like what is this
what is this weird thing in the
ground
oh uh uh uh what have we awakened oh no
oh oh it's a whole
n one getting knocked
about wait are my other people even
there right
now where's everybody there you are oh
they're strong and
fun Magics are at your
disposal oh they're frozen though let's
go okay okay okay okay
I Shan let
them ensure your next attack is no less
purposeful almost
done oh
[Music]
ni
yeah might have been one of the most
difficult fights so far
I had a high five you like to see it you
love to see it oh what luck is a chest
eggs let us hope your curiosity will be
rewarded T an egg oh I cut up his tail
for
real not the reward I I would have like
some
money would have preferred some money
where am I what am I doing here oh
we shall use
this oh why do I always
jump
H wait did one of my pawns take the
camping kit with them shall we prop up
our tent and get out of the rain for
come that sucks what
[Music]
gold
oh oh question mark question mark
question
mark Exquisite Robo rent is what I
made out of that
thing I am carrying so many things
help I want to um
[Music]
give how can they use it oh wait that's
stamina no great deal of health and
stamina oh [\h__\h] oh
always give n
yeah I have learned my lesson from now
on I know better
[Music]
but I think the story wants me to go
over here right over this
bridge or is this path okay
they combine again
here not very dangerous recommend to go
to
City
really no keep
going head
south
okay South the sun descends night will
be upon us soon we shall have to rely on
our other senses as the darkness robs us
of our sight no we only still had the
camping kit man
there is still so much stuff to collect
but I want to sell
stuff also that yeah I was going to say
that looks
sus oh
nice wobble wobble wobbly water is
trying to kill
me what is
it can I pick up something
no you truly are formidable
Arison creatures will serve as well go
right ahead the [\h__\h] high five of
that
phrase
heyo most impressive Master a few more
pict like that we have a running for
a resounding
success sh ow ow ow ow I fell
back help help it's so
slipp mostly done help me once
more help
me can I go this way or will no help me
there [\h__\h] can I
teleport can I
teleport oh hel SP okay a worthy prize
but he's going to die too
only no no Ernest Ernest no Ernest come
no Earnest My Level 12
dude grab him but I'm I'm also oh [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
man earnest earnest earnest no earnest
earnest PR save your strength for our
enemies no
H oh wait what the [\h__\h] we still here
that's not going to help
no was it because I was
slippery now I can suddenly get up here
Ernest come back to me no that sucks no
I need a new pwn
[Music]
oh that was
funny
man the wobbly
water we should
hurry I don't know if I'm going anywhere
should I proceed going this way or is it
like
here
maybe I should
no
destination
ah I guess it's that
there on the other map I can't see it
but here I see
it yikes
oh there another fire BL I don't have a
fire
thingy no keep on going
guys oh my God turn on Lantern
oh
okay hello can you help can you be my
pawn attack now while the
I'm not very confident right now
anymore I'll put an end to this
master do not dispair I'm coming to your
a she one to be alarming with
those
uh time is an Ever flowing river in this
world anti activities and behaviors of
its inhabitants reflect this people are
unlikely to remember remain in the same
place all day long and may only appear
in the morning at night or at midday to
pass the time you can either stay at an
inn or make use of one of the special
seats found outdoors and set
locations come Nightfall you will be
able to see no further than the ground
at your feet and the onset of Darkness
summons fearsome monsters not seen by
day explore the Wilderness after sunset
at your own Peril and be sure you have
your Lantern in your pack this sounds
like a travel guide like a vacation like
at the beach at the beach
resort enjoy a nice massage or a
candlelight dinner by the beach with
your loved one with a a nice meal
created uh by your uh uh one and only
most beloved Chef
Tak some items that can be gathered will
change over time such as by ripening and
growing more
flavorful there are also items that if
allowed to age just long enough there
are also items that if what just long
enough will become more useful when
combining materials however you should
keep a close eye on Raw items in
particular as consuming anything that
has been aged past its prime is likely
to have unpleasant side effects now
please buckle your seat bels and store
your tray and your armrest to its
original position ition please open up
the window blinds and put any of your
big
Electronics uh back to where they
belong certain objects and structures
that can be destroyed by your attacks
will regenerate after a set amount of
time has passed oh oh the tendency we
must
exploit so would be the D oh my [\h__\h]
God how do I heal
barara cuz I feel like I can only heal
myself
okay does that heal
her does she use it herself if she has
it
ah good to
[Music]
know all right all right all right
anything else you might
need okay let's not [\h__\h] die
now uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh my
stamina no they're
dying it's all ogre now it really
[\h__\h] is you might want to run
uh
uh-oh ogres are no
joke even if I run now oh my
God wish me to return at once mon come
on feel like we almost had though no
actually we didn't Iain is yours to am I
going the right
way there's something here what is this
what is
that anyway we we we we we must proceed
there's another dude finding something
I'm so [\h__\h] I lost the pawn I can't
pass time because another Pawn uh took
my stuff with
him Master we field Tak
fives run out we're done for I know not
what to
say this one's strong too a forward he
they're all strong aren't they targets
marked by my own mon I trouble you to
assist oh no we're good we're good
they're
all or ogre is
gone okay
are we are we good no where where is
it or fell from the the brief is lo
okay oh I got a rank up cool uh cool
very cool very
cool very
cool um can I hire you I'll carefully
conserve my strength an Endeavor to
survive every battle by way of sound
strategy and defensive tactics BL blah
blah blah she cost something but better
than nobody right it will be an honor to
serve by your
side I'll collect that you needn't
trouble yourself thanks
man the good thing is I don't have an
Archer right now
so she was a good
class when TD be sure to avoid Open
Flame okay oh uh nice
I see the capital up
there I would like to
what why is Barbara not healing
[Music]
herself wait wait wait
wa wait wait wait wait she just carrying
it
away
dude why does why does Barbie not heal
herself does does she uh not have
anymore oh she's already
out
what girl what the [\h__\h] are you
doing city is too far it really is I
don't know I need to find another
camping kit and I don't know I don't
want to rush through because I feel like
the enemies will just get stronger and
strong or
no maybe I should have stayed on the ox
cart
[Music]
maybe I should have stayed on
oart [\h__\h] can they come back to
me they scar with me oh okay okay okay
that's
good
man man oh God what does this sound I
just hope it becomes daytime again soon
so at least I can see
better there's a fire there maybe
sometimes by the fire there's
the a thing
right
oh any l words
now there's a
idea seen my own such a feat something
that I appreciate that's a really cool
in games when they scale with you is
there camping kit no no
really I don't see one there's a dude
over there though
maybe he will give me a camping
kit I can camp without the kit it
says I don't think I
can it says I
can't M Mama we're
okay it'll be fine must you run so fast
I can hardly keep you in my sights are
yeah you're a little bit to keep up
though we are less Fleet of
foot stall berries oh Beetle I didn't
even see what I was
collecting let's
go more please are they at set locations
is there like Guides of where to find
them Barbara get
good Barbara start time to start the
died with me oh hey oxie do you know
where the cart
is oh don't no are they going to attack
me please
no sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry for waking
you I could look upon this sky for all I
learned of a forgotten Rift Stone in
this area during my time beyond the rift
oh I can take you to it if you like uh
allow me to Le the way I can take you to
our destination by the optimum route
all
righty oh it's a nice little herd um
please do not attack
[Music]
please I would stick to the name of
night are you saying that because you
play the game or because you are
Splendid does that even heal me that
[Music]
Circle dare I say it we trounced our foe
well and true well I'm sure there's
still room for
improvement did we just fist
bump that's a
amazing that's
amazing oxen are sturdy creatures aren't
they such beasts are a fair source of
meat when rations are
lacking doesn't he my Max hell
huh that's so the HP that I'm at right
now that's the maximum now the gray part
I can't
recover yo good job but like this is
generally used as a material find a camp
of a camping kid different combinations
of materials result in different
Creations What's happen I thought you
might like this so I picked it up here
you go the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] are
you what's
happening what
what
huh what is
this why would you leave me here you're
trying to kill me oh thank you us quick
what what am I
fighting oh come here don't fall down
don't fall down don't fall down don't
fall
down then I shall remain by your side oh
no oh
oh good we love archers we love me some
archers I'm level 10 now what the [\h__\h]
man oh this is so
chaotic wait what the [\h__\h] what did I
what did I get out of
this is there any
loot I don't see any loot it died here
though archers no no Nerf please wait
the dude the
dude dude or whatever lady
hello what did you a well organized pack
is my specialty I'll see to sh between
USS level 12 Thief
mhi I could hire her for
free
uh get rid of Barbara cuz like Barbara
[Music]
maybe I don't
know cuz we weren't resting maybe her
health is already like so
[Music]
low yeah that's what I was
thinking hope she's not still
carrying can I
see I'm just going to send her
away sorry
barbs m
I'm only glad to have proven my
worth are you fit to travel then let's
not Dole thanks for joining me what the
delightful uh meeting we have had with
no Panic
whatsoever what is this
dude what what what you want me what
what you want me to help you pee or I
would Fain Aid you if you are in need oh
oh you are you just what is he
doing what's this mean is he just
another
Pawn that I can
hire I'm so confused guys this game is
confusing
me it's very chaotic too what is this
loot
loot is good ha one can never have too
many materials I'll Harvest some
now can't break it
okay that's all there
is no I did not want to perceive you but
the Beet shall be
perceived did you guys cat my magic IMB
your weapon with the fury of the element
shush did you catch my shush did you
catch my uh really funny pun uh in h
talk in the beginning at the
announcement like the the opening where
I said a uh uh a sheep with many
achievements did you catch that I was
really proud of that one
yeah I'm on the right way
right you missed it you heard
it got to listen
closely my WR are kind of dying we
cannot break it from this
side
what break
what just let me rest for [\h__\h] sake
please maybe wait maybe there's
something in there oh wait what the [\h__\h]
why is this
glowing why was it
glowing tell is verman was once the bean
Kingdom she healed herself right there
indeed though it is not widely known
among the common Folk
some doors that can be interative but
cannot be opened by keys or me
mechanisms this can really be a matter
of timing and you may find that such
doors will be open oh at a particular
time of day somebody sleeping in
there
open there's stuff I want to
get maybe there's another
door no
your girl
missing no no I have free people with
me under the bridge to loot there under
the bridge to
loot no hold
on under this
bridge thr your
pond but there's water dangerous water
sick ah run I knew you would Prevail
Master stay with me wait right there
Casper
disgusting [\h__\h] the
rats oh they're leading me maybe it was
the bat
actually is it
so I hear
something is this
dangerous what the
[\h__\h] what's happening what's happening
what's
happening they killed the rats
or make some quick
coin under attack
I'm going
I'm I'm I'm D I'm
D come with
me too dangerous I
think too dangerous everybody here oh
thank
God uh I'll be
back I'm too scared
who are they are you trying to piss me
off what what what what what what what
what are you trying to piss me off what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] my
[Music]
stamina where was the St stamina stamina
St this one
you're asking for it no no not in
particular I'm asking for a place to
rest and a place to sleep and just be
treated nicely because I'm the
hero did they leave oh thank
God
oh oh my weapons
oh wait would that guy inside the bridge
also not have challenged me if I didn't
have out my weapons
why has it been night for so long oh
hello Dad approaching the gates of veror
capital of verand none may pass without
the proper
documents yeah he was abanded right
M
okay he would still attacked I think so
too papers please if you've an entry
permit an invitation or proof of
citizenship present it
now do I see so you are to meet with
Captain
brand a shance imped you then come with
me thank
God I was informed of your coming would
be
Arisen would be
Arisen I am the aan you should know that
this individual fought valiantly to
defend the troops the watch head told me
himself is that the ox as decreed by the
great will of our world there can only
be one Arison that Arison now resides
within the palace what the [\h__\h] indeed
is our Sovereign and the rightful ruler
of wait is it from the cut scene in the
beginning where somebody walked up to a
throne and everybody was like ah hello
hello welcome welcome is that the one
that they think ah it follows therefore
that this Ruffian before us that one's
probably not Austrian that one proba
Australian you must submit to
questioning if you value your life you
will not attempt to
flee I shall conduct everybody makes
these mistakes it's so annoying stand
watch
outside everybody makes this us
up man what are you bow bowing
for I didn't hear a bow bow I beg your
forgiveness for my insolence your
majesty H you he called me Your Majesty
oh Queen AG had learned of your
existence I fear your life would have
been in peral called me ring you guys
have brain rot I had no choice but to
treat you as a pretender lest my actions
draw suspicion from watchful
eyes enough of this farce I don't
understand then you have truly lost your
memory in that case mayap I ought to
explain the situation before we
proceed you and no other are The
Sovereign the only legitimate ruler of
this
Kingdom some days passed you confronted
the dragon in the village of Mel
whereupon you became aisen m i did yeah
I I did the people
Rejoice for our true leads are finally
appeared ending veron's long years of
council
rule yet not all celebrated your
coming [\h__\h] haters
everywhere why few months prior
your rival would have robbed the queen
regent dieser of everything
oh during the time of the previous
Council she acted as a queen in her own
right ruling the palace as she saw
fit and just after the cil's passing
when was or certain that her son would
take his father's
place word reached the castle that the
Arisen had been found
to diesa your Majesty's very existence
is not but an obstacle to her own
family's continued
Prosperity well well
understandable medieval Politics the
assassination of the Arisen is an
impossible feed for Mortal
hands so shall I do it myself or what
thus daa chose to abduct your majesty
while you recovered from your wounds in
order to rob you of your memory with a
Fel curse and sell you to batal as a
slave following that oh yeah I was a
slave the beginning replacement to serve
as the already happen I forgot I was a
slave
puppet I I already forgot all about that
however with your majesty returned I
have no intention of twiddling my thumbs
as the I know I'm Dam that's what I'm
saying like oh so if you should I do you
the favor or should I help you out
somehow like if
no mortals can do it uh don't know I'm
making waffles oh my God K me I shall
devise some plans to further good night
pray I'm going to end it soon though me
a night in the tavern that we might
discuss I don't know when to end
it today's Sunday
right I I have no this one's cleared of
all suspicions clear plans for next week
yet to trouble the good sir no further
are we
clear good sir you called be the good
sir 6,000 gold and I've arrived in wor
wolf level 10 for
Nissa oh are we healed no not yet what
is
this hey this two is out and you have
perms I can recommend I was thinking
about that cuz I what are you doing I
thought I was not to be
Disturbed um uh I was wondering
like oh yeah it has been eventful I was
wondering if I didn't play Hades Hadis
Hades Hadis
one can I play Hadis 2 I must remain on
my guard it's early access yeah I don't
have access how do I get
access more stard you I don't know about
stard you
oh oh I just bought a game oh everybody
can have
access
oh uh by being
early playing as would be a delight I
don't really like is that a long game
it's probably shorter game right no
suspicious characters you SLI my face I
don't know I have to think about it I
think there was one game that someone
mentioned to me I already forgot what it
was but uh I thought oh yeah that's a
good idea I'll play that next week what
was that maybe we'll start Fallout next
week
already ah little kitty yeah maybe
that's what I'm thinking of cuz I think
I'll play that for like one
stream I already saw Dum tendo play
quite a bit of
it it's like no cute game but like
nothing too
special but we'll play it for like a
oneoff stream that game is super short
the kitty
one Cat Quest seems like it' be a cute
game Cat Quest did you watch the series
fall out I'm watching right now I
started last night I really like
it which fall were you thinking um I
thought new new figas I
think but
I don't
know I need to finish the show me too
but I'm going to take my time also
because you guys said they're not
connected
so yeah I'll take my
time it's so good though New Vegas is
pakc a lot of people like that one so I
think I'll play
that anyway regarding the O both verman
and batal regard The Scorch of the
dragon as a matter of most priority
should the baleful creature Al light on
either side of the border both nations
are sworn to provide Aid as well as to
assist in the evacuation of a populace
and with scouting missions as needed in
such an event all troops are expected to
put aside any disagreements of faithful
culture and devote themselves whole
heartly to the duty
I only
my yeah I think I'll think about all of
that tomorrow this week really was kind
of crazy for me I cannot afford a
moment's in caution this week and last
week
together um that was just
uh rushing through every
[Music]
day and uh crazy crazy
stuff the script extender what what what
what
what Amit was allowed to play with that
and it's really useful if you get
stuck many of those you guys might have
to remind me of that
whoops did you
just think about attack
me dude chill I accidentally draw my
weapon but I thought you are my
friend follow generally really buggy oh
really yeah I don't know and tomorrow
I'll make my schedule and think about
everything and I might also have to do
some stuff so probably not going to
stream
tomorrow is it daytime
pray forgive me I'm in a bit of a
hurry okay Conan it get back
here
what I can't move do that did you see an
urchin in a cap run past just now can
you tell me which way he went I honestly
don't know wait he's behind me is that
him no right many thanks I'll catch that
wretch yet
I a kind one aren't you it would seem I
am in your
debt in fact there's ought I would ask
of you if you've the time to
spare
uh what
you you're in my Deb but you want to ask
something of me aha there you are oh
come on apologies but our chat will have
to wait
bye-bye
aha it is good to be reunited I see seem
to be
safe in a city wonderful oh my my
minions are with me too make our journey
easier uh would allow us to save our
strength assuming we are not attacked
that are you guys like mocking me now I
know it would have been easier with an
ox card I know I put ourselves for a lot
of trouble but it was kind of exciting
it was kind of good streaming content
okay so somebody's got to think about
the entertainment value and that is me
you guys may not be thinking about it
you you guys may want to your lazy asses
on the ox cart but I have my whole job
on the line okay okay I can't just be
sitting my ass down on the ox card and
waiting for time to pass no no no it's
not that easy
okay anyway where are we
going may I heal somewhere perhaps in a
in a nice little
in anybody know a nice comfortable
little Inn that may let me sleep in
their fluffy little beds for a night or
two I'm looking at the map I don't I
think I see one now
[Music]
yeah oh what the [\h__\h] oh it's a little
market but no
people wait what's this is this the end
did I find ITA Shakira's
in can't you see well met you are come
to shakir's Inn a place of rest bite for
the weary traveler Shak Shaka you will
soon forget the fatigue of a long
journey when treated to the foremost
Hospitality 2000 but it's okay for once
we must rest though the son damn it's a
lot of [\h__\h] money
though this time I have enough money but
[Music]
still my Pawn has returned from Beyond
the
rift child together for a day and a
night oh I completed
it I got a raspberry really great thank
you Pawn traveled with Joel huh
you
sure what
uh what is this menu I don't like it go
away I witnessed a stunning display of
archery in my travels me thinks our a
band would benefit from such skills we
have an
Archer Archer everyone come we've much
to getting on with feeling rested I
trust um I'm all
right driver's
daybook which gets you your own house no
more need
really he
[Music]
yo the other day I arrived at the border
checkpoint only to realize I left my
entry permit back at the end ended up
having to make the trip back so I was
late for my delivery when I could play
to a fellow driver about it he said next
time I ought to use a beast mask seems
batal favors is Bean residents so they
can get through with the hassle without
the hassle of a permit might be worth
keeping a disguise at hand just in
case'll be the eh okay I'll let you guys
uh let me
see Main Pawn online access selector is
able to view and hire your main P
[Music]
everybody no
okay now give
code you guys so
greedy
[Music]
C she still has no Ida don't tell me I
have to sleep
again to get diry
I just spent 2,000 bucks
there save and quit does that work Al so
hey a new a new capping kid let's
go where is it I'm blind oh 7
kg there you go
also I feel like I just have so much
[\h__\h] in my
inventory and then not only my inventory
but there's also still a lot of stuff in
my
storage so I keep on opening the wrong
things let's try to craft stuff
[Music]
okay level 80
Adventure you guys can level M Arisa to
level 80 or oh does she get like
adjusted to your level when you hire her
or what what how what
can you level M
orisa
okay then what's the point we can give
her gifts and
knowledge
well whoa whoa whoa wait wait wait I was
doing it
[Music]
I was doing it
though I found a
chest
okay uh guys tell me what to do with all
the [\h__\h] I have in my
inventory oh dear I need to sell stuff
also wait wait wait wait wait wait in
the
in in the
in there was something I wanted to do
and now I forgot about
it what this
in different entry well you will soon
forget the fatigue of a long journey
when treated to the foremost shut up I'm
going to take all my things now thank
you oh how heavy are these also all
kilog okay is this my
PC handling the game well my PC is
feeling a little bit flattered by your
comment St the crafting Ms here
yeah but I thought I might as well
Hospitality in all ver oh wait oh I can
combine through this ah I was going to
like craft everything
flirting with my PC aren't you beef PC I
mean it's not that beefy recently also
it acts weird every now and then I got
to
say okay
[Music]
okay I don't know was this was this
using stuff from my inventory right and
now I
can are you saying I crafted everything
I possibly could
so I might just put it back into the
storage I don't
know what I do with all this stuff I
don't
know a hide K
PC I told you there's nothing
happening everything else in storage
okay
stle but what if I then need it later on
well okay these Stones I don't need and
these leather thingies I don't know what
I I wouldn't need it now at least just
is for enhancing equipment which I don't
even know how to do
it yeah
these are probably heavy and the arrows
I'm going to go
sell mishen Miss shapen
all oh the token I can put away
too they can stay in storage you don't
need to bring them with you to enhance
ah okay nice nice nice good to know
all right I'm light now what about
you oh wait I kind of wanted to sell
them I think
damn my grapes have rotten
no okay you know where to find me so
have you guys found my narissa yet or
what do you really need the
code try harder to find her
you must find her is's a chest I shall
take a look
inside oh you found something nice
there call it cult I call it dull some
call it cultur I call it
dull
wow what a
this the toe my
boots she must be first
uploaded m
this isn't well I'm not going to sleep
there again now when I just slept there
there's another in here no shame living
life for Pleasures oh I'm on the wrong
side it seems welcome to the we serve
all manner of fine Naes here shall I
pour you a cup to buying around for
2,000 is that the same as like sleeping
in an
inn wait my health why did my health not
properly recover question
[Music]
mark my health doesn't look properly
recovered mayap I ought to ask around
town oh you're just improving the
increasing the cuz I
fell well then I guess I have to spend
another 2,000 to sleep again or can I
use my uh fireplace
thingy what should I
do I don't feel what to do what to do I
did fall free floors
yeah okay no I have I have one Camp uh
with me I think I have no mother or
father to speak off you see I wanted to
get them a present to say thank you and
I thought about the problem is do you
think you could help me all I need for
true I do have some flowers you ever so
much I'm sure you'll find the prettiest
flow actually what what about the ones I
found in the
the ones that I have in my
[Music]
storage those should work
right yeah I want to get the house but
it probably costs a lot of money
now or maybe it's just like a loan kind
of thing like an animal crossing where
I'll have to pay off a loan endlessly
20k that's not going to happen now also
look how look on the mini map the arrows
above me they're like stuck over there
my
people come
on don't be like that say to a bit of
excit oh Port
Crystal oh good
night use of Fairy Stone will instantly
transport you to the location of the
port
Crystal all right I activated
it okay so one thing I want to oops well
me you will soon forget the fatigue of a
long journey when treated to the former
shut up I want those flowers didn't I
put it put them here
yeah uh probably just one right po
Hospitality in all
veror you know where to find
me I don't know I don't know about
resting
again location Gill is downstairs for
more
[Music]
skills but I think what am I to do this
would be a good
uh place to end it though for today I
don't know if I'm continuing though I
like it but like I don't know if I want
to make it a
series cuz we're doing
Fallout where where is the
where I've
lost my sense of
direction I could revisit it lots to do
yeah but it's also
like I don't know how I feel about
having so much time in
between streams for long series like I
will also feel like kind of disconnected
ouch I think but ho Arisen have you
brought me a bunch of flowers already I
did I just happened to have
them these should say would you mind
terribly if I asked you another favor
see one of my friends taught me a magic
all you have to do is find a silver
Stone put it under your pillow a silver
Stone there's the problem I would you
find a silver Stone and bring it to me
Arisen see that's something I don't know
how to help you with well that's all
right thanks for hearing me out
anyhow I'm just being realistic you know
I don't know where I can find such a
silver Stone if I own one I don't think
so sorry about that not trying to get
your hopes up you
know oh rotten [\h__\h]
that
guor can I cook here no oh cuz you
already cooked something
delicious wait a moment you're healing
me now why my HP
fine wait but that heal is so
Random arms arms for the poor That's So
Random those less fortunate could have
done that ages ago
lady okay uh if I just like save in the
menu are we
good so sorry guys you guys don't get
access to narissa after
all uh oops
boo I'm I'm
hungry I'm
hungry I want to make my
sandwich but this game is good
like I normally would like to make it
into a series normally
yeah it's very good I like it
but I'll think about it I'll think about
it a little
bit chicken sandwich yeah I bought like
lowfat turkey
[Music]
stuff one more shot at some
point yeah
H Maybe also just at a time where I run
out of all the games I want to play if I
have nothing in particular on my list
for a long running game then we can put
this one into our
schedule uh although now it would be
more
like recent now so it would make more
sense
now but I I know I I'm not
feeling I love the game right now but
I'm not feeling starting it as a series
right
now it also really just depends on what
you guys want more and I feel
like and usually I want to play the
games that I want to play but since I'm
a little bit undecisive now I'm more
like relying on what you guys seem to
want and you guys seem to want Fallout
more at the moment
so Fallout 76 well I'm playing I'm
playing the other one though if I'm want
to play Fallout 76 with me though I
would also be open to it but I don't
really know anything about those games
right now so it's hard to
[Music]
say Fallout going to be sick I hope so I
I don't know what to expect for that one
[Music]
either with Amit and
gaura oh maybe I don't I I I think I'll
play New Vegas first and then see if I
like it and then
uh I suppose 76 is like kind of similar
Vibe
[Music]
so yeah I want a taste for
it I saw some Japanese members are
suddenly playing 76 isn't that game kind
of old oldish like not new right it has
bugs many
bugs it's a bit different uhhuh
so
MMO well can you make like a private
server or are you with everybody at all
times
[Music]
n you can make private
server all right I might offer it to I'm
like hey if you want to we can play
together if she wants
to can make our own little group if she
wants to private eight person server
costs money
oh and if we don't play is that is it
not recommended to not play
Private for us I mean five bucks
okay well that's not expensive or
anything but like I don't know about
setting it up if it's like a pain in the
[Music]
ass yeah we'll see first of all I just
want to know if Amma even feels like
doing
[Music]
it
oh yeah yeah New Vegas first ah man I
don't know
I don't know what to do because I'm
like I want to
eat
uh what what the Wawa do Wawa kind of
lost Wawa brain
lost I'm like so like uh brain
cannot compete
[Music]
am asked me to play it really ah you
mean during that one time when I went
into her room was that even
serious was that really
[Music]
serious h no I I read some super chats
just a few just okay we we we'll we we
we we'll do a short one when then I go
eat
something uh oh you know what maybe I'll
maybe maybe maybe the RPG office isn't
so
weird do I
fit do I fit in maybe if I adjust my
colors a little
bit oh
[Music]
I think you guys are maybe you took
something weird that you're seeing this
this is not on me you're seeing weird
things RGB RGB you're
tripping looks kind of
sick now what's the normal color guys do
you know anymore I lost
track now this is
normal maybe like
this how about
this do I fit in I think I do maybe I'm
a little bit too clusty but oh well
yay taking a seat in alter
ki's little office let's
go Empress waah although the the big
like ball haul that I have with the
piano is probably the most suitable for
Empress
wa yeah
but and a little bit of music wouldn't
hurt CU I think I'm a little bit low
energy because I recently I haven't been
sleeping so well both the mattress and
the pillows all my pillows are
just so uncomfortable for me right now I
don't know why it's more uncomfortable
than
usual and then not being able to eat so
much is
also giving me less energy
I
think so ti ti
[Applause]
tiop sorry that was
[Music]
loud I figured You' be into it on some
level but wasn't sure hyp for Fallout NB
have you ever thought of playing the
Dragon Age series Dragon
H Dragon Age
I got to Google it and remind myself
what that looks
like ah yeah uhuh
uhhuh I
mean it's not really on my mind but it
looks
cool gives me the same
Vibes as today's
game
so it's not a a noral not a no
[Music]
no oh we have been
waited W welcome I'm just about to start
reading super chats though
sorry we played until we got to the
capital that was fun though I like
it I like Dragon DOA
too oh that reminds me I saw when I I
was browsing through my TV yesterday I
saw
um what did I see a yeah one of the
movie
recommendations was Dungeons and Dragons
not the new movie though the like zero
no number so I was wondering if the
other Dungeons and Dragons movies are
also as funny and as good as the new one
don't watch the old one the the first
one is so bad did they go for the same
Vibe though like a funny comedy kind of
vibe it's famously bad a they're very
bad so only the new one is
good oh no oh
no oh they played it straight so but
it's really bad everybody says it's bad
it's in not a funny
way it's more like so bad it's funny oh
no but she loves cats so she might like
it that will haunt me to the end of my
days
[Music]
apparently okay then I guess I won't
watch it I don't know I just got kind of
curious and I thought I'd better ask you
guys all right let's see which Super
chats could we read
ah start your Valley second
stream I think
[Music]
so this
one
okay thank you guys for watching until
now
super
47 this is when we reached 1 million on
Kima so happy edf5 fencer Jim Dan Jim
Tracy Dan Alvar Dan Alvar again Dan
thank you strawberry yeah I wanted to
ask my friend I want to ask
BFF m I think now should
be the right season I think cuz my mommy
and I we were already able to harvest
strawberries
so max
[Music]
to
the I want to last car it's not even
June you think it's not
[Music]
ready I think so H thank you for the red
super chat New
Zealand let me go let me go let me go to
New
Zeal you you you're just like you're
just here to send a Super Chat to flex
with the place you live
in you're using that currency and shove
it in our face so that we know you live
in
Paradise in an unreachable Paradise man
why you make me jelly like that I want a
girl taking the wa to New Zealand we're
taking the wa to New Zealand New Zealand
New Zealand
iing guard I and guard I and guard
that's why I moved to Germany you're
from New Zealand and you move to
Germany you can fly to them yeah but I
think it's really far and uh expensive
let me see New Zealand
[Music]
fluke yeah it's uh it will take me more
than 24 hours
yeah the flights are just [\h__\h] absolute
[\h__\h] it's like one of the because I have
to change I think there's no direct
flights and then there's no good
connections and [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] so sad
I think Australia also is kind of hard
to reach because of that
but you may be extend it to New
Zealand if I go to ID yeah like if I
ever go to New Zealand it's got to be
kind of like maybe like on some kind of
World
trip where I have like several
destinations and just go from the
closest one to the closest one to the
closest one to the closest
one yeah yeah V to
Welter
yeah as you get closer to New Zealand
New Zealand moves further away from
you who says that they just maybe
they're just you know they're um
defensive protective they don't want
people to come
closer so they they just like move move
move there actually a
ship an island built on a huge ship
[Music]
I might have made that up
okay sounds like it might be something
they actually say around
there a massive Turtle back yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah if you're doing that you could
visit Antarctica H nah no thank
you that was really uh fascinating when
seeing other people there uh wait that's
where that's where pom went
right anartica
right yeah it's interesting when other
people go I think I will
[Music]
refrain I think I might refrain from
that prefer to go to the males thank you
or Thailand again or something like that
[Music]
weren't you going to sleep
Psy okay let me continue reading uh
where was I Jim
[Music]
Tracy yeah here I was here wet one but D
GD d
[Music]
K thanks for the pinky can't stop
listening to Kima it's so [\h__\h] good
even bought it as a highrise download oh
thank you like I do with all your
amazing music for the full Ki pop
experience huge congrats on the 1
million success it's absolutely deserved
you are the greatest myami Oni thank you
so much yay I'm really relieved that
Kima did so well now ever since it
reached 1 million I feel relaxed and
calm
I'm in my zen
mode I
think regarding that yeah but oh [\h__\h] I
really oh w w w w I realized oh God now
I reminded
myself
[Music]
uh I need
to quickly start working on the next
song because I kind of got a deadline
for something
um I just need to get that going let me
just write to
JMA
hey
[Music]
can make a channel
okay yeah I think she's feeling better
she's not sick
[Music]
anymore Austria lost heart at ESC it
already
happened Oh you mean they didn't get
into the like for the preliminary or
so finished second last oh in the actual
event that was yesterday what I I I
actually didn't see anything about it
not even like in social media stories
people posting about it
[Music]
nothing whoa I don't think I I mean I
never really pay much attention to it CU
I don't watch it like actively but
oh I know what it was drama yeah but e
[\h__\h] I don't I I had no idea that it
happened already
1.2 million live live
viewers the stream like some online
stream on YouTube you
mean what what placement did Germany
have 12
wait let let me let
[Music]
me
ranking
results Switzerland
[Music]
one the [\h__\h] baby
lasagna what the
[\h__\h] oh Germany not even in the lower
half almost
Austria 24 out of
25 man Austria they're I always bad they
won
[Music]
once she
that's sad nor only Norway was below us
and of course there's non-qualified
countries such as Netherlands Australia
Czech Poland Denmark mova Belgium San
Marino San
Marino Albania Malta aaban and
Iceland did not qualify
[Music]
Germany got more points than in the four
years before that
together sheesh well then that's a win
for
them we would have won for sure if we
had you well I don't know about that
don't n don't put that much uh like you
know trust in me a lot of people would
have probably thought it was cringe and
all that so
nah no I know about Sun Marino I'm just
surprised is like even
[Music]
there uh oh yeah maybe for for Austria
maybe I would have done better for
Germany I don't know because like being
12th is already pretty good I
think like that's they're like in the in
the middle pretty much that's pretty
[Music]
good but yeah I
mean this is
what it
is freaking Switzerland
winning when they don't even use the
euro but they have fancy money so that's
all they need damn it their fancy
[\h__\h] money that is upside not upside
down it's
like portrait
[Music]
mode yeah vertical
hello from Germany hello
Goot so yeah h rockar s oh here we go
again face for the pinky K let's say
that you are sent to a world where
instead of hugging them Ena likes to
greet her friends by pressing her
forehead against stairs are you okay
with creating Ena like this
nah like that sounds like it's kind of
[Music]
hurts it kind of hurts it doesn't feel
comfy
[Music]
like a well you would think maybe flat
two flat
surfaces uh against each other wouldn't
feel bad but then the reason you know
why Ena hug feels good still is cuz
there's usually more than just a flat
surface involved my Surface Ain't So
flat but the
foreheads the foreheads though that
hurts that's just flat
[Laughter]
low key
[Music]
roasting so I prefer not to thank you
Rocka dear
sja sad chunky bir D oh don't be sad
Studio roing SLI pinky can you it you
are bigger than big and smarter and
Smart M I'm big
the smart I
like I don't necessarily want to be that
much bigger though I think
um relatively happy with my size well
thank
you made yuk mik than space waterful
than Nathan cotton thanks pinky hi
attention just a curious question ented
my bird brain if you got any more
animals for your farm would you name any
of them after us viewers Oh you mean
within the game
yes I want to I just don't know how to
name them um but I feel like maybe I'll
play stard you Valley a little bit in
members
only and then we can do
[Music]
that you think it's a
metaphor oh you think like if I get
any pets no I think they mean in the
game I think
soar Phoenix
CS pinky our BP call is so sophisticated
that different languages can't agree on
what we're saying oh really we're the
superior linguist here well do we know
at all what any birds are saying ever
besides
[Music]
parrots but I thought that was quite
funny how I roasted you about your
guys's birth calls not being as elegant
as others I feel like that was one of
the best roasts I've ever given you
quite proud of that
one iguana five chickens in a trench Co
thanks the pinky it's okay thano we will
always be willing to dance with you ah
what a great comeback from the five
chickens in the trench
coat they are there when I need
them D the singer Dan Sapp Pro for dang
mu a dang smelly Mayo
dang speaking of
[Music]
mayo yesterday I watched a little bit of
Raina
stream
um and the game she was playing it just
looked like a
non-pixel uh stardo Valley she even made
Mayo out of the eggs that she collected
from her chickens
and a Mayo
machine what I was like isn't this just
stardo
Valley I guess they don't have like a
dungeon fighting uh side aspect to
it ah stud Valley is inspired from
Harvest Moon and story of seasons is
just formerly Harvest
[Music]
Moon A oh so okay but does uh start does
story of seasons have The Fighting
[Music]
aspect
no are some of them do s of season has
no fighting oh okay
[Music]
okay there's a a bunch of these like
little bit similar games I guess all
these farming games are
similar it looks cute though but I mean
I'm already playing stard Valley so I
don't need to pick up this one
too outrun the win Alejandro
aleandro Al Alejandro Al Alejandro thank
you for the
super Tracy H thanks for
I went to K collabo Cafe this week last
week this time I really went oo the
collabo menu was CF fries and potatoes
it was heartbreaking for a the friend
but it was quite delicious I was sad
that K didn't appear in any of the
random Goods oh man can you not like
exchange with someone I'm sure there's
someone there other fans if you go again
they would probably exchange with
you I'm sure they would
if they get the waa try again honululu
go again and exchange with other
people I feel like people are always
open for that if they can get their Oshi
or
so depends on who you got I guess
Hulu Che It Monkey D seven seven d
Slavic fellow dun space waterall dun G
dangun and space waterall again dun
thanks for watching
[Music]
Yahoo
okay you know now it's like an awkward
time where it's already 10
p.m.
and it's I actually too late to make my
sandwich I should just make full on
dinner but the sandwich would be
[Music]
faster h
I need I need a quick
snack what do I do I think I'll make the
sandwich then I eat it then I record the
dances I wanted to record which I didn't
have time for before the
stream that that's some workout so that
will maybe make me feel less hungry
faster and then it might be after
midnight but then I'll cook
[Music]
again uh does that sound like a
plan I don't know what am I even cooking
I think I need to make something with
the fish cuz otherwise it's going to go
bad I have a yeah it's the fish the fish
with the with the uh the rice and stuff
[Music]
ooh I hope that turns out
good I'm
tired what kind of fish I think it was
salmon pretty sure fish should be cooked
ASAP yes I'm on
it I'm on it
okay guys sorry for being
[Music]
like wobbly
brain the blight has affected
me wake up wake up weak
brain but I read some super chats yay
next we have next time I still have to
read EUR trun the rebroadcast which is
like almost nothing rythm Royale has a
few and then Buckshot
roulette and then Hol talk and then
today it's not too
much your Tru has one super chat okay
let's read
it Sky D safe trip W also if you're into
diving may I recommend you a game
Pacific
Drive didn't uh crony play that a few
days ago was it crony I think it was
crony
[Music]
I've got my eyes on
CL Pacific
drive
a I don't
know is it just like driving
around is that
it actually I saw no application that we
got um perms
for what's it called Endless Ocean
another ocean something like that that
big ocean game that came
out I was thinking maybe I'll play that
too as a oneoff
[Music]
game yeah the one for
switch think it's for
[Music]
switch yeah I think it's Endless Ocean
looks pretty cool oh yeah there it is
gura should play this this is a gooa
game but actually like I think of ocean
and I think of blue and I feel like ah
gooa game but then it's not like she
really plays games like these that much
right like
exploration in the big big world like
this where it really just seems like an
exploration game
doesn't necessarily feel like a game she
would play but it's blue and it has
sharks
so oh online multiplayer what do you
just swim around together or is there
any
other gimmick to
[Music]
it yeah yeah the little kitty I know I
know I talked about it might play it
soon yeah I know for debut really early
on she played that like shark
game but that's about
[Music]
it Dives with a handful of divers that's
it that's
it I don't know if that's so
interesting man eater
[Music]
okay I might still change my decision of
making a sandwich but I have to use up
the bread too you
know whatever will happen
I
shall
[Music]
vanish oh do you want to see my
asparagus pasta that I made two days
ago before I go I didn't upload it
because actually The Taste was really
underwhelming but it inspired me to make
uh make the cheese sauce for the other
[Music]
thing or did I post it I didn't post did
I wait did I post it did I post a
picture on Twitter
no I'm like no I'm like maybe I
[Music]
did oh wait I
did wait I did I did I
did I think I
did
oh we you guys some of you guys forgot
about it too are you actually looking at
my Twitter properly
eh hey yo
how did you forget you're losing it
we're losing it we're all losing
[Music]
it all right I'm going to go I have
to eat and then I can think
again and dance dance dance dance with
my hand hands
hands yeah thank you guys for watching
thank you guys for keeping me com
that was fun it had some good moments
actually
really clippable
perhaps all right then have a nice day
probably no stream tomorrow but schedule
and maybe we can get the short up
already if we're fast looks at
chy but no
pressure no
pressure and and we
say
[Music]
V how about ni stay yeah how about oh
yeah oh after the stream I I uh talked a
bit more in detail with fat Senai and I
just want to say just to put up the
pressure off of her too
um she told me that there like for the
year it's already pretty much mostly
planned out so the
summer probably can't squeeze another
one in there so maybe another time maybe
it's also better to do it outside of the
summer because it's going to be hot
anyway throughout the year apparently in
Okinawa if we're really going to do that
um but yeah I just told her yeah don't
worry about it like uh I understand that
it's already planned out and maybe maybe
a different time then yeah but just so
you know just so you don't expect
anything to happen this summer in terms
of me and what Miss Senai doing have a
nice day yeah lower your
expectations yeah yeah yeah yeah
no pressure no
pressure didn't even know that was on
the table well we talked about it in
whole talk quite a lot
yeah okay now then I'll F in bye-bye
[Music]