[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is nice
assistant
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello happy Halloween hey what what it's
not Halloween yet what do you mean it's
not Halloween yet of course it's
Halloween oh
oh hello kitty kitty
yeah I'm pretty I don't know why but
look look I got wings
where is the butt though where is it
it's still missing I put papers with my
phone number on the trees outside
yeah asking for have you seen my butt
but so far nobody called me back
I'm starting to think it's forever lost
[Music]
where could it possibly be I'm sure my
butt Somewhere Out There
really scared alone and cold freezing
is it's starting to be winter again you
know
maybe it's in Brazil
no no
I wouldn't no no who who would do such a
thing to my butt bring it to Brazil so
far away from its owner ah
I'll give it a hug if I find it no no if
you find it you should [\h__\h] call me
what do you mean how did we get to this
topic we just started and this is
there's no such answer to such a
question it's just a topic that we're
rolling with
wait what happened I lost my [\h__\h]
Buck you should know that
why the Gods Must Be so unfair to me
what have I done to deserve this
[Music]
why
what have I possibly done
here here
[Music]
see
see the thing is you don't see anything
because it's not there
oh
[Music]
I find it especially funny
I can have a minus but
I I noticed it before
it's literally like
minus but the butt crack is at least
there at least I have a butt crack oh
yeah I got marioed
uh this weird butt crack oh well
I maybe maybe this game I'll find it who
knows
who knows maybe I'll find it but I and
now see um I have a problem by the way
guys maybe you can help me you know how
you guys taught me before to move a
window from Monitor to Monitor will
shift windows and the arrow keys but
it's not working for this and it opened
up like this the game without
um giving me anything any option to
change it to Window mode
and out space
oh yeah
oh why is it German
on it
wait is there a settings here oh game
starts like that but you can what
French
English thank you
a bit more quiet here thank you
wind thank you
unfair you can do that in this game
excuse me let's go
um
how tiny is that oh that's that's
[\h__\h] tiny wait what's like 16 to nine
but one more one more bigger
is
I have no idea
16-9 ah
let's see let's go
can I choose this oh this is way too big
what the [\h__\h]
this okay okay that's good that's good
uh
ah okay and now we can play with her
okay wonderful finally finally finally
better
now I can place myself properly oh my
God the color is
are so perfect for my screen
it's so beautiful should I do myself a
little bit sideways because like you're
now that we're reading it we might as
well
be sideways no
foreign
okay okay and then uh I move chat back
we have a Halloween guns
no we're not doing 800 600 pixels
that's way too [\h__\h] tiny so we're
playing a game called what the golf
today
which is just a little joke
game small small but funny joke game
perfect you are
cute
I don't really use my 3D much because
you know reasons
happy Halloween
oh really yeah okay so
um you play golf in this game
like so yeah
they're eating the fish
Hello Kitty cats I can I'm I can't hurt
the cats are they gonna play with the
ball
no wait but that was too easy
that's just a tutorial I guess but I
thought they were gonna play with the
ball
okay okay I
usually I don't have much experience
with oops
um golf games
did I kill the kitty cat so it happened
so fast
[Music]
um neighbor in real life no one in games
I've seen a little bit just the
beginning of bottoms and by playing this
so I know that we're now gonna play
enough with the ball but with the with
this thing here yeah yeah there's
toasters why is there toasters what if
we can we does this work if I go full
power nope [\h__\h]
I thought maybe that could work
[Music]
it's ready honey
a pineapple too
yeah this is good breakfast some
vitamins and and some
some bread but I I need a spread like
Nutella or something welcome to the club
[Music]
not feeling well I hope you will feel
better soon I love this game oh you
played it too
it's it's cute
you know every once in a while oh my God
you idiot that's how I would play golf
probably oh oh again okay every once in
a while a little stupid game like this
is necessary to loosen up oh what are
the cars doing who am I the house
oh
is this how you move houses how you oh
are you moving from one house to another
in this game very smart
home in one are you gonna do puns like
this for the whole game the whole
that was not even on purpose
you're welcome
yeah they are oh my God okay maybe you
know I'll I'll take something away from
it I'll learn from this experience
why would you do that
and learn from this and hopefully take
some puns home with me
is that a cat sitting on a tube
let me in thank you
oh that's it that was the tutorial
okay
so we continue the main campaign I guess
oh start from the same Maps am I in the
right place
[\h__\h]
oh
as long as that counts very nice of them
doesn't even really have to go into the
hole
but
okay let's see let's see now that we're
not supposedly not in the tutorial let's
see if we go through all the all those
levels again
impossible
no no
okay I'm I'm being impatient oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I'm being impatient I'm
sorry I'll do it properly if I want this
to be my future job I have to do it
properly okay okay I have to take it
more seriously
we all want
to be taken seriously don't we
okay now you my friend
you lied to
me the charging thing was on the ball
not on you liar
okay the house
cars hello cars usual oh jumped nicely
over the car
men
[Music]
oh yeah right this one moves I forgot
dad ah perfect
it says house flippers oh I've heard of
that game never really saw any footage
about it let's see what happens now
[Music]
yeah
okay okay I think yes
[Music]
okay I think this this is right now
it's fine this is fine
oh
hello ball hello
what are you doing here the golf lab is
closed Golf Club where what's a golf lab
this is goal for science
what
all right we push the button push the
button let me know before
[Music]
yes I want to hear a wholesome joke
I love that song it's so old this just
proves you and me we're both Boomers
like a blown up tube cute what am I
shooting
the whole of the hole
okay not quite
the inside of the hole
let's go inside of the hall into the one
a hole in ah
um
that's very funny
oh so funny you think you're so funny
huh this game thinks it's very funny I
when I was looking up this game on Steam
I saw there was another one from
seemingly uh it wait wait no no
seemingly the same makers
uh it was it was what the bat I think
oh is the middle one the one that really
matters
oh no we're losing them all
clubs
what are you trying to tell me
yeah because it had like the same logo
kind of so I figured oh that's probably
same maker absolutely cat no why would
you do that
well the cat has a insanely long tail
also yummy hot dogs
[Music]
hot dogs for laughs
perfect pots uh-huh but is that
that's that's some kind of golf term but
I'm not sure what it is
oh
questions
unless when you hit the golf ball
a short hit short shot with a putter
you guys see some of you guys explain it
Without Really explaining it to me
access denied all right [\h__\h] you I'll go
here then ah oh oh I heard I looked up
this game is like three to four hours or
so
so let's see if we can finish it today
actually
oh we're going with the couch
that's not funny that's not funny I
laughed but it's not it's not funny
enough
yeah I guess now that Ina is on a break
I am it's my job to bring to you guys
the puns
hold up
although I can never
do it as well as she does it a [\h__\h]
hell
yo
yeah kind of sad
um I don't know if you guys heard but
you know you're not going on in her
words and indefinite Hiatus why does it
keep on rolling like that oh yeah
just a vase what's that supposed to mean
uh
now I I didn't I don't know either how
long she's gonna be gone I hope she
comes back soon
watches she's gotta take some time for
herself and I respect that I respect
that but
it gave me a really bad flashbacks of
something
I think maybe maybe in English it
doesn't sound so bad
but uh remember guys when I
told you before I was a I am I was I am
a fan of Betty's cool but an idol group
in Japan who is not active anymore they
were active for like 10 years
um since they were children now the
thing is they never had like a proper
graduation
in exchange day and child
in exchange they ended their activities
uh with an in directly translated
indefinite Hiatus and
back then everyone was like oh which
only know what that means oh they're
just saying that they're just saying
that but
and in fact they never did come back and
it's been it's been many many years you
know I don't know why they even worded
it like this because it kind of leaves
you with some hopes it did leave me with
a few hopes well I know I don't think I
don't think this is the case with Ina
but I'm just saying this gives me bad
flashbacks I just think that in Japanese
if you use that phrasing it sounds very
dooming
and yeah does not have good history but
I think yeah you know Ina didn't mean to
do that right
the memories Thanks for the Memories
even though they weren't so great
um
it's like man there's always this hope I
mean satsugani
it's been so many years I wouldn't I
would not I'm not hopeful anymore but
for the first couple of years
since I was a huge fan I was really
hopeful for that group to come back
as I said I don't think that's how she
meant it ah funny huh
I don't think that's how she meant it I
don't think she I don't think it even
has I know the same kind of implications
in English does it I'm not sure
are you sure a button
oh this is a good thing right it's a
good thing yeah we're powering
everything okay I'll go get
it does oh
well
enough
you know I know you can't do this
but I'm sure she'll come back soon
soon
I am I hope
please Inna
what Alice's work
oh
oh wow
what is that a pun how is that a pun
whoa
whoa funny what now
ah spider ball funny
yeah she said she'll be around on
Twitter at least something and I mean
maybe she'll even be okay with appearing
in some collapse
by the ball I didn't
accept
funny I hate Cliffhangers
eh
she still do she said that oh nice
okay then all right I'll I'll invite her
to daily collapse since she's not gone
okay everybody you're welcome
daily collabs with me on my channel
she can't say no she can't say no to me
can she
[Music]
oh sure balls
ah where where am I
did I play that one already no okay or
bounce ball
[Music]
I'm missing many levels
what well as long as I'm moving on
forward
oh that bounce feels good
[Music]
kimotsi bounces
I'm not missing my what are you talking
about oh I can re-enter them
oh do I click par
who's the same
what is the challenge that I'm doing it
in one hit
fail uh-huh
[Music]
and I thought it was a movie I don't
know
and let me out I don't want to do this
challenge
huh
is are they showing me how
is this
eventually gonna end up in the hole no I
think it's just endlessly doing that is
it is it
is it getting higher
is this a sample of how a pie would work
in this level
no way
wait did I do that
I don't think I did that
anyway anyway okay
so it's just challenges no
kitty cat if I was gonna play with the
kitty cat and now I'm playing with it
shall we that sticks onto places
[Music]
it's like the Minecraft jelly
and
stick with it stick kids
stick it not a whole doll what what was
that what is that telling me
I don't understand
I wish I could
play this with
like a real golf
stick
I guess it's called a club
huh
wait oh golf club is abundant on its own
isn't it
hello ball show me what you got
oh are we doing like a boss fight
and do I have to reach the heart
oh is there a time limit
[\h__\h]
because the music is getting faster
no time in the middle
what what's happening what's that
was that mean was that mean
is that gravity
sorry I did not understand this
yay lucky
[Music]
stop stop nah don't stop don't stop just
go your oh
I have destroyed the boss computer
there's a cow hello cow
cowabunga
not funny thanks for its hip
because I tipped you back
you little [\h__\h]
stop your puns at once also this makes
you think that it's over there but wait
the holes are where do you want me to go
[Music]
oh you think you've what
oh
it's laughing at me
my God
it's not going in though
what
do I have to be faster than the flag
baby no
hit the flag
okay then then I'll be slower
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
flag
let me see it is this still like just a
challenge
wait no but this this time is bigger
okay that was just a bad example maybe
oh wait
[\h__\h]
coffee master
why
and then there's like a what a Master
Level hit the flag oh it said it at the
bottom huh okay you're going there first
[Music]
oh
okay I'll try to pay attention to it I
wonder if those three hours are
speed running the game or if they also
include all those extra levels
[Music]
I care too much about you know
completing the whole game it's a [\h__\h]
golf game
so let's let's just try our best
and get some experience engulfing before
we change our career paths
free houses any percent casual
extra little take 13 hours now I thought
I saw a completionist eight hours in the
information that I had
mm-hmm
so that's probably if you do all the
levels okay I don't want to do that
[Music]
okay there's there's wind so oh close
yeah big fan
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah that's
um oh wait there's another one over
there
oh wow why why why why why why why
now we have someone protecting also
there's a [\h__\h] UFO in the background
and it's about to pick up but it is the
wrong way around somehow
the laser goes the wrong way
what's your thing
oh [\h__\h] okay that was that was too
aggressive of me sorry
easy rock and go
oh the music is good oh wait what
happened is there aliens living there
now I [\h__\h] I missed I missed the last
scene what happened did he get abducted
hey yo
hey yo that was unexpected
see maybe I'll try some of the extra
levels but not not all of them
oh soccer balls can be shot at any time
ah like even Midway while it's so I
couldn't do that with the
I couldn't do that with the golf ball
all right is the girl gonna come for me
a little [\h__\h]
yeah
[Music]
no no no no
no no yeah yeah let's go let's go let's
go let's go
same same for real for real
okay wait I want to try that one more
time let's see what else it has to offer
oh
look at all those curves
what
at least we can still do it
in air but oh okay okay
I wonder if I could have uh just gone
you know straight like this
yeah I probably could have
oh
okay on Master Level oh they're huge we
just should just go under the legs oh we
can't
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
what if I no
do you have a carrot on your nose
oh hi
hi
was I was I uh too long uh away
from
the land
now [\h__\h]
[Applause]
no no
maybe I need to
you know make you think I'm going this
way but then
oh yeah
[Laughter]
jokes oh what's that when you when you
make someone think you're you're going
one way but is that what you call that a
Juke
I don't know I'm so smart huh okay
oh yeah I only know it is a faint that's
what I was thinking
oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh man I don't know
okay okay okay
[\h__\h] where do I go oh
they're safe they're safe nice
[Music]
yo that was really difficult holy [\h__\h]
what
um
maybe maybe I can consider golf
is my future career
who's this oh okay maybe not golf but
soccer actually
no you can't get me can't get me no no
hmm there's one
oh okay I'll check it out
what's the difference oh I'm a chair
oh I'm I'm a soccer ball on a chair oh
is is the thing I'm I'm not supposed to
have the ball fall off or something wait
why did I fail
what what what
ah part two means do it within two
hmm
[Music]
oh okay I mean
we can we can get there maybe it's just
in theory it's just straight but
you know me
stop it don't touch me
sitting Ovation no I just Standing
Ovation alright
what the [\h__\h] is going on Free the
Horses yeah we have to
wait
[\h__\h]
why did I fail in five turns
do I also have to get into the goal or
is that optional
wait how do we even Freedom how do we
even Freedom let's see
just by touching it because
okay just by touching uh
[Music]
but this [\h__\h]
okay okay
maybe I'll go with this one first
uh I'll you know what I'll go in a round
[\h__\h] okay I [\h__\h] it up but I wanna go
from you know from there here to here to
here to here instead of going zigzag
zigzag
but then if I do have to go
infinite strikes
but when did I fail sometimes then what
okay this time maybe I failed because
oh because I was gone for too long
that one
[Music]
the [\h__\h] okay oh there's another horse
okay let me go down
or is it there
okay wow
[Music]
I'm suckering I'm golfing
soccer golfing
with that one
calm down calm down
[Music]
wow
that was quite a challenge
got a lot of Challengers here
okay car coming through there's a hot
dog man again
I would like some hot dog please
I rarely ever eat hot dogs but I had I
[Music]
I had some more advice wished you know
the
the sausage the white sausage that I
talked about the other day yo [\h__\h] go
[\h__\h] yourself go [\h__\h] yourself
I'm in quite the Oktoberfest mood
thanks to the sausages
come at me bro
[Music]
wow it's gonna be fast because gotta be
fast gotta be fast
dribbling dribbling dribbling not much
of a vice versa
why not I don't think it's yummy look
the little fluff the mustard yeah yum
yum yum
I'll check it out I'll check it out
yeah yeah yeah
I haven't got all day so I really don't
want to do it for all of them but what
ruined a hot dog party no why would
anyone do that
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no huh
I started fast
oh
I see you okay we have free like cows
and we have to destroy the hot dog carts
all right I know we have endless
cows and we have to destroy the hotel
carts
okay wait that's too much
[Music]
at least we got the back one
how about this how about that okay
voice party uh worst spotting I know the
worst is uh Deutsche German for sausage
worst body haha that's German fun
another
one
interesting interesting interesting
interesting oh that's fun
okay we're not allowed to bump into
anything
what about the car
this one's not as difficult as some
others but I would say but maybe I'm not
hey the timing of the car felt different
but I guess if I just wait
um before I go other car is Gonna Come
no okay ah yes they are okay
well then
goodbye
okay I'll wait a little bit one two
three go
okay I'm gonna burn them
with my ball
oh
come on
my my eyebrows in 3D
I was so angled I look so aggressive
I think I think if you look at someone
like this from Below
they look even more intimidating don't
they
[Applause]
so cute on me thank you stop it you're
distracting me
hmm
yay
how you guys doing down there um
are you doing good all right all right
just checking I guess this is really a
realistic point of view for you guys as
chickens
this is just realistic
chickens this is how you see me right oh
my God my nose yeah
the [\h__\h] out of my nose okay you got
a problem with that
oh
I don't make fun of my nose
this is cute though
every angle of koala is cute I can be
your ankle or your angel
or your angled angel
a I don't know man don't ask me
the cat I'm so sorry please forgive me
I'll give you lots of Kibbles later and
a snack
you can have some chickens fresh or dead
or alive however you prefer skins over
feathers
I I will not judge you mm-hmm
hello backside why would you want my bag
signed
again have
I guess a little bit of my bag signs
look at my cheeks
you see that
come down
[Laughter]
watching
my cheeks
well they're quite round
um
I'm holding on holding my breath oh
wow
you want to pinch them
don't cheek my pinches
I will hurt you
I'll stream like this
I'm a side streamer
which angle do you like the most of this
angle
was this part seven in seven turns hmm
yes don't shake my pinches
do you have a problem with my
sophisticated English
[Music]
wait let's wait let's wait for this
thing to move us maybe that helps
and oh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
almost had it
so close
go
wait we'll wait a little bit I guess I
should use as much of the distance that
this bowl can do on its own as possible
[\h__\h] I'm in the mountain
why that's not my fault why is the
mountain open
afraid these things are pretty let's
stop
I requested to be able to take off my
hats because I can't put on all the all
the accessories properly so let's hope
that let's hope that happens
sometime soon let me try again
oh that went over whoa
holy [\h__\h]
no not for me for some reason I I know
it's like in theory somehow should be
possible because I mean my life today
can do it so my 3D whoa better be able
to do it too
okay I think this is the run this is the
Run
hot dogs oh no
no hot dogs okay okay yes yes
and go
oh well wait
thank you soon
wait ah one more I saw that wait that
wasn't the last level I thought that was
the last level with one I have one to
spare no way
I'll play it oh thank you oh I'm the
girl
do I have to bring the ball
oh
what wait oh I have to I have to pass it
to the other girl oh my God and she can
like dribble dribble the ball
ah
I'm taking the ball oh that's funny oh
God
she's doing this trick oh my God ah no
no
[Laughter]
ah
she did a slide yeah I want to try it
again in a second
sake moves girl
I am
all right all right all right
believe believe
hey
okay so far no slight necessary no no
panic yet oh [\h__\h] no
and
I I I slipped
I slipped man
sorry yeah
wait oh
what why can't she do the the thing
no
come on girl oh [\h__\h]
here I'll get up there
okay she did
us uh one of those moves but she fell
off the mountain
it's dangerous dangerous why aren't we
playing in such a dangerous place
there's no fences how did they even get
up here in the first place huh
at it again with questioning everything
it's in my nature I can't help it but
it's just I want their safety you know I
don't even need that girl I can do it
alone do I need all of them
we don't even need this
let's do it on my own
so much smarter just the first task was
necessary because there was a gap what
the [\h__\h] are you doing oh oh oh oh
okay they're once again chasing me but
on their own before I even the first one
didn't even wait for me to move
no
awesome
are we yes we're first trying this
gold for me
thank you for helping me he's on my side
I'll do another one now I'm kind of like
I like the challenge oh
wait what what ball is that
what am I supposed to do I didn't get to
read
do I need to kill the kids
I need to get them off the field or
it must be a reason why I can do this
oh yeah yeah okay
ah
one sec
okay
so I am hiding behind the tree ah
cute
get out of the way
okay that should be enough
oh ah don't have to push them off just
have to touch them okay okay
ball wings
okay from different angles so cursed
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
he's loving it
good angle
I don't like this angle
well what about oh this angle
ah
how about this angle
like my head like my head I have
this on my head
yeah
quite endearing I know all right let's
go go girl
[Music]
I failed
score a goal
I believe
oh [\h__\h]
oh
girl I swear to God I swear to God you
have to catch up okay okay this is our
chance oh
oh
[Music]
ah
that was lucky that was really lucky wow
you seeing his face
what is the face
is that no that's not smug smug is this
big Chihuahua cute
I'm gonna step on you
big big
stamp stamp stamp stamp
how do you like that
[Laughter]
wait
wait oh no
I scrolled too aggressively where am I
okay
hi
[Music]
I'll be here
all right we mastered all of these yo
okay let's let's speed for you again wow
I got way too much power
whoosh
[Music]
and now the other side oh there's like a
a thingy a block do I get do I get a
mushroom out of it
we're playing Flappy Birds
oh my God is this how Flappy Birds wait
no wait this is like Mario inspired
never mind oh my God and also unlike
that game we played the other day Pico
Park
oh my God oh God oh God fly high little
bird
[Music]
I like I like that there's more than
just
ah more than just golf going for tonight
Oh I thought that was that little thing
on over there
no no I want
I want
that thing yay no ah can I even get
anything out of it I wonder like a
secret
no please please ah
maybe go no
did anyone try this and get something
out of it and I feel is already several
times
[Music]
[\h__\h]
maybe now
that I have this bird I I have more like
power and now I can push it
too aggressive too aggressive children
I swear to God this one I swear to God I
look like an eyeball like a bleeding
eyeball oh
I look like a bleeding eyeball I have
some kind of eye infection
what if I do it from above okay no I
don't I don't think yeah I give up I
don't think it's a thing
I'm I'm surely not the only one who
tried that though
okay I suppose we have to get this thing
again
don't pop
no
oh wait we can come back that thing
stays there
gent gently
gently
the music sounds a little bit like that
theme
you hear it too guys bubbly
bubbly
you can see you reflecting my eyes so
clearly
pretty huh quite pretty huh
the music is different now golf
[Music]
ER
that's definitely inspired by that
oh [\h__\h] I swear to God
what's up
what if I go here
oh okay
[Music]
some more Mario
[Applause]
it's not quite though it's not 100 copy
of course because they would get in
trouble I assume uh
oh
oh I'm better at this than real Mario
games
[Music]
oh can she do it can she do it
my pancakes
oh my God
foreign
[Applause]
what was safe and do I even have to
touch these things I wonder
it's not like I'm getting like an extra
life out of it
did they not saying water hot
what the golf
wow I feel like the jumps are a little
bit inconsistent but what do I know
possible I can but last time I touched
it
it was facing away from me I think
and still I I died but okay I don't know
rip
[Music]
indeed
oh my God Donkey Kong but with frog
um
[Music]
wait he's so cute
that's really difficult oh my God
I felt that
Donkey from you prong well
um by the way we're having uh Donkey
Kong
frog week next week is frog week
um so look forward to it I didn't do it
this week after all because
because
um
oh yeah because Donkey Kong is busy with
my frog I don't know no
um
[Music]
is currently
um being
um
she's currently being like kind of
rigged so I can use it like outside of
outside of yeah bye outside of VR I got
permission to do it if it's just you
know for like
like a once once in a
while a special stream like that so
[Music]
I am not interested in uh Donkey Kong
please don't ship
yeah bye
please don't ship me and Donkey Kong
[Music]
it's like the most difficult level so
far
[Music]
okay
so fast
[Music]
why is that not possible here
what what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
God
I hate this why is it like this
[Music]
no
what the [\h__\h] what
oh my gosh
[Music]
it's so sensitive
this will be the end of me
foreign
okay okay come on come on come on
[Music]
I swear to God I swear to God
oh no
[Music]
oh no come back
the golf it's not even gold
but I guess I guess what this is really
about is um you know Helen golf you
always have these meters
to control how fast you your ball your
your golf ball goes and that's really
the only thing that
um you know it's it's using from typical
golf games
that's that's the thing that's the thing
please don't touch me am I safe here
yeah okay
[Music]
it should still be safe here
okay okay time to go
yeah finally
I'm not bothering with the extra levels
here thank you no thank you
not necessary Danke Schoen
golf node one one that's the first golf
note golf is really boring maybe we can
fix it how
do you think okay
how would we fix it oh wait is this your
way of fixing it
so I mean I'm sure there's some golf
lovers out there let's not insult them
does anyone in the chat play golf
regularly
no no
Goldberg last
only once a year mini golf
only five minutes ago golf is for rich
people
I don't know about that is it is
getting to golf courses are they
expensive I've never been to a real Bank
Golf Course
[Music]
I was lucky
clubs are expensive
ah why can't you just rant them maybe
nowadays you could even 3D print nailed
it 3D honestly
depending on you know what exactly you
build they can be so fragile
I've had things 3D printed before it was
really fragile
like like
um small small tips
will just you know easily go off
am I supposed to touch that
but I from what I've heard Angry Bird
this is what Angry Birds is like
from what I've heard um there's like I
think also different materials that you
can do 3D prints with like different 3D
printing materials but I think in
general they're all pretty similar
oh I think
pretty sensitive nonetheless I would say
so if you make a club
what you can print with steel and metal
now what oh I was talking about the
typical 3D printing material oh what
that's a thing now
that's that's insane
they're too very difficult to work oh
3D printers from metals and Ceramics
what
that's really cool
[Music]
Industrial Level printers though that
can print miles aha
super expensive and used in big plans ah
okay well at least you know the for the
printing thingy has at least become
so that you can kind of afford more or
less to do it at home
what was that if you wanted to
print something yourself a couple of my
friends have like 3D printers
um
you can print yourself some cute
Carefree chickens or your own figure of
tacos oh that reminds me at that
Comic-Con that I went to
um there was
oh I'm so alive I'm sorry
boom there was um there was like a booth
that does
um like they they make a model of you
like a figure a figurine of you
and you step into
it
I like that
[Music]
yeah yeah you can step into this big
Booth they have it look they have
cameras everywhere it's kind of like a
it reminded me of how 3D studios are but
they were not the same kind of like
cameras it was like normal cameras I
guess they take they take photos of you
from every side and then they make a
pretty model out of it and then they
um they print it
and then they painted so it takes like a
week or two until you actually get it
and it was really expensive eight
hundred dollars Euros approximately
I'm pretty fast yeah probably because no
one does it so they have a lot of time
because I
did it even at the Comic Con yeah you
could do it right there
but it would cost you 800 bucks so my
friends were like actually wow don't you
want to get one for yourself you could
actually do that and I'm like
uh I mean
that's some really stupid way to spend
my money I think because I don't
necessarily require I mean
of myself so
they're literally I guess our figurines
of myself as merchandise so I I really
don't need another one I guess but
but my friends are like you oh you
should do it you should do it you've got
the money and I'm like um
no I
I know I
[Applause]
it's like
people do that because I mean I
understand at Comic Con the only thing
the only scenario where I understand it
is
um at Comic-Con there's cosplayers right
so if you're in a cosplay I guess it
could be oh no no I guess it could be
cool to have a figure of yourself in the
cosplay but not really
not really self so I don't know unless
you're like really really proud of your
cosplay but even then
don't think I would be interested in
that
then I might as well just get a figurine
of the character I'm cosplaying don't
you think oh my God [\h__\h]
yeah I just buy my own fake my Flex
the 800 is hmm
it's reasonable for the fact that they
do all the work and you get it painted
even though
no no I really don't want it boom
I really don't want it
I really don't want it no thank you
what was I gonna say
oh yeah unless maybe
maybe if if I don't know if you think
like if you have a partner and you think
that partner would be happy
about receiving a figurine of you then I
guess that's a really expensive gift for
your partner
would you guys be happy if you had a
partner and that partner made a figurine
of themselves for 800 bucks and give it
to you for your birthday or whatever or
anniversary or whatever would you guys
be happy about that
I mean if you really really really love
your boyfriend girlfriend
I don't know if you're really down bad
for them
wouldn't you maybe actually be happy one
but
but I know but think about it
most I would
I would present of you would want if
offered for free and gifted a Kiana
figurine wouldn't jump so you're saying
you would be happier about receiving a
figurine of me than receiving a figurine
of your boyfriend girlfriend
[Laughter]
laughs
it was me Kiana's different ah
you guys
um
hahaha
if am I mean judging by the statistics
in my chat
I would say that boof really is not
lucrative then if you if you wouldn't
even want a figurine oh my god of of
your boyfriend girlfriend then
really I cannot think of a good use
it's not even life science it's just
small
maybe some of you guys would want a
lifestyle I mean that takes up a lot of
space and we're talking about you know
proper
proper material
yeah if my boyfriend did that I'd be
creeped out
if you mean if a boyfriend made a figure
of himself for you you would be creeped
out
800 is too much just don't mention it
that's creepy time
of creepy
poor Booth man
literally they have no future
go for 23. the experiment was a blast
we're moving on funny
this is like
in really simplistic Graphics this is
like the the portal
lab
I feel like but it's it's testing with
with golf balls you know what I mean
does anyone get the same vibes
and it's more happy it has happy Vibes
but
if you if you put on some dark filters
it might give you the same Vibe oh don't
eat the ball wait what the [\h__\h]
that's a challenge here
do we want no we just we just want the
human to go over there or I'll run
is that really what we want
tell me what you want what we really
really want ah
[Music]
I'd tell her she's a muppet because I
see her every day anyway
was that mean
oh
wait that's actually pretty useful it
helps me get a bit further
don't fall down
oh [\h__\h] bye bye
we start
bottom
[Music]
um
why am I so always looking so sideways
oh well
oh [\h__\h] my boobies look big
[Laughter]
[Music]
they look so big when looking from the
top
oh
they look so big
they look bigger than usual
bye guys
not from here though not for oh oh oh
[Music]
hey
meow
[Music]
you never noticed that my buttons are
shaped like wings well yeah yeah they
are
coming right I've heard about things
like that before
really concerning stuff man please
please don't make me fall down
oh oh oh oh okay I [\h__\h] up
oh okay that catapulted me forward
that's good
that's good oh oh okay okay
uh I see the girl
I see the girl
and here we go
[Music]
we catapulted
oh yeah if I read them about context
later no
and up we go up we go I say come on come
on come on did you guys see the schedule
for this week I made a schedule I put it
out today oh oh my God
did you guys see it
we're playing GTA twice
oh that wasn't so bad
GTA twice probably finishing it most
likely finishing it God damn it
no
well we're playing this right now and
then uh we're having a snack box
tomorrow
no wait what's this with cats
what's this with cats
okay
I'll wait this one there
oh it's coming after me
okay but all the cats are behind those
explosive barrels oh my God that's more
than just taping no I'm hurting now I
don't wanna
[Music]
oh I'm so sorry
why did I fail what happened
huh
funky wonky
so far so good
uh oh yeah snack box snack box yeah yeah
you're doing Starbucks tomorrow I'm
excited for that finally it's been a
while since the last snack box stream
yeah
and and
what else what else what else ah cooking
simulator yeah I was going for the games
I was like I need one more
one more game for just some
some one stream fun and I was going for
a while I was going for the list what
and I saw a cooking simulator I was like
all right okay
why not I guess that looks fun oh my God
okay no trees okay I was just testing
now
can I go like here
I can't easy myself
[Music]
can I join I want to join the cat
meaning
oh is it weird and it took me so long
I don't know I was always kind of like
skeptical about
um simulator games
because I wasn't sure like
I don't think I've ever really
oh what's happening
oh I need to get away from that ah
before it gets to me
that was the story about like the
quality of those kind of simulator games
but a bunch of them do look good I I
agree with that
I just wasn't quiet
um you know
sure of it because I never really tried
them
I was like I guess you know eventually
I'll play them but
I don't know at cooking a statement
later I've seen from aquosm by when I
was you know doing her clips for
all that what about that though for a
whole talk
and it looked funny when she played it
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah there's so
many simulated games out there I'm sure
not all of them are really really that
good but cooking simulator looks good
yeah
hopefully we'll have some fun with that
what's happening why are we in space
[Music]
what
[\h__\h] oh wait oh there there are the
challenges
oh my God even just getting to the
challenge is a challenge
testing me
testing me ah
what boys uh-huh
should have said something like I need
some space
oh
I'm gonna do it again ah the gravity
it's sticking to whatever planet that is
[\h__\h]
why
wow cruncher
no furniture something like a
Square Enix game
sounds like it
oh yeah your gravity is pulling me your
cavity is pulling me constellations oh
wait that's not quite it
all right so clear today
[Music]
what's going on let's see which which
gravity is stronger here
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh way too far hey yo
oh that that should be good okay
oh where where are the other ones
two out of five where are they uh here
why the [\h__\h] is it on a
what's that called in English
or Orca no
that's a lot more good it's a big whale
whale
like the gacha players thank you guys
already figured it out
[Music]
safe
oh
[Applause]
why
what the [\h__\h]
are we the big The Big Red One
oh
it's like billiard
you're still we have a problem ah
because he's an astronaut ah
hello
I am ashamed for not understanding that
one
wait
oh that's
the person
Oh I thought they were talking to a
person they were talking to the to
Ascent to like a headquarters that's
based in Houston Oh I thought I mean
I mean not the only one who assumed
such a thing right
I don't know every American person that
exists oh my
um
no problem
[Applause]
I mean I know of the place Houston
[Music]
that could easily be a person's name no
don't you think
what's happening
oh
I'm sure there's someone called Houston
I made a huge once there you go thank
you
there you go Whitney Houston yeah I met
her I met her
so they were not calling her
like Whitney Houston we have a problem
I understand why you would go to Whitney
Houston for your problems you could sing
them away
I'm little Space robot
okay I guess we can't go really back so
let's be careful
let's land anymore after taking off once
it's like me flying the hot air balloon
in rest oh let it go let it go let it go
oh
[Applause]
yeah
Luna Orlando Oh are there a lot of like
game references in here so far I only
really understood Angry Birds and oh
I understand that's what that is for
yeah everybody's in Mario Super Mario
I'm trying to stop the whole life
um no
small steps for chihuahua
or the giant step for chickens
the Phoenix has landed indeed
big button robot fighting
hello
[Applause]
oh oh yeah I was supposed to go
towards the height yeah yeah let's let's
fight for the robots
[Music]
no no okay okay I can just go straight
okay I thought they were gonna stay
where they are
here
oh
wow
[Music]
call this a challenge
oh Something's Gonna show up
different way
should have been faster I
think there you go
I I I knew that was gonna happen with
the heart yeah oh
too easy
be cold oh they want to touch me no no
no no no no no no no no let's go listen
to a fact
I want to listen to the fact God's not
doing these things obviously I'm not a
golfer
what's is that funny
what does that mean
is that funny
the reference
oh is that like
well obviously you don't own an air
fryer
or ah they're just hinting at the fact
that this is obviously not golf so the
developer must not really know what golf
is
no
grabby hands no yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
stop laughing at me stop laughing at me
a little [\h__\h] I know you're going there
oh [\h__\h]
he got two got you got you
someone in the chat said something about
natachi had meet and greet and that
reminded me
one thing
fun to meet and greet that I wanted to
mention but I totally forgot about it
one um meet and greet was
quite
funny to me quite different
I mean there were a couple ones that
were quite different but one of the ones
that I haven't talked about yet
[Music]
um
one meat and greet was like
ah
ah I get it now
what meet and greet was like you know
um some of them had cameras on so some
of them I could see and this person I
could see
and
I think
I'm not 100 sure anymore how we got to
that topic I think it's because
um the person praised me the chicken
praised me about my
about me you know doing some workout
I think maybe
oh
and then hello
somehow we talked about
you know I don't know how but but but
but you know I I noticed they were
um the type of person to do workouts
what's happening
and turns out there were like some kind
of a boxer fighter yeah
so I I
challenged them to in the middle grade
show me how to throw a punch
yeah so a part of the meeting green was
used to show me how to throw a punch
that was really
really educational
[Music]
why you're not happy with that you want
more
all right I have to get rid of all that
that's really annoying there's only a
couple of them standing oh wait that's
excellent pretty kind
foreign
please don't expect that
I don't think
I honestly don't think I could ever
really successfully throw a punch I'm so
[\h__\h] weak and that's okay that's okay
[Music]
come on
not the candle
anyway I thought that was funny because
like
that was such an unusual did you let
meet and greets
I used up the meet and greet time they
had
forced them to teach me how to throw a
punch
[Music]
put my back into it nah my back's broken
how can I put my bag into it
we're like
I don't know I know what I was gonna say
come on
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
it was so
perfect Direction I can't get it any
better than that
you can get stronger than
come on come on this must be it yeah
okay okay okay which is two weeks okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay
do we get more bowling oh I can just go
I thought there was a wall there
that's it
I can't be yet
[Music]
that's the same oh wait here we go I'm
gonna have to go around
hey
[Music]
no one would go around there oh
well first we get the wall
this is what I got
oh I was too weak
oh what we don't need the wall
we don't need to take it down
[Music]
like that no one no one
oh wow
beautiful beautiful absolutely beautiful
why what am I using
this is a hat
and we're using hats now
have we thrown away so many balls
music is loud isn't it I'm sorry oh
obviously not a bowler
[Music]
whoa
good night
[Music]
we're bowling with a carpet okay I mean
carpets just want a plane too
and it makes perfect perfect sense
yeah yeah okay okay no no [\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
the ground the one that we're not
shooting
I look at it and I just have to think of
although that one's [\h__\h] up but I have
to think of Triforce all the time when I
see this but that one's [\h__\h] up this
one
[Music]
look at it this that's the only one
that's [\h__\h] up what
[Music]
Triforce what the [\h__\h]
that ball just does not want to go
anywhere
um next door
there's a PC
no
wait
what do you say sometimes you play golf
and sometimes while golf plays you hmm
some deep [\h__\h] that's like saying
sometimes you will live life or play
live and sometimes life plays you
it do be like that don't it
oh
there it is
ah number one of those where you have a
[\h__\h] ton of them
[Music]
how can you mess up with so many balls
hmm
no oh they go everywhere no
no need you I need
okay I have an idea one if it's not the
obvious
way of doing it by going straight what
if it's you know chill
I don't know I don't know I don't know I
don't know I don't know I hate it
foreign
[Music]
I figured it out
if you want them also go the same way
you have to go full power
okay just a couple need to survive or
one a one one is fine I mean
just one
honestly maybe that's really the best
just focus on one [\h__\h]
la la la
before you lose everything
[Music]
please please
okay
[Music]
oh it's so fast it's too fast no okay
okay yay
that's that's nice I got this
[Music]
beautiful
yeah
by the way I watched the new house of
the Dragon episode don't worry I'm not
gonna I'm not gonna spoiler you I just
want to say
two things what the [\h__\h] Damon
someone please stop Damon and and the
King holy [\h__\h] I feel like I feel like
Damon is like a vampire in terms of
Aging because Damon is the only one of
the few actors
uh or honestly in some way the only one
besides that one guard I guess like uh
who's not aging
not [\h__\h] aging at all while everyone
else is aging so much that they're
apparently died and had to be replaced
by other actors hmm
just kidding I mean they were just
replaced to show the change of age but
you know they did that really well I
think with the King because he's like
aging like crazy
but then you look at Damon and over
those what 20 years so far I don't know
roughly it feels like 20 years have
passed
but he just
still looks absolutely the same they
made no effort in making him look any
older
oh interesting
oh
which just kind of bothered me this time
because yeah
they once again replaced the kids with
new actors you can't get used to the
actors
and it keeps on changing everything
keeps on changing it's kind of like
bewildering if that's the right word I'm
not sure
hmm
I understand why they're doing it but
hey sorry
I understand why they're doing it but I
I wish I wish
wouldn't change quite that much
Max welcome yourself leveling but he's
not max level
okay well the build it was fine hmm
also they uh in this episode a new new
one of the new actors
you know the one with the with the I I I
think me
look I I know that's a famous actor
right I've seen him somewhere who is
that
I've seen him somewhere before
but I mean who is the who's the actor
what what where could I know him from
because he looks very familiar
squish
a torch I am the torch
last Kingdom
[Music]
what's going on
that's it what the [\h__\h] give me more of
a challenge
oh
What in in two tanks
no
[Music]
wait now I'm I'm having a little bit of
um
what's the word
when you see things not the way they are
because I thought you know this is going
downwards but I didn't see it like that
I saw it like
um
differently
no
no no
optical illusion thank you
yeah Fufu you're getting me
um I thought I thought this path
was like different I can't even explain
it
foreign
[Music]
that's what it is actually that's what
it actually is
oh [\h__\h] but I saw it kind of on the same
same level all of this all of this
looked like it was on the same level for
me
yeah like it's going towards us if
anything
anyway
fly high my torch fan oh that went
further than I thought it would
oh oh there we go oh
yes yes
I don't know I can look at one more
hit the flag ah and then it rains we
don't want it to
oh
let's go let's go
what the [\h__\h] oh
we skipped quite a lot there
that was really
it was really it went for the rain once
but it didn't seem to bother nice
okay some more water
everybody hydrate
yeah
oh
guys you want to know something
you want to know something next week
next week is gonna be super special
and you're gonna look back on this
statement and be like uh
I understand now
well we know frog week is happening
but what could I mean with next week is
going to be special do I just mean frog
week
oh this is fun I don't have to do
anything
foreign
in between as well
[Applause]
what's that oh
you can do it don't be scared
I was never able
in my whole life I never jumped from a
tower that tall into a pool never
when we had to do it
like when we went swimming with school
some some would go up but I I could
never do it
it's my chance
and some would go even higher than that
you know that was actually a really
interesting
German TV show
from this famous German uh TV show host
talk show host actually
that that guy he came up with a bunch of
TV shows back in the day I don't think
he's active anymore
yeah
um but yeah what he came up with a show
I don't know what why but the show was
oh
um with a bunch of celebrities German
celebrities
uh what's Tim's playing in English
anyway
you know jumping from those Towers is a
sport
so you would get points for specific
jumps and all that and how how
beautifully done they were and they even
had um like double jumps so there was
um also points for
um being in sync with your partner base
jumping I guess so yeah and also
depending on from how high you jump they
were like different bases like do you
know you know how in the proper pool
inside pool indoor pool
they would do it like that
oh
yeah yeah yeah so all kinds of
celebrities that just have never done us
anything like that before they would
train for this TV show and honestly it
was quite popular it was quite the quite
quite the big event
even I watched it really
like excitedly even though like I would
never watch something like that in my
normal past time
but I thought it was really interesting
to see all these amateurs actually doing
really really good at it like they were
for an amateur
from from the point of view of an
amateur what they were doing looked
really professional
we had it in the UK well you had
something like that too
the problem oh yeah yeah yeah that was
also a thing they had all kinds of like
fun TV shows that that dude came up with
I mean maybe not he probably didn't come
up with it himself he was just chosen as
the representative
as the host but yeah they had a you know
those those car derby
things they had um celebrity was it
celebrities
was it celebrities driving with Pros
because I don't know it seems too
dangerous now that I think back on it
was really just celebrity
celebrities driving driving in in those
cars
demolition derbies
where are my German friends
wrong
not alone ride probably was a
professional
they had pro teams but celebrities
driving
it was really just celebrities that's
that's so dangerous
wait this is wait this game reminds me
of the game where you have your son on
the back
that's the dad and the Sun
Flash game
Happy Wheels yeah it's a happy wheel
looks like I never played Happy Wheels
before I think well maybe once I don't
know back in the day
back in the day when flash games were
such a big hit oh wait you can just
drive normally
going for those Flash game websites
I felt like such a gamer playing all the
flash games
I was like I don't know nine ten years
old I don't know who knows how old it
was
[Music]
funny oh [\h__\h] I need to get up there
okay
wait that's really difficult holy [\h__\h]
did you guys also go for these websites
of all the flash games it was like like
compilation on one website did you use
those
oh good job
[Applause]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah listen deep very fun I
barely remember them though the games
themselves
I don't remember any any of them
but some of them were like you know like
it's similar to Super Mario like
platformer games
um
Miniclip concrete I never heard of those
I mean you know our hours were maybe
partially different because German
websites and all that
[Music]
okay we're in the boss fight again
quit
maybe you just have to be fast before
everything
comes falling crumbling down
okay this one yeah
be very fast oh yeah Frogger Frogger was
definitely one of them
well I'll toaster John
missing my friend thank you golfing
prosperity
yeah oh wow they have a fancy fountain
in here
we're going this way to the toilets a
mongoose oh
I was gonna ask where the games I guess
we're going there now
secret place you found a secret place oh
me and Dana's sacred place
this is our secret place oh my
[Music]
the secret place is [\h__\h] with me tell
it to stop
[Music]
hi I've captured the flag yeah Maldives
I want to go back
[Music]
no [\h__\h] you I want to see if that does
anything over there oh yeah
oh they have like
statues to collect oh I have no idea
wait what the [\h__\h] where am I
there's like a statue room
and how do I get back
wait after you have all the statues
there's like more to see
oh how do I
how do I get back
don't let the car I don't know
I don't know which one I want where did
I come from
is that is that is that
the whole I don't
Maybe
no you don't know what the least
percentage though the number six
ah no apparently not oh yeah right it
has no tube okay that must be this one
okay okay
I need a bag
all right all right I think we've seen
what we needed to see
I'm not here
oh a computer
nothing new to report go for super
GoPros don't play this game
anyone who has golf as a hobby and
thinks oh I love golf but I'm also a
gaming let's play some Steam games that
have something to do with golf don't
don't play this game you're gonna be
highly insulted
foreign
not gonna make you happy at all
gonna feel depressed
where are the games
I can't free him
what happened what did you do to the
golfer everything's coffee yeah okay
again
but you don't answer my question what
what did you do to the golfer
it's getting really dark now huh
simple enough
okay okay here we go
yo I have like a really dark
gamer spots on my on on my hand
it's like really red and dark from
it's like super hot yeah
from like holding the mouse constantly
I call it gamer spot because the gamers
maybe not only the game is any any PC
using person
as a it hurts
it hurts
because this isn't just oh I was gonna
ask is it just the visuals no it's not I
want to play this game too at some point
it has a VR too right a VR version
seems really stressful in VR though oh
no is it easier in Via I wonder
uh the only rules when I'm moving
super good it's super fun really cool in
VR
well I don't have much experience in VR
games my VR experience is so far really
mostly just uh the myth collapse oh I
can kill them
foreign
super hot
stream a little bit
they say the thing
oh this is so super hot themed
did they get permission to make super
hard references
they must have read but ah but I kind of
can't imagine them asking for like
Nintendo perms to put references into
their game
but super hot seems kind of more
reachable you know what I mean
so I can kind of see them asking super
hot because this is quite blatant isn't
it ow
that way then maybe maybe because
there's a lot of games like that maybe I
don't know
you don't need it if it's a parody but
yeah I feel like you wouldn't want to
make any game developers angry though
would you
publishers
I feel like you don't wanna oh I can oh
I can shoot them
oh
interesting
yeah it's super hot you can also pick up
weapons right and then shoot them back
[\h__\h]
where'd it go no way to go
am I is it just
am I too used to being in whole life so
asking for permissions for everything is
just
it just has become too normal for me
and I can't imagine it otherwise
oh
oh oh it's several shots
yes baby super hot
that's cool
I like the combination of golfing with
super hot
[Laughter]
combination that works really good
[Music]
hmm
getting chronologies was pain
ah you did that you went so far
all right there's a gun here
[Music]
stay
well I need to move otherwise it doesn't
move
oh
I'm gonna shoot him
yeah bye yeah bye
yeah bye
[Music]
yeah it was like super hot tutorial next
week I'll be playing Super no I wasted
it
oh [\h__\h]
no I'm not actually gonna be playing
super hot next week but yeah okay
[Music]
I feel like that one only shoots once
doesn't he and that one over there would
be more important to take down probably
but I'll
nah I can try to get both though I think
I think we can manage if I just
Dodge his yeah okay that's fine and now
I take my my weapon back
[\h__\h]
does that is that gonna
is that going for the the wall I wonder
what [\h__\h]
foreign
I
was smart by going down
[Music]
okay shoot him and then go
here
but I have to continue moving
i i i i i i i i i okay
okay now I would like to retrieve my
weapon
this is the Run
hey oh now I'm shooting several ones
okay uh just stay safe
nice
it's coming at me whoa okay
oh
that was a
that was a finger
that's fun
open up
more super hot please thank you I would
like more of that thank you
oh yeah oh yeah
what's going on here oh my God
tell is this super hot with golf with
Toho
okay let's see because they're not gonna
give me a weapon but can I kill them by
just like bonking them I feel like yeah
no oh no oh I can't because they are a
little higher than me
but we can I can really easily Dodge
them actually not so bad not so
difficult
super golf
I wouldn't mind trying that one
a little bit more difficult what's
what's the next thing I'm a chair why am
I a chair
what makes a difference
oh my god oh I'm fast I move faster
and there's more space that they could
hit oh my God
yeah
wait oh wait no never mind it's part two
oh wait this is part two
hey
there's no [\h__\h] way
part two
what is it like a really specific angle
that gets you through anything
because that was certainly not it
that was also not it
no
and I don't know if I want to rank my
rate oh
for that that's no way too we're free
maybe even number two
let's just go straight oh
[Music]
that's not at the last one
that was so close
saying why it's not working anymore
I went straight that time too oh
oh really really really
oh
yes
[Music]
no [\h__\h] I forgot but I was there
okay so basically it's not about angles
it's just about going straight come on
come on and believing in yourself
a super power I say I said yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay I'll look into
the last one
real time
what does that mean
yeah no time
oh no slow mo oh okay okay
but
yeah
what
too close too close
that is manageable
this kind of get always through the
closest point where they cross each
other Maybe
I was going trampoline that's super
close yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
foreign
okay we can try to brute force it too
let's see how that goes
Brute Forces anymore I'm scared
[Music]
that was some
low-key enough but it wasn't it wasn't
it's funny though
uh yeah
[Applause]
always stop oh I don't need your pity
I don't know when to go
I screamed so loud I hurt my ear I feel
like I just broke something in my ear on
my own is that even human is that is
that humanly possible
well I'm a phoenix so it doesn't really
apply to me but it's so loud in my in my
head
foreign
can you burst your own eardrums
that would be so [\h__\h] stupid and it
would be your own fault so that's really
unfortunate if that happens to you
[Applause]
and one at a time no [\h__\h] that
I mean I guess you could but no
ah due to ear infection
foreign
no way
like properly bursted her eardrums by
herself
I'm worried
Roost is covered her ears when they wait
chickens don't have ears why do you guys
have ears
I mean I guess where are your guys's
ears
I don't remember chickens having ears
where where are they let me just Google
that
where are
chickens ears okay
oh
oh wait that's like an earworm
I'm learning chicken and a nut and the
Tommy and not to me
that's an earlobe
what
[Music]
you guys are weird oh you guys look
weird sometimes
that's a [\h__\h] ear and those are yeah
no way
what about other birds
wait what about other birds
beside them
tell me tell me a different bird
about Eagle where are eagles ears
they have a hole what the [\h__\h]
was like mostly covered by feathers
normally I guess it's like this with old
birds they're all like
they all have like hidden holes there
a yellow owl's ears are interesting
wait no he really got me with that topic
that's actually so interesting
where are
owls ears
that looks absolutely [\h__\h] disgusting
to me
I do not wish to look into
somebody's body so deeply no thank you
we're done with this topic now
laughs
[Music]
a monkey
I can't oh my gosh
what a cursed topic though what the [\h__\h]
and how how we got there
unbelievable
how close can we get
oh
my God I don't like this one let me get
me out and get me out of here can I
thank you I don't want this one I don't
have to I'll have to force myself
I mean I could do it but I don't have
the patience for it right now
no
please no
I was hoping for today to be relatively
short you know
these kind of streams I
I look for these shorter kind of games
for having some shorter streams every
now and then
so
let's keep it short all right
it's already been two and a half hours
how far am I away Jessica by those
tunnels we saw I feel like we're so far
away from
the the fee finale maybe maybe it'll
finish no need
is that the Companion Cube
is that a companion cube
foreign
oh my God
I never thought I'd see you again I'm so
hungry I want to eat a companion cube
and what is that okay no companion
killed what
we're thinking of portals are we
oh
my God
oh yeah
oh golf is alive
I'm I'm happy to see portal here
yeah I'm in 3D yeah and I was barely
noticeable because even my 2D is so good
it's different oh wait what was the
friend
is it par or something
honestly it's possible with one car
though
ah
one more
poor tiger what the [\h__\h] portal all in
one
what's going on
I'll have to do it with one
almost
no wait
no wait does it want me to use all
portals
ah
what the is does not matter whether or
not I get the the flags
but fail
fail
what
[\h__\h] impossible what the [\h__\h] are you
talking about
no [\h__\h] way
why did I get an immediate fail though
foreign
I think we got to start with the red one
but we want it so that when it arrives
when it comes out this we want this
thing to be there
okay well that's manageable
how long does it take
okay
that was um okay we need to do it when
it's closer maybe when it's
when it passed the red one
yay now you're thinking of golf oh
[Music]
come on
happy happy oh
which where do I go
let's go here
help
[Music]
wait
huh
well I only have one cute monkey can I
multiply myself
oh wait can we listen golf notes we're
so close we can't stop now
are you referencing portal
wait how do I I guess I just have to
stay strong
literally can't do this
bring a box
you say
from where
there's no boxes here
ah from
[Laughter]
I can take ah
we go together
oh wait
come back are you coming back you're
coming back right yeah okay
no no [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] one more
private Landing too oh that's a that's a
riddle within before getting into the
actual game
what's happening
oh it keeps on getting faster I have
portals all over my Cube oh my God
foreign
[Laughter]
oh take some time takes some time but
we'll get in there oh my God
what
it aren't they they're all red ones
wouldn't they all be connected I guess
not is there one right one
oh
man don't need it don't need any of the
pores really if you're just a little bit
oh patient
I'm gonna do it this way
there you go shrink Theory because of
the strings aha a funny one aren't you
I don't need to find it right when I did
it without
told ya I told you it was possible
what what is this
I make I make holes
why would I want also is it a portal
wait this is so confusing
oh I will make one here
and then we
um
stop turning like that
here
perhaps here
yeah
[Music]
oh
and we all so happy about that
didn't we all miss portal
[Music]
it's you know it's really sad like
fruity I finished games that I really
like and then you'll never get that
Feeling Again of playing it for the
first time
but also like I only really want to
stream things once on my Channel I want
to repeat things obviously
but it's also things it's never gonna be
like that again you can't bring that
back anymore it's so sad yeah
you know when I'm I'm never gonna get
that portal experience again is what I
thought but yet here we are getting a
portal experience thank you you thank
you what the gulf oh my God I'm so
grateful oh I feel like I need to send
some super chats to want to go with the
golf they deserve some super chance you
know all the portal fans this is portal
for
this is for free the yo oh we have to
fight to fight them Yo they did this and
they didn't have to they could have like
parodied any other game and yet they
chose to parody The One and Only
what portal
[Music]
I need to write a strongly worded love
letter
after this
hey yo
oh come on
to the developers and Publishers of
course
hello
that reminds me of that one of those
games
yes
it's just scary games
for the folder you have to you know some
of some are thicker walls than others
and takes more more bounces to get rid
of them wow
[Music]
ah bamboozle of course it doesn't go
that way it's it's all these levels are
um the other way around oh
you have to think not with portals but
you have to think like you're on a
handstand
I'm not quite I'm not sure what's going
on to be honest I I say that as if I
knew what's going on but I don't really
know what's going on
should
this is too big foreign
[Music]
I have a feeling
uh for example that one we didn't do
that one I guess I'm really skipping
some levels for rizzos
apparently that's possible
and what the [\h__\h] what's happening
we didn't do that one
wait we did we did not do this one it
looks so familiar
[Music]
I guess we're done okay now we did
yeah
[Music]
um
as much as I love portal I don't really
have the time to go through
all of the but look what about this one
hey what about what that's super hot oh
no no these I already did I already did
those
okay okay
yeah but I don't have time to go for all
of the
all of the things sorry even if I wanted
to do
[Music]
yeah you're moving so fast oh but it
stops
after I move once I can follow me once
uh-huh
yeah
ah lovely game of puzzle as hell
fine
maybe eventually yeah maybe maybe on my
private time people must know the whole
truth tell them tell them yes they must
know the whole truth of takanashikiwawa
is number one super kawaii cute
ah by the way guys
egg I
egg
that was unexpected by the way guys I I
was gonna say oh wait I'm a bread now
what the [\h__\h]
I was gonna say he's moving
away hey come on come back
there you go
you could even go eat one one forever
and staying out flying pan with flying
pun
foreign
sorry um I was saying
um
[Music]
I was saying
let's hit the Jukebox no nothing there
really yeah
and make some sounds though
funny
um I was saying did you guys see
um
Minecraft sports festival has once again
been announced it's that time of the
year
but this time uh
they did not invite everyone but I was
one of the lies
yeah so I'm participating
it's an honor it's gonna be a little bit
of a shitty time for me but I could not
possibly turn it down because I'm
excited I'm excited
I I honestly I don't even know what's
what my role is I just like a long time
ago I was asked only when I participate
in this I'm like yeah
but I didn't know that we were uh you
know not uh part of the teams I'm not
sure what we're doing what our role is
yeah I saw the Savannah team is really
based I want to go into the subello team
but ID and Ian is uh like yeah it's
different from last year we're not
really
not really part of the teams we're
guests so um I don't know how much will
be
only the relay wait that possibly
however means that I can sleep until the
end because the relay would be at the
end no probably probably
that's actually kind of good so I don't
have to wake up so early
and oh only only the relay huh
oh my God what is that oh I was hoping
to play a little bit more than that but
okay at least I get some sleep kind of
see the positive thing about it
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
golf
we'll be done sharing you thank you oh
what's happening where am I huh
oh it took a while oh what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh easy easy
[Applause]
one more
big time too thank you always doing
[\h__\h] well thank you
where is it
um is it there
oh Big Bird
where the [\h__\h] is it
I need to get rid of the birds maybe ah
now I gotta where's the last one I was
looking for the gold Bird
that's me
wow
funny
Chihuahua
oh my first person oh this is all gonna
be first person
oh my God
is that one of the levels we already
played before I wonder just in the first
person oh [\h__\h]
you could turn this into a VR game yo ow
[\h__\h] yeah
[Applause]
oh look again it's actually quite
curious
foreign
oh
I am manageable
he mustard
it would make me nauseous and we are oh
yeah probably now that you say it
probably
we go here
looks like lollipops but it's not his
targets
oh
[Music]
hi Bob
so [\h__\h] cute oh my god oh thank you
thank you I'm not young
I was cuddling with my kitty cats yeah
today while watching has a dragon and
smoothie
she when she was sleeping what the [\h__\h]
is the metal of you
when she was sleeping she had her tongue
out but while I was like holding her
kind of
I wanted to take a picture because she
looked really Derpy I tried but
I was trying to reach my my phone
without uh moving too much otherwise I
would wake her up because she wakes up
so easily
I did actually managed to get a picture
but it didn't turn out so good
unfortunately
because right at the moment when I was
taking a picture she woke up but while
she was waking up she still had the blep
she still had it he was so cute so I got
a picture of her waking up with the blip
oh
wait does it matter if we get a ball in
can it just be me
no okay ah no
no wait this is
golf question mark I guess this is
called oh come on
oh wait what there hey
why can't sometimes loves to me when I
pet him what
what why am I don't really do that
naturally
I guess I mean I think sideways it would
somehow work but I guess let's do
forward first yeah
no it looks sick
no
yo little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I swear to God
come on
yes yes
yo my my hand
the edge of my hand looks really damaged
at this point
[Laughter]
holy [\h__\h]
been putting so much pressure on it
[Music]
my mouse made of spikes no if anything
I'll guess it would be the table that
was made of spikes
oh
why am I a toast
it's almost
I didn't even do all of them okay they
let me go
they let me go
um but
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
oh oh oh can she do it can she defy
gravity
uh at some point I can't like a few
times it works but then ah
somebody kicks me out okay let's go down
I guess maybe it wants me to go down
instead
yep
[Laughter]
but what if I make it up
that's free maximum
point this looks like the portal office
I've I've played too much portal in my
life
even though it's it's really just you
know
one proper playthrough for a per game
uh where are we
yeah
ah interesting
we just need one right
okay
oh no that's fine let's find this one
yeah
easy
oh is there one here
is there is there is there is there oh
that's where it came from isn't it [\h__\h]
go back
oh my my hand hurts
how do I
if I can only do three times how do I
can go down here
[Music]
no no
oh [\h__\h]
no I have to go there
jump jump
finally
oh yeah what are you doing now
[Music]
do I need a ball I need the ball no
ah
[Music]
what about me
are you
you're missing the Y game
you're not speaking
our language properly I don't understand
you I don't know what you're trying to
tell me
you have to speak clearly
[Music]
doesn't really help me does it
now what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay this I think this is really simple
but I'm not getting it
oh
maybe towards the ground makes me jump
higher now
[Music]
a little bit that's it
almost had it
[Music]
okay wait wait wait
oh
thank God that could have been really
annoying
ah
it wants another one now over there all
right got you covered buddy
oh
no why you want to go back only Forward
Thinking No Looking Back
we must go towards a brighter future
right when the title showed up it was
exactly doing that but but but but
what are you doing here oh
wait are we doing a horotoni collection
is it is it all bird so is this just a
weird coincidence and I got the the
turkey
and the chicken
does anyone know who played the game is
it only Birds
or am I just lucky
oh and I got an eye for chickens
and no I'm not a chicken I'm talking
about you guys
you know that
all birds because of golf
words because a lot of golf terms oh why
is that so by the way
let's ask Google
why are a lot of golf terms uh bird
related
in 19th century American slang bird
referred to anyone or anything excellent
wonderful
way like people say cool
people would say that's so Birds but no
way
fruits invented golf I wouldn't believe
you
burden no way by analogy with Bernie and
the term eagle soon thereafter became
common to refer to a score one better
one better than the bird
uh-huh but the eagle is also just a bird
man also by analogy the term Albatross
became common to refer to a double eagle
bird is the one what what what does that
mean what are you what are you telling
me
are you are you joking with me
well now I do want to know if if a bird
invented call First
from the stone and and some scientist
was observing that and was like that
should be a game
yeah
I wouldn't I would believe in
who invented Bowl
shower
while the modern game of golf originated
in the 15th century Scotland the games
ancient Origins are unclear and much
debated that's because
I'm telling you yes
that's why we don't really know
simple as that everybody
ew why are you so disgusting
[Applause]
it was the bird Italia it was
you it's like it's it's tongue why is it
so slimy
yeah and slippery
I know too much
yeah Burns Burns invented life
meatball I would like meatballs now
oh [\h__\h]
oh boy
super meatball oh that's a reference no
no
oh yeah yeah
oh so scary and musical so very scary
and I just can stick to the wall right a
little bit oh
[Music]
oh
I want to land on that thing over there
two metal vibe
[Music]
no maybe I should go differently
oh that's what I want to thank you
[Music]
this is this video is like the Meat Boy
series is that so okay so it must really
be a reference it's a game like this too
like you
stick with your slimy surface
onto other surfaces
yeah oh
I'm having quite a lot of trouble with
it not gonna lie
why can't I not stick to the ceiling do
I not have enough power in my tongue
[Music]
oh
okay okay
[Music]
yay
meaty
a
bangs wow boss fight
what do you mean
I thought I had it all huh
what oh go back what so this one
but they're check marked this one's
checked and this one says
106 but then why is it
uh I need
what okay
okay I was just not hitting that button
properly
oh
[Music]
honey
oh what
wait
oh
don't know how I did that how I thought
of that don't ask me where is the heart
ah
hey
I have to push it away but then
still catch it
foreign
no idea what I was doing
yay
ah we're meant to be together destiny
oh
whoa
[Laughter]
ah the queen of the way
[Music]
Let's see we have the stop stops again
but they won't stop me
I'll just go straight through
Turtles no wait another is supposed to
be like oh
nothing else
oh by the way I know the word Turtle I
just didn't think you know
of course I know the word turtle
during Hollow talk I just you know had a
little bit of a brain empty moment
[Music]
I know that kame means Turtle but when
you like speak a different language when
you're in the middle of speaking a
different language and sometimes when
you switch in between
sometimes it's like a simple word what
does what does love mean but no I will
never know that one anyway
the meaning of love I truly don't
understand and truly don't know that one
[\h__\h] off
the [\h__\h] is the metal with them
What is love
I I I I I I I you guys love me right
I I I I love you
do I
I think I do
in a certain way
and not like I I want to
you know but
different kind of love oh
okay it's not immediately game over
when you get found you just have to
escape the laser all right all right
all right yeah there are many types of
Love mm-hmm do you do you guys love me
do you do you say
you do feel the same
spark me like a flame I know I'll never
be the same oh
do you do
bags I know
I know you I'm just about
it's back
[Music]
why does it make yourself done
one more
I want to be more than just a box oh
part zero
oh we just follow it how about that
but can we do because I have to
oh that worked
are you oh
box
infiltrate and hack the flag
uh-huh
I don't know how we're gonna do that but
okay
oh my God there's so many boxes hello
box friends
[Music]
get out of here oh they respawn oh
endless boxes
I've played myself
[Music]
oh my God
you need to do something about your
squeakiness
so and to get to the bottom
[Music]
but the button is connected with the
toaster now
you whistle
oh yeah
[Music]
you are the chosen box you are really
just the Box still I am much more than
just that
how do we get in though oh do we need
another is there another button on that
side
[Music]
oh my God
shut up but if this box doesn't show up
soon
I'm gonna lose it
shut up shut up I'm gonna get me crazy
foreign
box
thank you
yeah oh
what's the catch
oh ah I have to wait for this one I have
to wait until I'm completely still
are you are you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I know the straps I know
through fans and efficiently well okay
we can ah
that was I could have done it so fast no
get out of there oh yes okay chill chill
chill chill
[Music]
yeah swinger clubs oh funny funny
I don't get it I totally understand
it's like a museum
oh it's slow motion it's
they're combining super hot oh
oh
be careful oh my God they're gonna blow
up the children
maybe I can blow up the children by
doing this because if it's the motion
like this I could not possibly get
caught by that thing ah the kids
oh
yeah oh oh
the cats I heard a cat
[Applause]
oh
ah okay so the golf ball really does not
matter it's about this dude he has to
get through and we will help him with
that
hi kitty cats
oh
nothing can go wrong
I guess we
had quite the evasive skills there
I
don't be a little [\h__\h] why is there a
golden toaster there
this game really likes toasters huh
I haven't used my toaster in a while
maybe I should use it again maybe it
feels neglected
hey yo
no not the tree
so aggressive that's just nature
eliminated onion
uh everything that moves I guess
oh
no oh
yeah I was so close to that one yeah
how do I do my toast how do you toast
what
you mean toasting to toast who would
ever do such a thing who would toast to
toast hmm
I'm always lucky yeah
[Music]
I have a hat
and I make music
is that enough oh it is
foreign
[Music]
ER where are we going where are we going
big caterpillar with a cool hat oh it's
kind of sliver you know it would be cool
if they would somehow bring in Slither
into this game oh
[Music]
there it is
oh
[Music]
thank you
they play around too much no there's not
too much playing what happened
the part of my body fall down
[Music]
though
well I thought I could play
it looks like a sliver mascot like with
the colors I think that's why I thought
of it
[Music]
does it have the same colors the sliver
logo thingy
well I I don't know man I don't know
what I'm doing here
oh
the sauce is ready can I get some more
toast then can I turn it is that how I
turned into a toast before Oh no I can't
get it
seemingly
not
fogs oh yeah fogs was also stretchy
I played it before yeah yeah yeah yeah
Fox cute game cute collabo game always
need those for kuna balls
how far am i this is level four
floor four I feel like I've done more
than four floors so far what the
what what
[Laughter]
is this a reference to that singing game
I don't know maybe not
are they counting down I want is the
last one I was there like 10. oh another
pretty far
all right okay I I accept the challenge
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
my God
[Music]
can help I swear to God
you know who has been praising do you
can't
say I'm fine oh
bird
oh can I have you as a yeah okay can I
help you uh
me
what is orange sounds like a bear me
[Music]
[Applause]
that's funny
okay I was saying um yeah I wrote to me
I'm telling me she really really really
likes doing you and she wants to sing it
but English is so much it's so difficult
what is this oh wait the colors let's do
it in the same order
cover
you know I was really happy
that she said it to me so directly
messages
[Music]
listen I was so happy she said she
really liked it she was really into it
[Music]
oh no oh no no
I
[Music]
am so difficult oh God okay okay
oh
[Music]
finally my random gaming career
has begun
foreign
keyboard it was 100 times easier but
with the mouse
and having to aim like that if I could
just go with the arrow keys like left
right left right that is a million times
easier
it's fast on it
oh nice thing you look it just shoot
straight I don't believe you
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
you're not that easy anymore my friend I
know it
[Music]
I love that game what do you call that
game what's the official name for that
ah
break up space Oh I think I know it by
Space Invaders or so yeah
oh
feeling nostalgic feeling like playing
that game again here we are the game is
serving me all the games that I missed
I have to try to stay down here for as
long as possible because it will
eventually reach me
[Music]
but there's barely up right I'll just go
slowly oh no that doesn't really change
anything but there we
[Music]
go
ah another one of those
it's like cool
oh okay
[Music]
oh
I know angles I'm your angel and I know
angles oh
um
yeah cool
okay this was the other way around
interesting what is this a reference to
kfp apocalypse kfba
are you good bro
how do I play
what let me play
what are you not real
it's again
it's just his nose Maybe
it's not a level hey
oh they're gonna try to come and get me
please don't
I won
you find me now you know you know yes
okay I see you there
that touch you I have to touch it to
open it up oh that's so funny
[Music]
open up
no [\h__\h] idea maybe it's in the middle
maybe it's the same spot
no
here
[Music]
okay
you little [\h__\h] is it behind here
where is it wait is it an intent
what don't go
I'm got scammed worse in behind the tree
this tree
hey what hey what's here
oh you little [\h__\h] oh my God what is
this what is this
what is these
near automata
I don't know when I think of Apocalypse
I think of New York
[Music]
oh
my
God it does the cutest
[Music]
it's a driving range yeah you know those
cars that you charge and they go boom
they go very much from
boom boom more yay
[Music]
why is this little car so [\h__\h]
adorable by the way I never watched the
movie Cars
and I don't think I'm ever interested
[Laughter]
[Music]
I didn't miss out well thank God I
didn't think so I didn't think I was
missing out
working at the car wash
[Music]
when I had an MP3 there when I was like
in June Junior High School this was one
of my favorite songs to listen to on my
MP3 oh my God oh my MP3 player
yeah
another I had an empty free player
what do you mean what
sweet flips facts
I really like my MP3 player it was one
of those that you that they're kind of
like they're about as long as someone's
um pointy finger and
um about as thick as two two pointy
fingers
and on one side you can open them up and
there's a USB stick
um
and then I would put the music on that I
got from you nowhere
you know what I mean
from from iTunes
[Music]
family broke as [\h__\h]
can't afford iTunes
[Music]
who knows what do we ever know we can
never be sure
sometimes they hide their muscles oh can
we do a trick
get rewarded for now they killed me off
[Music]
crazy trick thank you
I wanna I wanna voice pack with the
babies
is this GTA reference
I I'm continuously wondering what this
this one is referencing to the book of
course it's not GTA but you know
foreign
[Music]
Micro Machines is that a game
I don't know that one I need to check it
out do they also make the cute baby that
sounds
if not then I don't want to play it
I need my baby
it's Micro Machines doesn't but now I
need to look it up
I am looking up everything today
micro
machines
wait is it not an actual game is it just
you know the cars
oh
wait was was it ever a computer game or
is it just the cars
what was the Gameboy
there's a game for them
[Music]
it doesn't work like this
is there a playthrough from PewDiePie or
soda that I can watch
you get a feeling for it
[Music]
I'm gonna marry this car
no
[Music]
yeah
oh you said I am I am I'm I'm dying of
cuteness because of this car
this is my new ocean
now you guys don't need to do that
you're already cute of your chicken
noises
yeah yeah like you you don't need to
make these noises
are we racing now oh yeah
are they gonna use items on me oh my God
that would be so funny if this was an
actual uh Mario Kart reference where are
the items where the bananas where are
the mushrooms where's the Bullet Bill
who's gonna use the Bullet Bill where's
Rainbow Road
[Music]
Mommy
so baby sounds like he's laughing like
oh
that was really Micro Machines
nice
that's freaking oh was I drifting oh my
God what am I oh
that is oh wow there's a strong Micron
machine oh oh I can I can still
um move it while oh [\h__\h] okay I thought
it was only no once but not you can oh
move it
well oh my God
oh my God
we're going backwards
get get up
okay easy easy
oh there's still something okay
monster gold that is a muscle car
oh oh oh oh well no that's not happening
it's not happening oh oh wait what what
is happening oh I thought we were
failing it
even that's the lotion going on
let's get oh an hour
oh we can jump too this place
look at my sick tricks man
and
another one come on
and last
Perfect Landing beautiful Landing but it
will be difficult for this single really
thin bike oh there we go so it hits the
goal but no
it is beautiful like a bunny hop oh
and we push the button
[Music]
yo I had so much fun at the last karaoke
yeah I don't want to spam karaoke but we
have to do it again
not not too
not too much later
I sang my heart out for you guys
oh oh
let's try to not touch those explosive
knees oh
what is this a reference to I wonder
[Music]
I thought I thought I would make it
dad's detection was nice I was um you
know I was looking for songs and then at
some point after finding one specific
song I don't know which one it was I was
like
kind of losing more more calm jazzy
songs like that so then I went for the
Jazz section in kada fun and they had a
lot of
um
those jukebox instrumentals
so I had that one and then combined with
um
another song I thought oh you know what
we can make this into a whole section
how about that
and then I was like okay anyway if I if
we do this into a whole section then I
kind of want to have like a a proper
setup for it too
oh oh fun oh they helped me now
and so I I made a little layout I was
stuck in a TV
but it gave a good atmosphere I think
create the right mood
to get you guys into the mood
the Jazzy mood
so of course on Twitter mine do you like
jazz was a hint
maybe it wasn't super Jazzy like someone
I don't know if you can really call all
the Jazz but you know you know it wasn't
a jazz
um section it was kind of fun
so you know and then it was more than
just for me it was more than just Jazz I
wanted to go
and do like
kind of
just just old I wanted to have old vibes
whatever that means
classic retro
whatever
you know what I mean
hello why are they blocking everything
in the way
Catherine opening vibes
Catherine the game oh look at me
oh don't [\h__\h] with me I will catch you
oh
[Music]
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa chill
chill chill is this how it's gonna be in
the levels too
oh no not necessarily
what what happened
oh
oh as I guess as long as we're not
leaving the screen
we're fine
easy win for me
okay let's go I'll wait
are we already ready to press the button
already
oh no that's a different button okay
it gets stuck all the time
[Music]
[Applause]
huh oh
thank you
it is
here listen please
[Music]
ah more chicken please
no more please
thank you
don't make dinner out of my chickens I
didn't give you permission no no I
decided that oh
there's some
imposters and mogus
now only the
no what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] why is it because the duck
left the screen
oh what what's happening
the duckling may not reach the goal huh
oh
none
no no
oh what the [\h__\h]
and that's so difficult
that one on the right side is so
dangerous
oh there's always full powered what the
hell is going on
what the [\h__\h] are you doing go away
[Music]
okay you go here
and then
hey
hey and raise your call though they're
not even allowed to leave the screen
and oh I'm rage pointing this [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h]
yeah [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] no no
I refuse
can't play with me like that no I'm not
a toy
I don't know whatever that was oh are we
cooking an egg oh
mother
[Music]
gently I know how to cook an egg
is ready
um now now we're kind of slippery
Flubber
one more I want to play it again
in four oh didn't we just do it in two
or like free maybe we played around a
little bit but I feel like I can totally
do it
thank you
so now just jump down easy
[Music]
I'm not gonna do the next one though
two are free ah we're missing this one
bye
oh we have to make both of them rage
oh but look
[Music]
ah one of those elements that decided
now for once and for all which came
first the egg came first apparently
it was a challenge I didn't realize it
was a challenge I thought I had to get
both of them there now we know we kind
of decided history there unintentionally
I wasn't that wasn't what I wanted to do
that was not my intention
ah
more eggs no wait what's going on
I can't do anything
debugged
oh wait
like what
oh yeah
no way there we go we'll take it thank
you thank you thank you
Smart Cookie answer
oh similar
oh
[Music]
can we make it through
oh God quick just keep on keep keep on
going and then how do I uh no okay let's
try to focus on the other ones
how
oh
I almost made it hi
hi no
quick quick
way so much momentum
Apparently one made it okay we'll go
I'll take it
a wind is a win
my chat stopped oh there we go now it's
bad
the wind is a win that was funny
one one wins everybody wins
what's going on
but not to a bank
I didn't even click anywhere there's one
made it through once again all right
this feels kind of longer than the
others have I just been doing more
levels in this one
unintentionally
no there we go that's the end actually
[\h__\h] help
what that
go
let's go we're almost to God guys
huh
we are we surely are
we surely are
what
what's happening
wait why is it not over yet like here
this area of course it's so long
two
it's down here
oh that's blocked off wow wait we went
from three to two never mind never mind
okay this is fine this is fine
that was free now we're into okay
I'm back
bye okay oh my God we can talk here and
then go to that level
hi
I'm crab oh and spider crab
spider crab oh oh I have to go that way
okay what game is this
find a crime spinal grounding oh
no I don't mean this water golf no no
it's not gold it's not gold no you can't
fool me
foreign
there was not even a golf ball there
what is this
nothing
why is there so much trash in this
[\h__\h] ocean
who put that there huh who was it
oh even oil spilled what the [\h__\h]
um
give a magnification you feed him for a
day teach a man to golf and board
to hate
oh yeah
oh
the fish
oh nice sand sand castle
good effort
oh
oh what what what what what
micro plastic yummy
yeah my cats would love that
send my cats to this place they will eat
up all the oceans just kidding and
please stop them I have to stop them too
these little [\h__\h]
[Music]
they tried they like start nibbling on
plastic and then I'm like chocolates I
told you no blessing and absolutely
take her away from the plastic oh
oh
you're gonna talk here wonderful
Yum Yum Yum plastic
oh two out of three
[\h__\h] up I need to go to a different
game let me take this boat perhaps it's
nice there's many boats oh oh my that
was my boat it's just dark there hold
off
I have the same problem with my cats
yeah I know cats always come with some
kind of
issue
some you know they they try to attack
um electrical outlets
for some reason some attack cables they
try to eat cables so mine thankfully
don't do any of that
but my kitty cats they like to sometimes
if they find plastic somewhere
I start nibbling it I don't think they
ever like properly ate it thank God
because I always stop them in time or
hide I hide the plastic now I've learned
my lesson so
I try to not keep the kind of plastic
they like around and there's a specific
type too that they like
for that kind of exercise
it's the Wild West
yeah I don't know what are you doing it
obviously doesn't taste good but I guess
they like the material
my parent cat likes to apply Furniture
yeah thankfully mine don't do that
either
they don't claw Furniture it's not like
I ever had to teach them not to do it
they just buy the get-go were good
babies Oh first
oh this is not golf
this is not cool
[Music]
I need a coffee on them what is golf
ah
it's some oh okay I guess that's golf at
some point you really question
yourself
what
is
golf
what exactly
I felt like I heard a meow
maybe it was in the bgm
it was in the bgm right probably
probably I hope so
wow what no Wild Wild West
oh
okay I'll turn it back around if I was
you partner Sal I'll bunker up in these
parts what does that mean
why are you talking to me what even
easily
[Music]
oh my God it moves like that
don't tell me this is a reference to
that game
it looks like that game
oh oh my God
getting over it I think was it yeah I
moved exactly like that although I never
played that game but I think that's what
it looks like
it this must be a reference
is
[Music]
don't hate the player
hate the game
so true
don't hate the YouTuber
hate the real life
oh what
[Music]
what's this
excuse me
am I
what do you want from me am I making
myself bigger with the cacti
being a hard time hard time turning are
we good enough okay
ah
I should play that
I should what there's like so many game
references hello
I mean I don't know what this would be
but I'm sure it is something
I know I know I know what yeah yeah it
looks like this
I think I know what you're talking about
[Music]
right now
what's happening no no I got so far oh
the like seeing the other horse
coming at me certainly dying
kind of scared me freaked me out as a
fellow horse
I thought oh is this my destiny please
no spare me
[Music]
oh money
okay that horse definitely is that holy
[\h__\h]
oh my God
why is this one so long these first
levels are supposed to be easy
well I think we've reached
up oh no
yes
yes horse on the train
what is that a York a little pun
I don't understand
how many do I need on here
there's so many oh zero out of five oh
this area needs zero okay okay oh shoot
to
it it's uh ah the other way around
Opposite Day
oh oh oh more shooting okay
oh oh God oh God
[Music]
ah what do you call these things that
you turn and then they make sounds
old gold
laughs
let me think about this one
wait no makes no sense what
ah yes
Music Box in Japanese they call it
all the gold why do it's like an English
word
but why is it not called all goal in
English then where did I get that from I
wonder
oh he's spinning
or go ah wait
is it from German language then because
we say wagon
in German in German and in German we say
[Music]
it's bad
a Dutch oh okay well in German we say
the same thing
foreign
this is how they do it in the wild west
is this their favorite pastime
so close higher or a little lower Maybe
[Music]
[Applause]
spit on the tip
oh my God
it's roulette it's roulette
it's spit roulette
spit roulette guys which way do we go
okay no playing
yeah
almost
no
okay let's be through
I want to move on
we're done we did we did the DVD
[Music]
we did that part oh it needs four parts
none oh no probably not this one
okay let's continue
I'm afraid the floor here okay
oh sure and horse
[Music]
oh
shooting ah smooth okay
we're welcome here now
foreign
two more
supposedly that should be the last boss
right probably
short stories is that you have [\h__\h]
hell man I guess no super chantos I'm a
dice that's dungeons
huh
because there's a flag on there yeah
yeah
no
oh that's cute that's that's cute
roulette we're left for a look for real
oh can we get it on the turquoise one oh
oh do we just have to okay house wins we
just have to touch the flag I guess
a fun fun cute cute cute
[Music]
two other four
this is one this is one
if we ever get in there
okay
as always when ah
yes
it jumps automatically when it touches
it nice
okay
I believe
oh now go go towards the goal the words
to go let's say
yay
the show horse now dead because show
horse went somewhere
somewhere into the abyss
let's say what the computer says
if you find yourself in the hole the
first thing to do is stop digging
hmm
well I mean what that sounds as if they
dug it themselves but
perhaps they fell into a hole someone
else created they weren't digging in the
first place huh
but anyway tell tell the Trevor tell
Trevor that she shouldn't have dug so
deep
on it can I go over there like so I
can't
hear no okay which one am I missing
the one on the island probably
do I seriously have to get my boat
ah
foreign
[Music]
I guess like it's going to be rough once
I finish it I did really originally not
expect to finish
I can't enter from here can I yeah I did
not expect to ever finish GTA
I thought you know when I started it I
thought okay let's play it for like a
one or two of free streams fun
I surely want
to be finishing this not my type of game
probably I didn't know
but hell I've been enjoying it so I've
been
on my way to finishing it
the [\h__\h]
isn't that
I can go down okay
um so once you're finished dad damn
gonna be sad and we finished another
game like that
but I mean there's so many GTA games
why did I do that
the thing is as I said before we only
really I'm stuck
oh there you go I'm gonna really stop
that we can play this one GTA 5 I don't
know about others
I know people ask about yo I'm cheating
people ask about San Andreas and so on
but I'll see what I can do but it must
be a reason why we don't have perms for
those yet
do I have to go back with the boat now
oh oh can I let go
okay whatever I'll go back to the boat
maybe maybe there's another on the other
side like parallel
that I can only reach with the boat then
I would like to go now before I'm gonna
get mad later oh no probably not
just I don't know I already visited
all right
today online collab yes yes yes yes I
have to get the PlayStation version
though
but what was that about you know
PlayStation PlayStation free GTA online
or so is closing down what was it was
that it
was that the thing
so as long as I get it on um PS5
okay
okay okay okay
there's no cross play I get on PS4
oh okay I'll ask them which version they
have
Amazon and Miku Senpai
why does this one lead to
ah oh this one oh I'm just missing one
[Music]
oh oh
up up
[Music]
what what
I make them
oh there you go up
what
okay let's go back
maybe we can take off like an airplane
you believe that airplanes tonight oh
never mind
can we get more
no
oh
oh okay let's go
shooting stars I got really good right
now dinner right now oh dinner right now
wow
I'm gonna use dinner right now
I have to cook it myself
I already ate my frozen food last night
so today I'm cooking myself but it
shouldn't be too difficult
here we are
oh
fun easy this is really the last one oh
[\h__\h] oh sorry ah
okay
no okay
don't go [\h__\h]
I'm recording does it react to where I'm
going I felt I felt like it this is my
favorite really
[Music]
oh
come on go go Cuba Go
row row fight the golfer
that's it
you said like what's what's next
money money oh
what happened here
secret tunnel
not so secret though
someone tried to escape with the money
what's going on
what is this
oh no the golfers are doing experiments
with humans
wait that's not a human we all end up in
a hole
I didn't know everybody ends up in a
grave if that's what you mean you think
you're very smart huh but now there's a
lot of people not only nowadays it's
been a long many many centuries
people like to bring themselves and make
them into ashes which me me as a phoenix
I look at that and I'm like new here
you can't even revive
turn yourself into ashes you can't even
revive yourself
[\h__\h] stupid look at me
try to do it like me sometime huh
oh
what's happening
for the computers
and then
what does that mean
what's the meaning of this
I have to go more often okay
foreign
is that possible
where
that reminds me why did I hear this
where did
that reminds us something where I'm
wondering
how did I where did I
okay
um I'm not gonna say what I'm thinking
of because I'm weirding myself out oh
oh it's another one you don't want to
fight me you have to
do is you're running out of ideas
I'm just all kinds of animals you ran
out of ideas didn't you
idea
lemon Brew
this is a hot dog though that's not an
animal huh
I just recognized it Emma
isn't there like a cute song where they
sing something like that
it was it wasn't at home
that's so grim
that's not a hot dog
what is that
obviously a question mark
Google Translate
was this
what a banana
you fooled me
ah it's one of those okay
how much Roundup
[Music]
we're free once again my achievement
says computer zero and zero so that was
the last one oh yeah I need to keep on
reaching me through I I I'm just an
object to you [\h__\h] you too
more than just an object I'm more than
just a golf ball I can be anything I
don't necessarily have to be only golf
holy [\h__\h] why is there
blood
what even is Turkey
they just go on so I'll be staying here
oh
[Music]
oh no
I have to return
it's a challenge baby
oh God
chihuahua has to survive what will
happen to KFC if I don't know
my gosh
bye Mommy
would I normally would have seen like
more trophies that I collected or was
that Turkish is always there are these
fake too
come on touch it touch it touch it
oh yeah okay okay
oh because of the tubes oh maybe it's
good though
maybe we don't mind oh perhaps we don't
mind that development
okay all the flags are fake remember
that
all the flags are fake
imposter Flags
oh no oh no
oh what's happening
is this real
No Maybe
maybe it is
can this one be trusted
what do you think guys
should I go for it should I go for it
should I golf for it
desperate puns for Desperate Measures
oh
well where am I who am I
m m time ago
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I see eggs can bear golf balls oh
it's just trying to attack you
with my ticking egg bombs no wait for me
oh
you need to be faster I need to be
faster
can I be faster I have to be faster
there we go
hey
what what's next what do you got next
come on let me move let me move oh now
I'm gonna talk about an aliens
alien skeletons
the aliens have infiltrated the golf
course
wait it's all the dead children never
mind they're just skeletons they look
like aliens a little bit to me but never
mind they're the skeletons of all the
children that I had ah oh
all the children that I kicked down the
mountains [\h__\h] which is really just I
guess
the
consequences of my own actions I should
have never played golf
what happened
did I do it
one more
thanks for coming I don't know what
would happen if I were to fall off or
too long maybe nothing in this case
[Music]
we're boss fight restart from beginning
Bumblebee
oh that was easy
what's next computer
you have no choice but to give in huh
why are you going that way
oh ah it's like checkpoints okay okay
are you you're going that way but I
can't
[\h__\h] wait I need to get used to the bike
again where the [\h__\h] am I okay
restart
[\h__\h] why why are we signing off that
Cliff let me let me like go back maybe
with the bike
and then oh no oh
okay oh yeah that's this this is good
going back once was a good idea hi
[Music]
where's it I've been too fast I was so
fast now it's the fact no no
no no no no no no
yes
can I please turn around no
hmm
oh why are we standing so close to the
cliff
it's hard to make a jump ah
okay okay this is it this is it okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
where are they where are they no go go
go I'm too fast again
[Applause]
hello
oh maybe oh are they all the way at the
end by now
and why did I [\h__\h] it up it was going so
well
oh
ah There It Is Well maybe it was bucked
honestly because now it's here
oh
this looks like the last stage
egg is ready
human
come from Ink
when click on enter
human make egg
and for me come human
why how
peanut John
tentacles stop please
it's your way of collabing with me
frog Detective
this looks like a
oh disgusting I'm not ready to be a
bragan you have to wait till next week I
know you want a frog week I know I know
I know I know I teased it I know it
taste is already on my on my anniversary
I'm sorry
how can I get faster
[Music]
Wind Waker Whirlwind flashbacks
and for all early release yeah this is
takanashi kiwawa is Frankie Wawa oh
oh I feel like I was supposed to catch
that one but I
would have had apparently had to get
much closer
it went good Duty
[Music]
more tentacles
tentacles
you're making a a wall
of tentacles
see what do you do
yes yes you're my friend I think you're
my
girl I
[Music]
go get him I know it I know yeah this
boss fight is so low bunches
oh man [\h__\h]
are we restarting from the beginning or
do I only still have that one hit
I hope that oh
hey a Walmart Buffet
I'm sorry bud
I mean I'm enjoying it and I like the
mechanics but it feels a little budget
oh man they need to spam those a bit
more often because otherwise I have to
wait ages until next chance
or they need to make the hitbox bigger
it's a bit difficult
foreign
[Music]
no I really wanted this reset or what
happens when I die once
do I have like literally in zero
HP
and we got one hit if the one from
before counted then we had two hits
[Music]
oh oh too well when's that the first and
another horse normally boss fights need
free hits
so let's see if the third hit counts
as the fern hits
[Music]
no oh yes
yes I think so
oh we're entering the Frog now
oh okay it's not over yet
what
[Music]
I swear
I'm Spiderman with a Spider-Man
reference let's go where are they even
this is the ceiling
where is the ceiling oh wait is that
enough yeah
spits me out come on frog oh wait I am
the Frog
this is a perfect segue to frog week but
unfortunately this is just the beginning
of the actual current week
should have played it at the end of the
week it would have been perfect
[Music]
golf is good again golf is healthy again
golf is happy again
everybody is welcome to play golf again
oh the final one this one are we gonna
actually play golf
it's a logo thank you for playing hockey
we hope you enjoyed it we really enjoyed
making it we're just a small team oh but
you did a good job where everyone made a
bit of everything oh everyone involved
the favorite games maybe so many people
helped us oh that's so wholesome
thank you for helping us I didn't do
[\h__\h] I mean I guess I gave it quite a
bit of
um eyes yeah
really thank you you're welcome if you
oh there are more golf experiments to
explore
remember to check back in once in a
while we might not go walk away when do
you want to go let us know
I mean I would expect it already to be
in there but what about Minecraft
or or holoca
Tales of arise
I don't know how you would make that
kind of impossible but it's your
challenge now yeah whole life whole life
please whole life golf
[Music]
whatever that entails obviously not not
normal golf because golf does not even
exist golf is Just an Illusion
the end question mark
ah 4 100 Strokes in four hours
wow that's about the fastest Strokes per
hour
oh I only have what 55 out of 50 what
does that mean
[Music]
what
ah ah you get achievements for how many
percentage so I did that I definitely
got over 50 but I did not get a 75
whatsoever
ah and my trophies are just the
important
wait I have the duck too
I got the most of our new ones
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] did I actually get
these the origin of horotoni together
I could have had any other trophy but I
got these ones
[Music]
no one else here just these couple of
birds
[Music]
yeah it's faint oh
wow wow wow all right that was fun guys
thank you very much for watching the
golfing stream we were totally legit
goldfish today
as to whether or not I wanna choose this
as my career path I think
I think I golfed enough for a whole
lifetime
I wonder how many strokes a professional
golf player has in his whole lifetime
because I think 4100 is at least average
if not more than average for a
professional golf player in his whole
career lifetime
did you even go I I did very much even
golf
I mean I mean the ghost jokes the hits
so I definitely was true
I definitely
[Music]
um golfed enough for a lifetime yeah
don't say that it's so dark oh my God
what stroke is enough
holy [\h__\h]
you're over like thank you
[Music]
did I do the funny I said comedian
all the goldfish be looking at me and
like damn if this girl enters our career
path and we're done for thank God she
decided to end it quickly
I did the funny but I'm done with the
funny and dancing with the funsie
it was a bit fun
too bad they made no joke about that in
the game or I just missed it
yeah golf was invented by birds you're
welcome everybody you're welcome
for you know creating this hell of a
game
which is way more than just gold
life is golf golf is life
bird is live Chihuahua is life life is
Chihuahua
that's it
so
I will leave it at that I'll see you
tomorrow for
[Music]
this time I hope I hope I get some of my
French Bros yeah French Bros and French
girls
[Music]
mm-hmm yeah I'm excited to eat some
snacks but I think this necklace is
really old and they gave me a notice
that it's been delayed and they
apologize for it
um actually I think the snack box is the
one that got sent to me once but was
returned because I apparently didn't
pick it up but I didn't even know it was
there
um
oh I think it arrived maybe while I was
in Korea and then you know while when I
came back it was already gone
uh so there might be some expired snacks
in there who knows but I hope that they
checked it before sending it back a
second time to me
but we've had some I think we've had
some one or two expired snacks before so
well I'll have to check every expire
expiration date closely this time
because the box is pretty old by now
[Music]
is
character
ew that's disgusting I don't wanna I
don't think there's gonna be cheese in
there guys there's normally just you
know like crackers and chocolate and all
that kind of stuff
are you coming back to France but how
about France comes to me like what the
[\h__\h] why do I always have to go why
don't
should come to me
I'm just kidding I don't know I mean
next is Italy and then in Japan
so I'll be busy for the next couple
months and you know I also don't like
spam travel too much but who knows maybe
maybe sometime in 2023 I might go again
who knows yeah
[Music]
so inconsiderate right what the [\h__\h]
yeah
he's always welcome to tell me are you
okay Wawa let's go here and there and
I'll be there and instantly but so far
so far maybe she's still settling down
but half a month
half a month
half a year is over so quickly
done so fast
I feel like it's already been like a
month or so
I think
[Music]
Australia have space for 1.4
1.42 million
is that how many people live in Paris
sure we have space Maybe on the
mountains
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey it was such a weird guess from me I
was like okay how [\h__\h] far off am I
wait is it
2.161 million or 2
161.
is that a Thing 2 000 no that I never
heard two thousand million before that
would be billion no
um
I know I know
checking with you guys just make sure my
chickens have other brain cells warmed
up and they shut up shut up shut up shut
up
[Music]
foreign
and
then
yeah okay
[Music]
and in Germany we say
um
today's stream was brought to you by
takanasi kiwawa in 3D
Wow
Come on good night
[Music]
thank you