thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
hi
[Music]
do you guys like my war helmet
I uh copied this from Cali
this is the peace helmet okay
obviously
[Music]
and I can't
my hat is uh currently stuck to my head
so
I can't remove it right now for right
now
and rest is open but I tried to click on
it and now it's not responding
hmm
the hat and the helmet it's for Extra
Protection you know actually some people
do wear like little hats underneath
their helmet to like protect their head
from the helmet so while the helmet
protects everything else the Hat
protects me from the helmet do you see
something appearing on the screen like
randomly like a little line
I I don't know if maybe it's just my
screen you see that
dude we're gonna turn off DVR mode
[Music]
I turned it off rebrush refresh
and
still waiting on Rust
do its thing I should have launched it
before I went to go have soup but I got
really distracted when I went to my
kitchen and I saw my saltwater fish tank
and my anemone turned all like kind of
black looking and bruised and I think
it's because the salinity in my tank was
too high
so I had to do a quick water change and
do a lot of testing the parameters and
stuff there it is
a long stop
don't look
anyways yeah the anemone is already
looking better
already looking better today
so today in Rust now that it's loading
don't worry it's there it's there
today in Rust my goal is to take
everything down scrap it
scrap what I can
and I'm going to be building a base
another base but this time with the sole
intention of it being a Bastion you know
what I mean like a Bastion Bastion
Bastion is that the right word Bastion
a a tower of of snipe
a Bastion of Hope a tower of Hope now
that Cyrus is saying mine is will be the
uh bathroom Nerf Bastion yeah yeah yeah
you know it's not just the OverWatch
character's name it's a real word okay
look it up look it up
uh the Tower of Power yeah I'm not sure
am I taking down the Derby no I'm gonna
leave that up uh in case anybody wants
to mess around with it and I I left the
cars in there I just took off like the
car's attachments I just left them Bare
Bones but they still have engines and
they still run
uh so yeah I'm gonna build probably like
a two by two
Tower how what is the sky limit in Rust
does anybody know
yeah my Fortress of Solitude exactly
yeah I was thinking about upgrading one
of my cars into like a tank or something
so my goal today is getting as many
scraps as I can getting as much metal
fragments as I can researching things
for the next rest
server I don't know if that many people
are gonna be playing rust again maybe I
missed my opportunity for some things
but I'll prepare anyways
build a moat I wish you could but I
don't think you can
my mic is weird what's wrong with it
is it the oh it's the fan huh
I can't even try the
video sound cancellation but I can turn
off my fan wait is it on
I think it's off oh there it goes I'll
turn it off one second
okay my computer fan though is just like
loud on its own but here I'll move this
microphone closer to me is that better
sorry I didn't join the server before
most of the end seem to want to play
next season cool
I wonder if there will be anybody new
because I was telling uh crony that she
should try playing she might like it
um
let me just do something really quick
hahaha
Granny's gonna join really next season
cool
the crony baloney
I never heard I don't think I've heard
that one before crony baloney
data is gonna play more oh nice and ID's
Gonna Keep playing cool
will I go full Mad Max Raider
yeah well on my car I have a storage
um unit on it now like a little not unit
what's the word storage module yeah
it looks silly
what do you mean
all right let me see maybe there's a
different hat let me try
let me see what I can do
I tried to get this hand to fit over my
own hat but it's a little scuffed
hey
ah
dude
what the
what the frick
oh
wait
[Music]
um
yeah this is good okay I'll let you guys
see now
it
what do you guys think
new upgrade
upgraded upgraded
oh I wish I could attach a laser
I don't look like a clown or anything do
I
maybe I should put my Cape back on
maybe that won't look so weird then
[Music]
there we go
it comes out way too much as you can
tell it looks like I'm in the middle of
flying trying to trying to fly
I'm so dangerous
it's spawning the world oh my God I'm
almost in
I really like this underwater base
that's on the screen I know it's blurry
so it's hard for you to tell
but it's an underwater base like how do
you even can you even build an other
underwater base or is this just like the
lab that you can explore because
building underwater sounds like a huge
pain in the ass because at least in
Minecraft you have like a Magic Helmet
that lets you breathe underwater but in
Rust you actually need oxygen
you can build underwater Oh God
has built over the water oh over the
water
yeah I wish I could build like over like
oh I had this idea because well
I don't know if anybody's watching
Cali's stream last night but I found
this item where it's a reactive Target
so when you shoot it
it does like
[Music]
um
it can trigger something right so
wouldn't it be cool if you could have
like um
you could shoot the react to Target and
we could have like a dunk tank
a dunk tank and then
it would like drop the person into the
water and then they die and drown or
maybe uh instead of a dunk tank it's
like
um
a minefields tank where like uh they get
dropped down onto like uh one of those
mines proximity mine
and then it explodes a spike
yeah or Spike
a pit full of bears I don't even think
you can catch Bears because they would
constantly like respawn even if you did
catch them it would despawn I bet
I'm ready just waiting
2 000 prefabs left in the load
so yeah like I said before what I'm
gonna do is uh gather all of my extra
items besides like weapons and stuff and
condense them scrap them
um get as many scraps as possible
research some things build my tower of I
don't know it needs to name a tower
Tower of Watson the Watson Tower
Warson war war Tower gonna tweet
yeah
all right I'll do while we're waiting
I have a cup that's in front of my other
monitors to try to see oh now we load in
now it loads in okay
foreign
tweeted let me uh link the art really
quick
we're finally in
oh yes I just had some soup before this
Stream So my hiccup a little bit because
I'm trying to eat it fast
foreign
[Music]
okay I'm ready
let us unblur
all right and it's nighttime and rest is
mute wait I can't hear anything
can I I hear it I hear it okay
all right we'll turn on the lights for
now now this part's gonna be pretty
boring I'm not gonna lie I'm just gonna
take some stuff
um I'm saving saw blades so that I can
get wood
um I can build a chainsaw
which I've already researched the game's
muted
okay okay how about now wait
you guys can hear right
all right so I'm scrapping stuff I'm
gonna say that in this Barrel right here
is gonna be stuff that I'm keeping to
transfer over to my
war base
oh I have too much stuff
all right wait wait let me transfer this
is where I put like my important stuff
like uh gunpowder these thingies and
this and my scripts oh my God I have
quite a lot of scraps
okay I no longer need anything like
solar panels or anything wow
I don't know I should keep it just in
case maybe I should build my new base
first and then decide like what I'll
need or what I won't
one thing I know for sure is that I want
I want like one of those walls like one
of those barriers
hold on I think I have to
have to research it or not to find an
intent tree
yeah I want some of these high external
wooden wall
uh well I guess this makes sense let's
see uh 400 total
all right
this is this a wise thing to spend this
is wise thing to spend my research on hi
everybody why are there so many people
saying hi it's because it's because I
tweeted you came from Twitter thank you
for stopping by today in Rust I'm
preparing for war and that means
destroying to rebuild to destroy
worse complicated okay
uh
okay
so go to Tech Tree
I think this is a good thing to spend my
scrap on or research this this this this
this this
and this
aha
I mainly just want this thing because I
want to build a little wall around my
tower
I think
hold on let me take a look
oh because I kind of just want to build
like a really tall tower and snipe from
it but I'm kind of worried
that
it's all gonna fall down
so I'm gonna build it out of yeah
there's stone wall I think it's in
the workbench too and look I can build
flame turrets
maybe I'll put a bunch of flame turrets
around my thingy oh yeah hold on let me
remove this
sorry
what
um
I wish I could go there we go
all right uh the wall there's the garage
door kind of want it
is it better to put this over because I
was thinking about making the sheet
metal walls
make Four Towers so they're like decoy
Towers
maybe I'll make um five but then I'll
put mine in the middle or something
what if I do four towers and I connect
them with a bridge no I don't think they
have a bridge huh they don't have like
anything like a plank here's the stone
walls uh so I'm almost there actually it
would be cheaper to just oh no wait
yeah I'm almost there
why didn't say 650 require oh because
the stone wall by itself
but finding So Many Stones sounds like a
pain like it's always such a pain to
find Stones all right well I have a car
I guess it's not the big deal oh what do
you guys think the wooden walls or the
stone walls
go to bed in each Tower oh smart smart
a cobblestone generator okay okay
yeah wood is easier but
everybody says Stone
all right all right
let us research wait um I have my scraps
never mind
crafting oh no I always do this open
Tech Tree
large water catcher
small oil refinery this will be good for
when I start my automobile business on
the next server
and then
okay
let me put some stuff away now we're on
a hunt for stones but let me organize
all of my stuff first
is this the
I think this is my current key so I'm
gonna keep that
um
trying to think things describe I want
to keep the smoke grenades this guy can
scrap this seems like a good gun so I'm
Gonna Keep it this can be scrapped this
that's here this I'm keeping to build a
chainsaw
all right now I'm gonna
move stuff over hold on let me make a
bunch of gunpowder
because I have a ton of charcoal to use
wait what do you guys know what I can
use this for oh for excavator
how do I use this
what offers little to no security
it's a good point wait this isn't what I
wanted
it's just not what I wanted
a really good rifle okay nice
on my mixing table I think I scrapped it
dang did I really
is it in my inventory
oh [\h__\h] I think I already scrapped it
because I was taking stuff away from the
Derby where I had it
it's a dig site uh
I wonder if I can build a mixing table
because I wanted to mix all that
gunpowder I mean I have 900 already so I
don't really need it but
mix what was that I just saw the screen
flash
damn it I don't have it
I mean I don't really need it right
I don't think I need it
or is it anyways
a reactive Target
I do want that for the next time but
this will be unlocked right all the
stuff that I unlocked so I can just get
to it easier if I wanted to use it for
something next time
a mixing table
don't go
all right here
okay table
and mixing table I'll just build one for
now and then scrap it
excuse me
what I need 100 Stones metal fragment
okay I have that
foreign
of the day
all right now I'll put this away for now
all right things that I'm Gonna Keep
I might need to build a battery or solar
panel so keep five of these I think
that's like the maximum I'll need a bit
oh that's what I meant to do I meant to
swap them
maybe I'll keep six
seems like a good number okay I'll keep
that scraps megaphone that might be
important
bullets pumpkins for eating
Callie's water gun will remain safe with
me this I'm gonna scrap camera
I don't know I don't you guys think I
should have a camera on my very
short-term base or no you can rewind the
video I turned that thing off
gunpowder
[Music]
my gun
nail gun to be recycled to be recycled I
put down this thingy again
all right crafting gun powder
yeah you gotta refresh the Stream
need camera for auto turret
I don't know how to connect that though
I don't even think I have a turret the
only thing I have is a shotgun trap
all right let me collect some more
things for scrappage
let me start up here because I have a
ton of stuff up here
and I have always electrical stuff that
I can take off and scrap
although some stuff I can't move like
the windmill the seconds grab
I'm not going to use this this season
subscribe this we have another camera
another rifle I'm gonna keep all of this
stuff this I don't really want this but
it does provide a lot of
well I'll keep it just in case
all right explosives everything I'm
gonna keep all of this
Zelda C4
yeah I could set traps
where can I research the bear trap is
that here
it might be useful
I want to snipe people and then when
they approach me
then they'll get caught by my trap sorry
keep doing this I keep trying to go to
Tech Tree did I just go to crafting okay
um
land mines I have some but oh there it
is
to research all of this
total 295 scraps this is what the scraps
that are meant for anyways right now all
I have 76 left
what I thought I had way more would they
where'd it all go
is this finished already
500 gun powder
added
right the stone walls they were
expensive
okay
ah
all right I think I'll start
okay I don't need this button this is
the scrub
cameras to keep for now possibly
what else to scrub oh I'm gonna put this
away
uh-huh
thanks stick with me to scrap this
thingy
this thingy this wheel
uh actually I'm Gonna Keep The Wheel
because maybe it'd be funny if like
somebody approaches my base I'll say
uh I don't know if I should kill you or
not let me consult the wheel and then
I'll spin the wheel and it'll be two
skulls and one half and two happy faces
and if it lands on the skull
then their death has been foretold
by the ancient ones it is what they
would like
it pleases them
oh
it's already starting
all right engine I don't need right now
this I'm gonna transfer to the other box
this will transfer this I can make more
gunpowder with this is a good helmet to
have these are my extra keys
oh this I'll probably need this is the
key to Kiara's house this is just
regular stuff doesn't really matter if I
scrap but this is transferring to
another box this don't really care about
this pants don't need pants I'm gonna
keep that wiring don't really need that
but the stack I do not stack
[Music]
this I'll transfer to the other box
binoculars I'll need these you might use
that gunpowder grenade transferring
transferring this this this this
and let me make more gunpowder
cold hold locks yeah I do need the wait
what's the difference between is it
actually better like this lock versus
the other log
is it
is it or does it just look cooler
watch a gunpowder and transfer this and
these
foreign
this is where my current gun
is for building
all right this stuff is all to be
scrapped
yeah nail gun binoculars keep
and it'll all be transferred
it's for sharing a base
oh I don't trust you guys
I don't trust you guys to know the code
maybe I could set the code off like I'll
hide my screen and set it I have to like
manually put it every time I get in or
can I just give it to people
if they want to get in
what do I need to repair this chainsaw
maybe it's better than starting a new
one for now
see
high quality metal okay easy
[Music]
easy yeah I think I'm gonna I might
build my base out of metal but it takes
quite a bit
only if you said it once
I see I see
foreign
like the Ping really sucks for me so
every time I think I transfer something
it doesn't actually do it when I click
because I try to do it really fast or
maybe I just clicked on gunpowder oh I
did just because it looks similar okay
it looks the same
and I'll leave everything else in here
all right other things to scrap I don't
really need any car parts anymore so I'm
just gonna scrap this stuff
these gears are mostly I collected them
for car parts
oh thank you for the subscription
membership I mean thank you thank you
I was reading chat it's confusing
what's up with my oh yeah I never have
any power
landed on one
good luck oh
you broke something
sorry okay
can I even pick this up because
um my computer thing
I don't know I guess I'll keep it
because I might want it
but uh I think the last thing I'm gonna
do after I build my new base now is I'm
gonna disassemble like everything but
for now I'm just gonna scrap
everything
that I might not need
like I have two of these pistols I don't
think I need two of them
uh I have an extra on one of these I
think I'll now I guess I should keep it
just in case I have two pistols I have
three of these rifles the m39s and two
Thompsons
seems good what's a good sniping gun
because so far I've just been using the
bolt action rifle and I've got an eight
time scope on it I I had my 16 time
scope but I think I need to re-buy it
because
um all right this I'm gonna I'm gonna
scraps the grill
draw
n thank you there's an OP really where
can I get that though I don't think I
can get it huh all right water and stuff
I'll have to leave this I can pick up I
think no I can't pick that up okay that
I'll scrap last
better sniper is only found in crates
damn
crates right now all right on my way to
go scrap stuff oh yeah I have extra food
here too good and extra water okay I can
scrap these buckets
nobody bought any of my buckets
and
might as well yeah
oh okay I'll leave this for now
and I'll scrub this flashlight will be
good to have look how many of these I
built by accident
okay now off to scrub
yeah yeah I'm gonna research the bear
trap so just uh
I'm just waiting to get more scraps
because I ran out
research and stuff right now
store what do you mean oh yeah so this
is my
oh yeah I forgot I can store stuff in
here I don't think I need to even take
anything with me uh I will take the uh
chainsaw with me so that I can build
stuff or get some wood
and stones
I don't have
how come you can't build like last time
I tried to build one of these I'll just
repair it
it didn't let me
I couldn't research it for some reason
one high quality metal on fragments
one
one would it say 40 something
cans why not you can only find them
that's weird
all right
I'm gonna take these to recycle
on that okay
all right that should be good
damn that my frames right now are so
shh the frames look shitty for you guys
it feels weird because I've been playing
so much rest offline and my frames
weren't this terrible it's definitely
weird
I wonder if it's because I'm in 3D right
now
it takes too much
it's normal okay that's good
well yeah I was lagging but that's just
server lag
oh
[Music]
I do not want to scrub oh I didn't bring
my little thingy with me today
I think I just
fixed
let me grab some more stuff
all this I'll keep
ax it's in this bucket like three times
things
[Music]
or with who everyone
anyone who dares stand in my way
[Music]
carburetor
all right
yeah I like this idea of Four Towers
I think I'll do that
a good idea nice to a lot of scraps can
I even scrub this
I picked this up from the uh the oil rig
that we went to
you cannot scrap it I don't want it
it's taking up space I don't need it
right now
I have a level two workbench
should I get level three I don't even
have everything on level two yet so
I'm building up the level three
workbench probably costs like a thousand
scrap huh
I have this shotgun well
all right
this looks good
let me find what else there is to scrap
in this area
Spinning Wheel another one
something else to scrap
yeah after I finished grabbing all this
stuff I'm gonna start building I think I
know a pretty good spot
um that I'm gonna build
in
uh specifically for uh actually before I
build I need to collect the [\h__\h] ton of
Stone since now I'm gonna be doing stone
walls
[Music]
sell the pistol to NPC oh really I can
sell it
and then I'll check and then let me get
this stuff
[Music]
noise
I saved my blueprints what don't they
just save automatically like all the
stuff I researched
oh nice the Watchtower I kind of want to
put one just in case
again
I'll keep the metal blade no I don't
need that all I need to build one
chainsaw
I'm not gonna really need this
um I can get 500 scraps
and get on the roof without the ladder
huh
I only sell fertilized cucards Claws and
fish ah
hmm
all right I'll keep this
I'll check the map I'll check the NPC
stuff right now
all right let me see
uh so you can buy this stuff but I don't
know if I can sell it I'm 39 rifle I
have the one I might buy another 16 Zoom
scope because actually I had scrapped it
because I found out I took a lot of
stuff that I wanted to scrap
and that was one of them but now that
I'm realizing my plan
I think I might need one
yeah there is a pistol for sale but I
don't know if that means I can
because it's not only for this grab
Exchange
all right I'm gonna go pick up my thingy
my uh
yeah
bye bye
I'm gonna go pick up my yeah I'm not
gonna do it again uh I'm gonna go pick
up my thing I can't remember the name
for it
the uh excavator thingy not excavator I
keep trying to say like a jigsaw or
something what the heck
what is that thingy called
oh I forgot the name
chainsaw oh no no no no no this thingy
that camera I know it started with a j
somebody's voice
huh
any
angel
is it
and it's gone
ah
hmm
oh
um
I'm gonna play on repeat on my speakers
and my new base
Empire
actually where I was planning to build
is kind of close to her
There She Goes
my new alarm clock I gotta I gotta I got
a personal voice pack are you guys
jealous
to be amazed to win
all right I gotta go search for rocks
I have to search for frogs
yeah yeah stay mad
Wow Let's see
what is here
I think there's a lot of rocks over here
so I'm gonna
start oh yeah let me put on this new
stuff
okay I need to I need to coordinate it
with something else because otherwise
I'm gonna be naked
I forgot I'm wearing a hazmat suit
I need some clothes
here's some stones
I need approximately
like 8 000 stones
I don't think you can play stuff in your
car like like a with the recorder or
with the uh tape but I am gonna take it
out of the recorder just in case I
accidentally
like do something with it
what if I accidentally hit record like
right click it would all be gone
there's no areas have more Stone really
okay then I guess I'll follow this road
which there's a road over here somewhere
that goes to the thingy
wait oh it's metal
I can attach it to the car Boombox
really
I didn't think you could attach anything
to the car
oh
E10 has a lot of stones it's very
specific
how do I know if I can trust you
although I think this road is going to
go to like a snowy place them
I don't need metal
I'm not planning on uh
melting down anything
that's a new one
and that's pretty good
I'm gonna steal it it's mine now I own
it is there even an E10 on this map
is it's in the ocean sort of there's a
little beach maybe on the next on the
next uh server thing ah
hello
be careful
[Music]
in the war
because I'm gonna snipe yeah wait which
way is it
that's the right way
to go the other way it goes down to the
Senpai is based on E10 oh is that why
lag lag my frames oh [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
okay
it's lag and my frames
uh if you guys see any rocks that are
minable please let me know
and I'm bringing a gas with me
all right I'll stop by my house really
quick because I have like 500 fuel I
just need to pick it up
[Music]
I guess I can burn some
I know the leg is so bad
[Music]
foreign
I'm like trying to move fast and do
things fast is it because I exit out of
the inventory too fast or is it my is it
like the server doesn't recognize it
yeah I might switch I might switch
models
all right let me go home one last time
not one lesson just uh
last time then I go mining
what
scary to drive it I don't think it's
like the for like the frames do
contribute to me
oh
the frames do contribute to it looking
like shitty for me but also I think it's
just the server leg
oh yeah I gotta check out my base
because I think it had like the last
time I checked in on it
was over 24 hours ago
and it had like 32 hours to go or 35
hours to go or something so gotta pick
up some I should
I need to get I need to add more uh wood
all right let me put something away
this way
uh put this away
right away
and
oh I'll put this away for now
um it's the way so I don't lose it
and put it this way
okay this should be good what was that
sound
sounded very
um
should I keep some of these with me just
in case I need to fix my car
okay
it's dark
and scary
my car
bye
[Music]
okay this way
here
I don't think so I didn't see her in her
house before
maybe she was
forgot to check my what
okay this base has 58 hours on it left
so
can I mine that rock thingy or no no no
I can't know why I'm asking
okay looking for scones the road which
leads to the snow areas like right over
here somewhere
oh
foreign
here we go
sulfur no
um
there it is there's the road
towel
yeah we only need like 10 hours of up
keep good point
oh
[Music]
oh this is a cliff oh there's a cliff
hey get up
okay this is fine we'll go down this way
it's a little thingy
oh
we're fine look here's the road
all right I should probably wait until
it gets lighter because I don't I can't
see where I'm going
I think if I follow it oh this is the
entrance to the
face weight surfaces right now
I am here I need to be on this road here
also turn around
the road find some stones
and then I'll make a uh what
like a lift
at the turn I can still kind of see here
we go
the sun here comes the shine
[Music]
oh wait what the heck
oh
[\h__\h]
you're not gonna shoot me right
I thought those bullets
oh that's a helicopter that ruined my
Derby it shot missiles at me Rockets
out of the road
okay
Stones I'm gonna get out here
oh there we go
am I gonna die here
where's my thingy
that I left at home was gonna be pissed
all right sulfur
eh
I'll just take my car over here I'm not
gonna stop it on the road just because
it's the road
this makes it every more exciting no it
was terrible because it I spent like a
few hours building some like electrical
wiring and charging up my batteries
and it just one rocket came and I took
off all my stuff but it was too late and
it kept shooting at me I can drive
across this water right wait is this ice
or
can't tell but that is a cliff there's
sulfur
this sucks where's all the stones
I need a [\h__\h] tone I need like 13 000
stones
my house
a little tiny Bush it's literally a bush
we'll care package
we got hopefully some meds
no meds but guns and metals and stuff to
scrap
shoot all right well since I'm going
this way anyways I'll just go to my
other
face
I'll make it
uh where am I
that way
was that a stone no it's metal ore
wait is that a stone
kind of looks like a stone
oh maybe it's sulfur it's sulfur
ah
where the stones at
haha
you guys like the thumbnail
I felt like it was fitting yes thank you
sulfur have you guys like ever been
driving on the road and you can smell
sulfur like just some natural gases
coming up from the Earth
we build up gas like that
um engines built of gas the Earth builds
up yes
hmm
hey
hello
stop you're gonna make me crash
all right car I need to take the brunt
of this damage because I found a stone
are they shooting at me do they just
like not like cars
all right my 57 hell I think it's the
last wait
based I think
okay there's
metal metal ore
anything to eat
combat mining yeah
I don't know how to make an armored car
I think that's in the level three
workbench I don't have it yet I'm not
I I haven't Advanced that far so
all right that's fine I'm gonna put some
stuff away in my car quickly
[Music]
okay
and I'll just grab it
everything's fine we're cool we're cool
it is a cute car isn't it good morning
good morning I guess yeah technically
good morning
stone stone needs some Stone there's
another Stone
ow did I just get hit by my own car
what the heck I've been betrayed
I built you
and brought you into this world
can bring you out of it and it will
actually like before the war is over I
might share my perspective but we were
talking about like possibly streaming
well just me and Cali about streaming on
Twitch so maybe while everybody's doing
their streams on YouTube I'll do mine on
Twitch and uh
one of the last things I would like to
do is send a car over a cliff in like
with me inside of it
oh I think I see some more Stones up
there one looks like sulfur one looks
like Stone
I'm full ah hold on my
crashed again oops sorry
yeah I do have a twitch but I don't
really stream there that often I
actually forgot again
to upload the freaking Cult of lamb bod
that I did on there I don't know I might
play again this week I'm not sure
I know my HP I'm at 44 right now I'm
just gonna get this and then
if I'm full then I'll go back home
how much thousand I have 6 000 stones in
my inventory currently
but
I'm gonna try to get as much as I can
sit down
they're gonna rocket blast my car maybe
I'll just leave my car well I have four
cars I have four other cars in the uh
Derby area which I'm hoping I'm hoping
nobody will try to destroy it because
you can't really get anything from it
it's just like stuff to destroy it's
[\h__\h]
oh I'm gonna die
I was gonna try to run him over
oh I'm gonna die I'm gonna die
I didn't bring any food with me
or oh
wait I might make it I might make it I'm
going to be line for my house
oh what am I stuck on
where am I
okay I can't make it to my to the derby
right now or I could just spawn there if
I die I'm not that far that's a glue
fine everything is fine
oh Road
actually don't really want to be on the
road because I gotta cross over I will
get past this little thingy
this little Bay Area thingy
I know my health is low it's fine well
we're gonna make it I'm gonna make it
I'm gonna have to refuel
let me see
okay
I'm gonna turn
here
[Music]
I think
and get down this hill
I think I see an entrance
here
no
I need to get down this hill
I'm gonna make it
I believe
here we go there's an entrance right
here
what
just a little Bub I do not fit through
there I fit
I do not fit
okay
new plan
new plan backing up
slowly oh God
slowly but surely
it looked like
it there we go slowly maybe it's better
if I get out and push
and then it's going it's going
[Music]
there's a tree in front of me a little
tiny baby tree I'm getting out to push
come on come on
let's have it
go go okay
here we go back in
back on track
is this way down the hill
that looks like a way down
Maybe
little tree look at this little [\h__\h] in
real life you could run this over no
problem I mean it might do some damage
but okay don't think that's an entrance
oh
looks like a cliff
I need to turn left let me turn left
all right there's an open pass like
before I've been here and I've I've
driven into that little Valley over
there
um
foreign
[Music]
I should organize a racing Journey
yeah but like kind of did
like I invited everybody to Derby the
town that Cali had a peace party but
everybody was like busy with the uh
concert that happened it was kind of bad
timing
foreign
like four hours
uh actually maybe less than like two to
four hours there's gonna be a lot of uh
ens on Rust
and Kiara because I asked Garrett to
help me she helped me collect cars
for the Derby
and
um
I can't see there's stuff that's loading
in still
what that little thing
driving in the snow like
off-roading in the snow is the worst
they can't see
what is that in front of me it's a
freaking
oh
I'm almost there it's like it's like
right past this line of trees
oh
there it is
Temporary Home Sweet Home
back
it's hidden by the bushes let me through
hey
we're here
we have some clothes I have some extra
clothes here
okay we made it these are all the cars
he took off all the back ends and I just
left the front ends
and then
uh there's the disco ball
oh yeah so my clothes is down here
I'll just switch for now and then if I
need to I'll just quickly put on my
husband's suit
my inventory
um
I feel like you can remake one of these
I'll keep the Boombox but only to drop
it off
and then I have stuff I want to scrap
I'll go scrap at Cali's place
[Music]
oh
look at my guns
stuff to scrap
I don't know to be honest I feel like I
already have enough ammo I'm just gonna
drop it
I have a lot
stuff to scrap
okay
and stuff okay wait my base time of 14
hours this is enough time right
Nico's tape oh no Miko Steve I put it in
a safe spot in my house right now
you guys I already it's not in my
inventory I put it away specifically in
the chest relax
it's not with me it's at home not here
oh yeah in this in that recorder that
was just uh some music that I recorded
for the Derby
okay stuff to scrub
grabs keep
I mean nothing
okay should be good I just need to
collect some more wood
I know some more another car
and then I'm ready to build my base
a new
a new one shall be reborn
yeah the next time I kind of want to
still make a derby but maybe I'll just
enclose the terrain
in like the barriers
who to hit first
okay let me scrap over here
another one there's so many today
where is he
ah
do well and scrap and stuff
I didn't want to set up any traps in the
derby because uh I don't want it to be
destroyed by like people driving the car
[Music]
free stuff free stuff
oh it's so laggy for me today
I guess it's a combination of just my
regular server lag and also the frames a
little wonky
where's this guy
and I was there
wanna kill him
foreign
cool moves
[Music]
oh okay
I like uh I like the Scopes like the
feeling of the Scopes in this game
yeah he fell in style at least
okay
oh what scared me
two of them
all right
[Applause]
all right last thing let's grab and then
I need to find some more
wood oh our Stone I keep saying wood
more Stone wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait a second
aha Stone
wait is that a stone yeah that's big
it's big
let's collect this and go on my way
is this the third season of rust isn't
this the second one
second season I don't know though
I just want to get this stuff so I can
leave
oh Mommy
[Music]
oh it sucks
missing wood
oh I think I stored some wood in here
what is in this box
did I already get it
to the stone
and then I can finally build
it's not if I need more Stone I'll just
click it more wait is Kelly's house
decaying already
no oh the pool of peace is gone
rip
you had a good run wait where did I see
that stone
was it this
kind of looks like Stone
sulfur
I think it's up here in this hill
does that mean Kelly stuff is up for
grabs isn't she gonna be uh to be on
later so I'm not gonna take her stuff
although I will say I did find somebody
else's house decaying and it was like
all the walls were gone all that was
left was the chest and I knew that the
foundations were gonna Decay like in the
next few hours
so I may have borrowed some things and
by things I mean all I took was uh metal
fragments because there was a whole
chest full of them and I knew that they
were going to disappear as soon as the
foundations of the house collapsed
so you know it would it's free free real
estate
I would say it's a pretty fair right I
mean everything was decaying
yeah I did the right thing
I saved it from being a waste I only
took like
three or four Stacks anyways and there
was like a whole chest full because I
felt bad like I probably shouldn't
probably shouldn't take this
reclaimed materials none of it goes to
waste well a lot of it did
foreign building my Derby so
I I uh I needed some extra stuff
yeah the waist is uh the wipe is in um
10 hours apparently or 12 hours wait
when is it I don't know nobody knows
uh I think
I think uh
I'm running out of fuel soon I don't
want to put it all in because it scares
me
then I won't be as conscious of how much
is left
in 12 hours nine hours
nine hours wait
seven hours I don't know we don't know
I could probably find out
I think I'll just leave it up to uh
chance
I'll leave it up to fate
I'm just kidding I'm sure there's a
specific scheduled time
can I go through this place
okay I'm gonna check here on the side of
the water plant yeah I know I don't care
package right now
oh
that was Stone
oh [\h__\h]
fine
everything is fine hey there's a little
thingy there
a little Community thingy
um
maybe there's somebody's house maybe
somebody's house is here in a decade it
must be it
here we go Stone
the polar bear
doesn't try to mess with me
on here can I get up on here should be
able to
okay looks clear
now I understand why people wear hazmat
suit because the helicopter doesn't
attack you in it but you're still
covered like head to toe
oh yeah now I have a husband too I can
finally get up on top of this orb
you can claim the orb is mine mine own
all right live back to the snow place I
look for more Stone wait how much do I
have let me count in total
uh one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
fourteen fifteen sixteen Seventeen
eighteen I have eighteen thousand
all right I guess I'll start building
now and then if I need more Stone
wait this is yeah this is the way home
okay so I was thinking a good place to
set up camp
I'll show you guys
I'll show you
is this the right way
it's driving
hold on
where am I
oh this is not where I thought I was
foreign
[Music]
yes anyways my car
otherwise you'll probably get some more
caffeine too
oh
all right hold on
[\h__\h] off
I thought it was reloading but it was
not
no no you're not getting away
all right wait let me drink some water
that might help
oh I wish you could eat and drink at the
same time in this game but it's only you
full
nope not this way either
[Music]
I feel like there's a lot of stone in
the desert area you guys said there's a
lot of stone in the ice area but I've
always seen more
in this area
short of
I don't know
and this this road leads it Loops all
the way back around to my place
I heal up what the frick the server lag
it couldn't turn I saw it I knew that
there was something there but it
uh
this is a server it's actually the Ping
this time you guys believe me right
[Music]
look I'm at that I'm like at the line
right now
all right I'll fill it up before it goes
out completely
I'll pick up more at my house anyways
Stone run successful
now the map also gets like regenerated
so it's gonna look different right
it's not gonna be the same map that'd be
lame
new area new map
and I already know this map like the
back of my hand
so it's kind of nice that it gets
refreshed
yeah it's random I asked I asked the
chat the other day and uh they said they
said that uh even for other Rust servers
the map gets reset and it's also random
did you guys see a little tiny palm tree
it's so cute
here we go I recognize this area
new map of the same biomes yeah I think
there's only like these three biomes in
Russ huh
you have the land where it's not cold
the land where it's really hot this is
the wrong way and the land where it's
very
old wait what'd I say
land or it's not cold to land or it is
cold and the land where it's really hot
there's mountainous there's different so
there are different biomes
oh I never knew
nothing is loaded and I'm gonna crash
into an invisible car
if there's a lake in Rust it would be
cool there's only there aren't I mean
there's ponds I've seen ponds in this
game but I haven't seen Lakes
server lag it's dangerous
all right here it is
let me just get heels and some fuel and
then I'm gonna drive to the new location
and first this
it's okay I can litter this is my
property
and you know the whole world is gonna
end so it's fine
healing healing I shouldn't leave my
door open right
it's gonna come anyways
Senpai was here that was surprising
do I need this whole Med kit to like
let me take some food with me
wait I think I got rid of all my food
all my food is at the uh oh here we go
yeah this is my long-term house but I'm
gonna be building a different
a little different
let's go
[Music]
um
I should probably fix my car up
before I break it
no wood
lies lies
[Music]
speaking of wood actually I kind of need
some
I don't have any space it's okay I'm
gonna drop
let me just wear this instead for now
let me just collect some so I can build
the foundations
foreign
oh I gotta pick up fuel
I can't just do it until it runs out
here we go
I don't know if I'll need that uh maybe
I'll do some electricity stuff it's
pretty easy now that I have some charged
batteries too I can bring
shall I speaking of that let me just
turn this off
okay I guess I'll spend the night here
save some power
fuel fuel fuel
[Music]
all right
here is the tape the makeup gave me is
he nickel senpai's tape
Nicole
Sam hi thanks guys love
mix
yeah
nice
Play it Again Play it again okay
I'm scared to do it on the recorder
because I'm scared I'm gonna record over
it by accident
I have a boombox that I bring that up
here
all right I'll do it in the recorder
I'll just be careful
don't right click no right clicking no
right clicking
foreign
[Music]
for real
all right just waiting for the night and
then
building time
all right let me design I'll open up
mess paint while we wait
so here's my plan where's Emma's paint
foreign
here's the plan
so I'm gonna build
walls can I do dotted lines in Ms paint
it's here
this is gonna be like the Outer
Perimeter made out of stone barriers
and on the inside I was thinking about
doing uh one by one
okay like Towers just as soon as one by
one but then I was thinking about also
like connecting it somehow or just
putting a bass in the middle
and then I'm gonna put a sleeping bag in
each one
okay right
see it should be pretty simple a bed
yeah yeah a creeper base
actually I I think this one will just
not this one's just gonna be storage
um it's not gonna be a tower but these
are going to be Towers maybe a varying
Heights
yes I think let me check how much
I have
I don't think I have enough
fragments
to make it out of metal
let me see
I have quite a bit I might be able to
make some of the towers out of metal
I don't know definitely should be out of
metal I don't know how tall I'm gonna
make them maybe I'll just make one
taller
son is fine too I don't know if I'll
have enough Stone because I'm gonna use
all this stone for the
barriers because it
um
let's see where are they
are these external stone walls because
they have they cost 1500 each and I got
18 000 and I want the whole perimeter
like this area
here
this whole Outer Square
make the center one metal
should there only be one tall one then
it'll just make that one out of metal
bed's too close together share the same
cooldown oh
try to avoid blind spots
wait how many cameras do I have let me
check I think I have three because
otherwise it's gonna put a camera like
on each side
so that I could observe each like
Direction so I have wait
I might have mounted another one out
here
I just have this one okay I only have
three
all right let's go
I don't think I need anything from here
right now but I can always come back
so I was thinking of building my base in
a really wide open spot so I can snipe
kind of by Miko senpai's face but also
pretty close to the
uh to where the casino is because I
think a lot of people will be at the
casino
and if they are exiting you know then
who knows maybe I could take a few pot
shots
I'm gonna build the Tower
and to make a senpai's base is up there
and
Missy so this is where the Bandit Camp
is
I wanted a really wide open place where
I could snipe from
let's make a senpai's face
I hope what does she shoots rocket
launchers at me during the war
should be a little further down maybe I
do want some high ground
oh
building on a hill to get high ground is
a good idea
also someplace where I can overlook
the Bandit Camp if this is a good like
this hill right here and access to the
road
and I can see the Bandit Camp from here
maybe this would be good or maybe over
there let me go across I think over
there might be better because the exits
in the casino
is over there
oh yeah Emma's paint covering my screen
sorry I forgot
a little leg we are
I think I'll pick this hill
all right it's the entrance to the
casino right here
I'm gonna die
okay
like around
if I can build here this will be a good
spot
I don't know if I can build this close
let me see
apparently I can okay
oh I need to build the stone barriers
okay for now I'm just gonna build my
Foundation
so I'll put uh where should the tower be
somewhere that's not blocked by tree so
my facing the Bandit Camp right now
that's it
here but there's a lot of trees
maybe it should be on the Stone Hill
I wonder if I'll be able to see if I
make it tall enough I should be able to
right
what is that wait what is that
what was that
he goes Empire
Maybe
all right through this opening I'm gonna
try to get through the opening because
look I'm staring almost straight at it
like right there
if not I'll just go and cut down some of
those tall trees
I think it should be tall enough
I'm gonna build a little
base area around here
now oh but there's this rock back here
to get all in case that in the stone
barriers too maybe
okay so this will be where my tower is
and I'll put spiral stairs
for now I guess I'll upgrade hopefully
if I make the foundation stone it should
be good enough and then I'll have the
walls surrounding
maybe I could put a wall there while
there okay I need my level two workbench
so I'm gonna go back to my house really
quick and come back wait this is gonna
decay
hopefully nobody will mess with it if I
just put a quick tool
cabinet on it
all right let me Mark this position on
the map
okay
I put my tool cabinet down here
the cabinet I just take so long
this happened after like when I was in
the middle of making my Derby thing
I uh
what if I could sign people in the
casino from here
uh what's that oh yeah I uh
my tool cabinet got broken because the
rocket that was shot at me from the
helicopter
foreign
it broke my my tool cabinet and I was so
scared that everything was going to
Decay really fast
for now
lock it
lock it okay I just put a simple lock on
it for now
[Music]
foreign
I should probably bring my level 2
workbench here just in case no I don't
want it to be broken it might be safer
for now
in my house wait
huh
let's put a little bit for now
Stone
I don't know how wide the walls are but
I guess I'll just make as many as I can
while leaving like 3 000 Stone to
upgrade some of the foundation
use me actually should I put my
Foundation out of like metal
it might be good
let me just take this road
it's a little bit faster I think
well
only the main Foundation
yeah well I want the walls for my tower
to be made out of metal just in case
foreign
[Music]
connection that's proper banding like
crazy
you on the battlefield soon
Cali you're participating in the war by
the way Kelly the peace pool's gone
does that mean that you've declared war
since the peace pool is gone
hello
what are they planning are they taking
is she gonna take uh
what did you do what did you do to my
base
what happened did she do something
is there a bear trap a bomb did you
plant did you bring bombs inside my door
you gonna play a trumpet I see
what'd you do
what was she planning was she scoping it
out for anything to scrap
didn't get in here did she maybe she
jumped on her horse and jumped on the
roof
oh my God it's possible
all right let me build these stone walls
[Music]
four times stone walls let me collect my
stuff
oh God there's not a lock on my car
oh
what are they doing
let's play I'm just playing okay
I'll leave this many stones to upgrade
my foundation and maybe some walls
she left a message she used a message
threatened me with her presence
just her presence alone
[Music]
all right I only have seven walls that's
all my stone gummy
it's all gone
I don't have to collect more but for now
seven walls will have to do
all right I'll have or I guess I only
have six walls wait one finish oh eight
walls okay I have eight walls
anything in the mailbox no
clear
no wall Gates nah I didn't research it
maybe I'll just find a way to get in the
secret way to get in
foreign
thing only I can do maybe like a really
tall ladder and then I'll just use my
card to get in and then I'll hunker down
you know what I mean
how about that my car will be destroyed
maybe I'll use a horse and jump on the
horse and then jump on the ladder
or maybe I'll surround the ladder with
bear traps so I'll get into the ladder
I'll get on the ladder and then
uh
I'll get on the ladder
and then surround it with bear traps and
uh explosives because look I have I have
a proximity mine
so maybe I'll just surround it can I
connect to like these uh
it'd be cool if you could connect like
bombs just like a TNT thing all right I
got all my
my thing is
okay
I'm ready to go back to the road
here too it's not easier but it's faster
if I drive through this
line of trees there's a horse
maybe I couldn't use the horse's bait
yeah the server is quiet for now wait
all right now I know where the horse is
shotgun traps the Gap I only have one
shotgun trap
oops guys looking at the
side
eat
foreign
I just put in a little bit amount at a
time so that I can keep track of the gas
that other horse
what is that
dude what is that oh there's just
standing there menacingly sorry
here
through these unloaded trees Oh I
thought I wasn't gonna make it through
there it is
that somebody outside my base it's not
even finished yet
maybe I'm seeing things
Oh I thought I saw somebody
huh
okay
let's start with walls
just this part is gonna be walled in
and this will be the tower going up
I need wall frames
for now I'll leave it like that I don't
have a lot of woods I gotta collect some
now oh I forgot all my metal my metal
fragments
okay ah the door door the door open the
door here
foreign
's gonna be here then I'll put these
around
oh these are pretty big
okay
before I lock myself out of my base
oh maybe maybe I can get in from here
oh [\h__\h]
okay you cannot get in from there that's
good that's uh I was just testing it
just a test guys
oh I can't build it here
maybe I'll put uh something here like a
Trapper I don't know
three left
foreign
I don't think I can put one up there oh
no
my temporary base
right
why can't I put a hair down our space
right here
what about here
my poorly planned last minute sniping
Tower
all right let's find it damn it I need
to protect this part
wait what was that
we saw something
I saw something
oh
what the heck
where was it
bring it back
all right maybe if I stand
actually
I feel like it should be able to fit
here
I have to move my base bag just a little
bit
maybe I'll make this corner of the Tower
destroy
I'm a break
reimagining my last minute base hello
Kiara
[Music]
damn it's still still up
I think if I remove the wall frames
don't break
I'm gonna put a triangle here if I can
damn you
why not use the eggs I don't have one I
have a chainsaw but last time I tried to
use chainsaw on a wall it broke and
I was annoyed because I had to make
vanilla chainsaw but I didn't have all
the parts for it
use a hammer oh yeah I forgot this one I
just put down
foreign
you can only shoot at the other wall
from this angle unless they throw
grenade in here
uh maybe I'll put something else here
like a
I don't know what can I put here maybe
I'll
put a triangle Foundation
can't afford to play Stang it
I'm gonna just get under here really
quick
I'll just put this last thing and I'm
gonna collect some more stuff
all right I'll just put like a
something there
to block it
okay now I just need one more wall
that'll hopefully fit
maybe not
I can make it a triangle Tower
let me try that
um
all right let me go collect more wood so
I can complete this should be pretty
easy with my
handy dandy chainsaw which is
not in my inventory
maybe at my car where did I park my
others I think it's in here
hopefully
what the heck where is it
I was just using it
did I scrap it by accident
there's no Stonegate but I'm gonna
figure out a way to get in
somehow
maybe there's a little Gap right here
Maybe
I'll put a door
can I put a door on maybe if I make it
like this
all right that's how I'll do it what the
heck
they leave it at home I put it away with
the Mikko tape
damn it I gotta drive all the way back
all right stay safe for now base I'll be
back
drive across the land
yeah I'm gonna start transporting some
things that I'll need
like my proximity mine
I kind of wish I could make more I only
have one
it's easier to take the road for now
Come On The Road Again
I need like one more Stone
stack
one more stone wall try to build
finish to complete the wall
where there's Stone somewhere
what
um
yeah bear traps gonna do bear traps
I think I have to research them first
but I'm not that far off from uh getting
them so I'll have enough scrap to get it
I'll probably do that right now not
research it but uh
find it in the tech tree all right I
need to build let's bring all my metal
fragments so I can build some metal
walls
for me
the bear traps now
take a tree
right here
uh what the [\h__\h] this is misleading I
thought it was right here
damn it
oh
okay I got it anyways it just cost extra
scrap
I'll put it away before I lose it
this
one maybe I'll be able to fit a
watchtower there somehow
spikes are really helpful yeah they're
pretty good
take these all right let me build one
more wall I think I'll just need one
more
it's like a gorilla base you know
waiting for that
now I'm scared to like rig the
landmine at the moment maybe if I just
research it that'd be better so I can
build some for now because I only have
one and I don't have enough scraps to
craft it or find it in the tech tree
let's see
I already researched I already have one
bag I can build some wait what workbench
is that at
work bench little two right up I'm gonna
bring my workbench I hope it doesn't get
messed up I'm not gonna bring it yet
actually no it should be fine it should
be fine
foreign
I think that's everything I need for
right now
I'll probably be back
I hope nobody destroys my house my real
house like this house
look it looks so nice you know it's
looking so cute
it wouldn't do that right
chainsaw oh
fruit good point you guys thank you
oh stop
stop stop stop
okay
oh I should probably bring my other
workbench too just so
I don't have to rebuild it because it
costs 50 scrap
I think I'll have enough space in there
place it
just collect some wood for now so I can
build as soon as I get back
actually
[Music]
maybe I'll wait to cut down trees I'm
gonna use fuel anyways I'll just do it
by my house so I get a better view of
the casino
[Music]
making my way downhill driving fast
trees go past
and um
weaving through the trees I like that
they put the trees a lot of them are
like at the perfect distance just for a
car to squeeze through
probably intentional right
I squeezed through some trees I did not
think I would be able to whose base is
this
all right
probably should have gotten some more
fuel oh well
it's at my house right now but it's fine
I can always go back
there's the road
that's enough
surprise
all right I'll turn
perfect
all right I think I have to remove this
but it's okay I'll build in the confines
good thing I didn't turn dystonia
because it'd be a pain in the ass
I can't use the hammer
it's not ready or it's been too long
since I put it down
see
okay it's almost gone it's almost dead
but I don't want to use any of my tools
so I'm just going to shoot it I think
the best course of action here
yeah
up and down this
a little Gap here
it's not so bad
okay
now my tower let me see
should be good
uh oh I should have brought some extra
claws with me okay for now let me build
the door
put in the door ready
can I get into her way didn't I put it
somewhere else
I thought there was a wider Gap
somewhere oh it's up here
yeah
put the foundation here
can't afford to place did I oh no I
haven't collected one okay okay
now what
uh
all right the tallest trees which are
blocking my view
okay definitely this one
it's on a hill
I don't think I go for that white one
next
X confuses me so much but I realize it's
where the Crosshair would be
connect and then there's another tall
one back there I want to get
where is it where's the eggs
okay and then I think
the other one I wanted to do
this one
is that stone
or
Stone
oh this one
okay
let me take a look
much better okay
they're asked if she can be in my tower
we'll have to let the wheel decide
it's up to fate
God
it's dangerous I can't even get into my
own Fortress
all right hopefully I can put a wall
right here
I can't he'll put a door frame
I don't have space
all right this is fine
It's Too Tall anyways right
what should I put there I don't know
what to what to put to block it I can't
really put anything maybe if I put
maybe it's like that
all right is this connected to my base
like
this is connected right it's within the
walls
it'll decay
ready
all right well I'll just extend like
something like this
too far away
and now it's connected
right look it's touching
it seems good
all right now the most important thing
for my Towers obviously I need a way to
get up
and so we're gonna go with the like
Lighthouse method
foreign
how do I put walls like on the triangle
or on triangles I haven't done that
oh it just goes on okay
anything there
um
I should be able to still get up right
like if I do this
okay I can
it's dark
I didn't have my flashlight we'll have
to we'll have to resume uh
resume building
and during daytime I think
let me see if I could try to get the
stairs up
foreign
get these stairs to connect like it's
supposed to be right here right
let's go
how tall are we now
I get a 16 time scope damn there's still
trees blocking me
I'm gonna get rid of them
I think we can go taller
I don't have an entrance
uh
I do I put a door frame wait where am I
I can't see
too dark
oh we're outside
we're outside
there's that and then there's up here
oh I don't have an entrance to the wait
how did I get it out here
all right we'll just wait until the
sun comes up
in the meantime make a flashlight but I
already have one I don't want to make
one
I have to make one again
I don't have my workbench I don't have I
don't have a put down right now
did I pick up
I put the other workbench in my car
I know I can't see anything either we
have to wait
[Music]
how long until the war
like
um
oh my God
two hours
an hour and 20 minutes
that's my day
it's pretty good
you know just dream the whole day I had
a corn dog I had some creamy chicken
rice soup
and
that's all I ate today yeah
no sleep well I'm not planning to stream
tomorrow until like pretty late so
yeah tomorrow I was planning to play
there were two games I was gonna play
Mario Galaxy and Elden ring and I think
I was gonna play Mario Galaxy on Friday
so tomorrow we'll play Eldon ring in the
night time
and then on Friday
we'll play Mario Galaxy 2 and then
on Saturday I'm not sure but on Friday I
have a collab with Kiara so we're gonna
play something earlier in the day
yeah I can sleep in tomorrow
oh is the sun coming up
yay okay yes I've got a door there
oh yeah this thingy I don't have an
entrance
this is where I'm gonna put my door
huh
what the heck
there we go
stairs
it's better to do it from down here
yeah what's the what's the sky limit
where's the sky bugs
all right let's take a look
I can just almost see inside I just
gotta remove those trees in the way
uh
on any wave uh where's the wave uh hello
[Music]
oh my God can they jump in if you jump
on the horse you might be able to jump
over that wall maybe I should make it a
little taller
scary if I fall I'm gonna die
oh Uber Eats
should bring me something funny
hello
[Music]
me uh
no food
oh wait I have one okay
[Music]
I have one salmon I can share
oh
yes
oh yes thank you
[Music]
okay bye bye
yay delivery free delivery
now let's see if I can actually get up
into my door
parkour
all right what if I put a uh
no that'll make it too easy it's too
easy I can figure out a way to get it
I just have to strafe
almost almost
oh wait
[Applause]
oh
huh yeah you can get up it's possible
it's definitely possible
what the heck it feels like it should be
possible
any cooked chainsaw it's getting in my
way
oh awesome
kind of like crowds oh
[Music]
okay it's okay I'll bring some stuff
back with me
I almost made it I mean I made it in
it's just I didn't have enough Health to
get past it like wearing some claws with
me so I can build a bed
and
let me bring my Med kits
and my medal
and
um
this
and this
one of these some of these
from these
what's there
all right I should be good
I'll walk back
pull my car around to get in that's true
that is a good point
I think Miko's armor yeah I'm gonna take
I'm gonna transfer a lot of stuff but I
wanted to finish building first so that
nobody takes it
it's a horse
yeah I need a horse
we get all my stuff
build the platform and then destroy it
that is true
that is a good point
I'm going towards it yeah
cross the Bandit camp
the door has to be connected to the
tower it is it is
it's connected
I gotta get rid of
these trees along the road
I don't know maybe as is my tower might
be tall enough to see
somebody's just gonna come with a rocket
launcher and aim it at my tower but
that's why I'm planning to build
hopefully the walls out of stone or
metal I don't think I have enough metal
though to do it
key
ha ha ha ha ha ha
all right
uh okay
I'll come back for this stuff
give me a moment I'm gonna drive my car
over here
all right I'll be able to get it now
hey hey wait
I put the brakes on
what
okay just a little bit closer
[Music]
okay look it's connected see it's
touching
frames are literally the the foundations
are touching it's fine right
[Music]
somewhere over here
all right I have stone right okay
I'll get the rest of my stuff in a
moment
I need the hammer
look at this for now oh listen this
actually maybe I should just keep the
torch since I don't have any light at
the moment
it's a good idea and then
come back for this
[Music]
put in my car it's gonna go into a
backpack anyways it's not going to get
destroyed
oh for now I think I'll just upgrade
this part to Stone
and then
see how much metal
I don't really have that much metal
make that like that
please help make stone
let me get inside my base this is how I
got out
[Music]
okay I'm just gonna make this last
foundation stone and I'll put the rest
in
should we get I don't even need that
much stone in there because it's not
gonna stay
okay
it's decaying
how do you know
I see it's not connected
let me try from up here
maybe if I put a wall
foreign
[Music]
all right I got it watch this
[\h__\h]
all right all right
uh maybe if I extend it this way
mind you this is a base I don't really
care it's gonna get destroyed anyways
probably because I'm gonna [\h__\h] with
people while they're in the casino
I don't think anybody's gonna tolerate
it really
and
let's see
now is it connected
I can't get up now
hi
oh what a mess
look what you guys did
it's gonna be late to put stairs
somewhere here
I'm gonna blaze it
I'm not doing anything [\h__\h] I got an
explosive
I'm doing anything
[\h__\h] this
God bless you stare
downstairs
look
okay
all right now is it connected
I can build the ladder wait let me get
my stuff
oh my God I'm gonna [\h__\h] die trying
to get out of my in and out of my base
I just have to be really careful
I'm gonna put some wood away for now
I didn't want to get
um this
yeah yeah I'm gonna make a sleeping bag
wait
and all these damn pumpkin seeds
don't take any damage
do I need this oh this is the roof
okay
this I will
pick some of these
I said this wait
ah
uh-huh
okay
now let me check my line of sight
I think this is about how tall I should
make it I could see I can see
just barely if I just knock down these
trees I'll be able to see inside look I
can see something blue okay this tree
mark it with a bullet
did I hit it
I'm gonna go take it down now
hopefully without dying oh yeah let me
make a sleeping bag first just in case I
do die
oh my sleeping migrate down here
actually safer down here
uh crafting oh yeah let me put this down
[Music]
foreign
it was blue for a second
it's not it's not most ideal but I don't
even know if I need a I probably don't
oh well I need to put it down anyways
oh my simple bag look right here
hey
oh my base is cool you guys don't think
so
[Music]
all right where's the top so I don't
accidentally close myself in
right here
[Music]
am I like missing a wall or something
I think I've reached the wait oh
okay now I'll build
uh
[Music]
-huh
can I jump up there maybe if I jump it's
so deadly
okay okay
like hang a half wall
it'd be nice if I could just put one
right there like kind of Stack it but
remove the bottom one
I wonder would be better it's okay I'm
gonna make this out of I'm gonna upgrade
this to metal
uh where is it
hammer
wait okay so I have more
metal fragments than I do so it should
it be let's use metal fragments high
quality metal Okay so
this is what I got it's fine it's
probably gonna get destroyed but
okay
let me put my other metal fragments in
here
it's out some of the lower walls I think
I'll have to do out of stone just
because it'll be easier to get
okay
that's all we need
okay it works I can get up I can get up
okay
uh [\h__\h]
all right I have more metal fragments in
here I need to grab
I don't want to grab this let me eat
this last thingy
I want to see if I can put this anywhere
oh yeah I'm gonna put my sleeping bag
down
and then go get that tree
foreign
okay
it's not it's not a bed it's a sleeping
bag I actually don't have a bed I don't
know
where is it in level one
[Music]
level two
windows in all directions
where
then people will be able to shoot me
from behind
I'm just going for the casino pretty
much although maybe I should make this
shorter if I can let me see
I might get as tall as this wall is
so I can get on top of it
I wonder if I could I like that there we
go
and then I'll put something right here
or right here
maybe if I can
okay
all right let me check how much metal so
I have
1 000. okay
well then I just gotta there we go wait
it's pushing me off
let me in okay I can get in I just need
to wiggle a lot
too late I already made it out of metal
all right now
um let me go chop down all that wood I
think I'll just make the internal stairs
out of like the heavier type of wood
I don't know
let me put some
that should be enough
uh
is that the spawn point good point
or bed
wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle wait
yeah
all right wood
I want to see if I could put this
anywhere I don't think I can but that'll
be really funny if I could
no no I can't there's not enough space
damn it
stay away from that I'm gonna put this
back on my truck
oops
um
okay I'll put that away
I'll put these away
and for now I'll put a little sweet and
this will wait in this way
these this
okay should be good for now
actually I don't know if I want to leave
that there
okay let's see if I can find that tree
that I need to get rid of
this is facing
uh
that way
I shot it oh this one I think this is it
is that a bullet hole
I don't know probably gone the Pluto's
probably gone
okay
uh I'll shoot this one's pretty tall
or I'll take down this one
and then I'll take down these two if I
have enough yeah
yeah we're gonna remove the forest
it's fine it's all gonna be removed
anyways
look maybe I won't shoot people people
in the casino but you know as they're
leaving maybe they're gonna mess around
outside you know this seems like a good
area to
make some of these down
all right some tree cover is good I
think
I really won't know when to like check
let me check
steal the scraps
no I wouldn't do that that's ice cold
you think I'm that cold huh
internal check I think I'll have to go
looking for more Stone because I want to
do some of these outside walls I don't I
don't have enough time to get enough
metal fragments to do all of the tower
walls
okay I think I'm gonna remove
this tree
I was looking at that one I'm thinking
about it
but look I got a perfect line of sight
okay so I'll remove this white tree here
and then this big tree there
should npcu not yet not yet
okay I'm gonna upgrade the internal
stairs though get rid of some of my wood
I'll just upgrade the rest of the stuff
that was just throw away
things outside
like am I stuck on
I say no way I'm out of wood already
what the heck okay
nice
so for now I'll leave that let me
upgrade some of these inner walls here
because these are already inside the uh
ah
I wonder if I could no probably not I
was thinking of putting a wall frame
here put it on the good can
I don't know
this one these two I'll make out of
stone but this one I think I'll make out
of wood
I always upgrade it again if I want
okay let me upgrade these
guys
oh my God
I think upgrading it to wood has made it
so I can't get in now
foreign
here we go no problem
oh
I don't know if I want to waste metal
fragments on that
[Music]
I'm just gonna put a bunch of stuff to
absorb like you know shock absorption
like I'll stack
um
[Music]
I just put a wall here
there we go okay this will make a wood I
don't mind it's gonna get destroyed
anyways I think
you know it's fun to leave some weak
spots so that they'll have a chance
otherwise it's just
too cruel
problem just take the stairs normally
shock absorption
[Music]
and then
uh I'll put another short wall there
[Music]
okay yeah weak spot weak spot
I think I'm gonna raise this wall or put
a wall here too because oh man maybe I
can't here we go okay I can
uh only right here
[Music]
I just want to protect
all right I meant to do this
I want to protect this little part
slightly at least somewhat
uh okay
and upgrade that
put another Foundation here just so I
can get up
uh
um
maybe if I put
this
here
oh
I was having my level one array level
two
[\h__\h]
I think that was my level two why did it
break it just decayed on its own is the
workbench decay
yeah I'm gonna put stairs right here
that's why I put this here
my level two workbench no
Something's Gotta fit
somewhere
I could be able to get into my house
like that hold on can I put another one
uh
place them inside
there's no room inside
okay I don't think I really needed
anything I just need to build bear traps
so I do need this
I just hope it doesn't break
would I be able to jump over it if I put
it like right in the door
okay if I put it there I don't think I'm
gonna be able to
see if I can fix it
crap
scrap
[Music]
shoot
I gotta pick it up
it's gonna break
okay I have to take it home to repair it
I have a repair bench there
all right for some of these I'm gonna
make them out of metal
as much as I can
all right I'm all out I think I have
more in my car
all right we're almost ready
I feel like I'm getting close
oh if I can wiggle
let me in
oh
oh oh
I'm almost there
I'll never be able to leave once I
barricade myself and said
go
I forgot to upgrade this one
okay
oh
a few more scraps I'll have one enough
for one more wall uh fragments middle
fragments I might have more at home ouch
I'm gonna move it closer
foreign
what if I just planted them
sure why not
playing a pumpkin
when the pumpkin of Peace grows
that means the war will have ended
because it takes so long for pumpkins to
grow I probably won't even grow and I
think it might grow before the server
wipes
let me upgrade this
all right let me take a look
let me count okay so walls one two three
four five six actually most of the walls
are made out of
metal lucky lucky lucky ah I forgot one
okay I think after that one all of these
above will have been upgraded
just enough now I'm all out
I can't
um
where am I
fell okay
I can't
are these things named railings
the railing is my ladder
Michael
now if I want to I can get up there okay
it's made out of sheet metal nice okay
so
I have
maybe if I put
a few of these in the tool cupboard
then I will
upgrade
okay
Let Me Wait for the date light to come
put some lights in here
yeah I do Crouch and jump it's still uh
just the wiggle
I'm thinking if I should
just upgrade like this these at least
lower walls
because if somebody aims at me with a
rocket launcher they're probably gonna
hit this so I'm wondering if I should
just upgrade these to the the better
metal
what do you guys think like one two
three four five six
wait one two three four five six of
these things
upgrade them
remove the roof no this is so it can uh
jump up here and see all sides
I need to get that 16 times scope wait
how much is that
300 scrap okay I think I have enough
scraps at home
huh
I'm not ready yet
what are all those glittering things oh
those stones
that are glittering in the distance
oh yes I can remove that tree
it's gonna look much better once I have
my 16 times
all right warning shot
I don't see anybody
you could hide in the trees
I'm gonna remove them
trees must be removed
also somebody has like a rocket launch
oh okay a stone I'm gonna go get that
stand right here
aim at me
that's why I gotta get my own rocket
launcher I have enough to make one
that's the last thing I need to research
it's also why I need my level two okay
the next thing I want to work on now
after I take down that tree
uh and get that stone I'm just gonna
upgrade the bottom walls to Stone
and then I'll upgrade upgrade these to
like a better metal
oh yeah I also need a door
[Music]
I think the door that I can make
this one
oh I'll just have to find some stuff to
scrap
all right let me upgrade these
[Music]
foreign just the walls would be okay for
now
some armored
let's see I have enough for the floors
okay that should be good
I wonder though kind of worried about I
might as well with like the extra that I
have because what if it collapses
that should be good
now with these I'll go get her down I'll
just make it wood
all right
I'm gonna empty out all this wood
expensive okay we're still at 13 hours
the only thing that's keeping me at 13
hours I think is uh either this
you have the stone or maybe the metal
fragment no it's just the stone
I'm gonna go collect some more right now
10 minutes left
it's already starting
or is it just until people are going
online
because maybe they need to do some prep
time too
I dropped off all my wood okay okay I'm
gonna [\h__\h] gonna kill me
don't
where's that stone
you
I don't think I'll be able to build the
level 2 workbench in time because I only
have 300 scrab
ble but I kind of have to
oh I'll just drive my car and see what I
can find
because I need fragments to build a door
too wait I don't have any more metal
fragments in here do I
seen
okay
let me get to the road oh yeah let me
get that tree
I know which tree it is
still
uh let me see
actually I don't think I can cut it down
because I think it's too close to the
their base
this tree
I'm risking it
I don't seem to care
I don't care
I really want to break that tree maybe
if I Ram it with my car enough
yeah there was a white tree that was in
the way
which one was it was it the Sun
straight it's that tree
damn it it's that tree
maybe I'll just run in
I'll stay inside the Zone stay outside
the zone go in and out
foreign
dang it okay maybe I'll just uh
use the C4
how do I use it
I think they're gonna start shooting
did it bring down the tree I didn't hear
any tree crash
do they bring down trees
yeah
I want to use all my C4
all right one more
why am I doing anything bad
damn it
need that tree gone
okay we'll go in and out strategically
we're getting it slowly but surely
I got it
tree has been removed now I have clear
line of vision okay
let me go to my house really quick
still hold it up
okay I don't have to
damn I wish I picked up my level two
workbench before it got destroyed
I want to make a rocket launcher I'll
probably just have to work with uh
that's what I got
uh
where's my thing
oh yeah my sniper scope I guess I'll
just get that and just work with all my
ammo
bring this that's all I need
I have to borrow someone's bench
who's gonna let me
all right let me go home and pick up
some last minute stuff
you say two minutes but I don't think
it's gonna start that fast
people still have to log in and gather
their [\h__\h]
you know
[Music]
I have some stuff I can scrap
like my lights
I wish you could pick that up but I
can't
go pick up my door so I could reuse it
okay phone
being scrapped
I'm gonna drop off all this wood
I don't need it
I'll just keep one stack
take one of this for upgrade
actually just take more since the server
is going to end in like what how many
hours
okay I'll just leave it at 24 hours
I can use the door just remove the lock
how do I do that
I don't think you can remove it
foreign
workbench here
goes the phone
uh stuff that I can scrap
oh
I don't think I'll set up the camera so
let's grab that
let me take some stuff out
this
like those
scrap that
the text grab oh yeah I'm not gonna use
it
you take extra ammo with me
and then what do I have the most ammo
I'm gonna put some stuff in my car
[Applause]
what kind of ammo does this use
machine gun probably this ammo
I think I'm good on stones
and wood
[Applause]
[\h__\h] hopefully it doesn't get blown up
immediately
oh God
what did they do
where's my truck
still here
maybe I should just put stuff that's not
that important like the stone in here
instead
I need to scrap like just a few things
so I have enough
metal to fix something
haha
these last few things
uh
some of these some of these some of
these one of these one of these some of
these
uh one of these
all right hopefully that should be good
wait is it did I pick up a shotgun
another Thompson
this is a rifle
I guess oh these
okay hopefully it'll be good wait please
okay
all right I think I'm ready
I'm going back I'm gonna stop by the
recycle thing really quick
hopefully if I have time
ah okay got all my fuel
the last of my fuel
say goodbye to our sweet car
[Music]
it's just all the planes is that like uh
that's how we can get cool weapons and
stuff
help park my car around here
if anybody shoots at it
buys online
I can make 500 maybe I'll have enough
stuff to build my rocket launchers but I
got rid of all my metal pipes
okay let's grab this
uh anything else
I don't have my repair bench
oh I said yeah
this three sandbags
I have pumpkins I have nine pumpkins
okay that should be enough
I saw something over here
[Music]
well I guess not
all right let me collect my stuff and
I'll go
[Music]
right
four base
oh yeah I need to craft the door
um
I only had a love if I had a workbench I
could borrow
s got one
I'll run to Kiara's house I'll drop off
all my stuff
let me get to the road
foreign
something that was not loaded in
I leave my car
actually I just leave it by the house
it's fine if it gets destroyed
oh just push my car away and nobody can
get in
to the house even if they blow off my
door
oh
ow
come on car
even I can't get in
out
[Applause]
than a person I hear
paranoid
yeah hold on I'm gonna put a workbench I
think I can make a level one if I can
make a door
right
this is
[Music]
what are you shooting at my base I never
got my level 16 skull but it's okay
can I be placed on construction
now my door
all right that's what I got
it's not much but it's something
maybe I can quickly go and buy my scope
foreign
I'll just store some stuff in here oh
yeah I gotta get stuff from my car
really quick
and I'll put the rest of my wood
and the rest of this and this
put my door down
I just wait for my box
five four three two one
foreign
out there oh well
it'll just fall out
I'll just put uh this in there this in
there this is this
you should maybe I'll keep some with me
put these extra cool ammo in there
this ammo with me put the extra [\h__\h] gun
in there
uh keep this with me put that in there
keep this put the card key
let me just go pick up
some of the things
it's gonna Decay really
can I move it I can move it I know I can
everything just okay like just doesn't
matter what it is
okay
that's just in case I die and I need it
immediately
stuff
a man let me in
all right my door
unlock
ow
oh [\h__\h] I'm gonna die
I need more food
yay my car key I didn't know you could
get you couldn't get into it without the
make sense
all right not a lot of Health
yeah the entrance is super deadly we
don't need bear traps
we don't need it
I need a better way it's okay I don't
need to really get out after I'm in
huh
come on how
damn it
all right Lisa now I'm at almost full
health
and I can pick up my stuff because my
body was right there
ah
I'm gonna drop a proximity mine here I
think
because I don't think I could push here
we go
okay there's no leaving
no going in and out if somebody pushes
the car over it will it trigger
all right we're in
I have four pumpkins and two bars
maybe if I build a bonfire
that'll be good
so I can get some comfort no 16 times go
but I have an eight-time scope so it's
not bad
still not bad I'm still pretty good with
it I think
okay waiting for my bonfire I'm gonna
put some stuff away here oh yeah I want
to upgrade these last walls
uh to Wood
Stone I mean
better than wood
more durable
I forgot Mikko senpai's tape I was gonna
play in a boombox
well this uh can I put this here
stack
nice comfort
bring up my health
yeah
make some more water
what's the deal with all those planes do
they all drop packages
foreign
you have to use openvc or anything so
I think I'll make this one
I'll die by starvation no worst case
scenario I could just always go back
outside and get uh some bear meat or
something
put a sleeping bag on top I don't think
it matters because uh it's not far
enough away from the other sleeping bag
is everybody just camping their bases
pretty much
of the proximity line I can just jump
over that
no problem
if I have to get out then I'll go get
the 16
time scope
let's see who's online
hey Crouch while doing this
[Music]
um
oh those are just the home phones
Kelly's based the cape so the sheriff's
office is out
[Music]
you think I'm hitting it what is even
the drop off for this like I don't see
the bullet it must drop off quite a bit
huh
is it scan oh okay yeah it looks like it
who is that I don't know whose face that
is
they're shirtless though
how many bullets do I have
uh I have 59 right now on hand but I
have uh 60 more in my
thingy
in my chest
it seems like a tit scan
I don't want to shoot them because I
because I might want to go there for
safety
let's say my debate my base Decay so
much I can maybe make a run
I can make a run for it towards the
casino
why did they come up to check did they
know that it was gonna be that their
turret was gonna
like explode or something
kind of does house
oops
doesn't make good Senpai she probably
doesn't have a camera on here right
see she's got a camera on her shutter
let's open is that like a flame turret
in over there
a flame turret okay
maybe some people will attack in the
night
oh you know I hadn't I have night vision
goggles like I can build them
but I don't have
[Music]
um
okay at least the Knight is short I'll
just
I'll have to
I'll have to hide during the night
but my base uh seems pretty sturdy like
down in there because of all the wood
almost fell
I think I'll take down maybe I'll try to
shoot that turret there I wonder if I
could hit it through the bars
ah
all right the Sun is setting
I bet some people are waiting for the
Knight to attack
with their night vision goggles
get the 16 time scope
no if I if I if I try to exit my house
right now I'm pretty sure I'm gonna
set off the proximity line
let me see
dude
it's because I'm holding this torch
free
I'm gonna die
I'm fine everything is fine
foreign
there
[\h__\h] I forgot my
thingies
well now time to test if the proximity
mine won't blow up my car
it's fine as long as the card doesn't
move
foreign
I will close I will open the door and
push push the car and it'll set up the
bomb
easy
foreign
kids I thought I had syringes and stuff
[Music]
yeah I did accidentally use it
that's true
all right I will wait
[Music]
suicide and respawn at my base that's a
good point
ah
where's my supermarket
N7
supermarket and seven
[Music]
nobody's there
my son should be coming up soon
I'm gonna plant these pumpkin seeds
[Music]
all right I'm back at 60 health
let me wiggle through this
now that it looks like the sky might be
lightning possibly
the dark
oh I'm going I'm going
slowly but surely
there we go
[Music]
all right I think I just leave
a gun or something oh
let me just put down one of these guns
for now
pick it up when I come back
I'll just be going to the store
I'll be back
is that a person or is it a plant it's
definitely plant
all right
let's try not to set off anything
okay just a little bit of damage no
problem
maybe I can buy pants
okay okay
am I gonna join any team I don't know
I kind of just want to snipe people from
my base
and I understand if that's not the most
fun perspective for you to watch but the
good thing is there's a lot of people
streaming so
you have a lot of options
you know there's always a possibility of
teaming up I'm not planning on it but
you
know all right uh to buy
a scope
but it looks like oh hello
Graphics jeans
oh something I need right now
is that stuff
no
uh move over here
like well helicopter still shoot at me
if I have stuff in my inventory
if like uh I'm here food market
might be good to buy something
all right and where's I can just order
stuff there I know I can but I just want
to go to the market anyways
this way
no this way
on the safe Zone you want
ah
over here
all right
that building
here
stuff
turned around this is it weapons
uh one of these all right
what is this gun like I've never shot it
before it's got eight bullets
can't really check it right now oops I
didn't eat one that's fine
maybe I should run home quickly
and oh no I don't even think I have
anything to make it with
actually I might be able to
pants I don't have pants
have claws but I left it inside my base
okay I think I'm good for now since it's
daytime I just want to snipe worst case
scenario like you guys said I'll just uh
suicide
inside and like store all my stuff and
then come back
foreign
let me get some comfort real quick
Comfort on the Fly
okay
so what taxi is just a stool it always
was
it always was
oh so it hasn't started yet
or now it starts
[Music]
it starts now
yeah hey what uh type of ammo does this
use I guess it uses this type
let me see
okay what's this type
all right I have a lot see
all right
[Music]
what what
like like
a wiggle wiggle
oh this is the one with the scope is it
the same gun
although my chat crashed
M39 mp5a4 machine gun oh I probably want
the uh scope on the semi-automatic
if I can shoot anyone
anyone
maybe if there's no action here maybe
I'll go cruise around
[Music]
just some morning shots you know
saw Michael in her base
huh
there
does have a damage drop off
is it still alive did the polar bear
just have like a [\h__\h] ton of Hells
foreign
[Music]
what's the damage fall off on the other
one I was using
if that even is a thing in this game
damage 50 80. damn it second sucks
but I guess because instead
you get
um
higher
all right yeah if I root oh rhetoric
well I guess I'll keep the scope on this
one then
uh plus fire rate yeah I guess it's
better to keep on this current gun
okay
I guess I'll put the oh I put the eight
times
my tummy hurts
maybe I should go collect the bear meat
I could probably get over there
with my chainsaw
I'll just like leave my guns or
something so they don't lose them
let me put another box over here
Ellen Coming
okay I'm in my base they can't see me
right
laughs
but important stuff in here
bring two grenades
there's only second tens oh that's weird
can I put my Boombox down
I can only hold it
away
[Music]
okay
it seems good
it's okay if I lose the boombox
okay
maybe we should always bring a handgun
foreign
or actually I'll just bring the Thompson
reload
okay I'll bring a little bit more
and bolts two grenades and a dream
oh yeah let me bring my chainsaw so I
can cut the bear
where did I put my chainsaw
can I have it with me I guess I left it
at home
let me Craft Like a Knife or something
really quick
up too much
is this the king or is it just breaking
you can't tell
the king
oh yeah what do I need
um
40 metal fragments 100 Wood I can do
that
here bear
oh
and some wood
wiggle again
bandage oh yeah let me get my cloth did
you make a [\h__\h] ton
good idea
I can't change any of the platforms
right now
they're all like set in stone
it's okay this this way is uh you know
it's it's really secure actually this is
a security measure
and it wasn't because I built on some
type of
on top of some weird rock
there we go
oh yeah
let me graph this first
oh I can build a pistol
I thought I could build a machete wait
[\h__\h] I don't get enough wood damn it
what else can I make
um
tools
X
okay I'm gonna put something hold on I'm
gonna craft I'll just put my materials
up here because I might as well
uh
I just grabbed all my wood
I don't even need that much of it here
apparently
grab all of these
wiggle again
everybody's fighting I'm done wiggle I'm
here wiggling actually I don't hear any
bullets so I don't think anybody's
fighting yet
because you can hear gunshots from like
pretty far away
I think some planning is still going on
all right let me craft
s here what's the best to get a bear
with
uh like mcpants
better than nothing
advantages
let's make or can I only make 10 at a
time
okay can I walk away from my workbench
while it's working
the greatest enemy is my base
I'll be able to make a syringe if I get
enough animal fat I have some already
but okay so anyways uh
again okay
with good range this seems good instead
of an ax
now I gotta wait for all this stuff
all right well uh
let me see
let's see from here kind of
um
what is that
somebody else build a base or is that a
water tower
does that look a person made
any plans for Rockets yeah I wanted to
but my workbench broke I brought my
workbench
what was that I heard a beep
did you guys hear that
maybe that's just my proximity mind
finally going off
let me put my adventures in here
I can't tell if
like this thing is decaying is it or is
it just normal wear and tear
do you think it's decaying
oh God I can't hold all these bandages
it is
what the heck
can I put another tool cabinet here then
ah
let me put this here for now
I think it's gonna make three each
use one now
[Music]
yeah yeah I'll just put it to a cabinet
just uh
make sure this one's not decaying now
because this one's attached to my base
but this one is
I'll put it uh
where should I put it
[Music]
that's a it feels like if I put it there
I'm just gonna shoot it
[Laughter]
foreign
maybe I could connect this somehow
oh
base inspection yeah
um
I'm gonna put one here
here
go about this
what about
it's about to break
um
oh if only I could connect it just a
little bit just one connection a wall
frame
even that does not connect
s here but that's about it
I don't know what that's gonna do
uh
this considers another building but I
built it
ah
I wish there was a way to just connect
it easily that's lame
I will for now I'll just
keep it myself
I'm the
thingy
all right now I have to find a better
place for this because
it's not gonna stay
maybe if I do this
why can't I get this damn Boombox out
I think I grew over I built over the
pumpkin oh no
not the pumpkin
better
all right I'm gonna build one of these
you have my machete I got my machete
I'll just put one of these down uh
maybe like just right here
that might be good
right there that'll fit that'll work
sure I don't think it'll fit on that huh
it might wait it might
find out
ah
[Music]
it's touching
snatching and snatching and snatching
now is it working
look look
it's more stable isn't it
I can't tell
anyways
importantly
oh
okay
I planted some of these
laughs
pumpkins for days
[Music]
okay I think I'm good now
I'm ready to go
oh yes 10 bullets in a dream
hey let me go get my polar bear probably
despawn by now
hold on before I go let me just check
do do
all right now I can check
my 16 time scopa
so much wiggling involved
I wonder what is Cara online yet is she
streaming it
ah
there is gone
it's all right I'll shoot something else
what is that oh yeah okay so it's just a
just a base thing what was that
foreign
[Music]
still preparing
maybe somebody wants to do some gambling
yeah I can't see inside look at that the
doorway's right there but I can't see
inside
I built away from everyone but the
casinos here this was my plan
wait
I thought I saw someone
damn they're that far
it's not in the middle of nowhere this
is the place look this is the spot
this is the casino spot
Senpai is here it goes Empire's here and
my house which has like six people
surrounding it is not that far away
wow they do war in a safe Zone what is
the point of War money and what do you
do with money you gamble it
the
you guys just aren't thinking ahead like
I am
where are all the Bears at though I
don't know
okay I'm going over there
to get my loots
you've wore a chance yeah yeah yeah let
me get my bear meat and then I'll
come back
and take out my car
did I have grab some stuff to fix up my
car because it's kind of low right now I
guess for now I'll just bring my pistols
extra and a few extra bullets just in
case
put on my pants
okay
I'll bring this to fix my car
I'm gonna grab some heavy metal and I'm
good to go
all right you don't really need that
much heavy metal to fix the car
oh yeah I can't move my car
there's a oh wait I could I should just
I should be able to disable the
proximity button right because I'm not
standing on it somebody else has to
disable it
this [\h__\h] thing
this damn thing hold on I'm about to get
out my freedom oh so close
come on
I should build a ladder
I think I might be able to actually I'll
do it I'll do it when I'm back
how's it looking okay
[Music]
easy
ah I forgot my car key [\h__\h]
uh
dang it I'm gonna wiggle again I need I
need to build a ladder I'm gonna build
the ladder
done with this
where's my scrap
no more wiggling
stop it
hopefully this is enough to research a
ladder
I think it might be
oh the latter I've already researched it
oh the Rope I need rope
I can't craft rope can I
rope
damn it I can only find it I've gotten
rid of those 10 of rope because I
decided I did not need it all right well
I'm gonna go out and find
some rope
I forget my car key
which I did not forget and it's
somewhere in here
foreign
[Music]
one day
come on before my pig disappears
okay
that time was faster
only takes a few seconds
hey
all right my pig
I think it's over here
maybe I'll go on a
suicide mission
taking my truck out
the party
all right when the morning comes
I will go
hey maybe there's some stuff I can break
over here I thought I saw some barrels
or something
there's some barrels on the side
you know those are some stuff we could
recycle Maybe
all right all right I'll come back out
when it's
night when it's morning
and I'll go look
I'm hungry
real life
I'm gonna heal before I get up there
okay
wait what's in here
all right this stuff
kinda would be cool if I
no no no
never mind
I'm not going to
my workbench is gone
wait I moved it nevermind sorry I'm
going crazy you know how long I've
played Russ like without proper sleep
foreign
comes I will go
[Music]
wait let me get my sniper
oh
go
only a few bullets or explosions I've
heard so far where did I put it
when the night
[Music]
and the land is dark
Ness
no I won't
be afraid what was that
hello
oh
I've downed someone
the war has begun for real
we're all into safety I feel bad who is
that is that kind of testify
oops
we're a little war don't walk around at
night
[Music]
I don't have any more bullets
not that I would have finished them off
anyways
one kill for Amit
he'll count number one I don't have any
more bullets they're downstairs okay I
still see your flashlight or if her
light has gone out oh no
actually pretty easy to see people in
the dark when uh
they're wearing a flashlight on their
head
now my base on the other hand the only
thing you can see is the menacing
silhouette
against the night sky
go looter in the morning
I'll wait
here I'll light up you're ready to go
out
I could use a nice uh flashlight for my
head I'm not gonna take everything
though I feel bad I'll just take some
things
I'll just take a few things
oh
let me get up if it's kind of the Senpai
then her she's gonna be able to get to
her body really fast
I'm gonna wait until the morning comes
I got my Thompson
he's behind a rock
a truck a truck right
around there
or was it a different Rock
let's find out
okay I'm gonna die
oh I'm gonna lose my stuff maybe I'm
better protected in my car
okay it's fine
I'll get my spoils
I'm gonna die going back into my house
I'm gonna die to the door
why don't you crawl to
I'm gonna lose my armor if I die out
here
was it behind this rock
hard to see in the morning son
let me it must be like around here
no she couldn't have survived nobody
would have picked her up she would have
died okay I was here and it was this
first rock
that'll be here
where did you go
the only way she could have survived is
that somebody picked her up
yeah I don't hear any flies or anything
maybe she really did Escape
maybe she crawled up this hill
you're down for quite a long time so
oh but I found it for a second I wish
you could have got up here
my rock
huh well then let me see again from
my perspective
there's my tower
it was the first rock she crawled behind
this one
it's rewind time
you've gone for the tip kill I ran out
of uh I ran out of bullets
I only had four and loaded or I only had
three loaded
damn she could have gotten anywhere
let me check this rock
[Music]
but I heard footsteps
all right I couldn't find I'm going back
to my tower
the the tower the tower works
I don't have to leave
I was gonna get in the car and drive
around a little bit
I don't lose the car what if I need the
car as an escape
hopefully she's part of a team she'll
come after me challenge me I left the
door open again
one of these days it's because every
time I leave I'm like about to die okay
usually I don't take any damage when I'm
going in though
I know we're fine look
this is my
is how it
I have to have it here because of the
door
I have to have it because otherwise I'll
die through this goddamn Barbed wires
how's my base looking
at a pretty slow rate
[\h__\h] the binge just suck
I'm gonna go heal up top I can get a
good look
excuse me
God I need to build a ladder I need to
find robe
it's me
oh and take what I need
I don't have a little two workbench
maybe if I kill someone who has like 400
scrap I can build one and then I can
make more ammo because I have a [\h__\h] ton
of gunpowder at my house
still
still up
I don't hear anything any destruction
happening okay wait
I was shooting her and it was
was it here was it there
I was I think I was checking the wrong
rock formation
you let me Mark it
somebody's close
foreign
ER
do I take the shot
do it
foreign
did I do it I feel bad that this is rust
right
enter
[Music]
I feel bad
foreign
I can get out without taking any damage
damn I still have to heal
[Music]
was somebody going back for their for
their mainly
and just heal while I'm wiggling see the
wiggle is good
that means I can heal
let me take more
okay
did it I got out without taking any
damage
[Music]
behind this bush
foreign
[Music]
again
oh
I think I'll leave everything else and I
just take that
[Music]
um
I could use some more grenades
oh oh I feel bad
okay I'll leave so she can gamble them
what's a funny number
about 69
.
I actually kind of need a shirt or
something is she wearing a shirt
yeah okay well
I'm gonna take some of these
oh I need all of these
oh yeah I think I'm good
I just took the sniper bullets and I
only took some of these because I don't
really need the pistol bullets too much
I feel bad
but this is the war time right that's
dangerous
now she will spread the word
spread the word of
she's probably gambling right now
all right let's see if I can manage this
oh no damage
I think she's gonna stay away for now
but
there's um
you know
her body's hidden right now in like the
bushes so if she did come back for it I
think she would be able to get it okay
I hope it doesn't all Decay and go to
waste she still has a chance to recover
most of it
I'm being generous here I would say
what is that
holy [\h__\h]
me too me too
it was helicopter
did somebody just take that down on
their own doesn't it take a lot to take
down the helicopter
because senpai's helicopter really
oh no
then tag Kelly yeah I was reading online
about uh
how to like take down stuff
or take down the helicopter and it I
guess it has a ton of damage it's hard
to do alone
because I buy his helicopter no
I meant do you need me
uh
oh yeah what did you send me a message
underscore I'll check
no it doesn't look like it
I'll drop her off the phone
my course
I'm not gonna say in the global chat
it's safe she can get her corpse it's uh
right there behind that bush
hey wait a second
it's trap it's not a trap I'm just
saying I could probably wave at her or
something from here I don't know oh I
have my microphone wait did I bring it
didn't I bring it with me
not in the global check Kiara come on
yes go gamble please go gamble
I didn't leave my megaphone
mascara baiting me out there so I can go
all right I'm gonna drive to my house
quickly but I'm gonna drop off all my
stuff except for the Thompson
because I'm scared I'm gonna lose it all
all the scrap that I've
accumulated accrued
okay I'm going I'll go pick her up or uh
let me let me make another phone so I
can give her one so we can chat
stuck
I don't think this vase can accommodate
for two people wait how many scraps for
a phone or how many
foreign
okay I gotta go pick up my megaphone
because I think it'll be good to shout
at people from the casino or at the
casino from here
and I will make an extra phone for Kiara
so she can have one that's good because
then she could call me go Senpai or what
have you
what if it's a trap okay I'm going home
first
phone
all right let's wiggle wiggle wiggle
Let's Wiggle Wiggle Wiggle
slowly slowly
oh I found the I found the key
all right
exit slowly
okay
don't even have any fuel
I should have brought some stuff to mix
at home well Philly I'm not wiggling
again
car is a little obvious I think
okay the the bombing sounds further away
I still have some fuel door nobody can
get in
even if they do they're gonna be like
what the hell
I'm gonna be back quick
imagine if they try to get in they're
gonna get [\h__\h] by the barbed wires
all right maybe I'll stop by the
supermarket and pick up some rope if
there's any
majillion
my machete
I've got the weapon at home
if it's still up
yeah
oh God what if she's camping her base
I can have a few click
that one's kind of close
well let's start deceiving though the
gunshots kind of like it's probably
pretty far away but
it kind of sounds close
okay the house is still up
my things are gone
oh no I think I picked that thing up
okay
uh wait a second
[Music]
oh I can build a level two workbench now
okay I'm gonna bring all my gun powder
with me oh I can make the okay oh I
should have brought my hammer wait I
think I have an extra one here
I have wood
Orange
blades
my megaphone
yeah I have enough ammo
I'm gonna just bring my mixing table
with me
and all this fuel
let me let me meet Kiera first and then
I'll come back and pick up all this
stuff
just in case she's planning something
I walk we're gonna eat
because tape all right I'll bring it
so empty without all these houses so
many of them decayed
[Music]
noelle's not home right
oh my God Kiara how am I supposed to get
in
hello
I'm not gonna have lucky right now
not home right now
I don't feel like walking back is there
a waiting
isn't their way in
she's at the casino
fine
can I get out
here we go
oh no problem
all right I'll go back then I'll take
all my stuff and I'll meet her at the
casino let me drop off all my things
and I have some food at home I'll take
extra food
I need some metal pipes I thought I
saved them but I think I recycled them
because I was like well I don't think
I'll be able to make rockets anyways
I shouldn't be holding a grenade just in
case just in case my finger slips
I'm gonna go home make sure the door's
closed let me take some of this food
beans beans
berries oh my pipes
I might be able to scrap this
all right I'll leave this at home just
in case
oh yeah I want to take this table with
me
let me build a hammer
get the mixing table home
let me just double check
I got the megaphone here
this extra stuff
but it seems good
okay let me eat
oh I don't want to take Michael's tape I
feel like it's safer here
what am I taking or the mixing table
I don't know if I have anywhere to place
it I'll I'll make it work
I'll find something
I want to take the mixing table so I can
make
[Music]
um
more ammo if I need it
fuel I got it
oh
kind of dangerous to take the main road
but I think it's faster
hopefully she's not home
take my metal pipes to the metal pipes
hey
pick me up okay okay you're not gonna do
anything weird in my base right
[Music]
I thought you got oh come on I mean what
about the corner beans
okay maybe oh hold on I'll give you my
key but give it back okay here pick it
up hey
guys
what about the car derby uh
what about it wait I gotta get back on
the road actually
I got scared because I saw you later
oh I know if anybody's gonna be
interested maybe interesting today
I look interesting
you look interesting yeah uh Miko
senpai's armor
oh this is the wrong way oh nice
this goes towards the other area
team up what are you doing what have you
been up to
you saw my face right yeah I saw I saw
it
fine don't worry about it
we're good we're good I
am I have nothing
I I I tried my best to upgrade my base
but it's not as good as yours can I
wait can I leave what casino
oh yeah yeah this is my base all right
you can go
you gonna walk yeah
uh don't shoot me when I walk to the
casino I know your plan
okay bye
yeah I'm parking
oh my car key oh yeah I can have a bag
[Music]
thank you see you later bye
good luck
all right I gotta drop off my stuff oh
wait Kiara come back
come back
foreign
[Music]
okay here
this is a phone so that you can call me
if there's an emergency
[Music]
I don't know how to use it but we'll
figure it out
Good Luck Good Luck how loud is it
sound funny on her side I don't know how
I don't know how loud the megaphone
actually like does it work like it's
supposed to
oh no damage this time
and I'm hungry
[Music]
okay I got a lot of stuff to put away
oh yeah I gotta put down my mixing table
well let me put some stuff away first
foreign
No One's Gonna Go
see ya
I'm 12 steps ahead of you kid
also yeah I think I need to make a new
area okay let me just uh
organize my thoughts along with my items
uh can I put this in here
but then there wait I'm gonna put that
uh
what am I putting in here wood
[Music]
some powder so I'm gonna mix this I
might as well do it now maybe
I'm gonna recycle this
bullets I'm gonna use this for crafting
extra fuel
let me eat all these tuna cans
and I'm full
okay well let me replace it with hold
this
put down this way actually I'll store
these in the fire because I'm gonna cook
them anyways
and that wood when I put the wood in the
other thing okay
store this in here
okay
and I'm running out of space I need to
build another thingy
[Music]
I think if I have one more small thingy
it'll be good put it like right here all
right in the meantime
where's my blueprints
I can organize this take these
condensed these
uh put this away this way this way this
way this way
and
um
okay now I can put some more stuff away
binoculars you know
uh put a sponge away for now I'm Gonna
Keep one
advantages okay I'll put gunpowder away
now because I don't know if I'm gonna
make it right now
and stuff I want to scrap
okay
my car key away for now I don't need it
and stack this take this phone Hammer
where's my scraps
I haven't joined a team yet no
there we go now I can build I'm gonna
put this away in the cabin and these
and now I can build
um
I can make ammo
wait I need some wood
for building okay
let's see where can I place the mixing
table
uh if only I had any room
uh I could put it up top here oh god oh
I need robe to build a
maybe I can
I'll call Kiara I don't think she has
her number set up yet
just needs to put her name her number
okay here we go I'll set it right here
I got a Decay right okay now I can mix
syringes and I can mix
um some more ammo
do the merchant cell rope
uh yeah I really need a ladder I don't
think they sell rope because I was
looking to see if they sold any
like stuff to craft with but they don't
they're gonna shoot them now all right
let me see where everybody's at
I don't think I can actually see people
inside the casino but I think I can I
want to get my sniper I think I can
see them going in and out
where do I put my sniper
here we go
I feel bad about said uh she was like a
walking pinata
this wiggling is not so bad
if they exit through this door because I
know there's a door right there I'll be
able to see them as they walk on this
bridge
I pretty much be able to see any like
NPC in the area
so what what are kill count right now is
that two both times
both times were her
see anybody though
Miko Senpai home
you don't think they're gonna leave
damn
if only I had my computer table then I
could check the casino camera
maybe I should bring it
maybe I'll do that the next time I go
out
the war areas on the left side of the
map or areas everywhere isn't it or is
it actually designated to like one area
I wouldn't be surprised
if they're there's rules now where uh
you cannot do War around the safe Zone
shoot through the door here I'll shoot
through this window
foreign
shooting some morning shots
yeah just scaring them a little bit
is that Kiara I'm not gonna shoot I'm
not gonna
they're like oh my God what's happening
what's happening
looks like the auto turret's still up
well I'm the only one who would attack
them I think in this area
take the shot
no
I'll shoot at the entrance again
well
the sparkly thingies is that what it is
the turrets
they can't take damage within a safe
Zone really
well if that's the case
just annoying them
all right now stream's knife being it's
the rules
she's baiting me
is that said
is Kelly yelling something
this is the safe Zone
I didn't know that was transmit
you know if Kelly has a problem she can
call me
but I lost my place where my hell
damn I was gonna I was gonna shoot I
thought that was her
all the casino oh yeah let me call the
casino
okay oh she didn't name it
I was gonna ask her if she could trade
someone for uh
about that
uh hello hello
[Music]
uh
can you stop please oh no no I wasn't
straight up please kill that person
all right let's keep an eye out
oh girl I wanted to ask if uh you know
you know trade for trade I did you a
favor you know get to get you a phone
some communication going
I kind of need like three rope
oh okay I'll uh I'll trade you
I'll see what I can do all right thank
you
call me back if you find anything
so dark
and I put my scraps away
before someone comes to murder me in my
sleep
all right stuff too that's your torch
stuff too
recycle
Mr wood good friends don't need right
now Hammer I'll keep
and my extra
phone let me grab this instead of these
yeah yeah it looks like we gotta look
out for the person shooting at the
casino guys
no I don't have night vision goggles but
I have them unlocked now that hold on
let me
ah
my phone rang for a second how do I pick
up a call anyways
maybe maybe she canceled it
Casino
uh
you can walk to me in the in the morning
in the Morning Light I won't I won't
snipe you I swear
okay okay bye
[Applause]
trust me no I wouldn't
then she'll have trust issues with me
forever what am I doing oh yeah I was
just gonna grab some scrap
and whatever I need to make the level
two workbench
again I don't know where I'm gonna put
it because I don't have any room
or oops
um
crafting
work bench level two
I need 500 metal fragments and 20 high
quality metal there I have enough high
quality metal but I don't think I have
enough fragments it's okay I'm gonna go
recycle some stuff anyways
I'll go out there and meet her
put my sniper away just in case
I just have stuff to recycle and
grenades
I'll go out
there we go
yeah I'm gonna recycle the casino
oh God this mixing table
holy what's up with my door is it hello
no oh it's just that yeah that is slowly
decaying
mix it up a little
oh yeah this one's connected to my other
thing
oh that wall collapsed I was here
okay this one's connected
okay everything else looks good
for now
right metal fragments
so kind but I don't know maybe she's
really fine her Tech Tree I don't really
need those scraps I should oh hi hi
uh here you can have all of it I
actually had uh some rope with me oh
thank you I'm going to the casino now
that's the cost of your phone
nine rope for phone is a pretty good
deal no no problem then
cause uh
just wants us all to have fun together
they close the door yeah [\h__\h] there's
Windows there's glass windows
[Music]
the door
hi
cool armor I like your strawberries oh
thank you
hello who are you
I'm here
I'm just recycling some stuff I'm gonna
use the recycling for you okay there's
another one uh right around here
sure I'll use it I'd love some more
scrubs
[Music]
cribe
whiskey
black jacket you need how much 500 to
make a workbench and then I can make a
rocket launcher and I don't even think
I'll have enough maybe I should mine
some metal that'll take a while
okay
[Music]
huh
let me check
launcher inside oh can I shoot rockets
inside
no no no I wouldn't do that is the door
open I left the door open
so I need it I don't think I can get
close enough
I wouldn't do that you know they're
they're having their peaceful times as
soon as they leave the safe grounds
though
I feel like that's
that's pretty fair
I heard something
you'll survive
all right next uh I need to build a
workbench but let me see if I can
possibly
let me see if I could maybe get my
get a flat surface where I could even
put it
what does it sound
is that a copter
now
let's see bring that I'm gonna stuck in
my scroll wheel
I may come play
I am playing
there's no time for cards that's what
I'm saying
imagine if if gooda wanted to use my
base with her rocket launcher
shoot Rock Casino where am I going oh in
here
I'm trying to get
a good place to put a workbench right
War
M where can I put
see maybe the triangle
somewhere
I might be able to fit it down there in
one of those thingies
don't know yet
I know I need 500 scrub
uh
wait let me check again
maybe I have enough I have 104 fragments
ah I have just enough but then I'll run
out I need 361 to keep the base up for
24 hours and it doesn't need to be up
for 24 hours oh
Mass quick Mass
okay can last for
five hours
what am I doing what
oh am I grabbing it from there
just enough
okay
new investigator hello
uh and 20 high quality metal
the 500 scrap
wait wait wait did I read it wrong
500 metal fragments right 20 minutes
yeah yeah okay okay
it's making sure
it smells good
all right now I can build a ladder
and
let's do that first so let's do this
first
there goes all of that
so much scrap to waste
I could have probably borrowed carrots
oh you can put armor in your horse I
didn't know that
uh
and then
wait maybe I should cancel it and then
just go into Kiara's house because I
have a two
a two
level two workbench
is that okay if I ask you guys is it
cheating
yeah I'm just gonna make a ladder
unless you didn't have level two
dang it
I don't want to waste so much crap
yeah I'll call her and ask
um
do you have a level two workbench in
your house
you have level two
yeah okay I have the key so I let myself
in
here all right now more of this damn
wiggling
where to put the letters away
hey
finally
okay let me put some stuff away so I
made the ladder let me check the recipes
for the thingies
kit
four metal pipe high quality metal I
don't have that much
high quality metal
maybe I can scrap something in my house
what a good crack my back
oh that's not good oh four cracks
you guys hear it
uh two middle pipes ten explosives
just a regular rocket
uh even if I don't need a rocket
launcher what else
can I make it the level two workbench
foreign
here
all right so I could make rocket
launchers that's an option
I'm not cutting her off she's just
hanging up
I can make rocket launchers and rocket
two rockets at people the other thing is
I only have six metal pipes so I can
build one rocket launcher and one rocket
I don't have explosives yet I don't know
what you need to make explosives oh let
me I wish I could check my oh yeah
uh explosive
just the regular explosives gun powder
low-grade fuel sulfur metal fragments
so I need that times five I don't know
it doesn't seem worth it right now
doors closed huh
[Music]
um
I'm gonna go get a snack
I'm kind of hungry
a lot more kills
I want to shoot
Subway's a good source of vibes
and we can go
look for Shum
oh PB J that does sound good
maybe I should
and eat a fruit maybe I'll go cut a pear
all right we're good we'll go on a quick
break I need you guys to watch the base
for me okay
let me get down here
all right
oh we go wiggle inside here
okay watch the base for me okay
okay
I don't think anybody will come anyways
oh but let me plant uh oops
sorry let me plant that uh
what is it
the proximity mine
Where'd I put it
here
oh you have the letter
we wiggled no more
we are free
[\h__\h]
I gotta put a floor there wait can I put
one
okay
um
damn it
please
come on
it's underneath that other thing I mean
the other thing went under it shouldn't
be a problem right
uh
I'm on wiggling Duty
I can get a cross note no problem
the other thing went on can I not put
like a
whatever whatever it's fine it's because
it's a triangle frame I think I'm not
gonna break it's too much with something
here this looks empty
looks weird
okay
let me go put this mine down
am I just too far
let me push this a little back
wait how am I gonna get back in
well then I'll plant it when I'm up top
okay I'll push it back
hi
[Music]
oh I'm gonna die
all right now that let me heal
down
[Music]
and just I should not get hit by it
push the car
plant the bomb
it's right inside that rock I'm gonna
forget about it
okay now I will go AFK after I eat
something I hear
bombs pretty close that sounded kind of
close
okay
am I gonna get out now
don't worry about it I'll I'll think
about that later
okay watch the base while I'm away
put text on the screen so people aren't
going crazy
okay we're back
foreign
[Music]
how's it going welcome back thank you
sorry I decided to eat my PB J
in the kitchen instead of trying to eat
it on stream because uh
[Music]
sticky
gluten-free bread is really small so
I got a snack
I could open it
open it
oh are you shooting
it's dark oh I don't want to go check
but as soon as the sun comes up
it's not safe I don't have my
run
someone called me I got a missed call
dang
I wonder who was
Yara
[Music]
foreign
okay the sun's coming up
I got some seaweed
I already ate the PBJ I cut a pair but
it was too ripe so I had some of it but
it was really squishy so
I had to throw it away
I had to drive it away it was pretty
much like all
bruised and stuff
sniping's a good job mate
well I sit here and eat seaweed
where's she pairs
so what all is happening can I ask for a
news update is that it's considered
stream sniping
I just want to know what's happening in
the server you know
[Music]
my parents do not care for it I haven't
seen that TF2 shorts in a long time
Luna's house fell oh no
who have joined forces
did you say
they fight in the West
hmm
like over here look by good as base
oh
sounds like a strong team
strong enough for the Boston though the
Snipes in I don't know
Cali went home where's your home
collapsed did she rebuild it or
something
thank you
also by night
dangerous I saw
hmm
because you know I get overrun
can you even kill like the NPCs to the
point where you can take over like the
safe Zone
okay I want to go to a car derby oh okay
okay yeah we can go to the car derby if
if she gets enough people go in and
Hypes them up or something
well there's enough cars people could
throw grenades at the cars or something
I'm just worried about the floors like
of the Derby because they're made out of
wood so if we throw grenades at the cars
the floors are gonna break
I have killed I have two kills by the
way okay
I've gotten many Spoils of War so yes I
have gotten kills this is a good spot I
can see people in the casino
when they come out
what am I hearing
oh I think it's just Mickey making noise
this is kind of like a boombox
try beating them
just it's so risky
did I down
no
maybe I don't know I don't think so is
Kylie talking to me
I guess I have enough uh
what's the Derby coordinates oh
I 13. wait let me just double check that
yeah I 13.
[Applause]
all right all right I'll meet them I'll
meet them at the derby
I will leave my sniper here
just in case
I can always come back
um
leave my good armor
and I'll take the Thompson
maybe I should take the
yeah I'll take the machine gun
and
we already have grenades
see loose bullets put this back
back
all right
I'll take a machete just in case we need
to melee
and I'll bring some corn even though
there's food at the place yeah I'll make
this while I'm there I'll pick this bag
some of these
all right I think I'm set I can put the
blueprints away
oh right the mine yeah I'll be careful
um I think that's everything oh
hello I'll ask the important questions
yeah yeah I'm gonna go I'm on my way
where are you
um
outside
and she just called me for a ride
oh yeah my key
okay I think that's pretty much it I
think I'm set with that
am I forgetting anything
maybe some more grenades because that
sounds
dangerous over there
probably nah I'll just wear the armor
it's fine I could always snipe
better than nothing
some more grenades
I have some more here heal up yeah yeah
[Music]
okay let's try not to
trigger this bomb oh good
oh God
[\h__\h]
dang it oh I could have respawn at the
Derby but then I wouldn't have my stuff
I hope it wasn't too messed up
oh they're shooting happening close by
okay let me get my stuff and then I'll
go back in
yeah at least we know it works right
is my car okay
[\h__\h] you
carb good
looks like it's okay
all right now I'm ready
maybe I should bring some stuff
uh to fix the car and it's probably fine
okay
I want to close my door
not that anybody can get in right now
anyways
didn't really do any damage to anything
well because I guess I mostly hit the
rock on the map
is that Kiara here walking
oh wait how much gas do it I don't
really have that much gas
shoot hello piggy you want to go
[Music]
all right I spawn in my house
actually maybe I'll just wait I feel
like running I'll just sit here and eat
seaweed
stupid door
hmm
I don't feel like running
it takes the same amount of time doesn't
it
my List's not gonna despawn
all right I'll spawn
I'll make a run for it
foreign
I feel is inside the other base
I cannot call Kiara my phone is in my
dead body
well I guess it wouldn't be so bad if I
died
because then I could just respawn
at my bed
we're almost there we're not that far I
think
I can see it
foreign
car troubles
not the dog
okay
what's the pig is still there
what bushes
look how they open for me
okay
now
let me just go back inside quickly
grab some fuel so I can actually drive
plus I need all that fuel for the Derby
itself
foreign
[Applause]
troubles but uh they're fixed now so you
can come over here I'm just getting
something for my base and we'll go
awesome
excuse me
no cars day
I hear a chainsaw
you're right do you have any help
yourself there
uh any what no don't worry about it all
done
my my base is too good
it's too good to let yourself in huh
I can do it I'm not gonna take any
damage it's very strong
if I do no problem I'll be able to
respawn
okay
I'll just grab my fuel I don't have any
healing items with me sorry
the car
what
easy ow
oh yeah one second it's my smoke grenade
me
sounds like
eat one thing
how about having anything better where's
all my food stuff did the pig eat it
and I have some oh no more wiggling
ladder
okay I'm ready I'm going looking good
yeah yeah okay FP okay I need the key
again to get in I guess
hold on let me get him first
hold that let me back up
that's your way of backing up huh
oh don't stand behind
don't stand behind the car don't stand
behind the car
[Laughter]
oh there you go
okay we're gonna run out of fuel soon
hold on let me mark it on the map really
quick
what the heck Kelly give her one
there it is
Justice
oh yeah I like it it's really nice thank
you
foreign
sounds good
I learned it um
[Music]
yeah
yeah trumpet oh there's a tuba holy [\h__\h]
yeah I didn't think it was so big
I was just expecting her to have the
trumpet damn I want a tuba it looks
really cool
I have all my ammo and stuff wait
where's my gun
okay
well then I forgot I forgot something on
the floor really quick
I just I left something on the ground I
gotta pick it up
okay and take one minute
just in case I can't go one arm
s
the fourth person could be um uh Bales
fourth person oh for the Derby
yeah I wonder what she's up to
she did I think she's just starting to
stream rest right now oh okay so it's a
good timing to get her reeled into the
Derby how nice
by the way do you have any metal scrap
or not scrap do you have any uh metal
fragments
oh I wait uh perhaps
yeah I don't need them anymore
where's my gun
must be over here
I'm confused okay Metals perhaps a metal
metal whatever
It Go Do you have any wood you see it
did you get it yeah I got it I picked it
up I'm not gonna use all of it I just
need some of it
no wood unfortunately okay that's fine
could I have the key bag can you drop it
on the floor
[Music]
thank you
damage high quality medal for that one
do you have any high quality metal
is one
all that with me
by quality
okay I can give it all back when we stop
okay we're ready to go not but don't
worry I don't need it oh that's true
he woke up immediately dead oh
Ward Zone oh
must be pretty tough out there
kill on site huh
you sound dangerous
[Music]
yeah
I'm sorry I couldn't help it okay I
didn't do it again
[Music]
to be like that in the middle of a war
yeah
although I think they wouldn't shoot
like uh people that are naked or
something but I guess
it doesn't matter
um
personally I wouldn't shoot somebody
that was a naked kid
his members are
[Music]
open now like oh
hungry or
violin sucks
awkward
nice tree
what what what is it
oh
probably
yeah yeah under attack right now oh
are we getting alive
I'm gonna say it's too strong can't
bring that one down the Derby oh it is
we have the rock kinda
yeah I just gotta get down this hill
no problem I've done this before careful
is there a hill Oh Yeah there does I see
it there's the entrance skiing
oh oh
whoa
I knew I spoke too early sorry
okay we're here hello
[Music]
are you here
collect the fire
yeah she died here
what was that it's not something Flash
oh and look at those cars yeah well that
one's a little bit longer than the other
ones is there music playing I don't hear
anything oh
[Music]
hi an MPC hi an MPC killed me I needed
no [\h__\h] is on your head
it's okay girl
very cool I'm gonna go grab my balls
oh my God
oh it's like fever died hey baby wait
[Music]
the freaking water bottle stuck
yum yum
[Music]
used water
nice you can actually record it you can
record it and play it
oh no no no no it's fine I'm the
recorder I'm I'm the music
kind of space for this I guess not I put
my life today on the on the dance floor
it looks oh realistic so immersive
[Music]
oh yeah dance dance collab with amen
can you do can you do this gel did she
die again like right here just standing
can you do this
yeah I'm right there
what on my stream I'm right there
I was asking about Cali where was she
I forgot my song
what's that what's with callion
uh
[Music]
she's she lost her instruments somebody
put a turd on her bed nearby
yeah I don't think does that happen just
bye
coordinates
get back into position
s
[Music]
I made myself the big
where am I
um
[Music]
age 14
all right you want to stay here you want
to go you're going down man yeah
I'll wait one second one second
[Music]
um
she had a house yeah
come on
I'm coming
playing with the Dance Floor wasn't she
and
oh do you need the key
and I gave it back to you before I
dropped it on the other side there it is
oh yeah I can't remember instruments
actually Cara can you uh
all done
uh can you drive that car I'll take the
other car
yeah we can't pick up three I forgot I
took off the uh backs of these trucks
too
oh let's see this one
this one's probably the easiest to get
back in
does it have fuel
why is this one so long oh this is where
I parked my other car that's right this
is the bus I was using and I took off
the parts and I scrapped them
oh [\h__\h] I forgot to put this thing here
hold on
I did this so nobody would steal my car
[Music]
almost done
on those protection
okay let's go to age 14.
okay
[Music]
oh wait hold on I think it's the other
way or wait what age 14.
I think she's going there what are you
doing
in my car
okay it's this way back it up
maybe underneath
[Music]
says there's an auto turret oh it's this
place
Cali
galley
middle of age 14.
where is she hiding
hello
hello Callie
hello care package
[Music]
I don't need no drinks tonight hello
I went way past it
her body's here but she's not
he wants me to pick up her body like
pick up her stuff
her body's in the middle of age 14.
power is lost I told her to go to age
14. it's in the global chat
each Fortune should be here somewhere
oh there it is I see it
oh this is too much stuff oh wait I have
a uh
no I don't have the wrong I have the
wrong car
[Music]
um
where are you
go down the road but the opposite way
you were going
again
age 14 in the middle of age 14.
hurry up because Cali stuff is gonna be
fine
[Applause]
what
'd she say
I guess if I drop it on the floor
it'll last longer
said it because I don't know actually
thank you
Kiara's got my
it'll last longer because it won't be in
the backpack anymore I think
this is what I did with the raid stuff
and the backpacks disappeared but the
items that I dropped stayed for longer I
think it works
[Music]
the bag lasts 30 minutes you guys didn't
tell me that you guys said it last for
five minutes
all right well okay I was gonna be here
soon
I believe
put in a box
[Music]
mm-hmm
where the heck are the trees
[Music]
yeah I found a horse
cool okay
that's good
this is good enough is that my car
oh there she is you can uh put you can
put stuff in the car because the
thing hold on hold on my car has a
storage so you can bring it over here
and uh stock it up
[Music]
I buy items it's fine
mm-hmm
[Music]
just drive it over here
what
drive the car over here so we can load
it up
hey what you doing
yeah can I have the key
yeah
attack
oh some of the car
okay okay I'm just gonna drive it by the
body so I can put stuff in there
did you pick it up oh okay
got my windshield
cursed until what next year
well
I do it for the Cali all right what's
her stuff oh look at all these okay this
is hers
uh where am I right now there's a
shotgun hers I don't think so this was
hers wait
um I need that
is there I'll put some of these I don't
know how much Cara gave me a lot but I
think Cali also had a lot and I walked
through here and I got rid of paranoid
yeah I don't know good old memory
memory I put the shot oops
with the shotgun in there
no no I picked up the shotgun from the
care package
um I don't know if this is mine I think
that's mine I also got it from the care
package I'll just keep what I have
Snapchat those were hers for sure
okay
that's cute that looks about right I
think she had some of these but I don't
think she had that many
does it even do damage I'll put that
back
I think everything else was mine
yeah
baby pistol I think she had these
okay are you still streaming yes
okay
are you not tired uh not really I have
like the superpower whenever I stream
uh sometimes like I don't I just don't
feel tired
unless I'm sick
okay uh you drive the other car I'll
drive this car
we're going back to the derby just go
down the road
I'm in power
yeah but I haven't felt like healthy
enough to feel like that in a long time
or I don't mind streaming for a long
time
and I feel like I've really been talking
in the chat that much because I've been
concerned with rust
howdy
oh there they are all of your stuff is
in this truck bed here just pick up this
key I appreciate it appreciate it and
then you can uh you can get into the
back thanks for the help
thank you so much I appreciate the help
thank you thank you
there's a light up here to fire up here
you guys can you're gonna die out there
Cali
one time right here
sorry a couple things
but now I'm a curse
no no that wasn't for you Kiara I
promise it's it's different you were
actually helping me you were helping me
you're good you're good thank you though
[Music]
or something
oh yeah I found a horse by the way his
name is Pinto I brought him over
cute yes
he's uh right where all the cars should
be
the flashlight
[Music]
as a car too for the car derby yeah yeah
for the cars yeah sure sounds fine to me
I just found him
chuckle
hey cutie he's a pretty horse
he'll be the commentator he'll look at
us crashing each other's cars that's
right good Pinto Pinto's a cute name
I know right
hey Kiara check this out
hey check this out hold on hold on
because we're on the same team
all right hold on we're just gonna rub
my eyeballs when I'm listening yeah it's
broken
down there I'm just too cold put some
water in it
let me park my be cool
I guess somebody will get the long car
yeah it's water
yeah it's just water yeah this is pretty
sure it's not this is how peace should
be no why would it be milk what the heck
boy because it's white boy
oh yeah oh yeah what's up Mommy hi yes
flash cards
though he's taking a shower aren't they
killing him
[Music]
hold on let me reload it stop okay hold
on I got you are you stuck there's a
battle of everyone versus pickle down
scary like if we went over there we'd
definitely die
you've had enough guns wait I have two
guns oh Kelly has a gun speak Korean at
me
I know what you're saying I know a
little bit of Korean you guys can drop
everything off here and we could go find
apparently there's a big war happening
against pekora so we could uh have a gun
if you guys watched some bear traps I
was gonna set him around myself oh yeah
I have some boxes here if you want to
drop off some stuff not anymore
let me put my fuel
I'm gonna go back to my house and grab
bullets okay you can take a car uh just
back it up you guys did grab my stuff
but I think you might not have gotten
the pistol what kind I was holding it
just don't worry about it
oh the pistol itself yeah yeah it was on
the floor back there sorry
bullets that's okay
nice of course there is this okay
I'll grab those if you don't mind and
then I'm gonna go make a pistol real
quick oh yeah
um
okay I'm gonna put enough in each car
yeah I'll just go make another one
[Music]
is that bandana Master that's not mine
I haven't held any of those
[\h__\h] uh you can take this car right here
you just have to back it up
okay sure
um question uh what's the chords what
are the chords for the big war that's
happening is it
um
oh a bunch of your stuff is here like
your plumber's trumpet
oh Kelly can I have my key back my car
key
sure
one sec
let me get out of here um you know this
car is super nice and whatnot I think
I'm gonna take Pinto okay
I think I'm gonna take Pinto yeah just
because you know I'm a cowboy riding
yeah it just makes sense
here's your key
thank you all there's your key right
there and I'm gonna go grab some weapons
and uh what are the chords can you
remind me one more time uh I don't know
actually
maybe she didn't want this
oh your pistol's right here revolver
it's here
to work yeah it's on the floor by all
this stuff
oh thank you hold on a sec
oh you can just click on her uh if you
hover over her it says like invite to
team and it's got like a plus sign
I think that's how it should be but I
think my horse is stuck
hold on
yeah and maybe only the leader can do it
maybe let me do it oh yeah
invite the team
I have one with five shots
oh what kind of gun
oh here's my stuff
gunpowder shotgun yes
okay here's I dropped some more bullets
for it and then I think you have some of
Cali's ammo or I think okay oh no I
think I just grabbed all this stuff I
put the 69 ammo into the box into the
oh thanks it's in the Box gotcha
and then let's see I got a roadside kill
water jug is this the pistol no it's not
it oh let's see there's a revolver on
the ground at home so if I die I'm just
gonna pick them up there oh there it is
because I see it thank you thank you
guys oh whoopsy doodle all right give me
a coordinate chat we'll see you guys
soon okay we'll type the coordinate in
the team chat when you're ready
all right cool that's fun you guys are
on my team so I'll just follow you oh
okay you're gonna follow one horse
apparently close to
oh you're good
you're good E10 really for real
uh what is how sir I know I know where
it is I know where it is I don't even
know where that is
no okay
yeah okay we'll make a look at your sign
by the way the Watson Derby signs oh
thank you
just seeing if Callie's gonna follow on
her horse or
just type it in there that's dangerous
but he wants to use the hoists E10 oh
wait sorry it's through 10. Rapid season
it needs it needs like 20 people to take
pekuda down so
grenades
I do
what
you broke my car can I have the car key
back
I think I just ran into fuel
[Music]
what did you do oh you broke my engine
I'm sorry
can you repair it me
maybe if Cali has the work level 2
workbench
I don't think she does
[Music]
maybe there's some leftover Parts here
sometimes there are
uh
let's see if we get lucky
no not the ones we need
Derbies nearby I don't have a level two
workbench there I think
why
Yara where are you
okay I'll be back
okay I don't know I don't remember if I
have a uh
take it from the other car that's true
yeah
okay
[Laughter]
can she not get out
she should be able to get out oh I left
all the stuff cooking I always forget
every time I put stuff to cook in the
fire
[Music]
come here
let me just see if I have a little two
workbench because I don't want to really
take it from the car
check
would be useful nah I had taken it
all right that's right okay I'll take it
from this car
ly give me a ride
yeah
um
it's okay it wasn't so bad we weren't so
far is not allowed to hold her gun
[Music]
there it is it happens to the best of us
it's fine you got a gun on you
yeah put it away if you have one I have
a license for it all right I got a
guitar
she's telling Kiara because she
accidentally shot
the car
yeah all right we're on the move again
let's go all right let's go let's ride I
wanna hit your horse
where are we going I get you I get you
I'm getting out the way which oh you
guys are heading this way I got you I'm
sorry Pinto is really yeah pinto is
really in the way right now all right
I'm coming hold on again off to War uh
okay
towards the bombs
what what did it
as a horse you're probably faster going
up the hills
what's up uh to be honest I don't want
to hit your horse
excuse me is that right I know you don't
want to hurt
up the hill
oh that was his name when I found it
when I found him maybe I can rename him
at some point I don't know and that's
the type of horse that it is already
oh oh I see I see I don't know much
about horses though oh but it is also
the name of a bean
don't walk behind the car
I can't see I love being with you guys
OBS went offline for a second we'll be
in with you guys
come back
up we're back
all right all right in the background
yeah yeah we're going towards them
where's that in my BTS nuts in the game
we're going towards the Amelia it says
with great confidence
foreign
all right I think we should go by foot
now
yeah yeah I want Pinto to get hurt in
the cross fire all right until you stay
with the car all right I wish I found my
sniper
the pew
scared
okay you can put your stuff if you have
stuff you don't want to lose you can put
it in here
if there's room yeah there's room all
right cool I don't care about this by
the way I'm gonna put spikes around the
cars you guys so if anything run around
the car to the back and it's a safe area
because I'm putting spikes around it
can I get in if I have the car key I'm
gonna walk myself out and inside I'll
wait until you guys leave before I put
it in there okay you're gonna go in and
fight or no
oh I'll go ahead and come in I'll follow
you guys with a few shots
what do I do with my car key take the
ammo I'll take half
all right I'm putting these right in
front of the car
in a burrowed satchel [\h__\h] horse
they're all very satchel
what's that I'm just for uh preparing
something really quick
oh whoopsy doodle
[Music]
buried
here it is 10 cloths does anybody have
cloths do you have any claws
maybe there's a pig or something I can
kill
a horse Maybe
need something to kill
anything
a deer
Pig a bear
a sleeping bag no I'm just trying to
make a uh buried
treasure thing
or hemp hemp gives
cloth
here it is
okay now I have enough
all right I'll leave it right behind my
car how do I find it I never used this
item before
it right in between these three stumps
actually
good sorry taco rice
oh [\h__\h]
is Cara dead yet
my binoculars
and I do this
and
[Music]
then
how do I uh hi just burying something
putting your important stuff down
okay yes also with you because I'm I'm
scared to go alone how do I get it back
and everything but
I have a friend
oh what is that is that a bomb no no
it's just uh my car keys I can go in and
die oh nice
idea I'm gonna go in it are you gonna
you ready all right
I don't really have anything I'm
attached to okay
I can see her too let's go oh this is
like a cliff so be careful
all right
oh
okay finally
on the battlefield one barricade when
they are already here hi oh [\h__\h] was
that one one
that was no it was Global that was this
Stones right here
I don't think I can do anything with 100
stones
of the blueprint but yeah
let's see a high quality metal I got
high quality metal
fragments some bars there's a tree right
here that's about it to be honest
yeah we can use this three for Haydn
put a bear trap if we wait here if we
bait people to come over here bear trap
will kill them instantly
oh yeah you can just break down the tree
breaking it down because I don't
know if you have a rock it should still
work
oh yeah sorry oopsy doodle
there's a wolf over there I'll keep an
eye on it some some wood galley
I don't have any wood on me right now
actually sadly
I have some hold on I threw maybe my
rock too
we should probably put it on like a hill
or something though so we have a good uh
view yeah
nice idea
hold on there's uh
I don't think anybody's really attacking
from this side Maybe
right here would be good
yeah right here
over here over here there she is
okay
[Music]
over here by this tree facing the base
nice okay
it's a good idea like right here
oh [\h__\h] who was that
I don't like uh
wait I'll give you the very case because
maybe you know how to place them there's
one there's more coming okay number one
I think it's happening on the beach so
let's go down there
all right you can drop did you drop it
already not yet okay I'll pick it up
all right over here over here
let's get a good Vantage Point first see
what's happening
hide somewhat behind this
okay okay
give me one more oh
okay I think they're going in the base
we can try going in
people are just running towards it naked
yeah if anybody has cloth you can build
a bed I don't have any though I've used
it all
oh it's a nice idea oh do I know I have
leather
[\h__\h]
okay I don't know who to shoot in third
party
look if I should run into it like where
did where did that team where did that
person Spawn from oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
so so close yes he was shooting at me
son won't even reach that far will it I
don't know anything about guns no you'd
have to go in
all right I have some yeah just look for
it
I wonder what they look like
an option guys
might as well they're running a naked
female just died oh man
bleeding how do I throw this oh calming
music can I not throw it do I have to
use it as like a grenade or if you guys
want to go there
no
[Applause]
friend Friendly Fire yes
oh is that another horse oh lord it's
getting loud yo they're all walking oh
[Music]
good if we had a bed then we could spawn
here
nice but yeah I'm kind of curious
yeah we'll definitely die if we go down
there but still if we find if we find
cloth we can make uh beds
did Kiara go in no she wouldn't go grab
some actually and come back
you guys want me to mix them and come
back well we just have to find him and
we can make it
we just have to find some hemp sure all
right I'll go grab some or something to
kill
yeah I got some clock I'll BRB
10 more minutes 10 more minutes so what
there's the horse
it's just because if we die go in and
die it's just a moment of Glory you know
but if we spawn and we have a chance to
go in multiple times
there's got to be a hemp plant somewhere
I need 90 hemp or 60. no 90.
if I found a bear that'd be good oh look
there's a broken down base over there
maybe they have some cloth
I'm gonna go ransack it
here dear
ransack the base
oh is that a bear
[\h__\h] I haven't really shot anything from
this far away with this gun before I
think it's like my first time shooting
it
okay let's do
let me get some
closet
25 claws
42 leather no more cloth okay it's
enough for one bed
let me check this
broken down base
yes
a bear
let me cross that while we're going
crafting
uh
but
uh sleeping bag
30 claws yeah where did all the claws go
oh I only have 25. whose stuff is this
oh well aha
nice okay now I have enough for one
little cloth
no cloth
oh hello
they won't miss it yet
all right I'm going back
one sleeping bed one sleeping bag
who's that was it vodka
I wish I had my sniper
it'd be fun
okay at least I have a sleeping bag
oh maybe I should like Kiara use it
first oh there's a sleeping bag
[Music]
can you even like
take stuff from the horse's body
I think I'll put it down
over here
yeah here Kiara you want to use the
sleeping bag you can go in
yeah there's one here just
just make sure you name it
I'll use that I'll just go hunt
at least Cara will be able to go in
can I get these
all right I can't make a bonfire I need
fuel
you have to hold e
sure the chat will tell her
hand cloth
what did Cali already go with it I
didn't see her there she must have
already gotten
or she went to her house
I need something to eat can I I can't
eat raw meat huh
oh but I can make fuel
[Music]
hey sorry this word I didn't get
disconnected from the server or anything
but I guess the uh
[Music]
I guess it uh
the stream disconnected sorry my brain
is
running low in energy
[Music]
only three cloths dang
make uh
on fire oh fire
oh I just need wood I thought I need a
fuel for it for some reason
I think I was thinking of something else
craft bonfire not yet almost
okay I have enough now
there we go
let me build it by the base area
it's Cali back
berries oh yeah there were berries over
there
she's on her way okay I thought that was
her
it's almost dead
okay
I'll drink some water
go in no I don't want to just die
at the very last minute shirt this is
saltwater wise and salt water isn't this
freshwater
sometimes it's fresh water
yeah I saw it for a second
oh man I'm hungry there's food in the
fire
sleeping bag
yeah I made one okay here
all right I wonder where we should put
it hold on where is it
oh
the [\h__\h] I just made it where is it
oh did I drop I dropped it oh my God
hold on a second
foreign
random dog or deer or bear or boar
let's go
I didn't want to go in but
I want to be able to spawn
foreign
hopefully she could spawn there
not to have to walk all the way from her
house
it's already over well at least Kiara
got to go in
is she spawn
Cara died can she spawn here she didn't
spawn here huh
if not then I'll take it spawned it the
wrong one
okay
I never gave it to her oh I have to give
it to her I didn't know that
all right I'm going I'm going
I'm gonna die before I even get there
damn
maybe I can get some loot my gun quickly
I didn't know who to shoot it if I
should be shooting
been eye on the
okay that's where I died
that's where the bodies are
gonna oh
I did only have like 30 HP so it's not
that impressive
if only I had my sniper
all that I got an idea
I might still have time to [\h__\h] him up
let me get my sniper
sniper don't go
where's my sniper
uh why am I stuck
with the big guns
um
there's some grenades
I don't know if I should go because it's
dark I guess it doesn't matter
four minutes left is it really like a
timed thing that's kind of lame
and then what
and I'm obviously not gonna make it in
time if it's only four minutes
ah [\h__\h] you
all right let's go to the one without
the Green Dot
[Music]
don't don't
I thought it was just Petco that I
thought we were just shooting a pickle I
didn't know it was so many people you
guys were like everybody's talking paper
I was expecting like one person in there
shooting everybody that's what I was
imagining
I shot first no I didn't
dare
all right free for all
they're waiting for kona's base I
thought they were on the same team
though
if they're raiding each other's base
or was she there like as part of the
crew
hmm
became a free fall after she died ah
nobody's saying anything like in the
it's complicated
I see I see
where am I oh God this is a cliff
I am currently at the water treatment
plant got it
okay
oh this will be useful
oh okay it's just a single bandage
that's nice
no no no
oh [\h__\h]
I'm not gonna [\h__\h]
BS
unlucky
all right let me take a car I'll drive
by the water plan to get my thingy
foreign
[Music]
okay this is kind of working
all right so the last place I did
there
down the road
run him over I think I'll die before
like I want to snipe I think it's fun
okay let me get my sniper
I think is it I guess it's over already
is that what they're saying in the chat
that's all right I still had fun anyways
I got one kill
where's my stuff
further along
two kills I got two kills
almost there
there's the bear
all right
now it's free for all oh okay
uh okay so I'll go to the other marker
stupid little [\h__\h] door that wasn't
even
loaded in
hello dear
hello there
yeah I know where I am
that is a cliff
maybe there's a hill here
okay
it's a cliff oh God it's a cliff hold on
there's a hill on the left I know that
over the year
I want to get my revenge
[Music]
foreign
or should I
wonder if I get up to this
spot up here maybe that's a good idea
I can get up this thing maybe nobody
will notice
maybe I can get up there
I don't have some cover
and High Ground actually maybe better
cover is this concrete thing here
I enjoyed a little bit too vertically
hello
oh
my revenge
is it over air wait maybe I shouldn't be
shooting
in all of them no
I think they're all having fun they can
they can rest whoever was whoever that
was that got downed
Chiara oh there's somebody wearing armor
nobody in Hazmat
throw grenade
okay
where should I throw in
[Music]
hey hey
I'm going to save her spot
please everybody was shooting at me
sorry
did you turn names on I think
I think if you leave the team you can
see the names
can't leave it
I'm not sure I think I have to turn them
on
a lot of stuff oh the walls crumbling
wipe them out should I maybe no options
somebody's got a tambourine I just kill
people that are sniping and stuff or
that are that are shooting
okay
foreign
what's happening
why is nobody shooting at me
there's an astronaut suit oh cute
girl oh wait I still left some things on
seems all peaceful now I don't know I'm
hearing a lot of uh bullets and things
whoa that's a cool rocket launcher oh is
it like supposed to be ancient pillar
thing
yeah I won't shoot unless somebody's
shoot no not unless they're shooting
I'll give everything back to her
damn that horse looks [\h__\h] up
get validated
bye
she's coming is it really
I killed Gouda
I did I got my revenge
are they all in a team they all look
like they're getting together peacefully
[Music]
so I'm here
it that way
I heard her
close
yeah they look friendly see
they're doing stuff
what are they doing
ceremonial kills
oh
is there Friendly Fire they just all in
a team
okay
okay I wasn't shooting anyone but okay
or a grenade
no hesitation hesitation gets you killed
all right I'm right here
I don't think anybody would be
interested in taking my sniper
oh somebody took it
got my grenades though no oh
we're going back arrows
[Music]
wait who is it awesome please help me
somebody building there's two
[\h__\h] would I throw it
no no
I'm gonna run
back to my bonfire
[Music]
hello
thank you
okay
I won't shoot at her
going back to my on fire hi
where's my bonfire is that it up here oh
no I know where it is it's on the other
dip
I just want a little more health
actually I can still uh there it is
all right
look at one more
I could still try to snipe from here
and take a closer look
s friendly now
I don't hear any gunshots or booms
and I'm scared to go in
I'm gonna find my buried chest
I don't I think I just had a machete in
there
I mean that would be fun though
drive up with my car
BBQ
no one's fighting really I feel like as
soon as I go over there I'm gonna get
killed so because I was just standing
there watching
I got killed for no reason so obviously
it's not over yet
yeah wait for her one more to cook and
then I'll go
put them with my car
oh yeah actually I want to build a ramp
let me get my car really quick I want to
drive off this cliff
let's see I want to build a blueprint
well then I just need to gather some
wood really quick
the [\h__\h] is this X
okay
yes
I'll just do it here
stop it I'm going down don't
I think I need at least 200 to build a
ramp
I gotta build a foundation I really want
to drive my car off a cliff that was
like the last thing I wanted to do
what a perfect audience to land right
into
I can't pass it up
come on give me the wood
s all right hopefully this is enough
let me get back to my car
[Music]
shaking pictures that's fine I got to
participate because I'm gonna drive up
right now
I'm so close just let me get my car
oh
there's somebody on a horse
dude
look real
so crawl
there's bikes
thank you
I don't have I need one more hands
my hand my hand my head my hands hello
hello
[Music]
I'm not the only one over here
okay okay
[Music]
come on there's a hill right here
okay here we go
no oh that's one way to do it it's okay
it's still good enough to drive where am
I
all turned around
is it this way
what the heck where am I facing okay I'm
facing the right way
okay here we go
I need a second now
and he's like now
and the game crashed
hello
rust
I gotta do me like this
dang I don't think I'll get connected
back in time
oh well I'll still be able to drive my
car off a cliff
it's reloading now
maybe it's a fast connection if you
already downloaded everything because
usually when you connect for the first
time I think it's like a little bit
longer
floating world
all right I'm loading
man I'm not gonna make a way for me it's
okay
I'll see the picture I'll draw I'll just
imagine myself there
yeah it's loading right now see
now we wait till
[Music]
ah
is that done I was like what already no
way
they're warming up the prefabs
yeah photo save I was Photoshop myself
in
[Music]
80.
I'm tired I wanna sleep
I want to drive my car off and then I'll
log off
still stream tomorrow oh yeah I was
planning to stream today really late
anyways
here we go
car
my car
oh there it is hopefully I can drive it
out of that
hopefully
okay it's the works
okay I just I want to build my ramp
really quick
all right let me just Scout the perfect
position even if they're taking pictures
right now I don't care
I need the ramp
I can catch up
building blocked
all right I guess it'd have to be right
here
hopefully I'll get enough air here
why can't I put it right here
okay let me try here here okay
hi please don't
foreign
just want to get my car off the cliff
hello [\h__\h] you
I just want to build my room go away go
away go away go away
yeah as you can drive it up all the way
go away go away go away
I like it
I just want to drive my car off the
cliff
let me drive it off in peace
hold on let me get a good running start
I'll get a good running start
foreign
[Music]