foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
tell me
I'm eating the Kinder chocolate
[Applause]
Heroes
[Music]
oh my God I already ate one two three
four five six six
[Applause]
of them
but they're really small
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
iki
yeah I didn't even say thank you last
time
to Olivia so thank you comes on Nina for
a really cool new background
uh loading screen
I am being spoiled getting so much cool
stuff
for free I'm prompted what
um
[Music]
stop saying or I will send you to the
[\h__\h] void
I'm serious
I'm drinking
um a sports drink and normally never
drink sports drinks unless I'm in Japan
for some reason
but now I'm not in Japan
and I still
decided to drink one because I thought
maybe it will help me with my sickness
[Music]
happy birthday
how about a croissant cake hmm
you know during the loading screen
I saw one person saying what was it
like really a passive aggressively or
more like aggressively
please use the skin
and I haven't even started a game
what makes me think that uh it's the
it's the the new
stop rolling of Elden ring
[Laughter]
and now now it's for Metro Prime
oh yeah that and use the missiles but I
think you know I've made some big um
improvements throughout the last time we
played
yeah
let's roll more or less can never make
up your stupid mind
um
ah anyway
I thought yeah oh I did not close the
switch last time
[Music]
okay everybody so I uh uh oh my God I
woke up
today
and my screen is broken
I woke up and I was feeling really sick
um
[\h__\h]
my screen is so broken I can't see the
game
loud
um
let me reopen that that's broken
yeah I was feeling sick that's more like
like really dizzy
and kind of nauseous
and I was like what the [\h__\h] is going on
why am I feeling so sick
yeah
so dizzy like when laying down and when
lying up
it was really spooky and it didn't go
away
and smoothie was like meow meow meow
give me my breakfast and I'm like wait
and
yeah it was a problem what are we doing
what
I already did
game was not saved but oh but still
replenished guy
um
maybe no
uh and then like even after 20 minutes
it didn't get better but movie really
wanted her breakfast so I stood up
carefully it really slowly walked over
she was like
and then I was like what oh
wait I think I need to for a while
before I reached the
the cat food
and then I threw up but I made it to the
toilet to throw up into the toilet
don't worry
and um
that reminds me when I grew up in Japan
I've been doing a lot of throwing up
recently huh whenever up there
I think Jen was scolded me for not
throwing up into the toilet but throwing
up into the sink because I I didn't make
it to the toilet and I just threw up
into the stick but you know it wasn't
like big
somethings and it was mostly just you
know it was really just like like you
know because I had nothing in my stomach
at that point
um it didn't clock the thing no because
like for real
it was just like I just I think at that
point I also was just woken up and it
was just water basically
yeah but she was like ah Japan this and
that yeah I know so yeah and I'm like
well okay
I said whatever at least I didn't throw
up on the ground or in my bed
you're having lunch here
you should
you chose how it goes wooky Wawa
wow I'm
um
yeah but anyway
uh I'm I'm better now the dizziness uh
got better a little bit after
after the ah wow bowling balling
it got a little bit better after the
throwing up but still it continued
it was really confusing
um but by now I'm fine
um
I rested a lot afterwards I got a
massage too
the one that I called yesterday what is
this
have I been here before
balling
is this new
do I want to go here oh oh wait I don't
remember how to fight uh okay
did that just like explode in my face
um
you investigate those rooms ahead what
are you saying I should or I already did
no no I'm good so but I I know I wrote
on
wait check map yeah I guess I guess so
yeah I didn't I didn't so should I go
there
you're more than welcome to it's neat to
look at what this exploration
up so much well I know it's not that
much it's just uh let's just ah
cutscene scare
impact crater
sure if it was really the strawberries
guys can't say for sure okay
a new pirate data entry
uh field team reports are in on an age
structure of an alien design built on
the surface of talon4 studies show this
structure projects a containment field
this field bars access to a prime source
of energy within a deep crater science
team believes the field is powered by a
number of strange chosen artifacts we
have found some of these relics and
studies on them have begun as this field
could hit could hinder future energy
production operations on Talon 4. we
must dismantle it as soon as possible if
this means the destruction of the chosen
artifacts it will be done
for real
I'm so happy
where were you tell me why did you send
that link to speak to explain to me
where the hell you were
that's why I threw up I was giving birth
to the baby again
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
something about you know seeing people
who haven't been here for a while where
I thought I might have finally lost them
and seeing them again makes me really
happy you didn't you didn't completely
forget about me
time to look for no don't look
thank you for half a year though thank
you
oh yeah okay creepy face is back again
blessed yeah where all the others who
are hiding from me huh well where are
the others
stop
[Music]
I know
sibling no no if anything cold was The
Sibling I've had that baby for a long
time
[Laughter]
[Music]
throughout our living nightmare as we
battle with this unyielding Darkness we
chose to see a light this light glows
with a promise chasing the Shadows cast
by the great poison and purifying
that which has grown toxic it is strange
though at times it looks to our eyes as
if the light Coalition yeah
nailed it into the figure of a woman
me Burning Brightly the luminescence the
sense from space then Retreats back into
the infinite Blackness from whence it
came when
when this
prophecy comes to pass
when the light recedes the chosen's long
vigilance of containment will finally
come to an end
I like all these texts
tell me more tell me more
oh
had collected then scanned the totems
here for Clues on the locations of the
remaining artifacts to gather the
artifacts will open a path to the center
of the impact crater
oh wait more lore
it's very important Kara okay well I'm
trying to understand
this is my ultimate goal this is the
worst part of the game oh [\h__\h]
tell us a script translated the
containment of the great poison this
task has fallen to The Chosen and we
will not flee from our duty even as we
suffer with the land and its creatures
we will pour our will into the twelve
the artifacts which form the lock that
holds this great evil at Bay in the
depths of the planet
this lock must stand up to all who might
come to assault it to preserve the power
of the seal and to protect it from those
who would meddle for their own designs
we will spread the artifacts across the
land hiding them from prying eyes the
lock must never open until a day comes
when This Disaster can finally be put
right
isn't my reading so beautiful guys
[Music]
anyway thanks you guys for all the
member messages thank you
yes don't look stop lurking make me sad
make it for me sad
oh yes I can wait of course I can wait
oh
I mean I already read this one right
isn't there more
I take
foreign
[Music]
this is the artifact of Truth the first
of 12. see I paid attention
I mean like no don't look don't like
like you're not allowed
no no no no no no no lurking
scan the totems here for Clues on the
locations of the remaining artifacts
together the artifacts will open a path
to the center of the impact writer
oh
[Music]
well if you're working you get an excuse
oh my
God all right it's bird faces
they're suffering look at them
um the heat of mad more was a test for
many warriors a shrine on their own a
holds the artifact of strength so this
is I have to go back to the lava world
huh
of course I have to
Sun chamber High atop our ruins home
became the nest of a great Beast and the
source of corruption many chosen Spirits
have been drawn to distinctive Place
release their bond to the world to claim
the artifact of wild
wild turtle
s
um from the ruins of our home we honor
our fallen Elders in a great hall a
chamber beneath the statue holds the
artifact of
world
foreign
[Music]
spoiler
yeah
oh oh this is the true one okay
and one of Talon's Far Corners a Grove
of live lies reveal the pillar beneath
the waves to find the artifact of choose
I understand
did I read this one already
I know I didn't well okay um artifact of
Life Giver
a tall cave stands as Ben drano's Edge
seek the Unseen entrance at its top to
find the artifact of spirit
did I read them all now I think
I mean even if I didn't well we have to
start somewhere anyway oopsie
so I guess the one where I know we have
access to is the magma one I guess
foreign
[Music]
from Poison
yeah toxic
[Music]
um
we love what you do don't you know that
you're toxic
what's up
well okay so um
of course we will probably realistically
not finish this today which is okay
um which also means that now I will not
like stress myself to do it within this
stream
uh because we're also we're starting
early also so that I can
um read some super chats at the end of
the stream also uh I want to
you know practice a little bit before my
Korean lesson tomorrow
but I think I'll just do that when I
wake up however I do want to not like
sleep too late
in terms of cooking don't worry I cooked
a lot yesterday
which was so yummy you guys need to
[Music]
do on there yeah
I did cook it was doing yummy so I
recommend if you guys don't have an egg
or even if you have an egg maybe try
without an egg if you make a a batter
with um
for breading a fried chicken
hello
it provides no eggs because I'm guessing
just because they can break so instead
they give always like mayonnaise and the
breading but it jumped up here again I
just want to jump around
yeah and I always I just actually I most
of the time I just used eggs anyway and
just put the mayonnaise packages aside
for you know whenever I needed
mayonnaise
because I thought I'll just it will be
better with egg they just can't give me
an egg because
it'll break so I will just use an egg
anyway but now this time I actually
didn't have an egg so I used the
mayonnaise but this time it wasn't only
mayonnaise it was also mustard so it was
um half mayonnaise
what what and
um oh is it mayonnaise oh [\h__\h] that it's
mayonnaise and mustard half mayonnaise
like one tiny package of mayonnaise and
one tiny package of mustard and then you
mix it and then oh yeah that is like
basically the thing that makes it sticky
and I think that's possibly what made it
taste so [\h__\h] good this time holy
[\h__\h]
absolute 10 out of 10 recommends so if
you guys say I should not go where
should I where should I go
where do I go
[Music]
why you tell me to not do the thing that
the game tell me to do
I gotta go to the ice Place head back to
the snow area where once the snow area
uh maybe out there
six
in the lava cave oh oh so I do have to
go for maguma wait what is that can they
not like brightest above the door
maybe here
am I am I correct here
[Laughter]
I mean I'm relying on you guys as a
nostalgic memory because last time you
guys told me that you most of you just
haven't played the remaster yet this is
just you guys going by memory
I have an elevator close to me
I mean before I came here
[Music]
map helps it didn't help me
is the E elevator
should I go to this one
that's what you meant with clothes okay
so I was going the right way
all right with
is it not a good idea to kill those
what what did I do they don't do
anything
they actually hurt it feels like they
hurt me do this
not that one
which one could it be ah ah okay uh this
one
what
what red said
okay I shall go there anyway
so I I just want to say when I said uh
half rotten
um strawberry
I wouldn't say it was like really rotten
it wasn't even like
not really moldy but you know when you
eat strawberries then you just you're
just like
um
this strawberry here is not the freshest
strawberry anymore it just tastes like
wrong
[Music]
there we go there you go
yeah yeah so I literally just have
bought these this package of
strawberries you know for breakfast I
like to do it with my um with like some
crap pancakes and
oh
where's the elevator
and the moment I you know they look like
okay-ish first
but then you realize
when you look closer at them
yeah they're not
not really that good anymore probably
but I taste tested them like tiny bits
before putting them into my pancake
and still
um and I cut okay I have to admit like
one at the bottom was actually molding
and then another strawberry that was
like lying right next to it
that looked overall like in good shape
there was like a tiny bit of molding
just like from it connected to that one
but but I could like it was really just
like an inch no not I don't know how big
an inch is I don't really know uh a
millimeter
and and and I I I I it looked like it
wasn't really from that strawberry but
from the other one so I just washed it
off
and then I I cut I even cut that part
off I washed it and then I cut that part
um
so anyway yeah um
I was I was just
some strawberry out of this [\h__\h]
package because I I
was for my breakfast
and yeah well
uh when I actually ate them in the
pancake you know I do this little
pancake wrap
I realized yeah
[Music]
some of these taste kind of off like not
that that's like completely like
disgusting off but just like just a
little bit
not fresh you know
but I don't
really make me sick because that was
over like at that point yeah maybe 24
hours ago
I don't know if that really was it it
could have been something else too
I just really wanted some strawberries
because like that that was I was feeling
crazy
busy man do you really think
I don't know
I'm better now so we're good
missile on the bridge
under
is that lava no
oh wow
thank you
ghetto
possible for traveling as well I don't
know because if it was food poisoning I
looked it up food poisoning apparently
goes away after two to three days for me
it's going to Lane after
six hours maybe
so
anyway so I gave up I gave up on
strawberries at this season the thing is
though in Japan
at this season they were still really
good
actually they're so good that they have
like strawberry themed uh buffets and
everything going on right now
but I assume that their strawberries
actually come from Japan I'm pretty sure
because you know I do have like this big
strawberry business
and This Is Us
in Austria yeah we don't get uh uh our
strawberries from Austria at the moment
sometimes we do but not right now
oh
Jay that's really interesting because I
it could be that because just yesterday
I started again
the doctor for
which side do I go
I was
side effects on the paper I was like
could this be one of the things and it
didn't say anything about getting like
dizzy
what maybe
yeah I was just like look at my [\h__\h]
skin I need
I need to do something about it which
side should I go
should I go down the long haul or the
the short hole that's a dead end okay
that explains it okay so we're not
blaming it on the strawberry anymore
I also think that my my body can take
more than that because it is really just
like
it's not that much
why do you not move Samus your little
[\h__\h] I swear to God
I hate him already already this [\h__\h]
again
why why
[Laughter]
I can't even look
[\h__\h] okay I'll just go
[Music]
[Laughter]
ha
[\h__\h] let me just chill here for a moment
close the door
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's too funny that's too funny
let me no I wanna I wanna I wanna have
some I I got you know Mao um do you know
mawam you know normally I when I eat
sweets it's always only
um
chocolate and stuff I never really eat
the other kind of sweets but now
actually I was in the mood
um
Chappelle of Elders Chapel
no they're not sour
but there are monkey chewy chewy yeah
the blocks um
stripes are good too though
haven't had that in a long while me too
like maybe 10 years man
but the massage place had them and I
took one and I was like damn now I need
more foreign
how do I get there what
I'm just I'll just um walk
maybe I'm nervous
oh
warning
um
[Music]
that little [\h__\h] again
huh
oh
yeah apparently last time I played
I did something incredible
I did a pro um speed running Strat I
didn't realize
um
apparently I did something with the
missiles where you cut it off
so you can spam them or so
and I didn't realize until people told
me afterwards like I don't know how did
I was that really so special it doesn't
feel that special
I want that
gamer LVN do I believe
it here again
do I really
look at those cute jumps no no no no no
not here I don't have to no right yeah
okay thank you
I have bad memories there what are we
doing here
am I supposed to I don't have a grapple
hook yet
am I supposed to do this double jump
can I really am
strong
double jump a little bit of damage
[Music]
the intended thing to do
there must be a way to do it without
damage taken
that's weird design
hmm
it hurt
my father had timing down
man this game so funny
there was a ball tunnel yeah
I mean the one where I was like nope
nope nope
thank you
okay
this one doesn't even see me even after
I start attacking it funny
anything else
oh
why is the stinky out
where are we going
I know
[Music]
the sound what am I hearing
where do we go
do I go to elevator
yeah okay
that one
did I get there again
[Music]
uh here
probably
I have been announced
as the official vice versa
ambassador
and I mean
I'm honored but also confused
but also honored
because I do not really
um know much about white Schwartz but
how about we change that
good thing is
no that's not what I meant that's not
what I meant but I guess it kind of
applies too I was not even thinking of
turning it down though I was just like
are you guys sure
um good thing is I have a friend
cool uh likes by strats
a lot
and I asked her to teach me
I mean I don't think that there will be
um occasions where they need me to play
it to be honest because I was told like
roughly what I'll be doing
and it seemed like there was no need to
actually play it
but I I am committed to my role
I don't want to be just you know
Ambassador and I don't know what I'm
ambassading for
no
mm-hmm
so
I asked my friend to teach me
yeah
and then the good thing is and she also
has someone to play with I don't know if
she normally has people to play it with
this really
um
this path looks so much
like the path that we walked on
when the VR Monster Hunter experience
usj I already told you before but damn
it looks so much like it
the graphics are so similar what the
hell
where am I going now
I'm still lost I don't know where to go
oh wait it's close though
I don't know what he's connected to
um maybe the big tall thing over there
should I go here
safe one first okay
um
[Music]
all right
they hunt volcano in the VR right did
you look it up
did you look it up
is that what that was called Volcano
it's very different from magic magic bus
tracks
how do I guess you don't have like you
know lands and stuff like that
Akana is the iceborn main monster oh you
guys know
mmm
you use your deck for energy
damn okay there will be a lot to learn
is it difficult
use double jumping uh-huh where
um
thank you
maybe I don't know that wasn't all
necessarily in the things that they told
me I was gonna do
but I don't know
um
you haven't been to early hours you had
hot pipes and platforms you needed to
double jump for okay
yay
welcome to new heights wait what is this
there's two rooms
where is you come out come out and play
come on
not this way
but then I go this way
oh
that's why
do I either to the temple
just fine
oh
um
yeah that's where I wanted to go
as frustrating as it is are you for real
this is already frustrating to you I'm
just playing the game normally at this
point what
I'm so sorry that this is such a
frustrating experience damn I'm trying
my best here I just I'm just still
chilling you know
chilling I'm taking it easy
we're still just exploring give me give
me some time please
but that's not the only way to get to
the temple is it because I feel like
I've stood in front of it before
I didn't get one guy and I mean maybe I
did but it's I'm genuinely wondering
like how can this already be frustrating
I'm not even frustrated
yet
love the helmet thank you
can I make that jump
look I should be able to make the trunk
how
it's like what
did we do
come on
okay this is frustrating this I will
give you me not being able to get out of
the water that I I can say was probably
frustrating but even then it was just a
second
hahaha
wait a bit before I I tried waiting but
before
pressing the second time okay
one more time
come on
[Music]
water is frustrating for everyone
crime won his weird water physics that
make it kind of well weird oh
so it's not just me
how about these ones can I still not
fight them
oh I still can't
It's Gonna Roll through then yeah
[Music]
pookie
once you get the gravity suit that won't
be a problem oh gravity
good morning goo
good morning
oh can I have pink no no no
no
what the [\h__\h] what [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] I
was just no no no I was trying to get
HP man
la la
wait where did he come from
I didn't even see him before
oh buttons Magic
I didn't see him
there we go
that is uh what are those
[Music]
oh you can just kill those normally
that's nice
auto lock on not working here
can I like scandals
a statue depicting a turtle above
balancing the plane of existence on his
hands the plane of existence
you like panicking Wawa that's good
because that's my normal state in a lot
of games
you came here to see me wear a helmet
and kick their butts I will do
exactly that
Cali said you clapped for minions uh so
what what so what so so what
do you have a problem with that
okay
what what is there any problem huh huh
I mean
I already told you guys I liked the the
ride I liked it I will not hide it
it was really immersive yeah
it was really good
but it also made me motion sick
interestingly because normally I don't
know
VR makes me motion sick but not stuff
like that oh there's another bird
what about
what about the low one
no
is there nothing here
okay
okay let's I'm scared
poop heads
this is scary
is it gonna attack me
I have a feeling it's not a real bird
not because it's a statue but also
because of the Wings
[Music]
I'm fine Clippers get ready ready for
work
the statue's hands seem to be frozen in
place oh I've only had something to heat
it up with
there appears to be a shell of ice in
encasing a water basin the water
originated from the statue's mouth
yeah okay so it's like constantly
vomiting just like me for real for real
Asian
oh okay I don't know
[Music]
sorry bird
somehow I must free you right
where there's a will there's a wave
but
what the it's not it's not snowing
what can I do
that's for later
more things to scan
I started to depicting the bust of a
chosen sham and adorns this door a
symbol is carved into its forehead the
translation reads to pass my gaze seek
my twin within the swim uh-huh
your twin wait your twin what there
I mean
don't you all look the same
kind of dark too it's hard to see I only
see your eyes glowing your twin
not not this one
maybe this one
maybe this one but not this one
yep
aren't they the same
maybe he doesn't understand he actually
is not a twin he's a triplet
yeah it's so dark
I can't fail
no I was I was I wanted to scan the
right one right away
um several stress fractures can be seen
running along the surface of this
Brimstone object
right
um philosopher the statue is flawless
wow sassy yes
go what are those
Maybe
I guess I'll look at you too
I did get it first try oh
okay well this one's closed okay
well no
seek my twins in this room I did
shoot oh
a ball
hey
where am I
ABC always be scanning
stretch
that is a stretch
kiwawa balling oh
[Music]
do I just fall off
no I can't I actually can't I thought I
I was always being so careful but I
actually can't even fall off anyway
below
oh wait ah I was like how
I didn't see this one
[Music]
um
oh
okay is this like a puzzle
again I have to go down
easy puzzle yeah
what now
this way
um
wait I'm in the room
oh I'm in the room what do you mean it
took you two hours to solve that
oh yeah bye
I can I can do it
I'll just uh excuse me I'll be taking
this
oh I can take it back no I can't
oh
why ball
how does that the side jump work again
why am I jumping I thought it was this
one
of course I'm not locked on I thought
that once I was pressing the button I
swear I swear
okay why did that on the side open up
another one opened up
oh hey did you
oh no there's more hey this is the boss
[Music]
that's the last for me
one more
look at my straps
ah there's more these are only the
babies
I'm a monster hunter let's go
foreign
ERS drifts she goes are invulable to
most beam well great well [\h__\h] great
the crystals are on their back absorb
energy which they can fire and prey
shingles have poor stamina they oh they
have a ventilate after using a breath
attack making the mouth area vulnerable
the soft underbelly of a chica is
susceptible to concussive blasts
is it ball time
so like
when the mouth is open I shoot
then maybe it turns around I don't know
and then ball bomb yeah
or am I bald for out this whole thing
and Valentine spelled blast The Frigid
gastroenter targets they are also fond
of ramming oh wow great and trampling
their hapless prey well who isn't I can
do either oh
everyone
okay so I have to exhaust it after this
it's exhausted right
okay
happy Gumball
can't do it anytime out
oh ow ow it hurts though ow
wow you know what I'm just gonna yeah
place them everywhere oh oh but I have
to load them
uh
it hurts to touch it though
oh so the camera sucks I can't move it
oh
that works that works I don't see it's
HP though ow
I'd pack my after he uses breath
[Applause]
I've got him on the roofs
goodbye
how are you not exhausted yet they lied
to me oh but I did some damage
I don't know if I'm really doing this
right I don't think so miss all the
mouse
but no why it doesn't work like that
um it said like the mouth is uh
vulnerable but
I buy my health
if that doesn't open
right up that's what I've been trying to
do
oh I I hit it once it worked once
and twice
come on come here
let's play
oh oh he's doing something else
no I wanna I wanna smell your breath
come on
yes oh am I running out of myth and when
it says four and 40s do I have to like
reload after I go down to zero
and then it goes to whatever pretty or
so is that how it works
oh no I really only have four left hey
oh I gotta make them count okay
bye
okay free
uh yeah I use so many on the baby ones
because I knew it was effective
okay uh can we make it work with two
and their boxes
okay oh well let me use up these ones
but wait don't I have to use the
missiles to open them up in the first
place
all right it's okay I I got the hang of
it now it's kind of boring though oh
wait
I'm stuck
you can use the beam crates oh okay
it's too boring now I liked it more when
I didn't know what was going on
see I'm even jumping over his
ah over his breath
yeah
[Music]
I'll take that thank you
so what is this
is that my grapple
[Music]
oh wave wave game
you lose X and right I guess a to switch
to the wave beam excellent eh oh no wait
excellent that one this weapon can open
wave doors
that's it that's all I can do
no way
there must be more to it also one is
this cave I guess that that was where it
was chilling
alrighty I'm sorry I killed you and your
babies
um
no more family
I'm so sorry we gotta load up my
missiles while I can
use some hp2 won the ball wonderful
more damage too
technically a slightly stronger beam
oopsie wait no wait at the same time
so do I just use this all the time now
or is there
a reason for me to not use it
if it's stronger
actually it's a little weaker what yes
for now
slower to fire oh
wait can I awake
oh wait can I kill them now
no well that sucks and can I wake you up
no
yes
oh oh
wait I can I find this one's working
just need a few more hits yeah
okay so we just go
and they're even spawning them here for
me to realize you can do it now believe
in yourself
these are no match for you anymore
[Music]
track enemies
this one tracks enemies too
yo
that's nice that's what I like about the
missile
so okay
I might be using it
it's kind of slow but that's okay
I'll use it until I change my mind
okay we did that
um is it now oh can I do this
no maybe too far uh is it now time for
Maybe
maybe
that artifact thingy
I'm just safe true
ah
where was it I see it where is it
oh hello
see I'm not so bad at this game anymore
am I I mean
look at me jumping around I've got these
bodies all figured out
oh
I'm doing fine what was that
which could scare me more that big big
scary chunky wonky or that little icicle
friend hmm
saving same time
night and day compared to yesterday
well coincidentally there was also night
and day between that
um
you were never bad I love you I love you
for saying that
thank you
you like screaming chicken noises don't
worry there will be more
it's not over yet my screaming my time
as a screamo amateur
is not over yet what is what are you
doing
no did it stun him
he didn't even get time to turn around
it's done Sam
okay okay wait have I ever been here
I feel like I have
yeah
I'm kind of like lost
as in where to go
today because like
I guess I have to like retrace steps and
stuff but purple door
purple
don't say purple
oh I guess they're not purple on here
how do I know
they're purple on there too huh
ah there it is
okay okay
so
so to the wait that's where it came from
that's why I came
there's one here there's one here
they're hard to see unless you really
zoom in
um okay see like right now it's not
purple
now it is
not purple not purple not purple not
purple not purple see why is it not
purple
triggering me okay we go a little bit up
to the left
up there
wait not up
why do I do that
not there uh opposite
[Music]
there
gotta select the room first oh
yeah anyway oh guys is there something I
feel like there's topics that I should
be talking about is there something I
should be talking about
is there something that's on your mind
guys
is that the writer
look at this one
ah made a muscle cars
muscle car uh wait a second I lost track
again
ah
can you mark things
no
the moment I like closed the map I
always um I I I I I I can't I don't
understand where I am
just this way
no
my droppings oh
[Music]
am I dropping I was there
am I dropping spaghetti moment well
first of all you have some muscle car
but that's not really anything to talk
about but I'm I'm really sure it was a
muscle car because it was really wide
and it went and um it wasn't only a
muscle car although a muscle car is
always classic cars
no right
that's not it
ah no that's not it I have to go here
you said I was right here
there are plenty of modern ones
but I'm pretty sure I saw a classic
muscle car
yeah and you normally never look up
you normally never
see those in Austria
oh
the path loops around
say first I already did
it really look oh you got outside again
and no time to deal with you
there's no experience points anyways
I wanna fight oh wait
oh
what why you sometimes no jumpy
oyster okay here we are is this where I
was supposed to go
I think so maybe let me check
purple door
where am I ah uh-huh uh-huh
oh [\h__\h] you guys
[Music]
I don't like them
okay here we go here we go there's a
path here wonderful
yeah anyway the cars color was ugly but
it made boom really loudly unlike all
the cars here in Austria and it was
really white and it was it looked like a
two-seater I mean it might have like
some back seats hidden
back seating
somewhere but
it looked generally on First Look it
looked like a two-seater
but closed
no no uh
no way of getting rid of the top I think
oh nice Dodge
it's so dark I can't see
maybe it's nothing
okay let me fight you
turn around turn around wait haven't I I
have been here before right
yeah fighting here is a bit annoying
especially if it's two of them
this is kind of narrow oh wow
oh damn the charging the charged one
makes like so much more damage
documents
uh where am I we're going uh oh there
right
what what huh
what
hi hi okay maybe not from here
maybe I have to go up here wait
wait there's a
oh
yeah not like that
no give me the house
okay
which means I have to climb up somewhere
Ice Climbers oh that's a nostalgic game
that I've never played before I only
know the Ice Climbers from
uh Smash Brothers
right here maybe
no me neither same oh
let me see what's going on here
everything's pretty high oh wait here
I feel like I've already been inside
here ah I didn't see you could go up
foreign
virtual console
huh can I destroy this
wait Lord
sorry
let's go as the great poison reaches
ever further into the planet we chosen
begin to feel the glowings of Despair
before it is too late we now make our
last stand we have begun to build a
temple to contain this Darkness at its
heart its will
place a cipher a mystical lock powered
by 12 artifacts and filled with as much
power as we chose who can harness we
wonder though that we wonder though even
when we are done will it be too late and
will the power of the temple and
decipher itself prove strong enough to
hold back the poisonous tide that even
now swells within the ground threatening
all life
apparently not at least not the first
time you tried
but I will do it again
right because they did it before and it
didn't work apparently
hmm
oh they didn't finish it maybe
like uh like an audio book what I'm
doing
speaking of audiobooks
yesterday I listened a little bit to
pomuse ASMR at the moment I came in you
know she was saying
let me styling from one side to the
other side and I must say you guys know
normally I'm sorry I cannot stand ASMR
most of the time unless it's like I
don't know if it's
um like I don't know cats ASMR you know
I I could dig that
but
yeah the most like I guess popular type
of ASMR I don't like I also don't like
those sounds of someone cleaning my ear
ew I don't like it ew get out of my ear
the whispering I really like the
whispering that that Pullman was doing I
like that
should I jump in there
I don't wanna I don't wanna
kind of don't want to is there something
in there
I feel like there isn't
no okay good ah
yeah so
[Music]
but it really like depends
on the type I guess there's some I can
accept
most of them I can't
the whispering was cute
I'm wasting missiles when you use them
on chords ah what
89 of the 40. oh so the crates have
missions inside a lot of the time anyway
don't they
I felt that I felt that was that even
the spot where you're supposed to jump
at though
oh God
look at that
ah
um
we all knew that was gonna happen where
where here
move on before
here wait that looked like different to
me I thought the wall was right there
oceans
cats and quotes
yeah I mean even then I wouldn't like
say that I needed
oh
and go out of my way to find it
um but that's that's fine
[Music]
and I don't know maybe writing ASMR and
stuff like that could be nice too
writing sounds not keyboard I mean just
with the hand
although I generally really don't like
scratchy sounds in my head I think
because at the massage too today but in
general I always know this
um I often tell the massage therapists
to please
uh not to a head massage
because
with head massages
is it just me like when they like
massaged ahead they moved the hair
around a lot the hair strands maybe it's
worse with long hair
but it's it's like giving me this really
weird scratchy feeling in my head
and I really don't like it it's like do
you know that paper the Sandpaper that's
what it feels like to me when someone
massages my head
maybe if my hair was wet in that moment
then it could be a less of a problem
maybe but normally when you get a
massage your hair is not wet
on the normal circum circumstances
you enjoy that sound
[Music]
really
think like once
um
I said ah and one massage I was like
sorry
um I don't like head massage please
don't do it and then lady was like yeah
but I have to massage your head I have
to I have to because
that's where all your pain comes from
and your head is too too stiff like too
hard and I'm like um
okay I guess
so she did it and I mean she did kind of
good
was pretty good
it wasn't so bad as other times
but generally I prefer not to that's
called the spell yeah right right
uh
-huh
going through my hair with a clump
that's that's completely different
where do I go
oh
I can't make that jump
looks at the birds all the time by the
way is that lower to those birds
wait flicker bad scavenger with Optical
camouflage in that renders is invisible
to the naked eye flickabots are
deceptive creatures the only way to
track them reliably is with x-ray
Imaging they fly ceaselessly hunting
insects and other small prey that float
on the air currents it's like a bits
tend to fly uh cyclical hunting patterns
using primitive sonar to navigate cool
me
does that answer your question
um
[Music]
I mean still like there are mysterious
creatures to me how do I wait
I'm blind again like why do I not see
where I need to go
like I don't think I can make that jump
I don't think I can make that jump
I can't make that jump
behind me
oh
yeah but it's so dark like I can't even
I can't
wait
it doesn't do anything okay it's not
active
you don't blame me thank you but
apparently this is not the one I have to
do first maybe there's um another one
elsewhere
that must be the first one wait that's
nothing see that on the
onions nothing
looks like because it's so dark looks
like a hole for me to get into I guess
wait wait wait wait
what about it here
that's what that was I was wondering
wait
that also doesn't do anything right now
oh yeah
Tony Hawk it's right boosting it wait
what does that mean
ah charging you mean or what what how
does that work again
wait no how does that work
boosting
I learned that last time but I don't
remember
B
oh
thank you
oh it doesn't do anything oh no now it
does
what
oh my babes
okay at least this one doesn't seem to
be timed wait there's another one over
there
so I'll do this one too
[Music]
there we go
okay all four are open
and now this one's active okay okay okay
oh yes oh yes
alrighty
[Music]
uh boosting too or no
bomb okay
and now oh water oh [\h__\h]
oh like the other one that was frozen
that's what they do these verbs spill
water
okay uh oh you're gonna help me good to
the top oh no they just stop okay okay
fine with me wait this time
[Music]
I made it
oh
[Music]
that's it
I thought it was gonna be so
of course something important for
progress
okay uh then let's see where else we can
reach after
filling it up with water
that was just one of many puffs surely
you think still important yeah
same it's not the same pop right
it's so important there's another part
there was another hole under okay
people people so same same path
basically
I was trying to be so fast there's
nothing underneath
what what if what if I
don't what if I just go up here
[Music]
right
did I get one guide because that sounded
like it was like underneath
but now I'm here
uh choices choices choices
so now I didn't use the missile
this one's not active
should I hide a knot
which means purple door uh these ones I
can open too right
yeah I'm going to go first
blue go first okay
it's kind of far
can I make that though ah it's foreign
I can make it
what yeah
okay the rate
[Music]
such a gamer isn't Gatorade like a
sports drink for sports people but also
kind of a gamer drink huh the two
opposites of people
unless you are a gamer and sports person
at the same time in that case respect
Gatorade runs in your veins
okay
okay I'm fine
what is this
what the [\h__\h] is that
what what what
oh I killed it
kill the camera
what a great thing that was a space
pirate am I not also kind of a no I'm
bound to Hunter
man
um
that music
I'm scared
am I hitting it
you know it's dead I think now it's dead
okay
oh my God cutscene
oh is this a bus fight
no wait that looks like a like a relic
like one of those things that I need
why was my first thought to escape
anyway in that moment
oh
I'm focused I'm focused please
yo using the charts while jumping is
really difficult but I keep on doing it
now because it's overpowered
that's it
I can touch with that R2
oh
all right I never used that my default
is a so I just don't think about that oh
I guess I that's I guess easier
normal shooting I think I'll continue to
use a but I would like to get used to
using that Arden when I charge
go for the bottom door first there's a
map room
this one
oh yeah
you got too good
I don't know I didn't think you know
that I would need that R but okay now I
understand
that with A and B so far
uh-huh oh damn oh that's a big place to
explore
hiroina
they immobilized in quarantine cave
relocation is recommended due to
increased violent activity is that what
I'm gonna be fighting
is that it
Faison ore appears to bind through phase
and energy thermal imaging Imaging is
required to detect the highest
concentration of radioactivity which
serves to bind the stones together
imagine Imaging research is being
conducted in the containment Vault area
of the facility
the nation
face and always extremely durable and
blast resistant although the armor-like
qualities of this shell provide ample
protection thermal imaging Imaging can
be used to detect weak areas in the
casing improvements must be made to this
shell in the event that these weaknesses
are found by aggressors
uh what
East quarantine cave is recyclable I've
also authorized Personnel permitted
entry only after bioskin oh [\h__\h] I don't
know if I can make it through
okay gonna
[Music]
yay but wait first I want to look up
here
oh which way should I go
is this the only way anyways
oh
hello boss I'm late hello welcome
I guess we're going here
this way now
I'm the aggressor
blasted his ass
hey give me a second
yeah she broke a box with me let's go
access to research lab Hydra granted oh
thank you I don't know if I want to go
in oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
okay I'm trying to use dead r
oh [\h__\h] I'm so good I'm so good at this
game
system yesterday for the first like two
three hours okay okay okay but now now
I'm good I get good
yeah why is the music still like battle
music
as if they were still
an enemy here it makes me very nervous
access to research lab theater
limited to team sclera only
sounds like a Pokemon enemy team of the
next Pokemon game
personal Bound for hold up Observatory
must use West elevator
whole little Observatory is basically
YouTube
because that's why you observe all the
holes
85 exterminated report any sightings to
security immediately
security
are they really gonna help me am I
increased a sentence levels recorded in
phase and amniotic bath Here We Go Again
of all the difficult words man nice
thank you
yeah most of them stream on Twitch as
well some of them no no not really come
on
you know what time to connect the World
tickets will go on sale April 5th
at this time no no idea connect the
world is it really called connect the
world isn't it just Halloween and
connect
[Music]
sounds so
so big
this is likely a side effect of Faison
in just ingestion by test subjects
like maybe midnight GST or they're still
gonna announce it when it will be
probably they will they will probably
announce it
hmm
of course
okay Iris did it okay
a new pirate data entry has been
downloaded to your logbook space pirate
encrypted data decoded
our initial tests exposing Talon 4 is
indigenous parasites to phase and appear
to be successful
increases in strength size and
aggressiveness are common in all test
subjects as well as unforeseen
Evolutions like additional poison sacks
within the abdomen and the appearance of
a second ring of mandibles in several
subjects these creatures were chosen
because of their resilience and the
pairs possible that given enough
exposure to Faison they may one day be
able to survive on any planet we
transport them to our methods will have
to be refined we currently have a
hundred percent Extinction rate after
the fourth infusion period and most
survivors of the third infusion stage
are so violent and
uncontrollable that they have to be
euthanized even still we remain hopeful
that further experimentation will result
in a success
foreign
so this is the space pirates data right
can I get a question
[Music]
stop following the law I'm so lost oh
I'm a little too but yeah it's all right
because they use so many difficult words
it's like my brain is overloaded
it's hard to digest it
maybe if I wouldn't you know be reading
it out loud
maybe I can digest it better love your
attention
tomorrow I have Korean lessons
fighting
mining operations have begun near the
crater where phaseen appears to be most
concentrated daily phase and yields have
increased 44 and our mining system
becomes more streamlined as personal and
Equipment flows increase several
incidents of phase and induced Madness
have been reported prompting augmented
life support regulations in the deeper
Chambers symptoms include loss of
equilibrium errantic respiration muscle
spasms in the most extreme cases
hallucinations a timeline reassessment
for the refinery operations is
recommended as the material proves more
unstable than initial analysis I can't
speak anymore I can't read all those I
can't my mouth is like feeling really
ouchy numby
yeah do I have to read all of them come
on
it's just uh yeah they have a problem
with uh that stuff
problematic okay I'll get it alrighty
[Music]
yo charge they're like nothing to me
look at his lighting
[Music]
sliding no why you disappear don't you
want to slide again
oh hi
dad there's another one up there
easy why is he not even looking wasn't
he doing anything
he was stunned by my beauty my orange
Beauty
Orange Is the New whatever whatever your
favorite color is
except orange as your newly there
Orangeburg Orangeburg super Embassy
let's go
more oh hi oh that's camera
ow
[\h__\h]
why are the cameras my biggest enemy I
hate them
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
aren't you glad
transform specimen 344 to lab Hydra
complete further infusion suspended
pending security assessment
anything red
oh [\h__\h] hell
bring me up Scott me up beanie what
should I should have thought about this
statement one more second
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
who is disturbing my love huh
oh my God
no way you're back
what can you read did they respawn
because I fell down
no way no that's just one from the top
okay okay
[Music]
no you no you're a dog no you
Scout me up BB
am I Scottish
sculpt me up baby
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] does that mean
uh out of context that's funny too but
oh speaking of out of context I saw that
clip
I have to say I that wasn't on purpose
but I was laughing so hard at the Cow
carrot out of context clip of me talking
about how wet we got oh
my God
hi anymore
[Laughter]
not handled sedated xanomes without
proper ice containment equipment
I do not have that wait let's rate this
one
space pirate encrypted data decoded
research Outpost Glacier one in fendrana
drifts region of Talons for Town Force
mountains is operating at 85 capacity
Sub-Zero temperatures have made the
metroids sluggish and easy to control
even those well in two phase and
infusion Cycles cold containment stasis
tanks what the [\h__\h] are all these what I
sufficient for the juveniles but some of
the larger metroids have been moved to
quarantined caves for safety purposes
security doors remain an issue as
malfunctions due to ice occur every day
large predators in the wastes are also
concerned as they continue to kill
personnel and breach secure areas
unfortunately it has become clear that
our containment teams cannot neutralize
all of them without a vast increase in
Munitions and soldiers
now I feel like that's the first time
that Metroid really was mentioned and I
saw someone telling me
and a Twitter reply next time there will
be like actual Metroid
or whatever that is
in the upcoming
part that I'm playing
until now apparently that wasn't a thing
so what are metroids
I'll see them soon okay
damn why are we going up what
I mean it can't be it's purple
oh wait I had the
wait oh sorry it's a missile I'm I'm
confused because now I started getting
used to using
um
the dead buttons
oh I probably should have added yeah
every once in a while I add things that
are
not on my channel
um too when I think of it um
actually good idea I should do that
no no I do not want to be recorded
without my
okay so please stop
I will have to eliminate you
no ah
is that the camera
all right let me try
finish him up yes you got me with the
funny
Clippers watching this stream why why
why why
[Music]
the [\h__\h] are you
thank you
one more
okay okay we're gonna fight here now
we're done
these are fun to fight
because they feel like more like
human enemies and all the other enemies
are faced so far you know what I mean
I feel like we're having like a like an
actual battle
holographic sequence initialized
people people
[Music]
[Laughter]
scanning
standard more ball slot this slot is
active inserting the mothball and
detonating a bomb bull usually okay I
know what this is what thank you for
telling me I guess
uh become ball
there's a little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] fruit fly flying around and I
want to kill it
don't fly into my nose
anything but that please
do not infiltrate my nose my nose is
private
there's no time around
uh at least yeah they kind of like tell
me when there's
time limit
oh boy
my nose goes you mean rose gold
Rose
pretty color oh that made me think of
something
did that tell you guys about how my
phone like I uh I had this like
cover on it right
um
and the moment I put the cover on top of
it immediately
like it got a huge crack and since then
I was like this was expensive so I'm not
gonna
immediately buy a new one
okay there's four of those are there
can I do the others too right now oh
yeah
um and then
you know after like ages I finally
removed it
and then again immediately after you
know I don't drop my phone that often
but whenever
I do something like that apparently
immediately after I drop it to like
really tilt myself
but I will tell the story before I
continue because I feel like something's
gonna happen when I do this
so I told you that before right and then
I put finally because I dropped it and
then the Frog of the phone did not crack
no but the back of the phone
broke and it looks like it's kind of
inside but I was like okay at least I
can like hide this by putting um
um like a plastic case on the back so
ever since then I just like quickly got
myself like a cheap but cute looking
case off of Amazon
and um
wait I will read that later
and then I put that on okay I'm really
happy with it it's pretty cute
and then you know a while ago when I was
with crony
chronini
uh we were sitting in the train together
right and she was in the row where I was
sitting if I'm in between but suddenly
crony asks me
chroni asked me if I got my phone
off of uh
how do you pronounce the English Ally or
Ali Express
I think that's what she asked me and I'm
like no why the the phone case not the
phone she asked me if I got it off of
AliExpress
uh I don't like that no
and then she tells me that
um let's see uh like she only saw my
phone case for a second and immediately
recognized
she got that phone case
and when when she said that I thought oh
do we have matching phone cases yes I'm
happy but no she tells me that she got
that same exact super cheap phone case
and actually that I could get it much
cheaper on AliExpress probably uh but
she got it for her friends
she gave it as a gift to a friend of
hers
so that means I'm matching with her
friend not from not with crony
unfortunately so I was kind of like
hype for a second and then not anymore
wait which one did I not activate
yeah too bad really too bad
this one
were you that friend no I wasn't but I'm
matching book one of Connie's friends
apparently ooh the universe
foreign
close enough I felt a little bit
embarrassed though
it's basically
she knew that my my phone case was just
a cheap randomized phone case
felt kind of like
cheap
explosion upgrade
planets mass
4.8 trillion trillion tarotons my God
how do you know how do you weigh a
planet
I guess science but how
do we know how much Earth weighs
you can calculate but how can you be
sure
if you can calculate
uh um planets
uh
a planet's weight without putting it on
a scale does that mean a scientist can
look at me and calculate my weight
without looking at without accurately
without putting me on the scale
laughs probably right
that feels kind of intrusive
did they ever ask the planets if they
want to be wait and have their weight
open to the public for everybody to see
maybe maybe it's a female planet and it
doesn't you know it's kind of rude to
ask them for the wait
and you're not even asking you're just
like
taking that information from them and
putting it out there oh hi Raiders
no Planet shaming in this room so yeah
let's let's uh censor all the weight
information on here I'm not 43 kilogram
I'm pretty sure I'm more than that
unfortunately
I feel like people have um
people have a an image
of
[Music]
um
girls weighing too little
uh but it's kind of unrealistic unless
you're like really really tiny um
[Laughter]
no no no no no no
and I am no whatever so profile planets
Crest is primarily perfect or making it
ideal for subterranean construction a
class XIX planet zebus is inhospitable
to most bioforms a world was considered
unremark that world was considered
unremarkable until it became a base for
space pirate forces oh
it's a space pirates go on there
no we will not look at the weight
uh
[Music]
I'm in habitable Wasteland Savaged by
nuclear and dust storms and constant
seismic upheavals well that sucks that
sounds not like my next uh destination
for vacation
no we will not look at the weight
ecosystem studies indicate that Talent
four was a biological Paradise prior to
the impact of an extraterrestrial object
I'm sorry my mouth is like so numb
uh what remains of the biosphere slowly
fading due to exposure to phase and
radiation at current rate of Decay Talon
4 will be a Barren class eight
Wasteland in approximately 25 years
that's so soon oh [\h__\h]
uh one one more which one was the one I
didn't read
[Music]
no like that one that one I got you I
got you
twin tabula
planet is best known for twin fever
oh interesting name a disease caused by
a viral strain native to Twin tabula
in the early stages of the disease
victims suffer from double vision cool
when the Twin side fades the victim's
new death oh [\h__\h]
when you think you're healed but you're
really not
okay I think I got them all wait there's
only four
there's only four
lower notes
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay
interesting thank you for the planet
lore thank you
I wonder if we'll ever visit one of the
other planets
I missed one
do I have twin version now
you're bye
this one eh no I already read this one
ah billion
quarantine
atmosphere is ripe with material
materialism materialist yeah a sentient
gases
Global exterminated virus oh
okay
what why some time
okay okay what now I looked at it what
now
up okay
[Music]
bye yep I saw that coming
can I go from here maybe I can
oh I can't
yeah
oh nice job
and I
jump into the sun is that the Sun
wait is that
the sun
is it this no don't
and nothing happens
why'd you get so worried that father
would make me go kaboom
doesn't do anything lamb
Michelle
maybe just because I'm a phoenix
why have you guys never like
urged me earlier to play this game by
the way because if you would have told
me that Sabbath is not only orange which
I mean that was
obvious to me but also a bird woman
if he would have told me that earlier
man
could have played all the Metroid games
by now
oh
foreign
[Music]
Metroid games anywhere hmm
power beam what what
how sorry
how
well how to power him
normal beam
charge
I don't know why
I became ball
missile
what how can
you uh how do I switch back uh
there you go
charge
yeah what
that's it
all right where do I go first
that might be a safe safe Point yeah
that looks like a safe point
that's super strong yeah
I don't want to like switch around a
little all the time though I wanna focus
on one
[Music]
um
takes five missiles yeah I saw that
anyway is it time for a boss because
we're all the way up here and we just
saved
foreign
I rarely use it in battle okay then I
don't feel so bad about it is this
another one of those
uh
was there no other way to open them
oh elevator
a normal missile would have worked oh
let's go
ah
switching again
what am I hearing oh God I forgot how to
find I suddenly forgot how to find it I
suddenly forgot okay no I'm good
you know when you're in the middle of
playing a game and suddenly you feel
like you just don't know how
okay
are we good
ready ready
you were hiding there's no hiding from
your boss hencho is here and there and
everywhere
oh what is that I thought we'd be like
in Evangelion
they also kind of look like mosquitoes
Sentai mosquitoes
Spanish words
even though it's used like in German and
English too
sounds so Spanish to me
mosquitoes
hey for real oh is it because mosquitoes
first came from
um
a Spanish-speaking country which could
be Spain or also elsewhere
hi
guys
oh what the [\h__\h]
I can clear my size like that
oh [\h__\h]
it means Little Fly
oh cute
we had spots that I'm having here in the
middle of gameplay
because it's interesting because a lot
of words come from I don't know Latin
and so on
you know
and we normally adapt like English words
and [\h__\h] but
what what
[Music]
I'm in an in the end all all everything
goes back to Latin though doesn't it
School and it was my downfall
oh sorry I keep on using myself also
triggering
what
thanks for the pinky
yeah yeah it should be Latin based
anyway I'm just say moment right because
Super Metroid free the absolute goat is
on SNES Virtual Console
um Metro Fusion Game Boy Advance thread
five switching okay I might play dread
but isn't that I think I saw Santa
playing a little bit isn't that like a
side scroller though
I prefer pretty
unfortunately
but it looked good besides that
hmm
it was quite pretty I'll give you that
hey why does Metro not have more 3D
games like this
why not
[Music]
that is the hardest one
they have
Prime two and four oh what
let's go
uh-huh
you little [\h__\h]
it's right
so why is this game named after you huh
what makes you so special
are you in your prime time right now you
don't look that priming right now you
didn't even put on any primer before you
do your makeup you know that's really
important yeah yeah but don't prime it
before
um
[Music]
baby it's a baby
that's kind of cute
Talon Metroid energy based parasitic
predator
you as much as a predator as good as
the effect effects of phase and have
turned these metroids a species of alpha
predator native to Sr 388 into a unique
subspecies found only on talon4
because
possibly but have you ever seen Gouda
crediting
on anything really like for real for
real I haven't
she hasn't even tried to take a nibble
on me
on that Apple she had to scratch the
Apple before it really
opening it up so
she could be a bit more of a predator
maybe if she put on some primer I don't
know
[Laughter]
uh
that pun was shaking in its boots for
real she couldn't even finish it
it's frozen Gouda
Italian
Metroid will latch onto its prey and
drain energy ooh growing larger as it
does the only way to shake and attach
Talon Metroid is to enter Morpho mold
and lay a bomb Oh
did I just do it
what was that the scripted
[Music]
oh it's getting smaller wait no it's
getting bigger again wait am I filling
it up with like energy what no I killed
it I'm fine
let's grab that
person never space pirate
oh he got stuck on the PC
lemon with the Thanks for opening up the
pack for me
oh hi
Howard stress working right now
shut up
[\h__\h] you get out of here get out of here
oh
me down
wait I'm coming for you
how the [\h__\h] is oh he's already dead
taking that
charging chatting chatting
[Music]
nice shot
yeah normally you can't kill mattress
unless you freeze them and then you have
to use five missiles
normally
oh no I don't want to open up all these
Metroid please no
please don't open them but look at that
oh yeah
yeah
and does that mean I can open up all the
other ones with missiles too but I don't
really want to do it
and there's only one here
there's only one what is this though
more help yay more and more have I
missed one so far hopefully not because
I'm relying on you guys to lead the way
they would attack the Pirates oh funny
um
[Music]
oh wait this one foreign
space pirate encrypted dialects College
Metroid the section continues to provide
more questions than answers our research
teams have isolated the energy conduits
that run from the invasive twin
mandibles to the energy core and the
creatures quadrate apartheid new clubs
what new clothes
but the manner in which a Metroid
actually extracts the life force from
its prey remains an utter mystery the
victim does not lose blood or any other
vital fluids and yet the Metroid
extracts energy identifying this energy
is our Central problem it takes no
physical form and yet we've added the
victim dies we will continue to research
research this matter
okay wow all this lore is making my
throat hard
man
what
let me open so you know I had that like
magical what was it called
the medicine right when I was sick in
Japan turns out they also have fruit
candies so
I brought a few
from Japan
um
and they tastes really nice it tastes
completely different than the actual
medicine because these ones taste like
um
orange yummy
oh wait what oh
shall I step into it
is that not just where I came from
I'm blind ah
are we going down here
sneaky
is it still the same ones
or is it a different one
damage can you take [\h__\h] you now I don't
care
what was that oh oh oh oh there's more
mosquitoes
they're they're kind of bulky I always
have to charge now oh we're charging the
beam
you know yesterday I almost ended up
doing a spontaneous
hot orchestrian just because I felt
really
I don't know it was in a good mood
yesterday
[Music]
it felt like singing but that means we
have to do another archived kind of open
stream sometime soon
I was fixing the audio
let her sing
I'm sure you will I'm sure you will are
we going down
because we read
and then before the strawberries then it
only started today morning but I you
know it really could be that it wasn't
the strawberries
[Music]
yeah starting to be a while since the
last one I mean I did an archived one
with two one Senpai recently but yeah we
didn't sing that much only like three
songs right
off days also important yeah I thought
so too Central tank control circuit
connection Terminator oh
honey what is that
what
oh
yeah Health back
just gonna should I just jump down
oh no I hope they're not all suddenly
gonna be set free
and attacking me
when I
press some button
is that exactly what's gonna happen
though
on camera again
why would you think so because they're
all enclosed in these cases it's kind of
Stuffy why am I not
able to kill it
okay with you guys
Miss Aldi I need to use myself for the
stupid cameras all right and apparently
I probably also have used to have to use
missiles for that one but let me see
first is there something interesting
huh
oh
I guess
just pick it up like this
maybe scan
what is this
force field Network active iron subject
object all three force fields must be
deactivated okay
already looked pretty deactivated
what there's no more red ones though
where are more red ones
are they up there did I skip them
[Music]
here
like this one I activated
no I didn't okay
is it
armor
now it's mine it shall be mine
oh
looks like for my head yes oh
a new visor
thermal visor acquired
he was down to activate
let's do
what the advisor do
oh boy here we go what
what's happening
wait is the lights off is that what's
happening can I not see it if I undo
this why is it so you're so fast
it hurts my eyes
but without the visor I hoard
okay
why am missing I thought this one
I bought this one uh follow the target
those are new Pirates oh
I think I killed them all
what if I undo visor not good idea now
maybe
can't say
or do I go I can't see the map in this
one either unless I look here
uh that door on the bottom right
[Music]
but I can kill them normally right and
if they if they catch me then I become
bald and missile uh involved
okay it's okay they're just small baby
metroids we're good we're good
[Music]
what somebody said go back to Safe point
but
cannot be opened with that weapon What
if I
ah
rain
okay
this beam well awesome I don't want to
waste my missiles
not this one I suppose
I've never been okay ah yeah bye I'm
getting confused with my interface
but I do have to go back to uh
to the
safe one
I'm not used to being on equal terms
with them until end game
feels weird
the mid metroids
why will I go back all the way back up
I don't like backtracking
it doesn't seem natural to me
I know hey hello dark dark panic ah
[Music]
well it worked
we had to have that happen at least once
so that we understand
um
what
uh
what what
is this
can I scan this
I solved it oh wait does that mean the
bottom door is open now
the door
do I go back here
oh it's so dark
let's hop on okay
[Music]
I can't see
what the [\h__\h]
yeah that that thing that this this
thing makes my vision even worse
what is that
why why why
is it because if I get closer oh
to the enemy
my vision gets worsened
you can find circuits of thermal visor
and connect them with wave beam that was
the puzzle
y'all
do I still have to wear it now
is that camera yeah that's the camera
nope nope nope
nope nope nope nope
still cannot see
this is bad I like how they turned this
the lights off immediately at the moment
where I
got my visor to
fix that problem
a Charged beam plus missile shots kills
them immediately
still alive
stay away from me
a little parasite stay awake oh did I
open up accidentally one of those cases
yeah
why why are you still alive
finally
oh I shot one by accident
so annoying okay where are we going I
wanted to go up
it would want to hug oh man I totally
get it though
I feel you
but I gotta say I'm so happy to be back
with my cats man we've been cuddling so
much
and we're so happy I'm so glad finally I
have my fluffy babies again
I really need a dumb
mental support you know you don't have
pets you don't understand like how much
it helps and why do you guys not just
all
so uh
allow me down all the time
bouncing around
[Music]
come down
that's right that's right
if I fall down one more time because of
you suckers
problem is the vision is shitty now too
so it's easier for me to fall down
the part is annoying yeah it is power up
on the right
which ride
what's Ryan
it's so hard to see
Where'd I go
there's a small track along the ceiling
football
a ball has no vision though man is it
here
is that this thing
how do I get there
what
do I jump as a normal person
oh wait what the [\h__\h]
ah no
what
it's near impossible when lights are off
oh should I could have done that before
when I passed for here the first time
because
how does this work
[Music]
maybe that's
maybe that's the first time I'm not
getting an upgrade
okay well one can try it without lights
okay uh
[Music]
let's go one Higher
no
huh what do you mean without I don't see
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I see a blue line but like
what
I got confused
in there
fail for it you can get it later I might
have to
try lucky jump
oh man
nah
what was I going down
I think I was going up
maybe we'll come back here even if not I
mean One Missed
upgrades
not gonna be the end of the world right
[Music]
okay can we go back and please turn on
the lights again
please
is it like this whole area
is this gonna be the norm now oh man
this place should be okay there we go hi
mosquitoes where is your nest I should
just like set your whole Nest on fire
I would [\h__\h]
he did he did
oh I want to try
I'm gonna try this um how do we do this
again
[Music]
give that to me
where's the other one
[Music]
no
no got him evaporated
I will free this planet of mosquitoes
you're welcome
what am I hearing again
I forgot
there you go
is that where it came from
nah they look the same
they look the same
um
uh
uh the map doesn't help me either
I could uh
go to the save point
bye
oh and in here it's actually in normal
vision
right right yeah yeah oh is it nope
I am still not free
[Music]
spooky spooky ah
okay
I'm fine I've done this before energy
okay uh um I'm too far from the save
point now I think I have to battle them
is it just two they're probably gonna
spawn more after the two
um
time for platforms
good
climb up
I don't know if I'm mentally capable of
doing that
uh what where's it where I can't see
where where go where go Wawa
[Music]
oh please
okay one left
really no I'm gonna die it's over it's
over I'm gonna be like backtracking a
million times
no no no no
I want to use my charge beam but like
switching over to it was like
I feel like I would fumble and then
no
no so far away from all of that [\h__\h]
I have like 16 HP left dude
that's so mean
don't blame me for this now
[Music]
I shouldn't have run away
I should have just battled them because
me running away made me an open Target
it's not my no
no it's not my fault
[Music]
what wait
where where
[Music]
no no no no
foreign
[Music]
what
do I have to
redo
the past
30 [\h__\h] minutes or more
I swear to God
oh I'm gonna send
a strongly worded letter
to Nintendo
that is a
a shitty
really shitty
game design
that is really shitty that broke my
spirit
that broke my spirit man
I was in such a good mood
to this big ass room
and I'm like I'm gonna go to who wants
to say for sure sure I had that in mind
but well [\h__\h] stupid terrible Vision
yeah number one
oh you guys I can't believe
oh my beloved chickens
I honestly in this terrible terrible
moment I'm having blaming me for real
like you could at least fake it and say
it's okay Kiwa it's not your fault
yeah
oh
no I kind of don't want to play anymore
I don't want to play
[Music]
that really ruined
my mood
[Music]
30 minutes
reset
for real
no I'm not happy now
do all this stupid [\h__\h] again
and then go back and do it again
so I will be doing it four times
[\h__\h] mosquitoes again there's way too
many mosquitoes
thank you
that is like a different kind of
frustrating
from yesterday
you know what
get out of me give it to me
I am playing I ain't playing no more
because I just don't want to play
[Music]
sorry guys but that really really really
pissed me off
sorry
emotional damage
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]
that was so annoying with the stupid
visor
no for real I'm so annoyed can someone
just take my save and do that for me
please
[Music]
that is so annoying
it will be even more annoying the second
time yes it will
bro Tony not even in the same City right
now
I asked him to come over sometime soon
though if he can because I ordered some
furniture
and I thought oh hey for once I don't
have to ask our RBF
what what do they want from me this time
but
you have to scan it all right we know
what you are I already know what you are
what do you want game you want me to
scan all this [\h__\h] again
really
it was such
a good day until now I mean in terms of
gameplay
yeah okay thank you Game code or at
least recognized I already read all this
[\h__\h] previously
just the Metroid
okay explode
all right
it is so punishing
man
like nowadays games don't do this [\h__\h]
to you
I feel like
I'm not used to being being
abused like this
wait the thing of the ball is this this
room we could do that now like after I
kill all the enemies
I don't know can I do it now
yeah
I'll kill the enemies first
emotional damage
emotional then
y'all
how could I do so much damage
foreign
thank you garlics but the thing is like
when I stream the plan of having a
longer stream I feel like I can't end
this early
has only been three hours
so I feel obligated
I'm committed
to it
oh
[Music]
and either way I will have to repeat
this [\h__\h]
so it's not like I can even do anything
about it
you have someone who can
replay this part for me
I want to do it myself
okay I'm Gonna Get You I'm Gonna Get You
Back
down
no brutally we're trying different
broccoli different City right now
oh
can I fall off
yep I can
then the momentum
the ball has too much momentum
oh [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
calmly
uh
and ball
[Music]
can't even adjust the camera
do it for the missiles
expanded bye bye
stuck
alrighty
moving on
investment in my skills no I don't see
it like done
no no no
damage
emotional damage
emotional
oh my God up or down or down
I knew you were coming I wasn't ready
for it
no I'm not gonna be no no no no I don't
wanna
I hate you all so much
[Music]
stories
I don't know
[Music]
I have to scan
I need a better reason to write you
a love song today
[Music]
promise
help me see foreign
[Music]
clogged
clock
uh what thinking brain brain so cannot
understand how
forget
how to fight
do not understand
why you know that
what
I have to go back up
you know I've been watching Charmed
so funny watched a few more episodes
today
so funny man
they come up with the most ridiculous
chunibio funny scripts ever
yeah yeah
I mean as I said last time I wouldn't
say like the whole
story is [\h__\h] it's just a
CG that's [\h__\h] the Ultron yes of course
yeah I was shocked to find out that
there is actually
uh like a new Charmed
as well
my favorite character in Charmed yeah
I don't know maybe Piper but you know
she has such a funny name do people
actually in America name the children
Piper or anyone because those names man
Prue from Prudence I still understand
that Phoebe understands Paige Maybe
but
Piper
whose name is Piper I always thought
that was such a weird name even back
then when my English wasn't so good and
I was watching Charmed in German yeah in
German
I've met never met a piper
never met a piper
pipe it's like sounds like a like a
tongue twister Pipers pipes piping the
pipe pipetty pipe Piper my dog's name is
Piper
yes I'm roasting pepper the name yes I
am
does anyone love
[Music]
I feel like it's such a weird name they
just ran out of P names but eh let me
think Prudence Phoebe page well that's
what we have done Penelope
yeah and then you didn't you didn't need
to call her Penelope at the time you
could you know they shouldn't Prudence
to prove so they could have shortened
Penelope to Penny yeah oh yeah Patricia
to Patty if they needed to be shorter
or pomu exactly
Pauline Paula yeah there you go oh my
God there's so many better names
should be a common name in America
hey you know what maybe we'll lift my my
mood now
chocolate I'm gonna eat some chocolate
um
[Music]
foreign
and now here we enter my favorite phase
of the game the game where I can't see
[\h__\h] and will be
punished constantly for it
yeah wonderful
and even the enemies they bring up now
are even smarter
they escape
my my stuff
it feels like it's a leash
you
super missiles yeah I need to you know I
just don't feel comfortable with like
switching to it mid-fight I feel like
I'm gonna fumble which I will totally do
because I've been doing that all the
time
you're just gonna spawn more and make me
fall down again it's so annoying
no
come on
there we go
chocolate is so good what is it about
Kinder chocolate
they have absolutely cracked code
okay of P may have
the 12 herbs and spices
but Kinder chocolate
um
they've got the magical chocolates
formula
down like no one else
not even like expensive chocolates
pralines whatever I don't even like
pralines that much guys can I just tell
you that
maybe the maybe the right people will
hear it
present for you know when you meet
someone here here's some cute brillians
I don't even like poor lens
give me the Kindle chocolate instead or
the spot
you don't know what do you mean you
don't know what the praline is do they
not call it praline in English of course
they do right
what do you mean you don't know what
is the more fancy like the chocolate
that's in the Box all the time
just a box
did I turn it on
how do I know that if I turn it on
supposed to go down though right
down the wrap
up
okay
but I don't see [\h__\h] man
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no that one's dead is there another one
huh
it absolutely killed my patience oh [\h__\h]
I'm sorry
confusing it's confusing to switch
between weapons and advisors and I don't
want to switch the visor but it's
a foam ball I'm not crumble under the
pressure
[Music]
he did he did
we're not in that safe room yet are we
are we
don't give a [\h__\h] I don't know
I don't care
what what oh camera
I don't want to say that word
I'm getting really
I must let it out my frustrations
beam me up Scotty that's the right way
to say it
yeah
hey
I had that ready for you won't you give
me 10 out of 10 for service
no need for waiting Lines no no no
you know I saw some feedback on Twitter
about the kfp chicken
at the Expo
somebody said actually for real sauce
and he might not be the only one
thinking it
said it's better
than uh
KFC
yeah can you believe it I can
I can
nice compliment
apparently that chicken was really good
I mean I know I've tried it too it's
really good
Friday
ah
huh
believable
I don't know how good KFC is in Japan I
know that for Christmas everybody in
Japan like wants to order from KFC like
it's they have this this is so surreal
to me I surely told before but it's so
surreal to me how in Japan for Christmas
the number one food to eat is fried
chicken and cake
I mean
but like
oopsie I was accident
about that anything let me think
oh [\h__\h] yeah I'm confused I'm confused
[Music]
so it should be good like if they want
to eat it for Christmas you would think
pretty decent food
but what confuses me as Japanese fast
food places
is they don't rely on sauces at all
I don't care about sauces
like in McDonald's and so on too
they have two sauces barbecue and one
more
they don't need sauces I don't care for
sausage but I do because like it's so
weird because you I would think like at
a chain
that in Austria has like 10 different
types of sauces
that that in such a big chain that that
would be like they fold everywhere but
then in Japan no
they have like two sauces but you can't
even I don't know they don't they don't
even offer it if you order
um
fries like for example I guess if you
ask for it you would but it's not
default they don't ask which sauce do
you want no no it only comes with uh
chicken nuggets
how are you oh very tilted but welcome
to the Stream
this is is this where no this is not
where I died before
also I can turn that off now
ah no no no okay no no no see I'm trying
to do something here
um
there you go that's what I wanted to do
did I just get to it once because I was
like wondering if that works if that
could actually happen
sick oopsie wasted
double kill
nice very efficient
[Music]
is there something if I jump up there
I won't test it
what secret space
oh why did I use the missile for that
I'm sorry hey but there's nothing cool
here
except a great view I guess
it really
cool
they should reward Me Maybe on this side
nothing
scan
you come back later for artifacts uh
is there something on the other side
yeah the glass eyes covering this up
opening can be melted with extreme heat
[Music]
um
wow I found that already just by
curiosity
so you guys don't have to tell me about
it later uh which way which way
right because we're getting closer to
the stupid
safe one I'm so salty about it still
I am not amused
but I still don't understand which way
don't fall this time even if I did right
now my health is like full
so
I would survive anyway
I just came in there already it was such
low Health man last time ah
but I think
huh
thank you
where are the [\h__\h] at
where the pictures at
down there I don't even have to go there
I can really just
I I I
just last time you know it's hard to see
and
I didn't [\h__\h] remember that it was
right over there
oh and you panic I will not take anyone
saying it was my fault no no no
foreign
do I not need formal here
oh okay thank God no I do
okay
you wanna play huh
Revenge time
where are you where are you
I thought I missed
if I could have like just done this
make quick business out of these
[\h__\h]
ah salty salty so salty where are we
going
I got the save point
now we're going back on the lower level
I suppose
let's play
cold
War what do you mean this way right
what is this oh my God it takes so much
help
I literally I can't see I think they're
dead now
I look but I can't say I have to stay
with this visor
please
those guys are the worst they are they
make my vision so bad too yo
so camera
[Music]
what is this what's this glowing stuff
ah they're waiting for me
[Music]
okay
I know [\h__\h]
Ah that's a problem
[Music]
that was a big oopsie that I did sister
run out of missiles too
yeah well I think
cleaned up nicely anyway
so mean
[Music]
no way you dodge that
dodging
I got some gold
yeah
yeah I gotta get closer
he's playing album ring
so many
there we go
yeah
[Music]
yeah he memorized my attack Titans he
was told by another one
they have exchanged information on me by
now I just want to go up where am I
going
here
can I have some missiles no why not
not you again
[\h__\h]
oh hi it's the expansion yeah I got that
one whatever one you're talking about
seems like I got it
all in one place
[Music]
all right
myself
bathing
cool
why
it's rough but
I'll still say nothing compared to
kiwawa from yesterday we are not the
same person
oh hey I can see you again
oh nice
but
it's kind of Dusty in here
I don't even remember this place
which way am I going
for that
the store towards the big blue room and
then we're done with this
specific area I think
yo I can see
what the confused right side
there's also a safe point over there so
let's aim for that
this area is what you died the most
like all of this
oh I died once but that was plenty is to
get me absolutely tilted
oh we're outside
uh safe over there okay okay I remember
this one
I feel so refreshing to be out here
I am forgot how to jump for a second
ah
[Applause]
do you remember how does this work skin
so try using the thermal visor up there
oh why
do I have the cookies
oh can I just jump
all right do I have to do this again
see what I have to do this again
[Music]
yeah
about to say if that's what I'm trying
to do I wanna
say yeah yeah
everybody telling me to save that's why
I'm
that's where where I failed to jump
[Music]
there we go uh okay
Heal Me Up Scotty or Scott me up healing
as we like to say
scale me up Holly how about that
scale me up hottie
I don't even know what I'm saying
anymore
[Music]
heal me a party imagine
uh who's the what's the guy's name who
says that to Scotty hmm
what's his name imagine he would say
by accident totally accident beam me up
hottie um
Captain Kirk
what
I never seen it when they should
but he actually doesn't what Oh you mean
he never actually says beam me up Scotty
or he doesn't say beat me up hottie well
of course he doesn't say beat me up
potty but
thank you
[Music]
yeah Mandela effect
he never said beam me up Scotty but I
asked you who said beam me up Scotty and
you guys said Kirk
now to say he didn't say it first you
say he did say it now you say he didn't
say it well which one
laughs
not a little
open up
[Music]
why is it so closed
I thought I had to go there
are we doing more backtracking
from all
that's why you said use the thermal
on it
am I supposed to cease ah
uh Power condo behind behind
what
behind
uh super missile okay
ah broken you know didn't we just make
it worse
behind
ah
please don't make me use the thing
anymore please
I don't want to use it anymore
I don't want to use is the thermal
thingy gonna be a thing a lot throughout
the game I say
guys
I saved
okay sorry
not only are you going to use it a lot
you are going to get two more no
[Music]
I am forever cursed
bye
just a ball
this is also like in the VR
oh this is like the bridge
I was like really crapple
step on everything carefully as much as
I could all of this looks like in the VR
thingy that we did
oh my God and here it looks like
something there
Popcorn Time
time to deal with project Titan oh no oh
well we are in a big room that we
couldn't enter until now so yes this
definitely looks like uh
boss time
good luck rawa
should I just Spam I don't even have
that many missiles right now I feel like
I wish I could charge them somewhere
here
um
this boss rocks oh you're funny
oh do I absolutely need my
super missiles
it was easier than the first
all right let's go
I'm gonna fumble so hard I'm probably
gonna lose once but at least the safe
point is close
oh oh nice cool scene
this really doesn't look like a GameCube
game anymore
this is like this doesn't look like a
remaster to me this looks like a remake
to me
oh no the rocks
he will he will rock me Bing Rock Me
super missiles for granite
to be grounded
it's touched up that much if a rampa
reel
uh uh goodbye goodbye
give me a second
um
see already great start I can't even
[\h__\h] Skype
[Music]
Daniel
if only it looks faster Bard is an
animated sentient creature of stone
trash or phase and radiation
the face and radiation given off by
Fighters negates all the targeting
no systems preventing that's why
it may be possible to acquire Alpha nice
targets with a different visor
um
the chaotic nature of phase and
irradiation leads to instability in its
structural Integrity Fighters can encase
Targets in ice and is colossal size and
strength make it a formidable opponent
this is something happening I think yeah
I think it makes people
I
all alone as you say
when do I know it's back to be usable
again
wait oh yeah it didn't do that before
interesting
can I just continue oh I can continue
shooting in here it's just for me to be
able to see it
but now I can see the playlist
oh I mean okay I guess we're just
chilling now he's a ball I could be a
ball too we could be balling together
man you want me ball friends
yes you do this to me why
why
we can play ball games together soccer
or do you prefer football
um
is that what you want
daddy why am I doing this I don't know I
want I want this one thank you
[Music]
what are you doing please do not no no
okay those people
I can't change the camera when when
you're bald that really sucks man
out
out [\h__\h] hell out
uh wait I was gonna say I'm doing fine
but damn his health
barely goes down but hey at least he
provides me with some help
out
[Music]
do I really need to okay
I just need to like see it once is that
what it is and then you can just use the
normal one all the time
I think I got that one
follow him
not as bawling as him
I'll call him
[Music]
thank you
I'm doing okay though I think
I feel like it could go better but
I think we're good
ow
L come on please stop can I have some of
that help that's falling around though
did I
oh
oh oh it's gone it's gone
you'll have to do that with all of us
where's next
what are you doing what are you doing
he's rocking
what
okay
I don't wanna
look
I
don't know okay I see it I see it I
indeed oh wait I really can't see
yo
taking too much damage these days
[Music]
oh
I can't see okay okay
I'm just taking too long
hey you literally like both the thermal
one end of the normal one you can't see
now
what about now okay
he's halfway down
I think I'm gonna try and use that
missile a couple more times just use it
up
oh okay
[Music]
I don't know if I got anything just now
okay Mrs low
my HP is still very good
um
where is he
this is really confusing
[Music]
oh
what okay oh we lost another one nice
he's going hungabunga mode
I'm gonna switch uh to the normal one
again
[Music]
are you done
okay okay
need some help thank you the first boss
didn't give me help at all this one's
really nice in that regard
and this one nice
yeah easy easy he's almost dead
I feel like first half was more
difficult
and can actually pretty nicely Dodge
these two
ouch
that was close
hey he's spanning that now I can't think
of anything else he's panicking just
like me he turns into a panic ball oh
man just like me for real for real so
that can relate to him now
not so bad
it was just a rock and now he's just a
ball man but
it doesn't the surface kind of treatment
doesn't he man
just like me
he fumbles with the controls he's not
actually trying to be a ball oh but he's
almost dead
I have really panicked at the end of the
chance
foreign
[Music]
what was that
kind of repetitive but it was all right
at least I didn't struggle too much
nicer
ball
Ultra Ball
I can catch me some Pokemon with this
one no way I'm a survival can I hold on
to the walls
press and hold ZL and then more fomo to
attach this pineapple trick or specific
tracks
like those ones
[Music]
wait is there anything else we'll see
yeah okay
oh spider ball spider ball does whatever
a spider ball can
it I can't
what is that L I'm pressing that L
that boss menu quit as a kid really hmm
I mean
I I guess there's like
because there's maybe like even though
as an adult it seems
easily understandable because the kids
there's certain things we just don't get
as easily wait is there anything else
before I go there
oh
[Music]
how do I
oh I've got it all figured out
yeah here's also a puff where do I go
first
I don't I guess that's where it came
from
[Music]
which exit do I take
I guess the one I just passed
I just want to check if something's
there too
I've got this ball figured out
oh man
fall figured out
I've got it all ball figured out he says
oh wait okay
wait it's not that door what
after all that back and forth
that's a bald ass back and forth really
almost fell down
ah finally man finally we have made
progress
you win some you lose some isn't that
where it came from though
no
let's just stay uh the same pattern is
over there okay
even though it's the same Bridge
[Music]
I get hit every time hello kiwawa hello
you did very well did you say um no
no
well no
well I would have had to go all the way
back
is
should I
say for the hand okay
okay not like last time
let's go
it but I feel like it
I need 12 of those relics right that got
zero like one I guess right now
how am I gonna do this in three parts
are they just really easy to collect at
that point
oopsie
Blue Door safe one thank you
basic make me press a
to actually go
I haven't lost to a boss today I haven't
lost your boss I have lost two
some small [\h__\h] though
six but no don't say six parts no
yeah I'm just I'm just doing my best I'm
just a little orange bird doing my best
trying to ruin my best
um
so happy to see you playing this Mario's
entire family is watching me
yo Mario why the [\h__\h] did you not let me
into Nintendo World when I was in usj
huh
why why why
kind of rude no I'm not gonna I'm not
gonna do that again no
[Music]
no tonight
it's 10 p.m now
played almost four hours
I don't know if I should
continue a bit more or
why did I do that
should I end it here
I just did a boss
maybe yeah I know
is there another good point to end up
ahead
you have quite a backlog yeah and I said
there's no pressure to
[Music]
today
I'm the boss yeah that's true
read while playing I don't think I can
do you guys think if I next time if I
stream like six or seven hours you think
I can finish it
because today it was only like three
hours 40 minutes
and I I took it really slow in the
beginning
what do you think no no
what if I do eight hours
more like 10.
yeah so two more parts is what you're
saying
damn okay
two two Medford streams next week
okay
damn
I might start them a bit earlier next
week then well like today at least
um
I'm halfway through
I've never said before Parts
um
okay
though
damn
foreign
that's what we'll do
oh man
nice
so many things to keep up on apparently
the general made another server
for me to keep up on things
Discord server
um
[Music]
I think maybe it's also just for herself
to be able to keep track of everything
oh yeah
hold on
one channel per project more or less
yeah
can one server invite me no
you're absolutely balling today my short
games are hard thank you
[Music]
um
I think five of them on the weekend will
be very refreshing for me
you can't land
wait we'll make it always happen don't
you already have a server okay server
hmm
oh I watched a little bit Yeah yesterday
I tuned in around the end
I was surprised you guys were still
going
with the kfb podcast
I heard a little bit
maybe the last 30 minutes or so
I listened to the rest never time maybe
you guys went on for so long what the
[\h__\h]
um
some of y'all were talking a little bit
about cheating on me so what was that
all about huh I have a gun right now
guys I have a gun and I'm not afraid to
use it
anyway while I was listening I was
trying to um I was experimenting
with my cats
specifically with smoothie
as my test object
I ordered
a leash
test if my cats like the leash
so that you know I could let them out on
the balcony again because I don't trust
them anymore on the balcony without but
I also feel like
you know especially now when it gets
warmer I would like them to
get some fresh air again you know
and if smoothie really likes it
then I would think about maybe bringing
her to a park maybe even yeah
now let's plop that on the ground in the
first to move okay this movie wasn't so
bad of it it was a little bit difficult
at first to put it on her
on the second try I got it to work like
I got it on her she was like still a
little bit like irritated but but
I then carried her outside on the
balcony
and I just like put her there and you
know she was slow and like not really
into it
but
she she took a few steps it's not like
she was completely Paralyzed by it like
some other
cats and dogs
[Music]
and then after a while I was like I
guess I'll bring her back in
and then she really wanted to take it
off
eventually she like started picking a
fight with the leash
uh
but then I uh I took off the just a
leash but she still had the harness on
and then I started playing with the
laser
the little laser that she loves to play
with and immediately she completely
forgets about having the harness on
no yeah it's not a collar they have a
harness yeah
I got a harness
you want one of yours
butterflies that's so cute
air goals
cat owner calls I mean I feel like it's
so weird to see people walk their cats
it's a really rare thing and whenever I
see it I'm also like well that's weird
but then again I always feel like you
know
cats that you keep at home
that you don't let out feels so bad for
them just never seeing the world right
it's funny it is funny and weird yeah so
[Music]
um
actually so when once I played with her
with the laser she completely forgot
about the harness and even before that
she was like okay with it so I feel like
you know
two out of four like it the other two
don't really like having on the harness
that's that's all right I didn't test it
on chonkers yet but she was like the
moment I unpacked it and put the stuff
on the ground the leash and the harness
chunkers was just like rolling around
and on top of it as if there was catnip
on it
she went like
and was on her back rolling around
[Laughter]
it was like I was gonna put it on
smoothie but you you seem very okay with
it too not until
probably not anymore once I put it on
her I didn't Thrive with her yet because
I think I'll have to buy a bigger size
for chocolates
I bought like a medium size
um gotta buy a bigger one for trunkers I
think
I was just trying to test it out first
on this movie yeah but for real if it
works I I think I want to try bringing
this movie somewhere maybe tonkers too
if she likes it
yeah
he'll have to buy that's all this nail
Liza
[Music]
one of your cats gets excited when you
get the leash yeah I hope that movie
will eventually get that too like once
she understands that leash means outside
time
maybe then she will be happy about it
when I bring it out and you know just
have to get used to it but so far the
first try wasn't so bad because I I know
I know some pets just completely refuse
it
um
here's hoping
oh
no
hmm
no shoes
okay let's go to office
[Music]
sorry I got so tilted for part of that
stream
but I got tilted in a different way than
yesterday
it was inevitable at least I didn't quit
I was I really wanted to quit but I was
like uh stream too short I cannot quit
now
I cannot quit
do you hear this
nostalgic
[Music]
you don't
oh guess I have like my dad
okay
there you go now I hear it don't you
silence
your final quiz quitting isn't anything
Minecraft oh this makes you think of
Minecraft you know I wouldn't mind
playing Minecraft again like every once
in a while but like I legit don't know
what to do and now they have a new
server and I haven't like
joined it since the new server is out
so I don't know what to do
but we're all like back home now right
so we could do the weather now
right
I should revive the weather chat
let me let me see I haven't played it so
long I need to warm up though
it's for real
much to die this is a group name
shall we
buy this
and do it sometime soon
[Music]
also uh oh yeah I am planning
and preparing the
um
oh my already typing the Easter
thing that I wanted to do
uh whole talk now it has
once again become difficult to get a
hold
of corner but we are more or less in
contact so
we'll get her eventually
um but no dumb
the Easter thing
oh
it will be a VR stream thingy VR project
so I'll be
um paying for that for the creation of
some things
um
currently I got quite a couple of them
you know I poked them who wants to
participate
not all of them are gonna be
participating but some of them
and for the sake of the others
participation it might be like in the
middle of the night before Europe
because I wanted to be possible for
everybody
so now I have like including me
I think
six and a half participants
because one of them said she's not 100
sure but she'll try
if she feels good at that time
but even if it's just I think that's
okay
oh yeah so
I gotta
gotta start like I need to make a thread
to make a thread how do you make a
thread
are Stalin
name Easter VR project
makeup
make of the channel
emote denma added
mode for me to the Discord
now we can use it
I'm gonna add
members later but
yeah
so that will be on the ninth I think
because Easter is I think on the 9th of
April
um I'm a bit nervous because
you know I did like some smaller scale
things like with the Maldives uh
Maldives Elena VR thingy I planned that
and all
but this is gonna be a bit bigger and I
feel a bit more pressured about that one
I hope it goes well basically I'm
planning like two games
um and one of them is just kind of like
the same system as
the one of the Maldives games that I
used
um
don't you also have animal Boston that
day yeah so I'm gonna try to just
you know it doesn't take so long what is
it a panel and a meet and greet
shouldn't take too long panels usually
are one hour
although probably
American time right so it's gonna it's
gonna be shooting time for me I don't
even know the time I don't think they
told me the time for our panel
I have a panel of Cobble
I'm so confused
I think there's two ID members right and
two young numbers
they asked me to take a video and I just
like
automatically when I took the video I
said ah I'll be here doing a panel of
bills
a couple days later they come back to me
and they're like okay wow can you retake
the video
you don't have a panel of bagels you
have it with Cobble I'm like oh
oops
I just assumed
oh yeah but also there
oh
actually I do get grouped a lot with
Bales like for this kind of stuff at
least last year
because for a Korean convention
was me and Bales and I feel like I was
also somewhere with bells as well some
somewhere else
Northeast I wonder what she's gonna do
for looking maybe she has a translator
does she even do a paddle I don't know
yo she did get grouped often with me
oh yeah that works yeah I mean that's
nice too like basically you're getting a
lot of performance singing
think a couple on me we're gonna like
mix a game with some singing too
both is nice oh are there any people who
are going to Anime Boston
anyone
[Music]
I am oh
me oh
I oh that's quite a bunch
in here
uh oh wait that's a lot wow
wait where is Boston by the way is it on
the left or the right side or the middle
where is Boston
is it East Coast
[Music]
right oh East Coast
um
so far I have really nothing lined up
for Europe
no convention has reached out as far as
I know
and we just didn't
wanna be at documents here
either
um I was gonna say oh yeah so everybody
who's going to anime blast then
please bring
[Music]
a towel
not a big one
bring a small narrow one lengthy one
because I want to do a heart Challenger
again
I will um feel free to spoiler that much
of my setlist
I felt like it would be fun to do that
again
at such a venue where I have the freedom
I feel like for non-kfp who will be
there they will be shocked but
um spread the knowledge if you know some
other non-kfps who are going to Anime
Boston and we'll try to get into the
panel maybe let them know or bring a
second towel if you have two like bring
it and then maybe give it to the person
next to you if it's not the cave person
have fun you want to say nothing so get
sweaty no no I mean you can use it for
that too what's the towel for
um I think there is a
I uploaded the Vlog right like a clip of
me performing hot challenge right
I think that exists
you can see the towels there right
yeah don't I'm gonna do that again
during the chorus everybody
this time well we won't have dancers
unless
we don't have the answers
unless I can quickly hire some cute
girls to dance for me but I don't think
so I don't even know
not in the budget I would have to pay
for that
on my own pocket I need us to back up
dance for you
now hiring Hugo
we'll dance for you oh
[Music]
it's cute fans to do it well I don't
even know like who's where and who wants
to do it
pain exposure
well honestly like uh I know that you
know paying for exposure people say
that's like rude to even offer that but
I feel like
the exposure some people got from me
brought them so many jobs right
so like Spirit snare for example it's
like now the go-to person for Logos
same for yunarun
another one gets hired by so many people
now
so I feel like my exposure actually like
really works is really promising I did
pay them yeah yeah I did Pace per snare
[Music]
yeah I think it's root so I don't offer
I don't I don't I don't go up to people
and I'm like hey can you do this for me
for exposure
I don't want to do that either that
sounds so cheap but I do feel like it's
definitely a thing
Olivia's for example also got
uh that's weather job right for example
but Olivia is for Olivia's I actually
recommended
I recommended the olivius among others
when staff was like do you guys have any
like pixel artists
that you know I was like these ones
okay
[Music]
this that's what happens when you get on
my good side
yeah
exposure should not be the main finger
painting with but they would definitely
be incredibly thankful yeah
I know about it about it until
afterwards
what happened if we got on your bad side
don't you know already
how many people working with you found
success while bringing in towns well
yeah
I'm happy for them as long as they're
still like making themselves available
for me too
and not just disappear in the void after
they're getting all the other jobs
[Music]
and I'm really enjoying the clips you're
making recently thank you thank you so
much it's really funny
like I like it when Clippers
um upload like at least part of the clip
on Twitter as a video too and I'll just
link it because that stuff is really
easy to retweet
your choreographer was also hired by
other member wasn't she was she
I know that like Cali followed her
so I was like
oh I wouldn't know I mean I hired her
several times
that I will probably continue to do so
because I just I'm not really satisfied
with you know
I mean I don't sound like choreographers
even in Japan to them that was
considering hiring but um
I'll just stay with Kiana for now I
introduced her to Reyna
what did you introduced her to Lena what
you're the middle man
higher Bay oh yeah I was shocked
I asked to like yo that choreo
before too right and she also did a
stick dance to it I feel like what am I
imagining it I was like is that the same
because I I don't remember is that the
same choreo as the one that LaPlace did
and she was like no no
I came up with that I'm like what
what
was that girl girl that's incredible
that's an insane talent because
I can come up with some simple moves but
that was so intricate on so many moves
it was crazy
[Music]
but in theory I guess I could hire her
for Aquario but I don't know
I don't think she has the time or you
know
30 minutes no way
30 minutes did she say that she needed
40 minutes only
I was sad give me a moment I'm warming
up
hmm
you know you like that don't don't act
as if you were
complaining about it
where do I even have to start
where did I stop last time
I mean I finished the the Showcase ones
and then
everything after the Showcase
that's it okay
[Music]
um
back already hurt again just had a
massage and already hot
did we really not read after that
damn
showcase okay
then okay Japan stories plus super chats
stream Head super Chats on
no no I always I'm always in pain
dancing
all right okay here we go I don't think
I'll finish the all of them but we'll
start
[Music]
excellent I was surprised you know
um I I met up with my best friend
and you know I know my best friend is
really [\h__\h] busy
but I was like kind of considering
um
she has this thing like oh my God she
just overloads herself with things to do
aren't you hot with the helmet on
good it's open in the back don't you see
anyway so she one of the things she does
is like she she was doing like a like a
a sporty thing sporty thing every once
in a while maybe weekly I think weekly
one
which ones maybe once
and I asked her if she stopped it by now
because
I have a feeling it was done and I was
like considering asking her if she maybe
wants to take instead take a dance class
with me
and I held back on asking it because I
thought you know
I really feel bad for her she's so busy
but then at the end when we were like
saying goodbye to each other she kind of
read my mind
she she asked me you want to do a dance
class with me and I'm like
girl
girl you're too busy
me
[Music]
yeah hmm
I don't know what uh I kind of want to
learn
something like Tango
or
I I don't know some hip-hop or K-pop
kind of style
of dancing
be fine too but I also kind of just want
to learn like a classic kind of dance
man
spicy because I for real don't know yeah
salsa I want to learn salsa
[Music]
yeah wanna learn a classic dance I don't
know [\h__\h]
how can I be really sophisticated if I
don't if I'm not able to suddenly bust
out some classic dance moves
like they do in the movies do they
really like is that even possible
people in real life actually are they
able to do stuff like that like turn and
you know fall back and all that why is
it so synchronized
why do they know
I want to do something like that
oh my best friend already attempted to
teach me the waltz before
I think I just had no brain capacity at
that time
yeah but if we do something like Tango
or so
one of us has to do the leading
she's taller than me though so I feel
like she would do the leading
I don't know if she wants to do that
though
the leading part
she was kind of like
lacking confidence in dancing
she wants to learn it
let's go but she already knows how to do
the vaults
she's probably more thinking of dancing
hip-hop now
she said she wants to learn uh do you
hahaha
yeah good luck with that
really looks rough man
it was really [\h__\h] rough
[Music]
stretched too much
good morning hello all right we're gonna
write some super chats now from
[Music]
wait
sure
[Music]
okay
here we go
the inside of my mouth kind of hurts so
I don't know how long I can do it but
I'll try
let's go Fox
um
[Music]
I still can't get over how incredible
yo4dw is I probably rewatched the whole
stream for more than seven to eight
times what
definitely the best 3DW ever I'm
seriously so proud of you Kiana you're
so [\h__\h] amazing you truly are the
best thank you I definitely had a lot of
time
so I continued to be sick after that
so lots of time to watch Chihuahua over
and over and over again thank you
[Music]
if I see you do hip-hop moves I'm gonna
be so damn hyped well I think there is
elements of hip-hop moves in my current
choreographies already
laughs
basically
isn't it isn't it basically like
inspired by that
I would say so
[Music]
uh
thank you for the rest of the chat
Freddy W behind us and you're behind was
also buffed that petition was worth it
it was really good showcase not only of
your model but also if you killed this
glad to be since glad to be since the
beginning to witness everything that led
to that very moment oh thank you for
being there for so long man
you've been there really
for a long time
when others leave me
[Music]
oh scratch tree
why are you attacking my blouse
did you hear is that more oh I'm just
gonna leave again she just said hi
she's such a sweetie man so sweet
you heard her it's been a while since
last movie let me stand to talking about
the spaghetti moment no you didn't I
still didn't talk about it I don't know
I don't know how to tell you
I'm struggling a little bit with um
deciding on how to tell you and what
exactly to tell you
to be honest
um maybe next time
I can talk about it um yeah yeah
in the distance
well I think it's better to just um wait
a while and then tell
just just I'm just gonna wait a while
you know
hmm
it's gonna need an uninterrupted tangent
okay I'll try
yeah we're letting it stew
I'm not gonna forget oh eventually I'll
be like oh guys is there anything like
in the Fire Emblem stream probably I'll
be like guys is there any tangent that I
was supposed to tell you
and then you can mention it
yes it's not unlocked yet
oh yeah guys by the way I know I've been
like saying oh I'm gonna make a do you
um call chant guide
uh before the concert
uh for completion's sake
um
I ended up not doing it because even
though
I I asked Steph I was like is it okay to
do it because it's the only song that
doesn't have a guide maybe not
necessarily it hints at me doing it at
the concert and they were like yeah
that's fine
listen it's fun even though they also
said very clearly do not hint at the set
list
of the concert in any way
so
however that I mean that was obviously
clear but I was like reminded of it
later on
before I was gonna do the the video
and then I kind of chickened out and was
like maybe I shouldn't do it
because if I do it before the concerts
well that would be ideal but at the same
time I'm obviously like hinting at it
yeah so I was like maybe it's better
before I get bonked even though they
said I could do it Ian management said I
could do it but before I get bonked I
was like
I better not do it and you know what in
hindsight even if I had done it I don't
think so many people would have really
like seen it and followed followed on
doing it
because well
it's hard to reach
thousands and thousands of people who
are not necessarily at all my fan base
to do it
so I thought it's probably gonna be fine
I will make one yeah
[Music]
maybe if
or maybe I mean I'm not saying I'm gonna
do do you
in the oh like that I'm gonna do
anything at all maybe I won't even
perform maybe I'll just run around on
the stage and do cartwheels for the EM
concert
but I just want my guides to be complete
until then
until the next big
uh
is like real concert where there's gonna
be a real audience
just for the sake of it being complete
[Music]
yeah
and I'm hoping that you know in an Ian
concert
still even though there will be mixed
fandoms
we just have 10 members
and on the big four Fest there were way
more members
so I feel like we have a better chance
at getting other fandoms to cooperate as
well maybe take a look
at the guides and honestly I feel like
you can learn from my guides and even
apply the same methods to other songs
like your own oshi's songs
because there's just really like simple
patterns of how to cheer and chant
um
see I'll even make one for
like General
my other songs I don't know
maybe I'll make one for Ultra mequino
for example
not saying that they will be also making
no but for example
maybe one for myth songs
not saying there will be MIP songs but
for example
you know maybe I should do some like
something like that I feel like
I should I should help out teaching you
guys
maybe I can even do it like a like a
general VR stream
and then teach like the general patterns
and and rhythms to all kinds of songs
and show how they apply to
like any kind of song
I just use all kinds of
whole live English songs solos
and whatever like anything really that
comes into my hands
and show you guys what I would do which
you don't follow completely but maybe it
will be an inspiration because let me
tell you it's so much fun
to cheer like that
on a concert
in unison
[Music]
don't worry I'm not gonna go change
on you guys
I mean I saw
I saw
um
bad in action
uh when
umu and the others were performed um
Diamond city lights and a convention and
holy [\h__\h] that was incredible
wow
they actually the audience actually
followed that whole chant
that was insane
where is your copy paste
[Music]
hmm
and it feels like there's something
missing is that really how it goes
[Music]
um
something like that
I need to listen to the OG again
nah I don't think we need to do that
because you know
it's easier to not do that
it's the version that fits in YouTube
Maybe
I mean
we can try having something like that in
a song
it would be epic
it would be epic if everybody followed
it but it's not easy really
but in general I feel like it in such a
in a venue like that if everybody
because I think almost all of these
words end with ah
if you just fumble Wi-Fi but I got tired
the whole time
or less
more or less it will sound like what it
should sound like and
you know you can't really clearly hear
everything anyway in a venue like that
where everybody screams like that
all right as long as it ends with R just
think of a couple of these words and
just completely repeat them again and
again
like that hmm
like no pressure to 100 nail it
or actually yeah I remember
um seeing this in like smaller scale
concerts
like underground concerts
um where there would be like many Idols
performing and therefore also many
fandoms
uh like being mixed together for the
sake of the the fandoms who are not
particularly there for that Idol
like one of the most prominent fans
would like stand in the very front
with like signs and throughout the whole
call
chance
show the signs in the front row to the
people behind him
yeah guide them
um
for the greater good
you could just read it off there
yeah
but I don't know just saying that that
happens not none of you guys should do
it but
um
oh we just gotta practice
make promo do that at the end concert
ticket
how do you know about it it's a thing
it's a common thing I've been to many
concerts
out of concerts
a project you know the bigger one in
general just didn't do that
I guess also just to be more
um
how to say
easily accessible for new fans and you
don't get too intimidated what they do
is fun but and you might have to learn
some things but in general it's just
always repeating the same patterns
oh
oh my proudest woman is
screaming a chance instrumental
were you the only person probably
but if you do it you really have to do
it in a loud like Gremlin voice
I've heard some
yo
voices that sound like they came
straight from hell do this kind of
chance in Japan before
it's scary but you gotta gotta learn it
all out
like you're doing screamo
I can't even
oh
thank you crayons good night
just get like a
not a megaphone but just like a
um
it's not a megaphone just in the shape
of a megaphone but
uh not with the megaphone part yeah just
a cone
let's get a cone
I don't know if that helps though that
will probably make it sound kind of
unclear
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is a vuvuzela
look at that
oh what
no that's not what I meant but oh my God
does that even work with that
it's not just for going dut I don't
think you can really say words into that
this one just goes like
funny
ah thank you cyanobsia
trauma
most annoying games of 2010 why was
there like a sudden hype of
vuvuzelas
it was just a zip world
Meister shaft
in 2010
um
that was so annoying it was overused
oh
I need to continue watching
Ted lasso because the new season is out
and I was about to finish the one before
when I left for Japan
and I couldn't watch it in Japan but
it was out as far as I know
I really want to watch the new season
let's go and then once I'm done with Ted
lasso by that time probably the new
season of marvelous Mrs Mason will be
out which is also the last one but I'm
super hyped for that one too because I
was waiting for that for a long time too
and then then they like say last year
November would be when the new season of
that other like fantasy show would come
out that was I was watching it never did
I think
Maybe by summer they deleted a lot I
think
[Music]
yeah this one I will finish Marvel's Mrs
maisel sounds difficult to watch us
we love time yeah
distract me let's go
we love time
[Music]
foreign
for the pinky hey boss I'm writing this
before I sleep what an honor to have you
stream on my birthday oh congratulations
on the amazing fruity debut uh get well
soon I hope to see you and I'm a boss
next month oh we were just talking about
it how fitting Chris Clements I don't
know if you're here now but happy
belated birthday
I'm trying hard to keep um this movie on
my lap right now happy belated birthday
congratulations sorry I'm so late to
sing this
but yeah you'll be an animal boss until
then please bring a towel uh uh a
lengthy but not like a bath towel more
like a hand towel you know kind of like
a scarf shaped towel you could I guess
you could bring a scarf as well
and Pen lights too
to be perfectly prepared
um
yes please do please do
I want to see the towels in the air
again making a air conditioning movement
yeah you can totally bring the full face
towel I think that one's perfect for
that kind of stuff
where twin tins no not necessary
[Music]
um Dr Professor Duncan
let's go Doncaster
for the pinky today's my birthday all
also your birthday you guys have a
birthday together it's my third birthday
I celebrate with you
for such a long time thank you
also congratulations to you too happy
belated birthday I'm really late on this
one too sorry
what are you guys saying the myth the
legend he's back to eating my Tyson's
ass
uh
Cinema
[Music]
at this time
foreign
I guess he never really left yeah I
think so
my baby's back
so happy
earlier times didn't have English on you
what they have they have movies at like
what 11 pm
anyway happy happy birthday I hope you
celebrated a little bit
green blue see thanks for the pinky I
can I want to say that I have been
watching you stream for a while now and
you never fail to make me smile laugh
really
I also want to tell you that I'm going
to Europe and also to Phoenix land
Austria in a few days are you here now
are you behind me are there any places I
should go are you here probably not
I wonder if you're back home by now it
could be very well could be God I'm so
sorry I failed as an Austrian tourist
Ambassador which I am not maybe if they
would have made me an Austrian tourist
Ambassador then I would have been on
time with recommending you something are
you here I also still in in Austria
City
yes
[Music]
which fitting you in
let me help you
only there for one day
[Music]
well what did you see
what day is like nothing
like I say we're doing like a Europe
tour
short
I come back
what
I mean this looks nice but
come one day to Austria and you go to
Instagram who forced you to do that
is
that must have been a reason
[Music]
toy was in the [\h__\h]
what kind of tour is that showing you
the most Niche corners of each Country
tour
the health
if you have a tour
I guess I was just
like geographically close to the next
location that you would go to
God
but I hope you liked Instagram I guess
in Sport's not I think I think ins book
was nice decent honestly
yeah yeah it's pretty decent it was
pretty good actually it's pretty pretty
it's quite pretty oh damn
that is pretty
but a lot of cities in Austria look like
exactly this
students look bad no I'm just surprised
it was that out of all the places you
could go to because I feel like there's
more important cities but I'm just
biased
I'm just really biased
but it's actually really beautiful you
guys should Google it my God
beautiful but it looks
honestly looks like a more colorful
sales book to me
I've also only been to his look what the
[\h__\h]
what
oh yeah that's what you guys were saying
there's is there more than one city
because of geographers shenanigans
ah
it's my pleasure nice that so many of
you guys actually went to Japan it's so
far
God no God's is nice too
is there any place that isn't beautiful
in Austria well I feel like there's
definitely Corners in each City that are
not pretty
hmm
but in general
Australia is nice so well you're really
pretty
kind of EST group is meaning again for
Boston oh
[Music]
so nice you know I
I was kind of mad
when I was seeing all that
Expo
and Fest
stuff
from my point of view again
just like last year
that's that's kind of mad like
what the [\h__\h] I'm missing out on so much
fun
like this looks so much fun from the
point of view of like a visitor
so
I Joe sarcastically but
also
[Music]
motivatedly said
in our Discord
um
I'm hereby announcing I'll be graduating
until if there is a fifth Festival
because that's it I want to see it from
the visitor point of view
[Laughter]
I'm just crawling the staff like that
and no I'm like for real jealous
it looks like so much fun calm down guys
it was a dork it's George
but uh
the thing is I even got one or two plus
one emote react
from other members
and then jenma and some others gave me
that a big eyes imma react you know can
you imagine the big one that's like we
also we also have one of those actually
no comment though there was no no like
actual comments like
just just react emotes laughs
yeah that one
um
wow you're freaking us out
oh I think I could reject if I really
didn't want to be with why would I not
want to be part of it
tap I want to be I want to see both
sides
um
I want to be in the audience and I want
to be in the Expo visitor Hall
and I want to hang with other fandoms
like kfb
as if I was a fan from the start already
like a normal fan
just back to how it used to be when I
was just a whole life fan
man
imagine
if I if I was still just a whole life
fan
I wouldn't I would definitely possibly
could have just been there as a normal
visitor if I would have gotten a ticket
okay realistically speaking I probably
wouldn't have gotten a ticket
but but I would have wanted to be there
for sure
I'd totally be one of you guys
and
[Music]
um
let me type
one of us you'll be here complaining
about no EU support
[Music]
I was a board Watcher anyway happily
but I think whole life would have never
got
um like come to docomo
or any European convention for that
matter
because I feel like really that dopami
happened because we were pushing it
and yeah
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I mean it's it's rough being the only
one in Europe a lot of the time
for some reason but at the same time I'm
enjoying my Monopoly
so far
[Music]
Dynasty
thank you guys
I will have so much free time if you
didn't join the whole life
thank you
oh you guys so sweet
sorry for taking all your free time
[Music]
if not you I would have probably dropped
a live already thank you wow
I get a lot of like moments recently
where I'm like I can't believe people
actually like like me what the hell
I mean a lot of people don't like me too
but there's also so many people that
like me and I'm like what why what how
thank you
I'm like not only five there's a couple
more than just five thank God
ah thank you Nathan
thank you one
not even carefully I probably wouldn't
be a whole fan being limited to 4am
stream mods from others wouldn't be
enough oh are you also from Europe
no one got me as hooked as you hey
need to get more EU people in here
though
more more
it's a bit of ID
ah
thank you Ellen
oh my God I have to raise up a chat
hey I want to say we need a new Branch I
think the new Branch could just be mixed
into en Branch but
just be nice to have some more I guess
or just in general it would be nice to
have more members right now
just doesn't even have to be Europeans
I know I know I know your rope branch
you have a rope cake
[Music]
um yo what
deduction
[Music]
um
because I've been done with this one so
much earlier
okay fine episode six doesn't have super
chats uh catching up before work super
chat's reading it doesn't have Super
Shots either because I turned them off
and then next is unbelievably believable
opposite
little genius
stream
that I have have you guys noticed in the
logo has anyone paid attention to what's
written behind the logo which is also
part of the logo
it didn't it's the purikuda tangent
yeah
Spirit snare came up with that wasn't me
it wasn't even me
[Music]
ah did he say it in the tweet
I like this logo I feel like it looks
legit like
it could be the logo of a game like a
like a board or a card game board card
game
[Music]
I really like it because like I got a
lot of
[Music]
um like mock-ups in the beginning I was
like that's not that's not quite it I
wanted to be more like this and that
then we got to this one I'm really happy
with this one
[Music]
yeah
it totally looks like it could be I
don't know from something like
um
uh what's it called
Family Feud also I don't know
looks really good
so super chat from that stream
[Music]
I thought it was a real Logo game until
this moment
until this very moment
no
I basically I mean it's inspired by
something but I came up with the name
with the collab and it's like just
basically one of those streams where I
make up a game
that's not really a game you know not
like a like a computer game
huh
but I guess it the logo helps that that
just looked that good
[Music]
yes it's based on that r9000.
make a part to one who come forward yeah
yeah I was planning on inviting them and
then maybe do like an international one
just to see who and Ian wants to do
another one and then mix it with ID
maybe I could
yeah maybe as a host I could host a
Japanese one
Maybe
not sure about that one though but
definitely I want to do a mixed one of
ID
yeah thank you
[Music]
thank you for the rest of chat this
looks super fun boss hype can I dedicate
monkey while okay so crayons in the next
Super Chat rating
what did crayons do deserve that huh
Koreans come here come here
how you like that
[Music]
imagine me oh
this crayons go to sleep oh no
maybe even said goodbye
no
not anymore
um
[Music]
look at that code for the support I
appreciate it you're the best
and then we have a rainbow
what kind of a double rainbow from all
or L thank you plus I'm here to
recommend the game again this time I
will not fail you all I have confidence
but first please don't push yourself too
much if you don't feel good take a rest
any time second thing some customers
complain that you disturb their meal by
singing in the restaurant
[Music]
um
that's about
it's too long ago and I don't remember
oh wait wait is it about the uh behind
the scenes scenes of Another 3D showcase
the transition where I was like dancing
and stuff
I was just lip syncing to the radio
wasn't singing you didn't have any audio
oh it's just lip syncing
supposed to say that
I was just mixing by the way a lot of
like random things I have thought of in
the moment it's not like there's one
reference to AKB song indeed that I
think some people noticed I want to I
need to I love you
but I didn't want to like do too much of
it because I thought maybe I'd get
bonked I was like mixing that or some
other like random moves and I thought it
would look funny
heavy rotation
I have people know that oh
wow
no I am excused for that because once I
turn the floor into the Disco floor and
bring out the disco ball you know it's
disco time you know that
foreign
then your job is not to serve the
customers
but to serve me with your claps and
Tents
hmm
company mandated disco time yeah
excuse me lular Hawk excuse me
I knew
just ignoring the existence of idol
master
I mean I almost had a
anime too
it wasn't really
like I mean was there more than one
because the one that I saw I guess it
wasn't
[Music]
um
was there ever Cinderella girls
um anime I wonder if not then they
really miss an opportunity but I watched
one really old one back in the day
there was well then but that was
probably a little bit later
oh my God what was her name shibuyadin
was that her name I love her
also I love
[Music]
um
okay is like
forever top-notch
cute Aesthetics can't get cuter than
that love her
laughs
no she's so cute oh my God I love her so
much
love the OG I'll mask anime
um
yeah the one that I watched was the
mecca one
um
it was um interesting
[Music]
because like
I think
I went in there after watching some
idolmaster game content
and yeah I think set the center one yeah
I was like it this is not like in the
game at all
yeah
it's a long time ago I don't remember
though
it
wants the actual I don't know did I I
mean I would say you know even if I
didn't watch it I would say it
definitely can compete with the it could
be one
just because I I am
strong stand for idle master
also over love life
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt
though that I could be anime may have
been decent too yeah
anyway oh
so wait let me continue reading back to
my recommendation drums please today's
game is
Dead Space remake yeah wait please wait
to the usual yeah the moment I saw what
you wrote I was like hmm
disappointed
ah please wait before you sent me to the
usual room I have one more but I don't
think you'll like it it's called
I'm serious
but I know you for so long I know you
don't like it
[Music]
[Applause]
when I joined the cafe I have heard
rumors that you're a hardcore player oh
oh oh you're trying to get on my good
side Charming me rumor has it that you
can beat Five Nights at Freddy's without
blinking an eye
I know the person tell me the rumor is
one of kfb the name is oh damn it
um
wow
I uh
I played
the Sophie one privately
I [\h__\h] love that one because Plata is
one of my all-time ever forever favorite
characters
in Italian games
and forever will be
those character designs my God oh my God
I was like oh
[Music]
I mean you know actually it's not
not logical
that
Riser is the one that gets
like until the games a little bit more
spread on the market out there for big
audience when in Sophie you already had
Plata who was hot as [\h__\h] also thick and
spicy
and just dream girl you know
I mean okay thank you Raisa for
spreading at the layer
but how come it didn't already happen
with Plata huh because she yeah they
didn't make her the main character that
was a mistake they should have made
plastic
yeah
she was the second main character
but the game wasn't named after her
unfortunately
she's a book well yeah
um so
she's a hot book
it's the only book I'm willing to read
I don't even understand you have to look
it up
we need to see ryza in a Plata outfit I
feel like somebody must have already
made a fan out of that rise down
[Music]
cosplay maybe ryzer cosplaying plaster
please oh
oh that's not the one I want to see her
in
why you guys not giving me what I want
oh but
I see screenshot of a dead or alive
character and plaster's outfit wow oh
they had a gust mashup
eye on it and practice outfit oh
looks good
too funny
when was this no idea but it happened it
was a thing
damn I want to see the ass turn around
Plaza's ass is all out there I think as
far as I remember
oh my God spicy it's so spicy
[Music]
this is so
un cosplayable
just such a struggle
I can't look it up a
[Music]
few coward oh we're supposed to see
little [\h__\h]
oh uh
[Music]
um
Dead Space
I'll do you really think
I'm interested in playing that
like that's something my mom would tell
me to play
no I'm not gonna play that no
no no no no no
open my dead body
nope
oh
I never said that
I like Metroid
nothing about this that tickles my fancy
is that what you is that how you say it
I would have a heart attack playing dead
space there you go
yes okay good night good night good good
good good good
anyway sorry Al to disappoint you
um I feel like every single one of these
games you mentioned
I will have to turn you down however
there will be an anteliorizer for a
stream
day after tomorrow so at least that's
something right
I'm so sorry to disappoint you
I hope you weren't actually having some
hopes with that sorry
oh I should be able to read this by now
[Music]
ah my teacher gonna be disappointed me
I think it's
no is it nape is this one nape no not at
all neighbors just two signs
yeah uh yeah cause the circle is there
so it's an r and an n
that one I don't remember well this one
might not remember was at ear anti
[Music]
um
I guess that one I remember because I
said hat
looks like a hat so it's an H
mm
ah tough
do your Korean hope work
[Music]
I'm gonna pick up Corinne so fast and
surprises you I don't think so
Ross I feel like once I get over the
first phase of learning the letters
properly ramming that into my head then
we might be okay
after that I think I'll be fine
I feel like I'll have an easier time
picking up words
vocabulary then reading Hangul
all to learn languages
oh wait this name oh
[Music]
um
welcome back here it was never there in
the first one
soon
[Music]
I had a hair in my mouth be fashioned
understand
thank you it's Yoshi
[Music]
um
I came here to nap at your Danke Schoen
Johnny
thank you
lpnt
thanks Raymond Silverman Junction thank
you
log 082 I am a chicken
I was too lazy I don't give a [\h__\h]
attention
I didn't admit it I just write someone
else's name
they are the chicken
not me
guys I'm not I'm I'm too no
I'm not up for that kind of joke anymore
today
no no no
okay next is Fire Emblem part seven
[Music]
uh
I see
what's the square what's the square
again
this is square again guys
in Hungary
[Music]
and what's the the lower uh just
straight line
that's not e one that's um like an under
score
huh this is a straight line
[Music]
so
how do you pronounce
um the pot
e
C
mom the last one last one I don't know
it was that somewhere
close
I said yeah
[Music]
and I just wasn't able to read y'all
wow
[Music]
it takes me a long time though to read I
have to look at each Single part of the
letter because they make they're made up
of several ones
oh wait this one
uh that one I forgot
the one with the two the straight one
with the two to the side
help me great human
don't don't tell me the whole thing
though
what's just uh the second one
just the second one
the second letter okay
[Music]
oh yeah
I forgot
[Music]
I don't know
I almost cooked
[Music]
under
well I helped myself a lot with that one
but it is
a late night workout
I never translated that one for me
before I think
because he also always had the English
one in it so I just read
human
sorry I need to learn this my teacher is
coming tomorrow
she will kill me
ah she said what was it
[Music]
some was teachers some
sure
I was like should I call you this and
she's like no you will call me songs and
it reminded me of what uh my Korean
viewers call me because that was uh I
think yeah
potential is
so
also now I'm confused I think
[Music]
did you say while in a Korean right now
I mean like right now at this very
moment or in general in general because
I only wanted to do it last year and I
didn't
I wasn't able to do it properly on my
own
and now I need someone to push me to
actually learn it in general I just
always wanted to learn another language
anyway
and with Korean you know I have like a
good reason for it because
of the Korean brows I want to be able to
communicate a little bit with them and I
want to be able to sing Korean songs
without like mumbling and stuttering
and when I visited Korea last year I had
a lot of fun there and I do want to go
again
I want to be able to you know talk a
little bit
the people there and enjoy Korean media
and so on
um
yeah and it's like who has some
similarities with
some Japanese words or like generally I
guess they come from like old Chinese
words
uh so there's like some similar ones
[Music]
again that would be nice
I mean why not learning languages you
know is always always brings benefits
oh my God benefits from learning English
and Japanese
I could have chosen
you know other languages too and it
would have brought me um advantages with
that too
there's always ways of like
getting
reaching new people with a new language
being able to communicate with new
people
so I always recommend people should
learn at least we should at least be
able to speak like at least
languages
it opens up so many doors to you
in so many ways in terms of career
but also just in terms of getting to
know new people get being able to go to
countries and communicate freely there
um
[Music]
I would say Latin doesn't really help
as there is no one who actively speaks
Latin no country but it would help you
as a base to learn other languages yeah
it's when I get good in my German final
s
[Music]
hmm
I mean I will say that one motivation
was definitely you know getting so many
Korean viewers last year or last night's
here
um made me really happy to be you know I
always had like some interest in Korea
but that definitely motivated me
to get into it
[Music]
ah bully yeah I haven't heard from Brody
in a long time
where is body
yeah anyway what was I
[Music]
emblem stream
conduction
Sarah thank you for two pinkies and a
yellow one
you are
[\h__\h] amazing Kiana with such easy
Commander stage draw our eyes to you
make us laugh and cry and Inspire us but
you're not afraid to step off stage
Midas at eye level and mingle spaces
Twitter threads you give so much to us
whenever you catch one of us with our
wearing eyes
cast the ground you find a way to lift
our beaks to the sun again your free DW
was amazing a great Showcase of your
love for dancing idols and kfb proud of
you Kiana never stopped chasing that
Horizon
[Music]
huh I read the last part quietly okay
seems more intimate
kind of thing thank you very much for
the sweet words yeah I mean
it's funny because
you know how I tweeted up until now I
tweeted more than all myth members
combined apparently which I find very
amusing so I thought I tweet a lot right
the other day when I was talking to Nina
after the collab
um somehow that topic came up about
Twitter and tweeting a lot and I told
her that apparently I tweet like really
a lot and I told her the number and she
was like shocked and she was like oh
yeah I should tweet more too I don't
tweet so much and I'm like I go on their
account and I check it and she does have
like more than me more tweets than me
and I'm like girl what are you talking
about I guess the standards are just
different
yeah she thought she wasn't tweeting
enough
[Music]
me yeah they generally tweet a lot over
there so
uh
um yeah apparently she um replies to a
lot of uh her fans well I do that too
every once in a while
um
you know tweet a lot during her first
year like a lot I don't remember
is she really was there such a big
difference now
hmm
I just can't stop you know I want to
communicate and I feel like if I don't
like I'm already like for real spending
so much time on Twitter going through
all the tweets that you guys sent me
takes up more time that you think it
does probably
and I know that you guys get happy when
you get a like so I try my best to leave
a like here and there but also ends up
taking a lot of time because I don't
want to just blindly like stuff I wanna
like know what I'm liking so I try to
read everything too
a lot of the time sometimes I just
really roughly like go over it because I
feel like I need to
um because if I don't then you guys
gonna be sad
so I try
I try I try
but it takes a lot of time man and
and nowadays since the Twitter update
I have this update only on one of my
phones I noticed the other phone doesn't
have the update yet so I should be using
that one more often again
but uh it's now like when you go on
Twitter on your phone
maybe you guys don't have the update yet
but most people probably do it's the
home button yeah it brings you
automatically to for you not to
following even if you switch over to
following
eventually
when you like you know you push the
update button again to get to the top to
like refresh something
it brings you back to for you and I
don't even know this because I just
pressed that button so often to just
refresh everything quickly it brings me
back for you so often and then I just
don't know this and I go through and I
like all kinds of things that you guys
tweet that don't even have the kfp
hashtag but I get so many
recommendations from the from the fans
and yeah I've noticed that I've been uh
liking a lot more things without
hashtags than before and you guys are
like why the [\h__\h] is she seeing this and
I'm sorry guys I'm sorry for freaking
you out Twitter is just like serving it
to me on the silver platter
can't help it
it's not like I it doesn't even show
anymore this tweet is being shown to you
because you follow this person they
don't even show that anymore but I do
think I mean it must have still that
algorithm behind it it just doesn't say
that anymore they took away that as well
um
no no I don't like it I don't like that
it's like bringing me back to that
column unknowingly by default
um
yeah also now literally every third
tweet on that uh
part of the site is a promotional tweet
like they're spamming promotional tweets
so bad like as if it was Instagram I
feel like in the past I was like oh
Instagram
promotional tweets uh not tweets posts
are just like
so [\h__\h] spammy like there's so many
of them if you go through stories every
third story is a promotion advertisement
the Vlog I was thinking at least Twitter
doesn't do it like that
but now it's so bad
it's like
so many shitty
advertisements
I mean some of them are interesting
I blocked every promoter tweet and it's
worked well so far yeah really I thought
that if I do that they'll just like spam
me with more maybe less um interesting
ones
also it's so annoying to go for my art
tag these days because I feel like
two-thirds of my art tag these days are
unrelated posts of like spammers which
use just whatever tag is popular it
pisses me off so much
so I go less for my art tag these days
because it's like
so annoying I'm sorry
I was thinking maybe I should change my
tag
but then
it's a little bit difficult too
it's not even the one I can filter out
random mask people
I don't know are they Bots
I wonder if they're Bots
[Music]
should I change my tag do you think that
would help
I just hope it would reach the the
actual artist stuff
hopefully they're not live
continue using lots of Ashes all the
time
it was like 50 attacks or Bots yeah they
do
pissing me off so much
laughs
we can try I guess
is
that
spam
can I talk about it
two birds I swear it's two thirds now
Watson migrate I think so I don't know
so many now
[Music]
don't start with the word art oh
is that a thing
where yeah I'll think about it
I feel like the ones who use Arts of
Ashes
just like because they remember it they
don't go to my account to copy paste it
you know to remember they already know
it's Art Of Ashes so because they do a
lot of fun out they will be reached with
like if I say hey I'm changing the art
tag that means they're already if they
already do so much fun out of me then
they already like follow me properly
things it will reach them properly and
the ones who don't
to just draw something once in a blue
moon they probably have to go to my
profile to copy paste the hashtag and
then put it in their post
so I feel like in terms of like getting
them to use it it shouldn't be too
difficult
the ones who don't know me well they'll
go to my profile just copy paste
whatever is there
and the ones who do not know me well
they will find out
and then there are some lost ones every
now and then I know some of you will
just quote for tweet it to me and show
it to me that way
I can't
that comes I tried to like block or mute
them before but it's just endless
and they're using different ones every
time it's not the same ones
artificials well I would say maybe typo
[Music]
maybe let's just give it a try and see
if it improves a little bit
let me read thank you all doing I guess
you get a kiss because those were two
pinkies
thank you for two pinkies as well and
some green ones in between Chihuahua
cute
kind of dances and Doug who gets an
extra turn wow okay one more cute ah
shoot that could this bench towards
limited moveset and a cute girl is
brother no
no oh I feel like I did use the dancer
once in a parallelog when I played
privately though surprisingly
hey what's hey it wasn't bad to me
nowhere
I know we all expected it but
bench forever
[Music]
oh yeah maybe I'll do something like
that shadowlands
[Music]
cool
ah oh Alexandra
uh
[Music]
boom
I just need to confirm what I'm reading
all the time try myself first and
confirm it and see so I was just reading
a Korean a long Korean name
I saw a long Korean name in the comments
I was like I'm gonna try reading that
you are trying to read Korean ASMR
second anniversary plushies I got mine
Chihuahua with her butt out
um
I did get it
oh
I want to finish this thank you Duncan
that's really cute you're so cute thank
you
[Music]
today
it was so cute a lot of people try to do
the things that I did in Japan so cute
I'll keep you guys updated in what I do
in like places
hmm
[Music]
metal scratch Squatch thank you for the
pinky how the bus is my birthday oh and
I want to send my first Super Chat ever
to thank you my Oshi for just being you
after five years I'm going back to
school this summer partly thanks to you
being a ball of sunshine I wish I could
say but there's a Carrick
are you here
metal Swatch are you here
[Music]
I'm so proud of you I'm so happy that
that made you
okay but I'm like so proud of you you're
going back to school
congratulations
[Music]
wow I'm happy thank you for letting me
know
I'm glad I have such an impact on you
yeah and thank you ah for letting me be
your Aussie
I'm very very honored
hope your birthday was nice too and I
hope school will be good to you no don't
know what kind of school
but you know
you should do
everything in your power focus on it do
your best
make the most of it
and you will succeed
but don't forget to watch Wawa
okay at the end of the day
you
oh you donated in US dollars so maybe
going to school and watching me will be
a bit difficult but
it will go good it will I believe
you will make it go well you have to
will will it
yeah sorry for being late but
congratulations
[Music]
but not quite
oh no it is
looks different it was so translated
mysterious green Wilder thank you for a
double rainbow oh my God that's a lot of
text
all right here we go the 3D reveal was
so great what a blast that was your
burger making skills need some work
but you can leave the kitchen to those
chickens so don't worry about it too
much if the spleen of swordmanship left
me a little worried though eh
what I feel like I did some sick moves
but with that out of the way the whole
show was amazing
that's all you're saying I'm only usable
as an idol
your idle power really shown through
your singing and especially your dancing
was beautiful
I mean that was my conclusion anyway as
well but still
uh
man
wait where was I and I really hope
getting to see you do stuff like this in
pretty can happen more often it would be
too much sad if it only happened like
once per year for real for real
the myth visits was fun too and I'm
super looking forward to the full myth
for the collab and your performances
with Subaru and then it was so great the
little interlude scenes with no dialogue
were cute right
I loved every minute of the show Viva
lafridiara and more than ever before
glory to kfp yes I watched the whole
thing uh wrapped in my beautiful quinoa
birthday merch blanket oh it's very soft
and warm it is I I have it here now too
but I don't really want to use it yet
because I know that there will be a
million cat hairs on it but it's kind of
inevitable Ryan
hmm
it's the one blanket I have that doesn't
have a million cat hairs on it yet I'm
not quite ready for
that step yet
I bought a blanket too
so
I want mine too yeah where is it
who took it
[Music]
I was hanging on the wall oh yo it's so
big that you know it actually really
works well on the wall too
I saw the Korean Bros in their Airbnb
they put it on the wall
and it made for a nice backdrop
Chihuahua dominance
I'm using mine to sleep every night ah
we're cuddling every night
I sleep next to it oh like a ducky
makura
basically a tapestry yeah basically but
I mean I feel like that's kind of a
waste you should use it as a blanket
my dog keeps stealing mine that's so
cute that dogs do be like that
me and my dog sleep with it oh
even though there's cats on it
Fold It Up in case it gets cold oh
that's good
I agree with that usage
oh ninja star
that's surprising to me that it took you
until now
thank you
[Music]
oh
GPS thank you for playing Fe engage you
got me back into my free houses say from
years ago I never finished I finally
beat one route last week all
then I start a new rap on classic
maddening oh my God
yes I missed my chance to send this
while it was immediately relevant so I
decided to add on some more originally I
should have sent it ASAP after your 3DW
but now we can talk about the 3D collab
too
Silver Lining I think you did great SMC
but I'm sure no one is surprised by that
kfp at least knows exactly why
management would want you to fill that
role
I was super nervous about that
like oh I wanted to say this like during
the
um empty Parts I asked them to put up a
timer
um of remaining time until we have to
move on and I have to cut it out off but
they did sometimes but in some parts
they didn't and it really confused me
like I had no idea how I was doing of
the time that's why there was like this
one segment where I was like
should I move on should I not move on I
was unsure
that's when they just didn't have a
timer running for some reason
and yeah it made me really uncertain
yeah
and then turns out
I think
uh overall
we ended perfectly on time didn't we
pretty much perfectly
oh thank you troll they did raise the
difficulty on me I wish I wish the timer
was there all the time for my solo uh
stream the time I was there properly all
the time
all was good I felt very much in control
um
I need to see that otherwise no feeling
of time because like you have to
calculate
how much more time will be taken up by
the other stuff that's following
man
can't possibly do it just by feeling
but I think it was still okay right yeah
oh
it was just that one part at the end
where it was really unsure hmm
timer was on zero
for a while I just stopped and was like
Hey did I run out of time or but wait
isn't there more time and I said oh we
we should we should probably go now and
then I think Ahmed Alyssa was like
really and that made me doubt it like
maybe we shouldn't and then I tried to
install a little bit more but then I was
kind of like scared again because I I
was because the another problem was like
if we were talking in English most of
the time I mean generally always but the
staff
I mean Yen staff was somewhere there but
the staff who were in control of like
switching scenes and all of that were
all Japanese speaking and I don't think
they understand much English
so you know I was trying to hint that um
but
I heard nothing back in my ear monitor
because we all have ear monitor and we
could hear
um some comments uh if need be
from behind
but really that makes it a bit difficult
um
for this kind of like English streams to
be able to
hint without having to clearly switch to
Japanese and clearly say something in
Japanese
so that they understand what I'm trying
to say
oh well even then I think it went well
yeah
choose something I had in the back of my
mind throughout the whole time trying to
time everything perfectly because we
cannot go over an hour however my solo
one was what 10 minutes over
so weird
I don't know man I was following the
timers though
I was going according to my timers
we did start like one minute late
I wonder what was it
like it was already planned that we were
gonna do three rounds of that game
beforehand
[Music]
no the whole time I was following the
timers they gave me like five minute
timers and stuff ah no I know I know the
um the myth call
went kind of too long
I remember that it was like [\h__\h] they're
like we're all tangenting and we're
having fun so I don't want to like
suddenly cut it off I'm trying to get it
to a point where I can say goodbye
but it's not working
it was a bit too long it should have
been a bit shorter there
um
yeah
yeah oh yeah well Cali just to begin
with already planned more time for that
call in
it really was just like however much
time you wanted to accommodate to each
thing
oh yeah there's there's staff around
there that's what makes me even more
nervous
[Music]
man
uh
hmm
yeah
makes it more challenging yeah makes it
awkward
I have to eat and I have to shower and
then I have to sleep and I have to wake
up early and then practice Korean and
then teach her come
I have lesson at 12 30.
Korean lesson at 12 30. it'll take 90
minutes
I'll end it around the hour
[Music]
um
I'm mentally exhausted right now
my mouth is exhausted why
[Music]
only
also Smoothie has entered
nobody's looking at me
why you look so tired
oh I'm almost done how do you know this
movie thank you green welder did I
finish reading no wait I didn't oh it's
so long
uh
uh pretty collab show was a lot of fun
anytime we get the five of you together
it's great but exponentially
more so when the limiters come off like
this also not to downplay the other
girl's stats and skills but it's obvious
how much work they all put in but it's
even more obvious how much work you have
put in when I see you all dancing
together I thought you kind of stole the
show can't be biased I have a few
characters left in the double rainbow so
I should say also I love you you're the
best man Aussie thank you I love you too
[Music]
thank you soon I appreciate it thank you
so much I already went to a couple of
tangents during your
Super Chat so I'm gonna leave it at that
but I'll give you a kissy
thank you very very much
for the big support and the big rainbow
very pretty
let me try to finish these boohoo 723
this is from 2023
yeah oh this guy this is what you guys
make fun of me
I love watching you play this game thank
you so why not cozy even my cats are
into it thank you
I see you right after you
you know there's some more jokes about
them
well I'm reading it in 2020 free
only 20 20 free
oh membership
anyway second time thank you
I'm glad your cats like it I like your
cats please show me pictures more more
and more
yes
[Music]
hopefully that will be a new Tales game
in 2025
oh thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky hi attention
scrolling is in Japan any fun stories
you can share I think by now I did
Jeff are you here did you hear the
stories hmm
Jessie
Jessie Jeff
I tried to share my stories about crony
the one with the joke the one with the
phone the one that she's you know has a
cute smile
yeah
unfortunately it was only one day you
know so I don't have endless
um stories that's pretty much it I think
oh yeah the one where we talked
endlessly about fire emblem in the
waiting line
hmm
yeah feeding her like a bird with the
turkey leg
stuff like that I think that's plenty
guys
that's plenty
hmm
well
the one where she knew what all the food
was and I didn't
[Music]
fashionable and you know I asked before
I was nervous I was like
what granny look like what I do I'm
nervous I asked the other girls to be
mentally prepared they told me she was
very fashionable
I guess she was
that she probably was
hmm just I hope that's enough for you
soon hope you had fun in Tokyo even
though it was from your hotel room
[Music]
I wonder if you also
hung out of kfp
anyone hung out with IO
because IO says I went to Tokyo but
didn't get a ticket
um
I hope I wasn't all alone
IO from I think Poland
[Music]
I
am
I'll not only hung out with oil
[Music]
nobody knows
are you I hope you had fun now I'm
worried because you know there were so
many cave people maybe maybe
Ayo wasn't that that um before the
festival the day before the festival in
that kfp of collab of corrupt of Kai
[Music]
you girls that kfp at New York City and
why the [\h__\h] did you do that you said it
you got a potato I love seeing
everything titty
[Music]
um
this is for Gemma buy her something or
some good food for being such a great
manager
our Channel
you know this time we parted ways on the
airport
the same
Airport
same like gate
as that one time when I
um
left after the one year
and back then we both cried General
cried more than me
but now this time we were like this time
we don't have to cry
actually no the first time I left you
know was the two weeks break in between
we don't have to cry because next time
I'll see you next time very soon
and then I came back and then I left
again and then that time too we were at
least not crying I was a little bit sad
though
because I don't know
when I'll be back again hopefully in
June to record birthday concert hi
Raiders
it could be a lie but if you think about
it June sounds like so far away but it's
already it's already the end of March
the third month of the year and June is
the sixth month of the year
so it's really not that long to go
it's always good we good
June will be there before we know it
no almost Christmas
true true
which means my birthday is coming soon
too oh no
Phoenix become older again
[Music]
foreign
tickets yeah
I'm sorry guys I don't know
I feel like Lottery both systems
are
[Music]
merciless
Lottery and first come first serve first
come first serve if your internet or
something
[\h__\h] up then you [\h__\h] but you know so
I've never tried something like this
I've never been in like such a bloodbath
first come first serve ticket situation
where the service crashed and all that
but
from what I hear with it doesn't work
well you just
continuously refresh refresh refresh
refresh eventually get in
even if it looks like nothing's
happening oh yeah you see I I don't know
Ticketmaster
but I I saw your concerns guys
and I was like eh
is it really that bad and I looked up
and I thought you know there's some
problems with Ticketmaster so I asked
staff
that the only way we're gonna be selling
tickets
and can we like do anything about it
I think the conclusion was
basically
well I think it's also connected to the
venue that you choose
and you can't really help it
right so much right guys
I said I don't want
you know
sculpting and all that botting and all
that to be a thing
hey
[Music]
well
I hope it will go well
just try to overpower the scalpers guys
in numbers
what this did I skip it already in the
[\h__\h] one oh let's see
falc I'm sorry happy
belated third birthday
congratulations thanks for letting me
know I missed it because I wasn't
too obvious right away thank you for
being here on another birthday
[Music]
I love you too
hope it was a decent birthday
um
on to the next one
where was I oh yeah thank you
um
thank you for the rest of the chat do
you know how to pronounce the name of
the final bleach antagonist his name is
supposed to be the German pronunciation
of the Hebrew God transliterated into
Japanese and the anime pronounces it as
yuha Baja
but I'm not sure how accurate that is
why is it why did you not just write it
down
why do you tell me how it was pronounced
but not how it's actually written
well the first part doesn't sound German
to me
yeah I mean I can see how in Japanese
they go to that pronunciation
because yeah they can't end a word on it
has to be ha
their syllables
oh
no idea
um but it's probably pronounced like
that
[Music]
he wanted to know that so desperately
from me Alexander babsky to send a
recipe chat I hope it helped
thank you for the support hope you're
enjoying bleach
final antagonist is it are they
finishing it
what
huh
is
foreign
[Music]
I want to watch your stream but I don't
want to be spoiled it's torture watch
spoiling don't watch on the menu yeah
[Music]
well you have time to check again I hope
you did because on the weekend we're
playing Fire Emblem
[Music]
sweetheart
yes yes
I gave you so much time
thank you for the pinky
well you get it right you understand
perfectly if you don't watch you will be
on the menu yeah
thank you
for the pinky progress today maybe
Veronica next time earlier someone
mentioned a Mario movie watch along once
it hits digital but you know there is
that live action movie
mm-hmm
don't forget the app potential to have I
didn't forget the Apple looking forward
to the aqua Labs there's a Mario live
action movie no no oh oh well people
don't have good memories of it so
I will stay away from that
[Music]
seems to be more of a meme
I didn't I didn't I don't think I knew
maybe you guys told me before but I just
ignore its existence
it's not worth knowing
[Laughter]
oh I didn't forget the Apple though
can you watch cats yeah so what cats
probably better
I'm tired now I'm gonna go now guys
[Music]
but thank you guys
for being with me today again
tomorrow members
[Music]
um
can I decide when I wake up
because I know we're in between watching
more Star Wars movies but
oh no we already did so many watch looks
previously with Lord of the Rings
I should probably do something else
might just do something else I don't
know I'll decide tomorrow
[Music]
okie dokie maybe game Maybe karaoke I
don't know
I gotta go to Smoothie now she's meowing
desperately
thank you guys for watching
um
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]