e
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
Ohio hello everyone good morning
sorry I think I think I think she f i
was a
snack
oh I just woke
up oh my God those n Reco stream are
really in my morning routine
huh yeah did you s well I actually s
very well
um yesterday uh I think I remember I was
watching
um I was
watching uh House of the
dragon and I fall asleep
so I don't actually remember what I
stopped I I think at some point I fall
asleep like suddenly it it be like very
suddenly I I
slapped I was like oh well
well interesting and
then good morning
tatini m is here I was like very excited
to to stream today
and
um yeah also I have a collab tonight as
well 7 PM
GD um with Kaa
Senpai and others you're going to check
more details on Twitter I'll post my uh
I think my POV as well so don't worry
about it I I'll give you more details
[Music]
later yeah is it gonna uh no it's gonna
be at Kaa server I think K's um because
I couldn't join the Kyla's birthday
party I decided to join today as
well yeah I'll post more details on
YouTube as well but like yeah just keep
it in mind uh it was like organized
pretty much last minute so I I just I
didn't know either that's why I didn't
included in my schedule as well let me
drink some water I'm so eepy
I haven't got any
breakfast any ah but this because like I
was not hungry so I'll wait until later
to get some
break how you doing how you how you how
much you doing
today did you guys still got a good
sleep if you if you just laugh or you
maybe a they just
started how is your day so
far tell me tell me oh yeah I got my
espresso if I didn't go my espresso I
couldn't
even um
talk you e it it's hard everyone is
hey maybe we should do like a nap stream
at some point where we just take a
nap
yeah yeah
good
morning you know as a queen of liin and
ever
grain in my you this those weeks has
been very very very busy been very busy
days right
here
so today though is a special day
because because
something is about to
happen and you'll see we should see
together
um
yeah no spoilers I
guess I am on the throne already the
throne is already
mine what are you talking about
yeah applaud to
indeed
yeah but we'll see together let me just
put myself here so you guys get to see
the
game mm I'm a big G but
sometime I need to make it
smaller there we
go I'm going to miss this
Village when he's
gone I'm going to miss the whole thing
when he's
gone oh I see something new
here
hello you
Che H she made a March
that is so
cute it's
911 that is so cute look at
that very
pretty very
pretty I really like
that she did such a good job
let's see what people build
around so this is this is pH
smart oh this is a very cool house what
is that the skirted one
Library brought to you by
phone I hear someone where is
she how can I
oh my my headphones are reversed again
huh hello
there how have you been hello night
cilia I'm doing good how you doing one
second please talk more hello hello D
this is the queen Mario the king of two
right now I'm little EP and just woke
up and a good morning good morning
morning good morning okay I think it's
okay how you doing what are you up to
sleep she SS so Mario I have a question
go for
it h do you know what happened to uh the
princess your daughter
no cuz I talked to her earlier at least
I tried talking to her and then she just
like did like this really weird
encrypted stuff and bed out of existence
and she didn't answer to me H I don't
know I don't recall what happened
like I the last time I saw the princess
recall recollect what happened the last
time I saw the princess she was just
fine when was that like about
yesterday yesterday yeah okay I wish we
had a detective who could help us figure
out this case but I did notice something
a little awkward today
oh really yeah like come here I just I
just I just logged in but so with you
know logged in what are what what what
are you I mean I mean I mean woke up
woke up woke up you know just woke up
yeah yeah yeah uh look this is a little
odd isn't it oh that is odd I saw it
earlier but it didn't register in my
brain yeah like seems like it's crying
red what the heck is that oh look the
queen oh wow the Queen's so
pretty the other Queen the other Queen
Don't Worry Mario don't I will
never defect
you well maybe if we find her again we
can talk to her about it and ask her
what's up maybe maybe someone else has
information that was U not sleeping
yesterday compared to me what is this
this what is this about also let me
check it out huh
I wonder if this has something to
do H that is very OD in
need I wonder what happened that's very
suspicious Mario can you open the door I
can't oh
sure oh no this
door no I cannot open this door why not
cuz that's
not I'm not part of of this build is
there anyone
uh let's
see seems like you can remember who's
who's in this one again the
princess I made it how did you do it I
know just backed
it I guess can you open it from
the God you scared me I I guess it's a
combination of
using the horse and you're a lock picker
very
impressive you can do it oh you made
it
well you made it good
job okay let's see these houses people's
houses oh a double bed how
romantic yeah jump on
it I didn't I didn't take off my shoes
e that's not very uh that's not a beavor
of
night how how would you go I mean yes it
is oh I made it I like that we just used
the horse now jump jump jump jump jump
jump well how to get out now I guess we
don't oo oh a
picture
heart as you can tell from this
wonderful piece
uhhuh the author the
artist had a huge dilemma at this time
Darkness fulfilled their right side left
side but the other one was filled with
colors green red complimentary as we
know this talks this speaks to the inner
conflict and inner turmo of the artist
at the creation of this piece yeah I
think see the little flame in the right
corner what do you what do you think
that one means Mario what do you think
what do you think I think it means that
the word is
ending the world is ending because of a
small fire I flying and I think you are
right that I mean I mean the the small
fire becomes big fire in the future
smallest spark can create destrction and
take the world that's what I think
too what do you think about my art tour
I think it's very nice and uh you should
do that in an alternative Universe you
should be an art critique critique art
critique yeah CRI an art art is PR yeah
okay the tour costs 200 gold coins
what you want to charge the
queen you want to support my desire to
become an art
critique
yes fine
is my duty as a queen to
support thank you mqueen you're welcome
you for supporting your local artist
gallery of course supporting education I
like artists after all so I got to
support them are you an artist no I said
that I like artist oh you like art no I
could never like throw I'm not really
capable of doing such things oh oh man
like oh another AR piece oh good for it
you're not going to charge me this time
I already supported no you already Tri
it okay as we can see on this AR piece
by
artist g g there's a blue character on
one side and a white character on the
other they are in a stance in a battle
you could say it seems like they're
fighting actually
however if you really think about it
this is the the depiction of a mirror
match oh known as subconsciously copying
the person in front of you because you
are attracted to them so we can clearly
tell from this art piece that these two
are lovers or at least the white one is
in love with the blue one uh but they're
also enemies so you could call it
enemies to lovers and that's what this
piece is called H this is very very
suspicious why maybe the queen was like
the second Queen
was thinking about something when she
got this
artfish oh do you think she's the blue
one what who's the white one then I
don't know like huh who's white
like think about it okay I'm thinking
about it
maybe this is the conflict between me
and her
and I got it now she's in love with
me you telling me T B is in love with
you how how I didn't know this
before oh wait wait wait wait wait think
about it it makes sense wait think about
it
yeah whenever you talked to her you feel
some type of
tension actually yeah when when you
talked to her did you feel like she
would keep talking to you yeah yeah yeah
whenever you talk to her did you feel
like she was like teasing you some call
it neing that she was like making fun of
you in a playful
way yeah
maybe maybe she just
wants to to to leave the king and get a
real queen with
her she loves
you she should I should I propose to
her sorry should I propose to her yeah
yeah you should you should you know what
I support you Queen you know what I
shall prepare I think you could make it
maybe you should get her a present maybe
you should ask her what she would like
as a present and then you should give it
to her and you know what I'll I'll
prepare something right away thank you
not Cecilia artist critic for your
support you finally got my memory back
yeah I'm also wait I'm also a love
advisor ask ask me for advice oh okay
listen so you
know today I shall propose and so I
should prepare something maybe here's
what I'm going to
do I'm going to build
something oh and write her
letter is that's a good idea and then
I'm going to send my pigeon to the sky
because the queen right now is not here
she's on a
vacation you should also give her some
flowers in the color of her and you some
flowers blue and pink get her some
flowers that's my
advice okay I think it'll work well
thank you then um do you maybe want
to maybe you want
to what
you may
want what do you may me wan
to give me a tip for my services as
advisor
what um
well you expensive
night just like just a small tip just a
small tip of 100 coins
50 65 6
okay there you go oh thank you very much
my queen I wish you the best of love and
best of luck can you gather some flowers
for
me oh yeah I have some I'll give you
some thank you see
you
[Laughter]
oh what are you guys doing in our base
um oh we were looking at the art I was
do yeah we were looking at the
art oh I see over here this one is
called allowed in yeah yeah we opened
the door this one is called enemies to
LS what do you think how does it make
you feel how does it make you feel what
do you think when you look at this just
can't believe you guys are inside of
[Laughter]
our Jonathan don't you remember that I'm
a honorary member of the blue seruan
Guild and I literally own every land
so that true you have why are you so
against me doing
here towards the queen who is our Queen
Tam gamber
what that's not even her name I will
excuse
me I do actually not remember the name
excuse me can can you explain now what
happened I want my money back Jonathan
what's her name again I want your I want
my money back G you feel you are the
queen of Evergreen we've talked about
this no the bestan is
Evergreen
yes I want my money back and I uh you're
not my KN anymore you really got to go a
CL is calling excuse me oh no excuse me
oh man excuse
me explain explain
explain can't believe everyone betraying
me I would have like loved to build
something if I was like
gone
hello wa it's me I'm stuck in this
place oh yeah oh oh my god oh don't
don't hurt your horse it's okay I'll die
oh no there you go I'm I'm I'm
alive where are
you here there we go hello what a
wonderful day uh my Amber coin mate
hello how you
doing uh I am fine thank you how are you
feeling today I'm e beard
Z same
same same well what are your plans for
this lovely
day I think I got to build
something oh maybe thing no it's just
more thing this time we'll see what you
like to build something as well I heard
you wanted to oh you heard me say that
yeah you're outside here ah it's okay
like I think
today uh since today is my last day um
I'm going to just try to clean up my my
blood lights
oh I see yeah yeah yeah well good luck
then thank you you can do it if you need
if you need anything while I'm free I
can help I can assist a thank you I hear
Hello fiery
one wait I have an E I have an echoey
voice her name is Shakira and I don't
trust you anymore get out of here I
brought you the flowers get out I don't
want your flowers brought you the
flowers well I'm going to destroy your
bed anyway you're not part of the
Kingdom
anymore but
why just betrayed me like that no okay
come come come here come here Qui I
don't trust you I'm
sorry wait Mario Mario it's Queen Mario
Don't You Queen Mario don't you remember
our PL that we're going to put Prin
beu on the on the throne and then you'll
be you'll be leading and you'll be the
queen of the kingdom it doesn't make
sense I already the queen just because I
believe you're the queen doesn't mean
everyone else believes you're the queen
we have to make them understand but it's
been hard and they don't they don't
believe us so we have to force them I
thought I had at least one friend here I
have no one I'm so alone it's okay I can
do
myself do you fire me is this what's
happening here even though I support you
you don't support me your you just just
betray in front of
everyone no it's I'm I'm lying it's a
plot Mario it's a plot I'm lying to them
Mario I'm it's a
plot what is a PL
wait see remember all the fun we had
like just now when we were laughing
remember the artist art that we did uh
what's a plot a plot is like a
scheme wellow okay then it's it's up to
I'm just very sad right now I cannot
think okay well if you must destroy my
bed and fire me I understand Queen Mario
I will never forget you thank you you
will forget me
no h
well oh I got my
flowers well you know what I don't need
anyone in this
project it's
okay going to buy some materials
now F I'll do myself exactly
do you do you hold
you your M when laughing watching the
screen move up and down with your like
this yeah I mean I mean of course like
when you when you laugh you just don't
use your mouth
anymore yeah I
mean I do
I heard the B
[Music]
B I'm going to get more
materials there you go got a lot of
instruction
[Music]
boxes I shall start my
preparation so
chatini so have us your lawyer chatini
a thank
you that makes me happy
thank
you it's fine I'm going to marry the
Queen the fake queen and we're going to
restore our your lawyer
our our
yes so here's my
idea my idea is I'm going to to
build something on the
air
right and it's going to be
like would you marry me and then I take
a
picture and then I send a
picture with my
pigeon to
her
today and see if she
replies how about
that does it sounds
good
okay I'm going to
one second I want to check how can I do
[Music]
that I'm looking for
it
[Music]
h so in English you should say will you
marry
me
correct
so will you marry me
how do I do
that I wonder how can
I if there's like a way to
generate the
Tex will you will marry me
I want to do like pixel art this is how
we get everyone on our side we married a
fake queen genius idea I
mean I mean
yeah that's how it
is make
brain I think so
I don't know how to make it happen
though I
think I want to make like
sure I want to build
[Music]
something hello hello hello good job
you're so pretty so many customers so
many customers are going to be
rich money so you're not getting
anything from me what that is okay you
have free
will what is this this is Nana
11 11 yes the sister store TOA Mar but
they are not related
oh person
related we offer the finest highest
Quality Meats as well as the juiciest of
berries we also have can have six
berries please you can have six berries
six berries six
berries oh what has happened this is
very inappropriate I'm so sorry oh I
don't know if a horse should be close to
food like that they did not mean to pull
the horse do not worry the food is all
protected inside of these barrels where
nothing can contaminate them
freebies freebies yes we do offer
freebies huh I never got free from faart
in fact nothing here costs any money
everything is
free what are you sure yes that is very
comeni I like it yes it is here let me
let me give your
berries and then I can assist you with
your
berries
two I don't know it's
free it's free I free for
free I got some
B oh she's invisible you want a free
Berry I would love a free Berry oh you
would like a free Berry yes that ghost
there is a qu there is a
que I want the b bs do you want ghost
she's a ghost what happened to her I
love freebies for you are you a ghost
yes I've been killed oh my God I
remember the the voice is this
is wait you died yes I was killed by
Shakira what Shakira Shak yes in the
last in the last not my stream but her
stream she killed
me she killed you ghost I mean yesterday
yesterday she killed me and she killed
my child sorry there was a ghost
whispering in my ear what is it that you
said this is so this is so sad that
makes me cry do you want to do you are
you happy as a ghost are you having a
good time I would like to be revived we
should revive her howan with a G was
going to perform a ritual to help revive
me so I was on my way to see if I could
find
gathan well gathan is over there he's
he's over there all right then we shall
go who killed you away Shakira Shakira
who is right there with
Jonathan I have fear
okay it's okay hide behind
us it seems there are people there's
people on their way
hello
hello that we have brought someone with
us
[Music]
terrifying such a beautiful voice though
you killed me Shakira and for that you
must pay why
hey do not hurt her back ghost back
gathan she has killed me and my child
what oh is that you lady narissa Raven
coft yes you looks so much her voice
does sound familiar yes it is very
familiar you're so
transparent well I have an idea yes
isn't there what is your
idea in lady Shakira's
memories in her dungeon is there not a
way for you to be
revived I am
unsure is there a way I am a phoenix
indeed
and if you are truly not a witch I may
be able to give you one of my Phoenix
feathers to revive you you and never and
never turn in but didn't you kill her no
she did kill me but if she wants to make
this right I will accept it makes sense
the phoen flim have chosen her as a
Target but I personally from my heart
and my soul want to offer her Phoenix
Feather to revive her once again how
Grand Phenix feathers must be very
valuable yes they are all
right I must however uh go pick one out
of my hair first so okay oh she must she
must her plumage fly
then I shall uh in I will try my best it
takes a little moment because it is very
painful to pick it out of my
hair you have have a 30 do that
sacrifice it might take uh a few minutes
longer I will I will hurry I will hurry
away can you stay those for a few more
minutes yeah yes is it painful prep the
ritual think so I I have I have been
reading some books and scriptures from
the the larger Library we will I will
see it right that you do not have to
look like this any longer thank you
Jonathan it pains me to see you this way
I don't see her what are you're talking
about my goodness I have found something
though quite troubling that I thought I
must report yeah it has to do with the
King and Le Estelle as a whole
what I have realized today as I have
been a ghost I have decided that I
should use it to uh investigate Lee
bestelle and as I have been
investigating I have found that a lot of
buildings are completely empty I have
returned
empty back already are you ready to
receive the Phoenix's blessing yeah in
about uh 40 seconds uh you can start
doing it now but make it take that long
okay can you come here yes yes my name
is
Jonathan Jonathan do do have don't
follow us she wants to speak to me
privately yes priv need a moment I kind
of like you like
this what do you mean like that she's
beautiful she deserves a body back I may
I may have
one
I you know like the mystery
wa maybe I should kill you so you can
become like that as well
hm maybe but why would you murder me I
thought we were you you betrayed me in I
never betrayed you it's a
misunderstanding my queen hand you over
my Phoenix Feather so that you may use
it in the right timing when you really
hello Jonathan hi
Gorden I need to still uh
put my Phoenix powers on
it I very excited to see
this me me as well I'm quite I'm quite
curious yeah well you must accept the
trade
request wonderful here is the blue and
turquoise colored Phoenix FEA that will
give you another chance in life this
this is a chicken feather is a blue and
turquoise colored Phoenix
oh Pho yeah it is sparkling and blue and
colored Phoenix Feather very shiny
except this gas lighting look it is
white what no it's blue and turquoise
it's going to work Jonathan I think the
eyes of a ghost cannot properly perceive
the phoenix feather is it because she
sees the world in a monochrome way I
shall use Poss go for it Phoenix
power what is this it takes a few
seconds it takes a few seconds
sometimes you are slowly regaining your
life energy I can see something
already maybe it's not working is it not
working you know what that is a phoenix
fow does not so easily revive a person
it takes a few seconds have patience for
Life hello everybody what is going on
what is the conversation topic we are
trying to give her body back and doesn't
work you save the ghost you not quite
ready for Revival in yes I wanted this
as well think we need to perform our
whole ret so that I could use her to my
advantage shall return what your
advantage what is it that must be done
to save her why did you say like that
loser says why where did the ghost go I
am not
sure loser said what loser said
what know what her is
now Jonathan I need your I need I need
to talk to you yes what what you need to
speak to me about you got to
come can you open the door please I need
to show you
something can't you just lockpick your
way in like you did oh you are back
she's back it did not work I think we
will need to perform the ritual the
ritual
is a long and grueling one are you sure
you are ready to go through such trials
and tribulations it is painful indeed
yes it is actually a very very long and
complicated ritual in order to get your
life and body and soul back into one I
will do anything your body is currently
being held inside the depths of of a of
a prison of the sewer system of the
sewer system we must get your body once
we have found your body we must bring
your soul which is you right now and
your body to the Temple of the Kings and
you must get the last hit on the statue
in order to combine your body and
soul oh all right yes all right yeah
yes but you must you must get you must
get Shakira's blessing because it is
through her blessing that she allows you
to use such resurrection and Revival she
the one who killed me
I sure sure that you can get it I'm sure
you can receive her blessing it seems
she wanted to try but
mayhaps if you receive her blessing and
get the last hit on on the the statue
you will become whole
again I see I see a very complicated
process this is the best you could come
up with very long and
arduous trials and tribulations but I
believe in thee I will come with you on
your quest that so nice where the go
through
together
H well why don't you get my body and
then we can go and do yes you know I
will seek your body I will find it seek
my body bring it back I find your body
call me once you have found my body yes
yes I will yes I you can ride
horses of course do you do that don't
worry about it call me once you have
found my body thank you yes I will call
you once I found your body to what to
what um conclusion have you
come sorry I was just so taken aback by
her horse riding skills we need to take
her body back and then you got to give
her a blessing so she can merge the soul
and body together in a ritual that
Jonathan J will perform yes you you must
give her your blessing and and heart and
and then we will go to your your temple
and she will get the last hit on the
Statue and then her body and soul will
combine and she'll be one again yeah I
suppose that is indeed how it's done I
just forgot about it so yes the long the
long ritual yes the long ritual yeah it
is necessary for the
impatient uh Souls out there yes all
right I shall assist you in regaining
her body mhm
we I will find her body it must be in
the sewer system somewhere oh I will
find it we'll find system yes we will
find it yeah brought her body in the
sewers it seems as if someone has
brought her body down there to rot in
the cave but we will find it it is no
matter that's why there was a smell such
a bad smell in the SE last time the bad
smell is because yes God
disres very disrespectful I cannot
believe this h and then you may come
along with us because it is your temple
and you know the ways and then we will
watch her as she fights against the
final statue and okay her body will
become one yes oh oh yes yes that sounds
like a
plan shall we shall we proceed oh but
did you want to tell me something yeah I
have something to do first excuse me
excuse us Shakira I I I need a moment oh
can you open the door you you not just
going to lockpick your way in like you
did earlier you can just gently open the
door for me I just I just feel as if you
have lockpick your way in earlier no no
no it was already open I
see thank you come with me so I was
talking to a certain Cecilia night uh
today and we were admiring the beautiful
art pieces in your
uh house and at some point we saw this
and we were like wait a second this
actually remind me something and then I
connected I started to connect the dots
and I finally realized that probably the
the second
Queen was in love with me all along the
second Queen and so I
decided to propose her I want to marry
you are going to propose to Queen Tam
Gander yes but
first I be I'll be
honest I need your approval and your my
why do you need my approval because I
cannot do this without your support I
realize how loyal you are to Tam Gander
and
so before that I need your
blessing before I
shall propose to the queen Tam
Gander myself and send a p I will send a
p a pijun my proposal I'll prepare it
and I see yeah but I cannot do that
without your oh oh my gosh she's
back are you good news your body the
phoenix feather has revived some of my
life force I'm it
worked you are no oh I can pass through
you you are a ghost
you are so cold when I passed through
you yes but I was hearing you uh dear
Queen Mario and I will support you you
your efforts are to marry Queen Tam
Gander correct thank you yes that's
that's my ultimate goal today let me
continue telling you of what I have
found yes uh uh gathan and and queen
Mario as I went into the castle I
believe that the king is a farce I have
come to the conclusion that stains are
liest who actually decided to defect you
know who has
magic yeah the king who summoned us here
to leave Estelle in the first place
correct goodness I have found out that
the King has transformed all of the past
liest who uh rebelled against him in to
stains themselves why there is a stained
King it was the person who was trying to
overthrow and usurp his throne because
he was not kind he has summoned us and
locked all the currently bestin here so
they may not see the treachery that has
been performed on their fellow uh towns
people you see my goodness he has wiped
their memories as they have wiped ours
he is not
Jonathan you heard that add up my
goodness it adds up it really
does so that's that's that that's what
it was going on along I never trust the
king I told you I never liked him me
neither something is always felt off we
have to save Queen Tam Gander and the
only way to do that is to have her marry
Queen Mario only the two of them
together can take down the king as he is
now indeed
so Jonathan I know you are a loyal
Knight but will we have your support in
this endeavor will you give me your
blessing
did you see that
no you did not see that
huh you not see that it was the
princess huh the princess is it the
princess here she was just there she was
just maybe it's a ghost it must have
been a trick of the light yes
mayhaps uh I must report one more
finding to you both yes yes in in the
castle I have found two Bewitched liest
who were unable to speak in complete
sentences but together they had one
coherent message which was land of faded
Destiny echoed or and or again break the
chains and it will flee Back to Where it
All
Began you see this very troubling this
is very
troubling it is I do not know the
problem with this entire situation is
that they will not get married in
time we can I Believe in Us even if they
have to get married after the king is
overthrown I think we can see success we
can just send a pigeon and the queen
will send a pigeon back with her
response you need to go through a
ceremony for the marriage no worries
like we can Witnesses yeah we have the
witness we don't need a an actual we can
we can do the marriage another time this
is an emergency situation
an emergency situ an emergency I should
send my Pon as soon as possible so
Jonathan G would you give me your
blessing for this duty of mine I do not
believe that my word holds such wait but
you may send a pigeon and it is up to
the queen to respond thank you a loyal
night you are Jonathan thank you
Jonathan you're very loyal to the queen
yes so is send your carrier pigeon Queen
Mario we must make haste on this matter
I will do right now and Jonathan J I
always liked you even though you hidden
me for a long while I always thought you
were very um I see her what oh oh my God
she's doing let me go out was not a of
the light it is her what is the princess
doing what what's my Dy
doing what is my daddy doing open the
door
where did she
go Princess Princess where are
you where did the princess
go what is she do you see her I do not
see her any longer is she hiding in the
moai
Statue
princess what is happening to
her my goodness
look
this what is
happening
Princess where is my daughter I miss
her she is
gone I shall eat something
well I should start my message right
away
need uh I'll be right back uh I'm going
to uh iidle uh Queen meeting I need a I
need a meeting with the queen with the
um um uh older uh the best still of
Kingdom uh citizen I I am going to um um
yeah I I I shall be her back
[Music]
I'm so back hello
tatini welcome back and enjoy your
cucumbers I
guess okay
I am
ready I should start right away there is
no time to
lose I need to send my
pigeon I will send the
pigon as soon as
possible how can I build up in the air
do I just use the dirt
or I'm going to make a shovel
now can you use scaff
holding but in that casid I
[Music]
will got to be pretty high though
I'll do
here in this space since Cass and Pie
will not build anything El she'll take
her
spot pardon
me hello hello I've just opened my new
establishment I saw 11 it was so pretty
but I heard you doing it for free
yes everything is free why do make sense
because we are in competition with fart
and we need the prices to encourage
people to come to our establishment
that's right ours it's
[Laughter]
ambercoin well you know what I think
you're right is there something I can
assist you with you know what you should
do oh what should we do I have got an
idea to be very
competitive oh
what what follow me oh
okay oh my goodness what could it
be I give you in a second one moment
okay okay I'm very patient I learned to
I wonder what this is supposed to
be what's this what oh yeah I think it's
just like ingame building I I think
really yeah
this is static I
think oh I see it's outside the line
yeah I lost my stff by the way I don't
find them
anymore I had something I want to give
you well I lost all my
diamonds that might have been me no I
have no it's not even me I have diamonds
I will give you some hold on no no no no
no no no I wanted to give it to you one
second I have
I I have a you
have I will give them to you no no no no
I don't want it this is what it is you
have diamonds now hear me hear me out
this is my plan oh okay what's the plan
you sell diamond
for one coin each and that's how you get
very competitive in the market oh my
gosh that's so smart I only had food and
lottery tickets available offering D
take the diamonds back please I will
take them back take back that is genius
you I you are a genius you I
know all right oh can you please go and
let the folk know that we are now
offering diamonds aren't the juiciest of
berries and the highest quality of meats
as well as a lottery ticket can you can
you yeah people know okay wonderful I
would let I let everybody know would you
you like a lottery ticket it is
completely free and the first 20 people
who take one win yeah I won it okay I
will hand it over to you second hold on
a second just a second that is a very
good deal actually it is is it
not here is your ticket
oops on the down
though it is it is not it is within a
realm of uh a real full of Discord yeah
got it got it thank you ni you're
welcome thank you do I have to give you
any number or anything nope I'm just
keeping track of who the first 20 really
are can't to tell you now I can reveal
it to you within an hour but I'm going
to win if I win you will win 100 coins
that's actually
good isn't it
it's great grand thank you so much I
think you're very competitive right now
I am I'm so competitive good luck
selling your diamonds thank you I will
win I will win you will win of course
I'll be there because I have a plan I
need to marry the other Queen so I'm
going to prepare a message for her right
now so I'll be around for a bit okay you
should you should ride it under a tree
yeah I think I'm going to do like right
there yeah that'll be romantic that' be
romantic I think I'm going to do this
side so she will like have it in the
background her
statue Mak sense I'm going to do
now should I use the colors pink and
blue together
that sounds
good I have no idea how to R Minecraft
does anybody
knows does anybody knows wait where is
my white wool I thought I had
it oh there you go
no actually right like do you know
there's a website where I can like refer
to not website sorry uh a manuscript on
the lbrary that I can refer to
um as a
guide or I think I'm just going to do
it how what's the maximum high I can get
okay that's I think the
max it's actually
not well I'll start from here
H I need the Seas
now let's
see I do have
that's okay I I'll put on an alarm um
would you like to oh yes I was going to
let you know since
you I think I need to do some pixel art
over
[Music]
there
H what doesn't make me build weird
uh I don't know how to make
it game gamer geek pixel
art okay you know
what if I check on my book
right on my book
okay I found it thank you uh Tini very
very
helpful thank you so
much this is indeed very helpful okay
let's do
it so it's one two three
four
oh this is going to
work can I not put this scff holding
over there
right I can't
[Music]
isn't it a little too high though now no
maybe not it's going to
work no
worries um will
going to
cut
yeah and then it's four blocks here one
two three
four
yeah I made a
letter let's go
[Music]
and
then
here
oh look at that
low
expanding I'm going to work hard for
this welcome hello
everyone well
oh too
long I wonder what Tam Gander will think
about
it okay we got we got
will we got a will
and then one two three four five
okay one two three four five and
then
this
okay will
mhm
yeah what do you mean wrong
way what do you mean the wrong way it's
perfect because like later I'm going to
do a screenshot like
that like look like that that's my plan
I'll make a screenshot like that that
and I'll send the pigeon
[Music]
to
um to to the second Queen that's the
pan let me cook why you never trust
me let me
cook no worry
there I'm going to use this to
differentiate
[Music]
okay oh there you
go I think I need more blocks soon
I know you have a single brain cell I
noticed you have one one Collective
brain cell but that's okay
cute it
works oh even from here actually is very
visible I love it
will
mhm
oops
Yeah is it turn with brain cell please
do not
fight oops
I need more
blocks no
way better I go buy
them let's
go CH stop
fighting
okay
oops I need more po salid soon
maybe I should tell M to make more
potato salads is she around her monent
Hi join our party call oh okay
sorry that was very
serious doesn't make me I am
not wait they were talking to
me a pleasure to see you today I'm sorry
I'm not I'm not in the party can you
invite Meed narissa ravencraft how do I
make a
shield a shield seems you may need some
iron and and some uh I will make one for
you guys no
problem see if I have any I have iron I
have iron too you have some iron I'm
here
now welcome my cat yeah welcome my cat
gathan you are quite the kind
Knight Jonathan with a G yes it is
Jonathan I will go get it I will go get
it
[Music]
cute so did you did you get your body
back she did oh my god really Saed my
body and her soul I'm no longer dead
let's
go yes I am alive again but now we must
search for princess beu cuz we are quite
worried about her my daughter what did
oh here you go I will trade
you take this Shield yes would you take
care of my daughter in my absence
problem fluffy one oh thank you I will
return in the party call but I have to
leave for now
[Music]
oops
meow
ouch will you up to
Shakira
I am awaiting our next
actions that
is it is looking for the
princess we are in a come to the gardens
princess is destroying it
hello what what is going on oh prin to
the gardens to the gardens the gardens
we must stop her which Gardens the
gardens right by the build area you guys
passed it see look I do not think
the stop it
princess I not starvation will come upon
us
princess do you remember
me
Princess
control oh um I must I know that
interesting but I must we need to talk
about
this princess B
Revelation I don't think it's going to
work not use my Revelation on I I don't
want to use my Revelation to the
princess I can't believe the person
princess talk about this please don't
you remember your
mom princess princess stop we will all
die do you want us all to die when we
have no food station will come
if we don't stop her no no that is our
last rations
rations I don't know to say the word
princess stop no no
I wait someone has to do
something I I don't know how to stop her
she is Unstoppable I don't know how to
stop
her stop stop
princess
princess princess maybe she just need a
hug come
here
no made the land
starve no no no no that is so
evil we cannot let this happen replant
replant don't just replant the seeds
make sure you replant the actual carrots
and potatoes too yeah
oh oh yes I
shall the think has happened would have
known that we were
get what happened to my lovely daughter
I don't
know destroying the
kingdom I can't believe
it it seems like we have uh become
is I got to fix
it it is my new occupation but for the
lands I shall do it all for the queen
yes for the queen I'm going to start
with potatoes
now maybe in this
area as as as an avid farmer myself it's
quite nice when the area is completely
filled with one thing for a
while is that in my sense or no no no
I'm just explaining what I'm doing so if
you see me tearing stuff up you don't
get
confused what happened to the
princess I wonder I'm quite
distressed how could your daughter do
such a thing Queen Mario I don't know I
just don't know what happened to maybe
you raised her wrongly no that's not how
it works
no I I'll make this back area beats back
here can be the beat
area
well I I hope she will not return and
undo all of our hard work once again
hopefully that would be cruel of her
she is possessed by something I I just
don't understand what
like Nisha do you remember about the
corruption that you mentioned about the
king yes maybe that's related this might
be his doing I think maybe since you've
been trying to usurp his throne as the
rightful Queen trying to also marry the
other rightful Queen Tam G
um that he has seen you and the princess
as a threat and is hence here to try and
take you
down via your
daughter cuz seeing her corruption will
make the citizens of Lee Estel doubt
you yeah you're so
right I need to do something about it I
need to send my pigeon as soon as
possible yes do not wait make haste I do
now
can't believe it it's happening to
us going to go
fast I shall continue
yeah looking
good what it would do if she says
no but I think she loves
me it won't be a problem
it will be
okay
yeah okay now the
RS oh is it with r do you write with r
I don't know how to ride
Mary is it with a
a would you marry me
oh
true there you
go is it too
big would you marry
me guys this English is hard
well I shall fix that other
way well
do it looks good to
me what you marry
me do you say marry even for Merry
Christmas no
even though I don't know what is
Christmas in this word unfortunately I
don't recall such a
festivity it is indeed a
mystery one two
three and mhm
okay and
thenuh Mar means happen Mar means to wet
I
see I
mean thank
you will
you marry
me wait but I forgot
something I supposed to write
Mary with the pink
one
no m
maybe I'm just going to write me with
the pink
one does it make
sense yeah let's do
that I forgot about it
[Music]
here you
go perfect and then
me let me one two three four okay three
blocks four blocks away from
oh no I need the Y I need the Y
actually I need more blocks
[Music]
okay Mary and
then one 2 3 4 now we use the pink
one we almost there I'm speed running
this why not Kingdom of the besting I'll
fix
it no
okay uhhuh
oh would you
Marry
Me Maybe
I should put the me
under yeah I think I'll do
that it will be better in the frame
mhm
mhm one two three
oh is it five one two three four five
okay now I know how to write so
yeah one two three four
five yeah like that
oh I like that there's also the
reflection I like
that
and
one yeah of course I'm going to add the
question mark one two three three
four
okay yeah and then question
mark question mark will be a bit tricky
to do but
doable watch me cook now
cute what do you think
it seems like this tiue was on purpose
now it meant to be
[Music]
there you can just sit
here you should be a different
color a different
color nah don't Overkill it let's not
Overkill
[Music]
it let's see it h I'm thinking what is
missing over there
you
know I'm going to use the
flower there you
go that is perfect indeed
it's
cute no
hats
well I'll remove my
hat
okay are you are you are you
[Music]
ready okay let's do
it I'm going to
yeah I want to remove
the oh there you go
perfect
actually something is missing ah there
you
go that is very perfect that's say yes
if something will happen to
me there you
go I don't know if there's a better way
to do this okay I will send now the
pigeon so please allow
me to send the
pigeon to the fake second
queen of Le
bestin indeed
allow
me to do this
quickly you know it takes time to go the
pigeon and everything right
to Tam Gander
okay I'm ready I'll post I mean I'll
I'll I'll I'll will send my
pigeon
Pam will you marry me
okay to wish me good
luck that's going to
happen you
ready wish me
good it is time indeed
Tom
Gander Tom
gander is it Tom Gander wrote correctly
wait let me just double check with
you it is
Tom Tom gender can okay Gander
yeah I don't know how to write okay time
gander will you marry me okay I posted I
mean send the
pigeon
please I
hope will
indeed probably the queen right now is
indeed in the realm of the dreams so
probably she will
nuts rep
away but I shall
wait on to her
return here we
go I made it
the pigeon has been
sent now we hope and
wait shall we I'm going to call the
others and see what they're
doing oh no one is here what
it hello beautiful hello Queen Mar there
you go there you are yes I I send the
pigon right now yes I'm happy to hear I
have recovered only half of the gardens
but I decided that maybe there is where
I should stop for now but the
destruction that your daughter has
caused is
immense I'm I'm so sorry we lessened it
just a little I will I will try to
understand and figure out what's going
on with her as soon as possible thank
you Queen Mario I will leave it to you
and in your very capable hands thank you
so much I'll do my best to protect Li
best
yep keep building don't let me distract
you no no I'm just done just done it's
over oh yeah see will you marry me and
that's to Tam
Gander should I ride Tam Gander
too no I think it's pretty
clear I hope so yeah who else would it
be about yeah I send the pigeon you can
you can see later if you want yeah yeah
yeah I believe that this will result in
the best case scenario I hope so well me
as
well and did you recover 100% your body
and power my lady yes me and Jonathan
with a G and Lady Shakira went and we
were able to fully review recover my
form and now I am human again well
whatever I was I'm I'm fat but is good
it's good to hear
well I must continue searching for the
princess beu yes sure go for it yes I
will I will continue to do my best do
your best you as well see you later
goodbye Queen Mario goodbye
narissa what did the is up to
[Music]
Shak what you up to I'm playing a mini
game currently in the in the red guilds
H Chambers oh should it come uh I think
we're about to end this one but there's
another game that we might start right
away the other mini game with the
chickens in the Big Blue
building okay I I should come there then
okay well we for me we are not sure if
it is rigged so maybe you're you can
help us determine
it
okay I'll come now the voices are not
helping ladies they're sabotaging me
too I see you later uh goodbye guys I'll
wait
[Music]
there
H where's my map oh there we go
so we have to go to the
blue the blue blue
are
throughing there you go
ranking
oh I never played this
before
what there you
go how do I do that
I guess that's the mini
game n n n n n n n
maybe I need to talk to someone
here in front of the board that is true
I want to join the
game waiting for the game to start would
you like to practice the empathy by
rescuing some chickens
yeah how the game
starts h h oh
oh
oh this is so
funny
a oh my God this is pretty difficult
inde
needed and
oh
uh-oh
a no what is the best score I
wonder do you win anything out of
it new personal best
score I
see hey how you get out of here a there
you
go well I want to do that again
if is
ready some already
[Music]
play hello
are you catching the chickens yeah I'm
catching the
chickening chicken very good thank you
for helping out it is
cute how wonderful does this distract
you
yeah now you can stay it's fine what
about now it makes it difficult I
see is okay very interesting can you
catch me yeah in the basket
it yeah I want to be I don't know if you
want that I think these are for dinner
they are for
dinner is over you know you know Shakira
I think you should open a restaurant
okay everybody click ready join the game
oh we can play together I think
so oh it says many already enjoying the
game is it only two people I two people
okay oh okay then I'll leave my spot to
someone else go for
it
uh I have joined the game did you join
as well you should start to now wait
wait who joined I have joined who else
has joined do you want to how many how
many
people'll do the
next it seems she's a little bit
preoccupied with player is already it
seems only one player can
play
Raven F hello can I interest you in a
start here completely tell them that you
would like to start the first 20 people
who take a ticket will win but I cannot
tell you whether you are how do I
move
oh oh maybe it's not worth to go for
certain chickens maybe some of them am I
destructing you no I my eyes are very
focused on the chickens oh the most
important Target Wonder yes the
wonderful and Shakira moves the bucket
from right to I move the buet too come
to me little chicken
buet
[Music]
buet impossible to get them all but I
will try my best to take you all on my
wing Shakira is focused here come here
into my safe warm fluffy
I don't know what she's going to do with
the chickens I can to remove they will
work for me and some will die for
me and for you hey
Sak focus focus
focus
fuckus how has it gone fuckus that was
really
good well was I up against
would you
like you have made the leader board
leard I want to play
again is it perhaps only one person at a
time after
all I want to beat J
no C go catch the chickens Dam it's
difficult sorry they
are going wherever they want to go we
hope to
[Music]
um there you go there you go they're
falling in my head as
well chickens
everywhere they're flapping their
wings they're excited to come to you
yeah they want to be
adopted can't wait to eat them adopt the
chicken
today we have the perfect em 0 oh you
have done it what a wonderful high score
not
bad same as
before two more Discord that is your
mind one more one more
attempt you're welcome there you go
byebye hello hello is it
happening what no I just sold tickets
over
this when is there a lottery being uh
announced in 11 minutes okay in Nana 11
minutes yeah
marvelous wait not quite because that
would be
oh it was 11 a
joke what is
that oh the
heck I see here sparkly one right away
how I love to see it sparkly go Shakira
go Shin chicken this is looking like a
good one oh oh the sparkly one is worth
it right how many how many does it count
for oh no I've abandoned it but for the
sparkly
one not my best not my best friend I
must say let's stay on the
side
and one games and then I will return to
Nana o what a
run amazing and there everyone else win
sparkly one I hope I'll win
more chickens oops more chickens come on
you got to do
94 20
more you're doing
good no what how is this worse than my
first try
impossible why are you abandon me
abandoning me chickens why for what
reason yummy chicken
do not give extra points they
don't why are they sparkly no they're
sparkly uh I think they give you like a
buff a temporary buff they got you get
little little little faster I think
oh oh no glowing chickens score free
points and give you a brief speed Bo so
they extra points okay they give you
extra points then
M okay do you want to play again yeah
sure I can try again okay go go go go oh
I need to talk to the
quest let's go oh I need to
start Yoo okay let's
go cats are pretty good at catching
birds after all you think
so it's in your
jeans in my pant in my jeans in your
pants
I thought you were going to say panther
in my Panther it's also in your pan
Panther
jeans it's also in your
skirt
yeah I have no
skirt oh
true as if I am playing through
you yeah almost as if I can control
you no oh no you have a lot of them yeah
no you in a bad I can recover I can
recover it is not looking very good for
you in this
turn you that's no you have missed it
once again oh so
bad I want to play I want to play you
should play I want to try I want to
try let's see all the luck that you are
sharing with people if it will come back
to
youing you see let me see Catch the
birds catch the birds good
luck sparkly ones are very very
good they make you a little bit
faster and give you extra score oh you
are doing great so
far you have a natural Talent it
seems chicken have you caught chickens
before in your life many a time I also
I've also been chased by chicken
oh and it seems you are destined for
[Music]
this I'm locking I'm locking oh I'm
locking are you locking in you're doing
good maybe new
score yeah new best score
wa w
100 what a Challenge 100
H good 100
chicken so
good I saw it
happening the leader board is growing
bigger you on top of it please be sure
to come by Nana 11 where I will be
announcing the winners and giving out
prize money to those who win okay just
one more time and then I is it going to
start now it will start in about 6
minutes I will miss it you won't miss it
no no no you won't miss it I won't miss
it I won't miss it and you will accept
okie dokie I will now return to my
market I come with you want come
with I shall return as
well there you go be back
H oh I
infiltrated
[Music]
Jonathan
Jonathan oh yes what do you think
about my message it is very bold
it was a very bold message was it good
enough yes I think she will love
it that's good I hope so
too yeah she she will surely love such a
thing wonderful and beautiful thank you
yes will you be sending the the sketch
through carrier pigeon I did already I
sent the pigeon already on the sky you
know where older pigeons
fly how wonderful yeah you can see it
too is on the sky right now yes I see it
well I hope your words reach her for the
sake of this Kingdom I hope so
too
yes well are you going to build her ass
now yes I will be building
her I have to finish her it is a
disgrace to leave her in such a way
it is very pretty oh thank you I've
worked very hard on this statue of the
queen I believe
you thank
you once I finish her I hope everyone
can look up and remember all the good
that she has done for
us
yeah yes well must to my blueprints
what is in
here
huh
oh oops oh I don't have to miss the
lottery around I'm ready to be a winner
11 have you seen my high score being
announced I did did I went oh wo she
beat
it
so to
me sabotaged by the Sun and still got
106 me let me look in the library saving
chickens is my
priorities I have a feeling every day
will everybody will be a winow
today couldn't be we have a feeling a
hunch it just feels like a I I want to
win something this
time I really need to win I think we all
need a win yeah after all the corruption
that has be fallen our lands uh oh sorry
very true very true I'm just trying to
make this land a better place and I
respect that even even forces I respect
that I hope
this 11 can bring us all closer together
and perhaps introduce a
piece to this
land there's a great responsibility to
carry but I am
strong I'm here oh hello hello I'm here
for the
lottery thank you
oh of the co hello oh the lottery
everyone the next
minute I'm so
excited
oh Lottery lottery we love
Lottery nice wait I saw a ghost I swear
I just saw somebody come
bye a ghost a ghost you know what it may
have been may have been my memories of
what fua of the wall sounded like
[Music]
confused is this all the players
exited I'm so excited three chance oh
the time is here but we are missing some
people it appears out of the room out of
the
deal where is Jonathan G jonath wait did
Jonathan G get one yes Jonathan G got
one perhaps we could call Jonathan of G
with I shall call Jonathan of it wasn't
important enough for them to be here
then huh no you see even if they are Abs
from the actually never mind I want you
all to keep me company I'm not going to
tell you the
truth truth the truth being that you
really don't have to be here right now
your prize money but but I just wanted
everybody together because I'm lonely
hello oh I am here for the lottery I'm
here for the lottery too is everybody
here except the single person who
refused a
ticket yeah refused a ticket a free
ticket
who refus the ticket I get another
ticket refus ticket she was very
suspicious and paranoid to her sister I
could sister sister sister wait a I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I you two just look
very similar I got I I assumed I should
assumed they look very different from
they look nothing alike yeah yeah one is
pink one is blue they look so much they
look as alike as you look
pregnant
what what time are you in wait are you
are yous not pregnant do you look
pregnant assume male pregnancy am I even
able I apologize even able to get I
shouldn't your business partner you have
to stop stop insulting your guest
iant try not to try not to
you pregnant backwards
backwards what do you maybe you and I
and I am just revealing it to you I have
a hunch what you have a hunch Jonathan
G is anyone a doctor do we have a
doctor Cecilia show you another doctor
too huh is there a doctor no but I do I
did take I did take a a first a Course
once does make is that good enough we
should bu like a hospital here I
supp oh yes good at all I guess but
Lottery Let me let me see m is more
important and if you were in fact
pregnant you would really need the prize
money wouldn't
you given that your wife seems to be out
of the picture now yeah you would be
raising it alone the child huh I supp I
would be baby PE what happened to her oh
how sad oh she is not of this world any
longer are you sure about that yes she
is no longer with us huh she died wait
what they talking about she's no longer
with us but she's not dead is she she
dead the verion I knew is no longer here
with us what are you talking about she
is maybe she can come backst the Pearl
you believe
so put all my eggs in one basket do not
give up
immediately I do not know you as
somebody who gives up so easily on their
love see well don't give up you know we
got Nissa back from an
underw this is just a small small
difficulty I think you deserve it too
honest yeah deserve a second chance
[Music]
Mone money money alert money alert money
alert the m has arrived the M's arrived
oops wait oh shoot hold
on oh she's snuck in wait let that's
fine that's F you can hang out she
really wants
money cuz you're a patient all right all
righty everybody I will now be
announcing the winners but please be
please have even more patience I have
encoun yes yes okie
dokie the first winner of the lottery
is you whose name I did not
get you who is
Green
Oh
Cecilia Oh cilia go by the green one oh
it is I go I can go by the green one I
like the green one but there's another
green one gets kind of
confusing heard the other well just
whoever is present is the green one and
whoever is not present is the other I
win I win but yes you win I win you you
win 100 coin
congratulations W congratulations on
your 100 coin what is going why is
this oh yes that's what I want this is
what I want I thought I was trying to
make me call somebody I will accept the
trade
request you get 100
coins
goods for
you at least congrats next winner is the
Lady of the oranges yipp huzzah yipp
huzzah indeed you win 100 coins what a
surprise so
cooling I hope I win as well for you I
think today we all
winners yes the next winner is I love
this Nana 11 March next winner is
Mario
yeah you get 100 coins thank you not
sure why you need it since you were the
queen but I'm just happy you enter my
lottery at uh yeah I'm always going to
gety extra extra tickets sometimes it is
required that you donate a portion they
need it the most don't
they they need all the
money starving people
[Music]
huzzah is Jonathan G thank goodness
that's crazy
[Music]
just got to keep your chin up Jonathan
yes I will thank you for giving me A New
Perspective
nanu you're wonderful glorious 100 coin
huz huzzah huzzah next
winner is or I believe would have
been narissa so the ring
[Music]
cross already departed for today she is
not here right now
we did confirm that she can pick up her
earnings tomorrow which she will do you
give money on
tomorrow on the mar the ghost one on the
mar but that's okay we have now the
final winner of today M of the
[Music]
co because you bought five tickets you
get there was the option to do that
you what I did not know
this could I have bought 20 tickets and
get everything you canot have
was I see
wonderful everybody addict won the
lottery well it's okay if she's addicted
as long as this the only Lottery she's
going to because then she not lose any
money here I am banned from today we are
yeah that prove one point by the way
everyone that the Nana 11 is better than
phom because pH is a
scam is no everybody won is scam without
spending
anything a family of one we said
destroy yeah destroy
destroy have to destroy
winning they Pro you a point has the
most
winning perhaps M would like to share
the been
sharing thank you
my Jonathan of the G yes I don't may I
speak to you on the side for I think you
should destroy the market uh course I
don't think that's it good job good job
M just like you concerned about what
will come of your baby If
there really is a baby it seems am I you
might be in big trouble that she is I
think you're pregnant well in case that
you are pregnant and then in in the case
that you are you were to be raising the
child alone if your beloved wife is not
coming back to you I shall just uh of
course platonically offer my assistance
to you you in raising your child of
course if you may be in need of any
assistance I will keep that in mind
thank you for your kind and generous
offer Shakira you are so kind and
wonderful yes since we also support the
same Queen
yes I yes of course I need to I am of
child if I am random suddenly male
pregnant I will do you think she's
pregnant I will need someone to do you
think she's pregnant but keep your chin
up because I have a good feeling about
have the fing good luck with your
[Music]
pregnancy thank you I do have something
unfortunate to mention oh oh yes that I
think we should all keep in mind and
mentally prepare
for the chances of a male surviving male
pregnancy is extremely
slim oh
goodness what you know this are you a do
no but I read I read books what kind of
books your Kindle close a Kindle well
anything that is written on paper must
be true yes there's no wrong things
written on paper that is true that is
true the library that you that you that
you of course is there anything we can
do to help her him through the M PR
pregnancy there is very little maybe
some healing items maybe potions
anything you can try but I we can do our
best to help but I think it's very
important that we just prepare in case
Jonathan G I see does not Jonathan G
just now that we became
friends no I don't believe it I think we
could still make it if I am to die Miss
Shakira if you would see to it that my
child is raised with their head on right
oh but I could also just uh bring you to
the temple and revive you oh that is
true she can revive me it's fine we have
done it today we can do it again we have
done it we can do it again true well
that's easy then oh okay
okay that wasn't too bad not so bad
Temple and I will there may be there may
be many things to be negative about like
the corruption that is spreading but
this is not something we have to be
sulking about don't worry we should prin
I do
princess the princess jewelry beu that
has been acting very strange as of late
oh yeah I'm going to kill her what you
not going to kill my princess why would
now you got you got to fight me first
you kill her I'm sorry kill wasn't the
best word kill wasn't the best word I do
apologize a different maybe maybe if she
were to be killed uh and then revived by
the Phoenix fire she could be cleansed
automatically I'm going to make sure
that she is a good girl and doesn't do
anything bad she is my daughter I will
protect her all cost I'm sorry we will
not let you kill you kill her for no
reason we need we need a good reason
kill there's a good reason I'm sorry
what the reason she's killing all of us
by killing our crops and we are
resulting in Starvation do you want us
die for one princess where's the proof
is she bringing up a the proof is in the
pudding where the proof Tri narissa has
rebuilt all the crops for us we
literally have seen it with her own eyes
when she was destroying them I asked for
a trial the gardens let us check the
gardens we need they rebilt it no we
rebuil it
actually oh
well that's convenient I don't see any
proof that we replanted everything I
promise you felt it I have helped
her H hell thank you forness fluffy one
the gardens yes the gardens it Wasa
attending to the gardens you are so
wonderful she was just taking it see oh
it was narissa thank you narissa Raven
cross tending to the garden
but but how can okay so she's been
destroying the crops what if it's just a
simple prank why would you kill her for
that what what's going that does not
sound like a good prank to me
iting of the prank necessarily it seems
that the princess is corrupt okay I I'll
be honest with you guys I mean the
princess the princess is my daughter and
I've never seen her acting that weird
this morning mm like I I I don't know
there was something extremely wrong with
her today and I couldn't stop her I
turned my
back that's a good point yeah I've also
noticed her being very strange but I
feel like murder is very ex extreme can
we maybe have a trial can we have a
trial no one will murder the princess
ever kill the princess I could get my
carrots oh okay well she does not want
to be involved in this murder fight for
air such as she um I I will ask well I
would like to ask maybe we could have a
set a court date for tomorrow court date
would you guys be okay with that Justice
rules it would be what what Justice I
what are you talking
about for justice with a corrupted evil
mind I have seen the evils that have
happened upon this land well we can we
can we can talk to her and see if she's
responsive and and then we can have a
have a trial I'm sorry but she seems out
of control it okay can I can I be honest
with
you it seems like something is
corrupting her from inside and Nisa
Raven coft the the she told me that
there is something about the king that
is going extremely wrong like a
corruption from from the kingdom itself
so really yeah and and yeah Shakira was
with me when she was talking about it
and like apparently
the king is corrupting the lies and the
the lies um transform into the uh stains
that we see outside the kingdom and so
I'm being called sorry one second you
who's
call oh we are at the gardens we are
currently at the gardens
Naru I
see if you needed any more proof the you
started wanting to kill the
princess
you
you true it's true s here we have to
explain her about what n told us before
okay okay yeah also the princess has uh
true the princess has used the community
notice boards to uh write a cursed
corrupted message to us do you want to
do true I have seen it Ive witnessed
it it was in a cursed language that was
really hard to decipher it was and if
you notice it is the same the same font
that plagues her her lands have you seen
the notices on her her for the corrupted
for at the Blue uh there's like water
one must be blind if one were not to
notice that is a garden or purposefully
ignore it it's like on on the side of of
the giant circular
building I
see
[Music]
well I hope she will feel better
tomorrow it was really out of the blue
where's my
pickaxe I lost
it
um I myax
what I want to go farm more
uh I'm going to ask Mo for some
[Music]
diamonds iing craft it again
oops what is
she who's calling me hello hi there can
I ask you to buy uh can I can I buy from
you a few diamonds so I can craft my
pickaxe of course and because we are in
the same Guild you are more than free to
just take them oh thank you that's very
weird of you yes thank you for your
business of course I appreciate you
asking when I didn't ask you at all if I
could use your diamonds no it's fine you
can take whatever he wants it's our
Guild you can take whatever you
want yeah you can take
him wa add
them they're in the barrel they're in
one of the barrels oh okay thank you so
much you're welcome
byebye
byebye wait that's a lot of diamonds out
there I'm going to get those
ones she'll be fine there you go what is
do I need to craft the diamond forgot
about it sticks perhaps
those are my diamonds I got them by
myself
remember
yeah I think I need
sticks it's okay I like to share with my
guild
members you
know AI I have a question for you
now so on the top can you read that is
like gather your strength to prepare for
what is to come so I have the feeling
that tomorrow something bad is going to
happen so shall we like prepare for
tomorrow stain bone oh I need stain
bone should we prepare for
tomorrow okay I have question how can I
um how can I uh enchant my my sword is
there a better way to do that do I need
like I need um I need blue
stones I need lapis okay well we go grab
lapis then now that's why I want to
craft
let's
go oh no I have a few
pickaxe okay let's go craft some lapis
the are six
enough oh more
levels yeah level
30 okay I'm going to go craft some
diamonds now
then so we
go it's okay if it's RNG if we got
enough
no I want to to a decent weapon
anything pretty much
for
tomorrow okay should be here I remember
saw some lapis on the ocean so we go
now yeah I know that there is an
enchanting books we really enchant uh
shovel there not not a big
deal oh probably I could just teleport
let me check
I didn't see it
[Music]
I don't I don't know like I don't mind
um something like super strong it's just
like anything I think is better than
just a diamond sword
no there we go
well let's
start I'm going to get level 30 pretty
quickly
[Music]
so I have a
lantern seems like I don't have any
Lantern
I've keep this in my
hand oh I cannot get it oops never mind
then we're in the
darkness lappies how many do we need
30 plus
okay there place I can find lapis H just
this
[Music]
H level three
is that the only place I can
Farm seems like
it I'm so bother don't have anything to
farm there's no coal in this
dungeon oh there is a lantern I can go
get it
[Music]
easy ah
oh there's an invisible
wall okay I didn't notice
that yeah I don't see another way to get
lais lastly in this game
[Music]
do we just get three at the
time this is enough oh oh wo whoo whoo
whoo whoo I wasn't expecting to have
that
many should we get some extra levels
though I'm going to get some extra
diamonds in case we need more swords
[Music]
yeah EXs are always good
indeed I think that's the fastest way to
do it
[Music]
I don't need to enchant my pickaxe like
if I have some extra you
know
time I
will no I don't get I don't get X from
this I didn't notice that we could
actually make farms in this game you
know with the redstones and such
[Music]
for let's do level 32 and then we go
back will be enough
[Music]
hey you go let's go
back
um I'm going to use my
teleport teleport powers
[Music]
and I'm going to put this here we don't
need this
now there you go
[Music]
um okay
one second give a
moment I want to stretch for a
second there you
go m
[Music]
there you go
okay need to drink water too
let's go back to the
[Music]
castle so now you you got to help me
with that so you got to the blackm
it is here and
then we hold here
and we put out sword pretty
good huh okay next
the
H how do I do
that huh oh I put lapis oh do we do
level three
huh and
then we click
here
this steak okay
steak okay sharpness we got
sharpness is it good it's pretty good
okay should we try a few more times
though does it
help
oh no you want to try a few more
times could be worse I mean I have
diamonds I can try
more what else do I have here 1,000
coins not for diamond sword that's a lot
[Music]
I don't
know should we do another one I want to
keep the sharpness I think it's a good
one but now we have to farm back the
levels ah
[Music]
yeah sharpness is fine we keep the
sharpness ah so we improve this more can
you actually improve this sword
more you can combine your enchantment
sword together using an
[Music]
envil yeah with books I need the books
I'm sorry I'm still a Minecraft Noob I
don't know many
[Music]
things I really don't
know I don't have any books I don't know
how to get a
book hey paper and leather how to get
how to get leather
paper with sugar cane or bamboo leather
leather and
paper I don't know how to get paper in
this game
oh sugar cane I don't have sugar cane
though
[Music]
I don't know you can buy it I can
check sugar
cane
oh we got it okay okay okay okay we got
it we got got it I'm going to clean my
inventory I have this as
well need to clean my inventory a
bit I do have a tons of leather I'm
sure thank you T is very nice of
you I'm going to plant
this and I need to clean the inventory
I'm going
crazy you know what next time I'm going
to
do next time I'm going to do this I need
to clean
[Music]
around like I need to make a deposit
where I can
um put all my stuff
[Music]
into
sorry yeah I have tons of leather
mhm
mhm oh we need a regular
[Music]
brother I need to go kill some
Moes I see well I can do that
[Music]
I want to go try my sword anyway so
let's
go okay ttin so after the books right
what are we going to
do sorry no okay we make the books and
then we in turn the
books okay I got it
hi there I'm going to kill you
[Music]
sorry where are you
running have a good sleep everyone if
you're going to
bed oh I just woke
up I mean not really just woke up but I
want to prepare lunch today
yummy I don't know what I'm going to
do maybe an nette with X
thinking I got leather I got some
leather is this enough
[Music]
hey go so
fast how many letter do do we need
oh the cows they go
[Music]
on well I think that's
enough let me go craft some paper
now hm
paper
oh
paper oh
sorry
um sugar
cane oh paper
I made
it
then so we need one letter and three
paper
oh
yeah let's
go okay 10 books are enough
now how do I
enchant like
this you need levels
[Music]
can I teleport to the
ocean
no to the coast
no this doesn't give me
[Music]
anything I need to swing
back I'm lazy
I don't know if I'm going to have a POV
for the collab tonight uh probably
yeah
maybe you know I'm not sure
is level 30
enough no
what oh it's going to take so long
[Music]
I'm throwing out things I don't
need there you
go three levels should I level three
[Music]
times okay got it so level 33 or 36 I
didn't know that okay thank
[Music]
you let's
go grinding time
I think diamonds are the on gives more
H I am starting to understand the
game it's interesting though I didn't
know about enchantment until
now this is very very interesting I
probably should start
like making enchantments
into my Minecraft
too so I believe you can actually
enchant everything like even the armor
and
oh she's here wait I'm going to unmute H
hello sorry I was
muted this is mine hello are you
mining this is my mine is it yours I
need to level up yeah good luck I can
give you the stuff if you
want no it's
fine no no it's fine why is the queen
why is the queen in the Min because it
needs to become
stronger is youren training
yeah no
worries I'll let you be then I'll go
over there I guess no
wores I I I can I can take this
[Music]
Square I don't mind sharing is caring
okay one more level and we can and
go I don't know if I want to do level 2
6 maybe
not so what kind of book we can get
actually out of the
enchantment any many oh so it's about
luck
[Music]
what is the worst enchantment that you
can get out of books
M maybe uh you know
my what was this
noise Oh weird oh have you heard
that what was
that I wonder
[Music]
I wonder if is it difficult to go from
Level 33 to
36 we can all right
[Music]
yeah I was saying once in in a Ravin
server I'd like to defeat the
dragon I've always seen people defeating
the dragon but I never made it
myself that' be cool
yeah I'll probably start to upgrade
stuff in raving too you know what that's
a good idea I think I'm going to
apparently from my
standing you need to craft a library to
enchant so the the I guess the more book
books you
have from my understanding the more the
the more books you have around the more
is going to be the enchantment
15 bookcase
okay what if it's like
more it doesn't really matter I
[Music]
guess okay I think I'm going to make it
so like next time we go to the server we
going to have
strong oh wait a
sec I
got
something important
[Laughter]
she said
yes
[Music]
she
said
yes good
ending we unlocked the good ending
[Laughter]
one second uh I need to
reply you know
priorities you know
[Laughter]
let's go
[Music]
I
won the
hell what was
that scary
let's
go I'm
happy you going to
celebrate when we come back
[Music]
let's
go so happy
oh level 36 can go
[Music]
back I think that would be cute to like
make two flags now one is going to be
pink and one is going to
be blue on the castle to celebrate
I made
it oh why am I here I need to go to
elaborate to the back me
okay so now I put a
book and
then and
then and then
lapis I have no
lapis I have lapis
uh
and and and the
book ah
yeah hello D
[Music]
hello thank you so much welcome
hello
beautiful I hope you get a good
stream I think she was doing a car if I
remember oh I hope you had fun welcome Z
my name is RA panta from uh actually a
queen Mario from uh King the kingdom of
letin it's very nice and pleasant to
meet you all
welcome hello
I got
flame I guess that's
good bad
book okay we do another
one SM
average
might
again how do I enchant my sword now
envil need a new sword
[Music]
no I need a new
sword but my sword
is already very good it's
it's
[Music]
sharpness I don't
know kind that M will not help at all
[Music]
yeah you I can actually combine two
swords
together
okay are you sure I'm going to I'm not
going to lose the sharpness
[Music]
May me confuse a bit I don't trust
anyone I don't know I I I mean I heard
that SM is not very good so why should I
get Smite in the first
place it's okay let's leave it as it is
it's fine I already got a did one
[Music]
it's like it's like 20 people saying 20
different things I don't get it so it
do Smite extra damage to Undead
sharpness extra damage for everything
okay
so now I can I can I can I mix can I
combine the sharpness and this m
together
no I can't so what I'm going to do now
[Music]
oh so we keep the sharpness and we maybe
the best thing to do is to find another
sharp sword correct so we have to turn
another sword
and hope hopefully it's going to get the
sharpness
[Music]
back okay got it so we have to go level
again just made a
grindstone I don't know what is a
grindstone
sharpness and fire
aspect I'm going to
ask I a
hello do you know what happened to my
chicken what happened to your chicken
they're gone they're
gone where did you C your
chicken what where you gone like where
do you are I here here do you hear me do
you hear me I hear Jonathan can you hear
me yeah you can I can hear
you what is going
Onan what's happening Str hello hello
where's ask her for me where are her
chickens what has happened to her where
are your chickens what happened to you
Jonathan
now yes hello I still can't hear
Jonathan I can't hear Jonathan what is
going on dad
Jonathan my two kids come here come here
come
here I'm coming
too right over here where they were
right here
M my last chicken is gone what your
chicken were here they were here I loved
them and there was so many of them and
now they are gone they every last one
was it the curse of the land you did bu
quite near close
to what to to the maybe they left no
they were very happy they were so f f
maybe you should like put something here
on the on the wood so they don't leave
anymore because maybe they just left I
don't think they flew away they were
very happy I think they they flew away
for wa I don't think can play I think
they can cannot
fly I mean I think they just jumped over
here my
goodness yeah can't you didn't eat them
right what why would you have them on me
it's it's not me it's not me it's not
me I swear I'm not going to eat a
chicken she ate your chicken I didn't I
didn't ate her chicken your chicken she
is I didn't I'm a good C I
promise bre are you
sure
yeah yeah I'm know your chickens though
I know I I I know what happened
I love
them you know what I can give you more
eggs come with me can you
yeah oh my
potato come here I give you all my eggs
all your eggs yeah you sure can you
accept my
trade let's see I got to move something
around one
moment and and and you know what we
should do we should make a better kids
so they're not going to leave a better
kids
yeah
okay oh that's a lot of eggs take them
okay thank you I for to repay for the
chicken I didn't made it though okay
maybe maybe you're in yeah you going to
put more put more fces around and you're
going to be fine I promise okay I don't
think they FW away though they did I
promise I if you can jump over it they
can jump too I can't jump over it though
I can look come with
me what
is huh what is
ah the she
is look look I can jump over here look
yeah but not the chickens the chickens
are that they
can there there there we go I found
it another one we need another one
[Music]
okay okay let's
see we need a friend we need a
friend let's go okay you want me to find
more fences for
you let's see I don't think they're
going to escape
though you so trust me for
w I trust
you I don't think they flew away though
really
really they did I don't think
so look I know how to play this they're
not big enough now when they grow up to
just
do are you sure oh maybe this fence is
kind of
small you got to put like another fence
like between those two trees and it'll
be fine it between these ones
I don't know I didn't make this pen
originally but because I didn't make it
I think it's good no wait wait there
they
are let's see I'll come back shortly and
we'll see if they all gone okay I won't
eat it I promise they were there for a
long time thank you for the eggs you're
[Music]
welcome they're going to run away I know
it benevolent Queen I
know okay there's one thing I want to do
before Oh my God I need to
go I need to go eat food I'm literally
starving right
now you should you should listen to my
Tommy is like ah it's going
[Music]
crazy what's for lch I don't know I got
to
cook I like cooking
[Music]
okay
please eat I go eat right now
[Music]
princess
beu princess Vu is here what is she
oh
daughter princess
B princess
[Music]
B princess no
he's gone
again it I saw her
[Music]
the feel are gone
again
uhoh there you
go I made
it
cute
indeed okay and then I'm going to make
some food for tomorrow and then I
[Music]
leave just in case we need it
m
I have potatoes I have
watermelon need books for
now I wonder what I can cook I'm going
to plant those again
maybe more
[Music]
EGS let's see the recipe books
so potato salad nourish soup carrot
sweet berries water bu
k sweet slime gems sweet berries stained
slime bow
sugar
interesting let me got the bows
I'm going to put this wood in my
backpack here you
go
[Music]
and
yeah I also think I need a bucket so
maybe let me craft one I don't think I
have
it in okaye I need water
check on chickens I want attack but I
think they run
away they're going to run
away they still too small to run
away I'm not responsible for
this I promise
I didn't do anything
wrong I
didn't you witness
this please
um what I wanted to do oh yeah I need to
go buy more sugar cane hello
[Music]
beautiful okay so
sugar oh do I need to craft sugar from
the sugar cane I guess
so much
proces just a warm up uh not warm up
hands up tomorrow stream will be will
start earlier than
today because it's the last episode so
we want to make sure to
complete everything I think 1 hour early
will'll be
fine
wait this is the
princess what she's doing what is she
doing what is she
doing I want to cook now
so it says lime ball sugar and
berries H good
enough and then what else
okay I think I'm going to continue
tomorrow I'm really starving right now
so I I don't want to faint I'm going to
go eat something I appreciate you I'm
going to meet tatini I'll talk to you
tonight we're going to meet tonight
again not sure I'm going to stream my
POV but in case I will I'll let you
know thank you tatini appreciate it
have fun I mean have fun have a good
time have a good rest I see you
tonight bye-bye Take Care thank you so
much it's
fun now I'm legitimately everyone's
Queen let's
see look I'm going to uh raate let's
rate
M sh everyone say hi to M for me
okay appreciate
it
byebye yeah call me Your Majesty
actually actually you're
[Music]
right you right
I'm
back my crown is
back
T see you very soon
[Music]
byebye and
remember big means big FL
twist byebye
[Music]
a